[Singing in native language]
[Birds chirping]
Good morning, boss.
Ahh, good morning, man.
Everything cool?
So far.
Good.
[Sighs]
Hey, that's one of them
masai warriors, huh?
Yeah.
Them guys sure
get around, don't they?
Kind of like us, huh?
[Laughs]
Captioning made possible by
lions gate entertainment
so, boss, how far
do you think they are?
Doesn't matter, man.
We're almost there.
Does that look like this?
I guess so.
Yeah? Close enough.
You sure your friend
will let us use his talents?
No problem.
Captain Morgan and I
go way back.
[Singing in native language]
[Squeaking]
Man: I can't believe how
someone so uncivilized
can become
so downright respectful.
I mean, when we came here,
we was just kids playing
cowboys and Indians,
learning to survive
and trying to make
a quick buck.
We were hiding guns
for the rebels
in some of the mines
and tunnels
he's working in now.
Bush rebels kept
calling him captain
for some damn reason.
Name just stuck.
[Singing continues]
Got your game face on?
Yeah, you always do.
Don't worry. We'll get
past these gentlemen.
Do it for love, country,
and mostly for money.
[Driver chuckles]
Not Morgan.
No way, man.
It's different for him.
It's more for respect,
for the people and himself.
He's a diamond among the rough.
[Motor stops]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Speaking native language]
[Laughter]
Ixnay on the ore-hays,
Peter Joe.
Why I ought to.
[Speaking native language]
Morgan.
How's it looking, Morgan?
Hey, fellas.
We got our work cut out
for us here, ok.
The water table's dropping,
but it's making
the dolomoth dry up faster.
Ok, man.
It's not a trailer, man.
[Shouting in native language]
Hey!
See this thing?
We've got to pump in
some cement here
before it brutally collapses.
And we better do it
on number 7 as well,
just to be safe.
[Shouting]
Come on.
Follow.
This way.
[Whistle blows]
[Indistinct shouting]
[Whistle blowing]
Hey, right here.
Excuse me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Stop means stop.
Just stay close, sir,
all right? Let's go.
We got it right here.
Right here.
[Speaking native language]
Look. Man... man.
Don't mess with me, man.
Don't piss me off, man.
I understand you're a dick.
Now you read, man.
Get off my case, now.
I'm gonna rip out
your headlights, man.
No, you listen to me, man.
Yo, I...
Morgan: Catch.
Captain Morgan.
Oh, God.
What's up?
How you doing, man?
Hi, bro.
Now don't you feel
like a fool, man,
treating me so bad?
See, he and me
are friends, all right?
Me and the captain,
we're tight.
Yeah, with friends like you,
who needs enemies?
Basically, this guy
needs an enema.
I'm about to give him
one with a shrapnel...
be kind, this is my associate.
Man, he's a punk, man.
Give the prosac
a fighting chance, will you?
You got to read the labels.
All right, all right,
all right.
Sorry, man.
What's in the truck?
Tony. Nothing,
couple scuds.
Scuds?
What's the scuds doing?
Hey, I missed you.
I missed you, too.
I thought you went
to the north mines,
messed around up there. No?
Bullshit.
I did.
What is this?
I don't know.
It's legit, though.
I got it signed by
the minister of
what's it...
whose its...
my initials!
Yeah.
Yeah. You forged
my signature.
That's... that's
very ingenious.
You know everything
comes in here
is my responsibility.
Well.
This is kind of steep.
All right, let's negotiate.
Ok.
The usual. You know,
case of red stripe.
Case of red stripe?
I got some.
Just fell off the back, man.
Don't you mean off the wagon?
Ok. Might have a case.
I'll kill you.
I'll kill you, man.
Get that shit out of here.
[Indistinct chatter]
All right.
Now hold your water, man, ok.
Just trust me.
You and I are going to
be richer.
6 foot up a bull's ass,
it's gonna be a ball.
Toxic waste?
50-50.
I'll give you 40-60
if you want.
What are you doing
transporting this shit?
Man, it's all right.
No one's gonna get hurt.
Just ca...
it's toxic waste!
It's not that toxic.
You get this shit out of here.
What the hell is this?
[Indistinct shouting]
Friends of yours?
Well, used to be.
Now it seems like
they're pissed.
Yeah, no shirt shitlock.
Kiss my ass, Chang.
You commie-supportin'
asswipe!
Oh, Chang? You've gone
international on me.
Yeah, I know no
discrimination. Excuse me.
Yeah.
[Shouts]
Keep the peace, bro.
God.
Sorry.
Get ready, Clifton.
Elvis, get the
artillery, will you?
Elvis: Yes, sir.
You just won't
let go, will you?
Card shuffle Buddhist.
Whoa!
What are you doing to my place?
I said I was sorry, man.
Got the next size up?
Yep.
Big and tall, bro.
That'll fit.
Wahoo!
What'd you do to piss him off?
He's an ex-business
partner.
And it's the "ex" he's
not too happy about.
Cover me.
[Gunfire]
Oh! Jesus Christ!
Ahh.
Now he's pissing me off.
Damn it, man.
Get this thing out of here.
Where is he?
There he is.
Man, I feel a stone wall
coming on.
Yeah?
Bring it on, you punk.
Ohh!
Why do I miss this guy?
Yeah! Take that, man.
[Gunfire]
It's ok. Come on.
I hope you're satisfied,
God damn it.
Hey, Chang!
Don't you believe in karma?
You must have been born
the year of the fool, man.
Yeah, yeah!
That's right, buddy.
I'm gonna make you
a baby again.
Man: There he goes.
Oh, man.
This sucks.
Don't hit my truck!
Elvis, fire it up!
[Bullets ricocheting]
Follow the truck, Elvis.
[Grunts]
Andreas.
Whoo! See you at
nando's, about 7:30.
Yeah, yeah. Y'all come
back now, you hear.
He's mine.
Oh, my God!
That rice lover's
gonna blow the jeep.
Jump! Jump!
No!
God!
Army.
[Alarm sounding]
Pull back.
Move out.
Back in the chopper.
Pull back.
[All shouting]
Morgan: Jesus.
[Breathing heavily]
[Speaking native language]
Look what they did
to my guys, man.
Look what they did to my guys!
New scenes of horror
continue to multiply
as the death toll rises
in the small African nation
of east zambezi.
The massive toxic spill
has spread
throughout
the Southern waterway,
forcing government troops
to break off
their running battle
with rebel forces
in an attempt to quarantine
the infected region.
In this village alone,
over 100 fatalities
have been recorded.
Earlier today, the zambezi
minister of state
spoke at a press conference
held in the capital.
We are still searching
for the source.
But we know who
the guilty parties are.
And believe me,
they will not go unpunished,
especially
the U.S. government
and its agents
who continue to permit
and support such transport.
They are the primary ones
to blame.
We hold them
the most responsible
for the crime
against our people,
our families, and our children.
Woman: Mr. minister!
Reporter: This man,
American mining engineer
Rick Morgan,
was quickly hustled
out of the country
only hours ago.
Male reporter: Mr. Morgan,
the barrels causing the death
of hundreds of people
have not been found.
Please, tell us where they are.
Sources close to
the minister have confirmed
that Mr. Morgan
was in fact responsible
for authorizing
the toxic dumping.
He was released
to U.S. authorities
after the American government
reconfirmed its commitment
to provide extensive
financial aid
to east zambezi.
Tracy candle,
new media network,
east zambezi.
[Boat horn blows]
[Indistinct chatter]
Man: You're not
an easy man to find.
I've come to make you an offer.
And you are?
Maurice dupont.
I am a ministerial consultant
to the Democratic Republic
of east zambezi.
Really?
Well, I've made it my policy
to not be consulted
by countries
that try to execute me.
Well, Mr. Morgan,
it was your signature
on the document.
The government still
holds you responsible.
More than 1,000 villagers
have died of toxic poisoning
from the drums
that you allowed in.
Yeah, well...
The chances of me
hurting anyone in here
are pretty slim,
but seem to be increasing
since your arrival.
Personally,
I believe your approval
was forged,
that the man responsible
walked free.
Mr. Jim Scott.
Buddy, you're late and
a life short, mister.
Do you not wish
to, uh, clear your name?
Your reputation?
You know, I lost both things.
Not you, not anyone,
gonna get them back.
Ok.
Mr. Morgan.
There were more than 20 drums
on that truck.
We don't know
how many have corroded
or have leaked.
We need your help
to find where the source is.
You got the wrong man.
The government is prepared
to offer you amnesty,
release your frozen assets,
including back pay.
Now you're just funny.
Oh, no.
Jim Scott has survived.
[Gulps]
He lives somewhere
deep in rebel territory.
It's going to be harder
for me to find Scott
than for you.
For 10 years I've
watched this nation
divide itself into socialism
against capitalism,
tribalism against nationalism,
father against son,
brother against brother.
The industrial nations,
they send in millions
of dollars
without understanding a
thing about the third world.
They don't need
a handout of money.
They need expertise.
People like you.
[Indistinct chatter]
[Airplane engine]
[Goat bleating]
[Speaking native language]
Very fine.
And you, sir?
Morgan.
[Speaking native language]
Because of you!
Because of you, Morgan,
all my family is dead.
I want to tell you something.
You're a murderer.
[Spits]
[Woman speaking
native language]
She's just an old African.
[Soldiers chanting]
[Speaking native language]
[Man singing
in native language]
Politics.
[Bell tolls]
[Horn honks]
Scott: See you at nando's,
about 7:30.
There's somebody
I've got to see.
What else?
Mr. Jack Daniel's.
[Speaking native language]
[Laughter]
This bar's closed
until 6:00.
What time is it at
your end of the bar?
Hey, this is that guy
that dumped that toxic stuff
in the river
that killed all the villagers.
All right, now, fellas.
I don't want any trouble.
Uhh!
You get out of this bar,
you murderer.
Look.
All I wanted to do
is order a drink.
Ahh!
Shit.
[Glass shattering]
Gah!
Uhh!
Hyah!
[Grunts]
Ohh!
The bar is closed
until 6:00.
So I've been told.
Aye-yi-yi.
Aye-yi-yi-yi.
You have any idea how
much trouble you are in?
I can see the quality of
your clientele hasn't changed.
Ricky?
You must be mad
to come back here.
You know, you're right.
You always did charge too much.
Look what you've done.
I could lose my license
for this, huh?
[Scoffs] You never
had one to begin with.
That's true.
But it's the thought
that counts.
I thought they deport you.
So did I.
I hear Jim Scott's alive.
Uh, well, um,
it's, um.
It's a rumor.
Uh-huh.
[Man groans]
Ohh!
Make him think you do this.
He never paid me nothing.
Filthy pig.
[Grunts]
So, where's Scott?
The rebels have him.
No one has seen him.
He might as well be dead.
And don't even think
of going up there.
There's full patrols.
Both sides.
Yeah, well, I'm going
to have to go up there.
And the question is how
you're gonna help me.
It's not the same times,
my friend.
The war has escalated.
The rebels have made
major advances,
and the government is ruthless.
It could be worse.
The bar can be in
rebel territory.
Do you know,
I have missed your logic.
Heh heh.
Dupont: Very classy.
Passed out in the
bartender's back room.
[Groans]
[Sighs]
Dr. Kim woods,
want you to meet Rick Morgan.
Dr. woods has been hired
from the world health
organization.
She's a respected researcher
in contaminates.
How do you do?
I'll wait in the cafe.
[Indistinct chatter]
[Whistling]
For you.
My best sausage.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
I've, uh, arranged
for 2 soldiers
to accompany you
and Dr. woods.
Kim.
Um, that won't be necessary.
I do not think you realize
how dangerous
this country has become.
I mean that, um...
It won't be necessary
for our contaminations
expert here
to accompany me.
'Cause, uh, I don't
need an assistant
to find the drums.
I'm not your assistant.
Though it looks like
you could use one.
I happen to be a member
of alcoholics anonymous
when I'm not drinking.
What's your problem?
I'm here to neutralize
the mess you've created.
And I'm not looking forward
to scouring the countryside
with a washout.
Especially one responsible
for destroying
an entire tribe of people.
I think you better tell
Ms. national
geographic here
that I don't think
I'm gonna help her
with her science project.
Call me when
he passes out again.
I'll be at the hotel.
Well, I always
hate introductions.
But I... I think that...
that went rather well.
Look, Morgan,
you don't have to like her,
just work with her.
Oh, terrific.
Where will you start?
Scott could only have
buried the drums
in about half a dozen places,
all closed mines.
You checked them all,
but you may have missed
a few stopes.
Good.
[Indistinct chatter]
[Children laughing]
If the casings
have deteriorated,
the U.S. recognizance
satellite
will zero in like
flies to horse shit.
I've done my part.
Ahh.
[Soldiers speaking
native language]
[Gate squeaks]
Supposed to go left back there.
The road is closed.
Land mines.
Rebels?
Quarantine.
The water is poisoned.
Man: Keep an eye out
for rebels.
Second man: Clear the fence
out of the way.
Move these trucks through.
Excuse me, boss.
Just got word Morgan
and the girl
have crossed into rebel country
30 Miles east.
Ok, let's catch up to them.
Third man: Let's go!
All this from poisoned water?
Everyone's dead, madame.
Morgan: Stop.
Stop.
[Car door closes]
You're not allowed here.
[Speaking native language]
What did you do that for?
You nuts? What the hell
are you doing?
What are you doing?
Hey.
It's better to kill it.
The poison's a terrible way
for it to die.
[Speaking native language]
How long ago did this happen?
The quarantine?
9 months.
Are there any other
villages like this
along the river?
There are many villages.
No survivors.
[Car door opens]
[Car door closes]
[Engine starts]
Soldier: Look.
Kim: What is all this?
They are mass graves,
and there are many more
along the river.
Hundreds of villagers
are buried here.
Thanks.
What is it?
Africans never bury
their dead in mass graves.
Only murderers.
And that buck
they shot back there,
it was about, what,
6 months old?
Doing pretty good
on poisoned water,
don't you think?
Come on.
One hour.
Rebels.
How long has this
place been closed?
About 10 years.
It used to be
the richest colonial mine
before independence.
It just ran out.
So this is where
you buried the drums?
This is my one
and only speech, ok?
I don't know where
the drums are buried
because I didn't bury them.
Now, personally,
I hope we get lucky
and we find them,
because then you can
do your job,
whatever the hell that is,
and I can go drink myself blind
knowing I saved the world.
Where are you going?
The back door.
Morgan:
There used to be
an emergency generator
somewhere around here.
[Generator whirring]
Don't have any phobias, do you?
You'll get over them.
Keep away from
the shaft on the left.
This level's partially flooded.
How come you know
this place so well?
I used to be on
inspections and development.
5 year contract
for the whole region.
That's very weird.
What?
This rock fault.
What's on the other side?
I don't know.
You must have been
a very thorough inspector.
It's man-made.
Someone's had charges
to keep the people out.
[Beeping]
Morgan: You can tell
'cause the rock faces
are all jagged.
Cleavage on the face.
I'm not trying to be fresh.
I didn't say you were.
You didn't have to.
What does that mean?
It means since I've met you
you've been giving me
nothing but attitude.
Personally,
I'm a little sick of it.
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Hold on.
[Grunts]
Ohh.
Where'd you get it?
You got an acid kit?
In here.
It's not serious.
Good.
It's clean.
[Water splashes]
Thanks.
Sure.
It means the barrels
aren't here.
What the hell is this?
Geiger counter.
I know what it is.
I mean, what are you
doing with it?
What do you think
we're looking for?
Toxic waste has nothing
to do with radioactivity.
No one ever said anything
about radioactivity.
You didn't know?
No, I didn't know.
What, you mean you knew?
Was there a death wish
on the application form?
I headed a team that developed
a powder bacteria
that can allow us to reduce
radio activity levels
on contact.
What, this?
Yes.
Good for you.
Personally I don't like
to be taken for a punk.
And I don't like to be treated
like one of the usual suspects.
Sucks, doesn't it?
Can you walk?
I think so.
'Cause we've got to find
out why dupont's been
giving us 2 different stories.
Wait here.
Kim: Morgan!
Dead soldiers.
Not a good sign.
[Horse snorts]
We've got company.
Slowly.
Nice and easy.
[Gasps]
Let's go.
We don't look up.
Nice and easy.
[Yelling]
[Gunshots] You drive.
[Shouting in native language]
Go left.
We came right.
[Kim screams]
Uhh.
Aah!
[Both groan]
[Horse whinnies]
[Grunting]
[Man laughs]
Hands up.
Aah-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya.
Man:
Aah-ya-ya-ya-ya.
[Horse whinnies]
Ya-ya-ya-ya-ya.
[Indistinct chatter]
[Speaking native language]
[Shouting]
[Chatter stops]
[Gun cocks]
[Man shouts in native language]
[Guns cocking]
[Speaks native language]
He's my friend.
Ain't you?
I heard your big ass
was back in the neighborhood.
Yeah, it's amazing
the kind of riff raff
they let in these days.
Yeah.
It's good to see you, Scott.
That's not my name
anymore, man.
My name is usando.
I'm sorry?
Usando.
Good.
Ohh!
Yaah!
Scott: Oh, man.
Let me rephrase that.
You wouldn't mind
calling me usando, would you?
No, that'll work for me.
Uh, it's all right, madumo.
It's all right.
Yeah, madumo.
Oh, man.
I liked it better
when we used to hug.
You got a lot of
explaining to do, man.
I know. Come on.
Let me introduce you
to my family.
Ow.
Sorry.
Your family?
Who's your girl?
Oh. Uh, Kim.
Hi, Kim.
Come on through.
Give me that.
It's all right, it's all right.
Hold on one damn second.
This thing goes with me
everywhere.
Come on, Kim.
[Indistinct chatter]
You got 9 lives or something?
Yeah, only got a couple left.
But only one jaw, so watch out.
Hey, there she is.
There they are.
This is my wife tebi.
Our daughter Scarlet.
Sabon.
This is, uh, this is Morgan.
Remember the one I told you
about, captain Morgan?
That's him.
Oh! Welcome.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
[Speaking native language]
[All laugh]
What's so funny?
Uh, no, she just, uh,
said you were pretty.
Yeah.
Come on in.
Uh, come on, take a seat.
They're headed down river.
It's all rebel country.
Let's go, go!
Man: Look out for rebels!
So what's the haps?
I know why you're here.
Uh, what's your agenda, ma'am?
Uh, that's
Dr. Kim woods,
the ever fashionable
contaminations expert
from the w.H.O.
Oh, I see.
All right, all right.
So what's who
looking for and why?
What did you bury?
What'd I bury?
What, are you talking
out of school, Morgan?
You know what you've buried.
What you know about
what I've buried?
You know something
I don't know?
Easy, you two, ok?
We're on a mission searching
for radioactive waste.
You seen any lately?
Nah, the only thing
you're gonna find wasted
is your time.
Who's paying your ticket, Rick?
Guy named dupont.
Pulled me out of
a perfectly comfortable stupor.
Imagine that.
Hey, don't let
the guard past, ok?
Check the roads on patrol.
Let me know.
Ok.
Whew.
Dupont.
Class "b" scumbag.
Guy shovels arms from
north Korea via east Africa.
You can think him for half
the carnage in this country.
He's in it for the money.
See, he's partners
with the fascist murderers
who run this country,
so watch your back.
I'll remember to do that.
Why's he looking for you?
I don't know, man.
You'll have to ask him,
I guess, you know.
Truth is, after Elvis died
I decided it was time
for a life change.
I'm not even the same
person I was a year ago.
Congratulations.
Where are the drums?
History.
I took care of them, man.
No one's ever gonna find
them puppies.
They're leaking.
Do you have any idea
how many people have died?
Leaking? No, I think
you're misinformed.
I think the only death
you seen is murder.
Murder by contamination.
Look, who, there's only
one water source
in this whole region.
All the rest are tributaries.
So let me ask you a question...
how many of the villages
upstream had no survivors?
Rebel villages?
That's right.
Unprotected.
Slaughtered.
You's a scapegoat, man.
You and our toxic drums.
Our toxic drums?
No, that's... that's...
thank you for sharing.
That's very generous.
The toxic drums, all right?
I didn't... that's not
my fault, man.
They were about to hang me,
God damn it.
We'll talk later
when we're alone, ok?
I got to check the perimeters.
You do that.
Scott: Remember
that freighter that sunk
off the coast
about a year back?
Morgan: No.
Why, is that your supply ship?
No, man. I got a call
from an associate.
He told me that
freighter was gonna be
in the Indian ocean
on its way to north Korea
to deliver
some rusted sub parts.
Parts? We're not talking
periscopes here.
No, we're talking
enriched uranium rods,
worth many, many millions.
Anyways, I figured why not
intercept the freighter,
take those rods,
stash them in toxic drums,
and build myself
a little nest egg.
Company doesn't exactly
give you a retirement fund,
so I just kind of took
it upon myself.
You're not in a cove
with a pirate,
you're a c.I.A. Spook
for the Indian ocean,
aren't you?
Been a family business
since the war, man.
50 years of tradition.
Now, you should thank them.
They're the ones who got
your ass out of here alive
instead of in a body bag
a year back.
Truth is, they're pretty
damn pissed off at me.
They definitely would
have killed me
if they didn't think
I was already dead,
so if you wouldn't mind.
Only you and nando know.
And dupont.
Dupont, man.
That dumbass prob...
you know, I'll say one
thing in his defense,
at least he wears his
bullshit on his sleeve.
We promised the American dream,
and we delivered
total destruction.
[Speaking native language]
Go home, Rick.
You didn't commit
no crime, man.
Now, get the hell out of dodge
so we can open up
a can of whoop ass
and give you the first helping.
Get the kids in the bunker!
God damn.
Tebi!
You got a piece.
Come on.
Got a piece?
Over here.
Scott: They set you up.
Morgan: Man,
I didn't know.
Madumo, get the women
up to the high village.
Shebo, give him a gun.
Get in the jeep.
What's going on?
Get in the jeep. Stay low.
Get in the jeep!
Let's go.
[Indistinct shouting]
Whoo!
Yeah, take that, man.
Aah!
Oh!
[All yelling]
Aah!
Damn you, assholes!
Uhh!
Take that group.
Aah!
[All screaming]
Come on!
Scott!
Ohh.
Scott: Morgan.
Oh! Shit.
Oh, man.
God!
Ohh!
Shit.
This sucks, man.
You got to tell nando
to call my Uncle.
Tell him my daughter's
got to go to college, all right?
That's... that's
code, right?
That's... that's code.
Uh-huh.
Tell...
God damn, man.
Hold on, hold on.
Take care of my family,
all right, man?
That's not code.
No, man.
You got it, man.
Scott!
[Car horn honks]
Get her out of here, man.
He ain't gonna kill me.
I'm already dead.
Kim: Come on!
Scott: Remember,
tell nando the code.
Run with it, bubba.
[Groans]
Get cash, captain.
[Sighs]
Attack!
Uhh!
I'm not even worried about
the shipment, Scott.
It's mine.
But you disappoint me.
You hurt my feelings.
What feelings?
[Grunts]
Who watched your back
all this time?
The truth is you was never
spook material, Chang.
[Grunts]
[All shouting]
We've got to move out, boss.
They're counterattacking.
Back to the boats.
Man: Back
to the boats!
Chang: See you
in the next life.
[Birds chirping]
I'm sorry about your friend.
Thanks.
I hated him.
You know?
I hated him for setting me up.
I hated him for...
For letting everyone think
I killed 1,000 people.
And I hated him...
For pretending he was dead.
Now that he is...
I still hate him.
I think I owe you an apology.
I was wrong about you.
Aw, skip it.
People are never
what they're made out to be.
Morgan: Let's go
to the hotel.
[Indistinct chatter]
[Car horns honking]
Just get everything you need,
and let's get out of here.
All I need is a shower.
What's that?
Yeah.
See you downstairs.
[Door closes]
[Siren in distance]
What are you doing in my room?
I was worried.
What happened to you?
Where have you been?
Falling down mine shafts.
Did you find anything?
Oh, the usual...
murder, deception, greed.
Oh, you've been talking
to Mr. Morgan.
I told you he's a drunken liar.
The only liar
I've met so far is you.
No one's dead from
radioactive or toxic waste.
I quit.
Oh, I see.
You quit, huh?
Well, unfortunately,
you cannot just quit.
I've paid you
a great deal of money
to bring you here.
That's your problem.
Now get out of my room
before I call security!
As you wish.
[Indistinct chatter]
Thanks.
[Speaks native language]
Bye.
[Faucet clicks]
[Water running]
[Thudding]
What are you doing here?
Oh!
Must have used
all the hot water.
Um...
[Both grunting]
Unh...
Cover him.
I'll be right back.
[Indistinct chatter]
[Snorts]
[Grunting]
[Clanging]
Morning.
Have a nice nap?
[Faucet squeaks]
[Water draining]
You're making
a big mistake, Morgan.
If you kill me,
they will not hang you.
They'll execute you.
Oh, say, that's much worse.
Either way, I'm really sorry
you're gonna miss it.
Relax, Morgan.
We are, for better or worse,
partners now.
Without me...
You two do not
get out of zambezi alive.
Huh?
[Gun clicks]
[Sighs]
I'm glad we understand
one another.
I didn't lie to you,
Dr. woods.
The shipment...
It is radioactive.
But it hasn't leaked.
Well...
There are no signs yet.
The shipment came
in temporary crates
designed to disintegrate
in about one year.
For environmental
reasons. Heh!
Ironic, isn't it?
Then we're sitting
on another chernobyl!
Who's the agent, popeye?
Mr. Chang.
He's a rogue agent...
Selling to the north Koreans.
Between us...
He's behind everything.
I only did it to avoid
an international incident.
Oh, what a diplomat.
And all those dead
in the village?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
That was the military's doing.
Dupont: Wake up, kids.
This country is in a civil war.
They're entitled
to a few atrocities, no?
[Gasps]
Chang: Guess who.
Ah, it's about time.
[Morgan grunting]
Would you be kind enough
to untie me, please?
Morgan...
You better know where
he hid the shipment.
Where is it?
Unh!
He doesn't know!
We don't need her.
Shoot her.
[Gasps]
Unh!
Chang: One less asshole
on the payroll.
[Grunting]
[Man shouting
in native language]
[People screaming]
[Gunshots]
Whatever you want,
come back after 6:00.
Nando!
Scott is dead.
You saw him?
Yeah, right before the chain
gang wasted his village.
Now, he told me to tell you
to tell his Uncle
that his daughter's
gotta go to college.
Now, what the hell
does that mean?
Sam, lock the back door!
What the hell is that?
Rick, what else Scott tell you?
Your line of work
and what he buried.
Where is it?
He said only 2 people
know where he hid it.
Who?
You were number 2.
Rick, you must find it.
If it falls in the wrong hands
or becomes exposed,
it could bury us all.
[Sighs]
Buried...
Buried!
That son of a bitch.
[Gunfire]
Rick!
The rebels will help you.
They know Scott's Uncle.
Go, go!
Kim!
Die!
Unh!
Unh! Oh!
[Hatch door creaks]
Aah!
Nando...
Gonna leave without
saying good-bye?
How rude.
In honor of the closing
of your bar,
let me propose a toast.
[Panting]
To the c.I.A.
Aah!
[Bones crunch]
Chang:
Now we're outta here.
[Dog whimpering]
I'm sorry about this,
but no one's gonna
follow us up this way.
Kim: I can't believe Scott
carried the drums up here.
Don't worry.
He didn't.
There's a road up on top.
Kim: Hey.
I already had a shower,
remember?
Morgan: Yeah,
but unfortunately,
the entrance
is behind the falls.
Kim: Entrance?
Entrance to what?
Scott and I hosted
many a rave in here.
Yeah?
Yeah.
That used to be the
d.J. Booth over there.
I don't believe it.
What?
He sealed it!
There... there's
an alcove in here.
It's like 20 feet deep.
[Beeping]
[Beeping stops]
No!
It's too hot.
10 minutes in there,
and you'll bake
every atom in your body.
Chang: She's right!
What took ya?
Just paying
my last respects to nando.
Morgan: You keep popping up
in all the wrong places.
I'd love to tell you
I'm psychic.
Compliments of dupont.
Tracking.
[Counter clicking]
[Clicking rapidly]
Here. This is it.
Right.
[Air hisses]
Morgan: I don't get you.
Who do you work for?
You're not north Korean.
You sound American.
100% born and raised.
Wondering how I'd sell out
my own country?
You ever hear of rockefeller?
Carnegie?
It was Chang's turn.
I'm gonna make a killing.
Take it up.
[Grunting]
You'll never get that out
past the check point...
[gun cocking]
Don't worry about it.
Dupont already
took care of that.
He served his purpose.
Morgan: No wonder Scott
never trusted you.
[Man grunting]
All right, let's go.
[Gun cocking]
No, just you, Morgan.
It'll kill him!
I'm counting on it.
At least give me a flashlight.
You'll be glowing
in 5 minutes anyway.
Unh!
Argh!
We're outta here.
[Kim grunts]
[Sizzling]
[Screaming]
Leonard, put him
out of his misery.
No!
Yes, sir.
[Sizzling]
[Grunting]
[Clangs]
[Morgan grunting]
Aah!
Come on.
[Grunting]
[Gunfire]
[Gasping]
Whoa!
Unh!
Whoa, whoa!
[Grunts]
[Grunting]
Aah!
[Panting]
You scared the hell out of me.
[Madumo laughs]
You are very much like Scott...
always in over your head.
[Laughs]
Come on.
We've got a train to catch.
[Train whistle blows]
Chang: 8, 9, 1,000.
Just as Mr. dupont promised.
Ok, we're all set.
You.
Good doing business with you.
Right.
Let's go!
[Indistinct chatter]
The station is here...
And our forces have
taken over all the roads
leading to the river.
There is no escape for
them except by train.
[Indistinct chatter]
Had a good look?
Beat it.
Train fed his troops
across the plains,
through the Mountain pass.
There is no other stop
until port city.
[Train whistle blows]
Once we get past
the old mine site,
we are in government
controlled territory.
What about
the old copper line there?
Oh, no.
We blew the railway
line months ago.
It's totally useless.
No, that's...
that's totally useful.
We divert the train
onto the old copper line,
and... and they're not
gonna get to port city.
Can you get a hold of
Scott's Uncle at the c.I.A.?
Yep.
All right.
Better get your men ready.
How fast can you ride?
[Men shouting]
[Horses galloping]
[Horse whinnies]
[Men shouting]
Break right and left!
[Indistinct chatter]
Whoa!
[Horse whinnies]
[Gunshots] Aah!
[Gunshots and shouting]
Unh!
Unh...
[Gunshots and shouting]
Unh!
We don't have much time.
[Gunshots and shouting]
Whoo!
We got 'em, man!
[All cheering]
[Both grunting]
You go up there.
Yah!
[All grunting]
Aah!
Unh. Help.
[Both grunting]
Man: I don't
see anything.
Andreas, check the engine.
Yeah, I will.
Aah!
[Both speaking native language]
[All speaking native language]
[Upbeat music playing]
Madumo: What now?
Find Chang.
Start with the engine
and work our way back.
[Both grunting]
Aah!
Come on.
[Gunshots]
Let's go.
[Train whistle blowing]
Morgan:
How far to the split?
Madumo:
About a mile ahead.
Let's unhook the car,
get rid of these soldiers.
[Grunting]
Morgan: Chang's got
to be in the back.
Unh!
[Grunting]
Go-go,
go check on Andreas.
Yeah, boss.
Unh!
[Both grunting]
Aah!
Good shot, man.
[Train whistle blows]
[Grunting]
Keep trying.
I'm gonna check that box car.
Ok.
[Train whistle blowing]
[Speaking native language]
It's the wrong track.
Unh!
It's over, Chang.
You shit.
What took you so long,
boy wonder.
Sorry I'm late.
In 3 Miles,
this train and everything
on it are history.
You and I know
the rods will irradiate
the whole area.
They'll never survive
an explosion.
They won't have to.
Go up and help madumo
unhook the car. Go!
So smart.
Everybody's dirty.
It all ends up
in the same place...
somebody's bank account.
Scott knew that.
Oh, you're wrong, Chang.
Scott didn't sell out.
Oh!
[Both grunting]
Unh!
Uhh!
Look out!
Huh?
Aah!
[Panting]
[Grunting]
Unh!
Will you be all right?
Yeah.
[Gunfire]
Aah! Uncouple that!
Unh!
[Grunting]
I've almost got it.
Whoo-hoo!
Aah!
[Sighs]
[Both grunting]
Oh!
Unh!
We have to stop the train.
Yeah, go right ahead.
[Both grunting]
What the hell are you doing?
Guns and ammunition.
I can't let them go to waste.
[Both grunting]
Aah!
You don't have what it takes
to play in my world.
[Both grunting]
Aah!
[Gasps]
[Helicopter whirring]
Man on megaphone:
Rick Morgan?
This is agent fedie,
Scott's Uncle.
There's no time left.
We're gonna drop you a line
and get you out of there.
He wants to take
the barrel out first.
[Gasps]
[Grunts]
Move a little over here.
Over here.
Yeah.
Aah!
[Gasps]
[Grunting]
Unh. Come on.
[Sighs]
[Wheels screeching]
[Screaming]
Chang!
[Kim screams]
You let her go.
Come and get her, Morgan!
[Kim whimpering]
No!
[Kim screaming]
Aah!
[Screaming]
[Kim coughing]
[Men speaking native language]
You're all right, baby.
[Madumo laughing]
[Chuckling]
[Music playing]
[Horse whinnies]
Captioning made possible by
lions gate entertainment
captioned by the national
captioning institute
...Www.Ncicap.Org...
[music playing]
[Crickets chirping]