Yeah, who is it?
Esteban!
¿Como estas, hermano?
Yeah, I'm just drivin' back
from the ranch.
Got everything handled
with all the business.
Everything's a go.
Yeah?
Come on, hermano,
I don't like surprises,
and I don't want no birthday
gifts, man.
I'm frickin' in my 40s. I don't
need a damn surprise party, man.
I just want to... Hey, this month
is about makin' la feria, man.
Forget about it.
Just tell everybody to cancel.
I don't want a birthday party,
man.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Esteban.
Mija.
What are you guys doing?
What kind of party is this?
Esteban, mija, you could've gotten
rid of some of these candles,
at least put them out!
Chingao, that's pretty good.
Esteban?
Now, you know I don't like
these surprises?
What the hell?
What?
What the hell are you doing,
What the fuck?
Where's my daughter?!
Who are you?!
Hey! Shut the fuck up!
Mr. Zelman, I finished my job.
I can go, yes?
No, you stay,
and shut your beaner ass up
and let's get down to the
business at hand. Sit down.
Where is my daughter?
Where the fuck is she?!
Juan, you're not a traitor.
No lo creo, no lo creo.
Let's get down
to the business at hand.
Where's my daughter?
Mr. Solis, don't you smell
the garbage in the hallway?
-I'll kill all of you!
-Shut up.
Shut the fuck up.
Motherfucker!
No, no.
Don't you mean "daughterfucker"?
Hey, you better straighten up
and fly right,
you fuckin' one-eyed spic.
I'm not here on my business,
all right?
I'm here doing a favor for the
chinks. I owe 'em one.
And this is a 10-year debt
that I'm settling.
You stir-fried the wrong
fucking chink, didn't you?
I'm just a gun for hire, Mr.
Solis.
Woo King started that battle.
My family only answered
to instigation, and you know it!
My daughter!
I'm gonna cut your head off
if you don't kill me.
Kill me. Do it!
So, I guess a blow job's
out of the question?
Sir, can I just blast his face
off?
No, no, no. I'd like to oblige
you, Mick, but we can't do that.
The deal is we deliver him
alive.
Mr. Woo wants revenge
for his son,
so we got to take you
to the chink warehouse,
and they got some deep-rooted
plans for you, buddy,
and for your little spring roll.
They're gonna slice it off,
and Mr. Woo's gonna cook it up
in a wok, like Chinese sausage,
then he's gonna eat it right in front
of you while you're still alive.
And he's gonna invite some
guests.
Man, these chinks.
When they go after revenge,
it's balls to the wall.
Get him up! Get up!
-Get up, Mick.
-Get up. Stand him up.
I knew you weren't a traitor.
I knew it, Juan.
They took my daughter.
That's the only reason
I was under the gun, carnal.
I understand.
You know I got you covered.
Mr. Zelman, just say green
light, and I'll blast him.
You think you're gonna take me
out? Come on.
You two burritos
think you can blast me away
before my guy gets you?
Come on.
This guy's ex-CIA.
He was a sharpshooter before I
started to pay him more.
He might hit me,
but you're going down with me,
you punk-ass motherfucker.
You took my daughter.
My boys got her back.
Now you got two dead hillbillies
in your home right now.
You're going to hillbilly hell,
motherfucker.
Your cojones
are gonna get you killed.
I never liked it here anyway.
Dumb Mexican.
You got no gun, beaner.
Come on out!
Come on, motherfucker.
Amor.
They killed...
They killed everybody...
Esteban, my wife...
I know who it is!
Fuck! Shit, I got heat!
I got big-time heat.
Listen, I gotta go.
Call out my accountant, tell him
dump all my fucking stuff
Do it right now.
Just do it now.
Don't fuckin' play games,
just dump everything.
Get the cash.
We gotta go liquid on
everything.
Do what the fuck I say, just do
it! I gotta go!
Girls.
You look like you're having fun.
You need something else?
More wine for starters,
Mexicano.
Yeah, go get my sister
some more wine.
What did I tell you about the
dog? Be respectful. He's dirty.
Solis.
Mr. Gonzalo.
I told you,
I don't work on Saturdays.
I'm sorry, abuelo.
Call me on Monday.
Yes, sir.
I-I need to negotiate with you
right now.
Remember that deal about my store,
my office, about a year ago?
You wanted my...
Sir, listen, please.
I-I'm sorry I'm bothering you
on Saturday, but listen, please.
We negotiated a deal on my store
and my doggy biscuit business.
Please, listen to me.
Yes, sir. We negotiated,
but I'll give it to you
for 10 cents on the dollar.
Sounds like you have
a distress business right now.
Right now, sir.
I need an answer right now, sir.
I have no weapons.
-I'm on the phone.
-Put your hands up.
I have no weapons.
Get your fucking hands up!
Get 'em up!
Officer, I have no weapons.
I have no intent to harm.
I'm on the phone with my
attorney.
Drop the fuckin' phone
or Henderman will drop you
to your panties, you prick.
-Drop the fuckin' phone.
-Call me when you make bail.
Stop. You're under arrest
for the murder of David Zelman,
Jonathan Skykes,
and Lee Renardo Catello.
And I'm gonna throw
in resisting arrest.
Listen, I'll be out in 18 hours.
They killed my family!
Get in the car. Come on.
Get in the car.
I'll be out in 18 hours.
Put your...
Put your Miranda rights up your
culo.
What do you think of that?
-Hey, hey, hey, hey.
-They killed my family!
-Get in the car.
Your belongings.
Bob, those motherfuckers
made my bail higher
than Charles fucking Manson,
man. What the fuck?
You killed a congressman's son,
Mickey.
A congressman's son?
That guy's the head
of the fucking hillbilly mafia.
-He was a drug runner.
-Yeah.
-Crow doesn't peck another crow.
They're politicians, man. -Yeah,
they're fucking politicians.
Politicians, fuck 'em all.
They should all be fuckin' hung.
Mickey.
Every one of 'em.
We're in a police station.
Maybe...
Hey. Fuck 'em all.
Fuck all of you.
My kid's dead, man.
They don't give a shit.
You think Obama,
or his dirty tranny wife,
or Bush, or any of those people
care about my kids?
Nobody gives a shit
about my kids, man.
Fuck 'em all!
They're all on the same team.
I've got the right guy for you.
This guy.
The best lawyer I've ever seen.
He got Jim Jameson
off triple homicide,
and the cop even saw him
shoot the motherfuckers.
So, there you go.
My job's done.
I have a barbecue tonight
with the wife.
Do you know the difference between
a lawyer and a bail bondsman, Bob?
-No, I don't.
-Nothing.
You're all crooks, all thieves.
Fucking mooch.
Mr. Harrison.
Mickey Solis.
Sit down.
Your mother was a Mexican nanny,
or a housekeeper.
Your father was
an Irish-American trucker
who embodied the stereotype
of a drunken Irish fool.?
So you embraced
your mother's maiden name
because your father...
Well, he left for some
prostitute in Las Vegas.
Let's see. You had two other
sisters,
Maria and Martha,
both of them addicted to heroin,
died by the age of 25.
That's interesting.
Why did you embrace
the low-life path
with those diabolical scumbags
who were responsible
for your own sisters' death?
Those assholes, I took 'em out,
both of them.
And they took my eye.
It's a tough world out there,
sir.
I charge 2,000 an hour.
I'm the meanest motherfucker in
court you've ever seen.
I got 60% of the judges
giving me head, so to speak,
on demand.
The ones who don't, I make sure
I never appear before them.
Never lost a case, and I don't
intend to any time soon.
You, Mr. Solis, are up shit
creek
with only a broken paddle
stickin' out your asshole.
You, my friend, are fucked.
Nobody is gonna take your case,
because even the judges
who suck my proverbial cock
won't touch you
because they don't want to lose
their Masonic memberships.
They got to convict you.
Yep. You are 100%
irretrievably fucked.
Your case, Mr. Solis,
is cut and dry.
A triple murder.
Four neighbors say they see you
going into the building,
they hear the shots,
they see you comin' out,
only one alive.
Boy.
Well, I suggest
that you digest cyanide.
I can, provide you
the spring water.
2K an hour to hear this cagada?
Your Spanish is atrocious.
I learned Spanish
from my grandfather.
He was a Scotsman,
but he had a Mexican nanny,
and he used to hear stories
from his granddaddy before him.
And granddaddy actually fought in
the 1845 Mexican-American war.
Yeah. The Scots and the Irish
Catholics fighting,
slaughtering the indigents
in the name of...
What is it called?
Manifest destiny.
Only, they would hear the bells,
you see, at night,
ringing across the battlefield.
See, all of the Mexican soldiers,
they would be called to mass.
And the Scots and the Irish,
the Catholics,
they hear these sounds, and they
would slip away in the night.
And they would never come back.
Some of them would fall in love.
It's very romantic.
I'm developing a TV series about
it.
I developed a fondness
for the Mexican community
a long time ago.
See, I was bullied in school
by, all the brothers
who would call me a cracker,
and they would
beat the shit out of me.
But there was
this one Mexican-American kid,
big, giant guy,
and he would come,
and he would protect my ass.
Of course, he would charge me
two milk cartons
and three brownies a week for
it.
They taxed you.
I became a successful lawyer.
And I remembered the Mexican
kid,
and I, figured
I owe something back.
I spent a lot of time in Mexico
developing an orphanage for boys
who had it way worse
than you ever did, Mr. Solis.
Take for example, this kid here.
Fernando.
You see him?
He is one of many whom I support
with 50% of everything I earn,
which I take from misguided
dime-a-dozen gangsters like you.
And I donate it to my chicos.
Mr. Harrison,
my family has been slaughtered.
My son, my daughter.
The Woo family, the Chinese
gang, they took them out.
I have absolutely nothing
to live for.
Nothing.
And I would take
that cyanide you offer
if it wasn't for my undying
desire to take...
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
To... to... to avenge your son
and your daughter
and all of that,
machismo mambo jambo bullshit.
I'm not like you, okay?
But I understand.
I think I would feel the same
way.
But, the hourly rate
remains the same?
Most assuredly so.
So, what you're telling me now
is I should kill myself.
Any other useful information?
Well, I've already made a plea
bargain, manslaughter.
You will do five years.
So, question is,
how long do you need to do
your Pancho Villa routine?
Like, six months?
I can keep you on the street
for about that time,
and then, yeah,
you gotta do your time,
but you'll be out in three
years.
I have nothing else to live for
but to avenge my family.
Well, there is...
a nun.
And if you need some
spiritual help
You should call her.
She charges, 5,000 an hour.
5K an hour for a nun?
She's in your neighborhood.
She has a very mysterious
history.
Anyway, I feel sorry for you,
but I'm also a businessman,
and you bet your ass
she cuts me in.
You know I don't speak that
Spanish.
Why's your sister still here?
Why don't you do me a favor?
Buy her a ticket to Ohio
and send her back.
My sister stays as long as she
wants.
You keep fucking around,
and you'll both
be floating in the pool.
Excuse me, sir,
Mr. Solis is here.
Let him come out.
-Ladies.
-Buenos dias.
I thought you don't speak Spanish.
I do in an emergency.
I told you to keep your dog
in the other yard.
I don't like pit bulls,
especially this one.
Barks all night long.
Mr. Gonzalo,
is it possible we can go inside
and speak
about a very important matter?
What the fuck are you doing?
Are you insane?
I told you, I don't like pit bulls.
I'm gonna shoot this fucking dog.
I told you to leave him.
He's a crazy Mexican.
You're a crazy Mexican!
Mr. Gonzalo, with all due
respect, sir, I can take the dog.
You like to play?
No sir, I...
I don't play.
Your reputation precedes you.
My reputation? And what is that?
We're warriors against the grain.
Maybe you're too old for that.
Don't you think that music's
a little loud, sir?
I hear the Feds are on you,
watching you to fuck up.
Well, maybe you're right.
That music will drown them out,
that's for sure.
What's the ugly gray van
outside?
Well, it's ugly,
but it's not gray, it's silver.
I do some research
on your business.
It's worth only 500K.
10 cents on the dollar means
50K.
I need 700 grand.
What the hell you talking about?
It's 10 cents on the dollar.
Mr. Gonzalo,
my family was slaughtered.
The Woo King family took 'em
out.
I know who they are.
I know what happened.
Why should I be responsible?
Esteban, my son,
when you were younger and on the
street, he helped you.
You climbed up the ranks
because of his hard work, too,
and because of the connection
in Bogata.
Did I have a contract that I had
to pay his father percentages?
No, you don't.
But maybe it could be considered
to be an unwritten law.
Maybe on the street that works,
but I don't live that life
anymore, as you see.
It's good to remember
where you came from, sir.
You might cross those bridges
again.
I'll lend you the 500
with a 10% interest.
You have no idea
what this means to me.
Yes, I do.
10% interest.
I'll help you take
the Woo King family out.
They owe me
three million dollars forever.
What's this?
I'm gonna pay my girlfriend back
for being a bitch.
It's better than the burrito
in the driveway.
Bring it back
when you bring the money.
With a full tank of gas.
It's electric.
You don't look very Mexican.
My mother's Irish.
Irish.
Some say from the seed of
Abraham.
I trained as a nun in Belfast.
I'll never forget
those beautiful children
with their pale, white skin
and their rosy cheeks.
How did you know it was me?
Mr. Harrison told me.
It's not every day
a pirate walks in here.
I haven't smiled for a while.
I heard what happened to you,
to your family.
May I say that death
is a door that opens.
I hope not for some.
You're angry.
I know that kind of spirit.
It can be a driving force
to obliterate evil.
I remember...
I remember well,
when I was young.
This older man...
with gray hair.
He was a priest.
He thought I was lovely.
He said it too often.
And then, one day,
he took what would remain
my darkest childhood memory.
Why are you telling me all this?
I wasn't finished.
As I lay there,
bleeding from my lower parts
at nine years old,
I knew.
I knew that the devil
lives inside this church
just as much as the angels do.
And I swore...
to devote my whole being
to avenging anyone
who harmed children.
What happened to the priest?
Le corte los huevos al cabrón.
Look, I don't have time for this
crap.
You don't have time to avenge
for your granddaughter?
She was pregnant when she died.
My daughter was pregnant?
Yes.
I don't want to live
in this darkness anymore.
I only took on this job
because of your granddaughter.
I know Mr. King.
I used to go to them for funds.
-Funds? What kind of funds?
-Funds.
It takes funds to find and then
to take out child abusers.
I thought Mr. King and his family
were good people, buena gente,
and then I learned that they
were in the black market
making snuff films with little
ones...
Mr. Solis, I know who is responsible
for the hit on your family.
I can get to his lieutenant,
and from him, I can find the
whereabouts of Mr. King himself.
The rest, it's up to you.
You?
What, you're gonna do it alone?
What are you gonna do,
choke him with your habit?
What's your name?
I'm a nun.
Cincuenta mil.
50K...
And I'll get you
all the information you need.
Good night, Mr. Solis.
Yeah.
Hello. It's a little late to be
calling.
Who is this?
I'm sorry to be calling so late.
It's very important.
I wanted to let you know
it's the pirate.
What can I do for you, Mr.
Solis?
It's a green light.
You remember what I said?
Well, yeah.
I got the money.
Half now, and half
when you're done with the job.
It's inside the flowers I got
you.
And you better get 'em quick,
because you never know
about these priests.
I only got you the flowers because
you were helping my family out.
You know, helping me out.
I'm a nun, for goodness sake.
And I'm a good Catholic boy.
Thank you for helping me.
I hope this works out.
Buenas noches.
Chinga tu madre!
Fuck.
I drank way too much.
Hey, you here?
Perro?
Hey.
You were right there the whole
time.
How you doing?
Hey, you know,
I never got your name.
What's your name?
When my...
When my daughter,
when she was young, she...
She got a little dog.
And she came running up to me, and
she says, "Papi, I got a dog!
And guess what
I'm gonna name him?
I'm gonna name the dog 'Dog'."
I said, "Mija, you can't name
your dog, 'Dog'."
And she said,
"Papi, it's my dog,
and his name is 'Dog'."
I'm sorry I'm not such
a good host,
but I'm alone now,
and, well...
It's hard for me to look at
this, so I-I keep it in here.
I'll get you some dog food
today.
Thank you.
"Pirate, this is your favorite
'N'.
I did good, didn't I?
Your China dream
is just a few miles away."
Yeah?
Mickey, hermano.
Hey, is this Rudy?
What's up, Rudy?
Come on, ese.
Mickey, we know everything
you've been through.
Sorry, effacito.
Gracias, hermano.
Hey, listen,
I really appreciate it, man.
Hey, Mickey, come by Sunday.
-We'll have a barbecue.
-Yeah.
We can talk there.
Okay, hermano.
I really appreciate it.
I'll see you guys there.
Bring whoever you can.
Órale, nos vemos.
Okay, carnal. Gracias.
Yes.
-Say, Mickey.
-Mr. Harrison.
Hey, I got a few questions for
you.
Quick, quick couple of
questions.
I don't want to waste
your precious time.
So, do you know
what date it is today?
You missed the wire date,
motherfucker.
Shit. Hey, look, I have
every intention of paying you.
My guy, he pays in increments,
you know?
Do you have any idea
what I had to do
and who I had to grease
to make the deal to get you
out of prison for six months
and to get you out for
manslaughter?
-Do you have any idea?
-Yes, sir, I understand that.
So, don't fuck around with me.
Okay?
You think I get intimidated
by some chalupa mob?
You cunt.
I want my fuckin' money.
Hey, look. Hey, look.
I understand.
Hey, I'm not the guy
to push right now.
Who am I, Mickey?
Well, you're a great lawyer.
I'm gonna handle it.
I am Barkley fucking Harrison.
You think some chink mob
or some burrito hit squad
can fuck with Barkley Harrison?
I never said anything.
Shut the fuck up, you cunt.
I will send the one-eyed
Illuminati Satanists
to pay you a fuckin' visit.
Do you know who they are?
They are my friends!
My friends!
Every black and white,
every guy in a tie,
every white trash detective
in Orange County,
every fucking congressman,
every mayor.
The fuckin' president of the
United States takes my calls.
This guy is fucking crazy.
If it wasn't for my daughter and
my son, I'd fuckin' blast him.
Only 'cause I wanna get
venganza.
I know your struggle.
We are one,
but don't you fuckin' forget
my chicos, Mickey.
My chicos.
Motherfucker.
Fucking lawyers.
Every dog has his day.
Rudy's waiting for you.
Rudy!
I hear you're makin' a lot of
ducats on the street, que no?
Mickey, all these pendejos
on the streets of LA.
I wanna live like Obama
but I ain't gonna change it
from the White House
to the Brown House.
Hey, Mickey, I hear that you
need to fire up some chinos.
Just let me know, mijo.
If these bam-bams don't work,
this will.
Mickey, then show me to do
negocios.
I ain't letting these motherfuckers get
away with all that shit they pull.
How many people knew his
daughter, let alone Esteban?
We all know what happened to them,
but now, it's time to fix this shit.
Hermanos, I,... I didn't come
here for a handout.
I came here to give people feria
who want to chop on my onda.
I got to fix
these Woo King motherfuckers.
These guys, we can't let 'em
get away with this
without retribution,
what they did to my family.
¿Tu sabes?
If we lose this respect
on the streets,
all our value on the street
will go way down.
We gotta do something,
and we gotta do it now.
You might think this is just
about venganza, revenge,
but that's not true.
It's about respect and honor.
Respect we had
since the fuckin' '60s?
And that's why
we gotta take 'em down now,
this fucking Woo King family.
But we gotta do it without an
army.
'Cause if we go in there with an
army, they're gonna run,
and everybody's gonna scram,
and it's all gonna be fucked up,
the operation.
I need two of the best here.
Hey, Mickey.
I'm not doing this for money.
I'm doing this for fun.
What about you? Let's go down
and fuck around?
Hey, jefito, you know I would be
in, but I got too much business.
A lot of shit going down in TJ,
homie.
I need Benjamin Franklins.
I can't fuck it up, homie.
Yeah.
I guess it's gonna be
just me and Mona.
-We'll take 'em down.
-I got Hector.
He can do some leg work for you.
You know what, motherfucker?
If you don't help Mickey,
you will get no pussy.
I'm cutting you off
for, like, dias.
No, years.
You got that, punk?
No pussy for 10 years.
Chingao, Mickey, I think
I can reschedule some things
for later that month.
Sir, you may go
with your brother and sister.
The Mahjong game starts from
eight.
I shall have your dinner
prepared at 10:00.
Meixiu, you're only half my age, but
you're sounding like my mother.
I will return at the time I
desire. Bye.
Sir, we got a problem at the
bank.
We need the money,
500,000 in gold and cash,
counted by 6:00 a.m. tomorrow,
in the shipment to Shanghai.
Is that all?
They told me by Monday
I would have to.
That was the case,
but our FBI tag said that if we
don't get it out by tomorrow,
Immigration's gonna come
and swipe it up.
Okay.
So, I will have to drop you here
now.
Enjoy the game of Mahjong,
and my dear daughter will come
here on Monday to meet you all.
Okay.
Hey, how do you know
Woo King's here?
Woo King plays domino every
single Thursday at the same time.
Hey, guys, that's it.
There is Woo King's car.
Hey, Rudy, there is a woman
in the car.
I don't care.
Kill them all.
Let's go.
Where's Woo King?!
Where the fuck is Woo King?!
Let's go. Woo King's not here.
Let's go! Go!
Sir, it's getting very dangerous
right now.
Please grab your valuables.
You must go to Meixiu's.
We may be staying a while.
Angels, if you're out there,
tell my beautiful, lovely
daughter and Esteban
that I'm sorry I brought their
souls to an early death
for my lifestyle
and my mistakes in my life.
I will avenge their souls.
Yeah?
Hey, jefe. It's Rudy.
Carnal.
This bitch Woo King
wants to meet with you.
Sir, I do not believe
this meeting should take place.
My suggestions to you
as your spiritual advisor...
What wisdom do you wish to
convey?
Mickey Solis, he falls under the
star sign of the Tiger.
It symbolizes the traits
of bravery, unpredictability.
I can assure you,
he will fight to his death
to protect his loved ones'
honor.
I too fall under the same sign.
Meixiu, a woman's stillness
is her greatest attribute.
The chinks have been checked
just like you.
No metal in this room.
Just us.
You know
the Southside Conference rules.
They're in place.
You both got 30 minutes maximum.
If you don't come to an
agreement,
then we escort all of you
out of here,
and then you can blast your
monkey asses off in the street.
If it gets physical, then we
blast whatever side starts it.
Mr. Solis, I never met you before,
but I heard a lot about you.
A couple of made guys
wanted to bring you in
as a consultant on a few things.
I'm sorry about the loss
of your family.
Well, then,
let's just get down to business.
I'm here to listen.
My father taught me
to observe all doors
before going through any of
them.
What do you want?
I say what he wants,
to bring peace now?
Because we whacked all his family,
and now he wants to bring peace?
He's just a coward.
He knows that Mexicans
don't give up.
Do you hear that?
Mexicans don't give up.
But we will hear
what Mr. King has to say.
What do you have to say?
Mr. Solis,
your son, your daughter,
they will never return to this
earth.
My son, my son, do you hear me?
My son, he will not return
to this earth.
You deserve death. Death!
Fellows, we do not get paid
enough
for this chicken chow mein
soap opera.
Hey, fuck you.
Fuck you!
The Italian mob went out with
disco.
You motherfuckers ain't got nothing
left on the street, and you know it.
You want to blast me, go ahead.
If my people green light you, if
my gente, they put you on blast,
you'll be out before you can say
"badabing badaboom."
Mr. King, you didn't say we had
to do deal with this shit.
What the hell?
It is courageous,
your display in front of these
nice Italian colleagues.
However, shall we think
about the rest of our family?
And I only have
my youngest daughter.
You took the rest of our family.
Is that not enough?
You are the one
who brought this fire on.
I only put it out.
It is not only my daughter,
a person I am eager for,
it is for all of us.
Are we so ignorant
to take all our lives down?
Yes, I won't lie,
I want my daughter's life.
I know you Mexicans
won't kill the young,
but when my daughter grows
older,
she might be the object
of your revenge.
I will do anything to stop this
war.
I know it's hard to believe,
but I'm sorry for your loss.
Mr. King, we're both
businessmen.
We both knew and understood
the risks involved
in this type of business.
We both knew that our children's
lives could also be like a vapor,
and they could go like this.
And they did.
And now,
we both suffer the anguish.
I live in hell.
I am the walking dead.
We can end all of this now.
Mr. Solis, you don't desire to
live.
I can't give you the reason for
that.
Your mother, she is...
She is not the reason?
What are you fuckin' playing at?
My mother left me long, long
ago.
Yet, she gave you life,
did she not?
Yet, she is safe.
She's very safe.
You don't love her,
but she's still your mother.
I want this war to end
for my daughter.
I have not seen my mother
in 30 years.
You think you get to me?
Is blood not thicker than water?
We can end this meeting
for my daughter's life.
My daughter's life
for your mother you hated.
-Man.
-Wait, wait.
Please, sit.
No way, jefe.
Enough blood has flowed.
Enough. Enough has flowed.
Can you assure me my mother
will stay alive and unharmed?
I assure you
that no harm will come to her.
Then I give you your daughter's
life.
My daughter's life,
you give me your solemn word?
I swear on my daughter's soul
that no harm will come to her.
Hey, Rudy.
Where are you, man? I thought
you were at the casita.
No, holmes, I'm not at the casita.
I'm at the accountant office.
Yeah, this guy,
he don't do shit I say.
I call him up 50 times,
he don't do shit.
Like, these, you know, lawyers
and his fucking' bail bondsmen
are a bunch of criminals,
holmes.
Hey, look, I need a takedown
guy.
Somebody quick, smart,
but a badass.
Yeah, man, Hector is the best.
Hector? Hector Ortiz?
Simón, Hector Ortiz.
Shit, he used to do my fuckin'
pickups in the 90's, holmes.
He's still around?
Yeah, man. He's still there,
he's still around.
He's puro soldado, homie.
It's certainly nice to ascertain
while you cancel
a perfectly good offer.
I'm very busy.
And, by the way,
I left you a message.
That was smart. You left
a message on my house phone.
You didn't think of leaving it
on my cell phone?
Ambassador Berman,
you know, I must have sat
in this office 33 times
since you became the German
ambassador to the USA.
I've never found one mistake.
You're an amazing woman.
Who'd have thought?
May I?
Two old age foes could have
such a collegial relationship.
William, I suggest you stop
trying to get me in bed
every time you wanna know more
about Angela Merkel's
anti-Obama spy tactics.
Maybe you are not British.
Maybe you are CIA.
-I loathe them, darling.
-Do you?
My father was not found with 23
bullets in his upper torso
for no reason.
He was raised in Bavaria,
and he did not know
any of this business
with the East side of Los
Angeles.
And for some mysterious reason,
he was gunned down
in the middle of the night,
on the night I bid him farewell.
Did you know something about
that?
Frankly, Greta, I,... I find
your paranoia disconcerting.
You know very well I have
no intel on your father's death.
And you also knew the risks of
your job, of your ambassadorship.
Especially a country like Germany
with so many historical enemies.
And let me ask you something.
How do you know it wasn't another
country that paid the Mexicans?
Our country is only rich
because we work damn hard.
Yes, Katrina?
Mrs. Berman,
there's a very demanding man.
Solis?
How did you know?
Instinct rules me.
We have a meeting.
I'm just finishing this meeting.
He can drive here
at his convenience.
He's already here
in the office, ma'am.
But how did he come through
Security?
He had your passcode, ma'am.
Yes. Yes, I remember.
Okay, send him in.
-Mrs. Ambassador.
-What's this?
It's Mr. Solis.
He's wearing an eyepatch,
for God's sake.
I don't know who you are,
and maybe I don't care to know,
but I got a meeting
with the ambassador,
and I suggest you let us have
it.
You "got" a meeting?
I "have" a meeting
with the ambassador,
-I think you'll find, dear boy.
-Out of my face, holmes.
-Let me just call Security.
-Yeah, you call Security.
They're all from my
neighborhood, motherfucker.
Please, it's personal.
What was your first name?
Mickey.
Well, touché, Mickey Solis.
What got stuck up that guy's
culo?
What the hell you think
you are doing here?
You can destroy my reputation
in one hour.
Hey, you told me to come here
when I needed to,
when I needed something.
And I need something right now,
a favor.
You could have called me
on my cell first.
I did. I left a message.
You didn't answer.
Well, I don't have always my
cell.
Why are you risking my
reputation coming here?
Mrs. Berman,
when your father was killed,
you came to me,
I didn't come to you.
You wanted to know
who killed him, I found out,
and I took care of business.
Now, it's your turn
to repay the favor.
It's not the proper time, Mr.
Solis. -Mrs. Berman!
My kids were
in the prime of their life.
Now, you owe me a favor,
and I'm coming here
to fucking collect, you got it?
I paid you well.
Money doesn't mean everything
when your life's at risk.
Now, you owe me a fuckin' favor,
and I need it now.
You need not curse.
I need two passports for two
ladies.
And two visas.
They gotta go to Asia.
They gotta take a boat.
And I need 'em now.
I'm not the queen,
I'm a damn ambassador.
How shall I get your passports,
and for whom?
You don't have to curse.
How was your day at school?
Very well thank you.
Hey. Don't think about it.
Give it to me.
I could kill you in front of the
girl and make it easy.
Take her in the car.
You got five seconds to say your
prayers, and then, you're dead.
-What's your name?
-Mulan.
Mulan. I know that it's been
a very difficult day for you,
but I assure you, nothing is
going to happen bad to you.
-Okay?
-Okay.
All right.
There's gonna be a lady.
She's gonna come
and take you somewhere,
take you to Beijing
to your grandparents.
You told me
that you enjoyed it there, yes?
Okay.
The lady that comes along...
It's okay. It's Norma.
Hey, Norma.
¿Como estas?
Come here, baby.
-How are you?
-Hey, Mickey.
-Sorry about your family, man.
-It's okay.
Here's 30K in cash,
and two plane tickets to
Beijing.
You got the passports ready?
The new ones?
Got 'em. Good as new.
All right. Take care of her.
Hey.
You're gonna be all right.
I promise you that, okay?
Go visit your grandparents
and have a good time, all right?
All right. Go.
Take care, kid.
-Come on, mija.
-Go.
You'll be all right.
Have a safe journey.
What the heck?
It's okay.
Mickey, is that you?
Yeah, it's me.
Look, Dora.
Dora, there's something
going on now.
I want to talk to you about it.
I haven't seen you
since I was a kid, you know?
But, I don't want anything
to happen to you.
There's some very dangerous
people.
They might try to hurt you.
Here's 20,000.
I don't want to go nowhere.
-Listen to me.
-No...
-This is serious!
-No, no.
This is not a joke!
Listen to me.
Now, you're drunk as usual, but
you're gonna listen to me now.
You're gonna take this money
and you're going to Ireland
until I tell you to come back.
Do you hear me?
This is not a fucking joke.
-How much?
-20,000.
-Really?
-Yes.
Hector, get her ready.
Get her stuff ready.
Let's get her to the airport.
There was never any time
for that before. Why now?
Please, get ready. Please.
Chingao.
Hey, Hector,
where the fuck are ya, holmes?
Hey, homeboy.
I'm over here in Soto, man,
checking out some firepower.
Yeah, right. You're probably just
trying to get into that electric car
all night or something, holmes.
It's hard to stay away from,
right?
Think I'll steal it.
Yeah, wait till you're done
with the job,
and then, you can steal it.
All right, hurry up.
I'm waiting on you.
-Yeah?
-Where's Rudy?
Rudy is getting ready to blast.
There's a time for war
and a time for peace.
Then, war it is.
What you need from me, cariño?
Hey, I haven't heard from
Hector. Have you heard from him?
Nada, mijo.
Look, I need you to bring
some fuego in your purse.
I always have fire in my purse.
I need my soul.
Hey, I got all the info we
needed. Everything's set up.
I got Woo King's address.
He's now in Los Feliz.
I'll see you guys at Beverly
and Highland, 30 minutes.
Mickey, we gotta pull into that
park because I left the AKs.
Hermano, fuck,
you left the AK's in a park?
Fuck.
All right, just...
We'll go in and get 'em.
What's wrong?
That's Mickey Solis's car.
I know it. I know that car.
He uses it on runs.
I got his ass!
I got his ass! I got his ass!
Arresting someone's
worth more than head?
Arresting Mickey Solis,
I'll get a big bonus.
Hey, where's my c-note?
You want to get arrested, bitch?
Get out.
Get out. Fuck off.
Fuck off, you bastard.
Detective.
I see you made bail.
Where'd you get the dough?
I thought you'd kinda lost
all your dough
from that sour deal
that went down last year.
Well, it's a land of
opportunity,
and I'm, trying
to make a comeback
after all my heartache lately.
Where's your boy scouts at?
I'm off duty, churrosucker.
Well, you know, sir,
discrimination is against the law.
And so is prostitution.
I hear that they're doing about,
I don't know,
about a thousand dollar fine
nowadays?
So, I suppose it's not gonna
make much difference
if I spill your hot sauce all over
this car, which is probably stolen.
Hey, we're clean.
Stay in the fuckin' car.
I'm calling this in.
Chingao.
Mona, you gotta take this
fuckin' guy and make him good.
Do something, baby.
Sex him up.
Make it...
Make this shit go away.
We're gonna do nine years, mami
. Go.
Make it happen, baby.
Chingal.
Okay, 1-Adam-7, 1-Adam-7.
Hey now, hold that...
Hold that call.
Hey, I thought I told you
to get your culo in the car.
-You got your pillow?
-Yeah, I got it here with me.
If she don't make it happen,
bro, you gotta blast him.
-You gotta blast him...
-Chingao, man.
Come on. I can walk a line for
you, if you want.
Please, come on.
Hey, you look sexy,
but I don't do beaners.
How do you call me?
Do you think you're gonna stop me
from calling this in, you beanhead?
What do you call me?
What do you call me, bastard?
Fucking make it happen.
Hit him hard.
Let's go!
Hermanos, you go in the back,
I go in the front.
-Let's take out Woo King.
-Right on.
Mona, stick with Mickey.
Cover him.
Are you crazy?
I go with you. You are my man.
I go with you everywhere.
Okay, come on.
I'm asking you one more time
again.
I won't repeat myself.
Is there any way
you can send me more security?
Five is not enough.
You know these Mexicans.
They're insane.
Mr. King, no one knows you're
here.
You are in my house.
It's safe.
Mr. Solis will never know
you're here.
You're worried, Mr. King.
The Art of War:
"The principle controlling
a large army
is the same as controlling
a few men."
Woo King!
You're mine!
Solis, you liar.
You lied to me.
Come on down, Emperor!
It's your day to die!
Mickey. Mickey.
Time to go to the loo.
The loo?
Rudy?
Rudy! Mona!
Let me cool you off.
Mr. Solis, I am only a rose.
Should a rose suffer
because it nears the thorns?
Fuck your Chinese philosophy.
Mr. Solis, I negotiated
your mother's safety.
Rudy?
Mona?
Rudy! Rudy!
Mona!
Rudy.
Mona.
Venganza!
Do you know, Mickey?
Do you know what plans we have
with your granddaughter?
When we steal her,
we're going to make sweet
one six million dollars
for one movie.
Russians pay top dollars, snuff
film from your granddaughter.
Come on, I got something sweet
for you!
The taste of your own blood!
You die today,
you fuckin' evil bastard!
Chinese, we're the smartest
race.
We shall overcome all.
The dragon shall consume
Mexico and America.
It shall consume it like a fire,
and take its gold, its land,
even its children.
You shall bow before our feet.
We shall be like a god.
God!
Hey!
Mr. Harrison, please, turn
around.
I have your final payment for
you.
I remember you said that you
loved the Mexican community,
that you embraced it.
But you forgot one thing, one
word.
Venganza.