♪ Hey, where you goin'
♪ Hey, I think I'm
goin' there too
♪ Now you got me thinkin'
♪ Maybe we can walk
there together
♪ Me and you
♪ Walking alone
gets contemplative
♪ Walking for two
gets conversative ♪
- We have four days left,
it's not that bad really,
if you think about it.
You know how these
things work, right?
Big burst of energy
at the beginning
because everybody's really
excited about the campaign.
And then you get a big burst
of support at the end
because everybody
wants to be the hero
that gets you over the top.
- You're not telling me
anything I don't know, babe.
- I know, I understand that.
I mean, I haven't
sent any emails yet.
I mean everything's been
super general to this point.
You gotta send the personal
stuff because that's what,
you know, really gets
people involved.
- Look, I'm not
saying I wanna do it.
I'm saying I think we
should consider it.
- They put up a tree.
- What?
- The rental company,
they put up a tree.
- I think it's kinda nice.
- Yeah.
It makes certain assumptions
though, don't you think?
- I guess so.
- It's pretty.
- You're pretty.
- Nur pey.
- We're not talking
your parents.
- Can we have a
conversation that's
just in the vicinity of reality?
I mean, I'm not saying I
don't believe in miracles...
- Miracles come in moments,
be ready and willing.
- But I know they would
help us, I mean, look,
they've talked about selling
this place for years!
- We are not asking your
parents for the money.
We will find it a different way.
Look, Sadie's agent is in
love with your script, right?
And once they package it
and make it for a
gajillion dollars,
I can finally retire and be
your dandy gentleman
about town, hm?
- Did we get Sadie's, um...
- Gluten-free, soy-free,
dairy free, taste-free.
Lots of...
- She has food allergies.
- It's gonna be okay.
- You're on onions.
♪ Hey let's climb a mountain
♪ Hey let's walk the plains
♪ We got plenty
of boot leather ♪
- You're like...
You're like a goddess.
You're like, like an angel.
You're like...
You're like a goddamn angel that
fell straight out of heaven
and onto my...
- Longboard?
- I love you.
- I...
I gotta piss.
- Do you mind if I...
- No.
Kinda like it quiet.
♪ In five minutes time,
I dropped the dime
♪ I juiced a lime,
slipped on slime
♪ I bought to the mime,
stopped some crime
♪ Sniffed a sign but
cracked a rhyme
♪ Imagine if I had
quarter-hour ♪
- Okay, how's this?
"" With arts education funding
decreasing sharply every year,
"it's more important
than ever..."
We okay?
- It's just a panic
attack, keep going.
- Okay, um, "it's more
important than ever
"for theaters like TPITH
to provide students with
"essential exposure
to the arts"...
- Time is it?
- It's 6:18.
- Fuck, we never
start early enough.
- No it's fine, everybody's
gonna be late and
Sadie will be here but she
doesn't eat anything anyway.
- You know, not helpful.
- All right, lay it on me.
- Roast in the oven.
Yams, dressing for the salad.
Go get flowers.
Um.
Go.
- Uh, five campaign
updates before midnight.
Grant draft is complete.
Calls to the Yancies
and Johnsons
- It's a holiday,
they'll hate it.
- Yeah but you have to
thank people right away
- Well, we're not gonna
have time for flowers.
- Can you schedule the posts?
- No, the Kickstarter
doesn't work that way.
You have to update...
- It's a holiday!
I get tonight. - Okay, okay.
But can you read
this in the bath?
- Yes.
Don't burn the yams.
- Go team.
It's okay, take a towel.
You got this.
Coming!
♪ I wish I was
rhymed all the time
♪ Way longer than
a quarter-hour ♪
- Happy New Year!
- It's good, good, man.
Good, good, hey.
You should totally
come here as well.
It's good to see you.
Absolutely, thank you.
- Yeah.
Should, uh...
- Fuck.
- All we're saying is
that remakes typically
You can't remake something
and make it better.
- In theory it's typical
but not always!
- Well give me one example
under exception then.
Give me one example.
- Obviously.
- Sabrina.
- Yeah.
- The original Sabrina
had Humphrey Bogart
and Audrey Hepburn... - Exactly!
This is what I'm saying.
He's like 80 years
older than she is.
It's gross! - No.
- Dude, that was before Viagra.
- Sorry, sorry.
We will finish this later,
can you handle this?
- You ready to do this?
- Mm-hm, hm-hm.
Yeah.
- It's in the, um...
- Okay.
Do you wanna read it, or...
I don't know, I just don't
want you to be shocked
- Did you write
something shocking?
- Well no, but...
I just don't know how
these things go.
Steven has excellent diction but
Jude seems like he might have
questionable reading skills.
- Does it tell the truth?
- Mm-hm.
- Okay.
- Meh, I tested for a pilot but
my agent said the money
wasn't good enough, so...
- Has there been any
movement on the script?
- Oh, Nessa!
Did I tell you Jude
wrote a song for me?
- Yeah.
I'll play it for you later
like an exclusive concerto.
I haven't even played
it for the guys yet.
It's gonna be a single.
- You know, actually I think
you should take a look at it.
You haven't read it and I...
- Can we just go inside?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
it's just cold out here.
You know how I hate the cold.
- Yeah.
- I'm sure it's fine.
- Here they are!
- Hi.
Steven, Jodie and
Bryce are here!
Get off your laptop!
Hi!
- You gotta spread the wealth.
- You gotta spread the wealth?
But the thing is you also
gotta have intelligent people
or it's just a disaster.
- Yes, yes.
- It's like playing
poker with people
that don't know to play.
I mean, what the problem
is, it's not, oh, oh.
- I think you have
to put a new...
- I just got the
look, so um, uh.
It was 10 years ago
that we moved back to the valley
with trepidation in our souls
and hope in our hearts.
And it was only through
your friendship
that we made it through
those early years.
You painted scenery,
you hauled costumes,
you got drunk with
us on the floor
when we didn't have
any furniture.
But no matter what
heartache or broken toes,
or mold-induced asthma
the months brought,
you always got
together with us here
at Nessa's family's cabin
to celebrate New Years.
- Yay.
- And so I just wanna say,
to our nearest and
dearest friends,
thank you for being here with...
- Steve, actually, Jodie
and I have something
that we'd like to contribute
to the toast this year.
- Babe, maybe wait
'til he's finished.
- We know where he's
going with this, right?
Friendship and their
theater, uh, and the usual
but we just thought while we're
talking about friendship
that it was a good time
to share some news.
Steve, if you don't mind.
- Not at all buddy,
the floor is yours.
- Thank you.
Tada!
- Bryce, you made something...
- Is it, is it...
- It's a home brew,
it's like an aperitif.
- Now he brews all
his own stuff.
You can really taste the
weedkiller in the domestics.
- Fucking Monsanto.
- Considering our audience,
we thought that the best way
to share our news would be
to perform it.
So, everyone gets a roll.
- How fun!
- And if you'll just open these,
and read them
in order,
we have the number.
- Is this like a riddle?
- No, each person has a line
and then you just
read it, in order.
- Oh, it's like a round.
Like a poem told in a round.
- I believe Sadie's says start.
- This is so exciting.
Fancy.
"Our darling friends so close,
"the time has come for a toast."
- "We've had a
good six-year run,
"but our relationship
is now done."
- "The fact is,
Bryce wants babies,
"and Jodie does not even maybe."
- "We're at the end of our wits
"so we're calling it quits,
"but we'll stay friends
because love doesn't die."
- So lift your glasses up high.
Come on.
And toast to new friends,
and not goodbye.
To friends.
- To friends.
- We just wanted to let
you know that we're okay.
We still love each
other, we just
can't be together anymore.
- Guys...
- This is intense.
- You really don't want
babies, like ever?
- Come on, Sadie, you
knew that about her.
- Well, I just thought
that was a phase.
I mean, we're thinking about it.
- What?
- Not tomorrow.
- Isn't full frontal
in your contract?
- And you have, food allergies.
- Well, aren't you
thinking about it?
- The theater is our child.
- You have to have
sex to be pregnant.
We just, we have
different priorities.
- But this is human life!
I mean, you can't tell
me that as artists,
you think your life would be
complete without that, like,
essential human experience,
raising a child, molding a life.
Uh I don't know,
what could be more
primal or dramatic?
- So I'm sorry, what
you're saying is that
a person has to have a child
in order to have a
complete human experience?
- I didn't say that, actually.
- Don't take the bait, Vanessa.
- No, I wanna know.
- Guys, we don't have
to do this now, okay?
- We're cool to start, right?
- Yep.
- I'm sorry.
Jodie changes the world
with her photography.
She has literally sparked
political upheaval
with her work... - I know!
- And so you want
her to what, quit?
- No I don't, I don't
want her to quit.
- There are 10 billion people
stretching this
planet's resources
to the breaking point.
- Yes, we know.
- You guys, you got her
started, this is the...
- What if their kid's
like the next Mozart?
- That's no pressure
or anything.
- What if their kid's
a serial killer?
- Or an asshole.
- Or an asshole!
- Okay, yeah, so the
world's gonna end
and we're all doomed, so...
- No, the world is not gonna end
- So what, we're supposed to
just give up, stop living,
and write bitter,
depressing plays about it?
- No, but the world is
changing and I think
that there are
choices other than
"I just want them
'cause I want them."
- Right, because having
children is selfish.
- Oh well, selfish
or not, apparently,
I'm not a complete human being
so I better stop with all my
crazy lady thought writing
and start breeding already!
- Steven, tell her I'm
not being selfish.
- I think a thing is
neither good nor bad,
but thinking makes it so.
- Equivocator.
- That is deep.
Was someone gonna say grace?
- You guys, enough.
I don't want to solve
global warming tonight.
I just wanna get
drunk and have fun
with my friends, who
are breaking up.
Are we gonna have to divide
custody like two New Yearses?
- No, Sadie...
- Honey, honey, no.
Look, we still love each other.
We just don't wanna
procreate together.
- Yeah, so if you have
any single friends...
- This brie is blowing my mind!
- I...
- Seriously.
- To mind-blowing brie.
- Can we get some meat, please?
- What is this,
the 18th century?
- You know what can we just
leave them out a minute?
- Oh, darlin'.
- I really missed you girls.
- Steven just posted
something funny
on the theater's Facebook page.
- Get off your phone, Steven!
I just can't get him to...
present.
- I think I'm gonna die
my hair this color.
- I just got a friend
request from TPITH.
Spammers should be like
eaten by zombie wolves.
- That's uh, The
Play's The Thing.
- Steven's theater
that he's always talking about.
- Yeah, you know,
"The play's the thing
"wherein I'll catch the
conscience of the King."
It's Hamlet.
You know Hamlet?
Shakespeare Hamlet?
Seriously? Not even like,
Mel Gibson Hamlet?
- What are they teaching
kids these days?
- You don't know it?
Dude, no, seriously.
You're gonna love this.
This is a great story, right.
So Hamlet is this prince,
young guy, right?
He's called home from school
because his dad is dead.
So he's gotta come home
for the funeral, okay?
When he gets home, he
finds out that his mom
has remarried, like already.
His dad is not even
cold in the ground,
she's remarried, right?
She's remarried to his
uncle, his dad's brother.
And his dad's brother,
his uncle has decided
that he should be
the king, right?
- And then he wrote that poem,
and I just... - Oh god.
- I couldn't...
- This whole thing
belongs on YouTube.
- What did I miss,
did I miss a funny?
- Where are you gonna live?
- I don't know.
I mean, Bryce'll
want me to stay, but
I'll just find a gig out
of town, something.
- You can stay with us!
I mean Jude's place is huge.
It's a little huge
messy but you know.
- Thank you, I don't
wanna impose.
- Are you...
- Relieved?
I don't know.
It's all logistics right now.
Here's the fun facts.
Documenting third-world poverty
does not pay very well.
- What are you gonna do?
- Shoot porn.
Well, thanks for the support,
you little assholes.
- It can be very tasteful.
- Maybe this will help.
- Mmm, are we about to go
on a magic carpet ride?
- Jude brought it
back from Tulum.
- It looks...
- Illegal?
- Okay.
- Uh...
- To, uh...
- Mm-hm.
- Horacio cradling his
head in his arms,
Fortinbras bursting
into the throne room
with his armies behind.
He dies.
"Good night, sweet prince,
"and flights of angels
sing thee to thy rest."
- I gotta write a
song about this.
People need to hear this story.
- You should come down
to the theater sometime.
We do this every day,
man, twice on Sundays.
- It would be so much better
if you didn't have to beg.
- Yeah, it would.
- No, I just mean, you know,
it's always like,
"Here's the airplane,
"open up, open up, please!"
It's just not like that
with litigation support.
- No, I don't imagine
it would be.
- Aww.
Oh.
- That is wrong.
- Play it again, play it again.
- That was a great
year for movies!
Rocky 4 came out that year.
- Yeah, but it's not...
- Rocky 4 is an incredible...
- It's no witness.
- Well, it might be a
little better than witness.
Rocky 4's incredible!
- I mean, it...
- Not better than E.T.
- Come on!
- Why is this so compelling?
- Because kittens no
nothing of Congress.
- This, he's thowin'
boulders, right,
he's carrying logs on his back.
- The ab thing!
- Like, 45 degrees.
- I can't do any ab things.
- Dude, he doesn't even, he
doesn't even go out of shape.
- He trims though.
- Yeah, no.
Get it, kitty, get it.
- No but seriously, what's
going on with the script?
Have you heard anything?
- Racist?
- I think it's racist.
- No!
- Yes.
- Seriously?
- Yeah!
- What's racist?
- Come on, come on.
Hold on, he's a cold-blooded
Russian fighter,
who comes to America, is
on steroids, by the way,
kills his best friend,
seemingly on purpose,
which the entire Russian
population thinks is awesome
because obviously, they too
are cold-hearted and evil.
- We're at the end
of the Cold War,
it's a commentary
on the whole time!
- Wait wait wait, in
all the other movies,
he just goes around
beating up black guys.
- Come on!
- He does.
- All right, I'm gonna
walk you through it.
We're gonna start back
at the beginning.
Rocky I, he loses that fight.
- But...
- He loses it.
- What happened?
- They have agreed
to run my story.
- And?
- If I can find my way
to Rwanda and back.
- Drago!
- It's so good!
- Okay, okay.
- That is basically
my point, basically.
- I'm just not
feeling it anymore.
- Dude.
- What?
- Plus, Paulie gets
that sweet robot.
- He does.
How many times did we...
- I loved that movie.
- We saw that movie, we went to,
this guy went to
Rockython with me.
- Rockython?
- Yeah, Rockython.
We wore like flag shorts
and everything, come on!
- It was different,
we were different.
- We're weren't different.
- If you say so.
- Plus, he got brain
damage in that fight.
He did, yeah.
- No, nope, nope, we don't
talk about Rocky 5.
Nobody talks about,
Stallone doesn't even
talk about Rocky 5.
That movie is not,
but Balboa, we get back to
Balboa and the end movie!
And that one ends the story.
- Hi.
- What is that stuff?
♪ Let's drunk to the sun
sinkin' a row the day
♪ Let's drink a
dozen now it's dark
♪ Let's drink to the
stars that shine away
mornin' spark ♪
♪ So early the night falls
♪ All around us
- Steve Buscemi.
- Yes!
- Oh, oh, oh!
- Pretty Woman!
- Oh, that movie, um.
- Little Mermaid!
- Interview, Interview!
- Yes, yes!
- There's clearly
cheating going on!
There's some kind of
vaginal telepathy.
- Smart girls are hot.
- Final score, ladies
12, gentlemen 10.
- Rematch, rematch!
- No, no no, new game.
- Come on!
- Yeah um, oh.
Two truths and a lie. - Boo.
- Oh, no, no, come on!
We haven't played
that since college.
- There's a reason for that.
- I don't know that game.
- It's easy.
Okay, for example um,
A, I have a third nipple,
uh, B,
eggs give me terrible gas,
and uh, C,
I have a birthmark in the
shape of New Jersey.
- C.
- Sadie, cable is the
Naked You channel.
We have seen it.
- And smelled it.
- You have a third nipple?
- Okay okay okay, my turn,
I wanna go, I like this.
All right.
A, my favorite kind of
pie is strawberry pie.
B, I once ate 15 cheeseburgers
and then barfed them
all up on stage.
C, my new single
just went platinum
in Japan.
- How many is that?
- That's like 250,000 something.
Like, at least, that can't be.
It's C, right? We're
gonna go with C.
It's C, definitely C.
- Ah, fuckin' C.
I have no poker face, man.
We went platinum in Germany.
We're trying for Japan but...
- What?
- Jude, that is...
That is awesome.
Congratulations, man.
- Yeah, thank you!
- That's incredible.
- Thank you!
Yeah, we just...
We let this one flow and
it just kinda worked out.
You know, it was really organic.
- I'm sure it was.
- Why don't you go next, buddy?
- Okay, A, I think argyle socks
are more stylish than solids.
B, I have an aversion
to electric staplers.
C, women who are mothers are
35% more likely to be happy,
healthy, and report a
greater sense compassion
and purpose in their lives.
- Is that true?
I don't think that's
true 'cause my mom
is a very mean person.
- You know, I have always
hated this game and uh,
we have due
resolutions so let's,
can you do resolutions?
- What?
- Resolutions.
- Oh, ah...
Well, I...
Um.
I did resolve to raise
$70,000 by Tuesday,
so I have that.
There is that, and um,
I don't think have anything
else other than that right now,
so uh Sadie, you go.
- No, I'm not ready,
you go, Jodie.
- Jodie doesn't believe
in resolutions.
- Okay fine, um, okay.
I resolve to be kinder, and...
Accept things that
I can't control,
and you know, not obsess
over skinny bitch actresses
who are stealing all my parts
you know, because I
really do love them
in my heart of hearts, and
jealousy only hurts me
and I just want the
best for them even if I
secretly want them to
develop warts and die.
- I think Sadie just modernized
the serenity prayer
for us, guys.
- Thank you.
I want you to resolve to
save me from these jerkoffs.
- Aw, come on!
- I resolve to save Sadie
from you jerkoffs.
And I resolve this
year to be happy.
- You just decide to be happy?
- Yeah.
- I just see these dudes like
deciding to lose
five pounds, right?
Or like learn a language,
or like watch less
porn or whatever,
and I don't think it
makes them any happier.
Are they really
happy being like,
"Pass the TV" in French?
- It's a phrase.
- Is it?
- I'm sure it's really
easy for someone
with your life to be happy.
- How do you resolve
to make yourself
happy this year, Bryce?
- Well, I don't know.
I guess I haven't
really thought about
what it's gonna be like to be
solo in the new year.
But I guess I resolve...
Yeah, I resolve to find someone,
to find someone who
shares my values
and who wants to have
children with me.
Resolution.
- He's on a spectrum, isn't he?
I had a cousin once who used
to say the gnarliest shit.
Man, no judgment.
- 250,000 records?
- I know.
- That's huge.
- Yeah.
- What is that even like?
- Do you still love him?
- I mean, he's on
another planet tonight.
But...
I'm not the easiest person
to live with either,
I mean, I'm...
It was just really nice to
have someone to come home to.
What is happening?
Sadie, why is that?
You are not a lesbian.
What is going on?
- Come on, Jo, everyone
is a lesbian sometimes!
Look, Bryce is an asshole.
And you, you, you're just this,
this smart, talented woman
and you deserve to be loved.
Where's your sense of adventure?
Look, it is New Years.
And Jude, Jude would
be right into it.
You could move in with us.
- No, Sadie, no.
Okay, Sadie.
Stop it!
- Nobody love me.
- Oh, babe, no.
- Nobody.
I mean they all think I'm
fuckable, I'm good to look at.
Even Jude, even Jude
will leave eventually.
- No.
- You don't understand.
This business is brutal.
I spent $200
yesterday on a cream
to brighten my arms.
No seriously, bright arms is
a job requirement for me.
You, you are just this
artist spreading truth.
Truth, you know, and beauty.
I just, I just, I
just idolize you, Jo.
And I'm gonna die
shriveled and alone.
- You are not going
to die alone!
Now, look at me.
Remember, Vanessa's
invited us all to live
on her survivalist
eco-commune in Canada?
It might be cold all the
time and have to churn
your own butter but...
- I'm a terrible friend.
- I'm terrible.
- Stop.
Vanessa's not gonna let
me into her commune.
- Babe, what are
you talking about?
- I don't wanna talk about it.
- Sadie.
Sadie.
What?
- My agency dropped her script.
- Oh.
- Because my agent's...
My agent dropped me.
You know, I wasn't booking.
And so I went in to visit him.
And he said that maybe
now was a good time
to start writing a cookbook.
- Oh, Jesus.
- I mean my manager's
trying to find me something
but he says that age
might be a factor.
- I want to carpetbomb
your industry.
- No, I am a good actor.
I'm a really good actor
when I work hard.
And Nessa's script
is really good.
And she's so very
fucking talented,
and I can't, I can't help her!
And I can't help you and I just,
I just wanna die.
♪ And the girl with
the strawberry hair
♪ Is like an angel in despair
♪ She teased me with her eyes
♪ When I'm touching
up on her thighs
♪ What would she want with me
♪ I'm just a dude
who loves the sea
♪ But if she really wanna fly
♪ She gotta be really high
- Maybe this is a gift
from the Universe.
Jude and I will have a baby.
Or I'll write that
cookbook for actresses
struggling with food
allergies, you know,
and maybe I just need to,
I just need to dig deeper
and live in the moment
and really embrace
the beauty that is this
experience, you know,
and just remember that
we're all just actors on the
stage of life, you know?
Yeah.
- Are you better?
How much of that was
acting, like, 40%?
- You're the worst.
- Oh, you're a nerd!
Oh.
- Oh my god!
Vanessa's pregnant! - Shh, shh.
- Oh my god, Vanessa's pregnant!
What are we gonna do?
We should start saving!
- We're gonna play a game,
we're gonna play a game.
We're gonna yell so loud so
that the whole house hears us.
- Oh my god.
Wait, how much did
she have to drink?
You can have muskal
when you're pregnant?
- No, don't ever
ever ever have kids.
- What? Why?
I'm like, really good...
She just tries to spit out
half of what she drinks.
With the pudding
and the Sigma Nus.
- So that maybe we
should do is...
- So what we're gonna do
is just march out there
like we don't know anything
and you never
sexually-assaulted me,
and nothing ever happened.
- No, wait a minute...
- Nothing.
♪ And that's why I'll behave
♪ Always gonna be her slave
♪ And we'll kiss forever after
♪ Because her bondage
is my master ♪
- Wow!
- Who is buying that?
- Germans.
- Totally.
- You guys really like it?
I messed it up a little bit.
- Nah!
Yeah.
- I fucked it up a little bit.
- It's really beautifully felt.
- Aw.
- Really was.
- Thanks, guys.
I mean, when you
find your muse...
- We should down to
the theater sometime.
We could do like a night of
music and spoken word, you know.
Yeah, yeah, like we
do this fundraiser,
I'd pay you a stipend.
- Be careful, Jude,
you gotta be careful,
because it starts
there and then it's
come to all my shows
and donate money.
And wait.
Wait, wait.
Wait for it.
We got eight inspirational
quote tweets in two hours.
- Come on!
- You know what
this reminds me of?
This is like legit
deja-vu right now.
Spring semester, senior year.
- No, no!
- Yes, he has to know!
He must know the tale! - God.
Jude, Jude, check it out.
- Yeah.
Okay, so Steven was making
us crazy for months
workshopping his thesis
performance, his opus.
I'd gone through six, maybe
seven costume designs.
You used to do costume
designs, right?
- And he still wears them!
- Yeah, but he was
really good at them.
He was.
- Sadie had gone through
six or seven hair colors,
Vanessa had done like
a million drafts,
and Steven, in his
infinite wisdom,
decides to cast Tyler Darrington
in the lead role.
- Tyler like Blues
Village Blues Tyler,
with Faith Darrington's kid?
- That's Tyler Darrington.
- And Tyler wasn't a star
yet, but with that family,
it was just a matter of time.
Well, Steven knew that
if Tyler was in it,
his family would come see it,
so we begged and we begged...
- No, no, you didn't!
- Steven not to do
it because, you see,
aside from being
relatively talent-free,
Tyler was, how do I
put this gently,
a shitstain of a human being.
- He could be really nice.
- Didn't you sleep with him?
- No, that's my sister.
- He would only agree
to do it if the performance
was during the finals week,
what with the family
cruise of Greek Isles
coming up and everything.
So Steven knew that
this was gonna be
pretty hard on us
but he persevered.
And you know why?
It's 'cause he had a vision.
He did.
He had a vision of the
brilliant production
that we would mount,
and of how the Darringtons
would surely,
like modern-day Medicis,
become our patrons and
shower us in so much money
that we'd be doing art!
With goddamn capital A!
Forever and ever, amen.
And Tyler was terrible.
He showed up to rehearsal
baked out of his gourd
every day, and for
weeks, none of us slept.
Sadie's hair fell out,
Vanessa developed
a bleeding ulcer,
but Steven was undeterred.
He was convinced.
He was convinced that
if he could just
teach Tyler to learn his lines,
and be a decent human being,
and not do all the
blow in the world,
that everything would
turn out fine in the end.
- Did it?
- Fucker never showed up.
Steven read his lines
from a binder.
Vanessa lost her grant.
And my father
nearly disowned me.
- Oh he did not.
The department asked
him to write a paper
and I helped, it was fine.
- Was it fine?
Because I remember that
that it was abject misery
but, fuck it, you know what?
Let's do it again.
Let's see how far up Jude's
ass your nose can go.
I'll come out of retirement
and do the costumes
for old time's sake.
What do you say, guys?
To starfuckers!
- Man, what the fuck
is your problem?
- What the fuck is my problem?
I don't have a problem.
What the fuck is your problem?
Yes, you pick and you
pick and you pick.
Do you think I like
busting my balls
20 hours a day to
keep this thing...
- Honestly, I don't know.
- No, you wouldn't know.
Do you know why you
wouldn't know?
Because you sold
out to take a job
at your daddy's
accounting firm, right?
Who's your biggest client now?
Is it Pornopalooza?
Or, no, no, sorry,
it's that chain
of dry cleaners downtown, right?
Either way, really
great contribution
to society there,
buddy, seriously.
- Fuck you, man, I am so
sick of your bullshit.
- Bryce.
- No, it is bullshit!
You think that you are so much
better than the rest of us.
You're so goddamned high and
mighty with your thee-ay-tah
that you shove down
our fucking throats.
And guess what,
newsflash, no one cares.
We all have to
pretend like we do,
and like we think it's
worth all the trouble
for you to raise
$70,000 by Tuesday
or God forbid Van Nuys
will have one less
black box production
of King Lear.
- Fuck off.
- Well, it's true.
- You think I don't know that?
Huh?
You think I like having
to beg my friends
to come and see our shows?
You think I like being
the harrassing-est
Whitman-quotingest
motherfucker alive?
What's the alternative,
buddy, huh?
Let another art form die,
let it just fade away into
some sort of oblivion?
If we were in any other
industrialized fucking country,
we were in any other
industrialized country right now,
I just don't even have the
time and the patience
to get into that.
I just, I just...
I just wanna run a food truck.
I just wanna run a food truck
like every other fucker in L.A.
And just drive around when
I want and where I want
and have my biggest
fucking problem be
that I smell like fucking
pot pies when I come home.
Fuck!
- Wait, Vanessa,
you're pregnant!
We found the pregnancy test.
- You're pregnant?
That's why you wanna
talk to your folks.
- Okay.
- It's because you're
pregnant, no that's cool.
That's great, no
that is awesome!
- Thank you very much, Sadie.
You are best.
Steven!
Steven.
- I don't wanna talk to
you right now, Vanessa.
- Okay, can we just...
- I am killing myself,
killing myself
to keep this thing
afloat and I am sorry
if that makes me a
terrible husband
and holy fuck, a
terrible father.
- Okay, okay.
But to keep this from me,
And what was all that shit at
dinner about overpopulation?
Were you planning some sort
of abortion or something?
Why wouldn't you just come to
me and talk to me about it?
- I am not pregnant!
You think you're the
only miserable one?
I have written 12
award-winning plays
and I have made more money
in one summer walking dogs
I teach Don Quixote to angsty
teenagers all day long
and then I come home to more
work and a husband who is
too tired to touch me!
And no, I'm not pregnant.
I took a test
because I was late,
and it scared the
living shit out of me,
because we have no money
and no time and no energy
for anything else
but this theater!
- Oh okay, you wanna quit?
Go ahead.
Oh oh oh, great! Oh great,
great, and do what?!
- I don't know care!
- And do what?!
- I'm not trained to
do anything but this!
- Sell jewelry on the
Santa Monica pier!
- Jewelry, are you
fucking kidding?
Why don't we just become mines!
Huh? Why don't we just.
I've always wanted to
be a train conductor,
I mean, maybe I'll get
a job at Disney Land!
No no no, I got it, I got it.
Why don't we come up with the
next fucking juice cleanse
'cause I think there's a
real fucking opportunity
for that right now...
- Why don't we, Steven?
Why don't we?
- You don't get to make this
decision for the two of us,
okay?
We went into this together.
This is a partnership,
so that's why!
- When was the last time
we ate dinner together?
Or took a walk?
Or slept a full night
without panic flailing!?
- 10 years, 10 years!
We've been in this for 10 years!
You can't just walk
away from that,
it's 10 years of our life!
- Walkin' away!
- Oh.
Oh that's, that's, that's...
That's great! - Here I go!
- Yeah? Yeah, me too!
- Great!
- Fuck this!
I'm out!
See you later!
- Fine!
- Oh, guess what?
Sadie has agreed...
to do a commercial.
- What?
For the firm?
- Yeah.
- It's so sweet of you
to help your friends
with all of their
little projects.
You're such a generous soul.
- Yeah, when she told me she
was having money trouble,
I just thought why not trade?
I'm sure she's not the only
person with tax issues.
Some of her fans are a mess
too, so, it's a no-brainer.
- That's great.
- Sadie?
Open the door.
Sades.
Sadie.
What the fuck?
- Help me in the kitchen.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I was...
I don't know, it was
humiliating, I was in
I was afraid.
- Afraid of what?
- That you'd leave me.
- Why would I leave you?
- Because...
Because I'm like this freak.
I'm like this...
I'm like this little
performing monkey that's like
loose and unemployed
in the streets
and everybody know who I
am and they're all like,
"Oh, look at that little
poor, dancing monkey.
"Isn't it time she
writes a cookbook?"
And I'm like "No,
no I still have it.
"I promise, look
look, I can dance!"
And they're like "Mm, actually,
"your agent has a younger,
sexier monkey now
"and come to think of
it, we like her more."
- Is it because I
called you monkey face?
I didn't mean that, my gam
gam used to call me...
- I'm trying to tell
you that I am failing.
I'm a failure.
And I'm stuck.
And my money, all the
savings are all gone.
I have all the money.
I mean like, I have
all the money!
You're such a little dummy.
Why didn't you come to me?
- None of this is
going how I planned.
None of it.
- They didn't like your poem.
- Well that's reductive.
- They don't teach
you about this.
Soul-crushing...
disappointment.
- Let's just skip
the disappointment.
I'm tired, skip it.
- No, we can do better.
Right? We can do better.
We'll sell the car, we'll um...
Can talk to your parents,
I'm okay with that.
I just don't think we could...
- No.
- But there's gotta be trust.
It's a spiritual,
spiritual experience
and it can't be taken
lightly but...
Do you trust me?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
I do.
- I think we made
a huge mistake.
- At least the food was awesome.
- I crushed that roast.
- You really did
crush the roast.
- So...
Mime.
You want to mime? - Oh, come on.
You're not gonna let me
live that one down, huh?
That's the one you're
gonna stick with, okay.
It's cool, it's great.
We're in a lot of trouble.
- We're gonna be okay.
- I've never...
had anyone be so
honest with me before.
- Oh honey, it feels so good.
- It feels so good.
- Oh, god, I wanna always
be that honest with you.
- Yeah?
- Always.
- Forever?
- Let's just tell each
other everything.
- Everything.
- No secrets.
No secrets, oh, ah can
I tell you a secret?
Yeah I wanna do it.
- Clean slate.
- Totally.
- Square from this day...
- I can be square.
- Okay I'm gonna tell you
the deepest secret I have.
- I'm gonna tell you one.
- What?
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Deepest-darkest secrets.
- Deepest-Darkest secrets.
- Together?
- Together, together, together.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- You're sure?
- Yes.
Yes.
Yeah. - Okay.
- Okay, on the count of three.
Ready?
- One.
Two.
Three.
- In love with anyone.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
Oh honey, I love you so much.
I love you so much, I just don't
love your music, you know?
- You're the worst.
- Wait, what?
What? - You're the worst.
- Wait, I thought we
were being square?
You said deepest-darkest secret.
- Oh my, what!
- Baby, baby!
- What's happening?
What's happening?
- I'm an artist, Sadie!
- Oh no no no no.
- What the fuck?
- I love you.
I love you! - Whoa!
Are you tryin' to kill me?
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
- We can work around it!
- Oh we can work around it.
We can work around it!
- Listen listen.
- Honey, if were an
accountant, would you like,
expect me to love math?
No!
No, right?
But what if, what if, what if,
what if you were a
baker, you know?
Because I'm allergic
to bread, you know!
- But you're not not saying
you don't love music.
You're saying you
don't love my music!
Like, like hey Mr. Baker-man,
I love bread, but your bread
tastes like shit, right!
- No that's not what I mean.
- But that's what you're saying,
that's what you're saying.
Honey, no.
- Okay, okay so, so...
- That's not what I'm saying.
- Okay so I'm gonna go!
I have to go now.
- Don't go, don't go.
- Because you just took
a huge
wet
dookie in my soul,
and I have to relocate
my happiness. - No!
- Somewhere else.
- No!
- Okay?
- Away, away.
- Please don't.
- Yeah.
- Please.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- No.
No.
And you love me, and that,
that can be enough.
For a while, right?
Look, you wanna do the
journalism thing?
That is fine, that is
fine, I was subsidize it,
and you can get it
out of your system.
That's not what I, um.
Journalism is dying, it is
dying and I will sit shiva
with you while it
dies and then maybe
you can do this for me.
Relationships are
about sacrifice.
Jodie, please.
I don't work without you.
Did Sadie spray you
with her perfume?
Um, let's talk in the morning.
Okay.
We'll talk in the morning.
- Fuck!
- This is so much fun.
- I'm not pregnant!
- You know, I think the whole
forest is clear on that, babe.
- I just need my pants.
Pants.
All good.
This is, it's really
nice out tonight, huh?
- Gorgeous.
- Really.
- Really beautiful.
- And there's a
really great moon.
- Mm-hm, the big
dipper I think is out.
- No I'm good, I'm good.
You guys have a great...
New.
Bye.
- I am naked in public!
- Well, I think your bra,
may have run away, darling.
Purple.
Should we see if he has
any weed in here, oh.
- I am free-boobin' it.
- Oh that's it.
Darling.
We should go back inside, right?
- Try me, I'm posh.
Think he's lookin' for that.
- But I thought it'd be funny.
- Think there's one
in the kitchen?
- Hey.
- I'm goin' home.
Yeah, I don't need this shit.
You know?
I can't find my keys!
Oh, she hates my music.
Oh yeah, well, well boning
a vampire on national
television's total
capital A art!
Oh.
Oh, god.
God.
I can handle it from my mom.
From my brother, you know.
'Cause they're just,
they're just jealous.
They're a-holes.
But from Sadie?
Oh, Sadie.
- It's okay, buddy.
- Oh, I know!
- Nope, it's okay.
- Oh yeah, think I'm dying.
I'm gonna die!
Oh my god I can't breathe,
oh my god I can't,
there's a big fat guy, I swear
to god there's a fat guy,
and he's sitting on my
chest, he's just dooking.
- Sadie?
Sadie.
Honey, if you keep doing that,
your teeth are gonna rot
and then who will want you?
Sadie!
Stop it.
- He just chucks this
chicken over the fence.
Oh god.
And now I feel responsible.
I don't know what else to do
but just tuck it into my arm
like a football and
just run, you know?
- Yeah, that thing took it
like a champ, I tell you what.
- And now the PETA
office has a new mascot?
- Uh-Huh.
Yep.
They named it Jodie.
- Oh, exceptional.
- Yeah, it was.
It really was.
- Oh no, no!
Is this downer-weed?
No!
- No.
Darling.
The human condition
is the downer.
I'm a downer.
The world...
is a downer.
- You're saving the world.
You have to save the
world, I want you to.
Take your important pictures
and save the world.
- Why don't you save the world?
I'm tired.
I made $11,000 last year.
I don't know, maybe I should
have a kid with Bryce.
I could just...
buy all the things, become a
functioning alcoholic and,
you could save the world.
I mean, somebody has to
speak for the trees and the
children and the bees and
the ozone layer and...
I'm so tired.
Maybe I'll open an Olan Mills.
- Are you having a
nervous breakdown?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I think I am.
- What's happening in here?
- I'm floating in a
field of love...
and acceptance.
- And forgiveness.
Man, you should charge
money for this, Steven.
Lots and lots of money.
- Sadie.
- Are you stoned right now?
- Sadie, come out,
we're floating
in a field of love
and forgiveness
and acceptance.
- Have pie with us.
- I have a little bit
of food poisoning.
- Oh, baby.
Well honey, if you keep doing
that, your teeth will fall out
and then, how are you
gonna have Nessa's pie?
Or mine, or anyone's?
- No judgement tonight, Sadie.
Nothing but love,
acceptance,
forgiveness.
- Pie.
I want pie. - Mm-hm.
- Yeah.
- Well this feels like a
night for announcements.
We're closing the theater.
- What?
- Yeah.
It's time.
- Wait, what are
you guys gonna do?
- We don't know.
Declare bankruptcy, probably.
Make a bunch of movies with you.
Go to mime school.
- Open a food truck.
- Really?
- I'm just kidding.
- Well that's good, man,
because food trucks are like
so five minutes ago, seriously,
it's not a good idea.
- Do you have to kill every
moment of happiness?
You ass-hat!
- Whoa.
- Whoa?
Whoa?
- Hey, get away from
me, you psychopath!
- Yeah?
- Stop it, Steven.
- Is this happening?
- Stop!
- You've been living a lie.
If you don't my music, then
what is it you love about me,
- What are you gonna do
when you catch me, Steven,
inspire me to death?! - Baby.
- No, stop!
I can't believe anything
that comes out of that lying
mouth of yours!
Do your friends even know
that your agent dropped you?
Like some little old, fat chick,
that you've just been
spewing lies like some
lying, lying lie-cano!?
- Wait, wait wait wait.
Is the script dead?
- You knew.
That is some cold shit.
- Oh, god!
- And I am not fat!
- Because you never
digest anything.
- Baby!
Baby? - Ah, don't.
Don't touch me, don't touch me!
Ever, don't touch me.
- I know you're all
tapped out and everything
- If you could just refrain from
shitting all over my dreams
for like a second,
that'd be nice!
- What, is that what
Steven said to you
- Is that what Bryce said
to you, when you made him
choose between having him
and having a child?!
- Oh, that is a low-blow.
- Oh yeah, well your
mom's a low-blow.
- If you hate everything
I do so much, why,
why are you even here?
- Oh no, no.
Shit!
These are Japanese
Selvedge denim!
Christ.
- Come on, man.
- Run, motherfucker.
- No, what the fuck!
- Would you just listen to me?
Look, yes, yes I lied.
And no, I don't love your
music, but I love your passion!
How much you try!
You're not always gonna
love the work that I do
but that doesn't make
you love me any less
and I know that you love
me because you wouldn't
be this pissed right
now if you didn't.
- And that's why I behave!
- Sweetie, sweetie...
- Always gonna!
- Shh.
- Wait.
You hate that song too.
- It could be tweaked.
- I wrote that song for you!
Oh, motherfucker!
God!
Pie.
- No, Vanessa!
Honey, you know I love you but
you cannot change the world
with a studio comedy! - Oh yeah?
What changes the world?
Miss Artiste, tell me,
with your infinite wisdom!
- Greed!
Greed, greed changes the world.
And, and, and corporations
buying elections,
and Halliburton he changes the
world, you know, Dick Cheney,
that guy?
- You know what your problem is?
It's that you operate under
the illusion that this
starving artist routine
is somehow noble,
when what it really is,
is just an excuse not
to grow the fuck up.
You wanna know what's noble?
Providing your wife
with health insurance!
- Is that what it means, huh?
Sellin' out and takin' a job
that sucks the life out of you
until you're nothin' but a
dried-up husk of regret
and ball cancer?
- You know who does?
Religious zealots
that feed people,
you know, make
change in the world!
And, and, Cultural Hegemony!
- You know what I really think?
I think you just can't stand it.
You can't stand that you were
this big star in college,
and now you're a total failure
and I have a sailboat.
- Do you wanna go there?
Who was it that was too
afraid to even try, huh?
Too scared that his
dad would disown him
if he went to design school.
Yeah, my theater failed, but
we had a great fucking run.
I have a great fucking wife,
and I have integrity.
But $100 haircut, some
stupid suspenders
and a closeted sewing fetish.
- Fuck! God-damnit.
- Stories change
the world, Jodie.
I know you're really depressed,
and I don't know how you're
gonna pay your student loans...
but you just need to tell
yourself a different story.
We just need a different story.
- Why.
Why I behave.
♪ Always gonna be a slave
Whoa, that is brilliant!
♪ Forever after
♪ Because her bondage
is my master ♪
Oh my god.
Oh, that's really good.
♪ And that's why I behave
♪ Always gonna be a slave
- Shit.
- Hi.
You've looked better.
- So have you, your eye!
- Yeah.
I got beat up by a
hipster accountant.
Oh, easy.
Okay.
Want some coffee? - Hm-hm.
- Did you fall
asleep under a tree?
- Shut up.
- I'm all...
- Shh.
- Where is everyone?
- God, look at her go.
- She's a better person
than either of us.
- Are you laughing at me?
- No, we're laughing
with you, Sadie.
Come and get your coffee.
- Is it...
- Almond milk.
What, I'm gonna give you dairy?
I'm not a masochist.
- You're not mad?
- No, I'm not mad.
I do however think you
are incredibly lame.
- Oh, good.
I thought that maybe
you had little people,
like, like little Keebler elves,
who are like...
maybe like, the neighbors saw
me and they tweeted a picture
of me and then they felt bad
about it so they came back
and gave me coffee.
- It was Vanessa.
- That's more pliable.
- Plausible.
- Whatever.
Hey, Steven. - Hm?
- Do you think my music...
- Should we say something?
- We forgot.
You got something in your hair.
- Yeah.
I do.
- Are we gonna be okay?
Are we all gonna be okay?
- None of us gets out
of here alive, babe.
- He's just sitting in there.
- We used to really make sense.
- It won't start.
♪ In the pale blue sky
♪ I see you
♪ And when it starts to rain
♪ You can walk away my pain
♪ In the pale blue sky
♪ I see you
- Thanks.
Well, I better get goin'
while it's runnin'.
Do you wanna get Jodie for me?
- She's gonna stay with
us for a couple of days.
- I'll see you around, Steven.
- Hey, thanks for comin', guys.
- Yeah, man.
Thanks for havin' us.
It was really, it was
really somethin'.
- That's awesome.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- Oh hey, Steven?
Were you serious about
the food truck idea?
I don't know.
- Well, if you are,
please let me know.
I'd really like to fund it.
- Okay.
Uh, thank you.
- Cool.
Yeah, very cool.
- That's...
What just happened?
- The food truck, but
not the theater?
- I like pie.
♪ You leave in the morning
♪ You come home at night
♪ Nobody wants your heart
♪ 'Cause it's not broken
♪ It's three hours there
♪ It's eight hours back
♪ Do you wish that
you could cry hard
♪ 'Cause this is
your pleasure cruise
♪ This is your red carpet
♪ I, I, I, I
♪ I'm not giving up
♪ When every single
voice in my head
♪ Is saying enough's enough
♪ Oh, I think it's
the first time
♪ They've agreed over anything
♪ We tried to move the left hand
♪ The right hand hurts so bad
♪ That's before you
had a couple of kids
♪ Before you even had
a reason to be mad
♪ And you're tryin'
to fill the dead air
♪ What do you have to say
♪ Everybody is talkin' it out
♪ All night and all day
♪ Do you wish it
would all go away
♪ I, I, I, I
♪ I'm not giving up
♪ When the big old
moon looks down
♪ And tells me enough's enough
♪ Oh, I think it's
the first time
♪ They've talked to
me about anything
♪ I think it's the first time
♪ They've said anything at all
♪ But 'til now they
never seemed to care
♪ One way or another
♪ And now they're talkin'
and they're talkin'
♪ And oh, they won't
leave me alone
♪ I, I, I, I
♪ I'm not giving up
♪ When every single
voice in my head
♪ Is saying enough's enough
♪ Oh, I think it's
the first time
♪ They've talked to
me about anything
♪ I think it's the first time
♪ They've said anything at all