Everybody Loves Hypnotoad
was filmed thousands of miles
below a live studio audience.
Everybody Loves Hypnotoad
will return after these messages.
is brought to you by
Garry's All Purpose Music.
When you must listen to music,
make it Garry's.
Calorie Substance.
Recommended by: Hypnotoad.
Guests of Hypnotoad stay at the
historic Cragmont Human Cage
where they are forced to fight
for his amusement.
Everybody Loves Hypnotoad.
Season One.
Now available on DVD.
You get all 365 episodes.
Plus never before seen footage.
Commentaries from the writers
and director.
All glory to the Hypnotoad.
And: hilarious outtakes!
Cut!
May cause internal bleeding.
Tonight at 11,
a sneak peek at Hypnotoad's
heart-pounding new medical drama,
Diagnosis Hypnosis.
On the count of 50,
you will awaken
feeling refreshed
and remembering nothing.
One, two, three, four...
five, six, seven, eight...
nine, ten, eleven, twelve...
thirteen, fourteen,
fifteen, sixteen...
fourteen...
I... I'm sorry.
I'll have to start again.
One, two, three, four...
five, six, seven, eight...
nine, ten, eleven, twelve...
thirteen, fourteen,
fifteen, sixteen...
seventeen, eighteen,
nineteen, twenty...
twenty-one, twenty-two,
twenty-three, twenty-four...
twenty-five, twenty-six,
twenty-seven, twenty-eight...
twenty-nine, thirty,
thirty-one, thirty-two...
thirty-three, thirty-four,
thirty-five, thirty-six...
thirty-seven, thirty-eight,
thirty-nine, forty...
forty-one, forty-two,
forty-three, forty-four...
forty-five, forty-six,
forty-seven, forty-eight...
forty-nine, fifty.
Next time on
Everybody Loves Hypnotoad: