[Music playing]
PETE: Nora?
What's wrong?
NORA: I'm just worried
about my parents.
PETE: You really shouldn't
worry about your parents.
It happens to everybody.
NORA: I know.
I'm being... I'm
being such a dope.
You know.
I mean, you have it worse
with your parents, you know,
Being gone, and all.
But hey, I didn't
mean it, you know?
No, it's all right,
it's all right.
I'm over it. It happened
a long time ago.
Yeah.
Anyway, why don't we get out of
this car, take a little walk?
Yeah.
Get more comfortable.
OK.
Sound good?
Let's go.
Look at that moon.
It's full.
My god.
It's really pretty.
Look how it shines
on your necklace.
Yeah.
Wait... don't.
What?
It's Valentine's Day.
Come on, Nora.
But... it's... it's
all nasty out here.
Come on.
We'll take a shower
when we're done.
No.
Hey... stop.
What?
I'm not ready yet.
Come on.
Let's take a walk.
We took a walk.
We walked from the car to here.
[Inaudible].
Oh, Nora, come on.
Don't play games.
Nora, come back.
Why does this have to happen?
Nora?
Come on.
OK, I'll be good.
I promise!
I'm not coming in
there after you.
Don't hide.
You can't play hide
and seek alone.
Nora!
OK, Nora.
Nora?
OK, I'm getting angry.
I swear I'll be good.
Just come back.
Nora, where are you?
Come on, this isn't funny.
Don't hide.
I'm not playing this game.
Nora?
Can you hear me?
Come on!
There's snakes out there.
It's dangerous.
OK, I'm gonna get
a bird's-eye view.
I'll find you.
Nora!
I see you.
Yeah, that's right.
Don't hide under that rock.
I see you.
Come here.
All right, I'm coming after you.
Here I come... agh!
Oh, shit.
All right, I'm here.
Hey.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Pete.
Come on.
All right.
I'm here.
Pete, come on.
It's not funny.
You don't fool my.
Come on, get up.
Come on.
Hey.
Pete?
Oh my god.
Pete.
What did you do?
Help!
RADIO: This is
KSTN college radio.
It's 9:37 on a beautiful
Valentine's evening,
And I am stuck here
without an [inaudible].
[Beeping]
Damn it!
Oh, shit.
Please, please.
Come on.
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
I need an ambulance,
somewhere out on...
[Static]
What?
Who is this?
NORA (ON PHONE): My name?
Nora Breckenridge.
I said I need an ambulance!
You're Nora who?
Why do you need
to know my name?
It's Breckenridge.
I... I said I need an ambulance.
You need an ambulance?
Where are you?
NORA (ON PHONE): I said I'm
out here on Olden Canyon Road.
Is there someone else
I can talk to, lady?
This is urgent.
There's nobody
here but me, miss.
I think you've got
the wrong number.
Shit!
I'm glad you're here.
My boyfriend is passed
out up the road,
And I need some help
to get him in the car
So I can take him
to the hospital.
Can you help me?
[Inaudible].
Please?
I mean, there's blood and
everything everywhere.
I didn't... I didn't even
see what happened and stuff.
I mean, I... I... I wish I
wasn't so mean and everything.
Calm down.
I don't even know
you and everything.
I mean, you're helping me, and
it's... it's so nice of you.
Hey, why are we back
here by this... your car?
There's some things
we might need here.
Like what?
Like you.
Ugh... shit.
Nora?
[Beeping]
Fuckin' [inaudible].
Nora?
Oh, great!
Where's my car?
Where is my car?
Nora, bring my car back!
No problem.
[Coins falling]
Nora!
Nora?
[Inaudible]
Where's my car?
Yeah?
Do I not do everything
you ask me to?
Do I not do a clean job?
PETE: Nora?
I don't believe this!
[Inaudible]
A nice, romantic
walk... by myself,
Through the fucking woods.
This is great.
Nora!
[Trickling]
Nora?
Oh, that's great, Nora.
There it is.
You leave the car
all by itself...
You know what this thing
means to me. [Inaudible]
Don't know how to
treat a vehicle.
Man.
Nora!
Oh, I'm gonna kill you.
What the hell... Nora?
Nora?
Nora!
[Music playing]
[Cars honking]
RADIO ANNOUNCER: It's going
to be a hot one today, folks.
It's gonna top out 97
in the civic center.
Smoke level's are still high.
In other metro news,
the bloody teen pack
That inspired the
tale of Dracula
Has been the victim
of bad press.
Research shows
that most of the...
[Honking]
Fuck you, too.
RADIO ANNOUNCER: It's been a
week since the disappearance
Of [inaudible].
Police are still holding one
suspect, a 17-year-old youth.
The name of the suspect is
being withheld by the police
Because he's a minor.
Also, in today's
news, filmmakers
Are talking about the hottest
new movie, [inaudible].
[Music playing]
WILL SPANNER (VOICEOVER): It's
been three years since I was
Last forced to use my powers.
It's a lot like
being on the wagon.
People will try to tempt
you into doing anything
When they know you've
got the [inaudible].
Anyway, things are good now.
And I've given up looking
for the perfect life.
Just doesn't come naturally
when you're a warlock.
[Knocking]
WILL SPANNER: Yeah, come in.
William Spanner?
WILL SPANNER: Yeah.
Come have a seat.
I'd offer you some coffee, but
my secretary quit last week,
And, uh... what'd you
say your name was?
Lily Wild.
Hi.
My brother's in big trouble.
He's been arrested, and
they're accusing him of murder.
What's his name?
What'd he do?
It's been on the news and
it's been in the papers.
His name's Peter Wild.
He's only 17 years old.
He went out with a girl and she
disappeared, about a week ago.
And the police
think he killed her.
Well, don't you have
a public defender?
He didn't care.
About my brother, I mean.
The secretary at city hall
highly recommended you.
I gave up public
defending years ago.
I really need your help.
I have nowhere else to turn.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I... you know, I have a
private practice now,
And I just handle
insurance cases.
Please.
Look, I can... I can refer
you to some other people
Far better qualified than
I to do this for you.
I don't have that much
money, Mr. Spanner.
I work in a bookstore.
I hardly make the rent
or the car payments.
I don't even have a car
now, because they're
Holding it as evidence.
I need your help.
All right, listen.
I've heard of the case.
I'll... I'll look into it
first thing in the morning.
OK.
Who's the officer in
charge of the case?
Lieutenant Hovis.
Well, it doesn't look good.
We traced the call
from the phone booth
To this old lady
who said she got
A call from someone named Nora.
When our guys got there, all
they found was Pete Wild.
It still doesn't sound like
you've got anything on the kid.
LT. HOVIS: Well, he busted up
the phone booth pretty good,
Not to mention he was
the only person out there
In the middle of nowhere.
Look, we found her
blood type on the phone,
He had a bruise on his head, so
obviously there was a struggle
And she hit him and boom, boom.
I mean, he's our guy.
So where's the body?
Ah, he must have gotten
scared and dumped it off
In the desert.
We're still looking for it.
Listen, the kid's
prints were all around.
WILL SPANNER: Oh,
that's ridiculous.
Why would he kill
her and then dump
The body somewhere and then
go back to scene of the crime?
He was hysterical.
Who knows?
The girl's purse was
found in his possession.
So what?
He's her boyfriend.
I mean, the deposition
that the old lady took
Stated that she was
hard of hearing, right?
Isn't it possible
that she could have
Misunderstood what Nora said?
LT. HOVIS: Hey, she heard
well enough to get the girl's
Name right, and the location.
You don't have a case.
Until you come up with
the body, all this is
Purely circumstantial evidence.
Look, I'm gonna tell you
this, just so that you know.
I don't want you
to think that this
Is some kind of boy-girl
teeny-bopper argument
We got here.
We're linking this guy
Pete to a whole shitload
Of serial killings.
WILL SPANNER: What
serial killings?
Come on.
We've been finding bodies
out in the desert for years.
I think we got six in all.
Really gruesome stuff.
Oh, come on.
You can't possibly expect
me or anyone else to believe
That a 17-year-old boy...
Yes I can, and I do!
I mean, was it
coincidence that she
Disappeared in the same area?
No.
Right now Pete Wild
is our best suspect.
And let me tell you
something... he is a weird kid.
He keeps taking his
sister's car, right?
Without asking her.
So I ask him where he goes.
He says he doesn't know.
And I don't think I have
to tell you that, uh...
There are certain
aspects of this
Investigation that cannot...
And I mean cannot...
Be leaked to the press.
If by chance this
Wild boy is innocent
And this killer's signature
gets out... I'll bet you 10 to 1
We have a whole string
of copycat killings.
Oh, this is the biggest
bunch of horseshit
I've ever heard in my life.
And I'm not gonna let you
guys get away with this.
Tell you what, if you try
to take this thing to court,
I am gonna nail your
ass to the wall.
Goodbye.
Those are nice chairs.
My mother had the same kind.
She's a witch.
Now, Lily, I've talked to Pete.
He's pretty reluctant
to say anything.
How is he?
I mean, OK, considering
he's in jail.
Can you help him?
Yeah, I think so.
I mean, I don't think
they have a case.
Well, when will he get out?
Well, they say
they want to hold
Him for his own protection.
The public's crazy
to get at him.
Someone's leaked
it to the press.
Oh, god.
How can they link my
brother to serial killing
When he hasn't ever
done anything wrong?
My guess is that
he's all they've got.
Anyway, as long
as they hold him,
The real killer would be
stupid to strike again.
So, as far as the
state is concerned,
This problem's
temporarily solved.
It buys them some time.
Great.
Meanwhile Pete's stuck.
We have to help him.
I will help him, Lily.
It's just not gonna be easy.
Hovis won't tell me
anything I need to know.
The DA won't release the files.
I'm gonna have to find
the killer myself.
Anyway, I just wish I
knew where to start.
I don't understand why he'd
bring his date out here.
So this is the
phone booth, huh?
Look.
What?
I found it over there.
Do you think it's a clue?
Oh, I doubt it.
The police would have found
it already, don't you think?
Maybe not.
But it's something.
Well, look at that.
LILY: What do you
think it means?
I don't know.
But I've heard of
the Coven before.
You have?
Yeah.
It's a club downtown.
[Music playing]
You need a jacket.
What?
OK.
MAN: I saw her, boss.
MAN: Fuck, what
are you, retarded?
You didn't see
nothing, all right?
MAN: I... I saw her.
The girl with the
long, black hair.
MAN: [inaudible].
She was gone before
you came back.
Got it?
MAN: Are you sure?
MAN: Fuck.
Yes!
What do I know?
Nothing.
You don't know a fucking
thing, all right?
Hey, want something?
Me?
Yeah.
You... you need a
drink or something?
No, thanks.
What's the matter, [inaudible]?
He's here to check out
the naked ladies, boss.
Yeah, that's right.
The naked ladies.
MAN: Oh, the naked ladies.
I see.
Yeah.
Who's going on tonight?
Boss, who's on tonight?
Maybe you are.
I'm gonna put a wig on you
and shave your ass and legs,
And then you can
do a strip tease.
How's that, buddy-boy?
That'd be good.
Hey, listen, do you guys
know what BD stands for?
BD.
That's big dicks, boss...
Shut the fuck up.
I don't know what that is.
You know what that is?
Ladies and gentlemen...
Well, gentlemen, that is.
Hey, I'd say it's a good
time for some disco.
That doesn't really
work here, I guess.
Tonight we have a
special show for you.
We're gonna present to
you the lovely Belladonna.
[Scattered applause]
What is she doing up?
Boss, what time is it?
Do I look like Big Ben?
Am I Swiss?
Am I ticking?
[Music playing]
It's time for you
to shut the fuck up,
That's what time it is.
She sure is
something, ain't she?
Oh, I sure wish I
could do like that.
You know, she's
like a real star.
A star?
[Inaudible].
Anyway, you want a drink?
No.
No, I'm good.
You gotta have something.
There's a [inaudible].
What?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Uh... vodka's fine.
Straight up?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's fine.
[Inaudible].
[Applause]
[Music playing]
Hi.
Can I help you?
Oh, I'm... I'm sorry.
I was... do you know
where the bathroom is?
Please come in.
Sit down.
That looks dangerous.
We all acquire a few
bad habits along the way.
Do you have any bad habits?
Listen, uh... I really need
to ask you a few questions.
Are you the police?
No, I'm a lawyer.
Oh, a lawyer.
Wow.
Let me tell you what I think.
I think that lawyers are the
lowest scum of the earth.
At least, that's
what I've heard.
Well, I'm sure there
are worse professions.
Sure.
You could be a bouncer.
Is he bothering you, BD?
- Bye.
- No, no.
No, wait a minute.
Do you know Nora Breckenridge?
She's a 16-year-old
girl who's disappeared.
Don't worry.
I used to disappear a
lot, too, when I was 16.
OK, I'm down!
Don't get me mad.
That guy's got my jacket.
What a dick.
Oh, the buzzer's broken.
Come.
I'm gonna be late for work.
Just relax.
Well, I appreciate
all your help.
It's no problem.
It's not out of the way.
I'm really worried about Pete.
I don't know how much
longer he can hang on.
We have to do something fast.
Well, I found out
some information.
I found out what BD means.
It's a woman.
The matchbook?
Is it gonna help the case?
I don't know.
Anyway, I'll tell
you what happened.
BD stands for a stripper
named Belladonna.
Really?
Yeah.
Anyway...
Was she pretty?
Who?
The stripper, stupid!
Oh, yeah.
Well... yeah, she was all right.
Anyway, listen.
So anyway, so I'm waiting for
her outside, and she comes out,
And she's kind of
sneaking around.
She gets on this
motorcycle and takes off.
And I followed her for a while.
And then I lost her.
What's so strange about that?
She's sneaking around
her own apartment!
Come on.
We've gotta go.
So what are we gonna do now?
Well, I'd kind of like
to get some pictures
Outside the Coven.
I'd like to get people
going in and out,
And I'd like to go see
what Belladonna's up to,
See if I can catch her
sneaking around again.
Well, if you want,
I'll take the pictures.
Well, I... I don't
think... are you sure you'd
Wanna do something like that?
Sure.
Whatever you want.
Hello, hello.
OK.
We'd like to bring a
lovely young lady out here.
And she's gonna
sing a song for you.
The great, the one
and only, Belladonna!
[Applause]
WILL SPANNER (VOICEOVER):
The inside of the matchbook
Said BD, 2 o'clock.
That's Belladonna at
the 2 O'clock club.
What does that have
to do with the Coven?
Why would she have to hide
from that stubby, wannabe
[Inaudible] thug
just to come here?
[Music playing]
(SINGING) Oh, oh, oh, oh well.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sugar, let me entice you
with my sweet perfume.
Uh-huh.
Couldn't keep my eyes
off you [inaudible]
As you walked through
the room, yeah.
Can you hear me crying?
Can you feel me dying?
Can you hear my crying?
[Inaudible]
Can't walk away, no, no.
You can't walk away.
[Applause]
Hey.
Hey, hey.
So you found me.
You have an incredible voice.
Thank you.
Can we talk?
Come on.
Not this again.
Listen, why do you... why
do you work as a stripper
If you've got a voice like that?
Don't you have a manager?
Yeah, I have a manager.
Sounds like you need a new one.
Hey, listen, I found these in a
phone booth out in the desert.
Regular, honey?
My number gets left in
lots of phone booths.
So what?
What is it that you
really want from me?
I'm working on a case
involving a 17-year-old boy who
Is in jail for a
murder he did commit,
And this is my only lead.
I'm really sorry about that,
but there's nothing I can do.
I think you're
involved in something.
I mean, why else would
you be sneaking out
Of your own apartment in
the middle of the night
To come sing in a blues club?
Whatever it is,
it's my problem, OK?
Come on.
Look... what's your name again?
Will.
Look, Will, you can
think whatever you want.
I'm not sticking
around this place.
If you can stop being a
detective for just one night,
Maybe you can come to my place.
Obviously you know
where I live already.
We can talk there,
and... see what happens.
Yeah, OK.
Let me get changed,
and I'll be right back.
Why don't you take
your jacket off?
Do you want to hear some music?
[Music playing]
Look... look, what I really need
tonight is some information.
At least you could tell me why
your name's on the matchbook.
Please, anything would help.
Because I'm at a dead end.
Don't worry about it.
Don't... don't worry about it?
Will, it's late.
Can't you think
about it tomorrow?
Come sit here.
Please?
I won't bite.
Come sit down.
Just for one night, Will, please
give in It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
[Knocking]
Oh my god.
Get in the closet.
Get in the closet, quick.
Why?
Who is it?
Don't come out.
Please don't come out.
He'll kill us.
Don't say a word. [Inaudible].
How are you?
Do you need anything?
No.
No?
You don't need anything?
Good.
I hope all is well.
Yes.
Yes what?
Everything is fine.
In the club?
The dancing?
You're happy with that?
Yes.
Why?
I wouldn't want you
to become unhappy.
You're not feeling
like singing again?
I would never do anything
you said I shouldn't do.
MAN: Really?
So you didn't do anything
like that tonight?
I don't know what you mean.
Oh, I wasn't clear?
I think I was fucking clear!
You must communicate.
You know those talks we had
about your career moves?
Those little tete-a-tetes?
I'm serious.
I know that you were.
How about men?
Have you seen any lately?
No.
MAN: No men?
Not ever?
None?
None walking down the street?
Seems odd.
There are plenty of men around.
I see them all the time.
I thought you meant...
What the fuck do
you think I meant?
Don't fuck around!
[Inaudible], I didn't!
You're hurting me.
Shut up!
You screw all the time,
and you lie to me.
[Inaudible]
Shut the fuck up!
Turn over.
I said fucking turn over!
[Scream]
Don't continue with these lies.
I gave you everything, and I can
take it all back in a minute.
Oh, shit.
Damn it.
Don't baby me.
I'm not a child.
Who was that?
That was my manager.
Right.
Your manager.
What kind of... what
the fuck are you doing?
Why don't you have him arrested?
Does this kind of shit
go on all the time?
I didn't see you
trying to help!
You probably liked
watching, didn't you?
You probably want
to fuck me too.
OK, tough guy.
Now's your chance.
Come on, do it!
Just forget it.
There's nothing
you can do, anyway.
What's that supposed to mean?
Look, I wanna help you.
But somebody has got to tell me
what the fuck is going on here.
There's nothing I can do.
He gave me everything.
My voice... I don't know!
Please just go.
But...
Get out!
Leave me alone!
I'm telling you,
I followed her four
Fucking times to this fucking
joint in the past three weeks.
So this is where
she's been hanging
Out, the lying little tart.
Yeah.
And that fucking
lawyer schmuck's
Been snooping around too.
You want I should whack him?
No.
He's being taken care of.
Well Jesus fucking Christ,
let me clip him, man.
I hate that fucking
tall-ass Texan
Drawl-talking
corn-eating fucking
Nelson-looking cow-humping
motherfucker, man!
Hal, Hal, Hal, Hal, Hal, Hal.
Such language from a man who's
so obviously well-educated.
Yeah, well, what
the fuck should I do?
Take care of BD.
She's the one that's
stepping out of line.
Fine.
Hey, man, I gotta clip somebody.
I'm getting out of
fucking practice, here.
If I ever needed a son, you're
obviously the man for the job.
Hal, you're heaven-sent.
WILL SPANNER
(VOICEOVER): No matter
What I do to get
away, eventually
The dreams come back.
But is it a dream?
Or have they found me again?
Jack comes out of the
barn with a watermelon.
A watermelon!
I mean...
Well, last night
was something else.
I'm surprised I didn't
get myself killed.
[Inaudible].
Well, great.
When'll they be ready?
You're lucky.
They're done.
I hope they're OK, or at
least what you wanted.
Remind you of somebody?
What?
So what did you
find out last night?
Well, a lot, and
nothing, really.
I followed her to
a club, this place
Called the 2 O'Clock club.
It's a blues club.
And, uh... she gets up on the
stage and starts singing.
She's the singer there.
Anyway, so I look
around... guess who I
See shaking hands with people?
Who?
WILL SPANNER: Lieutenant Hovis.
Now, I don't think he saw me,
but I tried to follow him,
And he took off.
That's weird.
What do you think
he was doing there?
I don't know.
That does seem to fit together.
Do you think he
knows what we know?
I don't know.
Did you try and talk to him?
No.
But I think he's involved with
those people, whoever they are.
Great.
So the guy that's trying
to pin it on my brother
Is involved in the whole thing.
Well, we don't know that yet.
But whoever these people
are, they're very dangerous.
What would I have
done without you, Will?
Don't worry about it.
I've enjoyed spending
time with you.
I like spending
time with you, too.
Lily, do you... uh... are
you... do... are you involved
With anybody right now?
Not really.
He left me for someone else.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I... well.
Probably too good
for him, anyway.
It was a long time ago.
I have to think
about Pete, anyway.
Oh, yeah.
What, uh... tell me something.
What... what happened
to your parents?
Why... why did you end up
raising him by himself?
My parents were murdered.
Thanks for dinner.
You're welcome.
What?
What is it?
Am I being a jerk?
I... I'd rather go inside.
OK.
Alone.
OK!
I understand that.
Goodnight.
Thanks.
[Inaudible].
Your purse.
Lily!
[Knocking]
All right, Hovis, I wanna
know what the fuck is going on!
Why won't the PD talk to me?
Hey, it's my day off.
Let me tell you
something, mister.
You just can't come over
here and intrude on my life
Every time you got a question.
You cut the shit, Hovis.
I want to help him.
I'm his lawyer, for
crying out loud!
Yeah, well, I don't think
that's the way Pete sees it.
Oh.
Well, how do you think
Pete feels about it, then?
Listen, if you want
to talk about this,
Why don't you come over
to my office tomorrow?
Don't jerk me around, Hovis.
I want to know now!
All right.
It seems that you've
been, uh... hanging
Around with that girl a lot.
His sister.
Looks like you're paying more
attention to her than to Pete.
How did you hear that?
Hey, I got ears.
You're involved in
something, Hovis.
What's going on, man?
You're into something,
and it stinks.
Is somebody paying you
to pin all this on Pete?
Did you happen to see
a picture of the girl?
Huh?
His date?
Unbelievable.
I had to get the parents to
come down to identify her.
And as far as they're concerned,
her father would just as soon
Put a gun down his throat.
Yeah, but did he do it?
I mean, you're gonna
say that he went
Around and did all these
killings for the past year?
17 years old!
Yeah, and 12-year-old
kids kill each other
Over a pair of sneakers.
Now get off my porch.
Look, I'm not gonna let
you get away with this.
I'm gonna find a way
around this, and when I do,
You're fucked.
You know what I'm saying?
OK.
But you better watch
what you're doing.
Because if things go
sour, I'm not gonna
Be around to help you out.
It's your responsibility.
You understand?
Look, this thing goes
beyond the law, Will.
You just don't see it.
Now, if I were you, I
would just back off.
We got it under control.
OK?
[Phone ringing]
Hello, this is William Spanner.
Oh, hello, Belladonna.
No, no, no.
Is everything OK?
Are you all right?
I'm just a little
surprised you called.
Yeah, yeah.
Sure, yeah.
Can I come down to the... your
house, or the Coven, or what?
What do you want me to do?
Yeah, OK.
[Music playing]
Thanks for meeting me here.
I know this is a
funky old elevator,
But it's the only
place I could think of.
Can I have one of my cigarettes?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Can I have one, too?
Sure.
Thank you.
So why don't you tell me
about this manager of yours?
OK.
What's his name?
His name is Rob Santara.
Oh yeah.
Isn't he that
controversial disc jockey?
KSTN, the college radio.
Yeah.
How long have you had
a contract with him?
Three years.
When does it expire?
It doesn't.
That's crazy.
And why is he your manager?
He's a disc jockey.
He likes the music.
He says it reaches the
right kind of people.
So, what?
He likes to play
records for a hobby?
I guess you could say that.
Listen, I don't know
what I'm doing here.
Can we just forget about it?
What?
This is crazy.
Will, if you know
what's good for you,
You'll stay away from us.
Don't ever come near me again!
What's the matter with you?
First you call me, you
tell me to come down,
Then you tell me to go away,
and then you call me again!
Do you want me to
help you or not?
[Door closing]
Well, where did he
work before that?
That's weird.
It must be an alias.
Well, you got an address on him?
OK.
All right.
Thanks.
Bye.
Uh, yeah.
In Burbank, I need a number for
a radio station called KSTN.
[Phone ringing]
KSTN.
Hi, yeah.
I need an address
on Robert Santara.
Look, how the
hell am I supposed
To know where he lives?
I mean, he's great and all.
He gets his stuff in on time.
But I just don't have
an address on him.
It just doesn't
work that way, OK?
What time does he
come in at night?
He doesn't.
He broadcasts from
somewhere else.
You don't even
know where your disc
Jockey is broadcasting from?
Look, it's just not
important to us, OK?
We're just happy to
get those ratings.
It's like, we're a
small college station,
And we're getting, like,
incredible recommendations,
You know what I mean?
I mean, it's fucking
hot right now.
People fucking love him.
You know?
OK?
You got it?
That's it.
I'm done.
I'm late for my art class.
Goodbye.
(SINGING) Well, where's
that little sister?
Where's that little thing?
Where's that little sister?
She's down in the middle
doing that mojo swing.
Little sister, where's
that little thing?
Where's that little sister?
She's down in the middle, doing
that mojo swing, mojo swing.
Excuse me.
How you going?
All right.
Belladonna gonna
perform tonight?
I hope so, man, yeah.
I play in a band.
I'm on.
You know ND?
Yeah.
How often does she perform here?
You some kind of cop?
What's with all the questions?
No, no, no.
I'm just a friend.
A friend, huh?
Yeah, you know, she comes in,
she sings, she does her thing.
You know.
I haven't seen her
around lately, though.
Could be trouble.
Trouble?
What do you mean, trouble?
Ain't my business,
ain't your business.
What are you talking about?
What'd you say your name was?
I'm Spanner.
William Spanner.
Yeah.
I'm her lawyer.
Says who?
You know her manager?
Yeah.
You really a lawyer?
Yeah, I'm her lawyer.
Yeah, I... yeah, I
know the manager, yeah.
Santaro.
Seen them together.
I'd stay away from him
if I was you, though.
He's definitely trouble.
Especially him, man.
That's like playing with fire.
What, what?
What's the matter with him?
Why?
You ever heard of the
Legend of the Blues?
No, I don't know the
Legend of the Blues.
What's...
I didn't think so, man.
Listen, man, this guy
Santaro, he's like, uh...
He's, like, around
her all the time, man.
He's like... most of the time
he's, like, across the hall
From her.
I don't know, don't
quote me on it, you know?
I'm not really sure.
But he's definitely dangerous.
WILL SPANNER: Listen, man.
You know a lot more than
what you're telling me.
Listen, you got the power, man.
I don't want to have
anything to do with this.
I told you too much already.
Do what you do.
I don't wanna have
nothing to do with this.
At all.
OK.
Appreciate it.
You have a good show.
Hello?
Didn't you see the closed sign?
I must have forgotten
to lock the door again.
I'm sorry, we're closed.
Come back tomorrow.
No, no.
I really can't do that.
Say, you look really familiar.
Do I know you from somewhere?
No, I don't think so.
Yeah, well, listen, I've
got to have some information.
I need everything you've got
on the Legend of the Blues,
Anything like that.
Well, now, yes, that's
something I know about.
It's in the book.
Probably this one... right here.
OK.
Here it is.
It's based on a quote
by Lyndell Johnson.
He said... and I ask him how.
He said, if you want to
learn anything and make songs
For yourself, you
take your guitar
And you go to where
the road crosses
That way at the crossroads.
Be sure to get there a little
before 12 o'clock that night.
You have your guitar, and
you be playing a piece,
Sitting there by yourself.
A big black man
will walk up, take
The guitar, tune, then
he'll play a piece
And hand it back to you.
And that's the way
the devil learned
Me to play anything I want.
Can I see that?
Oh, sure.
See?
It's got pictures of all
those guys in the early part
Of the century.
There they are.
What are you looking at?
Oh, yeah.
That's that manager
from the '20s.
Who was he?
He was this guy that come to
the south... nobody knows when...
And signed up a
lot of men and put
Them on their first recordings.
He was pretty famous
for that back then,
From what I understand.
What's the matter with you?
Oh, uh... how much do I owe you?
$50, plus tax.
$50?
Hey, I've got some
change for you!
WILL SPANNER (VOICEOVER):
The Legend of the Blues, huh?
What did that have
to do with Santara?
I could have sworn the
guy in the book was him.
If that's true, then he's
been around a long time.
How many people
does he [inaudible]?
How many souls has he robbed?
The question is, am I after
him, or is he after me?
Hello?
Somebody out there?
Can I help you?
[Inaudible].
I haven't seen you for a while.
MAN: Hello.
I still represent you, don't I?
Yeah, I guess you do.
Yeah.
That's the trouble with talent.
Whenever they get
any recognition
They think they can
get a better manager.
No gratitude.
They just think
about themselves!
Listen, man, I
thought you were busy
Doing all this other stuff,
with all that new music stuff,
You know?
Hey, music's music.
I'm a solid guy.
I'm loyal.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to ask you what you
said to that lawyer fellow.
- What lawyer?
- Oh, come on.
Don't lie.
You know what lawyer
I'm talking about.
The witch-fucker.
Santara, please, man, I don't
know what you're talking about.
Why do they lie?
I mean, I just wanted to
know what you talked about.
I didn't talk to
anybody about anything.
I'm telling you.
I think you did.
What did you tell him?
All right, listen.
Honest, Santara,
please, this guy came,
Said he was some lawyer guy,
some schnook guy, I don't know.
And I said... he said
something, and that was it.
He came and he went,
and that was it.
What's the matter?
Why are you scared?
I'm not gonna do
anything to you.
What do you think I'm gonna do?
I don't know, man.
Maybe you might kill
me or something.
How long have we been together?
10 years, isn't it?
Remember the first
recording session we did?
The sound engineer got his
finger shut in the car door.
That was so amusing.
Good times, eh?
Kill you?
I'm not gonna kill you.
I have very few clients left.
I need you, OK?
Just don't talk to that
lawyer guy anymore.
Good.
Enjoy the show.
Enjoy the show?
Agh...
[Inaudible].
Fucking hold him, man!
I'm trying!
[Inaudible].
He's fucking dead.
Come on.
[Inaudible] leave the body...
No, take him home and
meet your fucking mother.
Let's go.
Come on.
Doesn't anybody knock anymore?
I told you never to come back!
Yeah, and I told you
I couldn't help you out
Unless you told me the truth.
Get out!
What, are you gonna
sick fido on me again?
It's not gonna happen this time.
I'm not leaving here until
you tell me who Santara is
And who... and what... you are.
Oh, no.
Not two of them, sniffing
on 'em like a fucking dog!
Come one!
Open the fucking trunk!
It won't open.
Fuck!
Open the fucking... get him in.
Drive the fucking car!
Hold still!
Come on!
Stick him!
[Inaudible] bad
habit, counselor.
WILL SPANNER: No,
no... no, no, no, no!
[Laughter]
Sweet dreams.
[Inaudible].
What are you, a
fucking junkie now?
Shut the fuck up.
Well... what do we
do with the body?
I'm gonna bash his fucking
skull in 'til his eyes pop out.
VOICE: No you don't.
What do you think you're doing?
Don't kill him.
You leave him for me.
You know who I am?
You denied [inaudible]
yourself for too many years.
You've forgotten who you are.
Come with me.
No!
VOICE: I'm your brother, Will.
We were born as twins
to the same mother,
Just before the Inquisition.
Go fuck yourself!
VOICE: You haven't
changed one bit, have you?
[Inaudible]
You don't want to suffer the
inconvenience of death again,
Do you?
Yes, I do!
VOICE: Every time you die all
you've learned is forgotten.
[Inaudible]
You can't imagine what
it feels like there.
This is paradise, Will.
There's only one perfect
way of immortality.
And we're the only two
left who can achieve this.
No!
VOICE: Dinner.
Tonight.
My place.
I'm having your [inaudible].
And I think you know.
[Music playing]
SANTARA: This is Rob Santara,
here on KSTM college radio,
Playing the tunes just for you.
Thanks for joining.
We'll be rocking and
rolling all night long.
I love all my followers,
and I won't stay here long.
So turn up your stereos!
[Silence]
Will!
Uh-uh.
Why resist?
This is who you are.
I'll take your saliva.
We are the same.
From the same.
We are not men, human.
You know that.
You are part of me.
Make him look at me!
Look at me!
I have more power.
You've been biting your
tongue for too long.
You are weak.
If time is eternal, what
chance does she have to live,
Say, 65 years in eternity?
Take her life.
Do it.
Take her heart.
Just reach in and do it.
That's right.
To be, or not to be.
That is the question.
Whether tis nobler in the mind
to suffer the slings and arrows
Of outrageous
fortune, or to take
Arms against a sea of troubles,
and, by opposing, end them.
To die, to sleep.
Death is pure.
Life is abstract and muddled.
Filthy, dirty.
We exist beyond that.
Take her life.
Take her heart.
Just reach in and take it.
If you love her, she will
be part of you forever.
Go on.
Kill her.
You don't need those, Will.
Remember the way.
It's your life, handed down
from your mother and father.
Do it.
You're the last there is.
There is no one else.
Stop!
[Inaudible]
You bastard!
Are you OK?
LILY: Yeah.
I think I'm all right.
WILL SPANNER: I'm gonna
go check on Belladonna.
OK?
You killed him, you bastard!
Ugh...
I'm so sorry.
I wanted to tell you!
She was like me.
He had her soul!
She tried to talk her
brother into it, too.
Why?
I don't know!
Santara helped her.
Then why did she do it?
I don't know.
I'm nothing.
You must think I'm dirt.
[Sobbing]
No.
No, you did what you
had to do to survive.
It's OK.
Well, well, well.
Officer Hovis.
What's it gonna be?
It's your move.
My move, huh?
What's going on, man?
What are you doing here?
What do you mean,
what am I doing here?
I've come to congratulate you.
You solved all my problems.
Really?
I solved... I think you're
part of the problem.
Well, you can think
whatever you want.
But right now I got half the
LAPD outside, not to mention
A few key members of the press.
And we just made the biggest
pinch of a serial killer
That this city has
seen in... Christ,
As long as I can remember.
That's real tidy, then.
So I guess you're gonna
hang it all on Pete.
Nah, we know he
didn't do nothing.
We released him as
soon as we found
Out Santara was just after you.
Imagine that?
Hey.
Just listen to me
for a second, OK?
Pete was talking a lot about his
sister when we picked him up.
So I got to thinking,
well, maybe she
Was involved in this somehow.
As I dug a little deeper, sure
enough, she set the both of you
Up.
She was gunning for you, Will.
So why didn't you just tell me?
Oh, yeah, right.
With you and your bleeding
heart liberal sensibilities?
You would have asked
her right away,
And the whole thing would have
gone down the fucking toilet.
You got no foresight, Will.
He really doesn't.
Ah, it doesn't matter anyway.
[Whistle]
Some weird shit went
on here tonight, huh?
Yeah.
So I guess, uh... we've got a
lot of explaining to do, huh?
Does this mean that you're
gonna keep me for questioning?
Nah, we won't.
But I'd get out of here
and let us take the credit.
Might, uh... what's the
word I'm looking for here?
Confuse.
Might confuse things
if you hang around.
OK.
We're gonna go out
the back door there.
Good.
Let me ask you
something, though.
What actually
happened down there?
I mean, I heard a
hell of a scream.
Oh.
It was nothing.
It was all a dream.
A dream?
Yeah.
But it's... it's long gone now.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
[Music playing]
WILL SPANNER (VOICEOVER): Seems
like a never-ending cycle.
I'm back to pretending
to be normal.
Pete's out of jail, but he'll be
going into a psychiatric ward.
Couldn't take the news
that his sister was the one
Who had his parents killed.
Seems she felt she'd
been abused, [inaudible]
Santana to get the job done.
She'd worked for him ever since.
Belladonna has a
recording contract.
And Hovis... well,
Hovis and I play cards
On an occasional full moon.
[Music playing]
MAN: Damn!
What the hell was that?