(Music playing)
(Camera shutter clicking)
* In the city
* Feel the heartbeat,
you're not complete *
* Let it all go
* In the shadows
from the streetlights *
* Feel the spaces
* Moving in slow...
(Beeping)
- * In the city...
- (computer beeping)
- Hey, Mom.
- Hey, honey.
How you doing?
Let me guess... you
have to work late tonight
And you're not gonna
be back until after 10:00.
I'm so sorry.
I know I promised to take
you out to dinner tonight,
But we just got slammed.
There is some Chinese food
in the 'fridge, though.
So how was school?
It was incredible.
My teacher loved
the high contrast photo
I took downtown.
Oh, yeah,
those were great.
And she thinks
that I should send it
to that festival in Paris.
- Wow!
- Let's go to Europe.
- You and me?
- Yeah, we can go
to the festival,
Pick up the award
and then hit the road
in a convertible.
Ha! Okay, I'm in.
Now we just need
to win the lottery
to pay for the trip.
Hey, did you pick up
the mail today?
- Uh-uh.
- Well, why don't
you go downstairs
And, you know,
see what's down there?
No, you did not
get that lens that
I was looking at.
That is way too expensive.
Hey, let me decide
what is too expensive.
Just go.
Check the mail.
- Open the door.
Open the door.
- No!
- Oh, my God. Jodi!
I'm calling 9-1-1.
- You come here right now!
Get out
of the apartment now!
- Man: Come here!
- Jodi: Please let me go!
Get out!
- Jodi!
- Mom!
My daughter is getting
attacked right now.
- 52822 Loma Verde Avenue...
- What you doing, huh?
Apartment 18,
West Hollywood.
Oh, my God!
Send somebody fast.
Jodi, no! No!
Stop it!
Get away from her!
Oh, my God. No!
(Sighs) Okay,
this is the last of it.
Oh, I cannot wait to show you
the new bedspread I bought.
Come on.
I think I have
unpacked enough for us
To at least have
breakfast tomorrow.
I have to get up at
4:00 so I can be at
the hospital by 6:00,
So I'm gonna go to bed.
Good night, baby.
Did you lock
the back door?
Yeah.
What about the windows?
Yes, honey.
Hey...
This place is gonna
be really great.
I don't know how
I'm gonna pay for it,
but it's worth it.
This summer we're
gonna have so much fun.
And then in the fall,
you are gonna go to
a terrific new high school
And meet a bunch
of new friends.
Sweetie, the police shot
that awful man.
He can't hurt you
anymore.
This is a safe neighborhood.
We're gonna be okay here.
- Good night.
- Don't stay up too late.
(Wind blowing)
(Thumping)
(Tapping)
Mom. Mom, wake up.
Andrea:
What's the matter?
- Did you hear that?
- (tapping continues)
I think that's
the wind, honey.
No, there's someone
at the door.
(Sighs)
Do you realize
what time it is?
Put that down.
(Tapping)
See, it's nothing
to worry about.
Will you sleep
in my room tonight?
Sure, honey.
(Music blaring
over radio)
- Man: Fire it up.
- (engine turns over)
- Man #2: Yeah!
- (engine revving)
- What do you think?
- Give it a little more gas.
Hey, give it
a little more gas.
- (Engine revs)
- Nice.
- How's that?
- (camera whirring)
- A little more.
- (camera shutter clicks)
- Now we're
getting somewhere.
- Yeah!
Man #3:
Come on, honey,
you don't have to leave.
Are you sure we can't
talk about this?
Come on.
Out of my way.
- Man #2: How's that?
- Man: That's good.
That's good!
That's working now.
- (Engine revving)
- There. Nice, nice! I love it,
I love it, I love it!
- Awesome!
- Man #2: Whoo-hoo!
That's what
I'm talking about.
Man:
Uh-oh, turn it off.
- Man: You owe me 100 bucks.
- Woman: Nick.
Aw, jeez.
Mrs. Miller.
I know what you're gonna say
and I'm done for the day.
It's not about today.
It's about tomorrow
and the next day
And the next month.
You see, I work from home.
So I need to be able
to have a phone conversation
with a client
- and be able to hear them.
- I'm sorry, all right?
I'm just doing a favor
for some friends of mine.
- A favor?
- Yeah.
You're running a business
out of your garage.
- I'm not running a business.
- Come on, Nick.
Woman #2: Aunt Lisa, relax.
It's not a big deal.
Look at this place.
I mean, are you kidding me?
Do you have any idea what
you're doing to the property
values around here?
Nick: I'll tell you this.
This is one piece
of property
That you don't have your
hands on yet, Mrs. Miller.
All right, I've asked you
nicely. Next time I'm
calling the cops.
Go right ahead.
I'm shaking in my boots,
Mrs. Miller.
- Bossing everybody around.
- Lisa: Ugh, this is
ridiculous.
- Man: I agree.
- Hey, how are you?
- Great.
- Glad to hear it.
- Lisa: Kristen.
- Coming.
Hey.
- (Indistinct chatter)
- (shutter clicking)
(Gasps)
(Whirring and clicking)
(Telephone ringing)
- (beeps)
- Hello?
Hello?
(Beeps)
(Doorbell rings)
(Doorbell continues
ringing)
(Jodi sighs)
Hi, I'm Lisa Miller.
I live across the street.
I just wanted to welcome
you to the neighborhood.
Hi, I'm Jodi.
Hi, Jodi.
I made you some cookies.
Thank you.
So are your parents home?
I would like to say hello.
It's just my mom.
She's at work.
Okay, well, tell her
I dropped by, okay?
Are you all right?
- Sweetie, what's the matter?
- Someone just stole
my camera.
What? Are you serious?
This area is so safe.
I mean, we never have
burglaries out here.
I'm sorry.
I'm just a little
freaked out right now.
Don't apologize.
You wanna come
over to my house?
You can stay with us
until she gets back.
No, that's very kind of you,
but I'll be okay.
Listen, why don't
you and your mom
come over tomorrow?
You can have lunch with
me and my niece Kristen.
You'd like her.
Okay, I'll ask my mom.
Great.
Just let me know.
Here's my number, okay?
Thank you.
Andrea: Are you sure
you didn't misplace it?
I mean, look at this.
Yes, I looked everywhere.
I think we should
call the police.
Let's get this place
cleaned up.
If we still don't find it,
I'll buy you a new one.
Mom, I don't want you
spending that kind of money.
- Don't worry.
I can afford it.
- No, you can't.
You're always saying
how expensive it is
to live here.
I'm telling you,
somebody came into
the backyard.
We've only been here
two days and already you're
saying we've been robbed?
Yes, and I want
to report this.
First, let's clean up
the house, okay?
Okay, what time do they
want us over for lunch?
(Music blaring
over radio)
(Engine revs)
So where did you live
before you moved here?
- West Hollywood.
- Oh, I love West Hollywood.
Why'd you guys leave?
No!
We had a condo.
We needed more space.
- Mm-hmm.
- So, Kristen, I take it
you live in LA?
- No, I live here.
- Oh, I thought you were
Just visiting
your Aunt Lisa
for the summer.
This is my home now.
My parents are gone.
Her mom passed away
last year.
I am so sorry.
I asked Kristen
if she would wanna
come live with me,
And well,
I'm just glad
she said yes.
You know, you should
take Jodi with you
next weekend.
That's a great idea.
You'd love it.
What?
Our church.
They have this retreat.
It's up Angeles Crest.
It's so fun.
They have hiking and volleyball
and all the fun stuff.
Yeah, the van's gonna pick
me up next Saturday morning.
Okay, I'll think about it.
You should go.
That sounds really great.
Mom, I said I will
think about it.
- (Engine turns over)
- Andrea: Okay.
(Engine revving)
Not again.
Have you talked
to his parents?
He's a single father.
He's in the oil
business in Dubai.
That's enough.
I am so sorry, Andrea.
- Aunt Lisa,
what are you doing?
- Calling the police.
(Touch tones beeping)
(Engine revving)
Hi, I'm the one
that called the police.
- I'm Lisa Miller.
- Officer Weiland.
How you doing today?
You Nick?
- Yeah.
- Nick, you wanna step out
of the car for me?
I'm not trying to bother
anybody. I'm working
on my buddy's car.
- He's always a bother.
Always.
- What?!
That guy Nick
stole my camera.
He was the only one around
when I noticed it was missing.
You should go tell the cop.
I'm not gonna introduce myself
to our next door neighbor
By accusing him
of burglary.
Just ask the cop to come over
and we can talk in private.
It doesn't have
to be a big deal.
- Please?
- Okay.
- Thanks.
Weiland: Son, I need
you to calm down.
Just take it
from me, okay?
And if we get
any more complaints,
I'm gonna have to
come back here
and arrest you.
- Andrea: Excuse me, Officer.
- Nick: Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Miss Miller,
stay back, please.
I just wanted to talk to
you about something that
happened in our house.
- We live across the street...
- So you think somebody
stole your camera?
Yesterday I was
outside taking pictures
And the phone rang,
so I put the camera down,
Came in to answer it,
and when I went back out,
it was gone.
- What kind of camera is it?
- A DSLR with a 75 to 300
zoom lens.
Is it anything like
that camera out there?
What?!
Officer, I am so sorry
to bother you.
Not a problem.
I hope she gets
some great pictures.
- Thank you.
- Okay? All right.
- Well, that was embarrassing.
- Mom, I checked the backyard.
I checked the house, everywhere.
I swear it wasn't there.
- What do you think happened?
- I think Nick stole it
and then put it back.
Why would anybody
do that?
Sweetie,
it's a new house.
It's a new neighborhood.
You're still recovering.
What happened to you
at our old apartment,
It's gonna take you
a while to get over that.
I still see him.
- In your dreams?
- In my mind.
Every time
I go in a dark room
or I open a door,
It's like he's gonna
be there, but he's not.
I never should have
worked late that night.
- Don't say that.
- No, I'm your mother.
I'm supposed to protect you.
I should have been there.
I have to do some shopping.
Do you wanna go with me?
I just wanna
check my camera.
Okay, sweetie.
(Touch tones beeping)
(Rings)
Man: Hello?
Hello.
Um, who am I speaking with?
This is Nick.
Who is this?
(Beeps)
(Cell phone rings)
- Hey.
- Mom, I can prove it.
- Prove what, honey?
- That Nick stole my camera.
Remember when I got a call
and there was nobody
on the line?
- Well, I checked
the phone records...
- (knock on door)
Hold on.
Oh, my God.
He's at the door.
You don't have to open it.
Do you want me to come home?
I will if you want me to.
In fact, honey,
I'm just gonna come home.
I'll be there in ten minutes.
- (Knock on door)
- No, it's okay.
I'll just see what he wants.
- Jodi.
- Mom, don't worry.
I'll be all right.
(Clicks)
You called my house?
Did you call me?
Why did you steal my camera?
Because you were taking
pictures of me and you
didn't ask me if you could.
How did you get
our house number?
The internet.
Reverse address.
So you called our house,
made me go inside to answer
it, and then hopped the fence
- and stole my camera?
- That's right.
- You're good.
- Then you put it on the porch
- and made me look
like an idiot.
- No, no, no.
Well, I didn't mean
to make you look
like an idiot.
But if that happened,
I'll consider it a bonus.
- I'm going to tell
the cops what you did.
- Wow! First Lisa and now you.
Terrific. Go right ahead
and call the cops.
And I'll show them the pictures
you took of me, half naked.
Yeah, I downloaded
your camera files
onto my hard drive.
While I'm at it, I'll show
the rest of the neighborhood
the pictures you took of them.
Ted's wife across the street,
she's a lawyer.
She'd love to see them.
So you sure you wanna
call the cops?
I just wanna call it even.
Even.
I'm Nick.
(Sighing)
(Horn honks)
- Kristen: Hey.
- Nick: Okay,
Tuesday sounds good.
- Yeah.
- Woman: This is gonna
be so much fun.
- Nick: Yeah, 11:00 a.m.
- Kristen: Hey!
- I'll be there.
- Man on phone: Talk
to you later.
Bye.
(Cell phone rings)
- Hey, Mom.
- Hi, honey, what are you doing?
- Just testing out my new lens.
- Cool!
Well, I'll be done
at the hospital
in about an hour.
- You sure everything's okay?
- (camera shutter clicks)
- Everything's fine, Mom.
- Call me if you need me.
- All right.
- Bye.
- (beeps)
(Beeps)
(Bell ringing)
I think I just saw someone
in your house.
- What?
- I just saw someone.
Or I thought I did.
Downstairs.
Hold on.
You were watching my house?
I was taking pictures
of the street.
I saw you in your bedroom,
and I looked in the window
And I saw a
shadow of someone.
Are you serious?
Yes, let's just go to my
house and call the police.
No, no, no,
hang on. Hang on.
Just give me a second.
Wait, wait, Lisa, don't.
Are you sure you saw someone?
Yes, it was a shadow.
Male, female?
I don't know.
The shades were closed.
Wait here.
I'll check the garage.
There's nobody down here.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
At least I thought...
Look, let's just
get out of here.
- I'm gonna check upstairs.
- I'm calling the cops.
No, no, no,
just give me a minute.
(Sighs)
There's nobody here.
Oh, look, look at this.
Is this what you saw?
I must have walked
in front of it.
Maybe.
I'm sure that's what you saw.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Oh, no, no.
Honey, it's okay.
I really appreciate
your concern.
- Man: See you later.
- Bye, guys.
Woman: Bye, Kristen.
Hey.
Hey, Jodi, how's it going?
Good.
Did you have fun?
Yeah, it was so funny.
You have to come with us
The next time we go on one
of these camping trips.
Aunt Lisa, I'm back.
They did this improv show.
It was so hysterical.
This guy talks totally monotone
like he's got one brain cell
And he has a scene partner
who was talking a mile a minute.
Aunt Lisa, are you upstairs?
Anyway, they're on this gurney
and they're acting like
he's giving birth
Completely in drag.
It was so funny.
Jodi.
Jodi, where'd you go?
- Oh, my God.
- Kristen: Are you up here?
- Don't come in.
- Oh, my God.
- Aunt Lisa, what's wrong?
- 9-1-1. What's your emergency?
No, what's wrong with her?
(gasps)
(Stammers)
I need an ambulance.
- 8672, Via Colinas
in Santa Clarita.
- Aunt Lisa, wake up.
My friend, she's bleeding.
She's not breathing.
We need an ambulance
right now. Hurry!
(Police radio chatter)
Detective, I saw something
on Saturday night
That I think you
should know about.
I got here as fast
as I could. Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
I was so worried about you.
Hi. Detective Franklin.
Andrea Allen,
Jodi's mother.
As you were saying?
I saw someone in the house.
I think it was an intruder.
- About what time?
- Around 10:00.
I was across the street
in my room
Taking some pictures
of the neighborhood.
I saw Lisa
in the upstairs window
And then I saw somebody else
in the downstairs window.
You were taking photographs
of peoples' homes at night?
Yeah, is that illegal?
It's an invasion
of privacy.
Next time you do that,
you should ask your
neighbors for permission.
Anyway, is that the window
with the shades closed?
I saw a shadow,
a silhouette.
That's a long ways
to see at night.
I know what I saw.
Well, did you take a
picture of the shadow?
No, I didn't.
Okay, Jodi, so when you
saw this shadow person,
what did you do then?
I ran over
and I rang the doorbell.
Lisa answered, and we
looked around, but we
didn't find anybody.
Why didn't you
call the police?
Because Lisa didn't
want me to.
She wasn't worried like I was.
I mean, I even tried
calling her this morning
and nobody answered.
And that's why I waited
for Kristen to get home.
I watched the house all day
and Lisa never came out.
Thanks. I'll mention
that in my report.
I think the guy
next door did it. Nick.
Now is that the same
Nick Thompkin
That's running a business out
of his house without a permit?
Yeah.
Lisa called the cops on him
and Nick got really mad at her.
If anyone from the neighborhood
would kill her, it would be him.
Well, we'll talk to him.
We'll be talking to
everybody on this block.
Detective, what do
you think happened?
Well, we don't have
the whole story yet.
There doesn't seem to be
any sign of forced entry.
As far as I can tell,
nothing is stolen.
So right now it looks
like she slipped and fell.
- You're kidding, right?
- Jodi, don't.
When forensics
comes back with their
report in a couple days,
We'll have
a better assessment.
Oh, my God,
Kristen, I'm so sorry.
Come here. Ohh.
Kristen:
Can I stay with you guys
just for a few days?
Yes, of course.
You stay as long
as you need to, okay?
Hi, I'm Detective Ng,
Metro Homicide.
- You live here?
- Yeah.
We're getting statements
from a number of people.
- Do you mind if we ask
you a few questions?
- (Nick clears throat)
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Come in. Right this way.
Andrea:
I'm not going
into work tomorrow, okay?
I'm gonna be here all day.
Thank you, Ms. Allen.
(Kisses)
You try and get some rest.
- I wanna talk to her.
- Let her rest.
But, Mom.
I'm telling you,
somebody was in her
house that night.
Shh.
Keep your voice down.
She doesn't need to hear that.
She's suffering enough.
And why did you incriminate
the boy across the street?
- Well, what if he did do it?
- Then the police will find
evidence to support that.
Will you please
stay out of it?
Let them do their job.
(scoffs)
Can't believe you said
that to the cop.
- Oh, well, I'm sorry
if I embarrassed you, Mom.
- I'm not embarrassed.
Forget the fact that I'm
the one who found Lisa on
the bathroom floor today.
I didn't know I was
supposed to be worried
about how you felt.
I'm sorry.
Just leave me alone.
(Sighs)
- I need to talk to you.
- (gasps) You scared me.
I overheard you
talking to your mom.
You saw somebody
in the house Saturday night?
Look, I shouldn't
have said anything.
Please I need
to know what you saw.
Kristen, my mom was right.
And you've been
through enough already.
You don't need
to be worried about this.
It was only a shadow.
Is that it?
Did you see a face?
I couldn't see who it was,
And it was only
for a split second.
Suppose I was right.
Suppose somebody
did kill her.
I wanna catch the guy,
don't you?
Yeah, but who would
wanna kill her?
- I think it was Nick.
- Jodi, come on.
Lisa completely
shut down his business.
Nick was really mad.
We all saw it.
Yeah, but Nick
wouldn't kill her.
It was probably just
an accident like the cop said.
I just...
I just can't accept that.
The cops should be,
I don't know.
They should be watching him.
- Thank you.
- For what?
For trying to help.
I'm gonna go back to bed.
So what do you think?
Yeah, they're in good condition.
Where'd I get 'em?
I stole 'em.
What kind of question is that?
Do what you want.
You can melt 'em down,
sell 'em on the black market.
I don't care.
Yeah, I'm coming right now.
(Car alarm chirps)
(Engine turns over)
(Muffled dance music playing)
Woman:
Yeah! Whoo!
- Steve, what's up?
- Hey, what's up, Nick?
- How are you, man?
- Good. You?
- Good. Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Aww, man, really?
(Clears throat)
Driver's license, please.
I forgot my ID.
Turn around.
Okay. Come on in.
So how's your car shop?
Well, that's sort of
why I'm doing this.
Looks like I gotta
shut it down.
This way, Nicky.
- Nick: Let's see.
- (zipper zings)
Thank you.
Nick: Perfect.
Put this right here.
Someone's looking for you.
Hey, hey, come here!
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, I'm...
What... Hey, I'm not
gonna hurt you.
I'm your neighbor, okay?
And why are
you following me?
I'm not following you.
I come here a lot.
Oh, okay.
What's going on
back there?
What do you think's
going on back there?
- No, say it.
- You're selling her jewelry.
Wait, what?
What do you mean?
Lisa. You stole her jewelry
and now you're pawning it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I stole her jewelry?
- I saw someone in her
house the other night.
- Oh, my God.
You were mad at her because
she shut down your business
so you decided to get revenge.
You sound just like that cop.
Why you talking to me like this?
You snuck in, killed her,
stole her jewelry.
- And now you're pawning it.
- (laughs) I killed her?
Not only are you way...
Off-base, but you are
incredibly obnoxious.
- Am I?
- Yeah, you are,
but that's okay
Because I kind of
have a crush on you.
Oh, don't you try...
(Clears throat)
What did you say?
You heard me.
Hey, look, getting
my business shut down
Is the best thing
that's ever happened to me.
I mean, I got a job.
Now I'm gonna be fixing cars
in a shop across town,
and I can't wait.
I'm selling some
of my old tools to
a guy who works here.
But...
If you wanna believe
That I killed her...
Then go right ahead.
So what, you're just...
You're just gonna
stand there all night?
They're gonna check your ID.
What do I do?
*... this moment to arise
* You take my breath away
* I'm feeling cold
* But I'm holding on
* You turned
my world around *
Hey, Borelli.
We need check the back.
I'll show you.
* Because of you
* I know all the answers
* I'm taking all my chances
* Because of you
You should probably go.
* Letting go of everything
* I am
* You take my
breath away... *
Yeah, I'm sorry, Kristen.
Your aunt was murdered.
Now with your permission,
I need to discuss
the autopsy results.
Go ahead.
As you can see,
The impact to her
skull is quite severe.
Now for a woman her height
falling less than four feet
Hitting the side of
the tub at this angle,
There is no way that
her skull would be
crushed to that degree.
The physics of the
situation tells us this
was not a slip and fall.
Something hit her
in the back of the head
with an incredible force.
Now one scenario is that
the prowler entered the house
through an unlocked door.
Lisa surprised him.
He killed her.
He panicked and ran off
without stealing anything,
Or she was murdered
for another reason.
Now, Kristen,
we spoke to your church
- regarding your whereabouts
at the time of her death.
- Wait, I'm a suspect?
Well, your aunt made quite
a bit of money in Southern
California real estate.
You're the sole
beneficiary in her will.
So you're about to inherit
close to $4 million.
I loved her more
than my own mother.
Don't worry.
We confirmed your alibi.
Several people in the church
said you were definitely
at the weekend retreat.
I can't believe this.
Detective,
who do you think did this?
We don't know.
We talked to every
neighbor on the block.
We contacted Lisa's friends
and her business associates.
No one had anything bad
to say about her.
Well, about the guy next door,
Nick Thompkin?
Well, he said he was
home alone that night,
But nobody could verify it.
So he doesn't have an alibi.
He could've done it.
He was really pissed
at my aunt. Right, Jodi?
I don't...
I don't know about that.
That's not what
you told me before.
She's right, Jodi.
You said, and I quote,
"Lisa called the cops on him.
Nick was really mad at her.
If anybody from this
neighborhood would kill
her, it would be him."
I just don't think he would
do something like that...
- not anymore.
- So you're changing
your opinion.
Yes.
Can I ask why?
I just have a feeling.
A feeling?
Okay, that's... that's unique.
Wait, you're not gonna
arrest him because of
what I said, right?
Well, we're not gonna
arrest anyone until we
have more evidence.
Don't worry, Kristen.
We're not done yet.
We're gonna get
whoever did this.
Yeah, listen, I'm gonna need
to get a search warrant.
His name is Nick Thompkin.
The address is 1821...
Hey, can I show you something?
Sure.
What do you think
they're talking about?
I know exactly
what they're talking about.
Ted would hit on me,
and Aunt Lisa didn't like it.
Jodi, a lot of older guys
hit on me. So what?
If they arrested every older guy
who tried to sleep with me,
They'd have to start
building more prisons.
Yeah, but look.
- I mean, he's, like,
really mad at her.
- Jodi, stop it.
- What?
- Just because someone gets
in an argument with my aunt
Doesn't make them a killer.
- What is with you?
- Okay, well, then who
do you think did it?
I don't know.
I'm still trying to get past
the fact that she's gone.
And this cop tells me
that she's been murdered
And that I'm a suspect.
Then you go around accusing
everyone in the neighborhood.
Maybe you did it.
Jodi, I told you
to not bother her.
She didn't do anything wrong.
(sighs)
Kristen, I'm sorry.
I'm just gonna go back home.
Are you sure?
You're more than
welcome to stay.
I'll let you know if
I can't handle it over there.
Okay.
Thank you for everything,
Ms. Allen.
What did I tell you?
Mom, will you just look
at this and tell me...
- No!
- what you think?
Just please.
- No, this is just
making it worse.
- Mom!
Wait. Wait.
We have a problem.
The cops don't think
it was an accident.
They think someone
killed her.
You still think I killed her?
I don't,
But the cops think you did.
You said you were
gonna make it look
like she slipped and fell.
That's exactly what I did.
Well, you hit
her at the wrong
angle or something.
They figured it out.
Well, maybe you
should've done it then.
Baby, you know I
couldn't have done that.
That's not what
we talked about.
No, what we talked about
is I put her lights out
and then you give me half.
- Where's the money?
- It's in probate.
It's gonna take some time.
Just relax.
Relax? Really?
How am I supposed to do that?
- They're gonna figure out
what we did.
- No, they won't.
Don't say that, baby.
I'm tired of all
this sneaking around.
Putting ten hours a day
into this lousy job.
Do you really think I like
going to that church?
We have to act normal.
Jodi: Look at the way
she's talking to him.
Nick: Yeah, he looks really
mad at her about something.
Well, I wanna go show Ted these
pictures and see what he says.
I mean, I was hoping that
you would come with me.
What? Now? I can't.
I'm starting that new job.
If I don't hurry,
I'm gonna be late.
If you don't keep it together,
you're going to ruin this.
That girl across the street,
she's watching us.
- What are you talking about?
- She's been taking pictures
of the entire neighborhood.
Do you remember the argument
you had with my aunt?
When you talk to her
the way that you do,
Kristen doesn't understand
that you're just trying
to get in her pants, Ted.
It is not what
you're thinking.
It's exactly what I'm thinking,
and I don't like it.
- Look...
- Stay away from her.
I mean it.
Kristen: Jodi just
showed me pictures
of you arguing with Lisa.
You look like you're ready
to rip her head off.
Jodi's gonna show those
pictures to the cops.
You're gonna have to
answer more questions.
Okay. All right, well, that's
why we put together an alibi.
Yeah, you see?
I went to the movies.
Got a ticket stub right here.
We snuck out at 8:30.
I drove back here.
Parked around the way
and nobody saw me.
That would've worked if it
looked like it was an accident,
But now that it's murder,
it's not that simple.
You're right. You're right.
Oh, I'm screwed.
I mean, they're gonna
figure out I did this.
No, baby, don't say that.
Look at me.
I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you.
I've got an idea.
Let's go over to Ted's
later this afternoon
after I get home.
- Okay.
- Then afterward we can
go to dinner or something.
Well, just come
to my house when...
Wait. Wait a sec.
Did you just ask me out?
Yeah.
And you said yes.
(Camera shutter clicking)
This way.
Here.
(Gasps)
Forget it. Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
Jodi: Hey, Mom.
Can we talk?
Yeah, sure.
I think Kristen
and that guy Ted
killed Lisa.
Oh, man.
First Nick
and now these two?
I'm serious.
Okay, what makes
you think that?
What does this
look like to you?
It looks like
they went hiking.
Yes, I followed them to
the woods and they're, like,
totally into each other.
They're having
an affair, Mom.
Did you see them
get physical at all?
No,
But I saw him put
his arm around her
and then lean in.
And then they went behind
a tree, so I don't know
if they kissed or not.
So you can't say for sure?
Still, what is a guy his
age doing in the woods
with someone like her?
- Honey...
- I think I should show
these pictures to the police.
No, you can't.
You were stalking them
with your camera.
Remember what
Detective Franklin said?
I was right about
the shadow, wasn't I?
Yes, you were.
But this is pushing it,
And these pictures don't
prove anything.
What if you're wrong?
What if Ted and
Kristen did kill Lisa?
She was probably
attacked by a burglar
- like the detective said.
- You're my mom.
Why can't you just
back me up on this?
Why can't you believe me?
Because you have accused
three of our neighbors
of being murder suspects.
It's too much.
Don't you see
what you're doing?
You are inventing
a neighborhood boogeyman
To punish your attacker.
Honestly?
I'm just worried
about Nick right now.
The cops are looking at him
as their number one suspect,
Partly because of what I said.
And I know
he didn't do it.
We should've done this earlier.
We're cutting it close.
I'll watch the front.
Be careful.
Come on.
(Lock rattles)
Damn it.
Jodi:
Hey, how was work?
Great.
(Cell phone vibrates)
It was really weird.
- Nick: So we don't
have to talk to him?
- Jodi: Uh, no.
Nick: Great. I just heard
from my dad and I gotta
go grab him at LAX.
I talked to him yesterday.
I didn't think he'd
get here so quick.
But maybe afterwards,
well, me and you
Can go get dessert
or something.
Okay.
I wanna go
to the cops tomorrow,
- (sighs)
- show them the pictures
and tell them everything.
And I want you
to come with me.
Why do you want me
to go with you?
Because...
I don't know.
I just think it might
help your case.
Is that the only reason?
What do you mean?
What other reason?
Well, I just think that,
That you like
hanging out with me.
I just don't want you
to get arrested. That's all.
So what, you're just,
like, doing all this,
'Cause...
'Cause you're
a concerned citizen?
Something like that.
No other reason?
- No.
- You sure?
I'm not sure
About anything.
(Sighs)
You... you wanna go
into the living room?
Don't you have to
pick up your dad?
Not for like an hour.
I mean, I-I-I should
probably get home.
I mean, I've got work stuff.
- Um...
- Yeah, yeah.
(Cell phone rings)
- It's Kristen.
- Oh, go ahead.
- Hey, Kristen.
- Hey, Jodi.
Did I call at a bad time?
- No.
- Can you come over?
I really need to talk
to you about something.
- Right now?
- Yeah, it's kind of important.
Sure.
I'll be right over.
- You gonna be okay?
- Mm-hmm.
All right, so I guess
I'll see you tonight.
Yeah.
I'll walk you out.
See you when you get back?
All right.
Hey, come on in.
Jodi, I just wanted to apologize
for what I said today.
Oh, I understand.
I know you got a lot
on your mind.
I've been thinking about Nick.
I think you're right.
- Why is that?
- Because of what
you said to the cop.
- I mean, he did hate my aunt.
- No, I shouldn't
have said that.
Jodi,
you understand people.
- You see things
with your camera.
- I was wrong about him.
Like I told the cops,
I just... I changed my mind.
Why did you
change your mind?
Why did you change yours?
I saw you kissing him.
You know, Jodi,
Sex can cloud your judgment.
Really? How?
You know.
No, I don't know.
Why don't you
explain it to me?
Wait. You're not still
a virgin, are you?
- (Screams)
- (grunts)
No, I'm not.
Oh, my God.
Tell me all about him.
What is he like?
He was a complete stranger.
I never would've guessed.
I mean, you seem
so sweet and innocent.
I'll make a deal with you.
I'll tell you who I'm
sleeping with, if you tell
me who you're sleeping with.
I'm not sleeping
with anyone.
I'm gonna save that
for marriage.
Good luck with that.
Thanks for coming over,
Jodi.
I think she knows about us.
Doesn't matter.
We're in the clear.
You are my everything.
(Doorbell rings)
Hi. I'm Jodi.
I live across the street.
Is Nick here?
Yeah. Come on in.
I'm his dad Eddie.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Nick, you got company.
So you're the girl
who accused my son
Of killing
the nice lady next door?
- Well, actually...
- Let me tell you something.
You're wrong.
I got the
greatest kid in the world.
- Mr. Thompkin,
that's actually why I came.
- When he was this tall,
He used to follow his mother
around helping her
with the housework,
Scrubbing the floors.
Everybody he meets he tries
to do something good for them.
- Talk to any of his friends.
- Dad, Dad.
She gets it.
Thank you though.
Thank you. Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Thanks. Great.
Dad, aren't you,
like, jetlagged?
- Don't you need
to sleep or something?
- Jetlag. I'm tired.
- Hi.
- Are you ready?
- Mm-hmm.
All right, let's go.
Wait. I forgot something.
Mr. Thompkin, I have a court
order to search your premises.
- Excuse me.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You guys take the back.
- What's this?
- He's got a warrant.
I don't know.
- Warrant?
- Yeah.
- Can you explain this?
- I've never seen that before.
Well, it looks like
blood and human hair.
Bag it.
We're gonna take it down
to our lab to run
some tests on it
Along with some other
items we found.
- Someone must've
put that there.
- You're arresting him?
We're gonna ask
him a few questions.
We got a lot to talk about.
Nick, don't say anything
till we get an attorney.
- Keep your mouth shut for once.
- Wait. No, no, no, Detective.
I have to show you
some pictures, okay?
He didn't do it.
It was Kristen.
She's having an affair
with her neighbor Ted.
Look, I followed them
into the woods.
I think after they killed
Lisa, they buried the pipe
And then dug it up
and planted it
in Nick's garage.
Jodi, let's be honest
here, okay?
I don't know if you're
saying this to protect
your boyfriend
Or you're having another
one of your feelings.
Neither one
of 'em are credible.
Now if you'll excuse me.
(Buzzer sounds)
(Camera shutter clicking)
Okay, Mr. Thompkin.
Thank you for letting me know.
(Beeps)
The blood on the pipe tested
positive for Lisa Miller's DNA.
They arrested Nick.
What was it doing
in his garage?
Ted and Kristen
are framing him.
What?
- You don't think
he did it, do you?
- I don't know.
But how can you be so
sure that he didn't do it?
You don't know him
like I do.
Honey, you met him
three weeks ago.
You barely
know him yourself.
Don't you think
I wanna believe you?
But you're not looking
at the facts that
the police recovered.
I know what I saw, Mom.
I'm not gonna let Nick take
the fall for what they did.
- (Sighs)
- Just come to the station
with me.
I want you to hear it
from Nick.
Nick:
Sure, I was pissed
at Mrs. Miller,
But, then I realized she was
right, and I got over it.
I wasn't mad at her anymore.
What about your alibi?
I was at home that night
watching a movie on TV.
That's the truth.
Ms. Allen,
This isn't exactly the way
that I wanted to meet you,
And I know it looks
really bad,
But I swear
I didn't kill her.
Jodi brought me here
because she thought
you might say something
To convince me
that you're innocent.
- And I guess
that didn't happen.
- Mom, please.
Nick, if you can't prove
to me that you didn't do it,
How are you gonna
prove it to a jury?
Maybe I can't.
Maybe I'm gonna spend the next
50 years of my life in here.
- Jodi: No.
- You know what I don't get?
Is how you could...
- Never mind.
- Andrea: What?
Say it.
You're her mother.
What's your point?
Jodi's smart,
Courageous,
Beautiful
And she got all those
qualities from you.
So I'm just trying
to understand
How you can look her
in the eye right now
And see that reflection
of yourself and not believe her.
Okay, let's say for a minute
that you're right.
There's still no proof
that Kristen and Ted did it.
Have you thought about that?
Yes, I have been racking
my brain trying to
figure this out.
I mean, talking to
Detective Franklin was no use.
We've gotta try
something more.
- Like what?
- (sighs)
What about this?
I'll follow Kristen
and you follow Ted.
- No.
- Yes. Mom,
we'll get you a camera.
- I mean, they're bound to make
a mistake eventually.
- Jodi!
No. It'll only
cause more trouble.
I'm sure that Nick's dad will
hire the best possible lawyer
And if they need to get
a deposition from you,
they will.
And in the meantime,
you are not gonna go
spying on them anymore.
- You can't tell me what to do.
- Oh, yes, I can.
And you're not
leaving the house
until you've calmed down.
You're grounding me?
You've never done that before.
Well, I'm doing it now.
(Knock on door)
Hi. You hungry?
I was gonna make
us some lunch.
No, I'm okay.
I'm just gonna finish
retouching this photo,
But I'm kind of tired
so I'm just gonna lay
down for a little bit.
Okay.
- Hey, Mom.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry about the way
I talked to you last night.
Sweetie, it's okay.
We've had a rough
couple of weeks.
- You want the door closed?
- Please.
Okay.
(Doorbell rings)
- Hello.
- Hi.
We haven't officially met.
- No, I know who you are.
- Oh.
Well, then you probably
know why I'm here.
- Can I come in?
- I'm sorry.
- I was just running
out the door.
- Look.
Nick Thompkin is probably
Gonna spend the rest
of his life in jail
For something
that he didn't do.
We're... we're
kind of together
And he was arrested
Before we could go
on an actual date.
But, look, Mr. Wilcox,
If there's anything that
you can do to help Nick,
I'm... please...
I'm... I'm begging you.
Jodi. That boy killed
a dear friend of mine.
- I'm sorry. I've got
an appointment at the bank.
- Ow! I'm sorry.
It's my contact.
It's out of place.
Can I use your bathroom just
for a second, please?
- (Sniffles)
- Of course.
It's to the right.
Thank you.
It was nice to meet you.
Yes, a pleasure.
(Engine turns over)
Hey, sweetie.
I brought you some food.
Jodi?
- (Knocks)
- Jodi?
(Door rattles)
Jodi?
- Hey, baby.
- Hey.
Mmm, bank account is open.
Good, 'cause I've got
something to show you.
- Ted: Surprise?
- Uh-huh.
- 50 grand.
- (sighs)
Where'd you get that?
The college fund she left me.
Her money's starting
to roll in.
Perfect.
It's all working out.
Yes, it's incredible.
We're gonna leave here
and we're gonna get
our beach house.
- Everything we've
always wanted.
- Everything.
- I've got
something else for you.
- Oh, do you? (Laughs)
Jodi!
Relax.
Ted: Baby... (laughs)
(Gasps)
Whatever did I do
To deserve you?
(Gunshot)
(Panting)
(Beeping)
- Hi, this is Jodi.
Leave a message.
- (beeps)
Where are you?
I am really worried right now.
- Call me back.
- (beeps)
Get in. You're driving.
Give me your phone.
(Doorbell rings)
(Beeps)
- Go. Go!
- (engine turns over)
- Hi, this is Jodi.
Leave a message.
- (beeps)
Jodi, you need to tell
me you're all right.
- I'm at Kristen's
front door right now.
- (bell ringing)
What the hell are you doing
driving Ted's car?
(Beeps)
(Thinking)
First Nick and now these two?
What is a guy his age
doing in the woods
with someone like her?
These pictures don't
prove anything.
What if you're wrong?
What if Ted and Kristen
did kill Lisa?
Don't go too fast.
They're gonna know
you killed Ted.
What was that,
detective?
Did I hear the gunshot
from Ted's house?
No, I didn't.
Suicide, oh, my God,
that's so tragic.
I know he loved
his wife very much.
He was really distraught
when she left him.
(Laughs)
Keep going straight.
Man:
9-1-1. What's your emergency?
I think my daughter
is being kidnapped.
Ma'am, when they come
to a stop, call us back
and tell us where you are.
We'll dispatch someone
right away.
- That might be too late.
- We will get there as soon
as we can, ma'am.
(Sighs)
Exit up here.
That dirt road up ahead.
Pull over there.
Get out.
This way. Go.
Stop.
Put your camera down.
Smash it.
I told everyone you
and Ted were hiking
out here.
Shut up and do what I say.
- You're gonna bury me?
- Do it!
Now start digging.
(Shouts)
Oh, my God!
(Grunting)
(Gagging)
(Coughing)
- Baby, come here.
- Mom, are you okay?
Andrea: Yeah.
(Panting)
Kristen:
Her money's starting
to roll in.
Ted:
It's all working out.
I've got something
else for you.
- Oh, do you?
- Uh-huh.
- (Gunshot)
- (gasps)
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Jodi: A lot of people
have asked me why we moved
to this neighborhood.
Three months ago I was alone
in our condo and this
man broke in.
He messed me up pretty bad,
and it was even worse
for my mom
Because she saw the whole
thing, but she couldn't
do anything to stop him.
So we decided
to leave the city.
My mom sold the condo.
We packed up
and here we are.
And that is the official
reason why we moved here.
I'm glad you told me.
I was afraid to.
You got nothing
to worry about.
Know what I think?
What?
I think the real reason
I moved here
Is because...
I really need
a good mechanic.
My car has been making
this weird noise.
Can you help me out?
(Camera shutter clicks)
(Music playing)