THE LAST HEIST
Subrip: Pix
You are listening
to KRCW Los Angeles,
news just in of a grisly
homicide in Redondo Beach.
Sonya Jacobson is
live at the scene.
That's right, Nick. I'm here at
Redondo Beach where the LAPD
are investigating the murder last
night of 22 year old Lisa Gonzales.
They're not confirming
any details,
but officers I've spoken
to are saying that it has
all the signs of a serial
murderer they're calling
"The Window Killer."
It would bring
his known tally of victims
in the Southland,
over the last two years, to 15.
That nickname, by the
way, is because he
takes his victims eyes
with him
as some kind of sick trophy.
I'm being told now that
the LAPD are going all out
to find this maniac as we
roll into the holiday weekend.
What the fuck?
Civilian.
All right, everybody be cool.
What the fuck is this?
Geez, what the fuck
are you looking at?
Move on, asshole.
All clear.
Can I help you, sir?
I'm here to make a deposit.
Five minutes, folks.
Final weapons check.
Come on, man,
we did that already.
Then we'll do it again,
Echo Three.
It's a soft target.
There's no guards.
Skeleton staff,
handful of civilians.
Nobody is getting shot today.
So I want safeties on,
chambers empty.
We might as well go
in with squirt guns.
Hey, you know what? I've got
a butter knife in my pocket.
Tracey, chill the fuck out.
I'm afraid we're not
accepting deposits.
Actually, as you can see,
we're closing down.
Didn't you get our letter?
I don't get mail.
I see.
-What about her?
-She got our letter.
We've asked all our customers to
come in and empty out their boxes.
What if they don't?
Well, the feds come in
and they take everything
to a secret storage and
then they trace the owners.
I don't want that.
Most of our customers
feel the same way.
But it is procedure.
Why don't I take my stuff now?
Well, you would need
to have the letter.
-I told you.
-Yes, you don't get mail.
do you have ID?
I have this.
Well, Reverend,
I'll tell you what.
Come over to the counter
and I'll sort ya out.
We go hot in five minutes.
-Masks on.
-Somebody wake up Biggs.
Rock and roll.
OK, here you are.
You can have that back.
So... how long now?
Just a few moments.
I'm sorry again, Mrs. Waxman.
I know this has all
been very inconvenient.
I'm afraid that's not
good enough, young man.
I have had an account
here for 50 years.
That is no way to treat a
customer, closing down like this.
Well, times change, I'm afraid.
We're all very sad here.
Now, if you want to take a seat,
I'll call a cab to take you home.
Fuck you.
-Danny.
-Yes, sir.
The reverend would
like to empty his box.
Is he on the list?
He didn't get the letter.
But I processed him,
and he's set to go.
It's all very irregular.
But I suppose
it'll be all right.
You can take him back
as soon as I finish
-with Mrs. Gowan.
-Yes, sir.
I need to do this now.
As I'm sure has
been explained to you,
it's one at a time today.
So, if you don't mind
waiting your turn.
I'm sure you won't
mind if I go first.
Well, I've been here for
hours and I'm almost late
for my Pilates class, so...
OK.
If it's that important to you.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
You see?
She's happy that I go first.
OK. If you'll follow me,
I'll take you back.
After you, sir.
We really are in the
process of closing up,
so I am sorry about
the mess down here.
Watch your step here.
Been banking here long?
Nobody move.
Get your hands in the air.
Everybody stay
right where you are.
-Echo clear?
-Clear.
-Echo Three.
-Echo Two.
-Clear.
-Echo One.
-All clear.
You know what this is.
There's nothing here for you.
We're closing down,
everything is gone.
Not everything.
You know who owns this place?
Of course we do,
that's half the fun.
Sit down.
What do you want
me to do about them?
I don't know.
Gonna behave?
Listen, young man.
I wish you'd get on with
whatever you're going to do
because I don't want
to sit here all day.
Yes, ma'am.
We'll be as quick as we can.
Cuff 'em.
Hey, get your hands
off me, you bitch.
Are you fucking
talking to me, bitch?
-Where's your phone?
-I left it in my car.
Yeah?
OK.
One, two.
Listen, I've been tied up
by better people than you.
Christ, old lady,
it's not a fucking competition.
Where's your phone?
I haven't had one for years.
Jesus, living
in the Dark Ages.
I'm all set here.
Echo Five, is that everyone?
We're missing two, boss.
Two males.
Employee, civilian.
Where are they?
I don't know what you mean.
Stop wasting our fucking time.
Here, sir.
It's a little stuffy in here.
We switched off the
AC last week, so...
Do you have your key?
I've got it from here.
I'm supposed to stay with you.
My possessions
are very personal.
-I'd like privacy, please.
-I'm sorry.
It's procedure.
Stay here.
Sure.
What did I tell you?
This guy is messing with us.
Next one goes in your head.
Where are they?
In the back, in the vault.
Are you looking for me?
-Shit.
-What?
Sorry, Danny.
You weren't supposed to be here.
Paul? What the fuck, man?
Yeah, what the hell
is going on here?
Should I tell them?
This is my brother, Danny.
You've got to be
fucking kidding me.
It's been a few years.
Yeah, I thought I'd
never see you again.
We took different paths.
Thought you had the day off.
Checked the rota.
Yeah, well, the
assistant manager got sick,
so I picked up for him.
Is everyone OK?
Mrs. Wax...
No.
I really need to go home.
Please help me.
Absolutely, I'm
sure we all would.
Look, this nice
little family reunion?
It's really fucking
touching, but now what Paul?
Nothing changes.
Stick to the plan,
we'll be gone in 10 minutes.
Everything's
fucking screwed up.
You took off your fucking mask.
Your face is gonna be all
over the 10 o'clock news,
and then how long before they
figure out who the fuck we are?
They shut off the
cameras last week.
Isn't that right?
You're welcome to leave.
And give up my share?
You'd like that.
Well, then I suggest that you
shut up and do your fucking job.
We're still
missing a guy, boss.
Any ideas, Danny?
He's in the vault.
OK.
Echo Three, get to the vault,
secure the guy, do your thing.
Echo Five, get some
cuffs on Danny here,
and then you and Echo Four
get everyone in the back room.
Stick to the plan, people,
and we're out in 10 minutes.
Walkies on channel six.
Hey, hey.
Don't worry.
When we're done here,
I'm taking care of business.
My way.
Hey, Paul.
Take a walk,
we're all set boss.
Get up, going on a walk.
Well, that was fun.
Guess we don't need
these things anymore?
Damn thing this, anyway.
Hoorah!
Come out, wherever you are.
In this room here.
Come on, pick up
your pace, let's go.
Now everybody
get on the floor.
-Down!
-Not you.
I cannot sit on the floor.
Will you get the
fucking old bat a chair?
All right, here you go.
You're a nice man, thank you.
-You're welcome.
-You're a real boy scout.
There's nothing wrong
with being decent to people.
-You should try it.
-Says the armed robber.
Shut up.
You.
Mate.
What's the story with
you and your brother?
You'd have to ask our
parents about that one.
You think you're
smart, don't you?
Yeah, with your stupid
fucking little tie,
and your stupid fucking hairdo.
But you're not going to feel
very smart when this is over.
What does that mean?
What she means is you won't
be leaving any witnesses.
What?
-The boss said...
-The boss?
The boss is a fucking wuss.
Tracey's gonna handle
things from here on out.
You just used her name, Allie.
Jesus.
I mean Echo Four.
Yeah, well, like the man said.
It really doesn't
matter, does it?
Happy?
Now sit the fuck down!
-I didn't sign up for this.
-Yeah?
Well, you just better figure
out whose side you're on.
This is bullshit
and you know it.
Echo Three,
you in the vault yet?
Yeah, I just got here. There's
no sign of the missing civilian.
What do you want me to
do, keep on looking?
No, we could search
this place forever.
We need to be out of here.
Just get the stuff.
Copy that.
Echo Six, status report.
Fuck.
All clear.
Echo Four, status report.
We're having
a party back here.
Geez, Echo Four.
Geez your fucking self.
All secure, OK?
Copy. All clear?
Quiet as the...
How much longer?
Not much longer if she's
as good as she says she is.
I don't know about
her girlfriend,
but she's pretty damn good.
How's it coming, Echo Three?
She's probably listening
to her dumb ass music.
Echo Three, pick up
your fucking radio.
Helps her focus.
Echo Three,
fucking status report now.
Echo Three, status report.
Want me to do it?
Not yet.
Echo Three, can you hear me?
Why the fuck is
she taking so long?
Maybe she isn't
so good, after all.
-Fuck you.
-Language.
I didn't know we were
at fucking Sunday school,
you old fucking prune.
Listen, you may be gangsters,
but at least you can
show some common decency.
Gangsters?
What the fuck is this, 1936?
Don't be a bitch.
Sorry.
I'm gonna smoke.
Not in here.
Jesus, woman.
Stay focused.
It's not like
they're going anywhere.
Come on.
I need your phone.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Come on.
It's in your back pocket.
I'll give it right
back, come on.
OK, fine. Just hurry.
-What are you doing?
-I'm texting 911.
I didn't even know
you could do that.
What if they come back? You're
gonna get us all killed...
Would you shut up?
At least he's doing something.
You're supposed to
be the manager here.
Well, I'm sorry, Mrs. Cohen,
but this is all very irregular.
All right,
let's get back in there.
Get a move on.
What?
Never mind.
Chicken and extra avocado.
Yeah, and you know what? Can you throw
in some extra chilis in there, too?
You like the chilis?
I like the chilis.
That'll be 15.20, please.
15.20? You kidding me?
What did Wolfgang Puck
finally go into
the taco business?
Hey, puck off, lady.
I'm just trying to
make a living, man.
Hey, how about a little less
lady? It's Detective to you.
OK. Well, it's still 15.20
Detective, so why don't you
detect that money
while I get your order? Cool?
You're a fucking
comedian, aren't ya?
One William Six,
One William Six.
One William Six receiving.
Possible 211 in progress
near your location.
OK, got it.
I didn't even know
there was a bank there.
It's a safety deposit vault,
it closed down two weeks ago.
So who called it in, then?
It was a text to 911.
Are you kidding?
You can actually do that?
You are directed to attend the
scene and evaluate the situation.
You know what? Send the black and
white over and show me responding.
Roger that. One William Six,
be aware this has been
assessed a prank call.
OK, I'm on my way.
William Six out.
Hey, your burrito, Detective!
So, that's what
100,000,000 looks like.
I'm all done here.
I've got the stuff.
About fucking time.
Fuck you, too.
Put your hands where
I can see them.
Where the hell
did you come from?
Clever fucker.
Paul?
I found our missing civilian.
OK, I'm on my way.
Copy that.
You're not going to
tie me up, are you?
Hell no.
We're going to do this my way.
No witnesses.
You could just let me go home.
-I have what I need.
-Yeah, what's in there?
Just some personal items.
Nothing of value to you.
I'll be the judge of that.
What the...
All call signs, heat.
Say again, heat.
Shit.
So, you're it?
Dispatch said it was a prank.
So, they sent me a couple
guys out of kindergarten?
Everyone's out looking
for that Windows guy.
We got this.
You guys do
bachelorette parties? No?
Going in, cover me?
With pleasure, Detective.
Who the fuck are you?
Fuck.
Paul!
-What's going on?
-Boss.
We've got badges,
three of 'em.
Fucking hide, hide,
get out of here.
I just nicked
your radial artery.
I estimate you have about
nine minutes to live.
If I were you,
I'd contemplate what
you want to do with
the rest of your life.
Good afternoon. I'm Detective
Pascal with the LAPD.
Got a report of a
robbery at this location.
A robbery?
That sounds serious.
And who might you be?
I'm the assistant manager.
As you can see,
this branch is closed.
We're just packing things up.
Nothing here to rob.
Jesus.
You're the fucking
Windows Killer.
Leave Jesus out of it.
Mother fucker.
Would you mind if we came
in and took a look around?
Company policy, sorry.
You'd need a warrant.
Well, not if there's
a crime in progress.
Well, like I said, there's
nothing going on here.
Yeah, the funny thing is, the call
came from inside this location.
Really? I don't see
how that could have happened.
Well, it was a text, so.
Then it could
have come from anywhere.
Yeah, but it's funny.
I'll just show you.
See?
Hey.
Thanks for your cooperation.
Fuck.
See? I just severed your
femoral artery.
You have three, maybe
four minutes to live.
I'm no doctor.
Your heart is actually pumping
the blood out of your body.
I'm not laughing at you.
I'm laughing with you.
This is a beautiful time.
These are the last
moments of your life.
What does it feel like?
Do you feel the joy?
May I see?
Guys. The cops are coming.
Shit. Guys?
Hey, respond.
Fuck.
Fuck me, boss,
you need to see this.
-Shit.
-How you doing?
Hey.
Looks like you missed a spot.
can I help you?
Get out of the van, sir.
-Look...
-Step out of the van.
Come on, please,
give me a break.
It's not a request.
Out of the van.
Shit, she made Rick.
Let me help you.
There you go.
You have the safety on.
Now try it.
-Freeze, freeze!
-Freeze!
No, no, no,
you fucking idiot.
Freeze.
Gun, gun.
Fucking cover me.
Go! Go, go!
-Cease fire.
-They're firing at us.
There's civilians inside.
He's not trying to
kill us, you morons.
We'd already be dead.
Give me the radio.
This is One William Six.
Shots fired at this location.
Officers need assistance.
Copy, clear.
You're gonna be OK, buddy.
Jesus.
-How's it look?
-Not good.
You're all right.
I can patch him up, but...
Yeah, I know.
What's going on out there?
We heard shots.
cops are here.
Christ.
It's OK, they're outside.
We're inside.
We planned for this.
Just chill.
Put your hand up.
-Biggs.
-Yeah?
It's time.
We're gonna need a stitch man.
There's lead in him.
They're not gonna stop
him from bleeding.
It'll be all right.
The eye is the
lamp of your body.
So, if the eye is healthy, your
whole body will be full of light.
But if the eye is bad, your whole
body will be full of darkness.
If then, the light
in you is darkness,
how great then, is the darkness?
I did the best I could do.
-He needs a hospital.
-Yeah, I know.
OK, you stay here.
Just keep watch.
If we start killing cops,
things will get messy.
Shit's already messy.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go to the vault
and sort this shit out.
Stop, Biggs.
You mother fuck.
We're getting jumpy back here.
What the hell is going on?
Cops.
They shot Rick.
What the fuck?
Somebody must
have made a call.
A call?
That fucking Danny.
I knew he was up to something.
I'm gonna kill him.
It's best not to, OK?
We need all the hostages.
For what? We're making a last
stand at the fucking Alamo here?
No, we need time.
Time? Time for what?
Biggs has got a plan.
I've always got a plan, AJ.
What's in your bag?
What do you mean?
Wait, what about Tracey?
Did she get the stuff?
Better ask Paul.
He's looking into it.
Looking into what?
What the fuck, Biggs?
Screw this, we
should rush 'em.
Are you kidding?
-Well, we've got shotguns in the car.
-Yeah.
What, do you guys have
a death wish or something?
There's at least three guys
in there with M4's
who aren't afraid to use them,
and probably more inside.
Not to mention an unknown
number of hostages.
God, what did they teach you about
hostage situations at the academy?
-Deploy overwhelming force.
-Yeah.
You two don't look
so overwhelming.
So, what, we just sit
here and wait for backup?
Look, you guys
want to be useful?
Why don't you go
check the perimeter?
See if there's a
back way out of here.
You can handle this alone?
Probably feel a
little safer, actually.
-OK, we're on it, Detective.
-Great.
This is Detective Pascal, robbery
homicide, badge number 5397.
Go ahead.
I'm gonna text you
a photo for facial ID.
Copy that.
All right, thanks,
I'm sending now.
Who are you, mister?
What the fuck?
Jesus Christ.
All right, heads up, heads up,
everyone. I'm in the vault.
Tracey's dead.
What do you mean, Tracey's dead?
I mean, dead,
she's been fucking killed.
She's in the vault with me.
Who did it?
Best guess is it's
the guy we never found.
I think he's moving
around in the air vents.
Old place like this, there's
a whole network of them.
They're plenty big enough.
Well, then, let's go
fucking get him.
Negative, Allie.
We don't have time for
a wild goose chase.
He fucking killed Tracey.
OK, well, we can get the guy,
or we can get out of here,
we can't do both.
I'm sorry,
but that's the choice.
Now that we know what
we're up against,
we can stop him if
he tries anything.
This is so fucked up.
We're bottled up
in a fucking bank.
-What about the stuff?
-Are you serious?
It's the fucking reason
we came here, isn't it?
I've got the stuff.
Well, that's something.
So, now what?
We go to plan B.
Biggs is already working on it.
Just need a couple hours.
In the meantime, stay frosty.
May only be one guy,
but he took down Tracey,
so he's no pussy.
One more thing.
He's handy with a knife,
and he's some kind of sicko.
Gauged out Tracey's eyes.
Man, this just
keeps getting better.
What?
I need to go to the bathroom.
Well, you're just gonna
have to hold it, you old bag.
No, I mean, I really need
to go to the bathroom now.
What, you forget
your diapers, did you?
Bitch.
Come on, guys.
What harm can it do?
He's right. I think we're gonna
be here for a while.
Damn it.
Come on, Grandma Moses.
Where's the bathroom?
It's all the way down the hall.
Take a left.
Move it. Come on.
-Anything up?
-Just keeping my head down.
-Anymore cops?
-Not yet.
Well, she'll call for backup,
so it will get busy soon enough.
Shit's really
fucked up, ain't it?
Yeah.
But we still gonna
get out of here, right?
Yeah, that's the plan.
What?
Were you two separated
at birth or something?
Nope.
We're actually really close.
We grew up together.
Happy family.
So, what happened?
-We joined the military.
-Same unit?
No, we deployed at the same
time, but I was in the core.
Danny, he was always better
than me at everything,
so he ended up in the Rangers.
What, you go in as brothers
and come out as what?
Enemies?
I don't want to talk about it.
Come on, man.
We ain't got nothing better
to do for the next hour or so.
Go ahead, humor me.
Other than dodge
a fucking psycho
serial killer on the loose?
Yeah, there's that.
Wait, this is the men's room.
So take a fucking
dump in the urinal. Fucking bag.
Thank you, bitch.
Well, we both saw some
pretty fucked up shit.
At least, I know I did, and I think
Danny had the same, maybe worse.
We both came back in
one piece, but you know,
something like
that changes a man.
Lot of vets are really
fucked up in the head.
Me, I just learned that
life is short and crappy,
and you gotta take what you
can while you can, you know?
Hence the life of crime.
Yeah.
And your brother?
I guess after all
the mayhem and chaos,
he just wanted something
with structure in his life.
A little bit of order.
Did he know?
About you, before today?
No, no, I don't...
Nah, not really.
He knew I fell off the map.
So, let me get this straight.
While we out here doing all
this felonious bullshit,
your brother playing superhero
holding back the tides of chaos.
I never pegged you
for a philosopher,
but yeah, I guess, I guess we're
two sides of the same coin.
Time's up, old woman.
For fuck, I'm coming in.
Having a few problems, are ya?
Fuck.
I'm coming in,
you son of a bitch.
Come on, Allie, what the fuck?
I don't think
they're coming back.
Shut the fuck up.
They've been gone a long time.
Something's moving
around up there.
You don't know shit.
I know you need to keep
your eye on that vent.
I know you need to
shut your fucking mouth
and let me handle this, OK?
Just trying to help.
Boss.
They're everywhere.
So it begins.
Biggs, update.
I'm about done here,
machine room's next.
Time.
I'll know when I get there.
Took you long enough.
Yeah, we had to
stop for donuts.
So, what do we got, Detective?
Well, we've got multiple
perps with automatic weapons.
They know how to use
them, too, so I'm thinking
it's some kind of
military background.
-Possible hostages.
-Any comms?
No, not yet, but I
did talk to one of 'em.
Yeah, I know.
That photo you
e-mailed really got 'em
excited at headquarters.
Feds are taking a big
interest in these guys.
What are they doing here?
AJ, Allie, update.
This is AJ.
-What is it?
-Allie's gone, man.
What do you mean, gone?
She took the old
lady to the bathroom,
down the hall,
and she never came back.
Now you're telling me.
Hey, guys.
I think you're gonna want to
come in here and listen to this.
So, I've been scanning frequencies,
in case they're using radios.
-Put it on speaker.
-Yep, OK.
OK, AJ, sit tight.
We're getting out of here,
we'll find Allie after, OK?
Sit tight? We're being
picked off like flies here.
We've got to do something.
Like what?
There are four of us
and one of him.
We've got automatic weapons.
He's got a fucking knife.
Be patient, AJ.
This will all be over soon.
All right, but if
he does one more thing,
if anything else happens,
I'm going after him.
I mean, the eyes, man?
It's fucking disgusting.
You don't think...
This is LA, nothing
shocks me anymore.
I guess it's time
to talk to the cops.
Hey, Detective.
What's this?
Looks like you need to go
and talk to him, Detective.
Last time that
didn't go so well.
Well, then, it sounds like
you've already got a rapport.
-You surrendering?
-We need to talk.
I'm unarmed.
All right.
So, why don't you tell me
what the hell's going on here?
We got hostages.
How many?
Well, I can't tell you that.
How many of you?
I can't tell you that, either.
Well, that's great.
Quite the turnout
you've got here.
Yeah, when the LAPD gets
its head out of its ass,
we throw a real good party.
So, we have demands.
I'm sure you do.
I'll play. 747 at LAX?
Space shuttle, maybe.
Just a school bus.
And a medic for my guy.
You have two hours.
-School bus. Where to?
-Well, I can't tell you that.
No, of course you
can't tell me that.
So, what happens if we don't?
Then we start
shooting hostages.
Yeah, I don't really
think you're the type.
You don't know my type.
I'm guessing you served.
Core. You?
My husband.
He didn't come back.
IED out of Baghdad.
I'm sorry.
Which is why I don't understand why
guys like you do bullshit like this.
I mean, you made it back.
You should be doing
something good.
We all have our reasons.
-I'm sorry about your friend.
-Yeah.
I'll work on
getting you a medic.
-Thank you. What about the bus?
-What do we get?
Well, you give me the medic,
I'll start releasing hostages.
Fair enough.
I'm gonna go back inside now.
Semper fi, Detective.
Biggs, status update.
-It's gonna be a few minutes.
-All right.
We need to get the
hostages ready.
Go help AJ bring them down.
What about Allie?
Hostages first,
then we look for Allie.
OK. Hostages first.
Hey, Detective,
we're out back.
But there's no doors,
just a window.
Is it big enough
to get through?
I'm sure we could work it out.
You know what?
You guys stay there.
If this thing goes off,
you might need to go inside.
Roger.
-AJ.
-In here.
Get them on their feet.
Up, let's go.
Come on, move, let's go
for a walk. Let's go.
No ideas, OK?
I guess you talked
to Paul about me?
Yeah, well, we're not the same.
Yeah, I got that. You were with
the Rangers, right?
Once.
Yeah, so you got that
field medical training.
-You can stitch, right?
-Sure, but...
So, when I get your
ass downstairs, you gonna
-take care of my boy, right?
-Gunshot?
You gonna take care
of my boy Rick or not?
-You got a trauma bag?
-I got a first aid kit.
Well, then he needs a hospital.
There's nothing I can do.
See, that's the wrong answer.
When I get your ass downstairs,
you're gonna take
care of my boy Rick.
You're gonna stabilize him.
Now, they sending in a medic,
and that's what you're gonna do.
Let's go. Move.
Let's go. AJ.
The medic I get, but the bus?
Yeah. Seems too simple.
What's your take?
I think they're
up to something.
I just get the feeling
we're about to be had.
You know?
Who's this?
Looks like the feds
are crashing our party.
Captain Franklin.
This is Detective Pascal,
she's first on the scene.
I'm Sinclair, this is Chen.
These two, Smith and Jones.
Well, are the others coming?
We're it. One team, one crisis.
-That's not SWAT protocol.
-We're not SWAT.
-Then who the fuck are you?
-Detective.
-DOD.
-Contractors?
What the hell happened to SWAT?
SWAT is who cops like you call
when you get into trouble.
Who do you think SWAT calls?
I just smell the
testosterone from here.
-Let me tell you what we got...
-I know what you got.
You got him.
You know him?
Been chasing him for years.
When your detective
sent the photo through
for ID, all the lights went red.
So here we are.
All right, Chen, you go up high.
-Up there should be good.
-All right, Chief.
-Smith, you're it.
-Two minutes.
Jones, you're with me.
So, what is a master criminal
doing in a rinky dink
dump like this?
I mean the place isn't
even open anymore.
You don't know, do ya?
There's 100,000,000
in bearer bonds
in the safety deposit box,
it's cartel money.
Doesn't sound like
a cartel operation.
It's not. Our guy has been making
a career ripping off the cartel.
Must have a death wish
or something.
Anyway, this should have
been an easy job for him.
Something must have
gone wrong inside.
-Our lucky day.
-Yeah, about that.
-There's been a development.
-I'm listening.
There's a possibility
there's a wanted serial killer,
Windows,
operating on the inside.
Sounds like he's taken out
a couple of your man's crew.
And you know this for sure?
We intercepted
their radio traffic.
Ready to go, Chief.
We heard they
want a medic inside.
Smith's going in.
Now, wait just a minute.
This man is wanted by the LAPD.
That makes this
an LAPD operation.
I'm not gonna stand here and argue
jurisdiction with you, Captain.
You don't have positive
confirmation that this
Windows guy is even in
there, and the radio calls
you heard could be
deliberate misinformation.
What I know for sure is that
there's a very dangerous
armed criminal inside,
and your men do not have
the training or
equipment to take him on.
We do. You got a problem,
take it up the chain of command.
Until then,
this is our operation.
Clear?
Fine. Have it your way.
But this is still
a joint operation.
Detective Pascal
will act as liaison.
Get me headquarters.
Welcome aboard, Detective.
Move. Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Let's go, let's go,
Move, move, move.
Not you, you and me.
-Go.
-Sit down. Don't fucking move.
There he is, he's over there.
Stitch.
Washington.
It's Sinclair.
Must have been the picture
the detective took.
Shit's about to
get interesting.
Yeah.
So, what's the plan?
Smith will go in as a medic.
And get intel.
Chen will take over watch
and shoot out bad guys,
once he gets a clean shot.
Jones and me will breach.
What about the hostages?
We don't know that
there are any hostages.
Smith will tell us.
But it doesn't matter a whole
damn. We're gonna breach anyway.
This is pretty much the
worst idea I've ever heard.
It's gonna be a
bloodbath in there.
You're playing with the
big boys now, Detective.
This is how we roll.
Whatever happens in there,
is on you.
Damn right it is.
What happens if Windows
is actually in there?
Then we'll take him down, too.
-He's our caller.
-I'm going in with you.
Then you better get
a vest on, Detective.
Sorry about this, man.
You should have thought
about that sooner.
Best laid plans.
Boss, you might
want to come see this.
Here we go.
Put your hands behind your back.
You are?
-The medic you asked for.
-No, you're not.
You're Sinclair's guy.
AJ, take this medic
to the back room.
-You don't understand.
-Yeah, I do.
We've all read the same manual.
Get upstairs,
fuckface, let's go.
-Move!
Hurry up, asshole.
So, what's the
next play, Danny?
Why should I care?
Come on, you used to
be good at this stuff.
They're gonna breach.
They'd have sent a real
medic otherwise, man.
Yeah.
-We need to get him up.
-He's barely breathing.
He's better off out
there than he is in here.
-Hey.
-Looks like you're going home.
-Come on.
-I got you Rick.
Come on, come on.
There you go.
You OK?
Hold him steady.
You take care of him.
All right, come on.
Hey, Captain,
we got you some hostages.
Team two, go get 'em.
Everyone else cover.
-What about me?
-No, you we need.
Biggs!
Now's your
time to shine, boys.
I want you to go in the back
and tell me what you can see.
Yeah, we're on it, Detective,
but what if we make contact?
Observe and report only.
Do not engage these guys,
do you hear me?
Observe and report, my ass.
Fuck that, we're going in.
-All right.
-Get down.
One, two.
This room.
Now, you listen carefully.
You want to live?
You do everything I say.
Yeah, yeah, tough guy.
Shut the fuck up
and stand right there.
-Fuck you.
You do everything I tell you
and you won't get killed.
Sit down. Move!
How you doing up there, Chen?
Found my spot.
Setting up now.
Copy, let me know
when you're ready.
I could kill you
with my fucking teeth.
That's great, because I can
kill you with my fucking gun.
Hey.
On your knees.
Hello.
I said, "on your
knees," asshole.
I just need a
moment of your time.
Take one more
step and you die.
OK.
-You killed my friends.
-I saved them.
-You cut out their eyes.
-I just want to go home.
You should leave me alone.
Found an X-ray.
Good shot.
Stand by.
-You good?
-Let's go.
What have we got here?
What's taking him so long?
Biggs, tick tock.
Two minutes.
Yes.
All systems go, boss.
All systems go.
-I should kill you right now.
-Why don't you?
I'm not a murderer.
I'm not like you.
We're all the
same in God's eyes.
Just fucking shoot him!
I'll be with you in a minute.
-Shut up.
-Come on!
Shut the fuck up.
It took me a long
time to understand
that we're all the same.
The street punk, the
professional, like you.
The cop, the banker.
We're all the same.
Sinners.
And then God spoke to me.
Yeah?
What's He sound like?
You wouldn't understand.
It was like I suddenly
knew what I had to do.
You're fucking crazy.
I've been told so.
But you know what?
Maybe I'm the only
one who isn't crazy.
Did you think about that?
When God spoke to me,
He told me to save souls.
As many as I could.
Does that sound like
a bad thing to do?
God told you to cut
people's fucking eyes out?
Couldn't just preach,
join a fucking church?
He told me the eyes were
the windows of the soul.
And it was my destiny
to collect souls.
You see?
It's very simple.
God just spoke to me.
About fucking time.
X-Ray's about to
execute a hostage.
Green light, repeat,
green light.
Say hello to Tracey for me.
God protects
those who serve Him.
I just need
a moment of your time.
X-ray down, X-ray down.
Time to saddle up.
Keep your men outside,
whatever happens.
I don't know about this...
Listen, it's gonna be
crazy enough without your men
blundering around.
Just stay out of our way.
All right, but if
things start going south,
we're coming in.
Fair enough.
Ready?
Showtime.
Go.
Fuck you.
Hey, Paul.
You still with us?
That you, Sinclair?
You know this guy?
We go back a long way.
So, our mutual friends
and I were wondering,
did you get the stuff?
I got it.
It's right there on the counter.
So, it is.
Doesn't look like much.
Well, it's all there.
Shame you won't
get to spend it.
And you will, Sinclair?
You bring up a good point.
I don't think they'll miss it.
What's going on, Sinclair?
Just one of those macho moments
you like so much, Detective.
So, Paul, you know, the boys
aren't too happy with you.
Fifth time you've
ripped them off.
Sixth, actually.
Trenton, that was you.
We get around.
That's enough.
Really?
'Til I figure out what
the hell's going on,
you're under arrest.
I can see the wheels
turning, Detective.
So, let me guess,
you're not really DOD?
He's cartel, if you hadn't
already figured it out.
Is that true?
It's a gray area, but at least
you nailed a dangerous criminal.
We only realized what was
going on when you sent
that photo through,
so thanks for that, Detective.
You're welcome.
Jesus.
-What did you say?
-He said, "Run."
Looks like the
Calvary's arrived.
Hey, Detective.
Just in time, boys.
Like I told your
boss, Detective.
Stay out of our way.
Jones.
Over here.
-Don't be an idiot.
-Easy for you to say.
You don't have a fucking family.
Drop it.
We can all get
something out of this.
We'll just say Paul got
away with the money.
We'll split it three ways, it will be
a pretty good payday for all of us.
Good luck spending
it in Folsom, asshole.
It was just a thought.
I wouldn't worry
about me, Detective.
Give it up, Paul. There's
two of us and one of you.
It's time, don't you think?
You know he's right.
Fuck.
Well, you nearly did it.
Yeah.
Ten minutes, in and out.
It was supposed to be
the easy one.
Place like this, I didn't
think they'd miss it.
What was the back-up?
The elevator?
How did you know about that?
I'm not an idiot, Paul.
I read the building plans.
But you got it working?
Yeah, they bricked it up,
but they left everything there.
Smart.
Not smart enough, obviously.
No, sorry, Paul.
Paul?! Paul!
So, this is it?
Yeah, worth the trouble,
don't you think?
Yeah.
Sorry about your brother.
Go fuck yourself.
I'm starting to see
the family resemblance.
What are we gonna do with you?
If you're doing what
I think you're gonna do,
I'm the least of your problems.
But you can't be too careful.
Chen.
I'm here, I'm here.
It was always...
What the fuck?
Are you OK?
I've been better.
I got this, Detective.
Do me a favor.
Go put a bullet in him.
Absolutely.
What the fuck?
Danny, is that fucking you?
Don't fuck with me, Danny.
Danny?
Danny.
Hey.
Who the hell are you?
You're that fucking Windows guy.
I just want to go home.
I saw what you did to my men.
You should leave me alone.
Yeah?
Well, I think I'm
gonna do LAPD a favor.
Please.
Allow me to explain.
The eye is the
lamp of the body.
The lamp of the body.
So, if your eye
is healthy, your...
Stop right there.
You got to be
fucking kidding me.
Looks like you and me had
a pretty bad day, Danny.
That Windows guy is a
bit of a handful?
Yeah, not anymore.
Good for you.
So, now what, Danny?
You taking me in?
Those are my orders.
Your orders?
You, too?
There's stashes like
this all over the country.
There's always someone like me.
Nearby, keep an eye on things.
And you'd have stopped him?
-Your own brother?
-If I had to.
That's cold.
-That's a lot of money, Danny.
-Yeah, and then what?
Like I said, there's
always someone else.
Someone like me.
You shouldn't have killed Paul.
It's a bad world all around.
The eye is the
lamp of your body.
So, if the eye is
healthy, your whole body
will be full of light.
But if the eye is bad,
your whole body
will be full of darkness.
If then, the light
in you is darkness,
how great then,
is the darkness?