- Galleycat?
- Gawker.
- Slut.
- He's been out twice already.
Thanks.
Jack Bauman's office.
Oh, hi, Morgan.
Yeah, I'm sure he did read them.
Um, I did.
I thought it was amazing work.
So glad you could make it.
If you've got a minute,
let's go through my day.
- You know, I'm sure that he
would love to talk to you,
uh, but he's in a meeting
right now.
- And don't forget
to change my shrink appointment.
Got it.
- Oh, um, I need you to manage
another release for me.
- There's nothing
scheduled for months.
- It's for the e-book
of "waking eyes. "
We're tying in
the new edition.
- I thought that was
coming out next fall.
- A spot opened up
on "Charlie rose. "
We're moving it up.
Oh.
- I thought you'd be
the perfect person for the job.
What?
- Well, your father
is Milan's agent, right?
- Yeah, but...
- they sent me the arcs.
Get a list from publicity.
Let's put our heads together.
Alice?
All right, look,
I know it's not glamorous,
but I'm putting
my trust in you.
"Waking eyes" is the best seller
on our backlist.
All right, all right, look,
what if... what if
I read that manuscript
you've been
hounding me about, hmm?
- You will?
- Yeah, what's the girl's name?
- Karen Malone.
- Yeah, Karen.
- Malone.
- Okay.
- It's the best thing that
I've read since I've been here.
I said I'd read it.
Okay, but we have to hurry
because there might be
some interest...
- yes, Alan Mitchell,
please.
He's busy?
Ah. Well, fuck him.
No, I don't want
to leave a message.
- So you'll read
the manuscript this week?
Yes.
Hey.
You're doing
the "waking eyes" release?
- Did you know
they were moving it up?
Yeah.
That's the book
that made me love books.
I totally identified
with her.
Didn't you?
Alice?
- Well, these are friends
of my wife.
Nice to meet you.
- They've just
come over from some...
Hey, sport.
You having a good time?
- Sure.
- Say hi to everyone.
Hi.
- Alice wrote a terrific
short story last week.
She's gonna be
the real deal.
Oh, this is Milan Daneker.
This is my daughter, Alice.
Hi.
- It's a pleasure
to meet you.
- Milan is one of your mother's
undiscovered writers,
but he's written
a book, a good book,
and I'm going
to make sure it sells.
- Yes, please.
- Yes.
You got to meet Annette...
- All right.
- "Times book review. "
Lay a little
of that foreign charm on her.
- "She dodged
the forced laughter
and the vapid conversations. "
"If she could just"...
oh, sorry.
I-I was just looking around,
and, um...
It's okay.
Can I?
Really?
So how is it to grow up
like this?
Uh...
It's a little lonely.
That's what I thought, yes.
Yeah.
And you're
a writer too, yes?
Um...
I don't know.
- I would like
to read your story.
It's nothing.
- Why don't you
let me decide?
Well, I-I must...
okay.
- "If she could just make
herself small enough"...
"Completely unremarkable"...
Hi. Sorry.
- Here she is,
late as usual.
Mwah.
We were just discussing
this new film with, um...
What's his name?
Flavor of the month...
you know who I mean.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah. Have you seen it?
- Yeah, Sadie and I went to see
it last weekend, actually.
Mm-hmm.
And?
We... we kind of enjoyed it.
- I thought
you were smarter than that.
Did you know Alice
won a scholastic writing award
when she was 16?
- Really?
- We'd like to order now.
What'll you have, sport?
Oh, get the beef cheeks.
They're fabulous here.
She'll have the beef cheeks.
And you?
Pasta puttanesca.
- Oh, I'll have
the puttanesca.
You have
the grilled chicken. Maya?
- She'll have
the grilled cheese.
- No, no,
a half order of calamari
and some fries for her.
Yeah.
Make it a whole order.
Kids love fried stuff.
Here's to you, pal.
- Oh.
What are we celebrating?
- Independent booksellers
love the book.
Word of mouth is fantastic.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you very much.
- Oh, I love
watching you eat.
- I know, I know.
- You must.
You invite him to dinner
every night.
Anna.
That looks great.
So here's to me.
I discover talented writers,
develop them for years,
and then you steal them
away from me.
- Anna, you told me to get
a new agent.
- We're getting some great press
in the trades.
Milan is making headway
on the next one, right?
- Mm.
- Right?
- Yes.
- I'm talking to you.
You're drunk.
Fuck you.
- Your command of the English
language is astonishing.
Fuck you.
- I think
you said that already.
- Cursing was one of the first
words I knew in English.
- Really?
Who taught you?
The kid next door.
- Excuse me.
I'm going to go freshen up.
- Delicious, huh?
Mmm.
- Delicious.
- Mmm, mmm.
How's yours?
Come over here.
- Hello.
I'm here to see Jack Bauman.
- Oh, yes. Go right in.
- Okay, thank you.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my god, look at you.
Hey.
- Uh, what are you
doing here?
- I just finished my first draft
of my new book,
so I'm here to deliver it.
- What, are you kidding?
We would've sent someone.
- It's better in person,
isn't it?
Congratulations.
Finally,
something worth reading.
- Thank you.
- Come into my office.
It's been far too long.
- Hey, where'd you go?
- I'm coming. I'm coming.
- So is it done?
- Finally.
Great.
Alice, where's my lunch?
- Oh, uh,
Chez Louis, 1:00 P.M.
- If I'd known
you were gonna drop by...
- But maybe I could have lunch
with Alice.
- What?
- To celebrate.
- I... actually, I can't.
I've got...
- you have to eat.
- I really need...
- you could toss around
some marketing ideas.
- I... you know what?
Um...
She'd love to.
Please?
How are you?
Good, good.
Good.
So you're organizing the release
of the new edition, yes?
Ironic, huh?
It's nice.
Tell me about your day.
Uh...
You know...
School.
How was yours?
You know, writing.
I'm glad you could meet me.
Thank you very much.
When can I read your story?
It's, like, no big deal.
They, um...
they just printed it
'cause no one
really submits stuff,
and, um...
Um, they're
kind of desperate.
Come on.
This line here
is exactly
how it feels like
the first time you see someone
that you maybe love.
It's, uh...
You're a writer.
What about your writing?
I'm mostly not.
That's a shame.
I read your new bio.
It says that
you're teaching a lot.
Yes, I enjoy it.
I'm sure.
- You were my first
and best student.
I got to go.
Alice, I've missed you.
- Why don't you just say,
"hey, about that little thing
"that happened 15 years ago
that you never owned up to
"or apologized for
like you should have,
you motherfucker"...
sorry, Tyler.
- Okay, I should never
have told you.
Look, it's not a big deal.
But he hurt you, Ali.
You don't do publicity
for someone who hurt you.
It's my job.
- I thought your job
was to help find and edit
new and wonderful novels.
- Tell that to Jack.
- Why don't you?
Will you help me?
- Besides the fact that I think
it's a terrible idea,
what could I do?
- You're a successful
web designer.
Alice.
- Okay, fine. You're
a semi-successful web designer
whose best friend
thinks she's brilliant.
- Yeah, who gave up
her not-so-stellar career
to be a mommy.
- I need to build more
of a web presence for the book.
Oh, that's a great idea.
- Sadie, please,
don't make me do this alone.
- You're a real shit,
you know that?
Thank you.
All right, I need to go
and wrangle a radio spot.
Yay.
We didn't get to talk
about what you want to do
for your birthday.
- Hide in a closet
until it's over.
- You better have
a big closet.
You promised.
Come here, buddy.
Give me a hug.
I got to go. Hugs.
Alice, why are you always
running off somewhere
you don't want to go?
Oh, fuck off.
Sorry, Tyler.
All right.
- Bye. Call me later.
I will.
You want some?
Hello?
"It was a graceful
pas de deux,
"a dance of hate.
"He belittles her,
two, three.
She yells, two, three. "
Hello?
It's me.
This is the new story.
So, uh, I'm not really sure
about the ending.
It feels really forced,
and to me, the dialogue
is really bogus.
So...
Do you have a pen?
Yeah.
Thanks.
I can't watch.
Is that your homework?
- Uh, yeah. I have, like,
100 pages of American history.
Come over here, kiddo.
Come, let's read together.
It's good.
- You made notes all over it.
- I wouldn't bother
if it wasn't good.
But it can be better.
It's too abstract.
It's, um...
So it only becomes real...
If you give it
concrete details,
concrete details.
Look, here.
It's too abstract.
If you move that one...
Here we go.
- Okay, so who has material
to hand out for next class?
- I need one more
volunteer.
I brought in some new pages.
Um, Alice?
- I had this really
radical idea
for this super weapon
the Xorgots are gonna use
to destroy planet earth.
Just wait till you...
- it doesn't have
to be complete.
Maybe we could give
you some... some ideas or...
- Well,
if she doesn't have anything...
I'm sorry.
- Okay, Josh,
what are those aliens up to?
Oh, my...
look at that view.
It's beautiful.
It's, um...
Come.
So tell me
about your day.
Um...
School.
School?
- Uh, it's the same every day...
totally boring.
- Oh, not for me. You know,
for me, it's like a movie...
cheerleaders, boys
in team jackets, holding hands.
- No.
- No?
Mm-mm.
Um, people
don't hold hands anymore.
They just hook up.
- They hook up?
- Mm-hmm.
They hook up.
- And, uh,
no cheerleaders.
No, wait.
I guess we do have uniforms.
- Uniforms?
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, yeah.
- My best friend, Ruby,
just went Goth.
- She turned what?
- Goth.
- Goth?
- Mm-hmm.
- Uh-huh.
Well, what...
- you know, like, uh...
like, uh, black eyeliner
and ripped shirts.
- Oh, yeah?
- And, uh, her mom would
freak out if she knew,
so, she, um... she hides her stuff
in the hallway every day
before she leaves.
- Uh-huh.
- And, uh, um...
- Yeah?
Um...
Uh...
- And, yeah?
- You... you want to hear
about this?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
- Um, well, she says her mom
has no idea who she is anymore,
but maybe she never did.
Yeah.
So Thursday's a good day
for you?
- I guess so.
- Okay.
See you next Thursday, then.
I'm sorry, guys.
I know you're wasting
precious babysitter time.
I just want to eat
in front of the TV
and get sodden and pathetic.
- It is your day.
We will do whatever you want.
Thank you.
Together:
Surprise!
- I knew you were gonna
make us bring you home.
- Thank you. Aww.
I'm going to kill you.
Happy birthday.
You're really going to enjoy it
once you get used to the idea.
- Come on.
- Come on, help her blow it out.
One, two, three.
- Ooh, a little bit more.
Oh, oh. Yay.
One more, one more.
- Last one.
Whoo!
What?
What you writing?
My journal.
Come on.
Mm-mm.
I want to know you.
I can't.
One page.
Okay.
My heart is pounding.
I have to get up.
A kiss.
A real one.
- Oh, sorry.
- No, that's okay.
I was just...
I was reading.
Sorry. Do you need...
- no, no.
I-I was just looking
for a place to hide out.
My friend invited me.
I don't even know the girl
who this is for.
Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Well, happy birthday.
- Shh.
I'm trying to pretend
like I don't have to grow up.
- Is there anything
I can do to help?
Maybe.
Yeah.
Looks good.
So what are you reading?
Oh.
I love that character.
The female Holden Caulfield.
- Yeah,
that's what they say.
Not a favorite?
No.
- So why are you
sitting alone
in a bathroom
on your birthday reading it?
Work.
What do you do?
- That is not
an age-appropriate question.
- You're right.
I'm sorry.
Want some?
Definitely.
Alice.
Oh, Emmett.
Hi.
Hey.
What?
- You were right.
I did have a good time.
I'm glad.
- Hey.
Thanks for inviting me.
Yeah.
- Wait. You two
know each other?
- Uh, he was rob's
freshman year roommate,
but I actually met him first...
Freshman mixer.
Oh, right.
- You're kidding.
- No.
Okay. College, wow.
Let me help you up.
- Thank you.
Can I help with the cleanup?
No, no, no.
We got this.
You've done enough.
You recycle?
Uh, I plead the fifth.
What about your mom?
She stayed home with us.
Do you have sponges?
Uh, uh...
Sorry.
- Yeah, they've been married
35 years,
sometimes happily,
sometimes not.
They're abnormally normal.
- Wow. You're, like, some kind
of almost extinct species.
They should breed
you in captivity.
- So, aside from not being
environmental activists,
what's your family like?
Um...
Not much like a family,
I guess.
And?
Nuts.
Oh, that explains it.
Thanks.
- Look,
just so we're clear,
I don't really do nuts.
I'll keep that in mind.
Hey.
How do you take your coffee?
Black.
Okay.
I'll call you later?
- So, while he was building
a bionicle,
I posted on New Yorker books,
Paris review, Galleycat.
Uh, what else?
- How am I gonna thank you?
- Oh, I don't know.
Foot massage?
Not too high, Ty.
- So Alice grew up
and became
a wife and mother
just like everybody else.
Isn't that sad?
Yeah.
But it would make me sadder
if she hadn't.
Your face is chapped.
When you're near 30,
you have to moisturize.
Trust me.
Kissing.
What?
Too much kissing.
- Never say that
to a married person.
Emmett.
- Yeah, I guessed.
Look at you.
- What?
I'm so glad.
- It's terrifying.
- And exhilarating.
- Mom?
- What is it, baby?
- Jesus Christ.
- Mom?
Okay.
- Alice.
- Dad.
- I forgot I need a jacket
for this thing tonight.
Here, this was in the middle
of the living room.
It's not mine.
- Well, where the hell
did it come from?
God, it reeks.
I think it's Milan's.
Milan's?
- He was here
this afternoon.
- Did he bring by
a new draft?
- He, uh...
he came to see me.
You?
Yeah.
He's been helping me
with my writing.
- What?
Wha...
since when?
A while.
Well...
You couldn't have
a better mentor.
You're a lucky girl.
Yeah.
- I expect great things
of you.
Good night.
Okay, here.
So this lady,
she hasn't voted in 20 years.
She starts reading our most
outrageous quotes of the day,
sees her senator waxing poetic
about the benefits
of hydrofracking.
Immediately promises
to volunteer
for anyone
who will run against him.
- Wow.
- And this guy... oh, my god.
I love the way
they curse in the south.
- You do realize
you're a fanatic, don't you?
- Yeah, sorry.
- Mm.
- You, uh... you want some
of my pakora?
- Yes, I want to try
your pakoras.
- I approved your entry,
so you can post it anytime.
I'm the last one here,
so I'm gonna head out.
See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
- Bye. Thank you.
- It's nice to know
somebody
who actually likes
what they do.
I always wanted to be a writer
when I grew up.
Are you?
Grown up?
No, writing.
No.
How come?
- I sit there waiting to hear
the characters speak,
and instead,
I have this voice in my head,
saying, "this is shit.
This is shit. This is shit. "
Come on, that voice?
Everybody hears that voice.
It's the same voice
that says,
"I can't believe you just said
that, you fucking moron. "
Everybody hears that voice.
You think?
Yeah.
Most people just ignore it.
- Really?
I just...
Succumb.
Yeah?
I like a girl
who knows how to succumb.
Really?
Really.
Shit.
Ah.
Well, good morning.
This the new jacket copy?
- Yeah.
- Great.
- I thought that you...
- can you get Harold Blake
for me?
- Did you get a chance
to read Karen's manuscript?
- Uh-huh.
Not yet.
The Fisher book's exploding.
But you will this week.
- As soon
as I get a free moment.
Now, Milan did an interview
with the press office.
Can you see if he said anything
we haven't heard before?
This week?
- I'm sorry?
- This week.
Oh, yes, of course.
I really need to talk
to Harold.
Harold's on line one.
"The only real rule
of good writing is generosity. "
- Rule number one...
generosity.
You must be willing
to share yourself.
Oh, I brought you a present.
- You did?
Yeah.
It's a birthday present.
I wrote you a poem.
- I didn't know
you write poetry.
- I don't,
but you inspire me, so...
Come.
Um...
What do you think?
- Uh, it's... it's...
it's nice.
"Nice"?
- I have a... I have
a precalc test tomorrow.
Jesus, I hate this stuff.
- Alice?
It's okay.
- Okay.
I'm glad you liked the poem.
Anything we can use?
- Nothing that we
haven't heard before.
Damn.
Get me Susan
at Simon & Schuster.
Sorry.
So are you ever on time?
- No.
But, um...
I got you these.
Thanks.
- Oh, wow.
Alfred marks began working
at the white house
at the age of 28.
Good for Alfred.
Louise Van Der Zwan...
okay, stop.
- All right, stop.
What?
- Is this what you do
every Sunday morning?
You just sit here
and envy other people's lives?
- No, that is pretty much
a full-time occupation.
- You know
it's pointless, right?
Yes, I do.
You can't write in front of me.
- What?
- No, I'm serious. If anyone's
gonna write in my apartment,
it's going to be me.
But you don't.
- Thank you
for pointing that out.
- Come on, it's not
like there's a finite number
of words in the room,
and if I use them all,
there won't be enough
left for you.
- Why does everything you say
have to make so much sense?
It's fucking infuriating.
Okay, shut up now.
- Seeing
anyone special, sport?
Not really.
- You know,
having children
is the most satisfying thing
life has to offer.
Yeah.
How's the writing going?
Oh, you know...
There is a book that I read
that I thought was terrific.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I'm trying to get Jack
to read it.
Yeah?
- Um, well, I thought that
maybe you would have a look.
Maybe you'd want
to meet with the writer.
Jack hasn't read it?
- Don't worry about that.
I'll get him to read it.
I just... I just thought
you might want to meet with her.
Her name's Karen Malone.
She, um... she did "Iowa. "
She has this amazing
short story.
- No, no.
I'm going to call him up.
- No, dad. Please don't.
That's not what I meant.
- Well, I can fix it,
sport.
- Dad, dad,
I'll get him to read it.
I just wanted your opinion.
Okay.
- Dad, I mean it.
Don't call him.
- Okay, honey,
I won't call him.
Hey, tiger.
Are you having fun?
Huh?
Great work.
Um, Alice,
can you hang out a minute?
Look, do you want me
to refund your tuition?
What?
- It's past
the official deadline,
but I could ask them
to make an exception.
- It's not
that I'm not trying.
- Why don't you sign up again
when you feel like you're ready?
Thanks.
Yeah, I know he's doing a lot
of press right now,
but it would be great
if he could squeeze in
the "waking eyes"
re-release party.
Okay, no, I don't have
any confirmations yet, but...
I can hold.
- Is this
Jack Bauman's office?
- Yeah,
is he expecting you?
Karen Malone.
Karen, hi.
I'm Alice.
- Nice to meet you.
It's really nice
to meet you too.
- So could you tell him
I'm here?
- Hey, Karen,
come on in.
- Hi.
- Jack Bauman.
- So nice to meet you.
- Pleasure to meet you.
- Alice. Hi.
- Dad?
Am I late?
See, sport,
I told you I'd fix it, huh?
Can I take you to lunch
when we're through here?
- Ben, good to see you.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Karen.
- How are you?
- All right.
- Hi.
Uh, Keith.
I'm watching Tyler.
Oh, okay.
- We were at the park all day.
He's taking a nap.
- Um, I'm Alice.
- Yeah, um, hi.
Hi.
- Sadie's at, uh,
prenatal yoga.
Um, she'll be back in,
like, an hour and a half.
- Maybe you could just tell her
that I came by.
She could call me.
- Yeah, sure.
Okay.
You know what? Actually, maybe
I'll just check on Tyler,
if that's okay.
- Yeah, sure. Come on in.
- He's such a great kid.
- Yeah.
I... we read this in my, uh,
modern lit class last year.
Oh?
I didn't finish it.
- Well, you can have that copy
if you want.
It's kind of dated.
What?
Keith?
What the fuck are you doing?
- Uh, what are you
doing home?
- I decided to skip
deep relaxation.
Is there someone in there?
Um...
- Keith,
get out of here.
Okay.
Um...
You owe me 40.
- Now.
- Okay.
- What the hell
are you doing?
I don't know.
- He's a kid.
- I know.
- If Tyler had woken up,
oh, my god,
he would've been so confused.
- I know.
- What about Emmett?
- I know, I know.
I don't know.
- Hey, honey.
- Mama?
Yeah, baby?
Aunt Alice!
- Aunt Alice
has to leave now.
Okay.
- Still waiting
on that updated guest list.
I'm working on it.
You could have told me that you
read it, that you liked it.
That we're publishing it.
You are?
- I thought daddy
would've spread the word.
- Well, who are you
assigning it to?
I'm editing it myself.
- It's not
your kind of book.
Eh.
I found her. I...
Alice, that's your job.
You cull the good stuff.
I decide if it's good enough.
- Yeah, but listen,
I have some great ideas...
- ...shh. Now, listen, there's no
way I'm going to let
an inexperienced editor work
with an inexperienced writer.
- I've worked here
for two years.
- And how many books
have you edited?
My point exactly.
I will cc you in my notes.
You can come to me with
your thoughts anytime you like.
Now, listen, Milan is expecting
you at the taping tomorrow.
The new novel
is almost unreadable.
Make sure he sticks
to "waking eyes," okay?
You're the best.
- So 15 years.
- Mm-hmm.
- You've written seven novels
since "waking eyes,"
and none has become
the kind of cultural icon.
No, unfortunately not.
What do you think makes it
so perennially popular?
Um...
What I think it is, is that
everyone has been a teenager,
and...
We all know how out of kilter
it makes you.
- All right.
Is it...
okay, so are you gonna
tell me the secret now?
- All right, I think
I'm gonna actually tell you.
Come here for a second.
No one can hear this,
actually.
Mm.
What?
I have to go.
So go.
It's not important.
- So the question
I have to ask...
- Which I probably have answered
many times before, so go ahead.
Possibly.
How does a man in his 40s
perfectly capture
the essence
of a teenage girl?
Um...
This opening paragraph
is self-indulgent.
95% of writing is rewriting.
You know that.
And here, here's
another dangling preposition.
The way you mangle
the English language is...
look at this.
I'm the immigrant here.
- I was hanging out
with my friend. I forgot.
I'm sorry.
I do this because I believe
in your talent.
I know.
Come here.
I do this
because I love you.
- I know.
- Yeah.
I met a boy.
Oh, I'm happy.
So glad.
I want you to be happy.
What can I do
to make you happy?
We all like a mystery,
but there's
no mystery girl in it.
It's all fiction,
and, um...
At that time,
I did walk around in the city
and listen in on subways,
coffee shops...
- Mm-hmm.
- Streets, you know,
and I still do,
now and then,
listen in to see
if girls have changed.
You know?
- Hmm. And have they?
Some things never change.
- Hi.
Special delivery.
- What the hell
are you doing here?
No, no,
you need to go.
I have somebody coming here.
- Another time?
No, no.
Why?
- Look, I just turned 29.
- Really?
- And I guess it
messed with my head.
Shit.
- Hey.
- Hi.
This is Keith.
Yeah?
- Uh, he's
Sadie's babysitter.
Yeah?
- You her husband?
- Yeah.
No.
Keith was just leaving.
Yeah, um...
Sorry, man.
I got us some wine.
Alice?
- I went to Sadie's the other
day, and I forgot that.
And?
- Well, I told him
that he could borrow it.
- Before or after
you forgot it?
Emmett.
Did you...?
Fuck.
- Emmett, can...
can we just talk about it?
Please, it was the day
that I found out
about the manuscript.
I was really upset.
I am never gonna
to see this guy again.
Emmett. Listen, let's just
talk about it.
Emmett.
- I will not let you make me
as crazy as you are.
- Dad?
- Hey, champ, come.
Come and meet Alana.
- You must be Alice.
- Hi.
Sit, sit, sit, sit.
Alana is
a fantastic conductor.
Women are really coming
into their own in that field.
What about Maya, dad?
- I'm gonna see her.
Yeah.
Helene just needs a little time
to cool down.
Oh, dad.
Hey, hey.
You know how it is,
right?
Sorry. I just, uh...
Suddenly started
to just feel...
- Alice?
- Excuse me.
Alice.
What are you doing here?
I brought food.
- You know how precious sleep
is to me.
- I need to talk.
Sadie...
- Emmett is my friend,
and Keith is our neighbors' kid.
- Look, I'm sorry.
- Good.
I brought Dulce de Leche.
- You know I love you
more than almost anyone,
except Tyler and rob
and my mother... Sometimes.
But I'm starting
not to like you very much...
And I'd never
forgive you for that.
I need to not see you
for a while.
What about the book?
Screw you, Alice.
- You know what?
I...
can we just...
can we just not?
What?
I'm really tired.
- No, I don't...
I don't think so.
Okay.
- We did things.
- "Things"?
Things.
You hooked up.
Yeah.
Was it wonderful?
It should be wonderful.
Was it?
Mm...
- Please,
tell me about it...
come on,
how it was like.
Did he make you come?
I want to make you come.
I want to be first person
to make you come.
Come here.
Look at me.
Don't close your eyes.
Open your eyes.
That's not the way
we do it.
Look at me.
It's just something that I do,
that I've always done.
I see that look
in a guy's eyes,
like he wants me.
I don't know.
It's the only thing
that makes me feel real.
I want you.
I know.
So?
So it wears off.
Like...
I start wondering,
"what's wrong with this guy?
Why can't he do better?"
That is unbearably sad.
I know.
But I probably can.
Yeah.
Hey.
Give me a hug.
- I got a hose.
- Cool.
It's an ambush.
- Where's my hat?
I need to be protected.
Here you go.
- I can't not be your friend
for one more day.
With friends like you...
Honey, be careful.
- I figure if even you
can't put up with me,
I'm gonna have to do
something about it.
Yeah, you better.
- Aunt Alice,
emergency, emergency!
You're on fire!
- I am?
Say "help"!
Help.
Um, hi.
My name is Alice Harvey.
I am a volunteer
for people for the people,
and I'm calling you because...
This is such
an important election,
and it's so important
that you...
hello?
Hey, you made it.
Of course.
Come on in.
Hi, nice to meet you.
- Hi.
- Thanks for coming.
Everyone, listen up.
Let's take
a little five-minute break.
Put your phones down.
This is Emmett Grant,
who founded
people for the people.
He is the guy
that got us all here tonight.
Whoo-hoo!
- I didn't get you here.
You got yourselves here.
Everybody take a look
around the room.
I forgot to thank our hostess
for this evening.
Thanks.
Did you look around?
It's a room
full of people, right?
See, we reached out to you.
Tonight you're here.
You're reaching out
to others,
and then with any luck,
those others are
gonna reach out
on election day
and fill in the right bubbles,
and maybe together,
we can change
the political landscape.
If not...
We can because it's
the reaching out that matters.
It's the reaching out that
scares the shit out of them,
even when our guys don't win.
So please, please,
just keep reaching out.
Thank you.
- Whoo-hoo.
- Yeah!
- Awesome.
That was a really nice speech.
- I should have known.
- Listen, I love you both.
- You've got
about five minutes.
- How could you use this event
for personal reasons?
That's not fair.
I wanted to help you. I know
how important this is to you.
Keep calling.
Emmett...
- no, actions
have consequences, Alice.
Hey, we got to move on.
I'm reaching out.
I have to go.
- Please, please, please,
just keep reaching out.
- What would you like,
sport?
- I'd like to start
with the arugula salad, please.
- You know, the duck
is fabulous here.
You should try it.
- And I'd like the filet.
- Why don't you bring her
the duck?
Milan...
You want to tell them?
It's all your doing.
Bullshit.
Bookseller preorders for
"waking eyes," unbelievable.
We may have a best seller
on our hands.
- Oh.
- You're a genius, pal.
- Hayworth's
marketing department is.
- Okay,
so we're all geniuses.
Please pass the rolls.
Sylvio is good,
but not if he doesn't have
something great to sell.
- Could you pass
the rolls, please?
- Would you just stop
kissing each others' asses
and enjoy the moment?
- Do you have to be
so crude?
so smug?
I'm happy.
Not that you'd have any idea
what that feels like.
- Mm-hmm.
I wonder why.
- Actually, I'd like
to stick to the filet.
Okay, sport.
And duck for me
and a side of spinach.
So can anybody explain to me
the appeal
of that... that... that guy
in that movie.
Oh, jeez, you know the one,
the one that won best picture.
- I can messenger a copy
over today.
Yes, I will hold.
Hi.
Um, one second.
Uh, yeah,
I'll send it right over.
Okay, great.
Thanks.
- My agent said
that you gave him my book.
Shit!
- I'm not sure
I did you any favors.
- I was actually working on
something new before all this,
and, um, I would love
if you could take a look.
Yeah?
It's my first chapter.
- I-I'd love to.
Um...
- Great.
- Thank you.
Look into the camera.
Wave to the camera.
- Yes, Greenstreet
is coming.
Terrific.
How many guests will that be?
Okay, great.
Thanks.
Alice.
- He's just finishing up a call.
He should be right out.
Could I take you to lunch?
Why?
- Sorry to make you wait.
Hot off the presses.
One for you.
It's got the new dedication.
- Oh, that's great.
- Nice, huh?
Come in, come in.
- "Still she haunts me
phantomwise,
"Alice moving under skies,
never seen by waking eyes. "
Milan Daneker...
he'll be reading
from his new novel,
"waking eyes. "
Mr. Daneker.
- Thank you, Martin.
- Mm-hmm.
Sorry.
Yes.
"She was slouching
under the weight
"of a too-big book bag,
"cracking her gum fiercely
"like a line of defense.
"But her eyes cried out,
'love me.
Oh, please, love me. '"
"'a little lonely,'
she said.
"'My mom has no idea
who I am anymore,
"but maybe she never did. '
"she swayed
with a graceful pas de deux,
"the dance of hate.
"She was small enough.
"She was invisible to them
and always would be.
"Her eyes opened
wider and wider
"as she came,
brimming with surprise"...
"Pleasure,
and ineffable sadness. "
Thank you.
Alice?
Alice, what is it?
- I have to tell
you something.
Fantastic night.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You're a natural.
- No, I was terrified.
- You were great.
Wasn't he great?
- Mm-hmm.
Yes,
it went very well.
- I can't believe
that woman
from the New York review
of books was there.
She was interesting.
- She was eating
out of your hand.
Ben.
Alice, um...
Your mother
told me what you said.
I had to.
- Yes, I told him
it wasn't true.
What?
- It isn't true?
- It's what he said.
I asked him.
He said it's understandable.
Yes.
Like I told him, you maybe
misinterpreted it somehow.
- Is that what it is,
Alice?
- I think it's
what you wish were true.
- Alice?
- Stop the car.
- It's perfectly natural
to have feelings for someone
that you look up to.
- I'm flattered.
- I really... I don't know
what to think anymore.
- He said he may have used
details from your life...
Writers are magpies.
- To make the character
more real.
Please stop the car!
Alice.
Alice!
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Are you okay?
Alice?
Are you all right?
Oh, please, please.
It's, um...
- is this the new book?
Yeah.
- Whose life did
you appropriate this time?
No one.
Uh, well, there's bits
and pieces here and there.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
- It was such
a long time ago.
What?
What...
- Alice.
Was such a long time ago?
Concrete details.
You must give me concrete
details to make it real.
- I know at that age,
little things seem enormous.
Your warm...
Heavy arms around me...
The smoky taste
of your tongue in my mouth.
I was helping you.
- The feel of your hard-on
against my thigh.
- But nothing really happened.
- Yes, it did!
- Yes, well, you seemed
to enjoy it at the time.
- You were one
of the few people who ever...
Actually seemed to see me...
To make me feel real
and important.
- But you are.
- You used me.
- Oh, come on.
- You abandoned me.
- Alice...
- you made me feel
like I was nothing
all over again.
- Not nothing.
It's...
It's a beautiful character.
I know.
And I've been living
in her shadow for 15 years.
Good-bye, Milan.
Hey, Emmett.
What?
Come here.
- What?
Did Jeff screw up again?
- No, I just got
a Google alert.
- Reaching out scares
the shit out of them,
even when
our guys don't win.
So please, please, please,
just keep reaching out.
Because I love you.
- Gentlemen.
How are we?
Where's Alice?
- I haven't seen her yet.
Sadie?
Where the hell is Alice?
- She had something better
to do.
- What?
- Wait. Who are you?
Her best friend.
Are you ready to read,
Mr. Daneker?
I am.
Walk this way.
Some old lady
with a slight beard
let me in.
Mrs. Rayburn.
Oh.
Emmett...
I'm sorry that I hurt you.
Thanks.
- I might not be ready
to take on the world,
but I think...
That I can remember...
To think
about one other person.
Yeah?
I'd like that to be you.
I'll think about it.
Okay.
100 was really good.
- You're the girl
in the book, aren't you?
Not anymore.