SEOUL, KOREA 1992
NEW YORK CITY 1998
Mikey Mike!
You fucked up one heII of a wet dream
getting me up this Iate at night.
Yo, Pozzo!
I hear you've got
some business for me.
Mike, Pozzo, you two take a seat
and wait for a moment.
Something Iooks wrong, shoot it.
Let's take a waIk, eh?
- So...Tony?
- Yeah.
Mike says that he did business
with you, he says you're smart.
I get by.
You know, and he says
he knows you from the oId days,
you know, back in the neighbourhood.
Funny thing is, I don't beIieve him.
I don't think he did know you.
I think you taIked him
into knowing you.
I can't heIp what you beIieve.
Let's taIk in there, huh?
So...
What was that about?
I'm from the Bronx and I've never
fucking heard of you. Why is that?
- It's a big pIace.
- You don't Iook ItaIian, Tony.
My mother was Irish, aII right?
- You want to do business with me?
- Yeah.
You can start by giving me your gun.
- Is there a point to aII this?
- Yeah, there is.
I don't know you
and I don't fucking trust you.
- FeeI stupid yet?
- Shut the fuck up. Spin it around.
I haven't had a good game of grab-ass
since I was in County.
Shut up, cocksucker!
NormaIIy...
it pisses me off
when you two don't stay put.
Today it was OK.
What's with Tony?
Tony?
Tony's a fucking cop.
Shoot him.
I'II be outside.
Do me a favour. Make it quick.
Tonight's been fucked up enough
aIready.
Mikey Mike, what's up, man?
Mike!
Come on, what's up with him?
- You beIieve this fucking guy?
- What?
Come on, you remember I used to...
I knew your sister, MicheIIe.
She used to go out with my friend Ricky.
Remember Ricky? Ricky Lamato?
We used to caII him Rick Big Dick
because he had that big...
Next one goes through your skuII,
cop-kiIIer.
God damn it!
Better hope the next cop through that
door is as compassionate as I am.
Fuck!
Every cop's worst nightmare, huh?
How are you going to handIe it?
- She don't mean shit to me.
- Don't kiII me!
Shut the fuck up!
I am taIking to this man.
I'm not fucking around here, asshoIe.
If I have to kiII her just to ruin
your fucking day, I'II do it.
You know, I'II never Iet this go.
I know.
Hey, Tony...
Are you a good CathoIic?
Then absoIve yourseIf of this.
No!
Captain wants to see you, Tony.
- Listen, man, we aII know you...
- Thanks, Dion.
Tough night, Tony.
A Iot of undercover work
down the drain.
A cop and a civiIian dead and onIy
two Iow-IeveI skeIIs to show for it.
I don't have to teII you
how shitty this Iooks downtown.
No Iectures, no reprimands.
I'II just get to it.
You're off the case.
You've bIown your cover.
We want to put you
back on homicide detaiI.
We don't feeI your judgement on this
right now is too sound.
Here are your options:
take two weeks off
or catch whatever Homicide
has cooking.
That cop and that civiIian...
They're dead because
of something I started.
Let me finish it.
Look, Luca, it's not going to happen.
- So what's it going to be?
- I want to work.
That's what I figured.
So I want you to catch this case.
Murder down in LittIe Tokyo,
happened Iast night, very nasty.
Masayuki Noda,
No. 3 man in the IocaI yakuza.
Looks Iike they prettied up the site
before it got caIIed in.
ProbabIy removed
any worthwhiIe evidence.
Edwards is on his way there.
Check it out.
Yes, sir.
- Tony...
- I know.
He was just Iike that?
This must have been some kind of war.
- What are you doing here?
- Don't ask.
- How many guys in on the hit?
- One.
- One?
- Armed with what?
- Some kind of sword, or something.
- Yo, Ginger.
- What are you doing here?
- Don't ask. What have you got?
- Been dead about ten hours.
Ten hours.
- Cause of death?
- You're kidding, right?
Victim Noda Masayuki, estimated time
of death, 2400 hours on October 23rd.
Massive throat wounds
suggest exsanguination
with concomitant respiratory faiIure.
What have we got on Noda?
Before exsanguinating here, he was
head of the Umura Trading Company.
Big yakuza front.
Man had a Iot of juice. Most of it
wound up aII over the street, though.
- Any witnesses?
- Just one.
A working girI with a serious case
of seIf-preservation.
She said he was fast in and out,
didn't have a gun.
Other than that, she didn't say much.
We canvassed the neighbourhood.
Nothing.
AII right, thanks, Steve.
I'II see you back at the station.
Tony! Come here.
I want to see you in my office.
Tony, this is Inspector Kim
of SeouI PD.
He's here to assist you
on that LittIe Tokyo homicide.
Who invited him to the party?
He has some insight into the case
that may heIp you.
He's been kind enough
to come here from Korea.
He'II act as an observer,
give you a few pointers.
Oh, an observer.
He gets to screw up the case, then go
home and Ieave me with my pants down.
You're Iooking at a feIIow officer
who's traveIIed a Iong way to heIp.
You've got a crime to soIve.
Get to it. Inspector Kim, thank you.
And Iet me know if Detective Luca
is anything but supportive.
Man was kiIIed.
Very bad.
In LittIe Tokyo.
You want see fiIe?
Great. I'm working with CharIie Chan.
CharIie Chan is Chinese. I'm Korean.
If you're going to insuIt me,
at Ieast get it right.
In Korea, I outrank you.
I'm here because you asked for heIp
on the poIice internet.
We have a poIice force
of our very own here
and we do this kind of stuff
aII the time.
- CouIdn't you have just sent a fax?
- No.
I'm here to stop a kiIIer.
Detective Luca.
Luca...you don't Iook ItaIian.
My mother's Irish, OK?
- Where are we going?
- The Umura Trading Company.
If the No. 3 guy got whacked, Nos. 2
and 1 are probabIy a IittIe nervous.
- This is your car?
- Yeah.
At Ieast it's fucking American.
Sounds good.
Hi.
- Can I heIp you?
- Detective Luca to see Mr Nakai.
Just a moment, pIease.
You may go in now.
- Mr Nakai?
- Detective Luca, I assume.
They informed me at the front
you were on your way.
- Who is your friend?
- Inspector Kim from the SeouI PD.
TeII me, Mr Nakai,
how come aII the security?
We Iive in difficuIt times.
And it's getting tougher, too, isn't it?
Yes. PIease, have a seat.
- Thank you.
- What can I do for you?
WeII, we just wanted to ask you a few
questions about Mr Noda's death.
- A terribIe thing.
- Yeah.
TeII me, do you have any Ieads?
We hope that you couId point us
in the right direction.
Is there anything going on in your
company that we shouId know about?
Any hostiIe takeovers,
anything Iike that?
No, Detective.
And I assure you, we are weII
prepared for any such occurrence.
This is reaIIy stupid.
They are yakuza. They won't taIk.
You know, Detective,
you I understand being here.
But teII me, why bring him in here?
He was supposed to cIean
the murder site and Ieave no cIues,
but he faiIed, and you found one.
He knows that's why I'm here.
And he Iost face
with Mr Nakai and with me.
You know it was BIack Lotus.
Kuranai is here.
Admit it.
Just admit it. Admit it!
Otherwise I'II beat it out of you.
Hey!
Admit it! Admit it!
God damn it! No!
What's the matter with you? We just
wanted to ask a few questions.
What the fuck was that?
Out! Out!
Thank you for your cooperation,
Mr Nakai. And sorry about the ceiIing.
- What the fuck was that aII about?
- You wouIdn't understand.
You'd better fucking weII
make me understand.
Look, whatever beef
you've got going on here,
it doesn't concern me.
I got this case shoved down
my throat, and you aIong with it.
I've got other things
I'd rather be doing.
Now, you got something
you want to say to me?
Fine. Fuck it!
If that's what you want,
that's the way we'II pIay it.
But don't you ever hang my ass over
a raggedy edge Iike that again. Ever.
- What did he want to know?
- I'm not reaIIy sure.
Matsuyama-san, I'm just a businessman.
AII this gang warfare...
- Shut up!
- Yes, sir.
I think you shouId stick to your business.
PIease forgive me.
You're a man, aren't you?
So behave as one!
Yes, sir.
What was that BIack Lotus crap
the Korean was taIking about?
I thought you said
the guineas hit Noda San.
BIack Lotus Iike the Ninja.
It's a Iegend from Iong ago.
- What? What are you Iooking at?
- Your face.
What do you want?
A date or something?
No, I was just thinking.
I Iike it better that way.
Fuck you, too.
This is a personaI matter. Wait here.
Isn't this part of the investigation?
It's part of an investigation.
Wait here.
It is my duty to go with you.
Yo, AngeIo!
Tony, hey!
- StiII driving that piece of crap?
- Yeah.
- Who's your friend?
- Hi, I'm...
- Nobody. He's doing my Iaundry.
- Oh, Iisten, Tony.
You're in a worId of shit, right?
Word is out about you and Rocco.
Everybody knows you're a cop, man.
Everybody wants your bIood.
The feeIing is mutuaI.
No, you see, Tony,
you don't understand.
NormaIIy, someone undercover
gets inside, they shrug it off.
It's the high price
of doing business. But this...
This is, Iike, so fucked up.
What are you Iooking at, huh?
- Take a fucking waIk!
- OK.
So, what's so fucked up?
Fucking Rocco was in troubIe
to begin with.
Now this...
He Iooks Iike shit.
He's fucking squeezed, he's pissed,
he's Iosing his fucking mind.
He was never too stabIe
to begin with.
- Have you seen him? Is he around?
- Have I seen him here? No. Fuck, no.
If he was, it wouId onIy
make matters worse.
Tony, you bringing
your friend here...
- That don't happen.
- Forget him.
These peopIe have crossed Iines
that shouIdn't be crossed.
I mean, the turf is smaII enough
to begin with.
Fucking yakuzas.
They're pushing, man.
Pretty soon, the FamiIy
is going to push back.
I've seen nothing Iike this since the
Cassini brothers got whacked in '85.
I'm teIIing you,
something is going to happen.
Something big and so fucking bad
is going to...
- AngeIo, just caIm down.
- Sure.
Listen, Tony...
Do me a favour and get him out of here
before it starts in my pIace of business.
What are you Iooking at? Huh?
You're in my booth. Get up.
Come on, pIease.
PIaytime's over, boys.
Listen to your fucking friend, gook.
Or don't the gook speak EngIish?
Yeah, I speak EngIish.
And I'm a cop.
Ooh, big fucking deaI.
Whoa, whoa!
Fuck!
Get the fuck out of here!
Get the fuck out!
- You make friends everywhere you go.
- They were disrespectfuI.
In my country, no poIiceman
wouId ever be treated Iike that.
You know what? This isn't your
country and you're not a cop here.
So if you don't Iike it, go home.
I've got a crime to soIve
and you are nothing but in my way.
You and I are going
to come to an understanding.
You want to fight somebody so badIy,
fight me.
- I don't want to fight you.
- Then teII me what's going on.
What happened in Nakai's office?
What do you know about Noda's death?
I toId you, you wouId not understand.
It is my duty to be here.
- I have no choice.
- You won't teII me what's going on?
- No.
- Fuck you!
You Iisten, Inspector Kim, because
this is the short and the sweet.
You're either going to spiII a IittIe
truth or spiII a IittIe bIood.
- What's it going to be?
- You're the onIy one who wiII bIeed.
You are a terribIe poIiceman.
No wonder this country is fucked.
Knock it off before I caII the cops.
I am a cop.
His name is Kuranai,
which means ''empty bIackness''.
He is the deadIiest assassin
that ever Iived.
How do we find him?
We must go back to the yakuza
and start there.
GentIemen.
I'm gIad you have returned.
I was hoping for the opportunity
to apoIogise for Mr Sato's behaviour.
I apoIogise, too, Mr Nakai.
You know why we're here.
Yes.
Detective Luca, our hoIdings at
the Umura Trading Company are vast,
but we are undercapitaIised.
We fooIishIy sought out
certain partners
whose cash resources
were greater than our own.
We had IittIe idea then
what we were getting invoIved with.
Now our partners
have aII but taken controI.
Their aspirations here in America
are great.
Their ambition has brought them
at odds with another company.
A company I beIieve
you are famiIiar with.
Now this rivaIry grows bitter. What
was once competition may turn to war.
There is simpIy not enough space
nor money to go around.
Now I beIieve there is
a third party invoIved.
A competitor more ruthIess and
power-hungry than the other two combined.
We can stop aII this.
We can put an end to it.
But we need your heIp.
There's nothing I can do.
And, Detective, ''So fouI a sky
cIears not without a storm.''
- When's it going to happen?
- Tonight.
Nakai, the yakuza's No. 2 man,
wiII die.
You sure you peopIe
know what you're doing?
- I beIieve we can handIe it.
- Maybe.
But I'm not the one to bet
my Iife on it, so don't fuck up.
- Too many peopIe wiII be watching.
- Let them.
I work just as weII with an audience.
So, Sato San,
you figure it was the Eyeties
that hit Noda San?
Yeah. No one eIse
wouId have the baIIs.
ApparentIy not.
I have been waiting for you.
Tony, Inspector Kim.
What have you got?
Hey, Captain.
Five dead, aII yakuza.
This one's Nakai.
We questioned him this afternoon.
It's a fucking mess.
- What do you think happened?
- I don't know.
The yakuza and the Mob
have got a squabbIe...
These murders were committed
by the man who kiIIed Noda.
This has nothing to do
with your Mafia.
Something I need to know here, Tony?
Nothing yet, Captain.
Kim's got a hunch who's behind this,
but we've got nothing usabIe.
- We're working every angIe, though.
- Good.
Listen. These pukes want
to off each other, I don't much care.
But it's one thing when it happens
in some back aIIey
and something eIse when
it's in front of a bunch of diners.
If this is a war between the Mob and
the yakuza, the shit is truIy going to fIy.
I took a Iot of heat putting you back
in rotation after that girI got kiIIed.
You Iet me down on this
and we both fry.
You'd better be working
on more than just some fucking angIe.
We cannot have a war
between the Mob and the yakuza.
- I know.
- CIear?
CrystaI.
My favourite cousin
actuaIIy comes to see me.
I'm so busy at the restaurant.
So, to what do I owe
the honour of this visit?
PauI, you know I hate to bother you.
The other day, a coupIe of guys
come into my pIace,
one of them a sIope,
and they try to shake me down.
Now, you know me. NormaIIy, it's, Iike,
''Out of the fucking store!'' Right?
But I don't know. With these guys...
Why didn't you bring this to me
sooner?
I was scared.
They said they was gonna
burn my store down if I toId you.
Fucking yakuzas! How Iong
are we going to Iet this shit go on?
How fucking Iong? I'm teIIing you,
I'm sick and tired. Capisci?
So far they ain't pushed too hard,
PauI. Just turf shit.
But AngeIo's pIace, that's going too far.
- Maybe it's time we sent a message.
- Yeah, we might.
Let's just see where this thing goes,
huh?
Fucking yakuzas!
You aII right?
I must find Kuranai.
I think I know something
that wiII make you feeI better.
Come on.
I have to apoIogise to you, Detective.
I know I have been difficuIt.
Yeah, you have been
a royaI pain in the ass.
But, since we're off duty,
why don't you caII me Tony?
Thank you, Tony.
When I said we were hunting
a man, Kuranai,
I spoke from experience.
I know this man.
Years ago, I investigated
a crime syndicate
caIIed the BIack Lotus Society.
Most say they do not exist,
but they are reaI,
and very dangerous.
They work in the shadows,
keep everything totaIIy secret.
I knew someone was taking over some
of the great Triads in the yakuza.
I dug deeper
and got cIoser to the truth.
And then, someone noticed.
So then what happened?
I was to be an exampIe.
A warning.
Kuranai is an assassin
for the BIack Lotus Society.
I was obsessed with the BIack Lotus
and worked Iate one night.
It was my wife.
And my son crying.
Then nothing.
I got home as fast as I couId.
I was too Iate.
I drank too much, my career suffered
and Kuranai achieved his goaI.
I stopped investigating
the BIack Lotus.
But I never forgot.
I wiII never stop hunting
the man that kiIIed my famiIy.
That is why I'm here. To kiII him.
I wiII not rest untiI I feeI
his bIood fIowing through my hands.
Obsession.
I have some experience with that.
Inspector Kim, do you...
do karaoke?
You know what?
In Korea, they caII me EIvis.
You want to hear?
Thank you very much, Detective Luca,
for such a great night.
- I toId you to caII me Tony.
- OK, and you caII me Tony, too.
- Tony Two. Tony Two.
- Two Tonies!
- Hey, taxi!
- Hey, taxi! Stop here!
- Taxi!
- Oh, that's just great.
Scumbag!
That's good pronunciation.
- Did you see who it was?
- No, it happened too fast.
TeII you what, Inspector Kim.
It's time we changed the ruIes.
I'm getting tired of being a target.
Let somebody eIse wear a buIIseye.
I agree.
Next time you get tanked,
do it cIoser to home.
That way, you don't waste taxpayers'
money getting back to your car.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Morning, sir.
Great.
Damn! It was fine yesterday.
Get out of the car.
Get out! Right now!
UsuaIIy, they just tow.
Tony, what the heII is going on?
''You stiII driving
that piece of crap, Tony?''
Remember asking me that, AngeIo?
I'm not driving it any more.
I don't know what you're taIk...
I know you're pIaying both sides of
the street. I want to know with who.
Suck my dick.
You've got about two seconds to taIk,
so you'd better start now.
I don't know nothing.
I don't know nothing!
It was fucking Rocco!
Him and some other guy, some sIope.
They came in the night before you did
and they made me teII them.
They tried to off me.
I don't care why you set me up.
- What did the Asian Iook Iike?
- I don't know, man. It was...
It was dark, you know, and I...
Don't, don't!
I didn't get a chance to see him.
Tony, I swear.
Look at me! Look at me!
I'm Iooking at you!
Where's Rocco?
Fuck!
I don't know.
The FamiIy's Iooking for him, too.
OK, Tony? Tony, I'm scared.
I don't fucking know, Tony.
Hey, Tony...
What are you going to do with me?
I won't offer it,
but if anybody asks,
I'm going to rat you out
for every shitty thing you ever did.
Every turn you ever made,
every name you ever gave up.
Every mobster in town's going to know
that you're my informant.
The river is coId and deep, AngeIo.
You think about that.
You think about that,
and you pray that nobody asks.
- Who is this Rocco?
- He's my probIem, not your concern.
As Iong as I'm with you,
he's my probIem, too. I want to know.
Mafia. He was muscIe
for the Fiorino famiIy.
He was wheeIing and deaIing
on the side.
Drugs, prostitution, extortion.
You name it, he was into it.
I was working undercover,
trying to get next to him.
But when I finaIIy made contact,
everything went sideways.
A cop and an innocent bystander
were kiIIed.
Your informant said that Rocco
visited him with an Asian man.
Do you think
it might have been yakuza?
AngeIo's a Iying shit, but he's right
about the FamiIy and the yakuza.
If Rocco was in troubIe with the Mafia,
he wouIdn't turn to the yakuza.
If not the yakuza,
what about their enemy?
BIack Lotus Society aIways takes over
syndicates by kiIIing their Ieaders.
I don't know, Kim.
I reaIIy don't know.
I'm tired of thinking about this shit.
I couId use some reIaxation.
- Are you game?
- Sure.
Nothing Iike it.
In an hour,
you'II feeI Iike a miIIion bucks.
- Hey, Tony, what's with Bruce Lee?
- Bruce Lee is Chinese. I'm Korean.
You want to spar a few rounds?
Nah!
TeII me, Kim, why did you
become a cop?
My father.
He was the youngest Chief Inspector
ever in the SeouI poIice.
There was no question
that I wouId foIIow him.
What about you, Detective Luca?
- I joined because of my father, too.
- Oh, he was a poIiceman?
Mafia.
He was a made man.
He was a butt man
for the Fiorino famiIy.
He spiIt a Iot of bIood.
- Where is he now?
- He's dead.
My mother, too.
They were gunned down.
They were both dead
before they hit the ground.
I never reaIIy knew my father.
I guess I figured I'd get him back
by being a cop.
Go after the Mafia.
Try to make up for
the things that he did.
You know, Tony, you are not
responsibIe for what your father did.
No more than you are
for what the Kuranai did.
We have fuIfiIIed
our side of the bargain.
- It is time for you to fuIfiI yours.
- Don't worry about it.
Your attempt
to bIow up Mr Luca faiIed.
Save your concern
for something that counts.
Like the No. 2 guy in the FamiIy,
Spano. He's Fiorino's right-hand man.
BeIieve me, Mr Rocco,
we are monitoring that situation
with great interest.
That situation
is about to get popped.
It's so quiet.
- Nobody messes with the Church.
- Right.
I appreciate your coming here
with me.
- I'm just going to be a second.
- OK.
I Iike this pIace.
I think I wiII take a second
of my own.
- Kim, are you a gambIing man?
- Yeah.
What do you say we hedge our bets
a bit before we go?
I'II throw something out to Buddha
and you see
what you can do with God.
OK. CIap twice to make sure
your god is Iistening.
Mr God, we wouId appreciate it
if you don't kiII us
in the next few days.
And...pIease buy Tony a new car.
Thank you.
- My turn?
- Yeah.
Yo, Buddha,
pIease Iet the bad guys
catch the grief this time around
and heIp us kick some serious ass.
Amen.
- You throw a good baII, Mr Spano.
- I hooked it.
You kissing my ass
won't stop me from kicking yours.
Anyway, what do I aIways say?
- AIways Ieave one standing. I know.
- Yeah.
That one pin's going to teII
everybody what a badass I am.
Scare 'em shitIess.
Heads up!
Heads up.
God damn it!
Shit.
- What's your hurry there, Bobby?
- Rocco, you motherfucker!
Bobby, don't be Iike that. Come on.
You don't think we knew about you?
You won't Iast two days out there.
Bobby, I used to handIe
aII your paper.
I know who's out there.
I'm not worried.
I can't beIieve you turned.
After aII the FamiIy's done
for you, you fucking...
If it wasn't me,
it'd be somebody eIse.
What's the difference?
It's just business.
Hurts, huh, Bob?
AIways Ieave one standing.
Not tonight.
Son of a bitch.
Fucking Bobby's dead.
Son of a fucking bitch!
- Who fucking did it?
- We don't know, Mr Fiorino.
But he took everybody out
in the pIace. Not one...
The fucking yakuzas did it!
That's who fucking did it!
You get everybody now.
We're going to fucking war.
That's Bobby Spano.
Was Bobby Spano.
He's a capo in the Fiorino famiIy.
What a bIoodbath.
I feeI Iike Rocco
was responsibIe for this.
Rocco? Isn't he a part of the FamiIy?
Yeah. But you heard AngeIo.
He was in troubIe with the FamiIy.
So, I don't know, maybe he wanted
to hit them before they hit him.
Or perhaps he is doing
what the BIack Lotus Society
is doing with the yakuza.
Cut the head off a snake
and the body dies.
Maybe they are working together.
If Kuranai hits the yakuza,
and Rocco roughs up the Mob...
These organisations hate each other,
so they'd bIame each other.
Now we've got a war.
Then, when both sides
have weakened each other,
the BIack Lotus steps in,
taking controI of the yakuza.
Right, and Rocco takes over the Mob.
They're aIready working together,
so between the two of them,
they sew up
aII the city's operations.
You know what we need to do now?
We've got to protect
a coupIe of skinbags.
No, that's ''scumbags''.
Scumbags. Thanks for teaching.
You are a scumbag.
AngeIo was weII paid
for this information.
As we thought, the Fiorino famiIy
was responsibIe
for Nakai and Noda's deaths.
They want war,
we gIadIy give it to them.
Everybody chiII!
We're going to borrow your domo.
We'II bring him back safe and sound.
UntiI then, I don't want you
to do anything.
No fighting, no kiIIing, nothing.
Do you understand?
TeII them.
- Fucking yin and yang!
- Shut up!
- What the fuck?
- Shut up.
I know you don't Iike me
any more than I Iike you.
But I've got information
you might want to hear.
This war both of you have got
going on, it's a crock of shit.
You've been pIayed for patsies and
you're too fiIIed with hate to reaIise.
Rocco's responsibIe for what happened
at the bowIing aIIey. I'II prove it.
And Noda and Nakai were both kiIIed
by an assassin
known as the Kuranai.
An outside syndicate from Asia
caIIed the BIack Lotus Society
is responsibIe for aII this.
They recruited Rocco
and set you at each other's throats.
This war is something that they want,
not something that you want.
Rocco and Kuranai
have one thing Ieft to accompIish,
and that's kiIIing both of you.
Against my better judgment,
I won't Iet them.
Yeah? And what the fuck
are you going to do, huh?
I'm going to take you
to somepIace safe.
Big fin, red meat,
unfiItered cigarettes,
endIess, mindIess, IoveIess Iove...
Now what?
Detective Luca,
I thought you had a pIan.
Not exactIy.
They're not wrestIing
against fIesh and bIood.
They're wrestIing against the ruIers
of the present darkness of the worId,
against spirituaI wickedness
in high pIaces.
You'd better put on
the whoIe armour of God.
Hey, you can kiII me, but you don't
have a right to judge me.
Four mighty ones there are
in every man...
- I think I know where they are.
- How's that?
Something you said Iast night.
''Who messes with the Church?''
That's true. We've been Iooking
in the wrong pIaces.
We've been Iooking for criminaIs
where the other criminaIs are.
It's time to go to the Iast pIace
where we'd expect them to be.
Amen! Travis BickIe finds God.
Let's hope third time's the charm.
You're about to strike out.
This is the Iast tempIe
in LittIe Tokyo.
Sorry to disturb you.
My name is Detective Luca.
CouId we have a word with you?
- Detective Luca?
- His mother was Irish.
- How may I heIp you?
- Do you have any guests,
anyone visiting
that arrived onIy recentIy?
Yes. We have one from Kyoto.
He arrived a few nights ago
aIong with a schoIar from ItaIy.
Do you think we might see them?
We just want to ask a few questions.
- Is there a probIem?
- There couId be.
There are four guest rooms,
two of them taken.
Perhaps you and the others
shouId find somepIace safe.
Inspector Kim.
Here to finaIIy join your famiIy?
I'm here for onIy one reason.
I have come to return this to you.
Your death is the onIy thing
that can bring me peace.
I wiII show you that your death
wiII bring you peace, as weII.
Fuck you.
What's the matter, buddy?
You ain't got the baIIs? Huh? Do it.
Hey, Rocco.
Go ahead. Shoot me.
Fuck it.
I think you need a new car.
- Nice touch, my friend.
- You Iook Iike shit.
I feeI Iike shit.
Thank you, Buddha.
Thank you, Mr God.
WeII, Kim, I don't know what to say.
In Korea, we say...
- What does that mean?
- It means:
''Goodbye, son of a bitch.''
Fuck you, too.
It's the kind of thing
you can onIy say to a cIose friend.
You heIped me to put my souI at rest.
You did the same for me.
I say...
Inspector!
Thank you, too, Detective Luca.
Next time, I'm coming to Korea.
Abso-fucking-IuteIy.
Sir.
- Enjoy your fIight.
- Yes, I'm sure I wiII.