Can you tell us your name?
Do you understand me?
Yes.
I understand.
Where am I?
You are safe now.
Do you remember what happened
to you?
Is this a hospital?
It is like a hospital.
I don't understand.
Hey. It's me, Kate.
Got the new camera
and it's ready to go to Japan.
So, my boyfriend is flying in
from San Francisco.
I wish he was on my flight,
but that's okay.
I need to sleep on the plane
anyway.
And I don't know how Chris
is going to react to traveling.
So, Chris is
one of my closest childhood
friends.
We went to kindergarten
together.
And what's cool is
he speaks some Japanese,
and he really needs this trip.
He needs some good luck.
Good mojo.
He actually
had a breakdown earlier this
year.
His brother died in a horrific
accident.
You know,
we've been talking a lot and
I...
I think he's doing okay.
So I'm doing my thesis
on religious studies,
specifically how religion
changes myth and vice versa,
and I want to photograph
obscure shinto shrines
and Buddhist temples in rural
Japan.
Do you know this woman?
Where did you get this?
He asked where you got this
material.
Yeah, is it nice?
All right, I don't know. Hold
on.
Excuse me, how long 'til we get
there?
Ten minutes.
You hear that?
Okay, see ya soon.
I love you too.
Bye.
I can't believe you still
haven't met.
Has it really been that long
since I saw you?
Yeah. Goes by in a blink.
Well, I'm really glad you came.
Me too.
Nice to finally meet you.
I was beginning to think you
didn't exist.
- You good?
- - Yeah.
All right.
He's, uh...
He's not at all like I imagined.
What did you imagine?
I don't know.
Not him.
You don't like him.
Yeah, sure. Sure I do. Yeah.
I like him. He seems fine.
No you don't.
You're just telling me
what I want to hear.
Like, you two have been friends
for how long?
I just can't believe
he's never tried anything.
Yeah, well, not everyone is
like you.
If you say so.
Are you jealous?
No.
I'm not.
Should I be jealous?
'Cause I'll be jealous.
So, how'd you come to learn
Japanese?
Always wanted to come here.
Is it what you expected?
So far.
You know,
if we had trains like this in
America
I would not travel any other
way.
You two have been friends for a
long time.
I've never had that kind of
relationship
with a woman.
What are you guys talking about?
You.
You guys want anything
from the dining car?
I'm good. Thanks.
Kate?
She's good.
So, this is our room.
Feeling like a third wheel.
It's only for one night.
Are we looking
for anything in particular,
or...
Babe, how about this?
Exactly.
Wow. Come look at this temple.
Chris? Can you read this?
Looks like some kind of journal.
It's a kitsune.
A shapeshifter. Half woman,
half fox.
Do you think we could find this
place?
I think so.
Oh...
How much is it?
No, she's asking where we got
it.
Sorry, not for sale.
- Well, she said it's not for
sale, so...
- Okay, I got that.
Ask her how much it is,
how much she wants for it.
Leave now. Closed.
Do you think you said
something to insult her?
- Kate.
- What?
No.
No, I, I mean by accident.
You know? Maybe he said
the wrong word or something.
No. I didn't.
We'll find it online. All right?
Come on.
Babe. Can you please
explain to your viewers
why you won't be joining us
on this evening's adventure?
Jet lag.
There you have it, ladies and
gentleman.
Tune in next week
to discover how our heroes,
Chris and James,
got themselves into trouble.
Who is this woman?
That is a good question.
Hello?
The book.
Okay, okay, okay.
A whiskey.
Okay.
It's unlucky place.
Very unlucky.
Ah. I have a friend.
She's
interested in temples and
wants to start with this one.
This was not the start.
This was the end.
This temple.
It will make you... sick.
Sick.
Do not go there.
Many other temples in Japan.
I'm, I'm sorry.
How did you get this?
It's a long story.
Mmm, my head.
Wow.
Sorry I left you so
early last night.
Looked like you were having a
great time.
James said you made a friend.
A friend?
Oh, you know
that temple inside the book?
I can find it.
Doubt you can find
this place in any travel guide.
Yeah. You sure that's such a
good thing?
Oh.
That went well.
What's he say?
Um, he's asking why we came
here.
What's he saying?
Um, he's asking
why we came to his village.
Okay, okay.
He's saying this guy, hitoshi,
went up to the temple
and he had visions or something.
Holding his eyes.
Okay.
What is it. What is he doing?
Um, I don't,
i don't understand him, so...
Mucho arigato.
Hey, we're just going
to go for a walk, okay?
Yeah.
How great is this place?
It's perfect.
See ya later?
You are American.
You speak English?
It's been a long time.
They say you are here to visit
the temple.
The man in the village, he
said, uh...
You lost your sight there...
So, what's with all this...
Mystery about the temple?
What happened there?
Some children disappeared.
They had been playing in the
mountain.
It became night,
and the children had not
returned.
The search party
discovered a man living at the
temple.
He was a monk. A wanderer.
They questioned him
about the missing children.
But his answers were not
believed.
So, then what happened?
They killed the monk.
The children were never found.
Every year we burn candles,
and pray that the children will
return.
Someone was there, I...
Nobody.
Enjoy the show?
I'm sorry I woke you guys.
We could feel it.
As we got closer it knew we  were coming.
We should have gone back.
Who helped you find the temple?
The boy, seita.
All right. Isn't that something?
It's terrible. I hate it.
It's just a spider, baby.
Yeah, it looks like
it eats birds or small children.
Oh!
It's so quiet up here.
I was just thinking the same
thing.
It's cold, though.
Hold up.
What?
Here.
What? No. Honestly, I'm okay.
Thanks.
What do you think
the monk did to those kids?
I don't want to think about it.
I can't tell you how many
shirts of mine
have mysteriously gone missing.
Never to be seen again.
I gotta take a leak.
Yeah, you do that.
Have fun!
Hey. Let's go find him.
James!
Hey.
Hey, where were you?
I'll show you. Come on.
How cool is this?
It's an old mine.
I bet it goes on for miles.
Who's coming with me?
How about on the way back down?
Oh, come on.
Where's that spirit of
adventure?
I want to find the temple first.
I mean...
We might not be able to find it
again.
We'll leave something
on the path to mark it.
Fine. Fine.
You sure, babe?
Gift from my stepmother.
Hey, look. It's the statue from
the book.
We found it!
We must be close.
Chris, what do they call her?
This is a kitsune.
A shapeshifter protects the temple.
Bit of a letdown.
Look like little graves.
Maybe the monk-man
made them for his victims.
Was that supposed to be a joke?
I know. Right? I'm sorry.
I thought it was, then I said
it.
We should probably get out
of here soon. The sun's
starting to go down.
We still have time.
Look, I know you're not into
this.
- That's not true.
- It isn't?
Look, I just... I don't want
to walk down the mountain in
the dark.
We do have flashlights.
True. I just don't want
to have to use them.
Okay.
Hey.
I love you.
I love you too.
James?
I thought I saw...
- Saw what?
- I don't know, just...
You're right.
It's getting dark. We should go.
We can always come
back tomorrow.
No, I don't want to, i
just... I want to find
Chris and I want to go.
Chris!
Yeah?
Chris?
Grab a flashlight. Grab a
flashlight.
Chris!
Hold it.
Is he breathing?
Yeah. Yeah, he's breathing.
What do we do?
Oh, Jesus. Thank god.
Something pulled me through the
floor.
It's going to be okay.
We're just going to have to
wait here,
make ourselves comfortable,
- and go down for help
in the morning.
- No, I'm not spending
the night here.
Yeah? What do you suggest?
Let's get you out of here.
I'm going to take a walk.
A little moonlight stroll.
Care to join me?
We should stay here.
He's good. You're good, right?
Okay.
I'll be back in a few.
Be careful.
Yep.
He's going for help
first thing in the morning.
Okay?
He's not what I expected.
He said the same thing about
you.
I like him.
You do?
Yeah.
What do your parents think?
Mom's undecided.
Dad keeps trying to set me up
with some golf pro at his club.
- No ulterior motives there.
I never told him.
Never told him what?
About his baby.
So you're the only one who
knows.
What made you think of that
right now?
I don't know.
There were these... little
grave markers.
You cold?
I'm okay.
Okay.
- I'm going to tell him when we
get back.
- Tell me what?
Can, can you point that
somewhere else?
- What was it you were going to
tell me?
- Nothing. I wasn't talking
about you.
Never mind.
I think I got a pretty good
idea.
James.
No, wait. What are you going to
do?
Where are you going? James!
James!
I'm going to go back to the
village.
Okay. You've got all the food
and water
- you need here in my bag.
- No.
I'll send someone in the
morning.
I told him.
We're going to need some more
firewood.
It's okay.
Why don't we just go back
inside...
Fine.
I'll be right back.
Go fuck yourself.
No, please.
Come on, come on!
Oh... no.
Flashlight died.
This place isn't right.
No.
You gotta be kidding me.
James?
What's the matter?
What are you doing?
Kate. Wait.
He needs me.
Kate!
Aaah!
James...
Hello?
Let me help you!
James!
Help!
Help me!
Please, someone help!
There's no way out.
Do you know why you are here?
We're trying to find a miss
Thomas.
Kate.
Christopher.
What happened to her?
Why is seita here?
The boy from the village.
He's in the hallway.
There is no boy.
Where is miss Thomas?
We know you killed James.
What happened to me, Chris?
Where's Kate?
James!
Why did you kill your friend?