♪♪
♪ ♪
Evie:
Let's give Auradon
a taste of evil.
♪ ♪
Wicked ways
beneath the skin...
let all who taste it
now join in.
(laughs evilly)
♪ We got all the ways to be ♪
♪ W-I-C-K-E-D ♪
-Come on!
-♪ Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! ♪
♪ Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! ♪
(laughs)
♪ Hey! Hey! Hey! ♪
♪ Crashing the party,
guess they lost my invitation ♪
♪ Friendly reminder,
got my own kind of persuasion ♪
♪ Looks like this place could
use a bit of misbehavior ♪
♪ Happily ever after
with a little flavor ♪
♪ Bad to the bone
with even worse intentions ♪
♪ We're gonna steal the show
and leave 'em all defenseless ♪
♪ A fairytale life
can be oh-so overrated ♪
♪ So raise your voices
and let's get it activated! ♪
♪ Long live havin' some fun ♪
♪ We take what we want ♪
♪ There's so many ways
to be wicked ♪
♪ With us, evil lives on ♪
♪ The right side of wrong ♪
♪ There's so many ways
to be wicked ♪
♪ Apple, apple, dip, dip ♪
♪ Want to try it? Tick, tick ♪
♪ Take a bite,
come on, be bold ♪
♪ Change the way
the story's told ♪
♪ This time, the dark is finally
getting your attention ♪
♪ We're wicked by the book,
and class is back in session ♪
♪ You like it, steal it,
gotta beat 'em to the treasure ♪
♪ A rite of passage ♪
♪ Bad just doesn't get
much better ♪
♪ Long live havin' some fun ♪
♪ We take what we want ♪
♪ There's so many ways
to be wicked ♪
♪ Mother always knows best ♪
♪ Show her, pass every test ♪
♪ Hear her voice in my head ♪
♪ Evil is the only ♪
♪ Real way to win ♪
♪ We got all the ways to be ♪
♪ Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! ♪
-♪ W-I-C-K-E-D ♪
-(laughter)
Let's go!
♪ We got all the ways to be ♪
♪ Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! ♪
♪ W-I-C-K-E-D ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Long live havin' some fun ♪
♪ We take what we want ♪
♪ There's so many ways
to be wicked ♪
♪ With us, evil lives on ♪
♪ The right side of wrong ♪
♪ There's so many ways
to be wicked ♪
(cheering)
Yeah!
♪ We got all the ways to be ♪
♪ W-I-C-K-E-D ♪
♪ So many ways to be wicked ♪
(all shouting "Mal",
camera shatters clicking)
-Mal, please, over here! Mal!
-Only three days
to the Royal Cotillion.
Woman: Ever think a girl like
you would be Lady of the Court?
Man:
How does it feel to be the most
envied girl in Auradon?
Well, do you like
being blonde?
Is your mother
still a lizard?
(clears throat)
Okay. All right. Excuse me.
Uh, we will let you know
if and when
that particular situation
changes.
Did you ever think
you'd be with a Villain Kid?
(chuckles)
We're done here.
Okay. Shush, shush.
Shoosh, shoosh.
(chuckles)
This is still a school,
so if you're here,
you're either skipping
or trespassing.
-Just one quick question.
-Shush. Shush.
-Man: Fairy Godmother!
-Shhh.
Shhh. Shhh.
-Ben: Thank you, guys.
-Mal: Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Mal. Ben.
-Fairy Godmother.
♪ ♪
-Whew.
-(laughs)
Don't pay
any attention to them.
Well, that's a lot easier
said than done, right?
-(chuckles)
-I know. I know.
You know, maybe we should
do something.
We should go somewhere.
Get away.
-Yeah.
-You know, what do--
I have a council meeting.
I'm so late!
-That's okay.
-We'll-- We'll do it
sometime. Uh...
If we don't do
a fitting for your gown
right this minute,
you'll be dancing
in your bathrobe, okay?
Hi. Let's go. Let's go.
-Bye, Ben.
-Bye.
King Ben! King Ben!
King Ben!
-(indistinct shouting)
-Uh...
♪ ♪
(hisses)
(grunts)
Oh! Okay, Evie,
I cannot breathe.
Well, you can breathe
after Cotillion.
Well,
I sincerely doubt that.
I have at least 20 more events
directly behind it,
and I can't even remember
what a single one of them is.
(scoffs) Impeccable.
-Evie?
-Hmm?
Do you ever think about what
we'd be doing if we were
back on the Isle right now?
(laughs)
That's funny.
(dramatic music plays)
Ah!
Look who's on TV.
(chuckles)
Reporter:
As the royal couple
continues their tour
of the kingdom,
they dined
with Aladdin and Jasmine.
-Six months ago...
-Yeah. (chuckles)
no one thought King Ben
and his girlfriend
from the wrong side
of the bridge would last.
(chuckles)
Yeah. No kidding.
Mal must be counting the days
until the Royal Cotillion...
-(gasps)
-when she will officially
become a Lady of the Court.
(paper rustling)
Read it fast
at lightning speed.
Remember everything I need.
I know Mal's secret
to fitting in,
and Ben wouldn't
like it one bit.
Haven't you guys had enough
secrets between the two
of you already?
Evie, you remember
what I was like
before I started using
my spell book.
I mean,
I was a complete disaster.
Well, personally,
as your best friend,
-I strongly believe
that this spell book--
-Ah!
it belongs in the museum,
along with my mirror.
Don't give me
the face.
Put the pout away.
Mm-hmm.
You know I'm right.
You don't ever miss
running wild
and just
breaking all the rules?
Like stealing
and lying and fighting?
-Yeah!
-No!
-What?
-(chuckles) Why would we?
M, come here.
Look at where we are.
We're in Auradon!
And we're
Auradon girls now.
Since Mal revealed
her love of strawberries,
-she has received hundreds
of cartons from her admirers.
-(shrieks)
Here she is enjoying
a cozy bite...
See, this is the land
of opportunity.
We can be whatever
we want to be here.
So, please,
let's just leave the past
in the past, okay?
Besides,
I mean, look at the shoes.
(chuckles)
Look at them.
-Mm. Severe.
-(laughs)
-Hi, Jay.
-Hey.
-Jay.
-Hey, what's up?
-Hi.
-Why do you torture them?
Just pick someone to take
to Cotillion already.
(sighs)
I'm going solo.
That way,
I can dance
with all of them.
Ah! You're the expert.
Um, Jay...
if you were
gonna ask someone,
what's the best way to go?
Listen,
all you got to do...
is look like me.
-Oh, ha-ha.
-(laughs)
-Mal.
-Hey, Jane.
Hey.
I was wondering...uh...
♪ ♪
if you liked the....
carrot cake last night.
I had the pumpkin pie.
-Oh, cool. Um, uh--
-Smooth.
I have an opening for
a fitting at 3:00.
Who wants it?
Me! Sorry.
Perfect.
I'll take you later.
-Okay, well...
-Mal?
-Yes?
-I hate to keep bugging you,
but the decorating committee
needs more answers.
So, as much
as I hate to, um...
you know, um...
-Bug me?
-Right.
Yeah, Jane, I would love to.
I just have to get to class.
-You know,
just nod if you like it.
-Okay.
Chair swags. Entry banner.
Twinkle lights.
Napkin design.
Table bunting.
And you still haven't picked
the party favors yet.
Honestly, Jane,
whatever you think--
I mean, we can do chains,
key charms, pen toppers.
I kind of love
the pen toppers,
but, I mean,
we can do all three.
(chuckles nervously)
I say pen toppers.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-You won't regret it.
-(laughing) Okay.
I can hardly wait
to see what your wedding
will look like!
Me, too.
Wait! What?!
The Royal Cotillion
is like getting engaged
to be engaged
to be engaged.
-(gasps) I knew it!
-Well, everyone knows it.
I didn't know it!
How come nobody told me that?
-Is my entire life just
planned out in front of me--
-Hi, Mal.
-Hi, Ben.
Oh, oh.
Quick moment.
-Uh...
-All right,
they're almost finished
with the surprise
for Mal's big night.
Snow White,
Belle.
But the one you designed for Mal
is my favorite.
Make sure
her eyes are green.
Uh... see you later.
Okay.
-Which green
should they use?
-Uh...
This one.
What about
peacock feathers?
Yeah, I bet you nobody's gonna
have those at Cotillion.
Chad,
when I look at you,
all I can think of is...
-"king."
-(gasps)
-And fake fur...
-Uh-huh.
...fake fur
says it all.
Loud and clear.
Amphitheater in five!
Why did the coach make him
captain instead of me?
I'm obviously better.
"King Chad," though.
I do rather like that.
(chuckles)
You know who else
would like that?
-Who?
-Audrey.
-She would.
-Chad, let's go.
I'm coming. Yeah.
Oh.
It-- I--
-Come on.
-It's just--
(both laugh)
-Not a lot of there there.
Someone's obviously
having some trouble
dealing with
his break-up with Audrey.
Yes.
I've been
doing the numbers.
Yeah?
And after we collect
from all the girls
for their gowns
and Chad's cape...
(computer beeps)
(chuckles)
Wow!
No wonder
people work.
What am I gonna do
with all this money?
I think in the next
few years,
you could buy that castle
you always wanted.
(chuckles)
That way, you wouldn't
need a prince.
You're right, I don't.
Because I have you.
Hi, Mal.
(chuckling) Hi.
I have a little
surprise for you.
Again? Wow.
That's like
every day now.
Or every other day.
The even dates.
Because you're...
even more perfect
than I thought.
(laughs)
That is me.
I am perfect.
Come on,
let me spoil you.
You didn't have
a lot growing up.
We managed.
Hey, didn't you donate
that to the museum?
Is that
still in there?
Um, I got to get to class.
I really don't want to be late.
-No.
You come this way.
-(sighs)
-(Mal chuckles)
-First off...
-(gasps)
-Ta-da!
-What?!
-You like it?
Ben... (chuckles)
does an ogre
like cheese puffs?
This is amazing!
It's purple.
I didn't get you anything.
You're taking me on a picnic
with all my favorite
foods, remember?
No, that's Thursday.
-It is Thursday.
-No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
-It is.
I knew that.
-I mean, if you don't
have it, that's fine.
-No, no, no.
I was fully messing with you.
I knew it was Thursday.
I just have one more thing
to go bake, and then
I am all yours.
Well, what about class?
-She multi tasks.
-(chuckles)
-She dabbles.
-She dabbles. (laughs)
-You're the best!
-That's me!
All right, boys.
Let's line it up.
-Carlos, you're with me.
Let's go.
-Carlos: Yeah.
(chatter)
Assembler.
Salute.
Lower the point.
Masks down.
En garde.
(grunting)
-Jay: Keep your center!
-Carlos: Whoa!
(grunting)
Jay:
Eyes on your opponent!
Up and over.
♪ ♪
Boy:
Get him, Jay!
♪ ♪
Jay: Practice.
-Carlos: Watch out, Jay.
-Chad: Nice!
♪ ♪
-Jay, what happened?
-Finish him.
♪ ♪
-It's Lonnie!
-(cheers and applause)
(chuckles)
Not bad.
You should
put me on the team.
Hey, w-what?!
No, no, no.
We'll-- We'll be the
laughing stock of the league.
A-And what's gonna
happen next? We'll have
girls playing tourney?
-Come on, guys.
-So?
So? Uh, so, have you not
read the rule book?
Section 2,
paragraph 3, 11-4.
"A team will be comprised
of a captain and eight men."
Hmm? Why don't you read
the rule book?
Okay, yeah,
but you're down a man!
I mean, since Ben had to leave
to do all that king stuff.
Exactly.
We're down a man.
Jay...
I'm sorry.
Coach trusts me.
I'm not gonna stay captain if
I just throw out the rule book.
If my mother thought that way,
she would have lost the war.
(scoffs)
Okay.
Rule book.
All right, guys.
Practice is over.
Let's go.
Jane!
-Jane, hey. Hey.
-Hey, Carlos, what's up?
-(dog growls)
-Uh...
-Not much. You?
-Way too much.
We were gonna go with the blue
and gold banners for Cotillion,
but now we can't find
the right shade of blue.
Oh, yeah, no, that's a--
that's a bummer.
-Um, speaking of Cotillion--
-I know, right?
-It's all anybody is talking
about. Cotillion 24/7.
-I--
It's like they've never
been to one before.
Uh...I haven't, actually.
Oh.
Lucky. I always end up
serving punch
with my mom anyway.
This year, I got stuck
on the decorating committee
because Audrey went off
to a spa vacation with Flora,
Fauna, and Merryweather.
Jane, maybe we should just--
Skip the whole thing?
(scoffs)
I really, really wish I could.
It's so nice to have a friend
who's on the same wavelength.
Oh, you got me.
-(both laugh)
-(cellphone rings)
(groans)
I got to go.
Great practice,
though.
Yeah.
See ya. Hey, Mom.
♪ ♪
(dog whimpers)
It wasn't the right time,
all right?
(chatter)
(bells chime)
"How to get out
of the friend zone."
Reporter: They dined
with Aladdin and Jasmine.
I see you reading
over my shoulder.
Six months ago,
no one thought...
(camera shutters clicking)
the wrong side
of the bridge would last.
Mal must be counting the days
until the Royal Cotillion,
-when she will officially
become a Lady of the Court.
-(dog whines)
♪ ♪
(breathing heavily)
Whoa.
Easy, girl.
What? You think
this is so easy?!
You don't have people
taking a photo of you
every single time you open
your mouth to say boo!
I mean, it's not that
I could even say, "Boo,"
but, you know what I--
I'm sorry.
Carlos, don't you ever
miss screaming at people
and just making them
run away from you?
(scoffs)
You're thinking
of my mother,
and I was usually
on the other end of that.
So, not really. No.
Oh, hey!
-Did you bring it?
-(sighs)
(growls lightly)
(door opens)
♪ ♪
-(growls)
-Hi.
Just came to use
your 3D printer.
Won't be a sec.
How'd you get a key
to my room?
Oh, I printed it off
last time I was in here.
Uh...
you guys
were sleeping.
Look, I just-- Your printer's
so much better than mine,
and you install these hacks
and everything runs so much
smoother than mine and--
Out!
♪ ♪
Now.
Fine. Fine.
Chad!
What? Hmm?
Leave the key.
♪ ♪
-Mal?
-Hmm?
-My potion?
-Hmm.
Yeah. Um...
So, this thing
will make me say
what I really feel to Jane?
Yeah. I mean,
this is a truth gummie,
so take it
or leave it.
Perfect.
Hold on, though.
Are you sure that you
want to be taking this?
Because this is gonna make you
say the truth all the time,
no matter what,
and the only reason that
I'm asking is because I know
that if I took this right now,
I would get myself
sent back to the Isle.
Which, it's not that
that sounds super unappealing,
-but, you know...
-Yeah.
I'll take my chances,
I guess.
-Okay.
-(growls)
Ohh!
Bad dog!
(groans)
-(gasps)
-Man, that thing
was nasty!
And you-- you just
got to man up.
♪ ♪
And while you're at it,
scratch my butt.
You heard him.
Scratch his butt.
Mal.
-You're just gonna
leave me with him?
-(door opens, closes)
Come on.
You scratch your own
all the time.
♪ ♪
(dramatic music plays)
Ugh!
(all gasping)
♪ ♪
(seagulls calling)
(chatter)
♪ ♪
(grunts)
(laughter)
Poser.
Traitor!
-Hello?
-(indistinct shouting)
Oh, I would love to wipe
the smiles off their faces.
-You know what I mean?
-Gil!
You want to quit
choking down yolks
and get with the program?
(gulps)
Yeah. What they said.
That little traitor,
who left us in the dirt.
Who turned her back
on evil.
Who said you weren't big
or bad enough to be in her gang.
(parrot squawks)
Back when
we were kids.
Come on,
you guys remember.
She called her Shrimpy,
and the name just kind of...
-stuck.
-(sighs)
That snooty little witch,
who grabbed
everything she wanted
and left me nothing.
No, she left you
that sandbox,
and then she said that
you could have the shrimp--
-(slams table)
-I need you to stop talking.
Look, we have
her turf now.
They can stay
in Bore-adon.
Harry, that's her turf now!
And I want it, too.
We should not
be getting her leftovers.
Son of Hook,
son of Gaston,
and me, most of all,
daughter of Ursula!
What's my name?
Uma!
Mm. Uma?
♪ What's my name?
What's my name? ♪
All:
Uma!
♪ This is all hands on deck ♪
♪ Calling out
to lost boys and girls ♪
♪ I'm gettin' tired
of the disrespect ♪
♪ We won't stop
till we rule the world ♪
♪ It's our time, we up next ♪
♪ Our sail's about to be set ♪
♪ They ain't seen nothing yet ♪
♪ Tell 'em who's in charge
so they don't forget ♪
♪ What's my name?
What's my name? ♪
-♪ Uma! ♪
-♪ Say it louder ♪
♪ What's my name?
What's my name? ♪
-♪ Uma! ♪
-♪ Feel the power ♪
♪ No one's gonna stop us ♪
♪ Soon the world will be ours ♪
♪ What's my name?
What's my name? ♪
♪ What's it, what's it ♪
-♪ Say it loud! ♪
-♪ Uma, Uma ♪
-♪ All eyes on me,
let me see 'em ♪
-♪ Uma, Uma ♪
♪ What's it, what's it,
say it, say it ♪
♪ Uma-ah-ah-ah! ♪
♪ Uma, Uma, la la Um ♪
♪ Uma, Uma, la la Uma ♪
♪ I'm the queen of this town ♪
♪ I call the shots,
you know who I am ♪
♪ I don't need to wear
no fake crown ♪
♪ Stand up to me,
you don't stand a chance ♪
♪ It's our time, we up next ♪
♪ My crew's as real as it gets ♪
♪ The worst is now the best ♪
♪ And leaving us here
will be their last regret ♪
♪ What's my name?
What's my name? ♪
-♪ Uma! ♪
-♪ Say it louder ♪
♪ What's my name?
What's my name? ♪
-♪ Uma! ♪
-♪ Feel the power ♪
♪ No one's gonna stop us ♪
♪ Soon the world will be ours ♪
♪ What's my name?
What's my name? ♪
♪ What's it, what's it,
say it, say it ♪
♪ You know what they say,
bad girls have all the fun ♪
♪ Never learned how to count
'cause I'm number one ♪
♪ Ready, here we come,
we always get our way ♪
♪ It's a pirate's life
every single day, hey ♪
♪ She's the captain,
I'm the first mate ♪
♪ Enemies seasick,
can't see straight ♪
♪ Call 'em fish bait,
throw 'em on a hook ♪
♪ Uma's so hot,
they get burned if they look ♪
Oh!
♪ It's all eyes on me, on me
let me see 'em ♪
♪ I see your eyes on me, boys ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
-♪ You know what my name is ♪
- Dance over there!
♪ Say it, say it louder! ♪
-Hook me!
-(laughs)
(laughs)
Come on!
♪ What's my name?
What's my name? ♪
-♪ Uma! ♪
-♪ Say it louder ♪
♪ What's my name?
What's my name? ♪
-♪ Uma! ♪
-♪ Feel the power ♪
♪ No one's gonna stop us ♪
♪ Soon the world will be ours ♪
♪ What's my name?
What's my name? ♪
-♪ Say it louder ♪
-♪ Uma, Uma ♪
♪ Ooh, say it louder ♪
♪ What's it, what's it,
say it, say it ♪
♪ Uma, Uma, la la Um ♪
♪ Uma, Uma, la la Uma ♪
♪ Uma! ♪
(laughter)
(screams)
Ursula:
Shut your clams!
Mom!
These dishes
ain't gonna wash themselves!
(water splashes)
It's fine.
'Cause when I get my chance to
rain down the evil on Auradon,
I will take it!
They're gonna forget that girl
and remember the name--
Shrimpy!
♪ ♪
-Mm-hmm.
-Ah.
(stammering)
♪ ♪
(bell chimes)
Would you like
a hot hors d'oeuvre?
Yes, please.
Mmm!
This is the best thing
I've ever had.
-(Ben chuckles)
-So, you like it?
I more than like it.
I, uh...
mmm-- so like it.
(chuckles)
(both laugh)
-Beef ragout?
-Yeah. (chuckles)
-This is amazing.
-Did I surprise you?
Oh, yeah, you surprised me.
This is every single dish
Mrs. Potts made for my parents.
-What did it take you?
Three days?
-(clicks tongue)
You know,
don't even ask me.
-(both laugh)
-Yeah.
Well, it means a lot
that you stopped
and did all this for me.
Especially with all
the craziness you've been
put through.
I've missed you.
♪ ♪
We don't get much time
to be just us anymore.
I know.
♪ ♪
(both chuckling)
You can't take me
anywhere, right?
Uh... (laughs)
Do you have a--
Do you have a napkin
or something?
I do!
I packed some.
-Oh, there is--
-I think I stowed them away.
I can grab them.
What's this?
(chuckles)
I actually threw that in there
super last-minute
in case it rained or--
"Speed reading" spell.
"Blonde hair" spell.
♪ ♪
"Cooking" spell.
And I was giving you props
for fitting in so well,
for doing your best.
Take back this moment
that has passed.
Return it-- Reverse it--
Are you trying
to spell me right now?!
-Ben, it has been
so hard for me!
-Yes! Some things are hard!
Do you think
learning to be king
has been easy for me?
-No! (chuckles)
-I thought we were
doing this together!
Ben, we are in this together.
But we're not, Mal. We're not.
Y-You've been keeping secrets
and lying to me.
-(laughs nervously)
-I thought we were
done with that.
This isn't
the Isle of the Lost, Mal.
Yeah. Believe me, I know that!
Then why
are you doing this?
Because... (scoffs)
I'm not one of those
pretty pink princesses, Ben.
I'm not one of those ladies
from the Court.
I'm a big fake, okay?
(sighs)
I'm fake.
This is fake.
This is fake. (scoffs)
(sighs)
♪ ♪
Take this feast,
this sumptuous meal,
return it back
to what is real.
This is
who I really am.
♪ ♪
-Mal.
-No. No.
Peanut butter and jelly
is my favorite!
(plate clatters)
(Ben sighs)
♪ ♪
(sobs)
I don't belong here.
(breathing heavily)
Okay.
♪ ♪
Okay. Okay.
Let's blow this popsicle stand.
Yeah? (chuckles)
♪ ♪
(breathing heavily)
Noble steed, proud and fair,
you shall take me anywhere.
♪ ♪
Okay. Whew.
Please work.
♪ ♪
Oh!
-(tires screech)
-Whoa, what?
-(woman screams)
-Hey!
-Hey, hey, hey!
-Watch it!
♪ ♪
(clock chiming)
-Deborah?
-Deborah: Yes, Your Majesty?
Can you ask Lumiere to call me
regarding Cotillion?
- Yes, sir.
-Thank you.
-(knock on door)
-Ben?
Evie! Come on in.
Mal's gone back
to the Isle.
(sighs)
Ben...
♪ ♪
(mumbles)
This is my fault.
I-I blew it.
She'd been under
so much pressure lately,
and instead of
being understanding,
I just went
all Beast on her.
I have to go there
and apologize.
and--and beg her to come back.
-Ben, you'll
never find her.
-I--
You need to know the Isle
and how it works and...
♪ ♪
You have to
take me with you.
Yes! Uh, are--are you sure?
Yeah.
She's my best friend.
And we'll bring
the boys, too,
because there's
safety in numbers,
and none of us
is really too popular
over there right now.
-Thank you.
-But let's get
two things straight.
You have to promise me that
I won't get stuck there again.
I promise.
And there's no way
you're going looking like that.
(seagulls calling)
(chatter)
(cat yowls)
♪ What you rather be tonight? ♪
♪ Doesn't matter what we do ♪
♪ 'Cause I'd rather
be with you ♪
♪ Rather be with you,
Rather be with you ♪
♪ Doesn't matter what we do ♪
♪ 'Cause I'd rather
be with you ♪
♪ Rather be with you ♪
♪ Doesn't matter who is who ♪
♪ 'Cause I'd rather
be with you ♪
♪ Rather be with you ♪
♪ You, you ♪
♪ I'd rather be with you ♪
-♪ You, you ♪
-Mal!
Is Evie back, too?
(chuckles)
As if.
I, um, forgot that you guys
don't open till midnight.
Place looks good.
(giggles)
So what is
your deal?
Has your grandmother
given you
any customers yet?
Ah, just a witch
here and there.
Mostly, it's a lot of scrubbing
and scouring and sweeping.
Lots and lots
of sweeping.
Sounds like the old
Cinderella treatment, eh?
Yeah, she's gone
from Wicked Stepmother
to Wicked Grandmother.
That's not really
much of a switch.
Hey, Dizzy, you used
to do Evie, right?
Yeah. I thought
of the little braids.
You have
any ideas for me?
Mm.
The washed-out blonde
with purple tips?
-The best of no worlds.
-(chuckles)
You can't see
where your face ends
and your hair begins!
(scoffs)
Oh, what is this,
"Bored to Death Pink"?
Hmm.
How far can I go?
(clicks tongue)
The works?
I mean, whatever
makes me feel like me,
but, you know...
way worse.
Yay!
♪ ♪
♪ Hit it hard ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, yeah ♪
♪ You really like it ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ You really need it ♪
♪ So, come on, hit it hard ♪
♪ Whoo-oo-oo-oo-oo ♪
♪ Hit it hard ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, yeah ♪
Hey!
There I am.
(chuckles) Voila!
-Voila.
-(giggles)
-For me?
-Yeah.
-You earned it.
-(both laugh)
Fork it over,
you runt.
Now the rest of it.
(cash register dings)
Hmm. Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Still running errands
for Uma,
or do you actually
get to keep what you steal?
Well, well, well.
What a nice surprise.
Hi, Harry.
Just wait until Uma
hears you're back.
She's never gonna
give you back
your old territory.
Oh, well,
that's okay.
Because I will be
taking it.
(chuckles lightly)
I could hurt you.
♪ ♪
Not without
her permission, I bet.
(chuckles)
♪ ♪
Great.
More sweeping.
Ben:
Jay, keys. Remote.
Wait!
Something's wrong.
-Oh.
-There.
-Shotgun!
-No, Dude. Stay.
The Isle is way
too dangerous.
-(groans)
-(gasps)
Did he just...
Talk? Yeah. I know.
Tell you later.
-Let's go.
-Evie: Yeah.
Okay, once we
cross the bridge,
park under the pier
in the old garage.
Got it?
Ben:
Got it.
♪ ♪
Ben, help me
with the tarp.
♪ ♪
-Jay?
-Jay: Yeah?
♪ ♪
I got it.
It's really weird
being back here.
We'll get in
and get out.
♪ ♪
Jay!
Hey, what's in here?
Ben!
You don't want
to know.
Hey, guys.
Keep it chill,
all right?
The last thing we need
is our parents
figuring out we're here.
♪ ♪
(chatter)
Hey! Hey! Stop.
♪ ♪
Just take it.
-Go on.
-(giggling)
♪ ♪
Ugh. Ben.
(sighs)
(growls)
-Ben, stop. Just stop.
-Hey, man!
-Ben: Why?
-This isn't a parade.
It's the Isle.
Keep your hands
in your pockets
unless you're stealing.
You either slouch
or strut.
And never, ever smile.
-Okay, thanks.
-No!
No "thank you's,"
and drop the "please," too.
Just...chill.
♪ Let me tell you something
you can really trust ♪
♪ Everybody's got
a wicked side ♪
♪ I know you think that
you could never be like us ♪
♪ Watch and learn
so you can get it right ♪
♪ You need to drag your feet ♪
♪ You need to nod your head ♪
♪ You need to lean back ♪
♪ Slip through the cracks ♪
♪ You need to not care ♪
Carlos: Uh, you need
to not stare.
♪ You need a whole lotta help ♪
You need
to not be yourself.
♪ You wanna be cool ♪
♪ Let me show you how ♪
♪ Need to break the rules ♪
♪ I can show you how ♪
♪ And once you catch
this feeling ♪
♪ Yeah, once you catch
♪ You'll be chillin', chillin' ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Chillin' like a villain ♪
♪ Chillin' ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Chillin' like ♪
-♪ Hey! ♪
-♪ A villain ♪
♪ You draw attention
when you act like that ♪
♪ Let us teach you
how to disappear ♪
♪ You look like you would
lose a fight to an alley cat ♪
♪ You gotta be wrong
to get it right 'round here ♪
- (yowls)
-♪ You need
to watch your back ♪
♪ You need to creep around ♪
♪ You need
to slide real smooth ♪
♪ Don't make a sound ♪
♪ And if you want it, take it ♪
♪ And you can't take it,
break it ♪
♪ If you care
about your health ♪
Seriously, you need
to not be yourself.
♪ You wanna be cool ♪
♪ Let me show you how ♪
♪ Need to break the rules ♪
♪ I can show you how ♪
♪ And once you catch
this feeling ♪
♪ Yeah, once you catch
♪ You'll be chillin', chillin' ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Chillin' like a villain ♪
♪ Chillin' ♪
♪ Chillin' like ♪
♪ I really wanna be bad a lot ♪
♪ And I've giving it
my best shot ♪
♪ But it's hard
being what I'm not ♪
Well, if you don't
you're gonna get us caught.
♪ He's right,
we gotta stay low-key ♪
♪ Now show us how bad
you can be ♪
-Like this?
-♪ Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
Like this?
Oh, yeah,
I think I got this.
Let's go,
I'm ready to rock this.
♪ And I ain't gonna thank you
for your help ♪
♪ I think I found
the worst in myself ♪
♪ You wanna be cool ♪
♪ Let me show you how ♪
♪ Need to break the rules ♪
♪ I can show you how ♪
♪ And once you catch
this feeling ♪
♪ Yeah, once you catch
♪ You'll be chillin', chillin' ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Chillin' like a villain ♪
♪ Chillin' ♪
-♪ Chillin' ♪
-Hey!
♪ Chillin' like a villain ♪
(Ben humming)
Hey, man. Hey!
Hey, I know you!
Uh, no.
Don't know you,
either, man.
Uh, yeah, you do.
Come on, man.
Really? Huh?
Dude,
I'll give you a hint.
My dad is quick,
slick and his neck...
Huh?
is incredibly thick.
Come on, man.
I kn-- Huh? Huh.
Huh? Huh.
-(gasps) Oh! You're King Ben!
-Okay, let's go.
Yeah, yeah,
you totally are King Ben,
and you're J-Jay,
Carlos, Evie.
Hey, guys.
Oh, Uma's gonna love this!
(giggles)
Come on.
(mechanical whirring)
Wish me luck.
All the way up.
Good luck.
(sighs)
(can rattling, air hissing)
♪ ♪
At least I don't see
a picture of me
with horns and a pitch fork.
Ben.
Mal, I'm so sorry
about our fight.
It was all my fault.
It--
Please come home.
♪ ♪
Ben, (scoffs)
I am home.
I brought the limo.
(chuckles)
It's a sweet ride.
(sniffles)
I don't fit in, Ben.
♪ ♪
I really gave it
my best shot.
And if you think
that I can change,
I think you're wrong.
Then I'll change.
I'll skip school,
have more fun.
-You know, I-I'll blow off
some of my responsibilities.
-No, no! See?
I'm such a terrible influence.
It's only a matter of time
before I do something
so messed up
that not only does
the kingdom turn on me,
but they turn on you.
Don't quit us, Mal.
♪ ♪
-The people love you.
-(sighs)
I love you.
♪ ♪
Don't you love me?
I have to take myself
out of the picture
because it's what's
best for you,
and it's what's best
for Auradon.
Mal, no, please.
Mm.
Ben...
♪ ♪
I can't do this.
You should go,
Ben.
Ben, please go.
Please leave.
♪ ♪
(inhales sharply)
Evie:
So?
Where's Mal?
-She's not coming back.
-What?
I'll talk to her.
M?
Mal,
it's Evie.
Let me just talk to you
for a second.
- Mal, come on.
-(grunts)
Go away!
-(sighs)
-Let's give her a couple
of hours to cool off.
Guys!
Where's Ben?
Ben?
♪ ♪
Ben!
-(sighs)
-Ben, don't scare us
like that.
Don't scare you?
But that's my specialty.
-Harry.
-What did you do
with Ben?
Oh, uh, we nicked him.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
And if you want
to see him again,
have Mal come
to the Chip Shoppe tonight.
Alone.
Uma wants
a little visit.
♪ ♪
Aw, Jay.
Seems like
you've lost your touch.
-Hey!
-Jay!
(laughs)
Hey!
(whistles)
If you guys never
would have brought him here,
this never
would have happened.
What were you thinking?!
He was gonna come
with or without us.
We just wanted
to protect him.
Yeah, and we completely
blew it, guys.
Okay! Okay.
So, what are we gonna do?
"We" are not doing anything.
This is between
Uma and me.
And she's a punk.
And guess what?
Now I have to
go get him.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Mal.
You're still gonna have
to go through Harry Hook
and his wharf rats.
Yeah, you're
gonna need us.
-Uma said to come alone.
-Mal, come on.
She said
to come alone.
I know one thing.
I'm not
going anywhere.
We'll be here
when you get back.
(laughter)
Hey! I wanted
the fried clams.
And I wanted
a sea pony.
Life ain't fair!
(singsong voice):
I'm back.
Loser,
party of one.
Right this way,
please.
(laughs)
(sighs)
-Place still stinks.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
We're down
a butler today...
Princess.
Where is he?
You know,
I've dreamed of this.
(laughs)
You wanting
something from me,
and me watching you squirm
like a worm on a hook.
I'm so flattered
that you dream of me.
I haven't given you
a thought since I left.
-(slams table)
-Obviously.
♪ ♪
You have your perfect,
little life, don't you?
Doesn't she have
the perfect, little life?
(laughter)
And we're 20 years
into a garbage strike.
Listen, if you have
some kind of score
to settle with me,
game on.
I see no need
to bring Ben into this.
(laughs)
It may be
a little unnecessary,
but, oh,
it is so much fun.
Here's the deal.
Just like your mother--
always a catch.
♪ ♪
If you win...
Ben is free to go.
♪ ♪
Hmm?
Don't you want to know
what I get if I win?
-Still dreaming.
-Mm.
Last time I checked,
your mother thought
she had things
all sewn up, too, huh?
How'd that work out
for her again?
On three.
-One.
-Two.
-Three.
(chuckles)
♪ ♪
You know,
that whole princess act?
Ugh. Never bought it
for a second.
You can stick a tiara
on a villain,
but you're still
a villain.
And you can
slap a pirate hat on,
but you're still
Shrimpy. (gasps)
♪ ♪
(chuckles)
If I win...
you bring me
the wand.
-(cheers and applause)
-(laughs)
(cheers and applause continue)
Now... if you want
beasty boy back,
bring me Fairy Godmother's
magic wand
to my ship tomorrow
at 12:00 noon...
sharp.
Oh, and if you blab...
you can kiss
your baby goodbye.
♪ ♪
(laughs)
There's no way we're gonna
give Uma the wand.
We can't just let her
destroy Auradon.
Uma doesn't get the wand,
then Ben is toast, guys.
Right, so, we're gonna
give Uma, of all people,
the wand.
-Do we have
another choice?
-Mal: Wait! You guys!
-Your 3D printer.
-A phony wand?
-Yes!
-In my sleep.
And the second Uma tests it,
she'll know it's fake.
Well, okay, so then we just
get Ben out really fast.
We need some kind of diversion.
Smoke bombs!
That's perfect.
I'll get the chemicals I need
from Lady Tremaine's place.
That could work.
Oh, and sick hair,
by the way.
Evil Stepmom seriously
stepped up her game.
Okay, do you want
to know something?
-Dizzy did this.
-Little Dizzy? Shut up!
I know.
I'm, like, loving it.
-It's, like, a lot lighter.
-Really proud of her.
-(clears throat)
-Hello?
Right.
Carlos, Jay, you guys
meet us at Pirates Bay
no later than noon.
And, you guys, losing--
not an option.
'Cause we're rotten...
Together:
To the core.
Let's do this.
♪ ♪
(gasps)
-Shh.
-Okay.
Evie?
-Evie! You came back!
-Hi!
Hey. So great
to see you, too.
Is it all
just like we imagined?
Do they really have closets
you can walk into?
Have you been to
a real swimming pool?
What does
ice cream taste like?
It's cold
and it's sweet,
and if you eat it too fast,
it gives you a headache.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I saved your sketch book
for you.
You did?
Dizzy!
Oh, my gosh.
Wow.
♪ ♪
I made this dress
out of an old curtain
and safety pins.
(chuckles)
It reminds me of the dress
you made for Mal
when she met Jasmine.
-I spilled curry
all over that.
-You did.
(laughs)
Yeah, I saw that.
You're totally right,
Dizzy.
This was-- this was totally
the inspiration for that.
I knew it!
You can take the girl
out of the Isle,
but you can't take the Isle
out of the girl.
♪ ♪
Is this...
too much,
or is this fabulous?
Hand me
the glue gun!
♪ ♪
Hi.
Oh, I'm sorry
I'm so late, Dude.
-Ben got captured.
-Don't.
Why is our door open?
(printer whirring)
You've got
to be kidding me.
-I knocked. (chuckles)
-Go on, Dude.
-What is that?
-Oh. (laughs)
That's a little
Chad action figure.
Zoom! (chuckles)
Well, minus the head.
Sounds like
an improvement.
Excuse me.
All right.
Here we go.
(gasps)
Why are you guys making
Fairy Godmother's wand?
Oh.
Uh, why are we making
Fairy Godmother's wand?
Because, uh...
Ben's been captured!
What?!
-Dude can talk?
-I was stalling.
I thought you forgot.
Don't tell anyone!
Ben's life
depends on it.
Really?
So, if something
were to happen,
you know
what I'm saying...
Something bad,
we get it.
(chuckles)
God forbid.
But if something
were to happen,
who do you think
would be in line to be king?
-Is it me, or is that
in really poor taste?
-(scoffs)
♪ ♪
(scoffs) I'm taking this.
And if you think I--
Thank you, Jay.
-All right.
-(printer whirs)
-Got it?
-Yeah, I got it.
-Careful.
-I got it.
Perfect. That makes
five smoke bombs.
Okay. I think
that's enough, right?
-Yeah.
M, how amazing
would this look
with my shredded tee
and my heart purse?
-Very amazing.
-Dizzy: Take it.
Take a bunch.
Oh, Dizzy!
Oh, my gosh.
(gasps)
-Thank you.
-It would make me so happy
to know that you were wearing
something of mine in Auradon.
Almost like me
being there myself.
I really wish
I could take you with me.
At least one of us
had her dream
come true, right?
-(chuckles)
-Yeah.
-E, we got to go.
-Okay.
♪ ♪
She's gonna be okay.
Yeah.
But she could be
so much more.
(sighs)
Let's go.
(laughs)
That one was epic.
That went on
for actual days.
Like it mattered, right?
They were both undone
by True Love's Kiss.
Together: Works every time.
(laughs)
I really thought that's
what you and Ben had.
Do you want
to talk about it?
Nah. I'm not
coming back, Evie.
I can't. I really
tried to tell you.
Yeah.
But, I mean, I saw
the way your face lit up
when we walked
through those dorm rooms
for the first time.
And I couldn't
spoil that for you.
If you're staying,
I'm staying, too.
No.
Evie, you are
an Auradon girl.
And I am...
and will always be...
(chuckles)
the girl from the Isle.
(gears cranking)
♪ ♪
♪ I didn't know what you ♪
♪ Were going through ♪
♪ I thought
that you were fine ♪
♪ Why did you
have to hide? ♪
♪ I didn't want to
let you down ♪
♪ But the truth is out ♪
♪ It's tearing me apart ♪
♪ Not listening
to my heart ♪
♪ I really had to go ♪
♪ And I would
never stop you ♪
♪ Even though
we've changed ♪
♪ Nothing has to change ♪
♪ And you can find me
in the space between ♪
♪ Where two worlds
come to meet ♪
♪ I'll never be out of reach ♪
♪ 'Cause you're a part of me ♪
♪ So you can find me
in the space between ♪
♪ You'll never be alone ♪
♪ No matter where you go ♪
♪ We can meet
in the space between ♪
♪ There are no words
left to say ♪
♪ I know you got to
find your place ♪
♪ But this is not the end ♪
♪ No, you're part
of who I am ♪
♪ Even if we're worlds apart ♪
♪ You're still in my heart ♪
♪ It will always be ♪
♪ You and me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ You can find me
in the space between ♪
♪ Where two worlds
come to meet ♪
♪ We'll never
be out of reach ♪
♪ Never be out of reach ♪
♪ No, 'cause
you're a part of me ♪
♪ So you can find me
in the space between ♪
♪ You'll never be alone ♪
♪ No matter where you go ♪
♪ We can meet ♪
♪ In the space between ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ No matter where you go ♪
♪ We can meet
in the space between ♪
(laughs)
(snoring)
(printer beeps, whirs)
-Carlos!
-Hmm? What?
-Not bad.
-Yeah.
-Let's go.
-Let's go. Yeah.
Dude: Hey, guys.
What about me?
No, Dude. You stay.
I'm serious. Stay.
(whines)
I love you, buddy.
We'll be back
before you know it.
Oh, hey,
have you seen Evie?
Uh...
She went camping.
Evie-I-want-to-
live-in-a-castle
sleeping on the ground
with no place to plug in
a hair dryer?
You know
how spontaneous
she is, bro.
(laughing) Yeah.
Totally. Totally.
Later, Doug.
I'm coming with you guys.
(laughs) What?
We don't need
swords at the...
Waffle Hut.
You're going to the Isle
to rescue Ben.
Look, it's either
you take me
or I'm gonna have to
tell Fairy Godmother.
Okay! Really?
♪ ♪
(sighs)
Coochy, coochy, coo.
How's it feel to be
the king now, eh?
(laughs)
Give it a rest, Harry.
Give it a rest.
We don't want
damaged goods.
You said that
I could hook him.
I said at noon.
20 more minutes.
(watch ticking)
That says 11:30.
Ah.
You better hope your
girlfriend comes through.
Mm-hmm.
Well, she's not
my girlfriend anymore.
(Harry chuckles)
Leave us alone, Harry.
19 minutes to go now.
Go.
I get that
you don't deserve this.
(laughs)
"This?"
This island is a prison,
thanks to your father.
And don't pretend
to look out for me.
Because no one's
looking out for me.
It's just me.
So this isn't
your mom's plan?
-(scoffs)
-Isn't that her necklace?
My mom doesn't
care about me, either.
Well, not unless she needs
someone for the night shift.
Ouch.
I don't need your pity.
No, you certainly don't.
You're very resourceful.
I don't see
you tied up.
(chuckles)
All right.
So let's trash talk Mal.
I'd rather talk about you.
Mm.
Funny and a gentleman.
I really hope I don't have to
feed you to the fishes.
Well, you don't. Set me free,
and we'll go back together.
Oh, so now I get
an invite?
(laughs)
Gee, I wonder why.
When you brought Mal, Evie,
Carlos, and Jay to Auradon,
that's as mad as
I've ever been in my life.
And trust me,
I've been plenty mad.
I never thought of it
like that before.
That I could've hurt
the people I didn't pick.
My plan was to start
with four kids and bring
more people over.
I guess I was
busy being king.
That sounds lame.
I'm so sorry.
You're a leader, Uma.
So am I.
Come to Auradon
and be part of the solution.
Me?
Part of your solution?
Nah.
I don't need you.
I'm gonna get there
on my own.
Harry!
Let's see what
this puppy can do.
-I'll get the swords.
-Okay.
-Oh, Lonnie!
-I made them bring me.
Oh, I'm so glad.
Hi. Welcome to the Isle.
-It's good to see you.
-Thanks.
And Dude.
I told you to stay.
I flunked obedience class.
Great. And he
can still talk.
You're lucky
I love you.
Come on.
Ooh.
Here, let me see.
Wow, what a beauty.
-It's noon.
-All right.
-Are we ready?
-Yeah.
Let's do this.
Stay!
(Dude grumbles)
I mean it.
♪ ♪
Hey, guys!
They're here!
Welcome!
Finally! (laughs)
♪ Let's get this party started ♪
♪ I swear I'm cold hearted ♪
♪ There's no negotiation ♪
♪ I'm not here for debatin' ♪
♪ You need some motivation? ♪
♪ Just look at Ben's face,
then ask yourself ♪
♪ How long you think
I'll remain patient ♪
♪ I'll throw him overboard ♪
♪ And let him swim
with killer sharks ♪
♪ You either hand over the wand,
or he'll be ripped apart ♪
♪ Now let's all just be smart ♪
♪ Although for you,
that must be hard ♪
-(laughs)
-♪ You'll get your want ♪
♪ No one has to come
to any harm ♪
♪ Don't try to intimidate ♪
♪ Your bark is much worse
than your bite ♪
♪ Who's the baddest
of them all? ♪
♪ I guess we're
finding out tonight ♪
♪ Let's go, bring it on ♪
♪ Better give us what we want ♪
♪ It's the wand for the crown ♪
♪ If you don't,
it's going down ♪
♪ Let's go, make your move ♪
♪ Peace or war, it's up to you ♪
♪ Give him up and do it now ♪
♪ If you don't,
it's going down ♪
♪ We want the wand,
or else the king is gone ♪
♪ Your time is running out ♪
♪ You should really
watch your mouth ♪
♪ Let's go, pound for pound ♪
♪ We're prepared
to stand our ground ♪
♪ Put your swords up ♪
♪ Put 'em up, it's going down ♪
♪ Yo-oh, ho-oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ Make the trade! ♪
♪ Or walk the plank! ♪
♪ Yo-oh, ho-oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ Make the trade! ♪
♪ Or walk the plank! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Okay, look, this is not
a conversation ♪
♪ It's a do-or-die situation ♪
♪ If you don't give me
back the king ♪
♪ I'll have no hesitation ♪
♪ I'll serve you right here ♪
♪ And I don't need
a reservation ♪
♪ That way your whole
"pirate crew" ♪
♪ Can have a demonstration ♪
♪ Release him now ♪
-(laughs)
-♪ And we can go
our separate ways ♪
♪ Unless you want to deal
with me and the VKs ♪
-(laughs)
-♪ So that's your
big speech, huh? ♪
♪ An empty ultimatum? ♪
♪ All it takes is one swing,
and I'll humiliate him! ♪
♪ Matter of fact,
make one wrong move ♪
♪ And I'll debilitate him ♪
♪ And if he even starts
to slip, I'll eliminate him ♪
♪ All it takes is
one wrong look and I'll--♪
Harry, we get it.
Chill.
♪ Let's go, bring it on ♪
♪ Better give us what we want ♪
♪ It's the wand for the crown ♪
♪ If you don't,
it's going down ♪
♪ Let's go, make your move ♪
♪ Peace or war, it's up to you ♪
♪ Give him up and do it now ♪
♪ If you don't,
it's going down ♪
♪ We want the wand,
or else the king is gone ♪
♪ Your time is running out ♪
♪ You should really
watch your mouth ♪
♪ Let's go pound for pound ♪
♪ We're prepared
to stand our ground ♪
♪ Put your swords up ♪
♪ Put 'em up, it's going down ♪
♪ Hey, we don't
have to choose ♪
♪ We don't have
to light the fuse ♪
♪ Mal, whatever you do,
it's gonna be a lose-lose ♪
♪ There's got to
be a better way ♪
♪ Uma, I promise
I'll give you your chance ♪
♪ You'll have your say ♪
♪ Silly king,
you give me? ♪
♪ You're gonna give me
a chance? ♪
-♪ Well, not a chance! ♪
-♪ Yo-oh, ho-oh, oh-oh ♪
-♪ Make the trade! ♪
♪ Or walk the plank! ♪
♪ Yo-oh, ho-oh, oh-oh ♪
-♪ Make the trade! ♪
-♪ Yo-oh, ho-oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ Or walk the plank! ♪
Hold up. Mm. Too easy.
Why don't you give it
a test drive?
We want to see it work.
(laughs)
You always were
quite the drama queen.
Oh, and nothing too big,
or else Ben is fish bait.
(laughter)
We're dead.
(whimpers)
Okay.
Although it seems absurd,
turn your bark into a word!
Talk, dog.
Does this vest
make me look fat?
(laughter)
Hey, does anyone have
some bacon? Cookies?
(laughs)
-Give me the wand!
-Give me Ben!
Harry, bring him over.
Ooh, um, before you go,
tell your mom
that Gaston says hi
and also tell your dad
that my dad wishes
he'd finished off your dad
when he had the chance.
Oh. Cut him loose, Harry.
(sighs) I never get
to have any fun.
Yes!
Ben, go!
Yeah! (laughs)
-Go! Move!
-Okay, okay.
By the power of the sea,
tear it down and set us free!
(cheers and applause)
No! (grunts)
Ben!
You do not get
to win every time!
Trust me.
Get 'em!
Ben!
♪ ♪
Aah!
Go!
(screams)
Hello, Jay.
Well, well, well.
Aah!
Aaah!
Hey, Ben.
(laughs)
Here, take mine.
Amazeballs!
Hi. You miss me?
(grunting)
Let's dance.
Hey, Gil.
Get out of here, Ben.
Nice scarf.
It's mine now.
Ben.
Oh.
(laughs)
(groans)
(splash)
Aaah!
Harry:
Uma!
Jay, go start the car.
I'll meet
you guys there.
Ben, come on. Go!
Mal's mine!
Hiya.
Coochy, coochy, coo.
♪ Let's go, bring it on ♪
♪ Bring it on, it's going down ♪
♪ Time is running out ♪
Carlos! Smoke bomb.
♪ Let's go, pound for pound ♪
♪ We're prepared
to stand our ground ♪
-(laughs)
-♪ Put your swords up ♪
♪ It's going down ♪
Evie:
Let's go!
-Let's go, now! Go!
-Come on!
♪ Yo-oh, ho-oh,
oh-oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ Yo-oh,
ho-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ What's my name?
What's my name? ♪
-♪ What's my name? ♪
-♪ Uma, Uma-la-la-ooh ♪
♪ Say it nowwwwww! ♪
-You okay?
-Yeah, I'm good.
Nice work out there,
Lonnie.
Come on, Dude, hop in.
Oh, now you listen to me.
-Let's go.
-Come on, Evie, get in.
Let's go.
Mal!
No! Move!
Get out of my way!
Lonnie:
Come on, come on, come on.
Swords.
(engine starts)
(tires screech)
I'm really sorry
that things didn't go
the way you wanted them to.
I mean, as long as
you're safe, that's...
Well, I mean, at least
I got to see the Isle.
They're my people, too.
Uma helped me see that.
Ben, Uma captured you.
She's an angry girl
with a bad plan.
That's not so different
from you when you came
to Auradon, Mal.
Awkward.
Dude, I know you can talk,
but it doesn't always
mean you should.
♪ ♪
Jay: Here we go.
(sighs)
Why don't you
stop by practice later.
What, in the mood
to break some rules?
(scoffs) No.
Lonnie: I'll get these
back to the gym.
-Thanks.
-See you later.
Ben, there you are.
Cotillion's tonight.
Come here.
Look, this is the stained
glass window for Mal.
Isn't it beautiful?
She's gonna love it.
Do you want to cancel?
Um, you know what?
I can come back.
-Uh, but, like,
really, really soon.
-No, no, no.
No, no, no.
Now's fine. Um...
Do whatever
you need to do.
-We need to talk.
-Yeah.
No.
No?
You guys are always
going off in a huddle,
whispering your girl talk
stuff or whatever,
and Jay and I
are tired of it.
I'm not.
We're your family, too.
We've been through
a lot together.
We're not stopping
that now, okay?
-Everyone sit.
-(Dude woofs)
Come on.
-(Dude whines)
-You too.
(sighs)
I don't know how
to start girl talk.
What up?
(laughs)
Um, well...
I'm a mess.
I'm such a mess.
(voice breaking)
I mean, six months ago,
I was, you know,
stealing candy
from babies, and now
everybody wants me to be
this Lady of the Court.
And I have no idea
how to keep up the act.
Then don't.
See? This was dumb.
Maybe it wasn't.
We're always gonna be
the kids from the Isle.
I tried to forget it.
I really tried,
but those are our roots.
And we all did what
we had to do to survive.
But it made us who we are.
And we're never gonna be
like anybody else here.
And that's okay.
That's okay.
And we can't fake it.
No.
Yeah. I mean, especially
without my spell book.
Mal, if Ben doesn't
love the real you,
then he's not the one.
I like that.
Give him a chance.
I'm gonna make some
changes to your dress.
And if you're up for it--
only if you're up for it--
it will be
waiting for you, okay?
(mouthing words)
-Come on, buddy.
-(Dude whines)
(sighs)
Come to Cotillion
tonight, all right?
If Ben isn't smart enough
to love you
and you can't stand
another day,
I'll drive you
back tomorrow myself.
Okay?
Dude:
"Girl talk."
Crushed it.
(laughs)
Yeah, except when it comes
to asking Jane out.
Then I'm
a total chicken.
I'm gonna paraphrase one
of the bravest boys I know.
(clears throat)
If she does not like you,
then she is not the one for you.
You really are
a man's best friend.
-(bells chime)
-Come on, let's go.
Let's bring it in, boys.
Let's bring it in.
(sighs) All right.
You all know I come
from the Isle, right,
where things
are pretty whack.
(chuckles) No,
but there is one thing
the Isle's got on Auradon.
If you're strong,
we want you by our side--
girl or boy.
(scoffs)
Hey, Jay, hold on here.
We don't--
We don't break the rules
here in Auradon.
That's over
on the Isle.
"The team shall be comprised of
a captain and eight men."
So, uh...
give it up for your
new team captain.
-Whoa!
-What?!
(laughs)
Thank you.
Fine.
(whistle blows)
Give me 10!
Come on, guys.
-1, 2...
-Pick it up, Chad.
-3, 4...
-Nice form, Jay.
6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
(whistle blows)
Okay, practice is over.
Get out of here.
Go get ready for Cotillion.
Hey, Jay.
Yeah?
Wait until I tell my mom.
Let's get out of here.
Come in.
I have a scout badge
in s'mores!
How could you go
camping without me?
-What?
-Are you seeing
someone else?
-Are you?
-No.
Is it Happy's son?
Because let me tell you,
he is not as happy as his dad.
Kind of a dark streak,
in fact.
Doug, Ben was captured
on the Isle.
We rescued Ben
and saved Auradon.
So you're not seeing
Happy's son or anyone else?
Don't be dopey.
Besides, we have
dresses to deliver.
It is Cotillion day,
after all.
And you know what?
I was lucky enough
to have been given a chance,
and now I need to give
someone else a chance, too.
My Uncle Bashful
used to say that.
-Did he?
-Yeah.
But really quietly.
(laughs)
Let's do this.
-Mm-hmm. Uh-huh. Say no more.
-Jane. Jane. Jane!
Hey, hey, uh...
-Would you go to
Cotillion with me?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure.
We're all taking a stretch
carriage over at 6:00.
No, no, no. The pen toppers
are in the port side cabin.
No, I--
I mean... with me.
Yeah, want me to
swing by your room?
No, no, no. So, when you're on
the boat facing the left...
Yeah, yeah. Right.
No, no, no. Not right, left.
Uh...(chuckles)
This is gonna be tricky.
Jane?
Would you be my date
for Cotillion?
And if you don't absolutely
hate me by the end of it, um,
would you consider maybe
being more than friends?
-Maybe?
-Like boyfriend
and girlfriend?
Where we can hold hands
instead of slugging
each other all the time?
And we can text, and I can
tell you how great you are?
Because, Carlos, you're
really, really great.
And I'm-- I'm the luckiest
girl in the world!
-You're so nice and cute.
-Me too!
I am the luckiest girl--
I mean guy.
(laughs)
Luckiest guy.
Jane? Can you hear me?
Oh, sorry.
I'll see you later.
-Yeah. Totally.
-Right. So...
Good boy.
(laughs)
Yeah, oh, yeah.
Come on, Dude.
Let's go. Yes!
Finally.
(chuckles)
Oh, what's that?
Why no, Audrey,
I haven't chosen my queen yet.
Why no, Audrey--
(ringtone plays,
cellphone vibrates)
Who could be calling me?
Ohh! Audrey!
Audrey!
Chad! This is
my room, Chad!
What?
Audrey?
Yeah. Yeah?
Well, yeah. Oh, well,
that's wonderful news.
She got a flat tire
in Sherwood Forest,
and she wants me
to go fix it.
That's six hours away.
Really? Only six?
I'm gonna be there faster
than I thought.
Mwah!
Ah, ah.
My printer, my crown.
Oh. Yeah,
about that, I was j--
(laughs) Right.
I'm coming, Audrey!
Wow.
♪ ♪
♪ All the ladies in the house ♪
♪ Put your hands up in the air ♪
♪ All the fellas in the place ♪
♪ Let me see you
break it down ♪
♪ Let me see
you break it down ♪
♪ Let me see you
break it down ♪
(camera shutters clicking)
Man:
Evie, you look beautiful!
-Thank you so much.
-Did you design the barrette?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Uh, no, it's not my creation.
Many of the hair accessories
this evening are by
a fabulous new designer,
"Dizzy of the Isle."
That's me! I made that!
Eeeee!
-(pounding on ceiling)
-Granny: Knock it off!
I'm sorry, Granny!
(gasps)
♪ ♪
♪ I'ma do my thang ♪
♪ Let's be clear,
this is all my lane ♪
♪ Don't stop now,
'cause I'm on a roll ♪
♪ Dance all night,
let's lose control ♪
Jane!
There you are, my dear.
Well, everything looks
beautiful, my love.
But we just need to
ladle out the punch
before the sherbet melts.
Mom, I have a date.
A date? Really?
Do you have a date, too?
-Yeah.
-Really?
Yeah.
Mom.
Bippity boppity.
Oh!
♪ ♪
After you.
(cheers and applause)
(fanfare plays)
The future Lady Mal!
(murmuring)
(gasping)
You work it, girl.
(laughs)
Whoo!
-Yeah, Mal!
-Mal!
(cheers and applause)
-Hi.
Hey,
Ben is on his way.
-Okay.
-And you look beautiful.
Oh, thank you.
(laughs nervously)
I know we were
shocked at first,
but you-- you are
exactly what Ben needs.
And lucky for me, she doesn't
go by first impressions.
(laughing)
Of course.
-Hi.
How are you?
Uh, sort of feel like
I'm gonna throw up.
Yeah? Okay. That's okay.
Look, we're right here
with you, okay?
Okay.
(fanfare plays)
King Benjamin!
(cheers and applause)
-(laughs)
-Whoo!
(murmuring)
Go get him.
Mal, I wish I had
time to explain.
(door opens)
(gasps)
(spectators murmur)
-Hi.
-Hi. Hi.
(gasping)
(giggles)
I'm sorry.
It all happened so fast.
Something happened to me
when I was on the Isle with Uma.
A connection.
What are you saying?
-I'm saying--
-It was love.
(giggles)
It was.
I just-- I realized how alike
Ben and I are, you know?
-We are.
-(laughs) I know.
You're so beautiful.
Ben.
Did you go back for her?
He didn't have to.
I dove through the barrier
before it closed,
and I'm an excellent
swimmer.
-You are.
-Aw, thank you. (laughs)
Listen, Mal.
I just really want
to thank you, I do,
for everything.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
(laughs)
Don't you see, Mal?
You were right.
You knew that we weren't
meant to be together.
That's why you never told me
that you loved me.
-(sighs)
-Thank you.
♪ ♪
Come on.
Not too thrilled
I risked my life for him.
We're with you, Mal.
-Let's get out of here.
-Okay.
Mal.
Honey, we're so sorry.
We had no idea.
I'm gonna talk to him.
Lumiere, unveil the gift.
They need to see it!
And now for the unveiling
of King Ben's masterpiece,
designed especially
for his lady.
(fanfare plays)
(gasping)
(applause)
Ben did that?
Yeah, he did.
Oh!
Evie.
Ben's known
who I was all along.
Oh!
He loves the real you, M.
-A true love.
-Yeah.
-Told you.
-(laughs)
Cover that back up!
I will not!
Um, uh-- why don't you
tell everyone
the present
you have for me, Ben?
I have an announcement!
Uma will be joining the court
tonight as my lady.
-Son...
-Not now, Dad!
The...
Uh, so as my gift to her,
I'm bringing down the barrier
once and for all!
(gasping)
Mateys, we ride with the tide!
-Yeah!
(gasping)
Fairy Godmother.
Bring down the barrier.
I most certainly
will not.
I am your king!
Obey him.
(gasping)
Ben's been spelled.
Ben.
Uma found
your spell book.
Just look at me.
Ben.
-Look at me.
-No, look at me.
-You love me, remember?
-No, you don't.
-Yes, you do.
-Ben, look at me.
Bring down
the barrier now!
I do not take
orders from you!
Ben?
Ben, I never told you
that I loved you because
I thought that
I wasn't good enough.
And I thought that it was only
a matter of time before
you realized that yourself.
But, Ben, that's me!
I'm part Isle
and part Auradon.
Ben, eyes over here.
And, Ben, you've always
known who we were
-and who we can be.
-Don't listen to her.
Ben, I know what
love feels like now.
Ben, of course
I love you.
Ben, I've always
loved you.
(gasping)
Mal.
True love's kiss.
Works every time.
-Ugh, give it to me!
-No! Guards, seize her!
No, no!
Stop, please! Stop!
Uma, I know you.
You are so much more
than just a villain.
And you have to believe me,
because I've been there.
Do not let your pride
get in the way
of something
that you really want.
No, no! Uma!
Ben: Uma!
(screaming)
(laughs)
Ah!
(sighs)
True love's kiss
won't defeat this.
The world will know my name!
Aaah!
(screaming)
Aah!
(thunder crashes)
(laughs)
Mal?
(roaring)
(laughs)
Aah!
Come on, Mal!
Let's finish this
once and for all!
(gasps)
Aah!
Watch out!
(screaming)
(roaring)
(screams)
(thunder crashes)
Wait, Ben! No!
-Ben!
Mal, Uma!
Stop! Back down!
(laughs)
What are you
gonna do, Ben?
Splash me?
(laughs)
That's enough!
It's got to stop!
This isn't the answer!
The fighting has got to stop!
Nobody wins this way!
We have to listen
and respect each other.
It won't be easy, but let's
be brave enough to try.
Uma, I know you want
what is best for the Isle.
Help me make a difference.
(roars)
(splash)
There you go.
Jay:
Good job, man.
(cheers and applause)
(roars)
(thud)
Ooh!
(laughs)
(giggles)
(cheers and applause)
-(sighs)
-Whoo!
So, I did not know
that I could do that.
Tell me about it.
That makes two of us.
-(sizzling)
-Oh. (blows)
-Thank you.
-Shall we?
We shall.
Hi.
(sighs)
(laughter)
All right, all right,
all right, all right.
How about that son of mine?
-Ours.
Yes.
How about his girlfriend?
I think we're in
very good hands here.
Very good hands.
I owe you guys so much.
-Yeah.
-Really.
-Yep.
-You got that right.
-Just a little bit.
-If there is anything
that you need, or anything
I can do for you...
Um, actually, there is, Ben.
I know a girl who would
really love to come to Auradon.
It's Drizella's
daughter, Dizzy.
She's like
a little sister to me.
Then she should come.
Okay! (laughs)
Okay, great!
Actually, um...
(laughter)
Ben, there's a lot of kids
who would really love it
here in Auradon.
Kids just like us, who also
deserve a second chance.
Can I maybe get you a list?
Yes, yes!
Absolutely, please.
(cheers and applause)
Great.
M'lady Mal, we found
your spell book below deck.
Uma had it.
Ooh.
Um...
You know, this seems
like the kind of thing
that belongs in the hands
of Fairy Godmother.
Fairy Godmother?
That's me, thank you.
Mm-hmm.
This belongs
in the museum.
It does, yes,
and I'm gonna take it.
Go for it.
(laughter)
I'm not gonna
be needing it anymore.
(gasping)
(laughs)
Aah!
(cheers and applause)
♪ Looking back
at yesterday ♪
♪ I thought
I gave it everything ♪
♪ But still there's so much
road ahead of me ♪
♪ When I looked
into your eyes ♪
♪ I guess
I didn't recognize ♪
♪ Who we are
and all that we can be ♪
♪ Sometimes it's hard
to find yourself ♪
♪ But it's worth it in the end ♪
♪ 'Cause in your heart
is where it all begins ♪
♪ We got to be bold ♪
♪ We got to be brave ♪
♪ We got to be free ♪
♪ We got to get loud ♪
♪ Making that change ♪
♪ You got to believe ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ We'll look deep inside ♪
♪ And we'll rise up and shine ♪
♪ We can be bold ♪
♪ We can brave ♪
♪ Let everyone see ♪
♪ It starts with you and me ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ It starts with you and me ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ It starts with you and me ♪
♪ There's something special
that I've learned ♪
♪ It's together we can
change the world ♪
♪ Everybody's got something
they can bring ♪
♪ When you take a look
inside yourself ♪
♪ Do you wish that
you were something else ♪
♪ But who you are is
who you need to be ♪
♪ Sometimes it's hard
to find yourself ♪
♪ But it's worth it in the end ♪
♪ 'Cause in your heart
is where it all begins ♪
♪ We got to be bold ♪
♪ We got to be brave ♪
♪ We got to be free ♪
♪ We got to get loud ♪
♪ Making that change ♪
♪ You got to believe ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ We'll look deep inside ♪
♪ And we'll rise up and shine ♪
♪ We can be bold ♪
♪ We can brave ♪
♪ Let everyone see ♪
♪ It starts with you and me ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ It starts with you and me ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Hey! It starts
with you and me ♪
♪ If we all can do our part ♪
♪ We know that it can
be the start ♪
♪ To bring about
the difference that we need ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I promise
we can work this out ♪
♪ I promise we can
see it through ♪
♪ Don't you know it's up to me ♪
♪ It's up to me and you ♪
♪ We got to be bold ♪
♪ We got to be brave ♪
♪ We got to be free ♪
♪ Gonna be free ♪
♪ We got to get loud ♪
♪ Making that change ♪
♪ You got to believe ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ We'll look deep inside ♪
♪ And we'll rise up and shine ♪
♪ We can be bold ♪
♪ We can brave ♪
♪ Let everyone see ♪
♪ It starts with you and me ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ It starts with you and me ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ It starts with you and me ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Hey! It starts
with you and me ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ It starts with you and me ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ It starts with you and me ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ It starts with you and me ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ It starts with you and me ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ It starts with you and me ♪
(fireworks exploding)
(cheers and applause)
(dance music plays)
♪ You and me ♪
♪ It starts with you and me ♪
"His Royal Majesty,
King Ben of Auradon
"and his Counselor,
Ms. Evie of the Isle,
"hereby request
the pleasure of your company,
"Dizzy Tremaine, for the current
academic year at Auradon Prep.
"Please notify
His Majesty's couriers
"of your response
to this request.
"We'd love you to join us
at Auradon Prep.
"Will you come?
Signed, King Ben."
(screams)
-(pounding on ceiling)
-Granny: Zip it up!
(laughs) Yay!
What?
You didn't think this was
the end of the story, did you?
(laughs)
♪ There you see her ♪
♪ Sitting there across the way ♪
♪ She don't got a lot to say ♪
♪ But there's something
about her ♪
♪ And you don't know why,
but you're dying to try ♪
♪ You want to kiss the girl ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Sha-la-la-la-la-la,
don't be scared ♪
♪ You got the mood prepared ♪
♪ Go on and kiss the girl ♪
♪ Kiss the girl ♪
♪ Sha-la-la-la-la-la-la,
you can play ♪
♪ Let the music play ♪
-♪ That's right, kiss the girl ♪
-♪ Go on and kiss the girl ♪