♪♪
The Rumors Have
Been Out Of Control
Ever Since The Night Of
The Final Competition.
Some People Think
Danny Ran Away,
That He's In Hiding.
Others Think He Never
Existed In The First Place.
But Believe Me, He Is Real.
I Know. I--I Was There.
Some Of What
I Witnessed Was...
Pretty Terrifying.
I Saw Things That Were
So... Strange,
So... Unexpected.
Well, As Much
As I Like To Think
I'm A Champion
Puzzle Solver
Even I Still Haven't
Figured Out
Exactly How It
All Went Down.
But One Thing
I Am Sure Of...
Danny Sinclair Is
Definitely Real
And Unlike Anybody
You've Ever Met.
Oh, And Also,
What I'm About To Show You.
Was Never, Ever Meant
To Be Seen.
I Was Hired To Be
A Segment Producer
Of A New Reality
Tv Show,
Assigned To Make Sure
Every Bit Of Action
Got Caught On Tape.
Everybody
Take A Seat, Please.
Thank You.
As Thrilled As We Are That
This Is The First Show
In Television History
To Be Produced
Entirely By Kids,
Not All Of You
Will Remain.
Only Those Who Discover
One Of The 3
Final Magicians
Will Stay With Us
Through The Grand Finale.
Think You're
All Up For It?
Oh, Definitely!
Good.
Thank You. Heh Heh!
Before We Proceed,
What Is The Single Most
Important Rule For
Making Good Television?
Oh!
Make Sure They Spell
Your Name Right
In The Credits.
Yeah. Yes, And You Are?
Allyson Miller. I Think
The Most Important Rule
Of Good Television
Is To Always
Keep Your Camera Rolling.
Excellent.
I Couldn't Have
Said It Better Myself.
Actually, You Did.
I Remembered It
From A Quote You Gave
In An Interview
With Tv Weekly.
October Of 2002.
Well, It's Nice To Know
One Of You Came Prepared.
And Now It Is My Pleasure
To Introduce You
To Someone I'm Sure You Are
All Familiar With.
He Is Both
A World Renowned Magician
And The Host Of Our New
Reality Television Show,
Please Welcome
The Amazing Mystic Max.
Thank You.
Good Morning,
Ladies And Gentlemen.
100 Talented Magicians
Between The Ages
Of 10 And 16
Became Eligible For Our Show
By Figuring Out The Hidden
Message In This Poster.
It Appeared On Billboards,
In Magazines,
In Newspapers
And On The Internet.
Hidden Somewhere In This Ad
Is A Secret Message.
Just Out Of Curiosity,
Did Any One Of You
Find The Hidden Message?
Allyson.
Big Surprise.
Would You Care
To Show Us?
Well, As We All Know
Magicians Say The Secret
To Any Good Trick
Is Misdirection.
That Means They're Trying To Get You
To Focus Over Here While They
Do Some Hocus Pocus Over There.
So Most People Probably Thought
The Clues Would Be Found
In The Magician
And His Trick
Because That's What
First Draws Your Eye,
But Truth Is It's
The Background Things
You Need To Focus On.
See, The Spider Web
Made Me Realize
It Was Probably There To
Direct Us To A Web Site.
Then On Looking Closer At The
Book The Statue Is Holding
I Saw That It Was
A Farewell To Arms,
And Then Bam! It Hit Me!
I Mean Everybody Knows
That The Venus De Milo
Is A Statue With No Arms.
Sure.
And That Made Me Think Of The
Famous Founder Of The Magic Mansion,
A Magician Named
Antonio Demilo.
I Mean, How Obvious
Could It Be?
This Is
A Joke, Right?
I Went On-Line,
Typed In Demilo.Net
And Got Linked Directly
To The Contest Entry Form.
Simple, Right?
Well Done, Allyson.
Oh! Thanks.
Know-It-All.
Allyson, VOICE-OVER: Ok,
So I'm Not The Best At Making Friends.
I Know I Can Seem Like
A Bit Of A Know-It-All
But I Really Don't Mean To.
It's Not Fault People Ask Me
Questions And I Have Answers.
I Mean, What Am I
Supposed To Do?
Hey, I'd Love It If Kids My Own
Age Could Actually Relate To Me.
I Mean I've Tried Pretending
I'm Into Lip Gloss
And Text Messaging
And Hanging Out At The Mall.
I Just Can't Ever Seem
To Pull It Off.
Ok, Sorry. What Got Me Off
On That Rant?
I Have No Idea.
Seriously, I'm Not The Story
Here. Danny Is.
Ms. Mcallister Divided Us
Into Teams.
Each Team Had A Kid Producer,
A Kid Cameraperson.
And An Adult Mentor.
Our Team Was Me,
Our Camera Guy Cedric...
Peace.
And Our Mentor
Whose Name Was Paul.
We Were Sent To Find
The One Kid Who Could
Best Represent His Region
On The Show.
That's Good Work,
People, Good Work.
We Had Not Idea
What We Were In For.
Ok, Good Luck, Everybody.
Let's Do This.
Come On. Hey!
Hi. Are You Blake?
Yes, I Am.
Hi, I'm Allyson.
Nice To Meet You.
We're With The World's
Greatest Magician.
Wow! Sweet!
Yeah! You Ready
To Show Us What You Got?
Yeah, Let's Go.
Ok, Let's Do It.
World's Greatest
Magician,
Contestant
Number One, Action!
Don't Take It Easy On Me.
Get It Super Tight.
Good Luck, Buddy.
Unh!
I Present...
Siegfried...
As Dog Gone!
Ok, Now Be Prepared
To Be Astounded
As I Show You The Card
You Just Picked.
Ta-Da!
Um, No.
The Astonishing
Linking Rings.
Unh!
Um... Brian?
Ok, I'm Positive That
This Is Your Card.
No.
This Your Card?
Ugh!
Unh! Unh! Oh!
Go Back In! Go!
This One. This One!
This One?
First, I Take An Egg...
Crack It Into The Hat,
Add Some Flour
And A Little Milk.
After I Stir It All Up
And Place It On Your Head
A Cake Will Magically...
Oh, Wait, Wait, Wait!
Appear.
You Forgot
The Rubber Cake.
Oops.
Ok. So Basically
I Could Describe
My Contestants
In 2 Words:
Impressively Pathetic.
Hmph! Bummer, Right?
If I Didn't Find Someone Who Was
Cool Enough To Put On A Show,
My First Chance At A Career
Was Gonna Be Over
Before It Ever Started.
Cedric And I
Were Down To Our Last Hope.
Oh!
Hey!
Ok, This Better
Be Good.
Hi. Nice To Meet
You People.
Hi.
Nice To Meet You.
We're So Glad
You're Here.
Yeah.
This Is All Danny's Been Talking About For Weeks.
Great, Good, Awesome,
Perfect, Yeah.
He's Been Very,
Very Anxious To Meet You People,
Heh!
Uh, Please Come In. Yeah.
Oh, Ok.
Hello.
Uh...
Heh!
Hi. Danny.
Hi. Allyson.
Nice To Meet You.
Paul.
I'm Danny. Welcome.
Ready To Show Us
What You Got?
Heh. Only One Way
To Find Out.
Contestant Number 10
Danny Sinclair.
And... Action.
1... 2...
3!
Let Me Guess.
The Incredible Popping Balloon.
No, No. See, What's
Supposed To Happen
Is I Pop The Balloon
And A Dove Flies Out.
I've Done It
A Million Times.
Ok.
Just Let Me Try It
Again, Ok?
Be My Guest.
Ok. 1... 2...
3!
All Right, One More
Time, One More Time.
All Right, 1...
2... 3!
All Right, Next Time-- Next Time For Sure,
Next Time For Sure.
You Know,
Maybe You Want To Try A Different Trick.
No, I Can Do This,
All Right? I Can Do This.
You Need Any Help?
You Want An Assistant?
I Mean, We Could Always
Try A Different Camera--
I'm Gonna Do It, All Right?
You Just Gotta Back Off...
And Give Me
Another Chance.
This Really Matters
To You, Huh?
More Than You Can
Possibly Know.
Well, If It Makes You
Feel Any Better
I Seriously Need
For It To Happen, Too.
You're My Last Chance.
Yeah, And You're Mine,
So...
Let's Just Do This. Ok?
This Time...
This Time It's Definitely,
Definitely Going To Work.
Ok.
1... 2...
3!
Yeah.
Thanks, Kid.
No, No, No, Wait A Minute,
Please, I Can Do This.
Ok, I Can--I Can Do This.
Peace.
Guys, Guys, Plea--
Oh.
I Bet The Only Reason We Did A Bajillion Takes
Was Because Allyson Thinks The Guy's Cute.
The Only Reason
I Did A Bajillion Takes
Was Because Our Other 9
Magicians Really Stunk.
I--I Can't Believe I'm
Gonna Be Off The Show.
Hey, Now You Don't
Know That.
One Of Our Magicians
Could Still Get Picked.
You Seriously
Think So?
No!
But As Your Mentor I'm Supposed To Be Encouraging.
Whoa!
Ha Ha!
Tell Me You're Rolling!
I'm Rolling!
I Got It, I Got It!
Cedric, You Rock!
Wow, Man!
This Kid Is Good!
You Think Danny
Did This?
Of Course He Did.
Who Else?
Allyson, VOICE-OVER:
Ok, Totally Bizarre, I Know.
I Mean Danny Should've Been
Looking Really Happy Just Then,
But The Expression I Saw
On His Face...
Seemed A Whole Lot
More Like... Fear.
You're Right, Allyson.
Very Impressive.
Very Impressive,
Indeed.
Yes!
I Told You It Was
Unbelievable.
Yeah, A Little
Too Unbelievable.
What Are
You Saying, Hunter?
Isn't It Obvious?
Her And That Danny
Kid Must've Worked
The Whole Thing Out
Ahead Of Time.
They've Been Scamming Us From The Start.
We Were Not.
Oh, Get Real!
There's No Way You Pulled That Off Unless You Helped.
Hunter, Allyson Wouldn't
Do Something Like That, Ok?
She Knows The Rules.
Colluding With A Contestant
Is Strictly Forbidden.
Well, We All Know
How Much She Likes
To Be The Best
At Everything.
I Was There. I Mean,
I Saw The Whole Thing.
So What?
He's On Her Team.
Maybe He's Just As Big A Cheater As She Is.
We Didn't Cheat, Ok?
Yeah, Honest. I Mean--
Paul, You Were There.
What's Your Assessment?
Honestly, I Think This Kid's Real Deal.
I Guess We Found Our Last Contestant, Max.
Yes! Justice Prevailed.
Danny Made It Onto The Show,
Which Meant That I Did, Too.
I Was Going To Be A Part Of The
Coolest Reality Program Ever Filmed.
I've Been Thinking
A Lot About It
And You Know The Way You
Set Us Up Back At Your House
With The Whole,
"Oops! I'm Incompetent,
It's All A Big Disaster"
Thing Before You
Completely Blew Our
Minds With The Doves?
That Would Be The Perfect
Approach To Use In The Show, Too.
It'll Catch Everybody Off Guard And They Will Love You.
You Could Come Up With
Something Like That Again, Right?
Yeah, Yeah, Sure.
Whatever.
Great!
Oh, And The Other Thing We Need To Talk About
Is Costumes.
I Want Something Eye-Catching But Not Flashy,
Classy But Not Some All Black Funeral Guy Look.
Ooh!
What We Really Need Is Some Kind Of-- Of A Gimmick.
Wow.
An Exploding Wand,
A Parrot Sidekick--
Allyson, All Right,
Pick Any Card.
Um, Ok.
Any Card.
You Got It?
Yeah.
All Right, Place It
Right There.
All Right, Here's
What I'm Donna Do.
All I Want You To Do
Is Say "Jump."
Jump.
Right There.
Oh! Whoa!
Pretty Good.
That's Awesome.
Here, Here, Here.
Why Don't You Do This? Pick A Card.
You Want Me
To Pick A Card?
Pick A Card. I Want
You To Pick A Card.
All Right, Memorize It.
I Got It.
Put It Back Anywhere In The Deck.
All Right, You Got It?
I Got It.
All Right.
Is That Your Card?
Awesome, Dude!
That's My Card.
Oh! That Was Awesome!
But This Whole Mopey,
Brooding Thing You've Got Going On,
It's Seriously
Not Gonna Work For Tv.
Too Boring.
Wow.
Yes.
Welcome To
The Magic Mansion
And Congratulations
To Our 3 Finalists.
It's A Real Honor
To Meet You.
I'm Zoe And I'm From Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
The Honor Is Mine, Zoe.
I Am Brandon. I'm From
San Francisco, C-A.
Good To Meet
You, Brandon.
I'm Danny
From Pensacola.
Yes.
I've Been Looking Forward To Meeting You, Danny.
I'd Like You All To Think Of This As Your Home.
Follow Me.
Wow.
In Its
Illustrious History,
A Very Few Select People
Have Ever Been Allowed
Inside This Mansion.
That's Because Very Magic
Secret Known To A Man
And A Few Not
Yet Revealed
Are Hidden
Within These Walls.
While Here
During This Competition
You May Use Every Prop,
Every Book,
Every Illusion We Have,
And I Suggest
You Take Advantage Of It.
Remember, You Never Know
How Strong Your Magic Is
Until You Test It.
Good Night.
Oh, By The Way,
You Might Want To Search Your
Pockets For Your Room Keys.
Whoa!
Danny.
Ok, Look, Danny,
This Is How It's Going To Be
For The Next 7 Days.
You And I Are Gonna Be Like This!
I Want To Know
Everything About You.
I Want To Know What You're
Doing And What You're Thinking
24 Hours A Day
Every Day.
Right Now I'm Thinking
That This Is My Room.
So?
So I'll See You
Tomorrow.
Wait A Minute. We're Not
Done Talking Here.
One Of Us Is.
You're Blocking My Door.
So?
So Can We Continue This
Tomorrow, Please?
I Have Things
I Need To Take Care Of.
What Kind Of Things?
None Of Your Business!
Danny, I Don't Think You're Getting It.
Everything About You
Here Is My Business.
My Business Is To Follow Your Every Move.
Who Is This Girl?
Look, I've Watched Liked A Gazillion Hours
Of These Shows, Even
The Really Gross Ones,
You Know, Where They Have To Dive
Into A Vat Of Cockroach Larvae--
What's Your Point?
The Contestants Who Get
The Most Screen Time
Are The Ones Who Are Wildly Charismatic,
Extremely Competitive
And Have Usually
Overcome
Some Heartbreaking
Obstacle To Get Here.
Right Now The Only Heartbreaking
Obstacle In My Life Is You.
Oh, Come On, Please!
We're A Team.
Oh, Yeah? Then How
About A Team Cheer?
Like, Uh,
Go, Team, Go!
Ha Ha Ha!
Danny, You're Not
Funny! Open Up!
Look, There's Things About Me
You're Not Gonna Understand
Not Matter
How Much We Talk.
So How About
We Make A Deal.
I Promise I Will Do Whatever I
Can To Win This Thing For You
As Long As The Rest
Of The Time
You Leave Me Alone.
All Right.
Excuse Me, Did He
Seriously Think
A Bargain Like That
Would Stop Me?
Ugh! I Mean,
What Was He Up To?
And Why Was He Being
So Mysterious?
As Far As
I Was Concerned
Danny Sinclair Was My Favorite Kind Of Challenge:
Just One More Puzzle
Begging To Be Solved.
My Mentor And The Founder
Of The Magic Mansion
Antonio Demilo
Was Once Asked,
What Is A Magician's
Greatest Asset?
And He Replied--
"A Magician's
Greatest Asset
Is The Ability To Think
In Unusual Ways."
Well, That's Very
Impressive, Mr. Sinclair.
Yes, The Ability To
Think In Unusual Ways,
And That Is Exactly
What The Nature
Of Your First
Challenge Entails.
Watch Carefully.
A Basketball.
Oh!
Oh, Wow!
A Rope.
A Broom,
A 10-Gallon Aquarium
And A Bed Sheet.
5 Very Different Yet Common
Household Items
And You Have
Exactly 30 Minutes
To Create An Illusion
Using Any Or All
Of These 5 Objects.
Just Those Things
And Nothing Else?
Just Those Things,
Nothing Else.
And The Clock Is Ticking.
I Know. It's Gonna Be
Totally Perfect.
Where
Are My Cameramen?
There's Cedric.
So, Uh, Danny, Now That
You've Done All This
Intense But Not Very Interesting To Watch Thinking,
Anything You'd Like To
Hop Up And Show Us?
Anything You Want
To Try?
Any Probably Futile But Charming
First Attempt You'd Care To Perform?
Have I Mentioned You're Making
It Hard For Me To Concentrate?
Ok, Maybe You've Never
Watched Much Tv,
But As I Said Before
It Has To Be Active,
It Has To Be Captivating-- Where Are You Going?
I Can't Do This.
What Do You Mean? No, No, No,
You Have To Do This.
Listen, I Shouldn't Have Came Here In The First Place,
Especially Not If I Knew
I'd End Up With You.
It Might Help If You Try
Clueing Me In, You Know.
What's This Really About?
Is It Stage Fright?
Are You Freaked Out
About Having To Perform
In Front Of
A Bunch Of Cameras?
If You Are,
I Totally Understand.
Just Tell Me And We Can
Figure Out How To Work On It.
It's Not Stage Fright.
Then What?
I'm Only Trying To Help.
Yeah, Well, You Can't.
I'm Not The Enemy,
You Know.
Cedric And I
Are Your Friends.
Right, Cedric?
Cedric! Attention, Please!
Yeah, Thanks.
Huh?
I Was Trying
To Assure Danny
That He's Got Whatever Support He Needs
Because You And I
Are Here For Him.
Yeah, For Sure.
See?
Great. Well, Now That
We Have That Established
Let's Just Cut
The Chitter-Chatter
So I Can Focus
On My Trick.
Uh... Good.
100 Have Tried,
But Only 3 Have Survived.
And Now The Stakes
Get Even Higher.
3 Kids, 7 Days,
Only One Winner.
Who Will Be The World's
Greatest Kid Magician?
The Challenge Begins.
Zoe
From Philadelphia.
♪ Do You Believe
In Magic ♪
♪ In A Young
Girl's Heart? ♪
♪ How The Music
Can Free Her... ♪
Anybody Can Bounce
A Basketball,
But How Many Can
Do This?
♪ It Makes You Feel Happy
Like An Old-Time Movie ♪
♪ I'll Tell You
About Some Magic ♪
♪ It'll Free Your Soul ♪
♪ But If I Try To Tell
A Stranger ♪
♪ About Rock 'N' Roll ♪
♪ If You Believe In Magic
Don't Bother To Choose ♪
♪ If It's Jug Band Music
Or Rhythm And Blues ♪
♪ Just Go And Listen,
It'll Start With A Smile ♪
♪ It Won't
Wipe Off Your Face ♪
♪ Not Matter
How Hard You Try ♪
Allyson, VOICE-OVER:
Zoe's Trick Was Pretty Cool.
Max Must've Thought So, Too,
Because He Gave Her
A 7 Out Of
A Possible 10.
Not Bad For Starters.
♪ Do You Believe
In Magic? ♪
And Then...
It Was Danny's Turn.
So What Are You
Gonna Do?
Not A Clue.
I'm Not Laughing.
Good.
Because Neither Am I.
A Fish Tank.
Uh, A Basketball.
A Rope, A Broom.
Yeah, We Know.
Please Let Him
Do His Trick.
A Rope...
Broom.
Don't Blink Because All
The Objects You See Here,
They're, Uh...
They're Gonna Disappear.
Right! You Don't Stand
A Snowball's Chance
In You-Know-Where
Of Pulling That Off.
Oh, Yeah? Watch
And Be Amazed.
1... 2...
3.
No Way.
What Is That?
Hey, What's Going On?
Don't Stop.
Keep Going, Keep Rolling.
Whoa.
Very Impressive.
That's Truly Original.
Uh... Thanks.
Yeah, But Nothing
Disappeared.
What--What's With
That White Stuff?
The Trick Is Nothing.
It's Real Snow.
Who Does
This Guy Think He Is?
Hey, Hunter, Catch!
Wait. You Said
The Contestants
Can Only Use The 5 Original Objects,
But He Used This.
Yeah! Snow Isn't
One Of The Props.
That's Ridiculous!
He Just Did
The Most Amazing Trick
I've Ever Seen.
It Doesn't Matter.
Rules Are Rules.
Only The Original 5 Objects, Max.
That's What You Said.
Yes, The Challenge Was To
Think In Unusual Ways, Danny,
And You Certainly
Accomplished That.
Yes!
But Technically Speaking
Hunter Is Right.
You Were Meant To
Use 5 Objects Only,
So I'm Gonna
Give You A 3.
Yes!
Ok, Let's Clean Up The Stage.
Brandon, You're Next.
If It's Ok,
I'd Like To Use An Assistant For This.
Danny's Right There.
Use Him.
But--
Oh,
Stand By. Here We Go.
Everybody Get Ready.
Oh. I Call This
Trick...
Clean Sweep.
Heh Heh Heh!
Now, Danny,
If You Could Unfold This Sheet
And Hold It Up
Like A Curtain.
Easy Enough.
All Right, Danny,
If You Could Raise The Sheet A Bit Higher.
You Know,
Technically I'm Not One Your 5 Approved Items.
Just Raise The Sheet, Ok?
Don't Be A Freak. Heh Heh!
And Now For The Most Amazing Feat You Have Ev--
Brandon? Uh-Oh.
Brandon?
Heh!
That's--I Don't Know.
Go With It.
Max Seems Ok.
That Is So Crazy.
Just Keep Rolling.
Will You Slow Down?
What Happened Back There?
It Was Brandon's Trick.
You Ask Him.
No, I Saw--
Saw What?
I Think You're
Hiding Something.
Yeah, Well,
You're Wrong.
Are You Gonna Start
Letting Me In?
If Something's Going On
Maybe I Could Help.
Thanks, But No Thanks.
I Need To Sort This Out Myself.
I Can't Be Your Friend
If You Don't Give Me
Something To Work With,
You Know.
Look, I Realize
I Come On A Little Strong
And Maybe... Well,
I'm Sure I've Gotten
Too Caught Up In Trying
To Figure You Out,
But I've Got A Feeling We Might
Actually Really Like Each Other
If We Didn't Have To Be In Combat Mode Every Second.
Ok.
Uhh!
Can We Try Calling A Truce For A Minute Or Two?
Sure, Why Not?
Great. So How Did Brandon
End Up On That Wheel?
I Don't Know. You're
The Puzzle Solver.
Why Don't
You Tell Me?
Ugh!
This Is Where He Was
Standing, Right?
How Should I Know?
Can We Do This In The Morning?
I Mean This Place
Creeps Me Out.
No Trapdoor.
There's No Way Brandon Could've Pulled That Trick Off
Without A Trapdoor.
Who Cares How Brandon
Pulled Off The Trick?
I Mean, It's Past
Curfew, It's Dark.
We're Gonna Get Caught.
Shh! Someone's COMING!
I Know There's
A Trapdoor Here.
Hi, Guys.
What Are You
Doing Here?
Same Thing You Are.
Admiring The Fine Workmanship Of The Floorboards.
Pretty Impressive Trick You Did This Afternoon.
Sometimes I Even
Amaze Myself.
I'm Sure You Do.
No Trapdoor.
Yeah, So?
Let's Just Say This.
I Have No Idea What Really Went On,
But I Know It Wasn't You Who Pulled It Off.
Ok, So Prove It.
Maybe I Will.
Ooh-Ooh!
Look, There's Gotta Be A Trapdoor Here Somewhere.
Keeping Looking.
Look Over There.
Ok.
Good Morning,
Everyone.
I Trust You Had
A Good Night's Rest.
Now Let's Start.
For The Second Challenge
Each Contestant
Will Receive A Wand
Bearing A Famous
Magician's Name.
Zoe.
Oh, Wow!
Alexander Herrmann.
Brandon.
Oh! Harry Blackstone.
And Last But Not Least,
The Great Harry Houdini
Is For Danny.
Oh!
Wow!
The Challenge For You Three
Is To Research Your Magician.
Select And Perform
His Most Renowned Trick.
Buona Fortuna.
No Way!
This Is So Cool.
That's Awesome.
Ohh. Anybody Seen Danny?
Can't Exactly Say
I've Been Looking.
He's Probably Somewhere
In The Stacks.
You Know What?
Get Some Shots Of This And I'll Find Danny.
Sounds Good.
Hey, This Is Great.
You're Actually Studying.
What's Up?
I'm, Uh--
I Don't See Any Houdini
Books Here In This Mess.
Don't Worry About It.
I've Got That Wired.
Then What's This
All About?
It's, Um, A Long Story.
I've Got Time. Hmm.
Ok, You're Always Claiming To Be The Puzzle Queen.
Maybe You Actually
Can Help.
I'd Love To.
See, Every Book Or Web Site I've
Read About The Magic Mansion
Talks About Its Secret Rooms Or Hidden Chambers.
I Mean
Even Max Mentioned
All The Magical Mystery
That This Place Holds.
Ok, More
Information, Please.
Well, I've Been Searching
Through These Books That Are
Supposed To Tell The Mansion History, But...
I Mean They Were
No More Revealing
Than Anything I Could've Gotten Out Of A Public Library.
Where's All
The Secret Stuff?
It's Gotta Be Around
Here Someplace.
Hold On.
W-What Are You Doing?
J-Just Give Me
A Second, Ok?
Could You Please Tell Me
What You're Doing?
Look, See How
Some Of These Books
Have Markings On Their Bindings And Others Don't?
We Need To Find All Those That Have This Symbol.
Come On.
All Right, What Now?
See This On The Binding?
I'm Betting These Are
Your Puzzle Pieces, Pal.
Now It's Up To Us
To Solve It.
Allyson,
You're Brilliant.
Thanks For Noticing.
Don't Mention It.
Let's Get To Work.
Ok, Uh...
Oh, Try This One.
Switch Those Two.
The Head Goes--
Yeah.
Oh, This One.
Yeah, That's The Head,
There's The Tail.
Danny, Look.
Wow!
Serpents.
There's 2 Serpents--
Do You Recognize It?
I've Seen This.
I Can't Believe
You Figured This Out.
Well, Come On,
Anybody Could Have Done It.
Not Me.
I've Seen This
Someplace Before.
There It Is.
What Does It Mean?
It Means If We Want To Figure
Out Where This Is Leading Us,
We Have To Find
This Symbol.
We Find The Symbol,
We Find The Secret Room.
Follow Me.
Great.
Let's Get Cedric.
This Way.
Come On.
Uh, Guys, I Don't Think
This Is Such A Good Idea.
Would You Rather Stay
Here By Yourself?
No.
Ok, It's Got To Be
The Other Way.
Come On.
Yes!
Look Out!
Aah!
What Was That?
Follow Me.
This Place Gives Me
The Creeps.
Great.
A Dead End.
Hey, Guys,
Let's Get Out Of Here.
Wait, Wait, Wait.
This Is It.
This Is The Symbol.
Ok, So We Found It.
Now What Do We Do?
I Don't Know.
Just Come On,
Help Me Out.
Ok, That's It.
I'm Getting Out Of Here.
Hold On, Hold On,
Hold On, Hold On.
Maybe This Is A Clue.
"Qui Libri Legat Aracana Intra Reperiet."
What Does That Mean?
It Means "Whoever Reads Books Finds Secrets Within."
Or Maybe
It's A Misdirection.
That's What
I'm Thinking.
This Book Is
Made Of Stone
And If You Want To Read A Book,
You Have To--
You Have To Turn The Pages!
Whoa.
We Really Ought To Get
Out Of Here. Something's--
Let's Get
Out Of Here!
You Guys Ready?
Are You Getting This?
Uh-Huh.
Come On, Cedric.
Have I Mentioned That
I'm A Little Claustrophobic?
Will You Come On?
We Need You.
This Is
Pretty Creepy.
I'm Not Sure
I'm Really Claustrophobic--
Shh! We Probably Don't
Need Anybody To Know
That We're Here.
Why Not?
It's Not Like Anything Bad
Is Gonna Happen, Right?
How Did You
Do That?
With A Lot Of Practice.
Aah!
Now How Are We Gonna
Get Out Of Here?
Guys, This Way.
Come On.
Oh, Now What?
Wow, Here It Is.
Wow.
Hey, Guys,
Have I Mentioned That I'm Really,
Really, Really
Claustrophobic?
Just Get In Here, Cedric.
I Can't Believe It.
We Found De Milo's
Secret Library.
Now That We're Here,
What Are We Looking For?
Hey, Guys,
I Wonder What
This Does?
Cedric, Wait!
No, Don't!
Ha Ha Ha!
That Was Awesome!
Can Someone Please Explain
To Me What Just Happened?
I Don't Know,
But Things Just Keep
Getting Stranger
By The Second.
No Kidding.
Let's Get Out Of Here.
I Hope You're Ready
For Your Next Challenge.
I Proudly Present To You
A Classic Trick Invented
By Alexander Herrmann,
But Performed By Countless
Renowned Magicians
Over The Years.
Aw!
They're So Cute.
Maybe That One's Stuck.
For Generations,
Harry Blackstone Amazed People
With His Levitation
Of A Light Bulb.
I Will Now Attempt
The Same Illusion.
Whoa.
He Got An 8.
That's Great.
All Right, You're Up.
Although Houdini
Was World Famous
For His Incredible Escapes,
What You're About To Witness
Was The Most Mystifying
Stage Illusion Ever.
To This Day,
Very Few People People Know
How Houdini Made
A 10,000 Pound Elephant
Vanish In A Flash.
And Now,
Ladies And Gentlemen,
As I Attempt To Recreate
This Stunning Feat,
May I Present To You
My Very Own Highly-Trained,
Yet Deadly, Dangerous,
Wild Elephant.
You Know,
I Might Be Dressed Like An Elephant,
But I Feel Like
A Horse's Behind.
Get Over It.
All Right?
And Now,
Ladies And Gentlemen,
For The First Time
In Over 80 Years,
May I Present To You
Houdini's Original...
Yee-Hah!
Ha Ha Ha!
Vanishing Elephant.
Whoa!
Ha Ha Ha!
Uhh!
Hey, Hey, Brandon?
You Ok?
What?
Ok, People!
Everybody Keep Quiet!
Everybody Calm Down!
One At A Time!
He Has To Be
Kicked Off The Show.
You're Just Jealous.
Your Guy Levitated
A 60-Watt Light Bulb.
I Mean, My Guy Made
A Mechanical Bull Appear.
That's Exactly
My Point.
There's No Way
He Could Do That.
But He Did.
Ok, How?
How Did You Do It?
A Good Magician
Never Reveals
The Secrets Of His Tricks.
Or Maybe It's
Because He Can't.
Because It
Wasn't A Trick.
Then What Was It, Hunter?
I, Uh--
I Think Maybe
It Was Real.
Real?
Like, What If He Actually
Has Magical Powers?
Yeah, Right.
Do You Have Any Idea
How Crazy You Sound?
Look, It's Possible, Ok?
I Mean, There's A Lot
Of Bizarre Things
We Can't Explain Like E.S.P.,
Mind Readers--
And Donald Trump's Hair.
And People Who Make Mechanical
Bulls Appear Out Of Thin Air.
Exactly.
And While We're At It,
I Think It Was Danny Here
Who Made Brandon Disappear
During The First Challenge.
Look, As Much As I Believe
It's A Total Violation
Of The Magician's Code,
Why Don't You Just Tell Them
How You Did Your Trick
So We Can Move On.
You Heard Her, Man.
Give It Up.
Yeah, Come On.
Just Tell Us All How You Did It, Ok?
We Really Want
To Know.
Ok, Fine!
All Right, Hunter's Right.
Huh?
I Don't Know
How I Did It.
I Don't Understand Anything
About Any Of This.
These Things
Just Happen To Me!
Ok, There.
You Happy?
Very Good, Danny.
That's The Ideal Answer.
You're Really Learning How To Play This Game,
Aren't You?
What's That Supposed
To Mean?
Danny Just Evoked One
Of The Oldest Tricks
In The Magician's
Black Bag.
I Have No Idea What
You're Talking About.
Do You Realize
How Many Classic Illusionists
Have Garnered
Endless Reams Of Publicity
By Claiming To Have
Actual Paranormal Powers?
But I'm Serious,
All Right?
I Don't Know How That
Mechanical Contraption Got There.
Brandon Said He Felt
Like A Horse's Rear End
And There It Was.
Well, That's
Very Interesting.
So, I Suppose
You'll Have No Objection
To My Getting Together
A Group Of Distinguished Experts
To Test Your Claim?
Well, What Sort Of Experts
Are We Talking About, Max?
Well, As President Of The Worldwide Skeptics Society,
You Might Want
To Start With Me.
Worldwide Skeptics?
You?
Surprised?
Don't Be.
No One Knows Better
Than A Professional Magician
What Nonsense
Real Powers Are.
In Fact, There's A Long,
Illustrious History
Of True Magicians Debunking
Paranormal Pretenders.
Because What We Do Is,
We Provide Precisely
Practiced Entertainment,
And Every Fraud
Who Comes Along
Only Serves
To Devalue Our Skills.
So What Do You Say,
Young Man?
Would You Like To Settle This
Nonsense Once And For All?
Danny!
Are You In There?
The Panel Of Experts
Was Waiting
And Danny Was Nowhere
To Be Found.
Call It My Own E.S.P.
Or Whatever,
But After Checking
Every Place I Could Think Of,
I Finally Found Him.
What Are You
Doing In Here?
The Panel's Waiting.
Danny?
It's No Use.
I Can't Do This.
What?
Why Not?
Whatever Way It Ends Up,
It's Just Gonna Be A Complete Disaster For Me.
Why?
So Far, You've Played It
Perfectly.
Seriously,
Do You Have Any Idea
What Great Tv
You've Been Creating?
Wait, You Don't--
You Don't Honestly Think
You Have Real Powers,
Do You?
Look, I Need To Explain
Something To You,
But You Got To Promise Me
That You Will
Just Sit There Quietly
And Just Let Me
Get Through It.
I'll Be As Silent
As A Monk.
So, What's The Deal?
Come On,
You're A Smart Girl.
Think Logically.
How Did Those Doves Appear
In Your Van?
How Did Brandon Disappear
From A Stage
That Has No Trapdoor?
Nobody's Missing
A Mechanical Bull Anywhere,
But Yet One Totally
Appears On Our Stage?
I Mean, Do You Honestly
Think It's Because
I'm Such A Great Magician?
What Are You Saying?
I Was Serious Before,
All Right?
I'm A Freak.
Your Powers?
Look...
About 3 Years Ago,
I Was Walking To School
And I Saw This
Really Cool Skateboard
In The Store Window.
And I Was Thinking
To Myself
How Much
I Wanted That Thing.
2 Seconds Later,
It's Under My Feet
And I'm Riding It.
It Just Appeared?
No, No.
It Didn't Just Appear.
Ok, I Made It Appear.
A Couple Months Later,
This Jerk At School Was
Picking On Me,
Making Fun Of My Hair Or My Pants Or Whatever,
And I Was Wishing That
He Would Just Get Lost.
And Then He Was Gone.
Then They Found Him Like 10
Feet Up In An Old Oak Tree
Hanging By A Belt Loop.
But How Is Any
Of That Possible?
That's The Point.
I Don't Know.
Ever Since
That First Incident,
I Have Been Driving
Myself Crazy
Trying To Figure Out
What's Wrong With Me.
I Can't Control My Magic,
Allyson.
I Don't Know How Or When
Things Are Gonna Happen,
They Just Do.
That Must Be
So Scary For You.
Yeah. Yeah, It Is.
It's--
It's Terrifying.
That's Why
I Don't Have Any Friends.
And That's Why I Can't Get Up
There In Front Of Those Experts.
Either Nothing Will Happen
And I'll Look
Like A Total Fraud,
Or My Powers Will Get
Out Of Control
And They'll Recognize
This Great Gift Of Mine
And I'll End Up On Some Government Operating Table
Being Poked And Probed
Like An Alien Lab Rat.
Look...
I Can't Even Come Close
To Saying I'm Grasping All This,
But I Certainly Do Know
How It Feels To Be The Outcast,
The Weirdo,
The One Nobody Else Can
Ever Relate To.
Not Much Fun, Right?
No, Not So Much.
Well, See, That's Why
This Is So Perfect.
Maybe What You Need More
Than Anything Is
Just One Person Who's Really Gonna Believe In You.
And That Person's You?
If You Want Me To Be.
Isn't That What
Friends Are For?
Yeah, I Guess.
You Know What Else?
I Think You Should Go
Face Max's Experts.
Maybe They Can Help You.
Maybe They Can
Explain All This.
You've Got Nothing
To Lose, Danny.
I Mean, Isn't This Why
You Were So Desperate
To Get Here
In The First Place?
To Find The Truth?
These Guys Might Finally Give
You The Answers You Need.
Allyson, NARRATING:
Everything Was Set.
Max's Panel Of Experts
Included 2 Scientists
Who Specialized In Explaining
Unexplained Phenomenon.
You Know, The Kind Of Guys
Who Say That Crop Circles
Are Really Made By Kids
Stomping Around
With Cardboard Tied
To Their Shoes,
Or That The Loch Ness Monster
Is Nothing But Swamp Gas.
Oh, And Just So It Wouldn't Be
A Stacked Deck Of Techno-Geeks,
Max Also Invited
A Self-Proclaimed Psychic,
Madame Susette.
And Boy, Does
She Look The Part.
At What Age Did You
Begin To Notice...
This Ability?
Around 13 Or So.
It's Common For The Powers
To First Appear
Around The Time Of Puberty.
Tell Me, Danny,
Is It Possible
That These Claims
Of Paranormal Powers Are
Just A Ploy To Get
Some Extra Attention
Around Here?
No, No.
My Colleague Is Merely Making
A Reasonable Assumption.
Anybody Interested In Being
In A Reality Tv Show Is
Obviously Someone
Who Craves A Lot Of Attention.
Danny, Do You Have
A Family History
Of Paranormal
Abilities?
Your Mother?
Your Father?
No.
An Aunt Possibly?
Not That I Know Of.
Maybe A Long-Lost
Second Cousin Twice Removed
On Your Father's Side?
Look, I'm Sure We Could Go On
With This All Day,
But Either This Boy
Can Demonstrate
His Supposed Powers
Or He Cannot.
I, For One,
Am Ready To Find Out.
What Will You
Be Attempting?
Yes, Danny, Tell Us.
What's It Going To Be, Hmm?
A Little Localized
Snow Storm Perhaps?
Maybe A Mechanical Bull
Appearing Out Of Thin Air?
I Honestly Have No Idea.
Don't Force It, Danny.
Just Relax.
Clear Your Mind
Of All Thoughts.
Let The Powers
Come To You.
Are You Up To It, Danny?
Tell Us.
Are You Up To It Or Not?
Look!
What?
Do You See This?!
Whoa!
Remarkable!
Ok, I'm--
I'm Losing It.
Relax. Stay Focused.
Breathe.
What Are You Doing?
Get Your Hands
Off Of Him.
Why?
Are You Afraid
I'm Affecting
His Flight Pattern?
You Weren't Actually Levitating.
Were You, Danny?
I Thought I Was.
Of Course He Was.
Oh, Really?
Well, All Right.
I Suppose It's Possible,
But Instead Of Going
For Far-Fetched Answers,
Why Don't We Look At
A More Logical Explanation
Right In Front Of Us?
Stand Up.
Will You, Danny?
You See, My Friends,
The Secret Is
Not In The Boy,
It's In The Chair.
Please, Explain.
This Is A Very Clever Device
Invented By
A Scandinavian Illusionist
Named Lars Holmstrom.
He Made 2 Of Them.
One He Kept For Himself
And One I Have Here
At The Mansion.
I Keep It Locked Away
In Storage,
Although That Could Explain
Why I Received Reports
Of You Nosing
Around Downstairs.
I've Never Seen
This Chair Before.
Oh, I See.
I Guess It Walked Up Here
All By Itself, Didn't It?
I'd Like To Demonstrate For You,
Ladies And Gentlemen.
There's A Trigger Device
Right Here
Behind The Left Leg.
It's A Hydraulic System.
A Thin Plate Recessed Into The
Chair Seat Is Attached To A Rod
Which Runs Right Up
The Middle Spine
Of The Back Of The Chair.
It Is Able
To Lift 200 Pounds.
It's A Very Ingenious Device,
But A Device Nonetheless.
Danny's A Performer
Like All Performers.
But A Mighty Clever One,
Don't You Think?
Ah.
Well, Well.
Interesting.
Danny, Wait.
You Can't Run
Away From Me.
Whatever You Have To Say,
I Don't Want To Hear It.
Why? Because You Know
You Lied To Me?
I'm Not A Liar.
Nobody Can Relate To Me.
My Powers Make Me A Freak.
I'm So Alone.
Blah, Blah, Blah.
Every Single Bit
Of That Was True.
Oh, Really?
Because It's Feeling To Me
Like Professor French Was Right.
You're Only Using Me
To Make Yourself The Star
Of The Stupid Show.
Oh, Come On, Allyson,
That Is So Not It!
Don't You Get It?
Max Is The One Who Doesn't
Want My Abilities Revealed.
He's The One
Who Rigged The Chair.
Care To Tell Me Why?
I Don't Know!
Maybe There's Some Reason
Why He's Out To Get Me.
You Are--
You Are Truly Unbelievable.
You Never Quit, Do You?
You Actually Had Me Fooled
For A Minute There.
Except Suddenly,
It Couldn't Be Clearer.
You're Exactly Like Everybody Else I've Ever Known.
Setting Me Up To Make Me
Look Like A Fool.
Just So You Can Prove I'm Not
As Smart As I Think I Am!
Oh, Will You Get
Over Yourself!
All Right, Did You
Ever Stop To Think
That Maybe This Has Nothing
To Do With You?
You Know What?
Tell It Someone Who Cares.
Sorry I Was Ever Lame Enough
To Imagine We Were Friends.
So, Where Did That Leave Us?
As Far As The Expert Panel
Was Concerned,
Danny Was Just
An Ordinary Kid Magician
Who Also Happened To Be
A Truly Impressive Trickster.
Well, Much To Hunter's Dismay,
That Meant Danny Was
Not Only Still Eligible
To Compete
In The Grand Finale,
But It Also Meant He Was
Probably A Shoe-In To Win.
And As For Me,
Well, Losing A Friend
Did Not Mean I Was Willing
To Lose My Job.
The Big Difference Was
That From Here On Out,
Danny And I Were Gonna Be
All About The Show
And Nothing Else.
Hey, Shouldn't We Be Out
Getting New Footage
Of Danny Practicing
His New Trick Or Something?
I'd Love To, Cedric,
But I'm Busy.
Oh, Still Ticked, Huh?
Don't I Have
A Right To Be?
I Don't Know If Danny Lied To You
About The Levitation Chair Or What,
But He's Still
A Great Magician.
I Mean, If Nothing Else.
And We Both Know
He Totally Pulled Off
Getting Those Doves
Into Paul's Van.
No, He Didn't.
I'm Sure It's Just
One More Lousy Trick.
I'll Bet You I Can Show You How He Did It.
Sure.
Ok, Somewhere In Here
We're Gonna See His Parents
Or Somebody Show Up To Start
Loading Those Doves Into The Van.
How? Paul Locked It
When We Left.
It Was Still Locked
When We Got Back.
Maybe We Left A Window
Cracked Or Something.
I Don't Know.
Hate To Tell You,
But Here We Come,
And Nobody's Messed
With The Van.
You're Opening The Door.
I Still Haven't Seen
Any Dove Wrangler.
Did You See That?
Back It Up.
Those Doves Came
Out Of Nothing.
Now You See It,
Now You Don't.
It's A Miracle.
Absolutely.
Ha Ha!
Without A Doubt.
Danny's Not A Magician.
He's A Wizard.
Danny?
Come On.
Cedric, You Check Outside.
I'll Check The Vault.
Danny?
Come On, Danny.
Sit Down, Relax.
It's Nothing
To Concern Yourself With.
You're Sure?
You Came Here Looking
For Answers, Didn't You?
Isn't That Why
You Entered The Contest?
Well, Yeah.
I Guess.
I Have Exactly What It Is
You're Looking For.
Sit Down.
Danny, I Know All About You.
I Know About Your Struggles,
I Know About Your Confusion,
And I Know
About Your Powers.
But Aren't You The One
Who Said I Was Faking It
To Get Attention?
I Mean, Aren't You
The President Of
The Worldwide Skeptic Society?
It's A Perfect Cover,
Isn't It?
You See, Every Generation
One Or Two Truly Powerful
Sorcerers Are Born
With Magical Abilities
That Would Boggle
The Imagination
Of Ordinary Men.
I'm One Of
Those True Wizards.
And, Danny,
So Are You.
But How Did You Know?
I Mean, How Did You Find Me?
I Didn't Find You.
You Found Me.
I Created This Show
Hoping It Act As A Lure
To Bring Out
One More Great Sorcerer,
And It Worked.
If I'm So Great And Magical,
Then How Come My Powers
Are Always Totally
Out Of My Control?
Well, You're Young Yet,
You're Untrained,
But All That's
About To Change.
What Do You Mean?
Harnessing Your Power
Is About Focus
And Concentration.
It's About Learning To Believe
That You Are Entitled
To This Great Gift
You've Been Given.
Oh, MY GOSH.
It's Nothing
To Be Afraid Of.
Danny, I Have Felt
Every Single Thing
That You've Been Feeling.
I Was Exactly Like You,
Alone And Afraid.
And Then One Day,
I Met My Mentor,
Antonio De Milo,
And I Began To Feel
What I Know
You're Going
To Begin To Feel.
I Felt Safe.
I Felt Home.
And That's Where
You Are, Danny.
You're Home.
Watch This.
Now, You Try.
You Need To Be
More Centered.
It's All About Concentration.
It's All About Focus.
What You Need To Do Is,
You Need To Believe.
There.
You See
How Simple That Is?
All Right Now,
Let's See What You've Got.
Come On! Hit Him!
Come On, Come On!
Get Him!
Ow! Get Back!
Ohh!
Get Him!
Come On!
Yaah! Come On!
Yeah-Ah!
I'm Gonna Get You, Max!
Ohh!
Max, I'm So Sorry.
That Thing Could've Killed You.
It's Fine, Danny.
It's Perfectly Fine.
We'll Work On It.
We'll Work On It
Together.
That's What Mentors
Are For.
Meanwhile,
I Have A Gift For You.
Here.
Slip This Ring
On Your Finger
And While Your Tutelage
Proceeds,
Your Powers Will Remain
Totally In Check.
There'll Be No More
Unexpected Spells,
No More Vanishing Friends,
No More Having To Worry
About Your Every Thought.
Well, How--I Mean,
How Is That Possible?
Magic.
Here.
Go Ahead.
Feels Good, Doesn't It?
Yeah, You--
You Don't Even Know.
But--But Are You Sure
It's Gonna Work?
Yes, I'm Sure.
Look, I Know This
Is Overwhelming For You.
It's An Awful Lot
To Digest,
An Awful Lot To Grasp,
So I Think You Should
Go Back To Your Room
And Have
A Good Night's Sleep.
I Want You To Have
The Best Sleep
You've Ever Had
In Your Life Tonight.
Thank You, Max.
Good Night.
Paul.
Sounded To Me
Like That Went Pretty Well.
He Clearly Has The Potential To Be More Powerful
Than I'll Ever Be.
That's Why It's Imperative
We Keep A Close Eye On Him.
Not That It's A Problem.
As Long As No One Removes That Ring From His Finger,
He's No Threat,
Because As You Know,
He Can't Remove It
Himself.
And By This Time
Tomorrow,
His Powers Will Be Mine,
Just Like Demilo
Before Him.
Danny, Please Wake Up.
Are You In There?
We Need To Talk.
Please.
Open Up, Please.
Allyson.
It's Late.
Shouldn't You Be In Bed?
Yeah. Yeah, Sure.
After A Completely Horrible
Sleepless Night,
I--I Realized
It Didn't Matter
How Mad I'd Been At Danny.
Max Was Up To Something,
Something Terrible,
And If I Didn't Warn Danny,
Who Would?
We Need To Talk.
Nice Catch!
Will You Listen To Me?
This Is Serious!
Max Is Not
Who You Think He Is.
Yeah, I Know.
It Turns Out That He's The Only One
That Truly
Understands Me.
No, Danny, You're Wrong!
Look,
It Would Be Better
If We Could Talk Alone, Ok?
Why? These Guys
Are My Friends.
I'm Actually Making
Real Friends, Allyson.
For The First Time
In Forever
I'm Feeling Like--
Like A Normal Kid.
Yeah?
Well, I Hate
To Break It To You,
But Maybe That Isn't
Who You Were Born To Be.
Hey! What The--
Wait. You Followed Me?
No!
I--I Was Looking For You,
And I Heard Voices Through
The Grate In The Wall.
I--I Went To Investigate,
Saw You There With Max--
All Right, Great!
Then You Heard.
All Right.
This Ring's On Me To Keep My Powers In Check
Until I'm Able
To Handle 'Em.
But That's Just It!
After You Left The Chamber,
I Was Still There
When Paul Came Back,
And Max Told Him--
He Said Your Magic's
Too Powerful,
That You Need
To Be Watched.
And He Also Said That--
That As Long As That Ring
Stays On Your Finger...
Your Powers Are Totally
In His Control.
Oh, Come On, Allyson!
All Right, That Doesn't
Even Make Any Sense!
But It's True!
You Know What?
I Have Proof.
Come On!
Ok. Allyson, Good.
I'm Glad You're Here.
Hello, Danny.
Uh, Shouldn't You Be Getting
Ready For Tonight's Finale?
Uh, Uh, Sure.
Um, Miss Mcallister?
Danny And Max
Are Both Real Sorcerers,
And Max Is Out To Suppress Danny's Powers.
Allyson.
I'm Not Kidding!
I Have It All Here
On This Tape!
She Has No Idea
What She's Talking About.
Yes, I Do!
It's All Right Here!
Then Perhaps
What We Ought To Do
Is Watch This Tape
Of Yours, Huh?
What Is This About, Max?
I Can Assure You,
I Have No Idea.
Go Ahead.
Show Them.
Show Them What You're
Really All About, Huh?
Now You'll See.
He Clearly Has The...
Well, Now, Um,
What Do We Call This,
Allyson?
Polar Bear
In A Snowstorm?
This--This Can't Be.
It Was--It Was Here.
I Know It Was! I--
I Shot It Myself.
You Guys...
Please, You--
You Have To Believe Me.
Don't--Don't You Get It?
He--He Messed With It.
He Did Something!
Please,
You Have To Believe Me.
They're Sorcerers,
Both Of Them!
Only Danny's Basically Good
And Max Might Be Evil!
Oh, Yes, Yes, And...
The Big Bad Wolf
Is Coming
To Blow Our House Down,
Hmm?
Please, You Have To
Believe Me.
I Know What I Saw
And Heard.
The Problem
Is You're Confusing Fact
With Fantasy, Allyson,
And I Don't Think That's
A Very Good Quality
For A Reality Producer,
Don't You Agree?
You're Probably Just Overwrought And Overworked.
We've Been Asking
An Awful Lot
Of You
Teen Producers.
The Pressure Was Bound
To Get To One Of You.
Danny, Please, Tell Her.
D-Danny, Please.
Tell Them What,
Allyson?
I'm Just A Normal
Kid Magician
Who Happens To Be A Truly Impressive Trickster,
That's All.
Allyson, I'm So Sorry
That You're Upset,
And I'm Sorry
That You're Misinformed,
But I Do Think That The Very Best Thing For Our Show
And For Your Own Personal Health And Well-Being
Is That We--We Send You
Home At Once, Hmm?
Well, It's Just
To Get A Little Rest.
No, You Can't
Do This To Me!
Miss Mcallister,
Please, I--
Allyson, Max Is Right.
It's Painfully Clear
That You Need To Go, Ok?
I'm Sorry.
Wait, She--
Allyson.
Allyson, Listen--
Save It, Ok?
You Had Your Chance To Speak Up,
And You Didn't.
Speak Up About What?
All Right, You Said You Had Proof,
But You Didn't.
You Claim That-- That Max Is Out To Get Me,
But You Don't Know
How Or Why.
I Mean, How Was I Supposed
To Believe You, Huh?
Besides,
You Have No Idea
How Happy
I've Been Lately,
Feeling Like--
Like A Normal Kid For The First Time In--In Years.
I Mean,
It's The Only Thing
I've Ever Wanted.
That's Interesting,
'Cause If You Want
My Opinion,
I Think What You Really
Came Here Searching For
Was To Find Somebody Who
Could Accept You As You Are
And Be Your Friend.
Allyson, Look...
Allyson!
Wow, Look At This,
Your Last
Great Trick.
Managing To Make Your Only Ally Disappear, Huh?
I So Stupidly Thought
Danny And I Were Friends.
But There Was One Little Thing
That Wouldn't Quit Nagging At Me.
If Antonio Demilo Had
Founded The Magic Mansion
And Served As Max's Mentor,
What Had Happened To Him?
There Was Something
In My Gut
Telling Me
This Was One Last Puzzle
Crying Out To Be Solved.
Demilo's Power Seems
To Have Deserted Him.
A Prop That He Had Worked
With A Thousand Times
Fell On Him
During A Live Performance
And Crushed His Skull.
And Then I Saw It,
The Ring That Demilo
Was Wearing,
The Ring That Drains
A Magician's Power,
The Ring That My Friend
Danny Was Now Wearing,
And I Knew What Was
Going To Happen.
His Powers
Would Fail Him, Too,
If I Didn't Get That Ring
Off His Finger.
I Had To Tell Him
Everything I Suspected,
Everything I Found.
I Wasn't Sure Exactly
What He Was Up To,
But If Max Was Now Planning
To Rob Danny Of His Powers
Or Perhaps
Something Even Worse,
He'd Have
The Perfect Opportunity
During The Finale
That Night,
The Finale That Was
Just About To Start.
I Was Out Of Time.
I Had To Get Back Into The Magic
Mansion To Warn My Friend.
Sure. Ok.
But How?
Mr. And Mrs. Sinclair.
Hey.
Welcome.
How Are You?
It's Very Nice
To See You.
This Is A Big Day
For Danny.
He's Excited.
We Have A Table
Right Up Front For You.
Thank You.
Enjoy.
Hey, You,
Put That Trunk Over Here!
Hey, I Need That Camera
Out Here Now, Ok?
Just Now. You!
You! I Need You Covering
Arrivals In The Lobby.
Uh-Huh, Uh-Huh. Yes.
Don't Worry. I'm On It.
I Got A Delivery
For Danny Sinclair!
Let's Move, People!
We're Live In 10 Minutes!
A Little More Hustle
Would Be Appreciated!
Let's Go!
Hi! Looking Good, Huh?
My Headset, Please.
Oh. I Just, Uh,
Figured With Allyson
Booted Off The Show
You, Uh, Probably Needed
Somebody To Pick Up The Slack.
All I Need From You
Is To Find Max
And Make Sure Brandon
Is Ready To Go On.
I Hear He's Freakin' Out
Over Some Sequin Crisis
Or Something.
No Problem!
Ok.
I'm Going On, In Like,
5 Minutes, And Nothing's Ready!
Wardrobe Malfunction,
All The Way!
I Don't Get It, Max.
How Am I Gonna Do My Final Trick
If This Ring Keeps
My Powers In Check?
Don't Worry About It.
We're In This
Together Now, Danny.
I'll Be Right There
With You.
Just Go Out
On That Stage,
And I'll Make Sure
The Magic Happens.
Isn't That Kind
Of Like Cheating?
I Mean, Maybe--
Maybe I Should
Just Take It Off
Until The Contest
Is Over.
No.
Do You Remember How You Felt
Before You Put That Ring On?
Do You Wanna Feel
That Way Again?
Danny, I Want You
To Trust Me.
All You Have To Do
Is Go Out On That Stage
Tonight,
Relax, And Have Fun.
Miss Mcallister Needs You
On Stage, Max.
Yes. I'll Be There
Shortly. Look...
We Can Do Great Things
Together, Danny.
Don't Let Me Down.
I'm Counting On You.
This Jacket's Not Even Buttoned Up Right,
To The Light!
Nothing's Ready,
And I'm Going On In, Like, 5 Minutes!
Nothing's Ready!
Wardrobe Malfunction!
Tonight Our Search
Will Come To An End.
3 Incredible Contestants,
One Final Challenge.
Who Will Be The World's
Greatest Kid Magician?
Currently In First Place,
Please Help Me Welcome
The Brilliant Brandon Ross!
Keep Your Eye On Him.
Ok.
Hey.
What Are You Doing
Back Here?
I Thought Max Banned
From You This Place.
He--He Did.
But I--I Just Couldn't
Stay Away, You Know?
Me And Magic,
We're Like This.
Yeah?
Well, Too Bad,
'Cause I Think Security's Gonna Wanna Talk To You.
Oh, Come On, Hunter.
Don't Be A Jerk. I Mean,
If You're Gonna Rat Me Out,
At Least Let Me Show You A
New Little Trick I Learned First.
Well, What Kind
Of Trick?
Oh, It's Simple, Really.
All I Do Is Make
My Problem Disappear!
Allyson, Get Back Here!
Allyson!
And Now Please Help Me In
Welcoming Our Second Contestant,
Philadelphia's Own,
Zoe Cunningham!
Camera One, Get Ready.
This Should Be Fun.
She's Really Cute.
Hey, Man,
Have Some Fun Out There,
All Right?
Thank You. Thanks.
Psst!
Danny!
Allyson, What Are
You Doing Here?
I've Got Something
I Need To Show You.
It's About Max's Mentor
Antonio Demilo.
So?
So?!
He Died In An Onstage Accident
During A Live Performance
And Happened To Be Wearing The
Exact Same Ring Max Gave To You,
And You're Seriously Telling Me
That Doesn't Mean Anything?!
Yeah.
Danny,
You Didn't Hear Max Down In His Chamber With Paul.
I Did, And You're
In Real Danger Here!
Allyson,
That's Ridiculous.
Max Is Controlling
Your Powers With That Ring,
And I Heard Him Say You Can't
Take It Off By Yourself.
If You Still Don't Believe Me,
Then Just Take It Off
And See How Different
You Feel!
I Don't Want
To Take It Off.
All Right? I Know
How Different I'll Feel.
I'll Feel Scared
And Isolated
And Petrified
Of My Own Thoughts.
All Right?
I've Been There!
And I'm Not Interested
In Going Back.
But You Can Learn
To Master All That.
Danny!
You're On
In One Minute.
I'll Be Right There,
Miss Mcallister.
Please,
Listen To Me.
I Really Don't Wanna
See You Get Hurt.
Look, I Might Not Have
Concrete Proof About Max,
But I Know I'm Right!
He Doesn't Honestly
Care About You,
And I Do!
Please, Danny,
I'm Begging You
To Take A Leap Of Faith.
I Gotta Go, All Right?
Wait! At Least You Could
Let Me Take Your Ring Off.
You Might Be Able
To Fight Back If You Need To.
I'm Sorry, Allyson.
All Right?
I Won't Do It.
And Now, Drumroll, Please.
Help Me Give A Warm Welcome
To Our Final Contestant,
The One And Only
Danny Sinclair!
Go, Danny!
Yeah!
Come On, Danny!
Well, Danny,
Here It Is.
One Last Feat
Of Legerdemain.
How Are You Feeling?
To Be Perfectly Honest,
Way Too Ready
To Get This Over With.
Oh, Now, Wait A Minute,
My Friend,
You Mean To Tell Me
That A Young,
Skinny Fellow Like You
Is Claiming That He's Able
To Lift That Weight
All On His Own?
That's 1,000 Pounds
Of Pure Lead.
You Mean To Say
That You Dare
To Try To Lift That
And Raise It
Over Your Head?
That's The Plan,
Yeah.
What Do You Think, Folks?
Is It Possible?
Are You Ready, Danny?
Absolutely.
Well, Let's Get On
With The Show.
That's What We Came For,
Ladies And Gentlemen.
Whoa. Wait, Wait.
Hold On, Hold On.
Give It Up!
Go Home!
Come On, Danny!
Yeah!
Whoo!
See That?
Danny, Look Out!
Oh, My God! Oh!
I Can't Get
The Ring Off!
It's Stuck!
Please Come Over Here!
I'll Take It Off For You!
Please!
Come On!
Well, Well, Well...
It Looks Like
We're Going To Need
A Much Stronger Stage, Eh?
I Can't Imagine What It Is
Danny Intends To Do Next,
But I Hope He's Not Planning
On Using That Weight Again.
What Do You Say, Folks?
Why Don't We Give This Young
Man Another Chance, Eh?
Is There A Problem, Danny?
I Said I Know About Demilo And The Ring, Max.
You Tricked Me!
Yes. It's A Pretty Clever
Trick, Don't You Think?
Yeah, Well,
It's Not Gonna Work.
Well, We'll See.
Yeah, We'll See.
Ladies And Gentlemen,
This Young Man
Is Ready To Work Again.
Why Don't We Give Him
A Nice Round Of Applause
So He Can Finish
His Act, Eh?
It's Your Move, Danny.
Uh, Special Delivery
For Danny Sinclair?
Well,
What Could This Be?
A New Wrinkle
Has Been Added, Eh?
What Is It?
Well, Uh,
Every Great Magician
Deserves A, Uh,
Beautiful Assistant,
Don't You--
Don't You Think, Max?
Oh, I Don't Know.
It Seems To Me
That Whenever A New Element
Has Been Added Belatedly,
It Can Be Quite
A Sticking Point.
And...
It Has Been My Experience
That Not Every Assistant
Is Quite As, Um,
Sharp As She Might Be.
Allyson!
Well, Uh,
They Do Say
That--That--
That Good Help Is Hard
To Find These Days.
Well, As Amusing As All Of This Has Been,
Ladies And Gentlemen,
Particularly For Me,
Why Don't We Give
Danny A Chance
To Focus On His Trick?
Right, Right.
Ladies
And Gentlemen...
Allyson!
Aha!
Better Late Than Never.
That's, Uh, My Motto.
Allyson, What Are
You Doing Here?
I Told You. You Can't
Remove The Ring Yourself.
Someone Else Has To.
You Don't Give
Up, Do You?
Not When It's Something
I Care About.
Well, Be My Guest.
Oh.
What Do You Think
You're Doing?
Oh, Well,
My Final Trick, Max.
Isn't That What You've
Been Urging Me To Do?
Ladies And Gentlemen,
Max Has So Graciously
Agreed To Join Me
As I Perform
My Final Act.
You're No Match
For Me, Danny,
With Or Without
The Ring.
Your Powers
Will Soon Be Mine.
Never.
As You Wish.
Your Move, Max.
Ladies
And Gentlemen,
Let's Get On
With This Show.
Whoa!
Ohh!
Danny, The Ring!
It's The Last Piece
Of The Puzzle!
You've Gotta Use It
Against Max!
Now It's My Move,
Max!
Aah!
What Is This? What?
That Was Cool!
Yeah, Danny!
So, That Was It,
The Most Incredible
Experience
Anyone Could've
Ever Imagined,
And I Was There
To Witness It All.
Of Course,
Max Must've Gotten Paul
To Take The Ring
Off For Him,
Because By The Time We Returned
To The Production Office,
Every Single
Show Tape Had...
Mysteriously Disappeared.
But Then...
Someone Managed To Make Them
Mysteriously Reappear
Right Here In My Room.
I Cut Together
Everything You Just Saw
Because I Felt Like It
Was Really Important
For Everyone
To Know The Truth.
And Danny?
Well, Once He Realized That Max
Was Still Out There Somewhere,
He Went Into Hiding,
Hoping To Hone His Skills
And Get Real Control
Of His Powers
Before They Meet Again.
I Hear He's Definitely
Getting Stronger
Every Single Day.
Unfortunately,
Even I'm Not Allowed
To Know Where He's Hiding.
Ok, So Maybe I Do
Know Where He Is.
Aah!
How'd I Get Here?!
Magic.
You Know, I Still Don't
Know How You Do That!
Oh, A Good Magician
Never Reveals The Secrets...
Of His Tricks.
Show-Off!
♪ Do You Believe In Magic ♪
♪ In A Young Girl's Heart? ♪
♪ How The Music
Can Free Her ♪
♪ Whenever It Starts? ♪
♪ And It's Magic ♪
♪ If The Music Is Groovy ♪
♪ It Makes You Feel Happy ♪
♪ Like An Old-Time Movie ♪
♪ I'll Tell You
About The Magic ♪
♪ It'll Free Your Soul ♪
♪ But It's Like Trying
To Tell A Stranger ♪
♪ About Rock 'N' Roll ♪
♪ If You Believe In Magic ♪
♪ Don't Bother To Choose ♪
♪ If It's Jug Band Music ♪
♪ Or Rhythm And Blues ♪
♪ Just Go And Listen ♪
♪ It'll Start With A Smile ♪
♪ It Won't Wipe Off
Your Face ♪
♪ No Matter
How Hard You Try ♪
♪ We'll Go Dancing, Baby ♪
♪ Then You'll See ♪
♪ How The Magic's
In The Music ♪
♪ And The Music's
In Me, Hey ♪