- Isn't that 10 minutes gone Tom?
- You'll lose your Job!
Come on! Let's go!
Come on!
Running roll?
We are in side
one of the largest power plants, -
- Which supplies electricity to nearly
22 million consumers.
It now seems that its going to be
one of the biggest disasters in decades.
For WTSE, this is Tom Merrick
reporting live -
- from inside burning
Evanston Power Plant
- We need few more shots before we go.
- 10 minutes gone Tom!
- We must beat the Big Lead!
- We need to get out! Look at this place!
Go upstairs now,
or you'll lose your jobs!
Come on. Go!
Look! Devil babies and
resurrected dictators are out.
I'll tell you when I need. An alien
abduction or catastrophic disaster...
What's it's been? An year without
a decent earth quake or flood?
That's terrible....
I wasn't sure if you're gonna make it.
I'll take care of this later.
Oh! You are warm.
So you are alive.
- You looking well, Eleanor.
- You look like crap.
I was going poor-chic-style.
Always trying to stand
out from the crowd.
- Thank you for the job.
- No need to thank me...
I got an award-winning
news man witht
chiken-feet. Never could
understand why you quit.
- I was misunderstood.
- Yeah! Why you're a hero in my book.
The tape you pulled under
the power plant tops.
The fact that network used
it to grab ratings, and
still pursuaded you to
resign over it...hippocrates
So where do you want me to start?
Basement, research.
I need a piece on disasters.
I take it that Mother Nature
will not cooperate, the next
best thing is to take my readers
a blast through the past:
"Disasters through history."
- Starting out slow ?
- You complaining already?
- I see no reason to wait.
- Good luck.
This is a recording!
Elizabeth Winterns is not in today.
I know you're there:
Okay, I'm here, but not for long.
I will try to get out early today.
I say have a look... personally I
need some balance into my life.
I need those coms for next week:
I'll do a complete search for it,
but it'll have to wait until tomorrow.
What? No! No! Wait! Don't hang up!
Excuse me... I'm Tom Merrick.
And I'm overjoyed.
- So... what are you doing here?
- Grayson sent me.
No! I mean why National Inquisitor summing
here some kind of pants?
- You work here?
Yeah, but I'm not Tom Merrick.
I had a bad day
went into a few bad years.
Could you lend me
some research computer?
You know. I'll be back
tomorrow and then I'm all yours.
No! It can't wait.
First damn job is to impress the boss.
Okay! All those news articles are online.
The code word is Lizland.
- Use search engine and hard copies.
- What if I have questions?
For emergencies only...
Try to leave my desk
as you found it.
DISASTERS, 20th CENTURY
"What causes one disaster to
become part of our collective
consciousness, while
another fade into history?
Maybe some author our attention -
- because they remind us of the power
of Mother Nature over Man's technology.
Others because they shows us how-
- inheritantly flawed our most advanced
technology can be.
There're still others
because they reveal... "
Crap.
This is crap.
What the hell...
Hello?
- It's Tom Merrick.
- I hope this's an emergency.
Could someone have
altered your data?
No way! I have double firewalled
and keep built case guessing!
What is it about, though?
Mau! Where do you get
these pictures from?
All images are from our,
Smithsonian Institute
and the Library of
Congress archives
- There has to be a mistake.
- If there is it is not on my computer.
Can not it wait until tomorrow?
I must...
Whatever it is Merrick, it
can wait until tomorrow.
Larry King and Heating Pad
waiting for me at home.
Just take a look.
Titanic, the Hindenburg fire,
Hurricane Hugo.
I hope for your sake you have
more than a history lesson here.
Take a closer look.
Do you still want to catch Larry King?
- What is this?
- A guy shows at three disasters, a perhaps
across nearly a hundred
years without aging a day.
Now, is it someone trying
a hoax on us, or is this
the most incredible DNA
fluke in human history.
- Or is he not human.
- Come on Eleaner. It's just us two here.
And we are showing our theories.
I don't know what
you found Merrik, but this
is absolutely amazing.
Exactly what the Inquisitor needs.
We get to scoop the globe.
- I want 1000 words from you.
- I have no idea what this
is all about. We don't know
even the images are authentic.
That's why you are flying to D.C.
tonight.
Nine o'clock flight. The newspaper
credit card for the ticket.
No way. You have to send someone else.
We get originals from Smithsonian and
get friends to authenticate them.
I was looking for a nine to five job.
Remember? No competitions. No stress.
And make sure we will be running the story
day after tomorrow.
- If there's a story.
- If? Why the hell did you
come up here if you don't
think there's a story?
Come on Merrik! Admit.
You blood supply is full of adrenaline.
You've never felt this
good in a long time.
There has to be a
reasonable explanation.
Find! The way to fine it is to be on that
flight. You have 36 hours to get the story.
Order a ticket to mr. Merrick
to D.C. nine o'clock tonight. Coach.
- Hello?
- Kevin?
- Hey, buddy. It's me. Your Dad.
- I know.
Listen Kev, I was
wondering...I got a new job.
I would really like if
you came to Chicago.
We could hang-out,
watch The Cubs lose...
- So. What do you think buddy?
- I do not know.
I gotta go. Steve's coming over.
We're going to play some Quake.
- I'll put mama.
- Kevin, wait, Kevin.
It's Dad.
Please call him more than
once every two months.
Tom! Bad things happen
to people all the time,
but they do not just
draw back and give up.
This time get yourself a life.
As life you and Steve given
Kevin in Atlantic City?
I don't think you're in any position
to give an opinion about that.
Motel theme parks?
Okay it's Casinos.
- What is it going to do to our son?
- Stop it, Tom.
You can not only tolerate the fact
that Steve being in Kevin's life.
You know, Steve does things with Kevin.
He got us tickets to the final of the
hockey championship at Cops Collosium.
Buying half ticket for a kid
doesn't make him father of the year.
No, it does not, Tom.
But when Steve do anything with Kevin,
he makes more of a father than you.
Are you a photographer?
Passengers! Please
fasten your seat belts.
No, reporter.
So, like a news paper?
Yeah, like.... news paper.
- Are you doing a story about that guy?
- Maybe.
Because if you are...
... he is right there.
- Tighten your seat belt.
- What? What is wrong?
We are now flying through
a major turbulence.
If you fasten the seat belt
you're going to be comfortable.
It'll be quickly over and done with!
Thanks!
- Sir, please take your seat.
- Just a second.
YOU ARE HERE.... TITANIC!
EVANSTON POWER PLANT
12 DEAD
HINDENBURG explosion
33 DEAD !!
DEPARTURE 222 - 15 JUNE
Please Sir! Take your seat now.
Isn't today 15th?
What flight number is this?
Flight 222.
COLLISION IN MID AIR
307 DEAD
16th June...
That's tomorrow.
CHICAGO
GREEN LINE
DAYTIME
SUBWAY
CRASH
Give me that.
No one needs to get hurt.
Drop the gun.
What the hell is gonna happen
with this plane?
Land it!
Calm down, then we're gonna discuss it.
Bring it down now!
Or else all will be dead.
Let's go.
We got problems.
No radar or communications.
We got a bigger problem.
He's not gonna hurt anybody. He just wants
us to land, that's right, isn't it?
The two nearest airports are
Grand Rapid and O'Hare. Your call.
- Which one is the closest?
- O'Hare may be five minutes.
Do it.
Going down to 10,000 feet,
heading 2-9-0 by 6-2-0.
- Wait!
- We will take it down, like you wanted.
You got no radar, no radio.
- What would you do,if I weren't here?
- I don't understand.
If you didn't have a gun pointed at
your head, would you continue to D.C?
No.
No, it is considered an emergency.
Code one emergency.
We'd land at the nearest strip.
- Which is....which is you're doing anyway!
- Yeah!
- Bring her up.
- I thought you wanted us to land?
Bring her up now!
There!
Pull her up. Pull her up hard!
- We've lost hydraulics.
- Switch to manual. Both sides.
We're on manual. 7000 feet.
6700 feet.
- Damn it!
- 6400 feet. 27 seconds to impact.
- Come on! Come on!
- 6000 feet.
22 seconds to impact.
5700 feet.
Get her up, get her up.
- 5500 feet.
- I got her! I got her!
We're levelling at 5500 feet.
Are you alright?
Hadn't we taken her up,
we'd all be dead.
How did you know?
I won't be needing this any more.
They are waiting for you.
There was no way that guy
wasn't on the plane.
I saw him, the little girl next to me
saw him, the flight-attendant saw him.
Let's not worry about
this alleged gentleman for a while...
... and concentrate on you.
You see Mr. Merrik, you had the gun.
You commandeered flight 222.
Now in my experience, hijackers
rarely work alone.
I am NOT a hijacker.
The plane was going down, and...
Why don't you tell us
who else was involved?
No one!
The last thing I wanted to do  was even
get on in that plane. Believe me!
Believe you?
Mister I believe in looking directly into
a man's eyes and seeing the truth.
Right now as I look into yours
truth is nowhere inside.
Sorry.
Ask the pilot. He'll tell you!
As we speak, the agents are interviewing
the all flight personnel and passengers, -
- And I have a forensic
crew sweeping the plane.
Good! Then you'll find this brochure.
The itinerary you supposedly saw inspired
you to pull out your gun?
For the millionth time, it wasn't MY gun.
It was his.
The guy with the brochure,
the guy we couldn't fine
the guy that does't show up
on the flight manifest...
... He was not even on
the damn plane when it landed?
While you're sawing holes in my story -
- There's a guy out there
with a list of disasters.
The subway is next....
I think.
Something's going to happen to it.
So now you have designs on a subway?
I need to use a phone.
I get a call, right?
Stanton, why don't you bring Mr.
Merrik, a phone?
Check with weapons department.
Check Merrick through national BCI.
Stanton, what exactly is that thing?
The digital recorder built
into my watch. I made it.
You're sure that you
want field work son?
Perhaps you should've stayed in MIT.
Nothing wrong with being an engineer.
I've always wanted to be in the Beurau.
I mean....I can switch to a corner...
I can be an agent and
still have time to fiddle
around with things like this.
- Mind if I get you a watch...
- Forget the watch.
Concentrate on this here. Remember?
Please, just find Grayson for me?
It's an emergency.
Wait, wait...
Transfer me to Research.
Sir! What Merrick did....
It doesn't make any sense.
OK. Follow that line of thought...
Well.. the guy hijacks a
plane, doesn't ask for
any money, doesn't make
any demands whatsoever...
So? What does that tell you? Think.
Get a shrink down here.
To see if Mr. Merrick is always honest.
That's marvellous.
That's marvellous
- Research..
-  It's Tom Merrick! I need a favour!
You left my office in a
complete mess, you hung up
on me the last time we
spoke, and now you want a...
I found something in your system.
Yeah! That's the point of using it...right?
I do not understand it all yet,
but it may be something big.
Oh!Please Merrik! This
isn't going to be one
of the stories of the
century's history?
Do you have any idea how many reportes
have dropped that stuff, in my life?
Any of them come in the aeroplane, forces
it to land and get arrested by FBI?
Yeah, right! I'm getting out of here.
Wait, wait, wait!
There is a file in your system.
Merrick doc.doc
I dropped three photos in to it.
I need you to make hard
copies of each of them
and and bring them down
to me at the FBI office.
I do not have time to be a delivery woman.
Look, Merrik! I would like to help, but...
- Listen to me! You are a researcher! So
I hope that you're genetically curious!
Pull the file. Have a look at it yourself.
You won't be disappointed.
Merrick doc.doc
I'm counting on you.
Story of the century, my ass.
"Titanic", "Hindenburg"...
Wow...!
- What does he want anyway?
- At the end of the day....
What happened to Baker?
What's going on here?
Where are we going?
Who the hell are you guys?
Not now.
Emergency Medical Team to 348 on the
double quick. Put security on alert.
Seal off the building.
Merrick has escaped.
Freeze! Drop the gun!
Drop it!
Drop it! Now!
Against the wall.
No !!
Our orders was to stop him.
If we kill Merrick,
it violates the phenomenon on negative law!
Get out of the way! Move!
Get out of the way!
- Let's go!
- What's that?
Freeze!
- Are you going to kill yourself?
- Come on. Let's go!
- Come on! Let's go!
- He was going to shoot us!
Come! Further!
Surveillance displays Merrik's had
at least two assistants:
A woman of 160cm tall, black hair.
Black jacket. And a man...
Stay where you are!
Get down!
What the hell was that?
It would be a Glock 17L with ballistic
modificatins for an M 136. Right ?
Certainly, unheard....
That's enough! We got two
males and two females with us-
-Running eastwards along
the Fedaral building.
They are armed and dangerous.
Move in! Move in!
Why are we runing?
Why am I runing?
What's going on?
What are you doing?
It's the siren. They're cops.
They are coming!
If they are cops, they
will straight shoot us!
What??
Here!
Attention Please!
The train leaves from track on level 1...
What have you got me into?
What...? Ah!...
The captain confirms
Merricks statement!
We shall contact Grifasi.
Where the hell are they?
You guys spread out. Cover the exits. I
don't want any of them to get out of here.
Alright! Listen! If passengers
saw Merrick's guy on the
plane, we should be able to get
a sketch of him on the wire.
Let's also get the sketches of the two
freed Merrick.
What's going on?
- All I know for
sure is that the guy
on the photos was on my flight.
- What?
He was there. And he had
a brochure... of disasters.
And it doesn't make any sense.
No! The flight we were in was in the
brochure. My plane was gonna crash.
That's why you were arrested. You hijacked
plane all before crashing.
Great! So that it makes me
an accomplice to a hijacker.
So! Who was the guy in the
plane with the brochure?
Merrick and him working
on the insides, the two
goons and woman running
with Merrik on the out.
But now at least we got
positive ID on her.
The call we allowed Merrick to passed
through to... an Elizabeth Wintern.
She's a match with the
woman he just works with.
So Merrik! Whatever all this is about...
What are we supposed to do about it?
The brochure he had was
about past disasters.
There's one that hasn't happened yet.
A Subway wreck.
Right here! On the green line
at noon today.
- Wait a little....I
told the FBI, but they
wouldn't believe me.
- Well... I can imagine why..
Just one thing
that's little odd.
The captain on the flight
confirms what Merricks says.
That Merrick prevented a mid-air collision?
So that he's not a hijacker.
Merrick pulled the gun.
He and the other guy
probably tried to hijack it...
but got cold feet.
And the story now...The
three big questions: How
did Merrick know to prevent
mid-air collision?
How did the guy with him get out of the
plane, and passed the security....and why?
Why is Merrik run away
from the people who freed him?
I do not know, sir.
I don't know either..we'll
damn well find out.
Wait until we process the signal!
What's wrong with it?
I don't know. He is in a
shielded containment-bunker.
Now we shouldn't have
affected communication.
Grifasi...if you can read me... have them
charge up this place. We need a reset.
We can't reset you! We have serious
problems here that takes time to address!
- What is he saying?
- This chaotic stuff is a major deviation!
If that's not bad enough, I got
the time the police after me.
Having trouble in getting him.
Find the bastard and eleminate him!
If he keeps on saving more lives -
It will be a question why do you come back!
Kiss my ass!
Stop, Cortez. We can not
afford any unspecified casualties.
There won't be any unspecified ones.
We have to stop it before something
happens. We have twenty minutes. Let's go!
Hold it for a sec! You even don't
know if something's gonna happen.
Or even if it did, how'd you know
which train is going to crash?
No, I don't know.
But if we don't get every train on that
line stopped, one's gonna be history.
It's clear.
Away! Move away!
Find a security guard,
anyone and say that there
is a bomb and they need
to stop all trains.
What're you gonna do?
I'm going to find a way
to kill the power and...
And then what? What is it?
It's him! It is this train.
We got to get out of here. Come!
- How many stations are on this line?
- There're six. The last is Hill Horn. Why?
This is Baker. I need security units
set up in Subway stops...
- between Union and Hill Horn immediately-
Let's get some cars.
Merrick, this train is not stopping.
There he is...
- I do not know how you got
photos you found, but it's
Thrill Seeker's fault. Not mine.
- Thrill Seekers?
What's gonna happen to this train?
I won't tell...that's
part of the agreement.
This is Murray Trevor requesting
an emergency reset now!
What are you doing? I need that to get off
the train and I need it to get home!
- How is this train gonna crash?
- Ok! The engine driver had a heart attack.
When he died he was holding
the deadman's switch.
So the train kept
on accelerating.
After Clayton it couldn't hold
on to the tracks on the curve.
He speaks as if it
HAS already happened.
It did! About 70 years ago.
I'm a tourist.
The flight you were in was supposed to be
the worst mid-air collisionin US history.
Because of you nothing! Zero perished!
I need to get a refund.
Insane. Let's stop the train.
No! You can't do that.
Just...Just give me that.
- Do you travel to disasters?
- Disasters, sporting events...
- It's only a few minutes left.
- Let's go!
Wait...wait...It's against rules to
intervene. Please give me back my RTT!
Please!
You do not understand!
I need it!
Please
Open up! Open up!
It's an emergency!
Open up!
It is Whittier. Three stops to Clayton.
We have maybe two more minutes.
Open up!
- He can't hear you. He is dead!
- The emergency brake.
Damn.
Maybe we can separate
this coach from the others.
No! We don't know
how to do that.
Everyone! This train's gonna crash!
Move into the rear coach now! Go!
Go! Go!
Please! Give me back my RTT!
Move! Move!
Down the rearmost coach!
Train's gonna crash!
It is the last chance, come on!
I can't wait for you.
- What should we do?
- I do not know. Look around!
This is it.
One on each side. Both at same time.
Come on, jump!
Come on! Jump!
What now?
Come on! Move back!
Train's gonna crash!
Move back, everybody. Keep moving.
Get on the floor now. Get down!
Hey! Thanks.
- Is this your place?
- My folks'. Dad's out.
Dad always said
you can never have too many types of tools.
Do you surely know what you're doing?
Yeah! I once saw him use it when I was
around three. It looked so easy... kidding.
Hold the stretcher.
- Sure, we have a match.
- Get him out of here.
- Oh! Surprise me.
- We talked to the passengers.
Merrick and Wintern were on this train,
but they are not.
- Any luck at Union?
- The other two also escaped as well.
Oh! Great! It's great!
Okay, listen up folks!
I wanna run search on Merrick, Wintern and
the two unidentified purverts.
Check all hospitals, motels, hotels
within 50 miles radius. You know the drill.
I wanna check anyone
driving, walking or
riding a horse. You know
what they look like.
Right now! Results!
Do it! Go!
I'm not getting a contact.
You shouldn't have stopped me
from shooting him the first time...
- They were not our orders.
- That train would have gone down.
We were supposed to interrogate Merrick,
determine the point of deviation and reset.
We didn't interrogate him,
and thanks to you he's still walking.
Don't let this on me.
The man has figured out.
He knows.
... this kept the death
toll now standing at two.
....of course it could have
easily been in the hundreds.
It is the first subway crash in the
city has eperienced in 20 years.
Transportation authorities now speculating
whether it is operator error or...
- Right from the dryer.
- Thanks.
I have trying to put the pieces together...
In the plane...
That brochure I saw...
In this Evanston Power Plant fire....
It stated that 12 people died.
There was only 11 dead.
Who is the 12th?
- Me.
- What?
The tourist guy travels to disasters.
And Power Plant fire was one of his stops.
That's right.
His coin was there.
The one he had on the train.
He must have dropped it,
and when I saw it...
I hesitated. I mean...long
enough to change things forever.
Because if I hadn't
stopped when I saw it...
... I would have been
killed along with my crew.
- You can't know that for sure.
- It makes sense.
I am alive because that tourist
from the future... dropped the coin.
The two Freaks.... they
are from the future too.
They are to stop me
before I alter the past.
This is nuts. Okay?
The guy from the train was nuts.
But if some future
scientist were to develop
technology for people to
travel through time -
- Do you really think this is what they use
it for? To tourism? For entertainment?
If what you're saying is
true, they're not coming
back to see some TV image
gets blown to bits.
They are coming to see thousands of
real live people die....
It's sick.
I don't see how it is any worse
than tuning into 6'O clock news...
Or reporting.
Hey! There's no comparrison
between you and them.
Isn't there?
I've watched some of your news segments...
Occasionally...
Sometimes I got carried away.
Remember the time you drew
right up to that tornado?
That was quite a piece, wasn't it?
Thank you for purchasing
Thrill Seekers' ten pack!
Your best value at temporal
travel entertainment!
Your 10 pack covers some of most
famous disasters in the history...
- What did you do?
- I do not know.
Starting from April 14, 1912,
sinking of the "Titanic" -
and the December 24, 1998 the catastrophic
fire at the Evanston Power Plant.
And of course the big three.
That's right. Those legendary
3 days in June when
you get back to back, to
back a plane crash, -
- A train wreck
and the grand daddy of all disasters...
The Copps Coliseum fire....
that killed more than 11,000 people...
It's tomorrow!
When you're ready to begin your first trip
just use remote temporal transmitter-
- with the built in isometric
frequency blocker -
- that guarantees you from
the time police detection.
Within seconds we rescue you to
the start of another adventure...
- He's there. At Copps Coliseum.
- Who?
My son.
- Hello?
- Kevin, I need to talk to your mother!
She's not here.
Christie's here.
Okay! I need you to
listen very carefully.
I can't explain how I know this!
But tomorrow during the hockey
game, there's gonna be a fire .
You, your mother and
Steve cannot be there.
I don't understand!
I'll explain later.
Just promise me you won't go to the game.
No! I wanna go!
Kevin, this is one
time you gotta trust me.
Promise me you won't go!
Talk to me, Kevin.
Mom said you might get jealous,
because I'm doing stuff with Steve.
No, it is not
that, believe me...
I guess that he didn't believe you?
I have to get there. I'm
gotta stop them from going.
Okay! Maybe there's
something else we can try.
You suggested a bomb threat somewhere!
We can try that at Copps Coliseum.
No! There are situations
like that all the time.
When the security sweeps
and when they don't
find anything, the game
goes on as planned.
We can give the deivce you took from time
traveller. That will get their attention.
Maybe! But by the time you
explain what the hell
it is, the Coliseum
will all be in history.
No! This is an emergency! The FBI would
be able to move in pretty quickly.
No matter what FBI comes up with
those two people will destroy the arena.
They need those 11,000 people dead.
Maybe we can slow them down.
Wintern got parents in The Heights,
couple of friends in Eastburn...
... And one ex-boyfriend on the Gold Coast.
Put him through.
It is Patterson from the office.
It's Merrick.
Line 2.
I didn't cause the subway wreck.
I tried to stop it from crashing.
Then why not turn yourself in?
The man and woman who
grab me from your
office they tried to
stop me from saving it.
Now they wanna take down Copps Coliseum
tomorrow during the hockey championship.
You got to stop them.
I'll tell you what! Why
don't you come down here
and work with me to identify
who these two are...
Thank you. We got it.
It's her parents' place.
The sketches I ordered
of those two that helped
Merrick to escape, I want
them to be delivered -
- along with the photos of Merrick and
Wintern to the Copps Coliseum security.
Tell them to get extra police
and fire managers, just a precaution.
Do you believe it that those two
are looking for Copps?
I do not believe a damn thing he says.
But I do believe in covering all the bases.
Should I call off
the search Sir?
I don't know. Maybe he's
just trying to put us off.
Oh! You gotta be kidding?
I should be there in three hours if I fly.
You are suspected hijacker. If you go near
an airport, cops will be all over you.
Don't worry. It is old,
But it can get us there.
If we take turns at driving
even if we stay away major highways -
- We'll get to Copps Coliseum in 15 hours.
Well before the game.
I already emailed my mom.
I told her that we're
taking the car. So...well...
Let's get out of here!
- Finally getting him.
- How could you let this happen?
What the hell is going on?
- Grafasi looks different.
- Looks like there's some leakage...
Do you have any idea what you've done?
By not stopping
Merrick, nearly 500 people
lived, who were supposed to die.
So? Time-shift police again zeored
on your organisation again?
Just give up the
hatch money and...
Do you think that we're dealing
with some law enforcement issue
What else is there?
Just a few little problems like population
shifts in the hundreds of millions, -
plus new governments and
technology popping up
and disappearing, you've
never even heard of.
- What happening in L.A.?
- Who cares about L.A.?
My kid lives in L.A.
Southern California was wiped out
in a fusion melt down 22 years ago.
What?
I have to get back to my time.
You have to get us a reset now!
You still don't get it! Do you?
Your timeline does not exist any more.
Do you understand?
Your family, your friends are all gone.
And temporal accelerator...
that's right...
The core technology of
Stanza-displacement...
Somebody Merrick saved one on that plane
killed its inventor -
In an automobile accident
three years before he invented it.
So right now we can't
reset anybody anywhere.
But Sir you're in a containment bunker.
So the accelerator
should be shileded against
any timeline deviations.
We never had deviations
of this magnitude before.
It's blown all over
like fish out of water.
Have we got a team working on it?
A team? Get the whole
dame conglomorate on
this. I have to get a
reset and save my son.
Listen Cortez! I have bigger problems
here than worrying about your progedy!
If we are lucky, I
repeat if we are lucky,
we might have a working
model within a week.
Then you can reset us?
We can stop Merrik before
he gets on that plane.
That's the plan. But nothing's gonna happen
unless we get a stable temporal zone.
That means that you two
have to make it damn sure
that Merrick doesn't cause
any more deviations-
- from the current timeline,
or it's over for all of us.
How do we find Merrik now?
He's got client's RTT. He doesn't know
that it gives us the track of him.
- I transmit his coordinates.Standby.
- Standby for downstream...download?
- We have them.
- Good.
Now... whether you get Merrick or not
we need to get some insurance.
Insurancce?
The last of the big three disasters...
The fire at Copps Coliseum....
No matter what Merrick does...
make sure it comes down....
- You gotta be kidding?
- Fire or no fire...
- 11,369 people need to die!
It's our only chance.
Sir, with all due respect, I am a
temporal security agent, not a murderer.
Consider it done!
Hey! Wait a minute.
Lets pull this up,
Sabbar or I'll kill you.
- I'm the least of your worries, Cortez.
- What the hell are you talking about?
You saw Grifasi.
We got a temporal containment leak.
Few more deviations,
Grifasi and the whole organisation...
... will not know even we exist.
Merrick, if this is all true...
... may be we shouldn't interfere.
- Then 11,000 people will die.
- I know, I know!
But it's just that, the guy from the
photos, warned us about interfering.
The two who are after are gonna kill
or risk being killed to stop us.
What if somebody we save
goes on to cause something so terrible-
- to happen which is much worse than
Copps Coliseum coming down.
I don't see it that way.
If those three people are from the future -
- Then yes! Their past is set.
that's gone down on one way.
But our future
can go on infinite number of ways.
Any one of which may be a whole lot better
than the world they are from.
Or a whole lot worse.
You're right. But all what we can
do is act on what we do know.
And knowing that 11,000 people
are going to die, including my son, -
- I'm ready to do whatever
I can do to save them.
With this speed we should be able
intercept Merrick in about five minutes.
Round up this area for
any neighbors who may
have seen traffic coming
in and out of here.
Look for some security cameras, whatever.
Sir, I found this and an e-mail.
She had attempted to trash the mail.
- I just ran a digital decompiler...
- Just get to the point.
She borrowed her mother's car.
They're heading to the Copps Coliseum.
Damn!
This is Baker.
We're doubly heading for Copps.
That's right! Cancel the local search.
Put everything there. Let's go!
Merrick, can I ask you a question now?
Only if you keep calling me Tom.
Ah! I got this feeling earlier as if you
and your son aren't that close.
I was just wondering what reall happened?
After the plant fire, I.... shut down...
from work, the world, everyone...
You can't just drop out of a kid's life,
and expect walk back when you're ready.
You must really miss him.
Do you miss his mom, too?
From day one I married
I lost out to my job,
till the jolt I got from
covering disasters.
Were you that turned on?
Until I got those men killed.
That was when I crawled into my cave
and disappeared.
Now that you're out of hybernation,
what do you think?
I like some parts of it.
Maybe we should stop for gas.
He stopped. Just ahead.
Time to put him out of our misery.
- Fill her up. - Check the oil and tires?
- That would be great.
I'll handle this.
- Son of a bi....
- Why are you trying to kill me?
Did you ever stop to think about the
consequences of what you're doing?
May be my son is dead, because you
decided to stop the plane from crashing.
Oh my god!
Come and help me!
- How long till we're there?
- I don't know.
I said how long?
May be 50 minutes.
It's okay, it's okay. Stay there.
Just stay there.
It's alright. The ambulance is here.
It's alright.
No! Elizabeth!
There's nothing you can do for her.
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
That's my truck!
Officer! Park it for me. Will you?
Looks like local boys took our warning
hard. What are you doing now?
Setting for local time. Working on creating
one with few more changes, resets...
- Resets to whatever time zone you're in.
- I eagerly await. I eagerly await.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have a full house!
16347 spectators to watch the game.
Good day, I'm Baker.
I don't know if it really going to happen,
but for safety's sake...
- Ladies and gentlemen!
- Awsome!
Welcome to Copps Coliseum!
Here is tonight's schedule.
We got fire! Fire!
Cortez, Merrick's dead.
The fire which is supposed
to bring this place down
will still work, so we don't
need to kill anybody.
Listen to me! It is one thing is to defend
an existing timeline.
An other thing entirely,
to purposedly invoke a disaster.
Have you listened to a word I've said?
Do you feel
any responsibility? What
kind of a person are you?
Kind that'll do anything, anything,
to stabilize this timeline, -
- long enough to get a reset
and save my son. You understand?
You don't give a damn
about any of them. Do you?
To the extent that they
don't screw our timeline.
- Yeah! They're people.
- They are dust!
If you're so worried about them,
why the hell are you here?
Do you think I wanna be doing this? Working
for some two big underground firms...
- that uses the greatest technology
ever invented for amusement rights?
- I was a genesist oncee.
- You are right.
I was with the government
temporal development programme, Cortez.
Oh! Lemme guess! When they shut it down
and illegalised time treavelling...
- You were already hooked.
I'm trying to figure.
Who is low on your moral scale..
Me, who does it for money,
or you, who does it for twist?
The tragedy struck when a series of
explosions devastated the arena -
- killing nearly two thirds
of the 16,000 spectators.
Lord, have mercy on this soul.
This is Tom Merrick!
Leave a message at the tone!
Merrik, it is Eleanor! You're not handling
hijacking charges for the public defender.
There's an old buddy of mine, Irwin
Thompson who is now a Defense attorney , -
- he's agreed to represent you during
Tuesday calling. You'll get the details.
Good job with the Copps Coliseum!
The stable temporal zone you created works!
We'll be ready in a few
minutes to reset you.
Permanent insertion point 24 hours prior to
Merrick getting on that flight.
That'll give us plenty of time to stop him.
Just name any of these
disasters, and you'll
instantly be transported
back in time -
- exactly three hours prior
to the disaster you select.
One more thing!
Stanza-displacer is still unstable.
And each test run is causing
more for burn out. Bottom line....
You only have one round trip ticket.
Back to stop Merrick from getting on
that plane and redirect our timeline -
- and then back here, to home.
We are online now! Good luck!
Copps Coliseum fire.
Now that you have come out of hibernation,
what do you think?
- What the hell?
- This is all wrong.
You're alive!
Yes! Last time I checked.
What is wrong with you?
Nothing.
We are back at Copps Coliseum
three hours earlier.
Somebody must have entered
an alternate date.
- What the hell are you doing ?!
- Connecting with Grifasi.
He already said
he has no more resets on this timeline!
We have no choice.
We have to take Merrick
and Copps Coliseum down again.
And then wait a week
for Grifasi can create a new reset.
- Maybe we should stop for gas.
- No! We definitely don't wanna do that.
You're not one of those
guys who refuse to
pull over till the car
tries to run on steam?
In this case, yeah.
We get some near the Coliseum.
What are you doing?
Those guys who were after
us from the train station..
Let's just say I have a
very important hunch -
- That this leads them straight to us.
This time we'll get of him
out of our misery for good.
Where the hell is Merrick?
Hey! Did you have a 1984 Oldsmobile Cutlass
here filling up in last few minutes ?
An Oldsmobile Cutlass? No.
You want me to check the oil and tires?
Over here.
Damn it!
Hey! It's fine. We can save your son.
Officer! Park it for me. Will you?
Looks like local boys took our warning
hard. What are you doing now?
Setting for local time.
Working on creating one
with few more changes,
which automatically...
Automatically resets to
whatever time zone you're in.
I eagerly await.
I'm Baker. This is Stans.
I can't guarantee that
anything's gonna happen,
but thank you for taking
my warning seriously...
You can not come in.
- I have to get my family.
The grandmother is seriously
ill. It's an emergency.
- What's her name? - Ah! Lindquist!
A couple more...
... We'll be ready to go.
Lindquist party! Please report the
first-aid station on the main con-course.
Thank you.
If you could just point me
to the first-aid station?
Sure! Absolutely.
Alright! Go out through
the door here, straight
down the hallway, and when
you get to the end...
Open this up! Open this up!
Steve! Could you go and
get something to eat?
They just paged us.
It's an emergency.
No. There is no emergency.
- I'm testing.
- Hurry!
Hello? Is this thing working?
Attention! Attention!...
What are you doing here Tom?
There's gonna be an explosion.
We must get out.
Fine! Last time you said that there
gonna be a fire. And this....?
Attention! There's a bomb in the arena!
I repeat! There's a bomb in the arena!
- Please! Evacuate immediately!
- We must take Kevin.
Please try to be calm!
Head to the emergency exits!
Please stay calm! I repeat!
There's a bomb in the arena!
Hey! I'm out of here.
We gotta do this now,
before any more of these people get out.
Where's Kevin?
Dad!
I'm not gonna let you do it this time.
You idiot.
Put the detonator down, Cortez!
- You have any idea what you're doing?
- Now!
Merrick! This way.
Jen! We must try to get out of here!
No moves!
Drop your weapon!
Get away!
- We're trapped!
- How do we get out?
Stanton! You are Stanton!
You shouldn't have invented
Stanza-displacer.
You shouldn't have invented...
Stay down on the floor.
Merrick! Put it down!
Damn you! Put it down!
Put it down!
- If I do that, we all are dead.
- I don't negotiate.
Drop it! Now!
We are trapped.
You've seen what weapon could do.
- It's our only way out of here.
- He may be right.
Shut up Stanton.
Put it down! now!
My leg!
Everybody out. Now! Now!
My leg...
Easy.
Thank you!
Stanton! What I said
earlier, that you're not
having what it takes
for the field work?
Ignore it.
But Sir! I think I'm
gonna take your
suggestion and switch
to the technical field.
...killing 200 of the
16,000 in attendance...
Kevin!
Mom!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
How did you know about all this?
It's a long story.
I'll tell you some day.
Thank you.
Am I gonna see you soon, Kevin?
- Yeah!
- Sure. Anytime.
Look! I've got to take care of something.
- See you real soon.
- Okay!
- Bye.
- You can't stand here, folks.
Where are you going?
- Look, Tom...
- Tom. You called me Tom.
That's, that's good. Tom.
It looked like you were staying,
and I didn't wanna interfere.
Anyway, I thought...
We at Time Shifters, hope that you enjoyed
this rare and informative moment, -
- that combines first three disasters
with genuine statle selectors.
And now it's time to take a deep breath
and get those camers out!
As we prepare to temporaly reset you to one
of most fantastic disasters in the history.
Are you ready?