(Dramatic music playing)
Man (On radio):
You're listening to
the mellow sounds
Of kcup,
the k-cup,
69 on your
radio dial.
- (Alien noises)
- (Gibbering nonsense)
(Gibbering continues)
(Screams)
(Dramatic music playing)
(Upbeat march playing)
* attack of the killer
tomatoes *
* attack of
the killer tomatoes *
* they'll beat you, bash you,
squish you, mash you *
* chew you up for brunch
* and finish you off
for dinner or lunch *
* they're marching
down the halls *
* they're crawling
up the walls *
* they're gooey, gushy,
squishy, mushy *
* rotten to the core
* they're standing
outside your door *
* remember
Herbert farbage *
* while taking out
his garbage *
* he turned around,
and he did see *
*Tomatoes hiding in his tree
* now he's just a memory
* I know I'm going
to miss her *
* a tomato ate my sister
* Sacramento fell today
* they're marching
into San Jose *
* tomatoes are on their way
* the mayor is on vacation
* the governor's
fled the nation *
* the police have gone
on strike today *
* the national guard
has run away *
* tomatoes will have
their day *
* attack of
the killer tomatoes *
* they'll beat you, bash you,
squish you, mash you *
* chew you up for brunch
* and finish you off for
dinner or lunch, munch,
munch *
* dinner or lunch,
munch, munch *
* dinner or lunch
Woman (Over police radio):
One Adam 12. See the woman?
Man (Over police radio):
Houston, we have
a problem up here.
Man (On radio):
It's half past the hour,
And now time for the news
with Michael St. James.
Man:
What do you
make of it?
Man #2:
I don't know, Joe.
No weapons, no motive,
no clothes.
All we've got to go on
is this bloody corpse.
- Well, look again, Harry.
- Huh?
Not blood...
Man (On radio):
Due in a large part to
a major surplus of tomatoes.
Tomato juice.
The tomato crop
continues to grow at
an unprecedented rate.
Within the last 12 hours,
we have received
A number of
unconfirmed reports
from throughout the nation
That may or may not
be connected to
this strange phenomenon.
Man (Voice echoing):
Hmm.
Sure doesn't taste like
tomato juice.
(Gulping, gagging)
(Clattering)
- Look at the giant
tomato, Martha.
- (Growling)
I didn't knew
they grew 'em
so big, Jess.
I wonder where
he's going.
(Clattering, roaring)
He got little Timmy.
- Poor Timmy.
- (Slurping)
- He ate him all up.
- (Burps, gulps)
(Sirens wailing)
(Gunshots)
Man:
The tomatoes are coming!
Sheriff, they're coming!
My God,
did you see that?
A tomato...
You didn't see anything.
You didn't hear anything.
- The pilot's still in there.
- Forget about the pilot.
- Come over here!
- We can't leave him.
It's just too incredible!
A kamikaze tomato!
- Tomatoes can't fly!
- Yeah?
They can't eat people either,
but they're doing one heck
of an impression.
Jim, talk to that sheriff
and find out what's
going on.
Get over here!
How bad is it?
Well, sir, I definitely
don't think it'll fly again.
I'm not talking
about that, you weiner!
What about the tomatoes.
We found two more bodies
at the main road,
But we pushed the tomatoes
back to the north end.
- I don't think any
managed to bust loose.
- They better not have.
- I want this thing contained!
- I understand, but nothing
seems to stop them.
We tried chemicals,
bugs, bullets.
Nothing seems to work.
Look, the president
wants a complete
investigation.
- We can't let this out.
People would...
- Panic, that's what.
And you know whose ass
is on the line?
Yours, mine,
- and the entire
ag department.
- Look out!
What if the president
wants an investigation?
He'll get his investigation,
but we'll keep it quiet.
I've arranged for
the most obscure generals,
The most obscure scientists,
and to head the investigation,
- this man.
- I don't recognize him.
Nobody does.
His name is Mason Dixon.
He hasn't worked
since the bay of pigs.
- Is there any sign
of a problem elsewhere?
- Not yet.
I've ordered the entire
g.D.P. Program shut down.
Wait a minute.
Isn't that Jim Richardson,
the press secretary?
- What's he doing here?
- The president's got him
keeping an eye
On the investigation.
- Why him?
- He's got a vegetable
garden, that's why.
With peas and carrots
and squash and tomatoes.
That sheriff tells me
there were reports of incidents
like this all over the county.
Oh, bullshit.
One nut spots
a flying saucer,
And pretty soon
everybody's shaking hands
with little green men.
God, who would've thought.
All we wanted was a bigger,
healthier tomato.
Look out!
Here it comes again!
Where did you get
this one, general?
Oh, I won that one
in a three-legged sack race
- last armed forces day
picnic.
- (Snoring)
What's the matter with
general number two?
Oh, he was out
all night on maneuvers.
Let him rest.
Oh, I'm sorry
I'm late, gentlemen.
Would you follow me, please?
Certainly.
Oh, general, would you
wake up, please?
I apologize for the size
of this room, gentlemen.
It's all I could do
on such short notice.
Now, are we all here?
- Where's Jim Richardson?
- The press secretary?
Yes.
Perhaps we can give him
a few more minutes.
General, I've been
meaning to ask you,
Have you heard anything
about the nuclear strike force
Tactical training
command meeting?
- You mean operation nichefict?
- That's right.
Not really. I've been
following the personnel
proficiency planning
For pago-pago paratroop
platoon patrols.
Oh, operation ppppp.
- What's the poop on ppppp?
- Moving well.
Did somebody
mention misfits?
- No. Ppppp.
- Ah.
Well, then, nichefict
must be pretty well
wrapped up.
(Chattering)
Gentlemen, gentlemen,
may I have your
attention, please?
Now that we're all here,
I'd like to turn the meeting
over to Dr. morrison.
- Doctor?
- Thank you, captain.
- "Major."
- Pardon me?
Never mind.
Well, as I'm sure
you're well aware,
This tomato problem has
caused considerable concern
Within the scientific
community.
Scientists throughout
the nation have directed
their attention
To this very
vexing problem
With only
limited success.
However,
With the help of
Dr. fuji nokitofa,
We believe we've
made a breakthrough.
Gentlemen, may I present
Dr. nokitofa.
How do you do, doctor?
Very well, thank you.
Dr. nokitofa,
would you please explain
The project
to the gentlemen?
Gentlemen, what we have
developed is, in essence,
A half-man, half-robot,
a very sophisticated
Combination of
human intelligence
and superhuman powers
Which we are confident
will result in the ultimate
Destruction of the enemy.
Thank you,
Dr. nokitofa.
Are there any
comments, gentlemen?
Mr. black?
As head of the federal
intelligence agency,
I certainly don't mean to
question the background
Of these fine gentlemen,
But frankly, I don't think
the answer to this problem
Lies in trinkets
and gadgets.
This is man
versus vegetable.
Technically, sir,
tomatoes are fags.
He means "fruits."
Ah. Fruits.
You see what I mean?
Mr. Dixon,
I've been authorized
to assign you
Four of my best agents.
Gentlemen,
with your permission,
I'd like to
Introduce Mr. Dixon
to his operatives.
That's fine, Mr. platt.
In the meantime,
The rest of us will accompany
the doctors down to view
a demonstration
Of the latest
anti-tomato project.
We'll be going outside,
Mr. Dixon.
You'd better bring
your coat.
There's a little jap
in the air.
He means "nip."
(Music over dialogue)
Man:
Wash, wash, wash.
Scrub, scrub, scrub.
Can you get my back?
- (Explosion)
- (Screaming)
- Oh, my eyes!
Oh, my eyes!
- (Alarm blaring)
Water! Water!
(Electricity crackling)
Actually, gentlemen,
this project entails
The development of limbs
with superhuman powers.
Unfortunately,
Budget limitations
have restricted our
development to only
One of these
technologically
advanced legs.
Okay, Bruce,
now let's try
running first.
Uh, that'll be
fine, Bruce.
Bruce,
Please jump for us.
(Crash)
Despite some minor
recruitment difficulties
Caused by our recent
p.R. Problem,
I believe you'll find
that your unit
Will meet the highest
of standards.
Pynchon.
Your men, Dixon.
Sam Smith,
disguise expert.
Gretta attenbaum,
swimming expert.
Gretta defected to us
after the last Olympics.
We feel she's gonna be
quite an addition
to the department.
Greg colburn,
underwater expert.
The fourth member
of your unit,
lt. Finletter,
Is winding up
his current mission.
He'll contact you
at these coordinates.
Expect him
at "10-100" hours.
Good luck, Dixon.
Can you, like,
believe how he waffles
on every issue?
Woman #2:
Oh, right on.
We'll never have
Another president
as bad as this one.
(Women giggle)
(Tomatoes gibbering)
- (Women screaming)
- What is it? Over there!
No! No!
(Screaming)
(Gibbering continues)
Mr. Daniels,
I realize that
in the past,
There have been
some questions raised
Regarding the president's
use of public funds
For what some may consider
personal items.
However, I can say without
fear of contradiction
That under no circumstances
and at no time
Has the current
administration expended
Any public monies
whatsoever
For the purchase of
the Fluffy flower-print
toilet paper.
Now, if there are
no further questions...
Thank you,
Mr. press secretary.
Mr. secretary!
Just a moment,
gentlemen.
One more question.
The little fellow
in the rear.
Bobby jenks, sir,
p.S. 149.
I have a question, sir.
Certainly, young man.
What would you like to know?
We've heard nothing at all
about the growing
tomato menace.
(Reporters clamoring)
I...
Uh...
Wouldn't exactly call it
a menace, young man.
There have been some
isolated reports
Alleged incidents involving
some unusual activity
Associated with this, uh,
Particular vegetable,
But I assure you
that, uh,
This is not and never
will become a menace.
However, the president,
leaving no stone unturned,
Has called upon our most
noted congressional leaders
in this field
To begin a thorough,
intensive, painstaking,
And exhaustive investigation
Into the backgrounds
and origins of this
Interesting quirk
of nature.
Furthermore, you can assure
all of your young readers that
This will never become a problem
that Americans need fear.
This, uh, meeting of
the senate investigating
committee's
Called to order.
Anybody remember
what we're supposed
to be investigating?
- The tomatoes, Wayne.
- What was it?
We're investigating
those tomatoes.
Oh, yes, yes.
Yes, of course. Yes.
Well, there's one for you,
One for you,
One here for me,
One for you.
There's supposed to be
one for everybody.
Wonder where
it could be.
(Phone rings)
Woman:
Good morning, city herald.
May I help you?
Roberts!
- Sir?
- Get me Goldstein.
- He's still
in beirut, sir.
- Beirut?
Yes, he's fired, sir.
Oh. Yeah.
Get me Johnson.
Sorry, sir. He's covering
that trial in Texas.
Oh, cripes!
Okay, just get me anybody
in the special assignment desk.
They're all on
special assignment.
Goddamn it!
Who the hell is here?
Well, uh,
there's you, sir.
Thank you, Julius.
Wait a minute.
- There's Fairchild.
- Who the hell is he?
"She." Sir.
Lois Fairchild,
society section.
The new kid?
Society, huh?
Oh, what the hell.
Send her in.
Now, damn it!
(Motorcycle engines revving)
(Cheering)
(Groaning)
Man:
Hey, look. It's a funky
little tomato.
(Chuckles, choking groans)
(Screaming)
(Siren wailing)
- Where are we going?
- Take the old mission road.
Some crazy-ass biker
has got himself munched on
by a herd of tomatoes.
- So what can we do?
- We can keep it quiet,
that's what.
Didn't you hear
the police radio?
It's solid tomatoes
between here and holtville.
We're liable to get killed!
Will you can it,
you little pud-puller?
If John q. Public finds out
what's really going down,
We're both
as good as dead.
Fairchild, sir.
- Hmm?
- Fairchild.
You sent for me?
Oh. Yeah, yeah.
Have a seat.
Fairchild,
I've been keeping
my eye on you.
You've got
a good sense
of organization.
Thank you, sir.
- Fluid style.
- Thank you, sir.
- Sharp mind.
- A nice ass.
- Thank...
I'm about to
give you a challenge,
Your first
big assignment,
And I expect you
to use
Every attribute
at your disposal.
I'm sure that what
you lack in experience
You'll more than
make up for in...
Determination.
Now,
This will give you
the necessary background
To handle
the assignment.
Go to it.
Right away, sir.
Uh, one more thing,
Fairchild:
I'm certain
the government will go
to unbelievable lengths
To ensure the secrecy
of this thing.
Good luck.
- (Siren wailing)
- (Tomatoes gibbering)
Help! Help!
(Gibbering)
Do you read me?
Go away! Go away!
(Exclaiming)
- Do you read me?
Do you read me?
- Are you happy now?
You kept it so goddamned
secret, nobody knows
where the hell we are!
- Do you read?
Do you read?
- Help me! S.O.S.!
Give me that,
for Christ sake!
You can't tell me
to shut up! I quit!
What? You can't quit!
The department...
Screw the department!
I'm gonna die!
You conceited
little s.O.B.,
I'm gonna die too!
- Good! Good!
Good, good, good...
- (Clattering)
Not good, Mr. president.
Not good at all.
Frankly, I was not
overly impressed
With the level
of competency displayed
by the scientific team.
I haven't seen Dixon's
special forces unit yet,
But if it's anything like
what I've seen so far,
I'd say we're in for
a bit of trouble.
Man:
I know what you mean, Jim.
I know what you mean.
It's like trying
to stack bibles
On whipped cream.
- Yes, sir.
- Jim, an unusual problem
Calls for
an ingenious solution.
I think
I've got one.
Jim, have you ever
heard of mindmaker?
Certainly, sir.
The advertising agency
you used in your campaign.
That's right.
You know,
they said I'd never
get reelected,
Especially after
it got out that I used
the statue of liberty
As collateral
on that arab loan.
- Yes, sir.
- But...
I'm sitting here now,
and I owe it all
to mindmaker.
Incidentally, Jim,
you were in the mideast
last summer.
Tell me, how does
the old girl look
in the dead sea?
- Just grand, sir.
- Good.
I tell you, Jim,
if those fellows
could elect me,
- they can do anything.
- Yes, sir.
Jim, I want you to fly
to New York immediately.
I want you to see
Ted Swann.
Believe me,
the man's a genius.
I'm on my way, sir.
That's the whole story.
Say, would you want
to buy a used crib?
I don't think so,
but I appreciate
this information.
This could be
especially helpful in...
Fairchild, from the times.
What's this deal
about tomatoes?
- Look, buddy, don't try
and stonewall me.
- Man: Hi there, Lois.
Oh. Hi, Clark.
- What are you
doing here?
- Uh, no comment.
- And who's he?
- No comment.
- How serious is
this situation?
- No comment.
- The American public
has a right to know.
- Man: Up, up, and away!
You can't ignore
the press.
Dixon!
Man (On radio):
Hey, guys, here's the song
everybody's been asking for:
Ronny Desmond's
"puberty love."
Man (High voice):
* puberty, puberty love
Man:
Oh, wow,
what is that?
Oh, no! Don't tell me
that's the song.
Please, oh!
Turn it off!
Oh, it's torture on the ears!
I can't stand that noise!
(All chattering)
(Radio switching stations)
(Man on radio reading news)
Man:
Quiet! I want
to hear the news.
Man (On radio):
And today, the president
closed the nation's
Last remaining sub base
at groton, Connecticut.
When asked why he had made
the startling decision,
The president responded,
"those funny little
black ships
Just keep sinking anyway."
And in other news today,
in Newark, new Jersey,
A man was eaten by a bacon,
lettuce and tomato sandwich.
You're free!
(Airplane passes overhead)
Man:
Geronimo!
(Crashing thud)
Hmm.
So you're
finletter, huh?
I'm Mason Dixon,
and this is...
My God!
It's Adolf Hitler!
(Shouting)
This is Sam Smith.
He's our
undercover expert.
He's only disguised
as Adolf Hitler.
Guten morgen,
herr Hitler.
- Autobahn.
- Sprechen ze deutche?
Weiner schnitzel.
Get in the backseat!
What about me, Mr. Dixon?
What about me?
You...
You go disguise
yourself
As a tomato
And infiltrate
their camp.
Yes.
Thank you.
- Hi.
- Mr. Richardson
to see Mr. Swann.
Yes, sir.
He's expecting you.
I'll let him
know you're here.
Please have a seat.
Mr. Swann?
Mr. Richardson
is here to see you.
He'll be
right with you.
Jimbo, buddy!
How are ya?
How you doin'?
- Fine. I, uh...
- Super, super.
Hey, the president
tells me you have
a situation, jimbo.
Well, let me clue you:
You boys have come
to the right place.
Let me give you a peek
at mindmaker in action.
First, we have to convince
the little housewife out there
That the tomato which
ate the family pet
Is not dangerous,
no problem.
Then we have to convince
local authorities
That the thousands missing
from rural communities
Were merely stranded
during their
Bicentennial pilgrimage
to Philadelphia.
No problem.
Third, the president
wants us to do this
in such a way
That it can be covered up,
and no one will know
it ever happened.
That's no problem.
But then he wants us
to do this
And convince
200 million Americans
That this disaster
is actually a blessing.
Now, that's a challenge.
I understand
what you're saying,
Mr. Swann.
The president is a very
demanding person.
Sometimes he expects
the impossible.
But I don't...
I never said "impossible,"
Richardson.
What I said was that
it was a challenge.
Man was put on this earth
to meet challenges,
my boy.
You really think
you can do it?
Can I do it?
(Maniacal laughter)
* some sell, some buy,
and only we know why *
* the wrap is more important
than the prize *
* important decisions
are made each day *
* much too important for
the plain folk to make *
* they're always
in a bind *
* depend on us to help
make up their mind *
* red box, blue box,
a red box and a blue box *
* bright colors
and a coupon
on the side *
* hard sell or soft sell,
it's all the same *
* millions of dollar bills
are spent every day *
* where do they all go?
* mindmaker's here
to run the show *
* we sell cars and toys
for girls and boys *
* and chairs and beds
and shrunken heads *
* sugar beets
and baseball cleats
and ice to eskimos *
* leeks and mink
and boats that sink *
* no matter what,
we'll get it sold *
* we'll use catchy jingles,
snappy tunes and pretty girls
with big balloons *
* a little lie,
a stretch of truth can
turn the public's head *
* there's TV types
and ad execs and
everyone's the best *
* and yet
* they all look up
* to a single man
* and that one
single man *
* is... me!
(Maniacal laughter)
* they sell, they buy,
and only I know why *
* the human mind is
putty in my hands *
* important decisions
are made each day *
* much more important for
the plain folk to make *
* they're always
in a bind *
* depend on me to help
make up their mind *
* decision-wise
* policy-wise,
demographically speaking *
* mindmaker!
Well, let's go meet
that challenge,
young man.
I've already put
my staff to work,
So if you'd be good enough
to stop by in the morning,
We can take a look-see
at some of the
preliminary sketches.
Roll it.
Man (On recording):
Then I can tell the president
you'll accept the assignment.
(Chuckling)
You bet your booties.
Traffic cops
all over the country
meet this challenge
Day to day.
This man is like
any other policeman
anywhere in the country.
He works hard
and takes pride
in serving people.
Yes, he's a policeman
just like any other,
Except for one thing:
He is blind.
(Crashing,
tires screeching)
Woman:
This has been
a public service announcement
Produced for the national
health foundation.
(Horns honking)
(Hammer pounding)
Sir, I really
don't think this is
a good place to camp.
We're not sleeping
on the sidewalk.
Do you see that big
building over there?
It's called a hotel.
You and I are going to
sleep in the hotel.
No campfire, sir?
No campfire.
Well, then, what
am I supposed to do
with these marshmallows?
Here's the key to my room.
I'm gonna check for messages.
Be up in a minute.
Yes, sir.
Pardon me.
Do you have
any messages
For Mason Dixon
in room 401?
Excuse me.
May I have the key
to room 401?
I... i seem to have
misplaced mine.
Thank you.
Man (On TV):
Pray-tel records
presents
21 great dead beats.
You get the best
of jimi hendrix,
Janis joplin,
Otis Redding,
buddy holly,
Jim croce...
(Switching channels)
Man:
It's the evening news with
Charles collingsmith...
Turn that thing off,
will ya?
Let's get some sleep.
Marshmallow?
(Snoring)
Oh. I'm...
I'm terribly sorry.
I-I mean, I thought
this was my...
Really. You know.
Dixon:
What was that?
- A strumpet, sir.
- A what?
A harlot. A trollop.
A lady of the evening.
Go to sleep,
finletter!
(Ringing)
Hmm?
Wh-what?
Where?
I'll be right there.
- Breakfast, sir.
- No time!
- But... your vitamins.
Now, listen.
This is important.
You've got to go down
and warn gretta that there's
tomato activity in sector 2.
You got that?
No matter what happens,
you tell her.
- Yes, sir.
- Man (On radio):
We interrupt this program
To bring you
a special bulletin.
The following is an nbs
hotline bulletin
With Douglas keikler
in New York.
Nbs... the network
that brings you
The news
as it happens,
Brings you these bulletins
in times of emergency,
The news you need to know
when you need to know it,
on nbs,
The network
of the news.
This nbs news
hotline bulletin
Is brought to you
by schritz beer.
You're never too drunk
to ask for schritz.
And by bright gums,
the toothpaste
For people without
teeth or dentures.
And by...
(Chattering)
(Rustling)
What is it, spot?
What's in there?
Spot:
Gosh, Billy,
I don't know.
You stay there.
I'll go look.
- Spot? Spot?
- (Rustling)
(Tomatoes gibbering)
- What are those
red circles, sir?
- Machine gun emplacements.
We've got the whole valley
surrounded with them.
I don't think
we can hold them
very long, though.
And that green line,
that's their furthest
point of advance?
- That's right.
- Uh-huh. What are
the blue dots?
Those are mobil stations.
- Oh.
- (Vehicle approaching)
That must be
major mills.
- Take over.
- Yes, sir!
I'm glad you could
make it, sir.
- I think we've got something
that will interest you.
- So I've been told.
Dixon, I want you
to see this.
Captain?
Yes, sir.
(Gibbering)
Sir,
We've captured
a giant tomato.
(Gibbering continues)
I'm afraid, gentlemen,
that what we have
here before us
Isn't what we thought.
You don't mean...
This,
May God help us,
Is a cherry tomato.
- (Screaming)
- (Roaring)
(Rustling)
(Gibbering, slurping)
(Screams)
Mr. Dixon
has ordered me
to inform you
That there's
tomato activity
in your sector.
All right,
who wants to be
paper monitor?
I'm telling you, j.B.,
it's a great idea.
The first adult
breakfast cereal:
Kinky crispies.
Comes in three
delicious flavors...
Good afternoon,
Mr. Swann.
I'll call you back,
j.B. Bye.
Jimbo!
How's it going?
I believe that's
my question.
Right. Fun-NY!
(Chuckles)
Well, let me tell you,
we've been going
great bananas.
Sit down, make
yourself comfortable.
I asked myself,
"what do we need?
"Something original,
Something that strikes
at the very heart
of the matter."
And here it is!
Mindmaker at its best!
Who can argue
with that?
And there's more.
Listen to this.
Man (On recording):
Giant tomatoes mean
bigger pizzas!
- Man #2: Rolling on 2.
- * if you're feeling
sad and blue *
* tomatoes end it
all for you *
Last year,
more people were killed
By automobile accidents,
heart attacks,
Lung cancer,
and natural causes
combined
Than by
any one tomato.
Pretty classy, huh?
With a capital "k."
Right.
And Mr. secretary,
Being a public relations
man yourself,
You understand
the value of symbols.
Well, we have
spent a great deal
of time and effort
And over a million dollars
to create a symbol
which will wage this battle,
An effort that will
become known as
The "stop tomato
program."
I see.
It all looks quite...
Extraordinary.
- Thank you.
- Now if you'll excuse me,
- I think I'll be
on my way.
- Just a moment.
One more thing
before you leave,
Mr. secretary.
I'd really like you
to see this.
It's something
I've worked on
for many years,
The culmination
of years of effort:
The world's
ultimate commercial.
Roll it.
(Dramatic music plays)
Man (Deep voice):
Hi.
Jesus Christ
for technitron.
Man (On radio):
The nation is in chaos.
Can nothing stop
this tomato onslaught?
Last night, tomatoes
attacked Los Angeles...
(Screaming)
Boston.
Seattle.
Chicago.
Even the mere mention
of the word
Is sufficient
to induce panic.
Tomato.
(Screaming)
More news
at the hour.
Now back to the rocking sound
of the boober on super 101.
Man #2:
All right! Man, that's
really something, huh?
Hey, everyone,
I'm gonna play something...
(Slurping, growling)
That's right, man.
It's number one
in the charts this week...
The heavy sound
of Ronny Desmond's
"puberty love."
* puberty
* puberty love
* there is nothing like
puberty love *
(Continues, indistinct)
While the federal
agencies involved
have declared
-(snoring)
- That the necessary information
has not been forwarded
To state agencies
for their respective
review and approval,
We cannot ignore local pleas
for inter-governmental
cooperation
- (snoring)
- In what is obviously
an affair
Best suited for
international actions.
- (Snoring)
- This is a question
best left to people
For whom there is
no spokesman greater
Than those who speak...
(Men snoring loudly)
Dixon:
And then I put
my foot to the floor,
And I got out of there
as fast as I could.
It was all very strange.
I... i just don't know
what to think.
You made no unusual
motions of any kind?
Not to my knowledge.
Odd.
Were there any loud noises
or other extraneous activity
Which might have affected
the tomatoes' behavior,
Such as an airplane
Or another car
in the vicinity?
I'm almost sure
there wasn't.
-(Snoring)
- If you'll excuse me,
gentlemen,
I really have to be
getting back to Washington.
That's fine.
Give my regards
to the president.
- I'll do that, captain.
- It's "major."
Of course.
Priority-one message
for Mr. Dixon, sir.
- A phone call for you.
- Oh, thank you.
I'll need one of those
for my records too.
I'll need one
for my files.
And don't forget
the major.
(All chattering)
- Yeah?
- Trouble, sir.
- Hello?
Both:
What?
I haven't seen Dixon
all day.
I've been following
his assistant, but that's
getting me nowhere.
- "Followed"? By who?
- Following who?
- His assistant.
- A spy.
- A spy?
- That's right.
Both:
Well, what's
he look like?
Medium height,
medium build.
It's a "she," sir.
You know, the strumpet
last night.
- The one with the big...
- Guns and a sword...
- With long, blonde...
- Parachute...
- Sunglasses...
- Combat boots...
- And a dress.
- Nothing suspicious
about that.
- You can't be serious.
- What shall I do?
Look, I thought I made it
perfectly clear.
I don't think you've made use
of all your potential,
if you know what I mean.
Look, you're
obviously tired.
Why don't you go
take a nap?
- You mean, go to bed?
- I couldn't do that!
- Why not? You're a woman.
- I resent that.
I didn't say that
you were incompetent.
I just think
you could use a rest.
Yes, sir.
But i...
Well, I'll do
my best, sir.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Operator?
Operator, I, uh...
I've gotten
a wrong number.
- I'd like my dime back.
- (High-pitched chattering)
Hi, there.
Hello.
Listen,
about last night.
It was an accident.
I really didn't mean...
It was a dark night.
I mean,
The lights were off,
and it got dark.
I mean, it was dark,
and it was light earlier.
You want to
go to bed?
Uh, excuse me, ma'am?
- Uh...
- I've got to go to bed.
Newspaper editor's voice:
I don't think you've made use
of all your potential,
If you know
what I mean.
All your potential.
(Echoing) Potential.
Potential. Potential.
(Clattering)
I, uh...
I was right.
I was right!
A spy!
(Screams)
(Crash)
(Screaming)
(Fairchild screaming)
Did you warn gretta?
Uh, yes, sir,
but she was
already dead.
It figures.
(Slurping)
Man (Over intercom):
Attention. Attention.
The 56th combat
support group
Will depart
at 0900 hours.
All 3rd division personnel
report to the 5th division
staging area.
All 5th division
personnel report to
The 3rd division
staging area.
Will the driver
of tank 38421
Please go to
the parking lot?
Your lights are on.
- Had a few setbacks
during the night.
- Serious?
Well, it depends on
your point of view.
Did you have
any relatives
in Wyoming?
Say again?
"Arkansas"?
Are you sure?
Arkansas.
Dixon:
What's the situation?
Prime intelligence
tells us
That the tomatoes
are amassing for
a final
All-out attack
on the nation.
Our top brass wants us
to concentrate our forces
here on the coast.
If we can
hold them here,
we can win.
- If not...
- Is there anything
I can do, major?
Yes. The president wants
your personal report.
Call him on the red line
at 1100 hours.
Be back here tonight.
We'll need every man
we can get.
Damn it, Dixon,
this is war!
Very good, sir.
(Gunshot)
Sir, i...
I think somebody's
shooting at you.
- Where do you think...
(Exclaims)
- (Bullet ricochets)
So you can see,
Mr. Dixon,
We have no choice
but to make our stand
out west.
And I want you
to make sure that
our military people
Out there in that region
understand and are aware
Of their enormous
responsibility.
I'm sure they are,
Mr. president.
President:
By the way, have you seen
Jim Richardson out there?
Dixon:
Just briefly.
How's the ad campaign going?
Excellent.
My mail's running
30 to 1 in favor
of the tomatoes.
Terrific.
Oh, God,
I almost forgot.
- Shirley?
- Woman: Yes, sir?
I want you to get
general Mitchell
on the line.
Tell him to bomb
New York City.
But, Mr. president,
The tomatoes are not even
close to New York City.
Listen, you worry
about your problems,
And I'll worry
about mine.
Yes, sir.
- Is that the last pen?
- Yes, sir.
Thank God.
(Tomatoes slurping)
Hey, will somebody
please pass the ketchup?
(Angry gibbering)
(Screams)
As you were.
Man:
Order, arms.
The men look ready,
major.
As ready as they'll
ever be, Dixon.
You know, Dixon,
A man stops to think
at a time like this
About his home,
His wife, his kids.
- You married, major?
- No.
Me either.
I wonder what
the tomatoes are
thinking about right now.
* we stopped
* the Germans in '45
* then we crushed
- * the viet cong
- * almost
* for a greater glory
* we could
never strive *
* this crop uprising
* will not last long
* ain't no time
to make a fuss *
* we got to get
those tomatoes *
* before they get us
* we're gonna beat 'em,
mash 'em, squish 'em, bash 'em
in the street *
* we're gonna kick 'em,
kick 'em, mush 'em, crush 'em
with our feet *
* we're gonna meet them,
munch them, crunch them,
gonna stomp 'em in place *
- yeah.
- Yeah.
* t-o-m-a-t
* o-e-s
tomatoes *
* we'll squish them,
we'll mash them *
* we'll mush them
we'll crush them *
* we stopped to negotiate
at the first attack *
* we gave 'em Alabama
but they gave it right back *
* tomatoes, tomatoes
* tomatoes
* they said we'd live together
like sister and brother *
* but they captured a cannery
and bottled my mother *
* now she's at the store
and they'll soon be
back for more *
* those tomatoes
* tomatoes
(Gibbering)
(Growling)
(Groaning)
Male narrator:
Across the length
and breadth of the nation,
The tomatoes continue
on their rampage
of wanton destruction,
- burning,
- (Woman screams)
- Pillaging,
- Raping.
- (Woman screams)
- (Coughing)
- Let's shoot it from
over there, huh, bill?
Come on
over here, lady.
Stand by over here
for just a minute, huh?
Okay, don't go away.
We start with
a tight shot, huh, bill?
Tell me
when you're ready.
Don't run off.
Across this great nation,
almost everyone
has been affected
In one way or another
by this terrible
tomato onslaught.
- Mrs. Williams, I understand
your husband is missing.
- Yes, he is.
- Do you think he's dead?
- Well, i...
- Will you miss him?
Will you marry again?
- (Screaming)
What if he's laying
in a ditch somewhere
- with both legs broken,
calling your name?
- (Crying) Stop!
You will have to find
another man, you know.
You're no spring chicken.
What are you
going to do,
Mrs. Williams?
- Can you answer my quest...
- (Wailing)
Please look
into the camera.
Mrs. Williams (Wailing):
Get away from me!
Male narrator:
Last night's crushing
military defeat
May spell the end
for humanity.
The shattered remnants
of a once-proud
civilization
Lay scattered
amongst crushed spirits
and broken bodies.
Lawlessness is rampant,
panic stalks the streets,
And personal
grooming habits
Have reached
an all-time low.
(Gibbering)
(Gibbering continues)
Man (On radio):
I'll tell you now
what's coming up...
It's the song that's
sweeping the country,
number one all over,
From the west coast
to the east coast,
every coast in between...
Yeah, that's right.
You've been asking for it,
you've been waiting for it.
Here it is, boys and gals,
it's Ronny Desmond's
"puberty love"!
* puberty
puberty love *
* there is nothing like
* it's so deep
* it's so cool
(Continues, indistinct)
Get out of the car!
Hurry up, move!
(Shouting)
(Shouting continues)
(Engine sputtering)
(Engine clattering violently)
Hey!
- Sir? Sir?
- What?
- Sir! Sir!
- I'm driving!
(Exclaiming)
Dixon:
There's something wrong
with the car!
We'll get them,
finletter!
- We can catch it, sir!
- Don't worry!
Freeze!
Richardson:
Good afternoon,
Mr. Dixon.
Had a pleasant nap?
Richardson.
I'm not surprised.
Mr. Dixon,
I didn't really think
you would be.
That's why you're here.
What do you intend
to do with me?
Mr. Dixon,
don't be so naive.
You are the only one
with the knowledge
that can stop me.
Don't be a fool, Richardson.
You don't have a chance.
You know very well
I do.
You know,
It's funny, Dixon.
No man sits
closer to power
Than the press secretary
to the president
of the United States.
And yet
as close as it is,
That power
is never really
within your grasp.
It dangles
before you,
Taunting, daring,
Mocking your
very impotence.
I will not be
mocked anymore!
I will no longer give
other people's answers
To other people's
questions.
The answers
will be mine.
The questions
Everything
will be mine.
It'll be glorious,
Dixon.
It's too bad you won't
be around to see it.
What makes you think
that you can
Control these tomatoes
better than anyone else?
Questions, questions.
You missed
your calling.
Mr. Dixon, have you
had lunch yet?
Here.
Have a tomato.
(Chuckles)
Don't be afraid.
It's really quite small
and quite harmless.
It's from
my garden.
You might say
that I'm...
In tune
with my tomatoes.
At the proper time,
When all vestiges
of authority
Have disappeared,
I shall charge in
on my white stallion
And save the nation,
Or what's left of it.
My fellow citizens will be
eternally grateful.
At the very least,
they'll surely choose
My benevolent leadership
Over the obvious
alternative.
It shall be
my golden moment.
But, Mr. Dixon,
I'm afraid these are
your final moments.
You're awfully confident
for a man who has
failed twice.
Three times,
but who's counting?
I don't think
you can do it.
You know, Dixon,
you may be right.
I've never killed
a man before.
You may be right.
(Door buzzer sounds)
Who's there?
Man:
U.P.S. Package for you.
Come in.
(Shot fires)
Then again,
- you may be wrong.
- Wait.
Before you pull
that trigger,
Tell me how
you do it.
Really.
How melodramatic.
Very well.
It's really quite simple.
- (Footsteps running)
- You see, all I do is...
(Shouting)
(Groaning)
A real bad apple, sir.
It's a good thing
we got him.
(Exclaiming)
Finletter!
We've got to round up
everybody in the city.
You got that?
And meet me in the stadium.
There's no time to lose.
But, sir,
everybody's left town.
The only people left
will be crazy people.
I don't care!
Just do it! Move!
Sir...
Then it's
unanimously agreed
That the committee
recommend
That no further action
will be taken at this time.
(Crowd chattering, exclaiming)
I've got it!
Hey, guys, look!
They're starting to come!
They're coming!
(Tomatoes growling, slurping)
(Panicked shouting)
Turn on
the record player!
Cover your ears!
Everyone!
(Over p.A.)
* puberty, puberty love
* there's nothing like
puberty love *
* it's so great,
it's so cool *
(Continues, indistinct)
Dixon:
Look! The tomatoes!
It's working, it's working!
(People exclaiming)
Charge!
(Woman screams)
(Tomato growling,
gibbering)
I want to thank you
for saving my life.
Just doing
my job, lady.
Well, I guess
there's nothing
more to say.
Bye, Mr. Dixon.
Goodbye, miss Fairchild.
"Lois."
Lois.
Goodbye, Mr. Dixon.
"Mason."
Mason?
Lois?
Oh, Mason!
- Lois!
- Mason!
Mason!
* the first time
I saw you *
* I hated your guts
* I felt your love
* for cigarette butts
* but now that
I've touched you *
* I always will
love you *
* my love for you
will never dim *
* until all the fish
can't swim *
* the first time
I saw you *
* was such a thrill
to me *
* I felt your nose
* tickle my knee
* our love
will be classy *
* like Timmy and Lassie
* I know that
you're ever mine *
* until the very
end of time *
(Birds chirping)
(Animals calling)
(High voice)
All right, you guys,
they're gone now.
(Upbeat music plays)