He's like..bap-bap-bap-bap-bap!
I give him a tap.
Oh, man..
I thought God was gonna shoot
pool with the nigger's balls.
You know what I mean?
I know we was out in Chalet.
Shit was benini.
And then my man J. back there
think he's wild in' out,
'cause we already know
each other like that.
God got an ill sense of humor,
you know what I mean?
How come God make a man strip
before he beat him down?
Yo, let me tell you
somethin, G'
God say a beatin' don't
mean shit to a nigger.
Take a man's dignity away
and strip him down naked, humiliate him,
he'll never forget that,
you know what I'm sayin'?
That's some psychological
ill shit, you know what I mean?
That's life, though, right
there. I can get with that.
- How much this kid
come up short, though?
- God's like,
he told the crack head,
stop doin' all the wild shit.
He's still sucking on the glass
dick. All that's irrelevant,
because we ain't gonna
lay him down, you is.
You know what I mean?
You the new kid on the block.
You gots to earn your stripes.
- What you talking about, man?
- What you mean,
what I'm talking about?
- Keepin' it real with us, right?
- You know I am.
Then you ain't got
nothin' to worry about.
So he's gotta make sure his
angel's got wings. nigger, fly.
Here comes the exciting part.
After months of hard work,
you're finally where you wanna be.
You're deep enough inside
so that the boys want to test you.
Now, they want you to prove
that you're down, right?
No. Absolutely wrong.
What they really want you to
prove is that you're not a cop.
What do you do?
Aw, come on.
Anybody?
Huh. At least we got
one courageous cadet.
Come on down here, rook.
Show me what you got.
Now, check it out. crimson baby.
Main man gonna hang you the honor
of blastin' this punk.
He's skimmin' off the top.
We can't have that.
- What's up?
- I'll just hand
the honor right back.
I mean, it's the man's
beef, not mine.
It's not the way
the game is played.
You see, the man's beef...
is always your beef.
And you know what else?
If you ain't one of us,
you must be one of them.
Your stupid ass is dead.
Is that Play skool enough
for you to understand?
- You gots to earn
your stripes, baby.
- Make me proud.
No problems.
Show me where the kid at.
Don't you worry about it,
man. We're gonna roll by
his place of employment...
sort a "in cog-negro."
Then we going to see
if we got the right one, baby.
Let me showy' all Cincinnati cats
how to wet a nigga up right.
That's what
I'm talk in 'about.
- Right there?
- Right there. All right. Hold up.
Black cap.
Black cap right there.
Whoo-oo!
Yo, roll up.
Yo, roll up close, man.
I want to see the whites
in this cat's eyes.
There he is, right in front of you.
Just a little punk.
Can't keep his nose
out of the cookie jar.
What you gonna do?
You just got yourself
in so deep that you'll
never be able to get out.
He didn't pose
an immediate threat.
For God's sake, you didn't even
check to see if he was armed.
You all know what that is?
That's premeditated murder, Cadet.
You're hold in' that gun.
Time is runnin' out.
- We out.
- What you talk about?
Your brain vaporized
like ten minutes ago.
Your heart's dancin'
on your tongue.
Your life depends on
split-second decisions.
You better do somethin'
and you better do it now.
Damn! Go!
- You ain't hit him yet?
- Let's go. Let's go. Come on.
Let's get the fuck out.
- Why you ain't givin' me no co-op, man?
- You can't shoot worth nothin'.
- Yo, I had the kid right there, man.
- You ain't nothin' but a talker.
Yo, turn the car around.
Give me a little co-op.
Face up, bro. You whack.
Can't shoot. What?
My boy got a crazy heart.
I got a heart.
Ain't gonna was temyammo.
- Move over there.
- No, you come on up here.
Just..Just come on.
Come on, man. What you doin'?
Come on. Get yourself
in the picture with your mother.
Jeffery.
- Give me the camera.
- Give your sister the camera.
- Go up there with your family.
- Let me take..
No! Go ahead.
Ready?
I'm gonna go,
catch a football game.
Okay. Nice to meet you all.
It's okay.
Wait a minute.
- Captain D'Ambrosio.
- What's up?
I was wondering if I could stop by
your office tomorrow.
You saw the memo
on my bulletin board?
- How'd you know?
- Because three other rookies already
talked to me about the job today.
I'm sure I'd be better
than any of those guys.
Really? What makes you think you'd be
so good at undercover work?
My mother says I'm damn good at makin'
anyone believe anything, you know.
Oh, your mother.
Listen. I grew up in community
housing back in Cleveland.
So growing up in the projects..
that doesn't automatically qualify you.
- You know what a street gang does?
- Mm-hmm.
There's big players
out here, man.
They're gonna believe
I need in.
Nobody knows me in Cincinnati.
Be in my office
tomorrow, 4:00.
You know, you wear your shooting badge
on the wrong side of your uniform.
I don't expect I'll be wear in' it
after tomorrow, sir.
Here we go.
Attention on a 1-0-5.
Repeat, 1-0-5. All units.
Check out this walk,
Wilson.
They're gonna figure him
for a narc a mile away.
Cut the brother
some slack, will you?
This is his first
time on the street.
- What's up?
- What's up, dog?
Got some shit?
I don't know you, man. Take that
shit down the block or somethin'.
The sepunks ain't gonna
deal this rookie jack shit.
- Is this a joke or somethin', man?
- Go down the block, man.
- You know this nigger here?
- No, son. I don't know this nigger.
What's up, man? You a
po-po nigger? What's up?
I ain't no mother
fuckin' po-po.
Nigger, you sure
smell like you po-po.
You out your mother
fuckin' mind, man.
- Fuck, nigger. What's up?
- Oh, shit.
Told you this Puerto Rican nose
can smell heat a mile away.
I ain't fuckin' with you cats.
You out here with a little
Crackerjack knife.
- Nigger, fuck you, man.
- Fuck you, nigger. You don't know me.
Chill out.
Chill. Chill. All right?
What's up, man?
You buy in' or what?
Come on.
Damn. Yo.
- All right?
- Yeah.
Yeah! Well,
your Puerto Ricannose...
is gettin' as old
as your concepcion.
The rook detective bought
his first time out.
- What's up, Cap'n?
- How you doin'?
Hey, Pres, man, couldn't you
find a warm coffee shop...
or someplace we
can be just as safe?
I like this view
of Cincinnati.
You can bring a cup of
coffee with you if you want to.
I don't understand why we
have to meet every week.
Because talking on the telephone
is not enough for undercover work.
You gotta be able to
unload face to face.
Unload what, man? I made a buy
and bust on my first try out.
I'd say I was doin'
pretty good, huh?
I would say the department
is doing pretty good.
- That would be the way I would put it.
- Right. Right. Excuse me.
Look, the point is, I got..
We got some crack off the street.
Yep, we did. About a
rat's nostril's worth.
That much. And two hours later,
that corner was back in business.
So then what are we doin' here?
Let's go bust 'em again.
And again and again until they
get the goddamn point, man.
- Yep.
- What?
- Time out, dog.
- Wake up, baby. Wake up.
- What's up with this, man?
- What the fuck you think?
I'm sayin', man, you don'tjust
bust in here like that.
What's goin' on?
- Is there a problem?
- Yeah, there's a problem.
Some shit can't wait.
Yo, I can see that, man.
It must be pretty important, right?
Stop a brother from, you know,
gettin' his eat on.
I hear you're real good
with your tongue.
- Real good.
- You know, I do what I gotta do
to please the ladies, right?
- "Please the ladies."
- I heard you been pleasing
cops with that tongue too, bra.
Yo, what? man..Hell no, God.
In ever talked to the cops, man.
Come on, man.
I'm just sayin', everybody knows...
- what goes around here is
strictly God's business, right?
- Right.
I'm just a hard work in' brother
tryin' to survive. You know how it is.
Don't play me,
mother fucker.
I mean, a couple of cops
came down to Burger Castle
tryin' to scare a brother.
That's all, man. Yo, God,
I ain't tell 'em shit. They was
tryin' to get me to rat you out.
- 'Cause you took
the fuckin' cheese, didn't you?
- No, man, I wouldn't do that.
- I got nothin' but love fory' all.
- What are you, a faggot?
- I'm God. God, mother fucker!
- I didn't say nothin'.
What do you mean, you wouldn't do that,
you tall skinny bastard?
Tique, hold her stinky ass down.
Easy, now.
Close the mother fuckin' door.
What's up, girlfriend? Chillin'?
Everything's fine.
I ain't chicken, but
I can't deal with that cat.
If I was you, I'd pick the
nigger's tongue up off the floor...
and finish the job myself.
I know I ain't gonna hear
nothin' about this, am I?
- No. No.
- Huh?
I'm gonna holler at you.
Gotcha!
Where you goin' now?
Come on, champ.
One more time!
You ain't get him.
You gotta get T-Rex down.
T-Rex justjumped up on ya.
Marcus, get off
your Uncle Jeff.
You got a good thing goin', bro.
Yeah, well, you know,
you're such an expert, man.
Time for you to start
a little family of your own.
Shit. You musta been
talkin' to Mama.
- No, man, I'm serious.
- What?
You been on full-time
for over a year now, right?
- Yeah.
- I know you got some
green socked away.
- Little bit.
- Mm-hmm. Time to settle
down, man. Make you busy.
All right?
Yeah. Maybe after I get busy
with a couple hundred more women.
Then me and you can talk.
Come on.
Wanna dance with me?
Turn the music down,
college girl.
I been fuckin' with
Manny for months, man.
I'm tired of this shit.
What's up, man? You want to
do business or what, Holmes?
Let me check you out, man.
Won't take long.
- What you talkin' about?
- Then you got your three ki's, yo.
What is this, interrogation?
I can take my money
where it's appreciated.
- You hear what I'm sayin'?
- We have procedures.
- "Procedures."
- Oh, oh, oh, oh. Them
niggers from New Jersey?
Forget that.
You don't want to do that.
- They bad news, man.
- Oh, they bad news?
- That's right. Stay here.
- Check it out. They might
be bad news for you,
maybe, but for me..
- You know what I mean, bro?
- Oh, it's like that. All right.
You know what they
call the head one? God.
- You believe that shit, man?
- Is that right?
- Ese, I don't feel like it.
- Come on!
Can't you see I'm talking?
You wanna dance with me?
Or are you as lame as my
two tired-ass brothers?
Whoa!
Piece of advice.
There ain't no such
thing as one dance...
with Esperanza.
Well?
- It's cool.
- It's cool?
You don't have to ask him.
Come on.
Whoo! Go, college girl. Go.
So, uh, what happens
to the family?
- What do you mean?
- The girl.
- Why are you asking me this?
- Because I would like to know.
- Drop it.
- What if I don't want to drop it?
Then you're messed up,
buddy.
Look, look, look, guys.
Don't get me wrong.
I don't give a fuck what
happens to her brothers.
- I just want to make
sure that the girl's..
- The girl what?
If she's as clean as she says she is,
she'll be fine.
Not that it's any of your business.
You guys don't get it. Her
brothers are payin' for college..
Junkies are payin' for it, man..
some with their lives.
If I were her little mamacita,
I'd look into some student loans.
Either that, or she can work
her little ass out on the street.
- Fuck you!
- Hey, fuck you!
Come on, come on, come on.
Let's go.
Shit, Captain, help this boy
find himself a cover.
This battery's fucked.
Hold this.
Makes sure this
shit works, man.
What? I'm cool.
- I hope so.
- Cool.
He's right, you know. You
gotta find yourself a deeper l.D.
You gotta find yourself
some street character, you know?
Create one to hide behind
so your feelings don't
mess you up so much.
So what are you saying?
Act more?
No. Care less.
Ahh!
Whoo! Yeah!
Yeah, look at me,
look at me.
See? See, Mommy?
See? See?
Any one got a vacuum cleaner
like that for a nose ain't
no cabron, Mommy. Right?
I hope you're right. Cause you're
the one who bring him here.
Mommy, come on.
He's cool. I promise.
- You want one, Mommy?
- No.
I want to count
the money.
Man!
Yo, Miguel, man.
Moms..
Moms ain't no joke, man. Damn.
She don't trust nobody, man.
- Mommy?
- Que?
Sit and have a drink with us.
Long as he's been
felt good for wire.
Breakin' my chops.
What's up, man?
Shit.
- What's wrong with the reception?
- Got a wire loose.
- You mean you messed up.
- Hey, he's got it on
his balls, for Christ sake.
They got a mind of their own.
I mean, he snorted some coke,
he's sweating and it shorted.
Hey, quiet.
I'm sayin', come on with
all of that, man. Miguel.
- What's up, man?
- Dude, just two seconds, man.
It ain't nothin'.
- Yo, what's the problem, dude?
- It's not about that, man.
You want this money or what?
Ain't nobody feelin' me up for no wire.
Yo, yo, yo. You ain't gonna
be doin' business period,
you take that tone in my house.
I ain't feelin' that right there.
You got this money right here.
Yo, you better step the fuck off.
Don't disrespect me in my house.
- Goddamn it. She grabbed his balls.
- Move in. Move in. All units.
Move in now. Officer
in distress. Move it!
Shoot the mother fucker!
Don't fucking move!
What's going on here?
- Stay back. You can't go..
- Mommy! Mommy!
Mommy!
Thanks for nothin'.
I put my life on the line
for you, Preston.
The least I expect is somebody
to have my back out there, man.
- All right. I'm sorry.
- What happened, man?
I don't fuckin' know.
Some freak thing with the wire.
Last think I heard in there,
you were fine, and then the
mother grabbed your nuts.
"Grabbed"? She practically
ripped 'em off.
I know, man.
Are you all right?
- Believe that?
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- If you want some relief,
Jeff, you just tell me.
No, no, no, no, no. I just
got a little pumped, that's all.
- All right. You sure?
- Yeah. I'm cool.
- Okay. Okay.
- I'm in the zone, baby.
So you're ready
for the big score?
- I got in this line of work
for the big score, man.
- Good.
I'm going to make you
a very happy man.
You're going after God.
J. Reid.
You got me out in the
cold, man. What's up?
- BreezyT.
- Traffic bad in Akron?
- No, it's all right. Yeah.
- You all right?
- You ready to make this happen?
- Let's do this.
Dwayne Gittens
is his real name.
Comes all the way
from New Jersey.
We haven't been able to get
any body near him,
but we figure he's hooked in to
about 80% of the crack in this city.
- Hold the bag, Tique.
- I got you.
He's using the projects as his base.
Word is, though, he's
spreading out state wide.
- Tique! Hold the fuckin' bag!
- I'm holdin' it.
If you let this bag move one more
time, I'm gonna break yourjaw.
- Hold the bag.
- I hear you. I hear you.
Fuckin' stupid!
Yo, God. Man, folks is bitchin'.
They mad 'cause they ain't gettin'
no tickets for the turkey thing.
I told 'em, ain't no more.
We got enough fuckin' freeloaders, man.
Exactly who you call
a freeloader, Che?
These mother fuckers.
They actin' like we're the
welfare office and shit,
ike we supposed to feed
the whole world.
Come here.
Any parent,
grandparent,
aunt, uncle
or wandering fucking dog...
that wants to eat
Thanksgiving dinner with God
gets a plate, you understand?
- Uh, sure.
- And if I hear about
anybody gettin' left out,
you won't be decorating
your tree this Christmas, all right?
Stupid ass. So fuckin'
cheap. He acts like he's
spendin' his own money.
God, this here's J. Reid.
J. Reid, this is God.
This brother's turnin' out to be...
a top customer
and a down brother.
Oh, yeah? J. Reid, huh?
A down brother?
- A lot of niggas say they down.
- Yeah..
- Thing about it is,
he's the real deal. Yeah.
- Yeah?
Where you from,
real deal?
From Akron.
From Akron?
I didn't know they was gettin'
no money in Akron.
Well, if you don't say nothin',
we keep it our little secret,
I keep makin' money, you know?
Yeah.
Know anything
about boxing?
- A little somethin'.
- Yeah?
- Get the mitts from this fag.
- Let me get with that.
Get the fuckin' mitts.
Don't ever interrupt me, man.
- What the fuck
did you do to your hair?
- Come on, man.
Well, I say, uh,
you know a little bit more
about boxing than you let on,
J. Reid from Akron.
Make that happen for me.
- He was throwin'.
He was throwin', man.
- I'm nice. I'm nice.
You were excellent
not to put down them mitts, man.
Yeah, maybe me and him
can go a couple of rounds, you know?
Right now, I'm trying
to make this deal.
We'll see about a deal,
but God ain't gonna deal direct
until he check you out fully.
Life's a breeze.
You know what I'm sayin'?
- Life's a breeze?
- Life's a breeze.
Looking good.
What's going on?
- Same old same old.
- Mm-hmm.
But you know, I wanted to talk
to you, you know, for real.
- Right.
- Um..
You know, so housing is
really gettin' in my shit,
you know what I'm sayin'?
And-And I can't play the
damn welfare no more,
you know what I'm sayin'?
You ain't got to tell me
that shit. I was raised on it.
You know what I mean?
And-And-And, you know,
I don't know what else to do,
you know what I'm sayin'?
So I want to talk to you
and see, you know..
You trust me?
Well, they be tellin' me
not to fuck with you, 'cause, you know,
you're tough.
But all I see you doin'
is this, you know, help in'
all these people here...
who need a little somethin',
you know?
Look, this is how God's
gonna help you get yours, all right?
We gonna set up shop in your
apartment, you know, make it
a little part-time office.
It's gonna be strictly business.
I'm gonna take care of your rent.
I'm gonna take care of everything.
And if you get a little itch,
I'll scratch it for you,
all right?
- I don't do that no more.
I told you that.
- I'm proud of you.
I'm proud of you, all right?
Real proud of you.
So look. I'm gonna send
Breeze and Che around Monday,
straighten everything out.
We're gonna put a
little paper in your pocket.
We're gonna take care of you.
All right? You're gonna
be straight. All right?
Meantime, you go over there, get
you some of that sweet potato pie.
- It's bangin'.
Miss Johnson made it.
- All right.
- All right?
- I appreciate this, God.
God is with you.
All right.
Hey, little man. Enjoy yourself.
Eat somethin', all right?
Whoo! Nisey be
hawking you heavy, man.
- Nisey who?
- Nisey, right there.
The girl who just smiled
at you with her pussy.
- You better go get some of that. Huh?
- Yeah, maybe.
"Maybe"? Fuck the maybe.
You better get some of
that pie while it's hot.
- What's up, God?
- What's up, dude?
J. here didn't have no
place to go for, uh,
this day of Thanksgiving, so
I brought him with, you know?
Want him to see what sort of
organization he's dealing with.
What you see?
Look to me like
y'all havin' a ball, man.
Ballin', baby. We doin' our
thing, you know what I mean?
- Feed the people.
- I'm with that. I'm with that.
I got this little thing
of my own back home, you know?
- That's good. Yo, Pam! Frisco!
- What's up?
Pam, come here, man.
Yo, Pam!
- I'm comin', baby. I'm comin'.
- Come here.
I'm comin'.
- How you doin'?
- What's up?
- How my baby doin'?
- Kickin' like a bitch.
Don't be callin' my baby
no bitch. That's gonna be
God's little princess.
- Give me a fuckin' break, Dwayne.
- Run your mouth, huh?
- Yeah, I'm all right.
- That's my seed, man.
You know what I mean?
That don't mean nothin'
without what I got.
- Yo, what's your name, nigger?
- J. Reid, man.
Smart-mouth here's
Pam, my wife.
This is Frisco.
- That's my man. We grew up
together in Newark.
- Peace.
Word up. He's gonna be
my baby's godfather.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Our baby's godfather.
- Our baby's godfather.
- Don't start no trouble, man.
- Shut up, nigger.
Yo, you better watch out
for this nigger here.
He stronger than he look.
Oh, yeah? So you like
shootin' joints, kid?
A little somethin', you know?
- Yo, yo. You holdin'?
- I'm holdin', baby.
I'm holdin' it all.
- All right.
I'm feelin' that.
- What you need?
Hey, man. Whatever, man.
You know?
Rock, AK, shoddy-body,
whatever.
Yo, lines, trees,
long-nose, what?
- Got a necklace
that shines and shit.
- Uh-huh.
Hold it, now.
Get up on it! Hurry up, man!
- Do it!
- Get that nigger!
You got him, man!
Damn.
Give me the uwap!
What's wrong with you?
- Come on!
- What's wrong with y' all? I had him.
I'm a little disgusted with you.
I thought you could shoot.
Why you not give me the uwap?
I had the cat right there.
- Come on!
- Turn this shit around!
All that shootin',
and you ain't hit nothin'.
- What's up, G?
- What's up, baby?
Chillin'.
Did your man J. Reid
murder these mother fuckers or what?
- He's crazy.
- That nigger..
He didn't murder nothin'.
- What do you mean?
- He can't shoot.
He emptied out the whole
joint and asked for the Uzi.
I'm, like, with
that whack-ass aim..
So how you know
he ain't frontin'?
Listen, the way he was shootin' up
and all that, he's on point.
- I would vouch for that, for real.
- You'd vouch for that?
- Yeah.
So this is what you gon' do..
you put on with them new
kids. What's their names?
- Ozzie and Gash.
Whatever the fuck his name is,
you put him with them, let him do that.
- If that pans out, let 'em pray to God.
- Send it through.
So, you comin' back
tonight, baby?
What, you don't
get enough or somethin'?
Well, when you get it,
and it's good,
you wanna keep gettin' it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
So, what's up?
You got a woman in Akron?
For your information, no, l
don't have a woman. All right?
In Akron
or anywhere else.
That's what I want to hear.
- Why I gotta go through
this with you every time?
- What about mean you?
- I told you I gotta do somethin'!
- Huh?
- It's always Gash!
- Every day it's the same
thing with you, man!
- Hey, Nisey.
- What's up, girl?
Come here, man! What the
fuck is wrong with you?
- You don't fuckin' listen, man!
- Shit.
- Damn.
- What the fuck are you doin'?
You stupid mother fucker!
Come on, get up, man.
I ain't even kicked you
that fuckin' hard.
- Aw, look at you.
- No, man.
Fall on the ground.
You all right, man?
What you askin' for?
You just kicked her in her butt.
Bastard.
- Later.
- Get on out of here.
What's up with you, dog?
- You can't be smackin'
on your girl like that.
- I ain't slap her.
I'm sayin' let's go do this.
You got me out here waitin'.
- Yo.
- You was waitin' for
two minutes, man.
Don't worry about it.
God wants us to hook you up,
we goin' hook you up.
Y'all niggers better be
comin' on with some uncut...
to bring me all the way
out to Newport, man.
We'll set you up real nice.
You know we got
the good stuff.
I thought y'all worked
out of Horton Park.
I thought you was
from fuckin' Akron.
-Akron.
- What the hell you know
about where God do business?
Just sit tight, dog.
We be there in, like,
less than five minutes.
Hey, yo, what the fucky' all
used to do out in Akron anyway?
Y'all used to
deal corn and shit?
- Where the hell we goin', man?
- Downstairs, nigger.
Gonna take care
of this bitch.
I like them chains, dog.
Gonna get me some chains
just like that.
What's up?
They payin' y'all too?
No. They say we gotta
prove ourselves first.
That's just what we gonna do..
prove ourselves.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
We want all the money, man,
and them chains you got on.
This how God
do business?
No, this how Ozzie and Gash do
business. Where the money at, man?
Fuck that, Oz!
Do this thing!
Oz, come on, man!
Jesus Christ.
- Hello?
- Some crazy shit
just happened, man.
These mother fuckers
tried to kill me.
- Jeff?
- Wake the fuck up, Preston!
- These two cats
tried to take me out, man!
- Are you all right?
They just tried to fuckin'
kill me. Oh, shit.
- Did anybody see you? Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Did anybody see you?
- No.
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
Okay. I'm pullin' you out.
- What?
- I'm pullin' you out.
- What are you talkin' about?
I can't do that.
- I'm doin' it.
I'm gonna call Wilson.
Meet me at the spot in 45 minutes.
- Are you crazy, man?
We're gonna blow the whole thing.
- This is not a suggestion, Jeff.
This is an order. You
do what I tell you to do.
Hello? Hello?
Yeah, yeah.
Who the fuck is it?
It's J. Reid, man.
I need to talk to you.
Chill out. You
gon' wake my daughter.
- I wanna talk to you.
- Hey, man, what's up? What's up?
- "What's up"? I'm still alive.
That's what's up, nigga.
- What the fuck..
- Put the gun down, baby.
- Couple of your boys
just tried to kill me.
- What?
- You tryin' to play me?
I ain't tryin' to play you.
All right?
Hey, hey, listen.
Ain't the way we do business.
You know that, J.
- You oughta know who you
got workin' for you, dog.
- I know who l got workin' for me.
Maybe they was gonna
try to impress God with
some bullshit. Right?
They new to the fam, J.
That's it. My word.
My word. You tell me where they at,
we'll do 'em right now.
Last time I saw Ozzie,
he was bleedin' like a little bitch.
Gash scream
when I shot his dick off.
That's what they get
for fuckin' with an O.G.
ike you, right, nigger?
Let me make a call.
I'll get you the blow
tonight if you need it.
- No. No.
I'm not tryin' to..
- We'll make it square.
- I'm gon' take my money
where it's appreciated.
- We appreciate it.
- We'll make this deal square.
- You tryin' to play me, man.
Come on, baby. We can
still make this square.
Why it gotta be that?
Why it gotta be
like this sh..
Shit.
Damn, Pres.
In the dark, layin' in the cut..
You gon' get yourself shot.
I expect my officers
to obey a direct order.
What I don't expect is having
to go to their apartments...
to fucking say so.
Let me tell you somethin'
about your direct order..
it could've got me killed out there!
I'm the one in there!
I'm the one doin' it!
It's gonna be my call!
It's gonna be my call whether
you stay on this case or not.
I got seven other officers, seven
other, working undercover.. good ones..
and none of them
fuck with me but you.
Yeah, none of 'em can do
what I can do either, Pres,
and don't you forget that.
Why are you in such a hurry
to end up in a box?
That's exactly where I would be
if I didn't show 'em J. Reid
could handle himself!.
You ain't out there, man.
You don't understand what's goin' on.
Well, maybe
you'll understand this:
You're out of the God business.
You're off the case.
Hand me your gun and badge.
- What?
- I said give me your gun and badge.
You're off the case.
Are you serious?
Let's go.
I'll find you a
safe place to stay.
- God and his boys'll think
you went back to Akron.
- Whatever.
Sorry, kid.
You disobeyed a director oder.
This is the way it works.
Somebody used the place
as a drug lab...
until the D.E.A.
busted them a year ago.
They haven't gotten around
to auctioning it off yet,
so stay as long as you need.
Listen, the only hobby you
ever mentioned is photography,
so I made arrangements
at a college nearby...
if you want to
take some courses.
Every cop who's been
undercover as long as you
have needs a break, Jeff.
Just think of it
as rural R&R.
Well, somebody was
supposed to come out here
and clean this place up,
but obviously they didn't.
I can at least guarantee you
you will not run into anybody
who knows J. Reid around here. So..
All right.
Oh, yeah. Well..
A little dusting,
you know, you'll..
You'll be all right.
Preston, it's like
a tomb in here, man.
I-I'm a city boy.
I can't do this. Come on.
What do you want me
to tell you?
You can stay here
and get your shit together,
or you can quit the force
and lead an ordinary life.
Those are your choices,
so..
Thanks.
Look, I never been too good
at ordinary.
I know.
Something bothering you,
Mr. Cole?
Yeah, actually, I'd like to move
that light hitting her face.
Could you hurry up?
I have to pee.
- Hey, how you doin'?
- Hi.
I'm, uh..
I'm Jeff.
Myra.
Um, I was just wonderin'
if, uh..
- I don't drink coffee.
- Excuse me?
I don't drink coffee,
and I don't date the men
at my nude class.
Okay.
It's cool, you know.
You're a dancer, huh?
- What?
- You dance, right?
How did you know that?
'Cause you have posture
like a dancer, you know.
Back upright,
shoulders down.
Yes, actually, I, um..
I am a dancer.
But we're on hiatus right now,
so I teach ballet part-time
and I also model.
That's cool.
Well, see, actually,
I was just wonderin',
'cause I'm finishing up my
portfolio and I need a model.
So I was wonderin' if maybe
I could hire you to pose.
Strictly professional.
"Strictly professional."
- You can keep your clothes on.
- Oh, thanks.
Oh, you're so cute!
Oh!
You didn't tell me you had a puppy.
My God, he's adorable.
Miles is not quite a
puppy. He's a wolf.
You're kidding me, right?
Nuh-uh.
So, what made you
name him Miles?
After the man himself.
Miles Davis.
What you know about Miles?
I like Miles.
Actually, I love Miles.
Move over here
for a second.
Why don't you just
let me do my thing?
Excuse me, mama.
Go ahead, do your thing.
Just do it. Okay?
So?
So what?
So, what do you do?
- I'm an actor.
- Yeah, right.
Why?
What do you think I do?
I think you're puttin 'me on,
is what I think.
Okay, okay.
I'm a cop.
Really?
Really.
Really nice.
Very nice.
I mean the girl.
I-I..
I think she's beautiful.
So, seems like you two are
gettin' along pretty well.
Are you askin' me if
we're sleeping together?
No, no. I was just
making an observation.
Easy.
This one's special, Pres.
Watch yourself.
I'm glad you're doing
so well ,Jeff.
Personally, I think I'm doin'
well enough to go back in.
- We'll see.
- What do you mean, "we'll see"?
I mean,
we'll see.
I'm just thinking, what would my
mom think if I brought you home?
What would she think?
What do you think?
I think she would think
you're pretty cute.
What about my moms?
I don't think my moms' take
too kindly to me datin' a dancer...
and a part-time
nude model.
Nah, I dig it.
I dig it.
- I think my moms would love you.
- You do?
What a sexy!
Right there. Right there.
- Oh!
- Beat me up.
Sorry.
Did I get your eye?
Ooh, honey, I'm hungry.
Could you go get me a hot dog?
Please?
Please, please, please?
- I got your hot dog right here.
- Oooh!
Hold this. I'll be back.
See that?
Yeah!
- You're Dan Connelly.
- Daddy, Daddy, Daddy.
- Guilty.
- How you doin'?
I'm...Jeff Cole, Officer.
I was workin' with
Preston D'Ambrosio in Cincinnati.
We first met when you were assigned
to the Dwayne Gittens case.
- Oh, right. I remember.
- Hey, Daddy, I wanna
see the seagulls.
- Okay, sweetie.
- You wanna see them too?
- Go with Mommy.
- Bye-bye.
We'll be up on the deck, Dan.
I'll be right there, honey.
Hold Mommy's hand.
Uh, yeah, you were involved
in the Batista case, right?
- Great memory.
- You did some good work.
Thank you.
Something happened on the Gittens case,
they had to pull you, right?
I was just wonderin' if you
got anybody undercover now..
State, D.E.A., anybody.
We keep tryin' to get in deep
enough to get his main
supplier, but no one lasts.
Either they get made, or it seems
too risky and they want out.
Mmm.
So what's your plan?
We pull Gittens off the streets
on tax evasion charges,
hope we can make it stick.
Look, he'll plea-bargain after
two, three years tops, easy.
Well, at the moment
I don't have an alternative.
Put me back in.
I promise you, I'll get you
somethin' to crucify the bastard.
- How can you be sure?
- Nobody can get in as deep as me.
If you want God and his
angels down for good,
put me in.
What's happenin', Pres?
We meetin' early this week or what?
You know goddamn well
what's happenin'.
I got called into
State Attorney Connelly's
office this morning.
Did you know that?
- So, did you tell him I'm out of
my fuckin' mind or somethin'?
- Yeah, somethin' like that.
- I talked to the chief
about getting you fired.
- So why am I not fired?
Because Rick Scott of the
D.E.A. and Connelly got to
the chief before I did.
Somehow they're all convinced
that you can single-handedly
bring down Dwayne Gittens.
- I can.
- No, you can't. Not
by yourself, you can't.
Look, the longer it
takes me to get back in,
the harder it's gonna be.
You know that.
Just trust me on this, man.
What's up?
They want you to go
back in, don't they?
So were you gonna
tell me, or.. or what?
Was I just supposed
to figure it out?
Look, I've been straight
with you from the beginning,
all right, Myra?
And that's it? That's it?
Just like that? That's it?
What are you talkin' about?
I'm gonna be back.
It's not even that big of a
deal, man. It's just my thing.
Everybody has their thing.
Like, you wanted to be a dancer
since you were little girl, right?
Yeah, but not every
little boy growing up
in the projects...
wants to be an
undercover cop, okay?
Baby, you don't understand.
When I was growin' up in the projects,
there was this huge gray wall
that surrounded the whole thing.
I never figured out if the city
put it up to keep the residents in...
or to keep the scum out.
But, you know, they decided
that the wall needed decoratin',
so they got all the
graffiti artists together,
and they covered the wall.
They covered it with
the names and the ages,
sometimes the faces,
of every kid that got killed
in the neighborhood.
I had to pass that
wall, you know,
Leavin' home
or comin' in.
Every day.
It was like one day
I was comin' home,
passed the wall,
and itjust, like, hit me.
I just realized that
without even trying,
I memorized all the names
on the wall.
The youngest kid,
his name was Daryl.
Daryl Rolley.
He was only three years old.
That's when I decided that
I wanted to do somethin'.
I-I wanted to
make things change.
Hey, come on, man.
We gotta hustle, all right?
I told God you were in Akron.
He thought it was real smart...
for you to disappear
till things chilled out.
Hey, yo. What's up?
- What up, Breezy?
- Word. What up?
Do you, Sidney and Martha,
swear before God...
that you will protect
Anwar Sidney Gittens...
from any misfortune that
may befall his parents?
- Yes, indeed.
- Yes.
Will the members of the immediate
family please come forward?
That's a beautiful boy,
ain't it?
He's feeling a little better?
All right.
How you doin'?
Thanks for comin'.
- Peace.
- You okay, Nisey?
Take him to the car.
Okay.
Come on, you.
- What's up, J.? What's goin' on?
- What's up, baby?
- How you been, man? You all right?
- What's up?
- Got a little something for you.
- All right, cool.
Did you see the ceremony?
- Oh, no doubt, man.
Yo, congratulations, man.
- Thanks, man.
He may sound soft, man, but
he's gonna be somethin' one day.
- Know what I mean?
- Yeah, definitely.
- Yo, Frisco?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna hold you
to them words, brother.
That's my word
from the heart.
I'll tell you somethin'.
I'm with you all the way, man.
I love the baby boy.
Ain't nothin' gonna happen
to that baby that don't
happen to me first.
- I love you.
- Love you too, man.
Love you more.
What's going on, baby?
Where you been at, dog?
Well, got a little..
got a little hectic back home.
- You know?
- Word.
Yo, God, J. wants
to do a little business.
- Maybe later, huh?
- What ever you need,
you know I got it.
- No doubt, you got it.
Everything, everything, baby.
- Yeah.
- Lookin' good, man.
- Feelin' good, man.
It's been a good year, baby.
That's good, man.
That's good.
- Yo, um..
- What's up, man?
That thing that happened
over at the building?
No, no, no, no. The kid that went
to the hospital? Yeah.
He met with a little accident.
You dig what I'm sayin'?
Finito, all right?
He wasn't no good
without his dick no way.
- My gift to you, huh? My man.
- All right.
It's good to see you, kid. You
look good. As clean as a chitlin.
- Look at you. All right?
- I'll see you at the joint.
- All right, baby.
- I'll let you know, man.
- All right. Definitely
want to see you later.
- Stay out of trouble, baby.
- Good to see you.
- Yeah, yeah.
- What's up?
Yo, get my mans in, man.
- All right, my brother.
- Get 'em up here.
How are you, dog?
- All right.
- God in there?
Yeah, yeah.
- What's up?
- What's up, baby? You smell good.
- Have you seen God? What's up, bro?
- I haven't seen him all night.
- Hi, J.
- What's up? How you doin',
baby? Lookin' good.
- What's up, dog?
- How you doin'?
What's up, dude? Oh, come on, dog.
I'm gonna get you that.
Yo, J.
- Big Mel.
- What's up, dog?
- How are you, baby?
- Chillin'. I'm chillin'.
You know what I'm say in'?
I'm just checkin' out the scenery.
- What's up?
- Lookin' fresh, you know.
Look at these jewels.
You know how I do.
Yeah, but check this shit
out I got in my pockets.
- All new gold.
You know what I'm sayin'?
- Come on, man.
- I got it.. Hold on. Check it out.
- You seen God?
- Later for all that, man.
What? What, man?
- Come on, dog.
It's cool. You know what I'm
sayin'? Everything's cool.
I got the smoke. You
know what I'm sayin'? We
can go chief one real quick.
- Whatever. Let's go.
- Come on, dog.
Need a nickel bump,
nickel bump, yeah, yeah.
- Yo, Che, hold up. Che, Che.
- What's up?
- Is that J. over there?
- Yeah, that's J.
He's goin' out back
with grimy-ass Melvin.
- What would Melvin want with J.? Huh?
- I don't know.
- He's up to somethin'.
- Yeah, he's definitely
up to somethin'.
Wait, wait, wait.
Who did you say the other guy was?
- The other guy?
- Excuse us, lady.
We got to have a drink.
Wait.
- What's up, man?
You gonna smoke it all up?
- No, man.
- This is the good shit, baby.
That's the good shit.
- What's up with it?
"It's good shit."
Shit done went out, dog.
- Light it up. You got it?
- Can't get no wind.
Oh, shit!
Yeah. Remember that new gold
I was talkin' about in my pocket?
It's your shit, bitch.
Yo! What the..
Yo, bring him up!
Bring him up! Come on!
You ain't done!
You ain't.. That's right!
You don't fuck
with this family, bitch!
- You all right, J.?
- Yeah.
- Your boys always got your back.
- Yeah, baby.
Yeah. Always, baby.
- Fuck 'im.
- Yeah, Melvin.
- Get your punk ass up, boy.
- Yeah, Melvin! Come on!
- You sure you don't
want to shoot this man?
- Take that shit!
Yo. Yo.
- J.
- What's up, man?
God wants to see you, man.
All right, I'll come by
tomorrow or somethin'.
- No, he wants
to see you today.
- I can't do it today.
- I got something to do.
- He will be waiting for you
in the club at 4:00, all right?
Come on, man.
So this freak gonna tell me
she know this dude.
So you know, I'm like,
"Where'd you meet him from?"
So she gonna be on some old,
"Yeah, he busted
a friend of my family."
- You know what I mean?
So I'm like, "Busted?"
- What?
She said, "Yeah, that mother fucker
a cop. Fooled everybody."
Talkin' about you without a doubt.
The pig that brought him down, man.
- No, we were..
- You a cop, J. ?
- What you think?
- I think you know
the answer to that, clown.
Well, girl, she gotta
be tellin' the truth.
Why is she just gonna lie?
- What are you sayin', she's
gotta be tellin' the truth?
- Just like I said, brother.
- You believin' everything these
tramps is out here talkin'?
- No, no.
Huh? So then
what you talkin' about?
- I put my man on it.
- You know all these broads
went in with the weight.
- Yo, Tique.
Tique, Tique, Tique.
- What?
How long you know
this bitch?
- For a few weeks.
- A few weeks.
- Matter of fact,
bring the bitch down here.
- I ain't bringin' her nowhere.
- Fuck that.
Bring that bitch down here.
- Get that shit out of here.
See me smack her around
the fuckin' room, then you
ask her if I'm a fuckin' cop.
- What's that shit mean to me?
- What you mean, what it mean to you?
- You vouchin' for the bitch!
- I ain't vouchin' for shit!
- We here right now!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. I tell you what.
Don't you worry about it, J.
- What you talkin',
don't worry about it, man?
- Yo, don't worry.
She messin' up my money, dog.
She messin' up
my business with you, dog.
- She ain't messin' up nothin'.
- So what the fuck
is you talkin' about?
Calm down, cowboy.
Don't be screamin' in my
mother fuckin' office, dog.
- Relax.
- Yeah.
Come on down to the basement.
I wanna show you somethin'.
Yo, yo, yo. Obviously, you
got some business to handle.
I ain't got no mother fuck..
Just keep it movin'.
You punk-ass,
bitch-ass nigga.
Thought you were badder, badder,
badder and badder, fool.
You ain't nothin' but
a lame-ass dude, huh?
- You know, I know.
- Che, shut the fuck up.
Oh, Frisco!
- Mmm, mmm, mmm.
- Say, yo, what's up
with all this, dog?
I guess you see my man here
bleedin', all fucked up,
you say, "Damn, God,
what a foul nigger," right?
- I'm just sayin'..
- But you see, this here's
some fucked up shit.
Me and this nigga went to
junior high together, played
in the mother fuckin' sandbox.
And out of all the bitches
in the world, you wanna try to
step to my baby's moms?
- Yo, I was drunk, man.
- Man, shut the fuck up
that you was drunk!
Now I'm drunk
with revenge, mother fucker!
- All I did was tell her
she was beautiful, man.
- Shut up, man!
- Give me the pool stick.
- Come on, man.
We ain't gotta rock like this.
Ain't gotta rock like this?
We gonna rock like what?
Rock like what?
Give me another pool stick.
What's up, J. Reid?
- This is God's world.
- God, man.. Come on, man.
- Let me go, man.
Why are you wildin' out?
- What? Why I'm wildin' out?
- You're supposed to be my man.
- I am your man.
Yo, God, come on, man.
Please, man. Yo.
- And I'm gonna prove
it, mother fucker.
- I'm sorry, man.
Love it!
Love it! Think about her!
Think about her!
- What do you mean, tortured?
- I mean, he beat
the kid half dead.
- Why didn't you call
for immediate backup?
- It was a judgment call.
Why blow the whole operation?
Look, he didn't kill the kid.
How do you know he didn't?
I don't need your shit, Wilson.
- What is this, a fuckin' inquisition?
- No.
We just have to make sure
you didn't take any part in this.
Excuse me.
I know the procedure, okay?
Torturing a brother
is not my thing, all right?
- All right.
- A brother?
What the.. What the fuck
is your problem?
I don't have a problem.
He may be your brother,
but he ain't no brother of mine.
You know what, Pres?
You should've sat this bitch
down a long time ago.
- That's enough.
- Look, Cole.
You know, you are
becoming just like the shit
we trying to throw down.
Get out of my face.
Go push some papers or somethin'.
You can't even get wires straight.
- Okay.
- What was that?
What was that?
- I'd say that was
totally unprofessional, Cole.
- Oh, you'd say?
And who the fuck are you?
The D.E.A.?
You can't even get a guy to go
undercover long enough without
asking for an extended vacation.
At least I know
who the enemy is.
Jeff?
Wait there. Wait. Leave
him alone. Leave him alone.
He's totally out of control.
That's why Gittens trusts
him. He believes him.
Connelly was right.
Nobody will ever
get in this far again.
That's all you care about,
isn't it?
Mmm. Here it comes.
Here it comes.
- Hey, how you doin'?
- Yeah, yeah.
Can I get
another cup of coffee?
- Let me ask you boys somethin'.
- What's up?
God treatin' you all right
with the money?
He's payin'.
Banana money.
Only real cash he layin'
out going to that posse
he come up from Jersey with.
Word. He ain't
gonna start payin' us
Cincinnati dudes, right,
till we prove ourselves.
But he never say
when that is.
Me and Che been bustin' our ass
for two fuckin' years now.
Why don't you ask
him for a raise?
- Give up.
- What?
And wind up butt-ass
naked on his pool table?
I ain't feelin' that.
Nah, ain't worth
the risk, man.
God got us where he wants
and he ain't givin' us no way out.
I tell you what.
It's on love, right?
- It's on the love.
- Just a little somethin', you know?
- Whoo!
- Show more love.
Keep your mouth wet.
What we gotta
do for this?
- What you gotta do for it?
- Yeah.
Why don't you get
that waitress' number for me.
- Her? That's it?
- Yeah. That's it.
For this? Yo, let me go
politic that right now.
J. Reid. You definitely know how
to treat a brother, huh?
Shit. Actin' like this,
you can be H.N.I.C. around here
if you's down for it.
God, he's smart.
He's just gonna keep findin'
a way to slip through the net.
Till somebody takes him out.
- It's simple and plain.
- It's not yourjob.
Mother fucker's slippin', man.
Treats his boys like shit.
Makes them feel scared
and under appreciated.
I tell you what, though.
One of them young cats,
them little mother fuckers, man,
they'd smoke him in a second.
Hand the whole shit
over to me.
When was the last time
you talked to Myra?
Pres, that's none of
your fuckin' business.
Myra's a good girl,
you know?
She really is.
She's all worried about me
gettin' fucked up and..
Besides, man, I-I-I really don't think
she wants to see me anymore.
Well, I think it might not be a
bad idea to give her a call anyway.
Hear her voice.
Let her know how you are.
I, um..
I..
I can't do this.
I don't know what you mean.
What are you talkin' about?
I can't live like this
anymore.
Live like what?
Like..
Thank you.
Like wondering if I'm gonna
open the newspaper...
and see, "Undercover Cop
Killed In The Line Of Duty."
- So why did you agree
to meet me here?
- Jeff, you have your life.
You're happy. It's fun.
Yourjob is exciting for you.
I'm happy for you.
I just know that I cannot
be a part of it anymore.
- See all these niggers out here?
- Mm-hmm.
Strugglin' to survive, man.
When you're strugglin' to survive,
you need somebody to follow.
So I figured,
why not give 'em God?
Like these freaks who let us
use their apartments for free.
It's not only that we payin'
their rent or give them a free
supply, whatever they're usin'.
That ain'tjust it.
Mother fuckers wanna feel like
they're a part of somethin'.
Man, black people in this country,
they wanna feel like they
are a part of somethin'.
- No doubt.
- Stick around, J.
I'm gonna school ya.
I ain't had nobody tight
since Frisco.
- You gotta do what you gotta do.
- Mother fuckin' right. I always do.
Ain't that right, little man?
Yeah, that's my little man.
Let me ask you somethin',
dog. How much?
- How much what?
- How much the empire worth?
Eleven million.
I can feel that.
I can feel that like a
mother fucker, man.
- Been lookin' for these mother fuckers.
- Who that?
Bitch Nisey and this nigger.
No!
Leave him alone!
You and your man gonna rob
me, bitch? Gonna rob me?
Huh? You gonna rob me,
you stinkin' mother fucker?
You guys got it wrong, man!
You got it wrong!
No!
- Get up! Get up!
- What the hell is wrong, man?
Who the fuck is God? Point
at him! Point at him, bitch!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Get the fuck up! Get up!
Put the mother fucker's arm
in the doorjam! Put him over here!
Put your arm in there, cowboy!
Take it! Take it!
Take it!
Mother fucker! How does it feel?
Fuckin' faggot!
What the fuck's wrong with you?
Where you go in', bitch?
Get the fuck up!
Stinky mother fucker! Huh?
Open your mouth!
Open your mouth! Yeah.
Yeah, you like that, huh?
Huh? Yeah, suck on it!
You wanna suck on
the mother fuckin' pipe, right?
Suck on this, bitch! Yeah!
What you think ,J. ?
What you think, baby?
Man, fuck this bitch, man.
She dyin' slow anyway, man.
You know, there's people
out here, dog. Come on.
Who am I, bitch?
Who am I?
- Who am I?
- God!
That stinkin' mother
fuckin' bitch!
Yo, what's up with
little man, man?
Nah, it smells like
he messed up his diaper.
You'll be all right, Boo-Boo.
Know what?
Before we done,
you and me gonna be runnin'
this whole state, man.
I don't know, man.
Look, you got my back,
I got yours.
I ain't never seen you
back down to nothin' or
nobody including me,
which means sooner or
later I'm gonna have to
murder you before you do me.
So you can make up your mind
one way or the other.
You'll be all right, Boo-Boo.
I know. I know.
- I know. You okay?
- What's wrong, little man?
I know. I know.
It's cold.
Anyway, it's set up
for tomorrow night.
Make up your mind
one way or the other,
'cause you ain't makin' a
contact unless you down solid.
- It is. That was good, though.
- It was good.
- I'll see you guys later.
- Bye.
- So, I think we're supposed to
be in at around 4:00 tomorrow.
- Sounds good to me.
Okay, see you. Bye.
What's up, girl?
I guess you just happened
to be driving by, huh?
Nah, nah. I've been out here
for, like, two hours.
Tried you at home.
I figured you were down here
doing your thing.
I was checkin' you out.
You looked pretty good up there.
Jeff, I thought we already..
I thought we talked about
this thing already.
I know, I know, I know.
I couldn't stay away.
That's, you know..
That's why I didn't come
inside or nothin'.
I didn't want to make you
feel uncomfortable.
Um, listen, I've been, um,
modeling since this morning.
I've been rehearsing
all afternoon. I'm tired.
I just want to go home
and get into bed.
Baby, you can't hang out
for a few?
Huh? I just wanna talk to
you. I just wanna..
I just wanna hear your voice.
What's up, baby?
What's up?
So, um, let me
ask you somethin'.
- That's your new boyfriend?
- Who?
The boy over there
who was kissin' on you.
- Jeff, come on.
That's my dance partner.
- Oh, right.
Hmm.
You sleepin' with him?
No! What..
You know what?
Hold on. Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm sorry. Close your door.
Close the door.
- What's wrong?
- Don't talk to me like that, okay?
He was over there kissin'
on you and all that, you know?
- We work together.
He's my friend, okay?
- I'm sorry.
- I'm not..
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Let's start off fresh.
Give me a kiss, baby.
- I don't want a kiss. Jeff, I
don't want to kiss you right..
- Kiss me.
- What you runnin' away for?
What are you scared of, baby?
- Don't, Jeff!. Don't..
Damn!
Excuse me, ma'am,
is there a problem here this evening?
There's no problem
here, man.
- We just had an argument.
- Excuse me, sir. I was
talkin' to the lady.
- Look, I'm a cop. I'm on the job.
- We just had an argument.
I'm just having a little problem
with my lady, that's all.
Sir, why don't you come over to the
car and we'll settle it there, huh?
- There's no need for me
to go to the car.
- Let's go over to the car.
Please, Officer, stop.
He's a cop. He's not lying.
- Come on. Don't be like that.
- What are you, stupid?
- Huh? Didn't I just
fuckin' tell you I'm a cop?
- Okay.
- All right, look. All right.
Nobody's being stupid.
- Don't be stupid.
- Back the fuck up!
- Jeff, no!
You said you were a cop,
right? Then you know the..
- Move it!
- What are you doing?
Son of a bitch!
- You wanna play?
- Let him go! Let him go!
He's a cop!
He's not lying! Please!
It's too late for this.
We have no time for "I told you so's."
We're talking about potentially
the biggest drug bust
in the history of this state.
And I still think Cole
can get us there.
It's not Cole that you're talking about.
That's what you don't understand.
He doesn't know
who the fuck he is.
He doesn't know what he's
gonna do when he's J. Reid.
You saw what happened last night.
He understands
what he did last night.
He's sorry for that.
He's fully conscious.
He doesn't know what the fuck he did
last night, and he's not sorry.
You act like he
spilled a glass of water.
The court accepted a plea
of extreme circumstance
involving an officer on duty.
- Oh, my God.
- We gotta go.
I think it's definitely
worth the risk.
But it's not your risk
to take, is it? It's his.
Look, if you put Jeff back in,
he will never find his way out.
It's just for tonight.
That's all. We need him wired.
We need to have him wired
so that we can find out...
who Gittens' supplier is
and nail them both.
Then it'll be over.
Are you there, Jeff?.
I need you to meet me so you
can tell me what's going down.
Come on, Jeff. Pick up
the phone if you're there.
Jeff?.
Yo, this is where they're
meeting you at, dog?
Yeah.
This crazy mother fucker
might be here already.
He called me between
Chicago and here like an hour ago.
Let's cut that mother fucker
off. Just go direct, man.
Mexicans don't fuck
with niggers.
The federales there, they get
all hectic. They get crazy.
The shit is just off the rockers.
Them taco-eatin' mother fuckers...
do not like no niggers
down in Mexico.
It's easier to do it this
way, you know? Good prices.
It's cool.
- Yo. You all right?
- What's up?
- We're here, right?
- No doubt.
- What's up, Murph?
- What's up, homey?
- How y'all?
- Chillin'. What's goin' on, baby?
I'm all right. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Not too personal.
- How you doin', man?
- I'm good.
- What's goin' on, Thug Life?
- What's up?
Who's the new eggplant, man?
Why don't you knock it off
with the insults. That's my man.
What happened to Frisco?
Frisco, he's old news, man.
Frisco's old news?
What are you? You new news?
Murph, can we speed
up this process, man?
Who is this guy?
Are you a cop?
Yo, Murph, Come on
cut the crap.
Let's do business.
All right, man?
- I just wanna figure out
who I'm dealing with.
- Yo, Murph.
Let's do business.
- Are you a cop?
- What the fuck do you mean
is he a cop, mother fucker?
- Don't insult me.
- All right. Look, I just wanna
know who I'm doin' business with.
You're doin' business
with me, mother fucker!
- You want me to take
my money somewhere else?
- No, we're gonna do this. Alright?
Next time just call me
and let me know you're
gonna bring some new guy.
Yeah.
Let's do what we gotta do, man.
Hey, watch the car, man!
Sorry about that, God.
Hey, you got enough cocaine
here, you can buy
a whole fuckin' fleet.
Just take it easy, man.
All right.
- It's all right?
- Come on, man.
What's with that bullshit?
What's the problem, man?
What, you can count my money,
I can't taste your stuff?.
- 'Cause you're a nigger, Dwayne.
- Hey, fuck you, trailer trash.
You're lrish, but you're no Kennedy,
Murph. Believe that.
- Let's go.
- That's it.
- It's all good. What the fuck?
- Shit!
This is Agent Scott. You're
surrounded by the D.E.A.
- Drop your weapons and come
out with your hands up!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Let's go! Come on!
- Go, go, go!
- Let's go!
- I knew you were a cop.
J, watch out!
Put the mother fuckin'
gun down, Thug!
- Put the mother fuckin'
gun down! Don't be stupid!
- Put it down!
- Fuck you! Fuck you, mother fucker!
- Put the gun down!
Put the gun down.
Put that gun down!
I hear him breathing. Why
isn't he giving us the signal?
Abel One, Baker One. Do you
request backup at this time?
Hold it.
What are you..
What are you doing?
Abel One, Baker One.
Are you ready for entry?
J, put the gun down, man.
J, I got
a 600-dollar-an-hour lawyer.
We'll be out by the morning.
Put the fuckin' gun down, man.
You have ten seconds!
Wait.
Put the gun down.
It's crazy, you know?
It's all a misunderstanding.
How you doin' today, Officer?
Could you take it easy? It's
all just a big misunderstanding.
Officer Cole,
would you do the honors?
Read Mr. Gittens
his rights.
- Get the fuck out of here.
- Go ahead, Jeff.
Read him his rights. I'm
gonna play him the tape you made.
He'd love to hear
his own voice.
- You a cop?
- Come on, Jeff.
You did it.
You brought us home.
- You have the right
to remain silent.
- You a cop, mother fucker?
Anything you say can
and will be held against
you in a court of law.
You have the right to an
attorney. If you can't afford one,
one will be appointed
to you.
- At any time during questioning..
- All I wanted to do was
be there for you, dog.
All I did was be there for you.
That's all I did.
Huh, J. Reid?
You ain't no cop!
You ain't no cop, J. Reid!
You're a sellout!
Now the hard part begins.
I know a doctor who works with cops.
He'll know what you've been through.
This is gonna take
some time, Jeff.
Who we may have betrayed.
Who wants to talk about it?
How about you, Jeff?.
Maybe you can bring some
fresh perspective to the group.
Any cop who was undercover
as long as you were...
is bound to have some
lasting imprint.
You crossed the line.
But that's the reason
Gittens let you in so deep,
and that's the reason your
testimony could put him away.
- Tape make you nervous?
- About what?
I wanna see him
face to face.
Put that bastard
in his place.
I was undercover, and, uh..
He tried to kill me.
The guy called himself God.
So, you know, I'm ridin' around
with him, playin' my part.
You know what?
I just, uh..
I just wanted to see you,
'cause I wanted you to
know that I'm sorry.
I fucked up.
I messed up big time.
I never meant to hurt you.
You gotta believe me.
I love you, Jeff,
butjust because
two people love each other,
it does not mean that they're
supposed to be together.
Who was in charge...
when you started buying
mass quantities of cocaine
from the New York gang?
Dwayne Gittens,
known on the street as God.
- Did Mr. Gittens ever deliver
these goods to you personally?
- On occasion.
Officer Cole, would
you be so kind as to point
Mr. Gittens out to the jury?
Certainly. He's the gentleman
seated to the far right
with the bald head.
Hey, yo, J
Officer Jeff Cole.
- What's up, man? Look at you.
- What's goin' on, Breezy?
What's goin' on?
Thanks for puttin' in
the good word, man.
You're the one that
decided to testify, man.
You did the right thing.
Yeah.
I'll guess I'll see you
in about three and a half.
Be strong, man.
Dwayne Keith Gittens, you've
been found guilty by this jury...
of all the crimes in which
you've been accused.
Therefore, this court
sentences you to a penalty
of two consecutive life terms...
without the possibility of parole.
- But I would like to say this.
- Thank you.
I feel really good
about what happened today.
We did the job
we set out to do.
Dwayne Gittens and 16members of
the toughest drug organization
operating in this state...
have been brought down.
On be half of the D.E.A.,
I would just like to express...
my deep thanks to
State Attorney Connelly...
and all the local
police agencies.
We were fortunate
to have them with us.
This was a joint effort.
We couldn't have done it without them.
Now, this operation
may have taken years.
We needed to be sure
that we could deliver a blow...
from which this gang
could never recover.
And that, ladies and gentlemen,
is just the blow that was dealt
to Dwayne Gittens.
If you look around at the
positive changes that have..
You know, everybody that matters
knows who the real hero is.
I didn't get into this
war to be a hero.
Do you.. Do you really
have to go tomorrow?
Preston says
it's safer that way.
Besides, those rookies
in Chicago have no idea
what they're in for.
You know, I've been thinkin'.
It's not like you could just
pick up and leave or anything,
but, you know,
you should come with me.
I got a little
two-bedroom apartment.
Turn one of 'em into
a dance studio or something.
A friend of mine was telling
me that they got, like, great
dance companies in Chicago.
Oh, don't try to
sell me on Chicago.
Well, you know, I'm just passin'
off information, that's all.
I know.
I can go to Chicago
and run things, huh?
Any other bright
ideas out there?
Somebody help me out.
Come on.
Oh, come on.
You're holdin' that gun.
Time is runnin' out.
Your brain..
Your brain is vaporized,
like ten minutes ago,
and your heart, your heart
is dancing on your tongue.
We're talkin' about
your life out there.
Your life.
Here we go