Oh my God, you are so hot.
Great.
Seriously?
Am I beautiful?
Uh... No.
[Screams]
Am I Beautiful
Oh my God.
Can you believe it?
It's perfect.
We did it.
[laughter]
And it's all ours!
It's all ours.
I'm so lucky to have you.
Yeah. Yeah.
What do you say
we go break in the bedroom?
Oh!
Okay.
Give me a minute.
Where you going?
I'm going to rinse off.
You can wait for me in anticipation.
Whatever.
I didn't always think
you were that cute you know.
Oh?
No but you filled out nicely
since high school.
Thanks.
It's true.
Filled out nice.
Am I beautiful?
I'm sure
you are just as you should be.
Am I beautiful?
Yes.
You are beautiful.
May?
[crying]
Hun?
Am I still beautiful?
No.
[crying]
Scary Endings