Death.
That's how life is.
Good morning lady.
I have a terrible toothache!
I need the dentist immediately!
Did you call for an appointment?
I have no phone.
Well, then,
You must wait.
Wait?
My lady, please!
There is a vacancy
in two hours.
My Lady! It's not possible
to expect me...
... to endure this
horrible pain for two hours!
Very well. I'll wait.
And let's hope I don't
fall apart from the agony!
Good morning sir. You are well?
And I'm happy to meet you too!
My son, the circus clown...
What are you doing on my rigging?
Get down from there!
Get down from my rigging!
You want to kill yourself? You idiot!
Faster!
Otherwise I will climb up
and throw you off!
Philippe!
Can you hear me?
Yes I can, but I don't speak Czech.
Sorry, I will speak English.
You will never become anything
from doing stupid circus tricks!
Walking on a wire will not
put bread on your table!
- Edmond, you need to reconsider!
Give him a chance!
No!
His carrots are cooked!
Exactly!
Carrots cooked!
You know, I was doing fine
until you came along!
Are you proud
of yourself?
Since when do mimes speak?
No. I am not a mime. Nor do I
hide behind an imaginary wall!
Please do not offend my circle.
It is a sacred place.
You are a thief!
Who do you think you are, stupid?
Do you mind if
I take a few photos?
- Why?
I am Philippe.
Hello. Jean-Louis.
You need to know how to knock!
It's completely ridiculous!
- You're crazy!
Yes, I'm totally crazy!
Completely!
- Yes, but that's why I love you!
Philippe, you should hear yourselves.
Both of you are behaving like children!
Okay, Jeff.
Welcome to 'the crime'.
You will make a great accomplice!
Exactly. 110 floors.
That's how tall the towers are.
Hey Jeff, why are
you trembling?
I'm scared of heights.
There's no need to panic.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
This guy thinks we're stupid...
... he's trying to rip us off.
What's wrong with the walkie-talkie?
We need wired so the cops can't hear us.
Guys! If you're selling drugs, or...
robbing a bank,
less attention, right?
I know fuck all about robbing a bank.
This is bad. I don't trust these idiots.
...especially Grumpy over there.
Do you trust these guys?
Trust them?
It's these two,
or who else?
...have something to eat.
I don't want food!
I want to go over the plan!
...and find some more
skilled partners.
The carrots are cooked!
It's now or never, my friend.
The carrots are cooked.
Be careful.
I love you.
You hear that?
Did you hear that guy?
There's no way in today!
We have to stay here
and think of another way.
All right? Take a break.
Take a break.
When we reach the 110th floor...
invite this guy
downstairs for a drink.
He has to be
hungry or thirsty.
- That'll be difficult.
I need him out of here!
I don't want to be disturbed!
How long were we under there?
Three and a half hours.
What's he doing?
A little nap maybe?
I don't believe it!
Go watch the guard.
And be quiet!
Are you crazy?
What are you doing?
Did you find it?
No! Watch the guard!
Look, the guard has gone.
This is very special to me.
You think he's gone?
You know what they say?
It's just you and me, my friend.
Hey! The wheel!
Quick, come with me!
We need to go down here
and tighten these guide ropes!
It's too high! I can't do it!
It's too dangerous!
We need to tighten the carabinas!
- I'm scared out of my mind!
Philippe, I can't do it!
Jeff, my friend?
Listen!
You need to climb down
or we just worked for nothing!
Yes, you can!
You can do it!
Here, I'll help you!
I'm just going to fix the
other one over there, okay?
- Don't leave me here by myself!
You did well, thank you.
What are you going to do with that?
What?
I lost my costume! I cannot perform without it!
You've got to come in!
- You've made your point!
Please come in now! It's over!
You've done it!
Please! You need to come in!
It's over! It's not worth it!
Wait, wait.
Are you sure?
Yes, sure.
Bye now.
Goodbye.