[OPENING FANFARE]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
[TRAFFIC SOUNDS]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
[CHATTERING CONTINUES]
[MOANING AND CHATTERING]
[SCREAMING, GUNSHOTS]
[ZIPPING]
- MAN: Come here.
- WOMAN: No!
[WOMAN GROANING]
[WALKS DOWN STAIRS]
[MOANS CONTINUE IN DISTANCE]
[SIREN WAILS]
[CART ROLLING]
What's this?
Just an old case.
MAN: Take him out.
Got him?
Higher.
Good.
- Is this Greger?
- Yes.
GREGER: Do you work at
the sex club called The Cage?
WOMAN: The Cage was shut down
after Sadowski was killed.
- GREGER: Was he there often?
- WOMAN: He lived in the building.
He came for girls
and other things.
GREGER: You mean drugs?
WOMAN: You think we worked
there for fun?
GREGER: We found Rohypnol
in Sadowski's body.
- WOMAN: So?
- GREGER: Enough to kill him.
I need you to come with me.
MAN: Sure.
[GROANS]
MAN: No drag marks were found
on Sadowski's body.
The killer must
have been strong.
Sorry sir. I can't.
[PANTING AND COUGHING]
So. We know something.
Why are you still here?
Your shift's over.
You're up to something?
Are you still following Greger?
Don't forget, I fought
for you to stay.
Greger wanted you
fired last year.
"Tadek is Old Poland,"
he said.
Shifty bastard.
You find anything, I'll get
you your reputation back.
[ELEVATOR RATTLING]
[KEYS JINGLING]
TADEK: It's hot.
Thank you, Tadek.
Promise I won't die alone.
I promise.
Swear on your life.
Mama.
I swear.
My lovely boy.
[TADEK SIGHS]
[DOOR SLIDES OPEN]
The last days of The Cage.
[INSERTS TAPE]
How did you get this?
I was the landlord. I had to empty
the club after it was shut down.
They left so suddenly.
- [WOMAN MOANS IN PAIN]
- TADEK: Hm.
[MOANING CONTINUES]
Do you recall any
of the tenants' names?
People came and went
all the time. A lot of artists.
The owner tried
to keep the rents low.
I had to fight for money every
single month. Fucking artists.
- Mmm.
- Some of them became quite famous.
Marta Zygadlo, Viktor
Mentlewicz, Krystof Kozlov.
- The writer?
- Yes.
I like his books.
Not to my taste.
Too perverted.
Why did you keep these?
I like to look.
[WOMAN CONTINUES MOANING]
Take the tapes.
WOMAN: Some critics talk about
your clinical neutrality.
KOZLOV: Yes.
WOMAN: Is that deliberate?
I don't know. I'm not
responsible for what I write.
But as the author... the female
torture scenes, are they symbolic?
Maybe. Maybe not. [CHUCKLES]
I think communism
did women no favors.
We still have the sexual
sophistication of cavemen.
So, in a sense, your writing is a
counter-commentary on feminism.
I think my writing's shit.
WOMAN: But that's very bold. Er, thank
you for being with us here today.
KOZLOV: Thank you for
wasting my time.
[TADEK CHUCKLES]
WOMAN: Are you hungry?
No no. Thank you.
[TAPE REWINDING]
[SIRENS IN DISTANCE]
[EXHALES SLOWLY]
KOZLOV: Chapter One. Marek understood
there were no rules at the sex club.
If he wanted to beat a
naked girl, he could beat her.
He could hang her from the ceiling.
Really nothing was too much trouble.
As long as he didn't
kill the girls.
He could fuck them up, but corpses
didn't look so good in makeup.
VICTOR: Alicja. His last book.
Never published.
Just to download.
The men who came there,
by invitation only,
were currently grouped around the
naked girl in baying supplication.
- One of their number...
- Okay. Take it out.
...sodomized her.
Some of the watching men
drank bottled beer.
A couple sucked...
Back in the basement
of the sex club,
Marek observed himself ogling
five girls behind The Cage,
leashed like dogs on all fours.
It seemed to him then that all the
sex he'd had, however depraved,
was rendered bizarrely innocuous
by financial transaction.
Just look into those girls' eyes;
they weren't thinking about sex.
They were thinking about that night's
shopping or how their knees hurt.
For what drives most humans, and most
humans are unremarkably corrupt,
is not the need for self-expression,
but the need for money.
If they formulate any thoughts at all,
they are driven by the grunt of greed.
They fuck and lick and smack
without a trace of irony.
Greed has always taken
itself very seriously.
GIRL: Hanna! [SQUEALS]
KOZLOV: Hanna.
HANNA: Hi!
KOZLOV: Oi!
[GIRLS GIGGLING]
KOZLOV:
Can I play? Okay.
[DISTANT CHATTER]
Hello.
- Hi.
- Come here.
[CHILDREN SQUEAL WITH DELIGHT]
Come on.
[KOZLOV CONTINUES, INDISTINCT]
[FOOTSTEPS, DOOR SHUTS]
KOZLOV: Alicja tried to struggle, but
even if someone had heard her screams,
rape was just another
transaction here.
A girl screaming was like
shopping mall Muzak,
the sound of
buying and selling.
Her hair was matted
with blood and semen,
her feet and wrists clotted and raw from
the metal cuffs nailing her to the bed.
Here, she had no name.
Here she was breasts...
Do we have to listen
to this over breakfast?
...anonymous as a child's doll. No
trace left of anything so human...
It's annoying, switch it off.
[TAPE TURNS OFF]
[GROANS]
KOZLOV: Why do men require their
rape victims to simulate desire?
Isn't it enough that they're
humiliated beyond words?
For the nuanced sadist,
pain is sufficient.
This Marek knew, which may have accounted
for why he murdered so pedantically,
the way his victim's
body had the markings
of someone choked to death
in a sadomasochistic accident.
The precise way the body
had been tied up
using a fisherman's
knot known as the fly,
a particularly painful knot that made
the victim look like he was skydiving.
[KNOCKING]
WOMAN: Come in.
TADEK: I want to
reopen the case.
I know who killed
Daniel Sadowski.
I thought we understood.
You don't investigate anymore. You
don't do anything, that's the point.
You type the cases
into the database,
file the papers, move on.
Keep your head down.
I never asked you before.
Tadek!
I worked hard to save your job last year.
It wasn't easy. Just tick the boxes.
I want to try.
Who investigated this before?
Greger.
He's Chief of Police now.
Be careful.
And what is your opinion
of intellectuals?
Intellectuals are assholes,
because being intellectual
matters more to them than being
entertaining. It's bullshit.
There's only one idea
that matters. Nothing is real.
We create the fact,
we create the fiction.
Fact, fiction. Fact, fiction.
Fact, fiction. The end.
WOMAN INTERVIEWER:
Okay. We've time for one more.
You write a lot about Truth. Can
you say what Truth means to you?
Truth cannot be
separate from us.
It cannot exist
independently of the human mind.
Truth is strong
and it will prevail.
There's nothing wrong with
that, except it isn't true.
Truth is what you make it.
Reality is perception.
[APPLAUSE]
Krystof Kozlov?
Yes?
Follow me, please.
And who the fuck are you?
Huh?!
[REPORTERS SHOUTING]
[SIGHS]
[DOOR OPENS]
How long can you hold me
without charging me?
Forty-eight hours.
Correct. Can we be clear about something?
Article 30 of the Constitution?
The inherent and inalienable
dignity of each citizen
shall constitute a source
of freedoms and rights
that all public authorities are
obliged to respect and protect.
Can we be clear about that?
- Yes.
- Good.
I need a lawyer.
I'm allowed a lawyer.
Yes.
You wish to call someone?
A lawyer?
- Yes.
- No.
You don't wish
to call someone?
Do you wish to?
It's up to you.
You think?
You've been detained in connection
with the murder of Daniel Sadowski.
Jesus, you're slow. [LAUGHS]
- You lived in an apartment on Richter Street.
- I did?
- You were there for over a year.
- I don't remember.
- You were.
- No.
- I do remember.
- Huh.
Old building. Stank of cum.
Sex club in the basement. No?
Did you ever
frequent the club?
Frequent? Jesus. Frequent?
Does anybody frequent...
Visit.
Yeah I fucked some whores. Along with
the pigs from your Police Department.
[EXHALES]
The deceased went out
with one of the hostesses.
- What was her name?
- Daria Romanowska.
- And you asked her about this?
- We haven't found her yet.
- She'll have changed her name.
- We thought of that.
You did? [LAUGHS]
You never spoke to her?
The whole year you
were living there?
Do you speak to
your neighbors?
- Yes.
- Yes. I bet you live in a little house
and you wish you could have sex with your
wife but she's too old and you're too bored
and what the fuck, you can always
jerk yourself off in the shower.
Can you remember where you were
the night Sadowski vanished?
Can you?
- Answer the question.
- No. [LAUGHS]
Did you know
Daniel Sadowski?
- Yes.
- How?
- He was a friend.
- Where did you meet?
In the club.
Maybe the apartment.
Blond. Big cock.
How long...
had you known him?
A year. Maybe more.
You saw each other regularly?
As regularly as he'd let me.
Let you?
Daniel was... a busy man.
[CHAIR SLIDES BACK]
KOZLOV: The body had been tied up using
a fisherman's knot known as the fly,
a particularly painful knot that made
the victim look like he was skydiving.
Free, at last, from
the carnal routine of living.
Its long, littleness stopped, like his heart,
by Rohypnol, the notorious date rape drug,
for Marek would deny his
victim even the fractional joy
of the cold water
meeting his skin.
[TAPE CLICKS]
Your novel.
Same victim. Same location.
Same means of death.
Only a police officer or the
killer could know those facts.
The details of the murder were never
published. So how do you know about that?
You really want me
to tell you I murdered Daniel?
- Did you?
- What do you think?
I think the book
is your confession.
Why would I confess
to something like that?
Tell me I'm wrong.
You could be right.
You know the truth.
Truth. You really
want to go there?
You kill someone,
it's a self-evident fact.
Not according
to Christ's crucifixion.
I've seen dead bodies.
You don't make them up.
You killed Daniel Sadowski
and you made it look
like a sado-masochistic
game that went wrong.
Well that's what you say.
No. That's what you say.
- That's what I write.
- Ah.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[KNOCKS]
- Hello.
- I already told you everything I know.
I published his first books. We
divorced many years ago. That's it.
Has he tried
to contact you again?
I will never speak
to Krystof again.
about Krystof again.
[UNLOCKS DOOR]
[FLIPS LIGHT SWITCH]
VICTOR: Did she ever talk to her
neighbor Krystof Kozlov?
MAN: No.
- Anything?
- Mm.
Nothing here.
[CAR APPROACHING]
POLICEMAN ON LOUDSPEAKER:
Please move your car.
Move your car, now.
- You have no authority to be here.
- [STARTS CAR]
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
MARTA:
You are never with us.
TADEK: Work's been busy.
MARTA: Work's always busy.
TADEK: I'm on an important case.
Piotr wants it solved.
Piotr. Are you serious?
If I land this case,
he'll give me my old job back.
You're finished in a year.
Not like this.
I don't want to go like this.
Just don't forget who you are.
KOZLOV: Marek thought
how fickle memory was.
You murder a man,
and the moment it's done
you're already retelling
the story to yourself,
so that the act of killing
is not your act of killing,
but belongs, instead,
to some fictional simulacrum
in just the same way the men who
murdered so prosaically in Auschwitz
made peace with what they did, transmuted
their memories like pieces of fiction,
to the point where good
and evil lost all meaning
and the only lights by which they steered
were what they tasted, saw, and touched.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- WOMAN [CRYING]: Krystof.
- Mum, it's all right.
Have a seat. Please.
[MEN CHATTER IN BACKGROUND]
Sir. I found this.
TADEK: Are they yours?
They're planted.
You deny
they're yours?
I deny nothing.
Who did they belong to?
Well, you tell me,
you fascist bastard.
When you're finished...
then it's my turn.
[DOOR BUZZES]
Your boyfriend. Mr. Kozlov.
KASIA:
We're not together anymore.
He called you yesterday.
Might I ask why?
To talk to Hanna.
Daniel Sadowski.
Do you know this name?
No.
Did Mr. Kozlov ever give
you reason to fear him?
What do you mean?
Did he frighten you?
Threaten you?
No.
- Sexually?
- No.
He was never violent
toward you?
[SIGHS]
Come on.
Don't ever talk in front of
my daughter like that. Please.
Who paid for your drugs?
It's none of your business.
What kind of work do you do?
I'd like you to leave now.
Sit down.
Relax.
- Is your name Krystof Kozlov?
- Yes.
- Do you drink?
Is it summer now?
Yes.
No.
- Have you ever been violent?
- Sometimes.
- Yes or no.
- Yes.
Did you strangle
Daniel Sadowski?
No.
- Did you torture him?
- No.
Did you pay someone
to murder him?
No.
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS]
[CROWS CAWING]
[DOOR OPENS]
Did you let him have
a phone call?
It is his right.
Is he guilty?
Yes.
Greger will come after you.
I know.
I know it was you.
You're fucked.
Come.
[REPORTERS MURMURING]
[ALL CLAMORING]
I was stripped and tied
to a metal chair.
Mentally and physically humiliated
and threatened with violence.
Officer Pietzek, the man
in charge of the investigation,
verbally assaulted me
on numerous occasions.
He threatened to beat me, and then he wanted
to throw me from the third floor window
and say that
I'd committed suicide.
His words were:
"Two seconds and it's done."
I will be suing
the officer in question
for violation of Article 30
of the Constitution. Thank you.
[REPORTERS SHOUTING QUESTIONS]
[SCATTERED APPLAUSE]
[PANTING]
[SIGHS]
[TURNS ON WATER]
Sir? They want
to see you upstairs.
WOMAN: Take a seat.
I'm not here to judge, Tadek.
I just need to know
if what Kozlov says is true.
Of course not. It's in his book.
"Pawel leaned across
the table and stared at him.
Do you know what the police do
with people who tell lies?
We take them to that window
and we throw them out. Suicide.
Two seconds and it's done."
You memorized that?
How many times have
you read his book?
So you never used
violence against him?
We all know Greger's dirty.
I warned you not to compete
with him for the job.
If you want to beat him,
pick your fights,
check your facts, and never let
emotion cloud your judgment.
PIOTR: Microphone.
Transmitter. Receiver.
Officially you don't have this.
Don't screw up.
Discreet, Tadek.
[CAR STARTS]
- [DOOR OPENING]
- [KEYS RATTLING]
[DOOR CLOSING]
KOZLOV: My parents will
bring Hanna tomorrow.
I know, you told me already.
- You hungry?
- No.
- There's food in the kitchen.
- Later.
Here.
We were clear, no? You have
to stop coming here.
I need to be with you.
But not me.
Come here.
What? You want...
you want more stories?
No, no, no, no.
I've got a really
good one for you.
Shh. That's not fair.
Come here.
[YELLS] Just leave me alone!
- Kasia. Kasia.
- Leave me alone!
[SHRIEKS] How can you hear
all this and do nothing?
[CRYING]
No!
Shh.
You promised!
Stop. It will. It will stop.
It will stop.
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
The war of words between Krystof
Kozlov and the Interior Ministry
increased today with the author's impending
appeal against police brutality.
The original investigation was headed by
the current chief of police, Adam Greger.
MAN: Why did you shut the investigation
down in the first place?
Insufficient evidence.
- Are the accusations true?
- [DOOR OPENS]
I can't comment on
any individual case
but what I can say is that our police
force is a modern police force,
striving to protect its
citizens in an increasingly
complex and challenging
society. Thank you.
WOMAN: Mr. Kozlov asserts that the police
have fabricated their evidence against him.
Is it true?
No.
I hope so.
Last time you said the same.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
The same car
was there yesterday.
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[PANTING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
Sit.
Greger wants
the case shut down.
He doesn't like your
methods with Kozlov's parents.
Planting the dope
was a dumb idea, Tadek.
You don't play
Greger's game well.
That's why he's
the chief and you're not.
Don't disappoint me.
You're the last honest
cop in Poland.
The moment you took Greger on,
you were fucked.
You're too old school.
Greger's as empty
and hard as glass.
You want to fuck Greger over?
Officially, don't work on
this anymore. You're history.
Keep the files. Work on it
remotely. I know he's guilty.
Just prove it.
- Adam.
- Tadek.
You want to know the worst
part of my job?
Envy.
People see me as a chance to screw
over someone more powerful.
Like those whores who drive
up to the big houses.
You know the ones?
Big metal gates and those beautiful
girls who drive right on through.
I swear they'll do
anything for money.
Always the same.
Communists, capitalists.
But you get too close...
No ghosts, Tadek.
Stay safe.
[CAR DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
I'll go.
- What are you doing here?
- KASIA: Please help me.
Someone's watching
our apartment.
- TAKEK: Did you see who?
- No.
Come. Come in.
I'm going to drive them home.
Make sure she's safe.
Who is she, Tadek?
She's Kozlov's girlfriend.
He's been threatening her.
You take one more step
and I'm out.
Come.
[DOOR OPENS]
TADEK: Nobody's here.
You can come.
Krystof doesn't know you
were here the other night.
I never feel safe.
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
Hurt me.
[TADEK MOANS]
Victor? The door.
- You asked to see me?
- KOZLOV: Yes.
I killed Daniel Sadowski.
[WRITING]
I'll need you
to sign a statement.
Why?
You just told me you
killed Daniel Sadowski.
I'll write it down.
You can sign it.
I feel sick. I need a doctor.
Sign and I'll get you
a doctor.
You put something
in the water.
Sign the statement!
You raped her. Hmm.
Let him go.
KASIA: [SCREAMING]
Stop! Stop!
Don't! Don't!
GREGER: Shut up! Quiet!
Quiet, bitch!
No. Don't!
Say it. Say it! Say it. Say it.
Hurt me. Hurt me! Hurt me!
[SCREAMS]
[BANGING ON DOOR]
[BANGING]
Yes?
TADEK: Open the door.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I was, er..
You want..
you want some coffee?
Talk.
What do you want me to say?
How old is Hanna? Eight?
You have an eight year old
daughter and you're a drug addict.
I can have her taken away.
Is that all you can do?
Threaten me?
Talk to me.
You know Greger. You knew
Sadowski. You fucked him.
Yes, I did. I fucked him. He paid me.
I fucked him because he paid me.
And Kozlov knew about it.
You're the girl
in the inner room.
Alicja is your story.
You talked, he wrote it down.
- He loved me.
- He didn't love you.
He did. He loved me.
You drove him mad. He strangled a
man and dumped him in the river.
You talk about Sadowski as
if he was a saint. He wasn't.
He deserves justice.
You want justice?
You saw the marks. You saw
what they did to me every day.
This is what they made me.
In my head is where
they rape me. Forever.
Is that part of the show?
I can't tell anymore.
You're going to sign a statement. You
do that, you keep the girl. Come on.
Sit down.
I've brought it for you.
You see?
Here we go.
I even brought you a pen.
We'll do it together.
Pick up the pen. Pick it up!
You know how to sign
your name, don't you? Do it.
[WRITING]
[MEN CHATTERING]
KOZLOW: Let me go.
I haven't done anything,
you piece of shit.
Aaah!
Fuck!
[POLICE SIREN]
- Kasia said that?
- Yes.
I love her.
The things he did to her.
How could you let him do those
things and get away with it?
- Right.
And that's the story.
TADEK: That's the story.
You think?
I know.
[SHUFFLING PAPER]
Victor.
[SOFT LAUGHTER]
- [DOOR BELL RINGS]
- I'll get it.
That's good.
GREGER: You know this
changes nothing.
You get rid of me, who cares?
We used to get rid
of people from Solidarity.
They still won.
I'll tell you what this is.
Envy.
TADEK: Hmm.
I've heard this story.
[CHATTER]
Obviously I can't comment
on any individual officer
while investigations
are still pending.
Is it true Greger resigned?
Mr. Greger needs time
to answer the allegations
made against him by Kozlov
and other witnesses.
And for the sake of the police force, to
which he has devoted his professional life,
he has taken
the decision to step down.
REPORTER: Are you
his permanent replacement?
I'm an ex-Communist,
nothing in life is permanent.
You should see this. Sir.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[COUGHS]
[GASP]
WOMAN: Excuse me sir,
where are you going?
Sir?
Sir, you can't go down there.
I need to talk to you.
PIOTR: What do you want?
We've charged the wrong man.
Kozlov signed the confession.
Koslov is mad.
Did that worry you before?
Kozlov was abroad
when Sadowski was murdered.
He came back the day after!
And you didn't check it?
He was a very
compelling suspect.
[CHUCKLES]
Jesus fucking Christ.
If Kozlov is not guilty...
You think I am going to lose everything I
worked for so you can change your mind?
I don't give a shit who you paid,
who you fucked, who you lied to.
This is the story now.
Piotr, this is not justice!
Fuck justice! Were you thinking about justice
when you screwed Kozlov's girlfriend?
You want me to tell
your family about that?
You want me
to tell your daughter?
You think that case just
landed on your desk by accident?
I gave it to you,
you arrogant fuck.
Victor works for me.
Oh, and I had you followed.
See, people don't want justice.
They want good and evil.
Big, bright stories told with conviction.
That's what we do. That's what you did.
You wrote the big, bright story,
told with conviction. Well done.
I am the Chief of Police now.
Now fuck off
out of my sunshine.
TADEK: When did he leave?
After you were here.
Any idea where he went?
Hmm-mm.
Are you finished?
I'll be home soon.
You be a good girl. I know you
will, at school, with mama. Okay?
Time is over.
- Bye.
- [KOZLOV BLOWS KISS]
You lied.
About killing Sadowski.
No.
You weren't even there
when the murder happened.
What makes you think
the murder even happened here?
The river has an end...
and a beginning.
Fuck!!!
It'll be on later tonight.
Fine.
[CAR DOOR SHUTS, ENGINE STARTS]
[SIGHS]
[CRIES SILENTLY]
[SOBS]
No. No. No. No.
MAN: The implications of the direction
of the euro remain to be seen.
Now, an update
on the Kozlov case.
WOMAN: Missing papers given
to the press by a source
close to the investigation
reveal that Krystof Kozlov,
the main suspect in the
murder of Daniel Sadowski,
was actually out of the country
on the night of his murder.
The authorities have yet
to issue a statement,
but Kozlov's lawyer has already
recorded a miscarriage of justice.
MAN: The controversy surrounding the
brutal murder of Daniel Sadowski
has taken a new turn.
Documents supplied to...
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[BANGS ON DOOR]
What do you want?
Let me in. Please.
I have nothing
to say to you.
I did what you wanted me
to do, now leave me alone.
I was wrong.
I made a mistake.
And I was wrong to hurt you.
I'm sorry.
Where are the others?
They'll come later.
[SIGHS]
I've got to know
what Sadowski did to you.
You want to hear the truth?
It's all I have left.
You can look into your lover's eyes all your
life and never know what they truly think.
The truth is, Sadowski
was a sadist. The worst by far.
Sometimes he...
he liked me to play dead,
then he'd rape me.
I took drugs.
Enough, you know,
to just, to numb it.
Sometimes Sadowski
wanted me to choke him.
So I did.
This time I... I just...
I didn't stop.
I just... I didn't stop.
I killed him.
I called Krystof
as soon as it happened.
He never asked why.
He just did what he had to do.
That kind of love is..
is a rare thing.
Truly...
I do this for my daughter.
And for Krystof.
This is the only...
the only family I have.
And nothing is going
to get in its way.
Because this is
the best I can be.
I'm sorry.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
Subtitles by explosiveskull