So dad's gonna
bring pizza home.
Lucy?
Lucy!
Don't call me that.
What Would you
like me to call you?
Lucinda. It's more adult.
Okay.
So, Lucinda, huh?
Yeah.
You know, it wasn't that
long ago you'd have me
climb into bed with you
when you had a nightmare.
Whatever. I was four.
I, uh, I need to
ask you something.
What is it?
So, There's this camping trip
and everyone's going.
That's not a question.
Can I go?
Isn't it a little cold
to go camping?
We're staying in a cabin.
Are there gonna be any parents?
No.
Are there gonna be boys?
Morgan's going.
That's of very little comfort.
Please, mom?
Sorry, Lucy. I just don't
think it's a good idea.
This is not fair.
Yeah, and...
If your aunt had a mustache,
she'd be your Uncle.
I fucking hate it
when you say that.
You're not going. And you
talk to me like that again,
You're not going anywhere
for a very long time.
You have to trust
I'm just looking out for you.
Okay, Lucy?
- Lucinda...
- I'm walking home.
Luck, come on. Lucy!
Lucy!
♪ So, the wind blew for days ♪
♪ in so many ways ♪
♪ you were buried in clout ♪
♪ but now,
it's left you alone ♪
♪ You're drenched to the bone ♪
♪ but You're safe now somehow ♪
♪ the gales ♪
♪ had died ♪
♪ and your clothes ♪
♪ will dry ♪
♪ your questions
drifted away... ♪
Tess?
So...
What'd you think?
This is different.
You bring your skateboard?
- It's your skateboard.
- It's yours now.
Okay.
She shouldn't
skate around here.
There aren't any sidewalks.
Tell your mom not
to be such a fuddy duddy.
Don't be such a fuddy duddy.
Is she shaking her head?
Yeah.
Have you been playing
those cords I taught you?
A little bit.
The strings hurt my fingers.
The skin will get harder
the more you play,
then you won't feel anything.
Okay.
We'll practice together
when I come home.
When will you come home?
Soon.
So I'm gonna
be coming home late from work.
Just like the last job.
Yeah.
I double-checked
with the principal,
and she still thinks you should
start after winter break.
'Kay.
You'll get a fresh start.
You took your pill, right?
Yes.
You have to
take your pill everyday,
- and you get that, right?
- I know.
Come here, boy!
Hello. Father meyers.
Jessica.
This is Tess.
Short for Theresa.
Please don't call me that.
- Tess.
- Sorry.
I'll make
sure to say a prayer for...
Thank you, father.
- Tess?
- Thank you.
Hello.
Sarah?
It's...
Haven't see you here
in a while.
Is there anything
we can do for you?
No. Thank you.
Did you have a bad dream?
Hey, this is Lucy's phone.
I'm not here right now.
Leave a message,
and I might get back to you.
What're you gonna do today?
Read.
Explore.
Hey.
Remember what Dr. petty said?
Always make eye contact.
♪ I stood alone ♪
♪ and watched you go ♪
♪ my crying voice ♪
♪ was out of range ♪
♪ and as I stood ♪
♪ with none beside me ♪
♪ I felt the seasons in me ♪
♪ change ♪
♪ and a part of me ♪
♪ has lost my mother ♪
♪ has lost a child ♪
♪ and part of me ♪
♪ will rise from my roots ♪
♪ at least not
for a little while ♪
♪ I think of you ♪
♪ when I walk this city ♪
♪ and I'll hold you more ♪
♪ than time to time ♪
♪ and even though ♪
♪ it's such a pity ♪
♪ Can't make myself ♪
♪ just leave these behind ♪
Anxiety, depression,
disruptive behavior disorder,
hallucinations.
She's been in and out
of hospitals...
On different medications
practically her whole life.
I remember the first time.
She was five.
She was sitting in a corner
all hunched up and...
And just knocking her head
against the wall...
Over and over.
And we were so young
when we had her.
At her age now, actually.
I've...
Tried so hard.
I've made so many mistakes.
Abut then I... I think
she's good now.
It looks like
you've done well, Jessica.
She seems like a teenager.
Tess, come in for dinner.
All right. You want this
door open or closed?
It doesn't matter.
What're you doing?
Just looking.
It's freezing out here.
♪ You and I together ♪
♪ You're the jewel
in my crown ♪
♪ you and I forever ♪
♪ What goes up must come down ♪
♪ And you go north
till it's South ♪
♪ And you come back around ♪
♪ I could never leave you ♪
♪ No matter if I tried ♪
♪ And if you ever ran ♪
♪ I'd retrieve you ♪
♪ To keep you satisfied ♪
♪ And you Can't run,
and you Can't hide ♪
♪ But I'll love you
till I die ♪
What're you singing?
Nothing. I just make
it up as I go along.
Pierre asked if you were
coming on the camping trip.
I'd have to buy a new swimsuit
that hides my scar.
Oh, screw that.
Your scar's cool.
Peter says
it's like a badass tattoo.
So wait. Does that mean
your mom said yes?
Lucinda.
You haven't even asked her yet,
- have you?
- No, not yet.
Sarah's cool. She'll say yes.
- "Sarah's cool"?
- Cooler than my mom.
Yeah. Morgan, that's not hard.
Don't talk about my mom, bitch.
Sarah gets it.
She's, like, worldly.
- "Worldly"?
- Yeah.
Worldly.
Come on. Your grandparents
are missionaries.
They didn't stick around long.
And all she ever did
was end of back here.
She's never gonna let me go.
Well, tell her I'm going.
That'll make her happy.
Yeah.
Just ask her, you wuss.
Can I help you?
Alrighty, then.
I used to have a necklace
just like that once.
How come nobody
ever comes in here?
Excuse me.
I'm always across the street.
Nobody ever comes in.
No one reads books anymore.
I like them.
I do, too.
I just wish
we weren't the only ones.
If your aunt had a mustache,
she'd be your Uncle.
Come again.
It's just something
my mom says.
"Understanding your dreams."
That's a good book.
I get nightmares.
So does my daughter.
She has me sleep with her
when she has 'em.
Do you need anything else?
No, thank you.
Tess?
Did you take your pill today?
I know they don't
make you feel good,
but doctors prescribe them
for a reason.
You know?
You knew there were
gonna be side-effects.
No... I know.
That's better than
the alternative, right?
I just wish
she Would talk to me.
I mean, you have a better
connection with her
and You're 10,000 Miles away.
That's not true.
You're being too hard
on yourself.
The way Tess is...
Who she is inside...
Quiet, smart, awful.
She's just like you.
You have a stomachache?
Let me get you some
antacid, okay?
Here. Tess.
Take two of these, okay?
You chew both of them?
It won't stop.
I won't stop it.
I won't stop.
This'll all be over.
This'll all be over...
Go away!
Leave me alone!
Just go away!
Go away!
Please stop! Stop it!
Please!
Tess?
Tess. Tess!
Tess!
Robert, she started
cutting herself.
They're not gonna let
me leave, not even for this.
Don't worry.
We'll get you more help.
Why didn't you tell me
you were in pain?
You always tell me.
Tess! Tess!
Help!
♪ It'll be here just in time ♪
♪ just in time ♪
Help me.
Help me. Please help me.
- Hello?
- Please.
Mom...
Mom, please help me.
- Hello?
- Please help me, mom.
Hey, this is Lucy's phone.
I'm not here right now.
Leave a message
and I might get back to you.
Am I speaking with Tess?
Do you see that
person over there?
There's no one there.
Let's take a look at
the drawings we asked you to do.
You said you had a feeling
that something
was pushing you down.
You couldn't move.
Did you know that There's
a chemical in your brain
that makes you paralyzed
when you sleep?
It's so you don't get up
while you dream.
I wasn't sleeping.
Were you taking
your medication?
Yes.
But it doesn't matter.
They don't work anyway.
With the hallucinations?
The noises.
What kind of noise?
They think
it's a severe case of.
Dissociative identity disorder.
The doctors are suggesting
I send her to an institution.
Where she can be supervised.
You said she can move her limbs?
They need more tests.
Nothing's helped.
Well, let me try.
Do you believe in God?
I don't know.
"Be strong in the lord"...
"...And the power of his might."
Put on the whole armor
of God so that you.
May be able to stand against
the schemings of the devil.
For we do not rustle against
the flesh and the blood.
Or against the
principalities that powers.
"And against the spiritual host
in these heavenly places."
That's not going to help.
I talked to your
little brother...
Stephan, right?
He looks about nine.
Stephan says he forgives you
for what you did.
Where is he?
What was that?
I didn't say anything.
You're not serious?
Jessica, I want to help you
in any way I can,
but I have no knowledge here.
There's a seminary in St. Louis
that has experience
with this sort of thing.
I'd love for her
to talk to someone there
if I can get them to see her,
but they'd have to meet her
outside of the hospital.
They're making me
talk to a social worker
before I can take her home.
Well, maybe I can help with that
if they trust me here.
Here you go.
Are you taking me home?
It's for your own safety.
You have to eat.
Doesn't matter.
I'll make 'em go away.
What was that?
Tess!
I'm home.
I traveled a
lot when I was a kid.
My parents were missionaries,
so we...
Traveled all over the world,
but India was our first stop.
We'd only been there a few days
when I noticed all these people
filing into the house
across the street.
So I snuck over...
And all the people
were sitting in the semicircle.
And...
This woman was kneeling
in the center.
Swaying her head
back and forth...
Until something...
Overtook her.
She removed her hair
from her face.
And...
She kept staring until.
Her eyes began
to change colors.
And they all raised their hands
wanting to speak to the woman,
actually speak to their dead
loved ones through her.
She Would do this every month.
I Would say they were
taking advantage of her,
but I found out.
She willingly went through it.
She considered it a gift.
To bring the people
in that room some peace.
And to convince the spirits
they could finally move on.
I think your daughter
may have the same gift,
and I think my daughter
is inside your daughter.
Everything's that's happened
to Tess.
Could be a result of this gift.
Stop calling it that.
Sorry.
So what else makes you think
this is real?
She came into my store one day
and told me she had a
necklace like this one.
- She's had a lot of necklaces.
- And then she said a saying
that I used to say to Lucy
that she hated
that my mother always said to me
that I'm sure when she grew up.
She Would probably
say to her kids.
What was it?
"If your aunt had a mustache,
she'd be your Uncle."
Why Would Tess have this?
I think some people
are just born with it.
The Indian girl didn't ask why.
She just accepted it and dealt
with it in her own way.
I'm sorry.
I Can't just accept it.
Maybe this is all
too crazy to believe.
Tess.
Where's dad?
Ah... he left.
It was really hard after.
Can I talk to him?
It's not a good idea, Lucy.
He'll never believe this.
That's Martha and Rena, Becka.
My two cousins,
crystal and Lukas.
And pa Jeffrey.
Is that right?
What's in that locket?
I never got a chance
to put anything in it.
My dad.
He only gave it to me
a week before.
But if you need more proof.
I'm sorry
for doing this to her.
I just wanted to be
more like myself.
Lucy's appendix burst
when she was eight years old.
I'm not evil.
Just give me
some time alone with her.
She's just confused...
Stubborn.
You want to be alone with her?
For how long?
-  A few days.
- A few days?
However long it takes.
Look. I'll let you talk
to her now with me in the room,
otherwise,
I have to take her away.
And what if she
doesn't want to go?
Please let me stay.
I worked so hard
coming back to you.
I don't want you to go.
This isn't good for you.
You're only gonna get
more confused,
and then you'll never be able
to move on.
But I don't want to move on.
It breaks my heart,
but it's the right thing to do.
For Tess and there for you.
- Please let her come back.
- She doesn't want to.
The pills, the doctor's...
She's done with all of them.
She's in a place
where they Can't hurt her.
I'm sorry, but she doesn't
trust you anymore.
You have to move on, Lucinda.
- I Can't control it, mom.
- I know you can.
- I Can't.
- Yes...
You can.
Your other spirits...
If I leave, I may never
be able to come back.
Do you want that?
You have to try.
I'm so sorry
for everything I said.
Just for everything.
I wish I wasn't
such a little brat.
No, no, no, don't...
Don't say that.
I'd still be here with you and dad
and you Would still be together.
- It's not your fault.
- Yes, it is.
I just want you
to be at peace, Lucy,
and to be in a better place.
Okay.
What's going on?
I love you, mom.
I love you, too.
Is that Tess?
I'm not sure.
You have to try harder, Lucy.
Is that Tess?
- What's going on?
- I don't know!
Tess?
Tess.
- Tess?
- Just stop that.
What is she saying?
I Can't tell.
Tess?
Lucy?
Who are you?
Ugh! Tess!
Tess! Stop! -It's okay.
There's no way out down there!
No!
- What are you doing?
- She might be hurt.
She's my daughter.
Tess! Tess!
Please come out!
Please come back to me!
I'll keep you safe.
I'm begging you!
I'll do better! I swear.
I just need you back.
Tess?
Where's my mom?
Lucy's a strong soul.
That's why she was able
to fight her way back.
Maybe...
She just needs closure.
I don't know, but isn't
that what they all want?
I think they
just don't want to leave.
Morgan's gone.
She'll come back.
Everyone's trying to move on.
Even you?
Tess?
- Lucy.
- Tess.
Baby, it's only
gonna get worse.
Trust me, please?
Can I just have one more night?
Sure.
Hi.
Lucy?
Do you really want to go back?
I'll tell your mom
You're not sure.
Ugh!
Ahh!
Ugh! Ahh!
Lucy?
I came back for you, mom.
I won't leave you again.
Wait.
We can move back if you want.
Whatever you think is best.
I'll do better for you.
I know you will.
Let me see.
You got to keep
building up your calluses.
Keep playing, okay?
I will.
Promise me you won't give up.
I promise.
She seems better to you, right?
You don't think so?
I just don't know anymore.
She can be a normal kid again.
Can be even cool.
♪ You and I are together ♪
♪ You're the jewel
in my crown ♪
♪ so it will be forever ♪
♪ What goes up must come down ♪
♪ You go north,
till it's South ♪
♪ you'd come back around ♪
♪ I could never,
ever leave you ♪
♪ No matter if I tried ♪
♪ And if you'd ever run,
I'd retrieve you ♪
♪ To keep you satisfied ♪
You know,
I never did get your name.
♪ As you can run ♪
♪ You can hide ♪
♪ Love you till I die. ♪