( Woman )
No!
Help me!
Help!
No, no, no, no!
No, no!
No!
What do you think you're doing?
Help me!
Please, please!
( Screaming )
Oh!
It's after checkout time!
I want my money!
Mistress, the innkeeper!
He wants to be paid.
Honey, when I spend the
night in a man's room,
he better pay me.
I want my money!
Zou Zou, just go back
to sleep, would ya?
What's he gonna do, kill us?
Here's Johan!
( Screaming )
( Johan )
Give me the money!
Now!
I want my money!
Give me the money!
( Zou Zou grunting )
Oops.
( Johan )
Now I got you!
Come back here!
Pay me the money!
Hey!
Oh!
Hurry, Mistress!
Get up!
Go on, go on!
I'm coming down for you, eh?
I want my money!
Ooh!
( Wolves howling )
You getting tired, Zou Zou?
No, Mistress.
Well, I am.
Pull over.
Zou Zou, I thought I told
you to pay that inn creep.
With what, Mistress, my good looks?
Well, you got a point
there, girlfriend.
But, I mean, couldn't
you have done something
to pay for our room?
You know, wash dishes, dug ditches?
Oui, Mistress, you are right.
I mean, Zou Zou, you should
be grateful to do any labor,
no matter how menial,
because I can't.
I am a professional entertainer,
and I have to save every
ounce of my strength
for my audience.
Any more of that
blood sausage left?
Hmm.
This sausage is good.
Too bad you're on a diet.
I am?
But wait... Oh, oh!
Ooh!
Uh, did you call a cab?
Uh, hold on there, baldy.
Hold it just a minute.
I... I... I...
You forgot my makeup case.
Oh.
Hello.
May I offer you ladies a ride?
Well... Oui, oui,
we'd love a ride.
It depends.
Where ya headed, sailor?
I'm traveling north
to visit a client.
Perhaps I could offer
you and your servant
a nice lodging.
That is, of course, unless
you've made other arrangements.
Well... Oh, sir, arrangements?
No, no, we do not have...
Oof!
Well, then, shall we go?
Please.
My name is Dr. Bradley...
Dr. Bradley Bradley.
Oh.
Your mother must have
thought you looked so nice,
she named you twice.
Elvira's the name,
showbiz the game.
Oh.
I'm just in the process of
fulfilling my lifelong dream
of opening in a world-renowned
Parisian revue.
I know.
You do? But of course.
Your reputation precedes you.
Oh, damn, I hate when that happens.
I don't owe you any money, do I?
Good Lord, no.
I found your play
billin the village.
Oh... Yes, of course.
And I must say, it's quite
a titillating image.
Yes, it is quite a good
likeness, isn't it?
Quite.
Oh!
So, what kind of medicine
man are you, man?
I am a psychiatrist.
Oh, great!
'Cause my feet are killing me.
Charming.
I say...
Perhaps we could arrange
for a private performance.
Oh!
Lucky for you, I come
equipped with my own airbags.
I beg your pardon?
I'm so looking forward
to the next bump.
Uh... Thanks for the...
lift, Doc,
but I really gotta
get going, you know.
Nobody told me this was gonna
be Mr. Toad's Wild Ride.
( Horses neighing )
Oh, oh!
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, my God!
Help!
Oh, oh!
Ooh, ah!
Oh, ow, ooh, ah!
I say, coachman, are you
making out all right up there?
Coachman!
Welcome to Castle Hellsubus.
Cheery.
( Screaming )
Lady Hellsubus...
Allow me to present Elvira.
Charmed.
I think.
Please, forgive me, Madam.
It's just that you...
You...
You... Me, me, what?
You look pretty.
Please, come in.
Oof!
The lady and her servant
will be spending the night.
Very well.
I'll have the maid
prepare the rooms.
I trust that your
stay here will be...
comfortable, madam.
Your cloak, ma'am.
Your gloves, ma'am.
Your shoes, ma'am.
Hold it right there.
I mean, I usually get paid
for this sort of thing.
You know, when I take
a... If you please, ma'am.
I am afraid it is imperative.
You see, my husband,
he suffers from an acute
affliction of the hearing.
Sounds that seem
commonplace to you or to I
cut into his head like knives!
Are you sure it's not just
some kind of kinky foot thing?
The shoes, if you please.
Ooh!
( Cat screeching )
Zou Zou? Oh!
Would you help me?
Oh!
( Gong ringing )
Lady Hellsubus, would you
mind informing Lord Hellsubus
that he has a guest?
Something tells me he's
already figured that out.
Ooh, a piano bar!
( Playing upbeat song )
Stop!
No more, please!
Oh, jeez, everybody's a critic.
( Thundering )
Elvira, allow me to present
Lord Vladimere Hellsubus.
Enchanté.
Ow!
Hey, we haven't even met yet!
Oh, sorry.
Hey, nice jacket.
Who shot the stove?
( Rim shot )
( laughing )
Elvira is soon to be
one of Gay Paree's
foremost entertainers.
Lots of straight guys like me, too.
( Echoing laughter )
Thank you, thank you, but
seriously, folks... No!
This cannot be.
No!
Nice meeting you, too.
Who's the old dude in the dress?
Perhaps he has seen your act.
Oui.
( Door creaking )
( rumbling )
Oh!
Oh, oh, oh!
Don't be frightened, Elvira.
It's only the castle settling
down for the evening.
Come.
It's time for bed.
The village people say
this castle is evil.
Ehh, who listens to the
Village People anymore?
This castle and its
occupants are cursed.
It's the Hellsubus family blood.
It causes them to do strange
and unnatural things.
Sounds like fun.
Lucian Hellsubus.
Vladimere's
great-great-grandfather.
Sadist, murderer.
Thousands of innocent souls
died by his torturous hands
in the dungeon of this very castle.
Ew, nice hobby.
Captain Teodore Hellsubus.
Vladimere's grandfather.
Smuggler, slave trader,
pathological liar,
bad dancer, cross-dresser.
That's really weird.
Cross-dressers are
usually great dancers.
Careful.
The tremors seem to have
caused a bit of damage.
Yeah, duh.
Anybody ever heard of Spackle?
And last but not least,
the Lady Donya Hellsubus,
Vladimere's mother.
Slut, harlot, seductress.
Just one man couldn't satisfy her.
I hear you, Grandma.
Right.
I'll show you to your room, then.
This was her room.
Her?
Her who?
Elura, Vladimere's first wife.
Nobody has set foot in
it since her passing.
Whew, pee-eww.
Pass of what is the question.
Could you light a
match or something?
Elura died exactly ten
years ago tomorrow.
( Coughing )
Dr. Bradley, I thought I
heard a voice and I...
Oh, what's her problem?
Don't mind her.
She does this sort of
thing quite frequently.
She's not well, as you can see.
Who is she?
This pitiful creature
is Roxana Hellsubus,
Lord Hellsubus' niece.
She too is afflicted with
the Hellsubus family curse,
which has ruined many a life,
including that of Elura.
Beautiful, unfortunate Elura.
I must say, the resemblance
between the two of you
is remarkable.
No wonder Vladimere was so shocked
at the very sight of you.
Oh, my God!
Not only that, but
we're both wearing
the exact same nail polish.
Really?
How remarkable.
Well, it's getting kind of late,
and I'm off to Paris
in the morning.
Must you leave so soon?
Dr. Bradley, opening
my show in Paris
means more to me than
anything in the world,
even playing "Hide the
Hot Dog" with you.
Well, then.
What about a quick nightcap?
No.
Brandy? Mm-mm.
Champagne? Mm-mm.
Sanka?
Lemonade with a twist?
Ooh!
Mistress, it's time for la douche.
Yes, quite right.
Well, I'll send my carriage
around in the morning.
Good night.
Oh, Dr. Bradley?
Yes?
Didn't you forget something?
Ah, yes.
Quite right.
Good night.
Oh, and Doc?
I'll take a rain
checkon the physical.
Oh hi, Ema.
Thanks for spying on us.
Oh, this is so relaxing.
Oh, Zou Zou, turn on the
bubbles, would you?
More hot water, Zou Zou.
But, Mistress, I will have
Togo all the way down
to the kitchen!
Yeah?
And I have to sit here Ina
bathtub full of tepid water
until you get back.
Now scoot, scoot.
Oui.
Sacrebleu.
Arr, ye dogs.
We have come for your booty.
Oh, no, please, please, Mr.
Big Bad Pirate,
please don't pillage my booty!
Zou Zou?
Zou Zou, is that you?
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
You wanna blow the
rating on this picture?
Hmm.
Finders keepers.
Where have I seen
this thing before?
Oh.
Come on, you're
dripping with jewels.
You're not gonna miss one
little old ring, are you?
( Screaming )
Zou Zou, you scared the
caca-doodie out of me!
Shh!
( Screaming )
Haven't you ever heard of knocking?
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to startle you.
I'm Lady Roxana.
Oh, and I'm Elvira.
Hey, what do you know?
The lady and the tramp!
( Coughing )
I think this is a
piece of your lung.
Ew.
Thank you.
I... I just came to apologize
for my ghastly behavior
earlier this evening.
I was just so shocked
by your appearance.
Yeah, well, most people are,
but they usually don't have
quite such a strong reaction.
For a moment, I thought that you
were my Aunt Elura,
risen from the grave!
Yeah, I seem to be getting
that a lot lately.
So, Roxana,
is it true that you
also have the curse?
Yes, I'm afraid I do.
Really?
And you still manage to
look so fresh all over.
Uncle Vladimere says there is no...
escape!
From the family curse.
Hey, cheer up.
I mean, maybe it's like hair loss
and it'll skip a generation.
No!
Uncle Vladimere says
I am destined to
remain within these
dark castle walls
for the rest of my short...
happy...
life.
"Uncle Vladimere says,
Uncle Vladimere says."
You know, girl, I don't wanna
go sticking my nose in
where it don't belong,
but if I were you, I would
just pack my little bags,
forget about what
Uncle Vladimere says,
and get the hell on out
of Castle Hellsubus.
Oh, if only I could.
Well, what's stopping
you... your legs painted on?
Where will I go, what would I do?
We leave for Paris in the morning,
you could come with us, no?
Uh, no, actually, where we're going
is kind of an adults-only
thing and...
No.
( Coughing )
Of course, I... I...
I understand.
( Hacking )
All right, all right,
you can go with us.
Just be sure to have your
stuff ready tonight,
'cause we're leaving first
thing in the morning.
Oh, thank you, Elvira,
you're wonderful!
Good night.
( All screaming )
What do you want?
I just came to see if
you needed anything
before you retire.
A cup of warm milk, perhaps?
You know, actually, a cup of
warm milk sounds kinda good.
Thanks.
Very well.
I'll have the maid milk the goat.
Um... You know, on
second thought,
just send up a bottle
of scotch and a straw.
( Clanking noises )
( snoring )
( screaming )
Oh, what... Mistress, it's me!
Zou Zou, what the
hell are you doing?
Listen!
I'm scared!
Zou Zou, that's just the
grinding and clanking noise
that, you know, instruments
of torture make.
( Whimpering )
All right, all right, I'll
throw on something skimpy
and head down to the dungeon.
Let's see.
Now where's the secret door?
They always have one of those.
( Grunting )
Oh!
( Rat squeaking )
Oh, hello.
( Footsteps approaching )
Is somebody in there?
Hello?
Roxana, is that you?
Oh, I just saw the light on in here
and I was wondering what
you were doing down here.
You know, I wanted to
talk to you about...
( squeaking )
Uh, careful, that thing
might go off in your hand.
Oh, you startled me.
If you're looking for
something to steal,
there's really not much here.
I already checked.
Oh, sorry.
Lord Hellsubus' pistol
needed cleaning.
Allow me to introduce
myself, madam.
How does he do that?
Weird.
I am Adrian, the stable master.
I often come here secretly.
Books are my greatest
pleasure and as you can see,
the master has a
magnificent collection.
Of what?
Books.
Oh, books.
Yeah, I hadn't noticed.
I'm constantly trying
to better myself.
It's working.
And who, may I ask, are you?
Oh, me?
I'm just Elvira.
You know, house guest, bon vivant,
entertainer extraordinaire.
I'm just here for the night.
But then, a lot can
happen in a night.
Woo, Lord have mercy.
It is warm in here, isn't it?
( Gasping )
Your gown! Ow, ow, ow!
Are you all right?
Is the fire out?
Honey, the fire's
just getting started.
I mean, it must have been a cinder
that landed on my nightgown.
No, it was no accident.
This house is not a healthy
place for you to be.
Ew, not healthy?
I have been scratching
myself a lot lately.
And I'm sure Lord Hellsubus
has not been the most
gracious of hosts.
Duh, that's the understatement
of the 19th century.
Since the death of his first wife,
he has not been feeling himself.
Too bad.
It might relieve a
lot of that tension.
I'm afraid the poor
man is grief-stricken
ever since the Lady Elura
committed suicide.
Committed suicide?
Why would anybody living
here at Sunnybrook Farm
want to kill themselves?
The master blames
himself for her death.
Me, I blame the Hellsubus curse.
Oh, you poor darling!
But I had nothing to do with it.
I don't care.
I mustn't be found here!
Get behind the curtain, quick!
Yeah, good idea.
I thought I heard voices.
Oh, yeah, you and everybody
else in this bug house.
A spider.
( Dog barking )
( rooster crowing )
Hello?
Can anybody help me with my bags?
Zou Zou?
Zou Zou!
I'm coming!
Zou Zou, what do I pay you for?
But, Mistress, you have
not paid me in months.
Oh, right.
Oh!
I'm ready to go, Elvira.
Elvira?
Mistress, do you need some help?
No.
No, I don't need any help.
Do I look like I need help?
Get rid of that damn cake.
Merci.
Where's that coach that
quack promised us?
I tried to tell you, Mistress, Dr.
Bradley has the emergency!
Emergency?
What about my emergency?
He said something about
people in the village
dying of the plague.
Plague-shmague.
I have a show to do in Paris.
Oh, some people are so selfish.
Huh?
Oh, Adrian.
Uh, I've got an idea.
You two wait right here.
Mistress, where are you going?
If I'm not back in an hour...
wait another hour.
Oh.
Ooh!
Adrian!
( Cawing )
( cawing )
( gasping )
Ahh!
Oh!
( Screaming )
Oh, it's you.
Oh, you scared the hell out of me.
Would that it was
otherwise, my dear.
They've struck again.
What, gophers?
No, grave robbers,
in a never-ending search for
the Hellsubus family jewels.
Oh, for the love of God, why
can't they leave us alone?
Hasn't my family suffered enough?
What manner of fiend
is it that would...
That would desecrate a human grave
in their hunger for mere riches?
Why?
Snap out of it!
God, what are you
going for, an Oscar?
My eyes, my eyes!
Would you mind, my dear,
they're over there.
God.
Here's your precious horse
blinders, you big baby.
You don't understand.
My... my eyes are tortured by
all but the faintest of light.
Oh, so you've got a
hangover too, huh?
No, I suffer from acute
ocular sensitivity, my dear.
Too bad.
Listen, you know, your friend Dr.
Bradley
stood me up this morning,
so I was wondering if Adrian the
stable boy could give me a ride.
Oh, frailty, thy name is woman.
Look, I just thought
you were Adrian,
that's why I was following you.
I know.
You do?
Don't tell me you're psychic, too.
No, I heard your footsteps.
Each and everyone of them echo.
Echo? Echo.
Echo.
My hearing's hyper-sensitive, too.
I hear everything,
each cry in the night,
the deafening whisper of
woodworm devouring the coffins,
the scratching of rats'
claws upon the stone, I...
I hear it all.
( Howling )
What's that? What?
( Howling )There it is again!
Really, what does it sound like?
Kinda like, "ah-woo"!
Ah!
Oh, an animal, perhaps.
Wolves attracted by the
scent of rotting flesh.
Wolves?
Maybe we should head back to the...
( howling )
My beloved wife's grave.
She passed away ten years
ago this... this very day.
( Vladimere )Oh, Elura.
So beautiful, so young,
so full of life.
But as I carried her over the
threshold of Castle Hellsubus
on our wedding day, a strange
darkness befell her.
Soon after, she took to her bed.
She would neither eat nor sleep.
I tried everything to cheer her up.
Each night, Elura took
to wandering the halls
of Castle Hellsubus,
listening to the accursed
voices of the demented souls
emanating from within
its blood-soaked walls.
( Woman screaming )
I prayed that I might rescue her
from this infernal nightmare,
but aided by the corrupting
powers of diabolical cunning,
she eluded me.
And then one night,
those demonic deceivers
of suicidal destruction
imposed their poisonous and
cankerous will upon this
sweet, unblemished child
of innocence and grace
and ordered her to climb
to the top of the tower.
And then... to jump.
( Fabric tearing )
( thud )
We were married for just one year.
Well, you know what they say.
I mean, 50% of all
marriages end in divorce,
so it wouldn't have worked
out anyway, probably.
Are you okay?
It's you!
You!
Me, me, me, what? Elura!
Elura!
No, Elvira, Elvira, Elvira.
I'll send you back to hell!
Oh!
Ooh!
Oh, oh...
Oh, that smarts, what happened?
Uh, you don't remember?
No, I must have undergone
some kind of blackout.
Yeah, yeah... Uh,
you tripped.
( Howling )
You know, I'm a little sheepish
when it comes to wolves.
What do you say we head on
back to the castle, okay?
Oh, yes, good idea.
Oh!
Oh, thank you, my dear.
I think I might just go upstairs
and rest for awhile.
Okay, you do that.
And while you're at it, you
might want to grab an icepack.
Yes.
Ah-ah-ah!
Hold it right there.
Mutton stew.
Mm, mm.
Whoa, dude.
Somebody went a little
heavy on the Tabasco.
This is my husband's
chamber pot, madam.
( Rumbling )
( clock chiming )
Disturbing, yes,
but perfectly harmless,
I assure you.
Oh, yeah, no problemo.
I'm from California.
So, as I was saying, I
was in the village,
cleaning out the
pustular, runny sores
of this poor old woman
and I said to her,
"Madam, I believe you
have the plague."
And she said, "Oh, no, sir,
I don't have the plague."
And just at that moment,
her ear dropped off.
Roll?
I can assure you, Ema,
it was rousing good fun.
Bradley, you always have
the most amusing stories.
Mmm, gee.
This looks... delicious.
It's gruel.
Yeah, damn straight it's cruel.
I mean, I was really hungry.
No, madam, it's hot gruel.
That's... It's fine.
I'm afraid those of
the Hellsubus clan
can consume only the
most pallid mash,
wear only the softest of clothing,
tolerate only the
faintest of light.
You see...
My husband and Roxana
suffer from certain
peculiarities oftem perament.
Yeah, where I come from,
they call it hypochondria.
Pardon?
I said...
Maybe it's just all in their mind.
Precisely.
And when something is
in someone's mind,
it is more real, more
powerful than any mere...
physical malady.
Yeah, right.
Like there's something
going on in my mind.
Well now, shall we see?
What do you know about hypnosis?
It's a bunch of hooey.
I once did a show with
Ivan the Incredible,
he tried to hypnotize me and
make me bark like a dog.
And did it work?
Well, by the time he was done,
he was the one who was
sitting up and begging.
( Barking )
Girlfriend.
I assure you, Elvira,
the powers of hypnotism
are very real.
Allow me to demonstrate.
Look deeply into my eyes.
Trust me, I'm a doctor.
Wish I had a peso for every
time I heard that old line.
Give your will over to mine.
Woo.
Your hands are melting into mine.
Soon, very soon, they will
become one with mine.
Yeah, just watch the
nails, will you?
Close your eyes.
You will try, you will try,
but you will not be able.
You will try very soon,
you will try now,
but you will not, you
cannot move them!
Will you please hold it down?
I'm just trying to sleep here.
Is she hypnotized?
No, I am not hypno...
( snoring )
Elvira.
You're a little girl, very happy,
so young, so happy,
so very, very happy.
It's all brightness
and butterflies.
They're a wonder to behold.
See them.
See them?
( High-pitched voice )I just
love butterflies ever so much.
Why look, there's one on a flower.
Reach out, Elvira, you
can almost touch it.
Reach out...
Oh, it's a bee, it stung you!
Ow, ow!
Ow!
No, no, no tears, Elvira.
There's no reason to weep.
( Thundering )
( Elura's voice )Don't weep for me.
Weep for Vladimere.
I have come to wreak my vengeance.
Oh!
( Normal voice )Wow, who
turned out the lights?
See, I told you that hypnotism
thing was a bunch of hooey.
Ow.
I'm... I'm afraid I'm
feeling a bit "unstab-Le."
Speaking of "unstab-Le"... stable,
where's Lord Loco anyway?
( Thundering )
( piano playing )
So plague or no plague,
your coach is picking
me up tomorrow, right?
Oh, absolutely.
I assure you, Elvira,
you won't be spending another
night in Castle Hellsubus.
Happy anniversary, Elura.
Poor guy's had a tough day.
Yes, poor Vladimere.
I don't believe I've ever
seen him looking so morose.
I mean, who wouldn't be
with this dirge playing?
Move over, honey.
Let's see if we can't turn
that frown upside down.
* Many years ago when
I was so small *
* I slipped into a music hall
* How was Ito know curiosity *
* Would cost me my... virginity? *
* In a single night I
learned all the facts *
* About the birds and
bees and tit for tat *
* I remember seven
Turkish acrobats *
* Who taught mean unnatural act *
Come on!
* I was asked to play
with the entire band *
* I had them all right in my hand *
* The pianist confessed to me
* There was a horse
in his family tree *
* A contortionist needed
to get his kicks *
* Forcing little me to
do the Chinese split *
* Girlfriend the trained
dogs were quite a treat *
* They thought moi was
a bitch in heat *
Grr!
Hit it!
* I was gagged and bound
by a psycho clown *
* I'm not even married but
I've been tied down *
* By the way the jugglers
were living dolls *
* And they taught me how to
juggle all their balls *
* I learned how to
expose my derriere *
* Show my legs and bam
* Get them in the air
* Yes I often stop
thinking to recall *
* Life is like a music hall.
Yeah!
( Snoring )
( Elura )Vladimere...
Vladimere... Who...
Who is it?
Who's there?
Vladimere!
Vladimere...
Oh!
Vladimere, what is it?
I saw her... it was her.
Who, man?
Whom did you see?
I... I saw... I saw...
No one.
Nothing, I...
I must have been dreaming.
( Speaking gibberish )
All of you!
Oh... oh.
What... What?
What... what happened?
Uh, you... tripped again.
You gotta lay off of that absinthe.
Thank you.
That ring!
Where did you get that ring?
Uh, this old thing?
I just... found it in my room.
It was Elura's!
Her wedding ring... you took it!
Sheesh, calm down, will you?
Here, you can have it.
Too tacky for me, anyway.
No, no... No, get it
away, get it away!
Will you make up your mind?
Elura was wearing that ring...
when I buried her.
Ew.
Don't even think about it.
Then it's true!
It is true!
She's alive!
Vladimere, you know very
well that's not possible.
Well, there's only
one way to find out.
Oh, here, let me
help you with that.
Mmm... Here, here.
All spic and span.
I'll get the rest later.
Almost got it.
( Grunting )
Oh, my God!
It's true!
She is alive!
Girl, you are starting
to get on my last nerve.
Good Lord.
No heartbeat.
Mirror?
No breath, either!
I'm afraid she's quite... dead.
Well, at least we'll get
some use out of that coffin.
Poor Roxana.
She's found peace at last.
For a member of the Hellsubus line,
even death can bring no peace.
Oh!
If only it were me instead of her.
Yes, if only it was you.
Yes, if only... it was.
Yes, if... only.
Must you close the casket
so soon, Vladimere?
Yeah, boy, you guys don't
waste any time, do you?
I mean, the body's
not even cold yet.
It's time for Roxana
to join the rest of
the Hellsubus clan.
Come.
Why, why, why?
She was so young and so...
Young!
Roxana!
We hardly knew ye!
She was a good girl...
she never "hoit" nobody!
You're with the
angels now, darling.
Oh!
Oh, man, I don't know about
the rest of you guys,
but I need a drink.
( Creaking )
( dog barking )
( iron clanking )
Hello?
Adrian?
Adrian.
That's quite a big hammer
you're swinging there.
Elvira.
I was just shoeing a horse
for your trip tomorrow.
Yeah, well, I thought
I'd just bring you
a little something
to remember me by.
A book!
Elvira, you are as generous
as you are beautiful.
Ah, "Kama... Sutra."
Yeah.
Have you read it already?
I'm afraid I haven't.
Oh, too bad.
I hope there aren't
too many big words.
Yeah, well, don't worry about it.
I mean, it's mostly pictures.
Here, let me show you
the first chapter.
I'm not sure I follow.
Oh, read on.
( Humming )
( gasping )
( glass breaking )
Mmm... Nicholai.
Elura... At long last.
My brother would have my
head if he knew about this.
Vladimere will never find out.
No!
( Screaming )
Help me... help me!
No!
Help me!
No, help me, Elvira!
( Screaming )
( grunting )
( muffled cries )
Who's there?
Zou Zou, is that you?
What do you think you
are, a freaking parakeet?
( Muffled cries )
Oh, you will not believe
this weird dream I had.
I think that Elura's buried
alive down here somewhere
and I think that I know who...
Oh!
How did you two get down here?
This dungeon has been
locked for 100 years.
Yeah, right, and I
suppose you've never
been down here either.
Madam, I swear to you, I've
never before set foot in...
in this place.
Look, little Lord Paranoid,
I didn't say you did.
I just said that if you are the
only person with the key...
It was in this foul dungeon
that my great-grandfather,
Lord Lucian Hellsubus,
committed unspeakable
acts of torture.
Ooh, like, "Whip me,
baby, whip me"?
In a nutshell, yes.
Ouch.
Oh, my God!
This is it!
It's this wall!
It's... It's the
wall from my dream!
What on Earth are you
talking about, my dear?
It wasn't a dream... it
really happened!
Elura didn't kill herself.
You killed her!
I had to do it, Elura.
Don't you see?
You wanted to leave me.
Leave this castle.
No one in the Hellsubus
clan can ever leave,
as I told dear Roxana.
You mean Roxana was...
Yes, about to be buried alive, too.
That's another unfortunate
Hellsubus family trait.
Catalepsy.
Fear of cats?
It's a condition which
completely parallels
the look of death.
You mean, then...
She was...
And you knew?
Yes.And...
Yes, I'm afraid... I'm
afraid burying people alive
is another unfortunate
Hellsubus family trait.
And now, Elvira,
it's time to send you back
from whence you came.
To hell!
No!
I shall rip your black heart out
and feed it to the carrion crows!
Sheesh, you'd think he
would have learned by now.
( Door opening )
Ah, there he is.
Pretty as a picture.
It is rather amusing,
isn't it, dearest?
Your first wife,
Elura, an adulteress.
Your brother Nicholai,
an adulterer.
Your second wife, an adulteress.
Your trusted doctor and
friend, an adulterer!
Oy, mate!
( Whistling )
No, he's completely
off it this time.
We've done it.
Look at the pathetic milksop.
He'd be better off dead.
Yeah, but we wouldn't,
would we, love?
And now that he's off his nut,
you and I are completely in control
of the Hellsubus family fortune.
And no one will question
his need for constant care
from his trusted doctor,
with the help of his
faithful wife, of course.
I hope you've learned your lesson.
Never sign a pre-nuptual agreement!
( Creaking )
Elvira.Oh.
How nice of you to join us.
( Elvira )Hi there.
Um, I was just leaving, so
I'll see you guys around!
No, you don't, love.
Oh, no.
Don't leave, Elvira.
The fun is just beginning.
Yoo-hoo, Elvira!
Your carriage awaits!
Elvira!
Hmm, maybe she's upstairs.
God, it's great, isn't it?
Look at the size of that rack.
Elvira, I must confess, I
find the sight of you in pain
particularly arousing.
Ow!
Careful, Bradley,
or you'll be next.
I swear, you guys, I
didn't hear a thing.
Ow!
About you and the doctor
having an affair.
Oh!
And... and you trying to
make Vladimere insane
so that you could steal
the family jewels.
Ow, ow!
Nicholai!
Oh, Vladimere.
How are you?
I must confess you're
looking better.
Thank you, dear brother.
That's very kind.
I think that... Brother?
Vladimere, whatever
on Earth do you mean?
It was always you, Nicholai! No!
Always you! No...
First you stole my toys...
Then our dear mother's sweet love,
and then finally, my beloved Elura.
You must die, Nicholai!
You must die!
Vladimere, no!
As for you,
you too will suffer for
your faithlessness, Elura.
But, husband, I'm
not Elura, I'm Ema!
Before this day is out, you
will beg me to release you
from the unimaginable hell
into which you're
about to be plunged.
Die, die in agony, Elura!
( Screaming )
I'm not Elura!
She is!
Oh, that Ema!
She's such a kidder.
Oh, forgive me.
My slutty adulteress, darling.
Hey, don't call me darling.
Let me release you
from your bondage.
Uh, yeah, that'd be great,
because I'm really not into
this kinda thing anyway.
Oh no, no, no, no, no!
No, the other way, the
other way, the other way!
Please forgive me, my dear,
but old habits die hard.
Yeah.
Wow.
Elvira?
It's your stable stud.
Time to go to the train...
( Elvira screaming )
( Elvira )Help me!
( Vladimere )Do you know
where you are, Elura?
Shall I tell you where
you are, Elura?
Would you stop with
the Elura stuff?
Elura is dead.
I'm Elvira, remember?
Life is like a music hall, yeah!
Oh, prepare to enter hell, Elura,
the netherworld, the
abode of the dead,
the infernal regions.
That place of torment,
pandemonium, abandonment,
that vast unbottomed
place that's...
really, really hot.
Araka.
Gehenna.
Hades.
The boundless... All right, all
right, I got it, I got it.
Jeez, will somebody take
away his thesaurus?
Don't interrupt when
I'm on a roll, Elura.
Elvira!
Where are you?
Adrian!
I'm in here, in the dungeon!
Oh, Elura.
In this place, no one
can hear you scream.
No!
Adrian, help!
Elvira!
Adrian! Elvira!
Now let me present for
your final enjoyment,
the pit... and
the pendulum!
Oh, my God!
My God!
Adrian, Adrian, hurry!
Adrian!
Ah, ah!( laughing )
Where are you?
Elvira!
( laughing )
Adrian, I haven't got all day here!
Who is that laughing?
Hurry!
Really, hurry up!
I'm not kidding!
Adrian, help!
Oh, oh!
Help, help!
Oh!
Hold on!
I can't!
I have to do everything myself?
Ah!
Oh!
You can never escape me, Elura.
( Elura's voice )No, it is you who
will never escape me, Vladimere!
My eyes!
( Normal voice )Whoa, talk about
yourdys functional families.
Oh!
My eyes, my eyes!
Help, Elura!
( Screaming )
Elvira! Adrian!
You came too late!
Again.
Don't worry!
We're safe now.
( Muffled cries )
Oh, yeah, almost forgot.
( Adrian )It's your maid, Zou Zou.
What to do?
Here!
Keep your shirt on.
We've got everything under cont...
Oh.
Here, give me your hand!
That's it.
Come on, come on, hurry!
Move it!
Wait for me!
Mistress!
( Glass breaking )
Hurry!
This place is coming down!
Bradley?
Where are you going?
Save me!
Ema, there's no time!
It's you or the family jewels!
If I ever get out of here,
I'm going to kill you!
Right, it's the jewels then.
Damn you, Bradley!
Damn you!
( Elvira )Wait, wait!
Save me!
Oh, my God!
It's Ema!
She's still alive.
I must go back.
No, no, you can't go back in there.
What are you, nuts?
You don't understand, Elvira.
I'm Ema's illegitimate
half-brother.
No!
( Adrian )Bye!
Come back, you crazy bastard!
My jewels!
Ema!
Ooh, ow!
Ooh!
Thank you, Elvira.
Oh, my God!
That's... that's incredible!
What, Mistress?
That the spirit of Elura
is finally set free?
No, that... that we can afford
such a groovy special effect!
Oh, oui!
( Wolf howling )
Remind me never to hitch a ride
in a strange coach again.
( Horses neighing )
( whimpering )
Yoo-hoo!
( Tires screeching )
( horse neighing )
Ladies, may I offer you a ride?
Whoa, it's like déjà
vu all over again!
So anyway, we're lucky we even
got out of there with our lives.
Oui, oui, if it was not for Elvira,
I would be squished
like a French grape.
Where did you say this castle was?
Just there in the
Carpathian Mountains.
Yeah, Castle Hellsubus,
you ever heard of it?
You could not possibly
have visited there.
Hello, I think I know where I
just spent the worst weekend
of my whole life.
Castle Hellsubus was
destroyed 100 years ago.
( Wolf howling )
( horses neighing )
( laughing )