[cheerful music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Harvey ♪
[cheerful music]
♪ ♪
♪ Harvey ♪
[cheerful music]
♪ ♪
♪ Harvey ♪
[cheerful music]
♪ ♪
[air horn blares]
- Today has been truly magical,
dear.
[air horn blares]
Ahh!
No!
Take her!
[air horn blares]
- Jared.
- Ahh!
[air horn blares]
- [laughs]
Oh, my gosh.
[air horn blares]
That was amazing.
- ♪ Mi, mi, mi, mi, mi, mi, mi ♪
[air horn blares]
♪ This banjo will impress the
waitress at the steakhouse ♪
[air horn blares]
- Heh-heh-heh, heh-heh
Huh?
[air horn blares]
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
- Ahh, fine.
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
I'm here to repossess the banjo
you rented.
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
- But I was just getting good.
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
♪ Twinkle twinkle ♪
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
Uhhh...augh!
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
Well, you've killed a man's
dream.
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
- And I'll be back for that
rental hat.
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
- Gasp.
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
- This is so sad.
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
- [sniffing]
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
I can sense something else I
own...nearby.
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
- Uh...uh-oh.
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
- [laughing]
- [panting]
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
Oh, gosh.
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
You get back here.
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
[growling]
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
[air horn blares]
Ahh!
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
When I get ahold of you I'm
gonna...augh!
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
[growls]
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
Pretty nails?
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
Really?
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
- I could do this all day, dude.
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
- Ugh,
you're a real stubborn brat.
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
- I know, right?
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
- You want a job?
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
- Hmm?
What kind of job?
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
[cheerful music]
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
♪ ♪
- Randl, you know I can see you,
right?
- This is my storage room.
It's where I keep all the stuff
I need to rent out.
- This is my storage room.
- Kinda empty.
What are you renting, air?
- This is my storage room.
- Ha-ha, funny.
Shut up.
- This is my storage room.
People rent my stuff and don't
return it,
- This is my storage room.
so I have to go and take them
back.
- This is my storage room.
That's called "repossession."
- I want our stuff back.
- This is my storage room.
We gotta shave their heads and
throw raw chickens at 'em
- This is my storage room.
till they cry.
- No, Ma, that's weird.
- This is my storage room.
- This job seems super easy.
I'm in.
- This is my storage room.
- Bup-bup-bup.
Out there, you do what I tell
you.
- This is my storage room.
I'm just bringing you along
'cause some people might feel
- This is my storage room.
uncomfortable hitting children,
might slow somebody down.
- This is my storage room.
- Or they might hesitate to slap
a squishy old man.
- This is my storage room.
- Shut up.
- No, you shut up.
- This is my storage room.
[both arguing]
- Aw.
- This is my storage room.
- All right, ladies,
imagine your legs are confident
windmills.
- This is my storage room.
Do you feel the burn?
- Oh, man.
This is exhausting.
- This is my storage room.
- Good job.
Let's take a 30-second break.
- This is my storage room.
- All right.
I'm gonna treat myself to some
cheese and crackers.
- This is my storage room.
- There it is,
my workout bike,
- This is my storage room.
rented by Easy,
the exterminator.
- This is my storage room.
This guy's crazy.
- This guy?
- This is my storage room.
Come on.
He's vanilla puddin'.
- This is my storage room.
- You kids think everything is
pudding.
- This is my storage room.
See for yourself.
He's armed to the teeth with the
nastiest extermination gear
- This is my storage room.
from the internet.
- Randl, I'm sleepy.
- This is my storage room.
It's past my bedtime.
- Ma, you're our getaway driver,
so stay sharp.
- This is my storage room.
- You stay sharp.
- So how're we gonna get past
his defenses?
- This is my storage room.
- We just need a distraction.
[telephone ringing]
- This is my storage room.
- Hello, Easy
Extermination Services.
- This is my storage room.
- Yes, hello, is your
refrigerator running?
- This is my storage room.
- Excuse me?
I don't understand.
- This is my storage room.
I have four ziplock bags
full of chili.
- This is my storage room.
I need to freeze them,
or they'll go bad.
- This is my storage room.
- Um, ok, ma'am, let's back up.
What kind of chili are we
talking about here?
- This is my storage room.
- Let's clear a path.
- On it.
Pffft, hey Randl, look.
- This is my storage room.
- What?
- Did you rent him this?
- This is my storage room.
[laughs]
- A box full of doll heads?
- This is my storage room.
Wow, this is dark.
- [laughs]
- This is my storage room.
- Oh, hello, intruders.
- Ahh!
- This is my storage room.
- I didn't know there was a
comedy show happening
- This is my storage room.
in my living room.
Well, you've invaded my home, so
I guess I have no choice
- This is my storage room.
but to defend myself.
- Whoa, whoa, there.
- This is my storage room.
You signed this contract months
ago.
- This is my storage room.
[gasps]
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't see a contract anywhere.
- This is my storage room.
- Uh, hey, you can't hurt kids.
It's a law.
- This is my storage room.
- Pthew!
- Ahh!
- This is my storage room.
Did you just spit one of my doll
heads at me?
- This is my storage room.
- Nice shot, kid.
Now, let's get out of here.
- This is my storage room.
- Get back here.
- Where's our ride?
- Ma!
- This is my storage room.
- [snoring]
- You guys scratched my
contacts.
- This is my storage room.
- Move over, you old bat.
[tires squealing]
- This is my storage room.
- Whew, I really...I really need
to exercise.
- This is my storage room.
I...
- Whoo-hoo!
- Yeah!
- This is my storage room.
Hey, that was some quick
thinking for a dumb kid.
- This is my storage room.
- That's the nicest thing you've
ever said to me.
- This is my storage room.
- Where am I?
[funky music]
- This is my storage room.
♪ ♪
- Well, I gotta admit it.
We make a pretty good team.
- Hey, what's that over there?
- Well, I gotta admit it.
- Oh, don't get any ideas.
That repo is the white whale of
all repos.
- Well, I gotta admit it.
It's a one-of-a-kind lamp, kept
in a fortress,
- Well, I gotta admit it.
guarded by a ravenous beast,
my greatest treasure.
- Well, I gotta admit it.
- Whoa.
We have to do it.
- Well, I gotta admit it.
- Sorry, kid.
Some things are just impossible.
- Well, I gotta admit it.
- You're sounding like a real
old man right now.
- Well, I gotta admit it.
What if you woke up tomorrow and
the white whale was here?
- Well, I gotta admit it.
- Yeah, that would be nice,
but it just can't be done.
- Well, I gotta admit it.
I'm gonna order food.
- Let's see who rented this
white whale.
- Well, I gotta admit it.
Oh,
this is gonna be easy.
- Well, I gotta admit it.
Ahh! My lamp!
Thief!
- Well, I gotta admit it.
- [chuckling]
- Rahhh!
- Well, I gotta admit it.
- Crystal, get her!
- [chuckling]
- Well, I gotta admit it.
Whew, man, that was wild.
Oh, sweet, you're still up.
- Well, I gotta admit it.
Oh, man, you should've seen
Princess' face.
- Well, I gotta admit it.
- I've been worried sick.
You just left without sayin'
anything.
- Well, I gotta admit it.
- Um, yeah.
So?
- Well, I gotta admit it.
Look, I brought you your white
whale,
- Well, I gotta admit it.
that impossible repo that was
actually super easy.
- Well, I gotta admit it.
- That is not the white whale.
- Huh?
- Well, I gotta admit it.
- That's the white whale.
- Wait, was that there before?
- Yeah, and you would've seen it
if you took a second to look
before being reckless.
- Wait, was that there before?
You realize you just stole
something, right?
- Wait, was that there before?
- So?
So you could go to jail.
- Wait, was that there before?
And now my business is at risk.
Y-y-y-you know what?
- Wait, was that there before?
You're fired.
- What?
- Wait, was that there before?
- I can't have you runnin'
around causing trouble.
- Wait, was that there before?
Now, get outta here,
and return that lamp.
- Wait, was that there before?
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Wait, was that there before?
- Fine.
I don't even care.
- Wait, was that there before?
You're just angry because I had
the guts to try something
- Wait, was that there before?
impossible, and you were too
scared.
- Wait, was that there before?
Oh, pfft, I'm not scared.
That's ridiculous.
- Wait, was that there before?
- Ugh,
I can't believe that guy,
- Wait, was that there before?
the nerve to fire me.
So ungrateful,
and he thinks I'm reckless?
- Wait, was that there before?
Well, how about I just keep this
lamp and then he goes to jail?
- Wait, was that there before?
- [whimpering]
- All right, I'll return it so
he doesn't get in trouble.
- Wait, was that there before?
[sighs]
[knocks]
- Welly, well, well, the thief
returns.
[knocks]
- [sighs]
I'm sorry I stole your lamp.
[knocks]
Apology, guilt, remorse...
uhh...uhh...
[knocks]
uhh...ahhhh...ohhh...
- ♪ Ohhhhhm ♪
[knocks]
- I mean, I apologize for
hurting your feelings.
[knocks]
I didn't mean to do that.
So, um...
I wanna purify my...spirit.
[knocks]
Do you have crystals for that?
- Ah, I had zoned out for a bit,
[knocks]
but then I heard you say
"crystals."
[knocks]
I'll bring you some.
They're right upstairs, so I'll
just turn around--
[knocks]
- Wait, wait.
Can you get the crystals you
have in your basement...
[knocks]
really far down?
And maintain eye contact with
me.
[knocks]
- Ah, an energy transference.
Ahh...cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha.
[knocks]
I'll be back.
- Randl,
he's gone.
[knocks]
- Good thinkin' back there.
- Um, listen--
- Hey, so--
[knocks]
- Did you--I mean--
- Yeah, I, uh--what you said--
[knocks]
- And I--back there--
- I just mean--
[knocks]
- You know.
both: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay. Okay. Yeah.
[knocks]
- So how did you get past
Princess?
[knocks]
- Who?
- Daddy.
[knocks]
Daddy, we're out of tanning
lotion.
[knocks]
Huh?
[sniffing]
[knocks]
- Oh, no.
She's caught our scent.
[knocks]
- Ew, I smell less attractive
people.
[knocks]
- [gasps] Hide.
- [sniffing]
[knocks]
both: Whew.
- Well, it's over, kid.
That thing has razor-sharp
senses.
both: Whew.
No gettin' past it.
- Ugh, we're so close.
both: Whew.
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
- [sniffing]
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
- Hey, Princess.
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
- Why are you always in my
house?
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
[growling]
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
- [gasps]
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
- Huh? Wha?
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
Who--who is this beautiful
angel?
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
Oh,
you wanna fight?
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
[grunting]
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
- That should keep her busy.
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
- Usually, I only use these on
demons.
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
Ahh!
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
- This is a rental.
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
It was due two years ago.
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
- But it's my Princess'
favorite.
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
I'm not letting you take it.
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
- You wanna play that way?
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
Climb on, kid.
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
both: Ahh!
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
- Halt in the name of Dark Mana.
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
Ohh!
I've got an idea.
- Wait.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
[engine turning over]
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
- Did someone call for a ride?
[coughing]
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
- Ma?
What are you doing here?
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
- I've been sleeping out here
for two days.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
[tires squealing]
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
- Ahh, darn it!
- Ah, my crystals.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
Oh, my.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
- So we did it, kid.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
We got the white whale.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
Well, uh, I have all my stuff
back now, so...
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
look's like I'm all set.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
- Looks like.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
- But...uh...
maybe I'll hire you
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
for more repos later.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
- Okay, sure.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
I mean...whatever, I guess.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
- I like you, dear.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
You remind me of myself before I
burned off my fingerprints.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
- So long, kid.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
[air horn blares]
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
Hey,
you have to return that.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
Ehh, whatever.
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
- [laughing]
- Now what?
It's totally stuck.
- Attention strong people of
Littlebark Grove.
Come one, come all if you think
you can arm wrestle
- Attention strong people of
Littlebark Grove.
the twins of terror.
- Attention strong people of
Littlebark Grove.
- Rawr.
- Attention strong people of
Littlebark Grove.
- Whoo!
- Hooo!
- [grunting]
- Whoo!
- Hooo!
- Aww, I guess I lost.
- Whoo!
- Hooo!
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
- Hooo!
- [grunting]
- Whoo!
- Hooo!
[together]
Boo!
- Whoo!
- Hooo!
- [grunting]
- Whoo!
- Hooo!
all: [groaning]
- Wow.
Fee and Foo have mad muscles.
all: [groaning]
both: [laughing]
[cheerful music]
all: [groaning]
♪ ♪
- Any questions?
[together]
Dang. Whoa. Oh, my gosh.
- Any questions?
- And if y'all like that,
then check out Foo's guns.
- Any questions?
- [grunting]
- Dang it all.
You guys are amazing.
- Any questions?
- Yeah, you both are the best at
arm wrestling.
- Any questions?
- Well, they can't both be the
best.
- Any questions?
all: [gasp]
- What did you say?
Huh?
- Any questions?
You got doubt in my boys?
- Alls I'm saying is that it'd
be neat to know who's better
- Any questions?
at arm wrestling,
Fee or Foo.
- Any questions?
- That's a fair point.
Sorry I lost my temper, bro.
- Any questions?
I'm very passionate about my
boys.
- Any questions?
- Kratz is right.
We've never actually arm
wrestled each other.
- Any questions?
- I don't think anyone's
interested
- Any questions?
in seeing us fight
against one ano--
- Any questions?
- Do it right now!
[together] Yeah. Just do it.
Just do it right now.
- Any questions?
- Nah, Foo and me are like total
equals.
- Any questions?
- We respect each other too much
to go head-to-head.
- Any questions?
- Like, just for a second, let's
try to imagine
- Any questions?
arm wrestling
each other.
- Any questions?
- I'll try my best.
both: [grunting]
- Any questions?
- Nope.
- Can't imagine it.
- Any questions?
- So we'll just never know who's
better?
- Any questions?
I don't know if I can never
know.
- Any questions?
- Hey, everyone,
check this out.
- Any questions?
"The Littlebark arm-wrestlin'
championship."
- Any questions?
You two can compete against
these other guys,
- Any questions?
and then whoever has the most
wins
- Any questions?
will be the best arm wrestler.
- Sounds like a good place
to show our stuff.
- Any questions?
- Yeah,
let's go crush some dreams.
- Any questions?
both: Ahh...ooh!
[chuckling]
- Any questions?
all: [shouting]
- [grunting]
- Pthew!
- Well, this must be the place.
- [grunting]
- Ahh! My arm!
- Holy moly.
- [grunting]
- All right, everybody, uh,
buddy system.
- [grunting]
- This is awesome.
Oh, hey, what's up?
- [grunting]
- Hey, all right.
- Excuse me, sir, where should
we put our coats?
- [grunting]
- [munching]
- Oh.
- [grunting]
- Wow, these kids are huge.
- Yeah, but they still look like
chumps to me.
- [grunting]
- I guess they do look like
chumps, right, Harvey?
- [grunting]
- Guys, can you stop using the
C-H word?
- [grunting]
- Hey, dingus.
- Coach Dinkly?
What are you doing here?
- [grunting]
- What's it look like?
I'm hosting Littlebark's arm
wrestling championship.
- [grunting]
Well, co-hosting with my dad.
- Oh, right, your dad...the
statue.
- [grunting]
- [laughs]
Good one, Dad.
- [grunting]
So what, are you and your little
baby arms gonna enter?
- [grunting]
- Back off, meathead.
Harvey's our coach.
- [grunting]
Foo and me are the ones arm
wrestlin'.
- [grunting]
- Boop.
- I'm just a little concerned.
- [grunting]
There's a lot of big people
here.
- [grunting]
Where are all the kids?
- This is the big league,
full of big people.
- [grunting]
That scare you?
- Nope.
- We're the best.
- [grunting]
- Well, then, let's get out
there and see what you got.
- [grunting]
- Yeah, Fee.
I believe in you.
- [grunting]
- Thanks, guys, but save your
breath.
- [grunting]
I won't need it for this dude
with his stupid snaggletooth
and his weird ears.
- [grunting]
- Ready...
set...
- [grunting]
[bell dings]
[cheers]
- [grunting]
- What the heck?
- Oh, you had an off-day.
- [grunting]
- Thanks, dude.
Now go kick some butt.
- [grunting]
- Hello.
Let's wrestle with our arms.
Oh, no.
- Hello.
- Yeah, I like workin' out,
but I don't want to get too
strong, ya know?
- Hello.
- Uh-huh, uh-uh.
[bell dings]
- Hello.
[cheers and applause]
[bell dings]
- All right, tough guy, gimme
your best--oof!
[bell dings]
Okay, it's just me and--wah!
Okay, seriously, dude, just
gimme a second to--wah!
[bell dings]
Come on.
- So if ya just add a pinch of
cinnamon to your chili,
[bell dings]
you'll
be on your way to tasty town.
[bell dings]
- Whoa.
- Oh, hey,
you're tiny like me.
[bell dings]
[gulps]
- Is this table crooked?
[bell dings]
- Ahh!
[gulps]
- I think this table's crooked.
- [laughs]
[gulps]
[bell dings]
- I believe in you two.
- Yah! Yah! Yah! Yah!
- I know them.
- I believe in you two.
- Ugh, it's impossible to win
with all this light in my eyes.
- I believe in you two.
[bell dings]
- Ahh!
- I believe in you two.
- Ooh.
- [growling]
- I believe in you two.
- [inhales and blows]
- [giggling]
- I believe in you two.
[cheers and applause]
[bell dings]
- Ugh!
- I believe in you two.
[bell dings]
- Augh!
- I believe in you two.
- Ohh.
- Tied for last.
- I believe in you two.
Who's it gonna be?
- I think this whole thing's
rigged.
- I believe in you two.
- You two are doing so bad,
there's literally nobody left
for you to fight.
- I believe in you two.
Do you know what that means?
- We win by default?
- I believe in you two.
- No.
Both of you are gonna compete to
see who's the
- I believe in you two.
ultimate baby
loser of all time.
- I believe in you two.
[laughs]
[together]
The ultimate baby loser?
- I believe in you two.
Oh, no.
- Why is it so bad to be the
ultimate baby loser?
- I believe in you two.
- See for yourself.
[laughter]
- I believe in you two.
- Oh, shut up.
- Okay, we cannot let that
happen to us.
- I believe in you two.
- We gotta make a break for it.
- No one leaves till it's over.
- I believe in you two.
[together]
Heh-heh-heh-heh
- I believe in you two.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yeah! Yeah!
- I believe in you two.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
- Yeah! Do it!
- I believe in you two.
- This is terrible.
I should say
something encouraging.
- I believe in you two.
You can do it!
both: Which one of us?
- I believe in you two.
- Uh...um...both of you?
I don't know.
- I believe in you two.
- All right,
let the match begin.
- I believe in you two.
- Come on!
Tear her apart!
- I believe in you two.
- Yeah, rip his arm off!
- Rip is arm off!
- I believe in you two.
all: [shouting]
- They're not doing anything.
- I believe in you two.
- Come on.
I wanna see some action.
- I believe in you two.
- All right, you two, enough
messing around.
- I believe in you two.
Bob, set the timer.
- Sir, yes, sir.
- I believe in you two.
[grunting]
Phew.
- I believe in you two.
[timer ticking]
- If one of you doesn't give,
- I believe in you two.
you're both gonna be crowned the
ultimate baby loser.
- I believe in you two.
both: [gasp]
[laughter]
- I believe in you two.
boing!
- Augh,
that's horrible.
boing!
I'm not gonna let my sister be
the worst.
boing!
- Foo, what are you doing?
- I'm letting you win the match.
boing!
- What?
Oh, no, you don't.
boing!
I'm gonna take the fall.
- No.
I can't let you be a loser.
boing!
You couldn't handle it.
- You can't handle it.
boing!
You're the emotional one.
- No, I'm not.
boing!
You are.
- Just give up already.
boing!
- Hey, hey, hey.
Keep those elbows on the table,
boing!
or else you'll be ejected from
the game.
boing!
- Wait a minute.
That's it.
boing!
Foo, we have to get kicked out.
It's the only way we can make it
out of here
boing!
without being embarrassed.
- Are you sure this is gonna
work?
boing!
- No.
But do you have a better idea?
boing!
- [gnawing]
Nope.
boing!
- Hey.
What did I just say?
boing!
- Ha, looks like you're gonna
have to kick us out.
boing!
- You bet I will.
Do that 30 more times and you'll
get yourself a yellow card.
boing!
4 of those and you're outta
here.
boing!
- What?
Ugh, we gotta amp it up.
boing!
- Can do.
Whoo!
boing!
- [gnawing]
[growling]
boing!
- Stop that.
You're seven verbal warnings
away from getting a penalty.
boing!
both: Augh.
- Oof!
- Augh!
boing!
- Oof!
- [speaking gibberish]
boing!
- Yeah!
Break the rules!
boing!
Oh, listen to me go.
- Yah!
boing!
- Rah! Rah! Rah! Rah!
- Oh, I'm scared.
boing!
- I've never seen such reckless
arm wrestling.
boing!
[laughter]
- [chuckles]
boing!
Oof!
- Mm-hmm, interesting strategy.
boing!
- Guys,
you're running out of time.
boing!
Hurry up and get disqualified.
- Looks like you'll both be
losers.
boing!
[laughs]
- No one calls us losers.
boing!
Foo, ball.
all: Ahh! Oof! Hey! Oof! Hey!
Augh!
Ugh! Augh! Ugh! Oof! Ugh!
all: Ahh! Oof! Hey! Oof! Hey!
Augh!
- Oh, no! No!
all: Ahh! Oof! Hey! Oof! Hey!
Augh!
Dad!
all: Ahh! Oof! Hey! Oof! Hey!
Augh!
[stammering]
Dad?
all: Ahh! Oof! Hey! Oof! Hey!
Augh!
He's dead.
all: Ahh! Oof! Hey! Oof! Hey!
Augh!
[sobbing]
Oh, no.
all: Ahh! Oof! Hey! Oof! Hey!
Augh!
And it's your fault.
all: Ahh! Oof! Hey! Oof! Hey!
Augh!
You two dinguses are
disqualified.
all: Ahh! Oof! Hey! Oof! Hey!
Augh!
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
Dad?
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
You're alive!
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
[laughs]
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
He good.
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
- Well, guys, you did it.
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
As your coach, I couldn't be
more proud.
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
- Oh, right, you were our coach.
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
- Seeing how the dummy babies
were disqualified,
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
the loser award goes to...
this guy.
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
- Wait, I--I won something?
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
[laughter]
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
- Aw,
Jeremy makes a cute baby.
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
- Come on dudes.
Let's get out of here.
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
So I guess the lesson is, if ya
can't win, then don't play.
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?
- I...I don't know if that's a
good lesson.
I can't believe you killed my--
huh?