You must go back in time,
eliminate Billy and Mandy...
and act as their replacements...
until further instructions are given.
They are not to reach Horror's Hand
before the Lord of Horror.
Now go.
Remember back then, yo,
when we were young and innocent.
We need to get through
that vortex, Irwin.
Maybe we can make things right again
the way they were before...
Horror's Hand.
Yes.
Rats!
Oh, man!
I was so busy watching
the opening credits...
that I forgot to follow those
robots into the path...
through their post-dating
time travel vortex.
Hey, yo, don't worry.
Remember you drew up that schematic
for a time travel machine last night?
We can just build our own
time travel portal, go back through...
and save ourselves from this terrible
future caused by Horror's Hand!
That's right.
Get to work on it right away.
Billy, that's a drawing
of cops fighting dinosaurs.
What? They should be
working together.
We'll just have to wait and
hope that ourselves in the past...
figure out how to stop
the tragic sequence of events...
that led up to this awful future.
But doesn't the fact that we're here
mean that we don't?
You're right, I know.
Time travel is so confusing.
Besides is this future really so bad?
I mean, aside from all
of humanity being enslaved...
by the Lord of Horror.
Mornin', Death!
This is my favorite part of the job.
Reginald Skarr,
I have come for thee.
That's great.
Can you fix the antenna?
My one day off and
Shark Week 's coming in all fuzzy.
No! Reginald Skarr,
I have come for thee.
What?!
But I'm in perfect health.
What? This hole?
Well, it's just a flesh wound.
I don't even know where I got it.
Into the vortex with you.
And don't start cryin'
and drippin' snot all over me.
This robe has got to get me
through the week.
I'm busy, you rotten little munchkins.
Go play in traffic.
We're bored, Grim. We want you
to take us to work with you.
No way, I like to keep my work
life and my home life separate.
I think you misunderstood me.
I meant you will take us
to work with you.
You know, you'd have more friends
if you were little more pleasant.
I don't want more friends.
I have you.
And you promised
to be our best friend forever.
A best friend would definitely
bring us to work if he had a cool job.
Like a gorilla!
Or the Grim Reaper.
Well, I...
We've got a runner!
Aren't you forgetting something?
Was it my deodorant?
Oh no, that's you.
Fine, get on.
I'm OK.
This calls for track number 6.
You can't outrun Death.
That's why I have turbo.
You're not doing this right.
I'm driving.
Girls can't drive.
Everyone knows. Give me the...
Stop pulling.
Totally not my fault.
Time for the big guns.
Or should I say missiles?
I wonder what this one does.
Oh, now I remember.
I can't believe you two
scared off another one.
I've got a quota to meet.
They're dead, Grim.
They'll turn up sooner or later.
Your huggy bear is here
to maul you with love, yo.
Not now, Irwin.
My job could be on the line.
I have a reputation to uphold.
Jobs don't have
to be forever, Grim.
My dad starts a new job
almost every week.
Billy's right, Grim.
I've been fired before.
And it's not bad.
In fact,
I get fired all the time.
Why, just today I got fired
from my job at the Freckle Burger...
for eating all of the paper cups.
What was that, honey?
Nothing, Gladys!
Are you sure?
I could've sworn...
Me not speakee your language.
If you lost that job
at Freckle Burger...
Oh, oh, genie. Yub, yub...
Harold!
The point is, you kids can't be mixing
my business with your pleasure.
I can't keep losin' clients like this.
You're the only one who cares.
Hey, Grim.
How come you got moving zits?
It's the man!
Grim Reaper, you're under arrest
for misusing your powers...
and dereliction of duty.
He said "duty".
Order. Order.
I'll have a double
cheeseburger animal style.
But not if the animal is a porcupine
or a weasel or anything...
'cause then it would hurt
when you put it in your mouth.
Excuse me,
I think there's been a mistake.
Hey, how you doin'?
What is this? Why am I here?
You're here to pay
for abusing your powers.
The Boogey Man? Didn't we banish
you to the Nightmare Realm?
Yeah, but I'm not one to hold a grudge.
Well, maybe you ought to start.
I've never forgiven you for all
the mean stuff you did to me as a kid.
Grim, please. I was kidding.
I totally hold a grudge.
And when I learned
that these baboons...
were causing you to miss
work and abuse your powers...
Well, let's just say that I felt
it was my duty as a citizen...
to crush you and destroy
everything you love.
That's what I would do.
He said "duty".
Don't you find the justice
system fascinating?
What are you talkin' about, Boogey?
I've never abused my powers.
But I'm going to start
if you don't get out of my face.
Where were you when you met
Billy and Mandy?
That was the night these runts
won me in a limbo game.
I see. And where were you
on October 31st?
Well, it was Halloween.
That wasn't my fault.
Me scythe got stolen.
I wasn't anywhere near it...
when those giant pumpkins
wrecked half of Endsville.
Is it not true that not only
was your scythe stolen...
by a headless man wearing
a pumpkin on his neck...
but it was also taken by Billy,
Mandy, Irwin, Billy's father...
Billy's mother, Billy's cousin,
Billy's cat, Dracula...
General Skarr,
Principal Goodvibes, Mrs. Claus...
The Secret Snake Club, the Army,
Scout Troop 701, the Sleaze Tax...
The President, the Mailman,
the Dingleschmit Sisters...
The Boogey Man, a llama
and a turkey salad sandwich...
...hold the mayo?
Well, yeah. But...
He admits to irresponsibly
losing his scythe...
an epic and ancient tool filled
with terrible magics...
beyond mortal understanding
on multiple occasions.
I hate jury duty.
But it's not my fault.
It's these kids.
They're like lint brushes for trouble.
So you have no free will?
You must do what these mere
mortal children say?
Yes. Yes.
We're his bestest friends forever.
Bestest friends who steal...
powerful eldritch artifacts
from his trunk...
travel to forbidden planes
of existence...
and use the Grim Reaper's scythe
to unclog their toilets?
Yup, that's us.
It was a supernatural clog.
Would it be fair to say that
none of you would be friends...
if you didn't have to be?
That you're just using
the Grim Reaper for his powers?
And if he were suddenly powerless
he'd be useless to you?
Yeah, sounds fair to me.
I'd like to call to the stand
my first witness.
Myself.
Hello, I'm the Boogey Man.
Is it true that these stinking children
called you names...
and banished you
to a Nightmare Realm...
where the screaming
never stopped?
Yes, it's true. These children stink
and probably never bathe.
Yes. Yes.
He can't be serious.
If I recall correctly,
he can't be scary either.
It was horrible.
Modern children are so hard to scare,
I was just trying to do my job.
Hang him.
Objection, the prosecutor
can't question himself.
Jeez! Is that true?
Well, in summation...
these deviants are
unbelievably barbaric...
wickedly loathsome...
prunish pimples on the face
of our brave and honorable society...
and they're mean to baby animals.
I rest my case.
Does the defense have
anything to say for itself?
- I want to plead guilty.
- Shut up!
Please, Judge, it's not my fault
that I'm not doing me job.
These kids won me in a bet.
Illegal gambling.
But I'll do anything
to get out of me contract.
Invalidating a legal
and binding contract.
Shut up, Boogey. Or I'll come
over there and make you shut up.
Assaulting an officer of the court.
I think I've seen enough.
Has the jury reached a verdict?
Stone him!
We the jury find the defendant...
innocent?
Yeah!
- You idiot, that says guilty.
- Guilty. Yes.
By the power vested in me
by this infernal court...
I hereby strip the Grim Reaper
of title, rank and powers...
and condemn him
and his accessories...
to immediate execution.
I'm sorry, that says "exile". My bad.
How could you do this, Boogey?
He doesn't like you.
Haven't you been listening?
Judge, don't worry,
I'll take them with me.
My crew and I were just going out
for a bit of a sail.
And I know the perfect place to...
drop them off.
Drop them off, drop them off.
Very well. I give custody
of the former Grim Reaper...
to the Boogey Man.
Please take him far, far away...
where he won't bother anyone
ever again.
You made your point,
Boogey.
Who are you going to get to be
the Grim Reaper instead of me, huh?
The kids next door?
Hey, come on, I know my rights.
You've got the right
to a butt-kicking. Right, boys?
I've cheated Death.
This is the greatest day of my life.
Time for a frosty beverage.
What's this?
Damn! You're those filthy
children that go door to door...
selling candy bars
for their school fundraiser.
Well, I'm busy and poor.
So go away and stop tracking
dirt on my lawn.
No sign of the targets.
We must enter the domicile.
Query.
Why are we eliminating
Billy and Mandy?
Our job is not to ask why.
We are programmed to obey.
They are gone.
I told you that it took too long.
Statement.
If I'd known robots had to pee...
I wouldn't have had that
32 pounds liquid coolant...
right before we time-traveled.
Hey, kids, Billy's mom's
a little upset right now...
as she'll have to go back to work
at the dog-kicking factory.
So I'm supposed to take you
to dinner far, far away from here.
Query.
Will you, Billy's father,
teach me all that you know...
so that I may better understand...
and thereby destroy
my pre-approved target?
Billy. I'd hoped
one day that you'd realize...
that I'm not just a father
but a father figure.
Come, let me share my knowledge
over a root beer.
Now, the first thing you gotta know
is that life is like a basketball.
It has its ups and its downs...
Hey, are you guys going
to the Grand Canyon...
on this cruise ship too?
No, we're prisoners.
I like cruise ships 'cause you
get a buffet and it has shrimp.
The buffet has shrimp?!
How did that guy from the jury
get on my ship?
I need to make poo-poo, I need
to make poo-poo real bad.
I can't believe you got me fired, Boogey.
You can't keep me here.
Your stay here will be as brief
as your lives.
But we still get the buffet, right?
I'm not hungry, yo.
I want to go home!
Who's gonna be the Grim Reaper,
if I'm not the Grim Reaper?
Hey there, it's me.
Number 3.
I just wanted to thank you, Boogey,
for giving me this opportunity.
Thanks to you,
in addition to my charity work...
and love of rainbow monkeys...
I can now also reap
the immortal souls of grownups...
collecting my dark harvest
with a cold iron blade.
Yeah,
that will be fun.
She's on a six-week
trial period.
- If I had me powers right now!
- But you don't.
And without your powers
you can't be the scariest being alive.
That leaves the job to me.
Last time I checked,
butterflies were scarier than you.
You won't be saying that
after I sail...
to the Isle of Peril
and capture Horror's Hand.
My mom makes horrible ham.
I'd be happy to bring it to you
to save you the trip.
No, you doofwad. Horror's Hand.
It clutches in its mighty grip
the things we fear the most.
Horror's Hand?! With its power
I could be the scariest being alive.
I could easily
get me old job back.
Horror's Hand is the most
frightening object in the universe.
Horror's Hand makes you face
your deepest fear.
But if you conquer your fear
you can use the Hand's power...
to become an unstoppable force
of scariness.
Horror's Hand literally makes
your worst nightmares come to life.
When I enter the dreams
of children with the hand...
they will fear me again.
Mortals all over the world
will get so scared that they'd puke...
when they just hear the name,
Boogey Man.
Like that one lady puked
when I mentioned your name.
It was one date.
She didn't give me a chance.
Does that mean he does
or doesn't want the ham?
You're a hack, Boogey.
I've met marshmallows scarier than you.
Shall I set course
for the Burning Seas?
We could throw these punks
to the fire sharks.
Make it so, Mr. Creeper.
I usually think sharks
are scary...
but these fire sharks sound like
a fine lot of gentlemen to me.
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls...
it's time for a little game
called Walk the Plank.
Come on, Boogey, it's me you want,
not the kids. Let 'em go.
I don't think so.
Fine, take the kids. Let me go.
I'm going to miss you
the most, Grim.
This is just like Titanic.
I don't see why we have to walk
the plank.
We're not the ones who've been
your mortal enemies since the 6th grade.
True. But I really don't like children.
The feeling is mutual.
Come on in, the lava's fine.
That looks like fun. I wanna go first.
It's always nice to have a volunteer.
Hot down there. But it's a dry heat.
Dance, you little sausage, dance.
Do it.
I can't look.
Mommy!
Now are you scared?
Then pop his head open
like a gourd?
Grim, let's beat it while
they're distracted.
Not being kicked or keelhauled?
My goodness,
he's so brave and tall.
There's no braver boy
that I can recall.
I don't know if I'm thankful or appalled.
What is Billy doing?
We need to get out of here.
What do you mean
what am I doing?
I'm singing. There's always
songs in animated movies.
Get out of there or I'll give
you something to be scared of.
Over here.
Now that's scary.
It's a good thing I can't smell.
What I'm trying to say is
when a boy becomes a man...
he gets super, super hairy. See?
Another root beer, son?
Statement.
Me like another root beer.
Gladys, I forgot. Does root beer
always make Billy's head explode?
OK, he's fine.
Yeah, good one, Captain.
You almost had me there.
Would it kill you to fake it just once?
Lt'll make the time when
you really scare me all the more special.
- Good point.
- Not that it'll ever happen.
What's the status on our escapees?
No sign of the ex-Grim Reaper
and his cronies.
We're also missing
a Deathboat which means...
they could be
out on the river.
Well, if they make it
to the Gatekeeper...
We can watch their demise
through the Gatekeeper's magic eye.
We've got to stop Boogey
from getting Horror's Hand.
Otherwise, he'll become more powerful
than you can possibly imagine.
I don't know,
I can imagine quite a bit.
It almost makes me smile.
I know what I'd do with
limitless power, yo.
I gots the best idea.
One candy bar, please!
Idiot. And you. Don't ever
have that thought bubble again.
I don't have to imagine
what I'd do with Horror's Hand.
I know what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna use it to get me job back.
Well, no one is allowed to be
more powerful than me.
So we have to stop Boogey
and get Grim's powers back.
I'll enchant the boat
and we'll catch up in no time.
Now where's my scythe?
I've lost me scythe.
I love that scythe.
Great, maybe we can use you
for an anchor.
That's about all
you're good for now.
You two are the anchors.
Always draggin' me down,
holdin' me back.
My life was smooth sailin'
before you ruined it.
Is Grim gonna be OK?
He'll be fine. He's going
through the 7 stages of grief.
Shock...
How could dis happen?!
Denial.
It's a mistake.
No way this could happen.
Bargaining.
It's OK. It's OK.
Maybe I can fix it.
Fear.
There ain't no way I can fix it.
Anger.
I'm gonna pull Boogey's nose off
and put it in a jar!
Despair.
And when I'm done with Boogey,
I'm coming for you, little pukes.
He's stuck on anger.
Anyone hungry?
Half-chewed zombie arms for everyone.
Well, I guess we do this
the old-fashioned way.
Everyone grab an arm and paddle.
Let me do the talking.
These are my people.
I.D., please.
I am the Grim Reaper, I need no I.D.
Sorry, citizens,
can't let you in without an I.D.
Well, it's really not a good picture.
Can't you just take my...
Show him the I.D.
Wait a minute. I don't got no eye.
I can't read this.
I'll have to summon
the Gatekeeper to perform... the test.
What's the test, Grim?
Well, how should I know?
Tests are scary, yo.
I feel like all those
Scantron dots...
are little eyes
staring back at me, touching me...
Behold! Me am Gatekeeper.
Bring greatest riddler.
- I think...
- No, you don't.
Well, I'm not very good
at riddles.
But I'm not good at
a lot of things right now. Am I?
You're getting pretty good
at getting on my nerves.
Hey, yo, I know the question and answer
of every riddle known to man.
My level 52 troll warlock
is the only one ever...
to have opened the riddle door
of the math wizard.
Let me do this for the team, my pet.
Fine, great. Go away.
I am the best riddler here, yo.
Gatekeeper hate riddles.
Now me test you.
Let me look at him first.
Holy crud!
I never imagined that
the Grim Reaper would be so ugly.
I mean, he looks like a noseless
mother with bad shoes.
Good job, you passed the test.
This is what we get for
passing the test?
Seasoning.
Needs more cimmanon.
Hey, I'm starving.
Put more water on the fire,
mutton head.
You wait for cimmanon.
Cimmanon good.
Perfick.
Way too much cinnamon, yo.
Something bit me.
- Poisonous snakes!
- I don't think so.
If had me scythe
we'd be so out of here.
What are we going to do, yo?
Players don't get eaten by Cyclopses.
Yeah, I always thought
I'd be eaten by something cooler.
Like a biker gang.
Hey, One Eye, I think
your stew's gone bad.
Nope, secret ingredient cimmanon.
Not bad.
Did it just get warmer in here
or is it just me?
Billy, did you?
Oh, my goodness.
Did not!
OK, I did.
No!
Can't see! Need eye!
Not again! We're never going
to eat if you don't find it...
you big lump o' stupid!
It's like that little girl knows
how to use Billy as a weapon.
We need to stop those kids
before they beat us to the Hand.
Funny you should mention that.
I've been working on some designs...
For time-traveling robots
that could backtrack...
and eliminate
those meddlesome little nerds.
You work fast.
Wow! I totally do.
We are from the future.
Creeper built us to ensure
that the Lord of Horror...
reaches Horror's Hand
before Billy and Mandy.
We offer our services
as assassins...
or maids if you need cleaning.
Statement.
I am high.
I designed you to be unthinking,
unfeeling killing machines.
Billybot was damaged
on the surface world.
Damaged.
Check behind that rock
in the front yard where the hide-a-key is.
- Shut up.
- No! Check the refrigerator.
And while you're in there get me
a sandwich because this soup is terrible.
- Will you shut up?
- No, you shut up.
- Shut up.
Any idea how our dinky raft
with the powerless Reaper...
can catch that enormous yacht?
Cake!
Doesn't this seem a little odd
to anyone?
Well, strawberry frosting is a little
unconventional on a chocolate cake.
I mean...
Dude, you can kiss cake
in the mouth.
"Happy Birthday,
Billy and Mandy?"
It's probably a trap since
we don't share the same birthday.
Maybe it's celebrating
the show's birthday, yo.
We should probably leave it.
Frost-tastic!
This is good.
I can't say I've ever had
a cake quite this...
Good work, putting a sleeping potion
into the cake mix, Billybot.
Billybot?
Statement.
I am dreaming
that I am a caky marmoset.
Mission successful,
Captain Boogey Man.
The targets are neutralized
and ready for dream infiltration.
Excellent work, Mandroid.
Now, Creeper, it's time for
a good old-fashioned scaring.
Come on, you've got to laugh with me
or I look like a jerk.
I'm the world's
top cowboy astronaut!
Gotcha!
Way to go, Billy!
You're the best!
This is one of the most
shameful things I've ever seen.
What are you doing
in my dream, Mandy?
Reliving The Pit and the Pendulum
for the thousandth time.
What are both of you doing...
in my recurring dream
about Puppy Town?
- And who are you?
- I'm the real Grim.
The guy you're riding only exists
in your sad, sick little dream.
I do this for one of my charities.
It's called
The Stupid Kids' Dream Foundation!
Well, if that's true...
where's the real Irwin?
Right here, yo.
I have this dream every night.
If you're here to scare us, skip it.
We're not in the mood.
Oh, yes, little Miss
"I'm always in control."
You're the reason I'm here.
You're the only threat to my plans!
You're coming with me!
Let's see how you dupes do
without your brain trust.
I'll leave you with a gift.
That wasn't the gift. That was
this morning's three-cheese omelet.
Fear the gouda!
I wish I could wake up...
but I don't usually
wake up until I pee!
Pee, yo, pee!
Mandy's been kidnapped by Boogey!
We have to get her back!
How will we get her back?
Boogey's got everything.
A better boat,
a full crew and Mandy!
Grim, if we're going
to get your powers back...
stop the Boogey Man,
and save the world from tyranny...
then we're going to need
all of us to do it!
We have to get Mandy back!
Cake...
There's one thing Boogey doesn't have.
The power of love!
What am I looking at?
It's the view from
the Gatekeeper's Eye, Captain.
But I thought Billy ate the eye.
He did.
You don't want
to think about it too hard.
No matter.
Mandy, you admitted
in court under oath...
that Grim was no good to you
without his powers.
With Horror's Hand,
I'll be twice as powerful as Grim ever was.
If you were my friend...
and protected me
the way you protect Grim...
we could rule the universe together!
What do you say?
Just because I'll be best friends
with a loser bag of bones...
doesn't mean I'll be best friends
with a toad like you.
Careful, little girl,
or I could make...
the rest of your miserable
little existence very scary.
Ain't that right, Creeper?
What's that?
Yeah, scary!
Very scary, Captain. Yes.
Not scary at all...
Keep that up and the Employee
of the Month is going to be... that guy.
It's you who should
be scared, Boogey.
Why's that?
'Cause once
I get down from here...
I'm gonna kick
your slimy blue butt so hard...
you'll have to sit on your eyes!
Now, that's scary!
Maybe you could pick up
a couple of pointers from...
Enough!
You're not kicking any butt, little girl.
If you think you are,
you're dreaming.
I just had the craziest dream.
Was it the one
where you can't save us?
Where are you, Mandy?
We can't make it without you, yo.
We're doomed.
Doomed! Doomed!
Let me out of here!
She'll be under my sleep spell
until her will is broken.
Yeah, I remember
when you did that to me.
I hate you.
It's just smooth sailing
from here on out.
Sir, you might want to see this.
Now there's something
you don't see every day.
Mandy, I will find you
and save you, yo!
What are you doing? Get him!
Yeah!
Hang on,
how did Irwin get so cool?
He's driven by the power of love.
Really?
Love makes people do
all sorts of stupid tings.
I love everything.
Dat explains a lot.
Never send monster pirates
to do a robot's job.
Billybot, Mandroid, destroy!
She's still asleep!
Yes.
There is but one way to break the spell
this beautiful maiden is under.
OK, I get it.
Terrible, horrible, disgusting nightmares
that just keep getting worse.
Can we just move on already?
This is no nightmare, Mandy.
This is a dream come true.
I am the god of love!
When you're done there,
we've got a situation.
Please surrender yourselves
and come with me.
You will be assimilated.
Please?
If you're supposed to be me...
then let's get
a couple of things straight.
I don't say please...
I don't assimilate,
and I don't take orders from anyone...
especially your pathetic excuse
for a Boogey Man.
I, Mandy...
giving orders to Mandy,
who doesn't take orders...
who gives order to me, Mandy...
who doesn't take...
010110...
Random...
Think fast before they figure out
they outnumber us.
I was just there
for the "saving you" part.
How fast do I have to think?
I'm getting dizzy.
We got you this far.
Not bad
for a weenie, a dope...
and a useless bag of bones
with no powers.
You figure out the rest!
Am I the weenie
or the bag of bones?
That's so hot, yo.
We can't let them get to the Hand first!
There's only one thing left to do.
Oh, sir! You can't mean?
I do! Release the Kracken!
You'd think
she'd be a little more grateful.
Where are we?
The Isle of Peril,
resting place of Horror's Hand.
It's amazing, yo.
I know!
I can see
my grandma's house from here.
Shut up, Billy.
I'll never understand
why she moved here.
Halt!
- Who is that?
- I am Horror, the Ancient.
Long ago, I magically
channeled all of my fear into my left hand...
and then cut it off...
so I would forever be bold and brave.
You may pass no further
without defeating me in a battle...
of wits.
During which I will attempt
to strike you with my spear.
Mr. Horror, Mr. Horror!
Did cutting off your hand
really make you brave?
Oh, my goodness, no!
I mean, what was I thinking?
First of all, I'm a lefty...
so once I cut it off,
I couldn't even sign my name!
Then I just got bored,
and I gained like 20 pounds.
Now I do a lot of online gaming...
and I've learned
to play a guitar with my teeth.
Gets kind of boring down here.
So what you're saying is...
you're not really
going to engage us in battle?
You just want a little love
and understanding.
Irwin's here
and he's ready to listen, yo.
If you defeat me...
you will face your greatest fear...
at the hand of Horror's Hand.
Well, looks like
we've gone from bad to worse.
Billy!
He'll be fine.
Oh, great!
There goes our comic relief. What next?
I'm afraid you're outmatched,
Grim old boy.
Horror's Hand is mine.
If you want to be useful
without your powers...
now is a good time to start.
I... I don't know how, Boogey...
but we're going to beat you!
Smooth.
Well, you can't both
have Horror's Hand!
You'll have to make
the Cannibal Run.
Whoever comes back alive
will win the honor of fighting me.
Holy crud!
The Cannibal Run...
is the most dangerously frightening
section of the entire river.
- Well, we're not scared.
- We're not either!
Totally awesome!
You will start from Point Dread...
go through the Chasm of Blades
across the Bottomless Falls...
pass through the Hole of Oddities,
past Monster Island...
through the Sunken City
of the Witch Queen...
stop for lunch
at the Picnic Grounds of Terror...
jump the Glacier of Evil...
pass the Whirlpool of Suffering...
and, finally, overcome
the Cliffs of Crushing.
Man, I'm glad
I don't have to go through all that!
You have that all down, Grim old chum?
I'd hate to see you
and your delightful companions get lost...
or worse, along the way.
See you at the finish line, Boogey!
Our backsides perhaps.
I miss Billy, yo.
I told you, Billy's fine.
He's been underwater
for six hours!
Billy's always fine.
We can't do this without him.
We need him!
You ladies lose your mascot?
That's a crying shame.
We don't need Billy anyway, right?
We need to be together!
Billy's... always fine.
I'm fine!
First the Kracken ate me
but I kept alive by breathing my own farts.
Then me and the Kracken became friends.
He's really fun when you get to know him.
Told you he was fine.
We might as well quit now.
There's no way we're going to win.
The Cannibal Run is impossible.
No one's ever survived it!
- You can't quit.
- Why not?
Because I said so!
Don't treat me
like a three-year-old!
It was you kids
that got me powers taken away!
Boogey got your powers taken away.
Because of you two!
Grim, when we won you
in that game of limbo...
you agreed to be our best friend forever,
powers or no powers.
Don't remind me.
And best friends stick together
even through the tough times.
But this is
an impossible time!
You said that sometimes...
people do
stupid things out of love.
This is one of those stupid times!
But I don't love any of you!
In fact, I pretty much hate all of you!
And we feel the same way.
But our only other option
is losing Horror's Hand to Boogey.
Do you really want that?
I hate you guys.
But I hate him even more!
Let's do this thing, yo!
Go us!
And you're off!
Row, row, ye scurvy dog!
- I'm useless.
- Not yet.
Grab the back seat!
We're neck and neck.
Incoming now!
- We're ahead.
- Oh, curses. No!
I'll cut you.
We're gonna be the first into...
...the Chasm of Blades.
What now?
- We lose?
- What about all that stuff you said...
about friendship and trying
and never giving up?
Yeah, sometimes
I just say stuff, you know?
Where do we get one of those?
So, Grim, are you all cut up
about losing Horror's Hand?
Have I shredded any hope of victory?
Are you falling apart at the seams?
I can almost handle
losing my powers forever...
if I didn't have to listen to this guy.
Sorry, I'm allergic to blades.
Billy, hurry!
Sneeze on Mandy.
If you do that, I will...
Bring it on.
We're a river booger!
And you said you didn't need me.
Well, I hope
you kiddies can fly too...
'cause you're going to need to
to get over the Bottomless Falls.
Creeper, activate the rockets!
There's no way
we're getting over that pit.
Powers or no powers, we're not losing.
Quick, Mandy, me cloak.
Hang on to me cloak,
it's gonna be a bumpy ride.
Say goodbye to my butt!
Sayonara, suckers!
What's that, yo?
That would be the Hole of Oddities.
Why is it called
the Hole of Oddities?
We're about to find out.
Oh, now I get it.
I'm a forearm
from the waist down!
That was disturbing.
My bottom!
Hot, hot, hot.
I don't even feel it anymore.
Sunken City of the Witch Queen.
I don't see no city.
I really gotta lay off
those cheese blintzes.
No. No!
Yeah!
Row!
These are moving too fast.
We'll never get through!
We need more speed.
Billybot, Mandroid,
destroy them!
That's an order!
Statement.
I don't take orders.
Especially from a pathetic excuse
for a Boogey Man like you.
Suck cannonball!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
- We win!
- Yeah!
I'm the laughing stock
of the underworld.
Maybe scary really isn't your thing.
You are indeed fearless.
Now the only thing
you must do is defeat...
Owned.
All right, let's grab this thing
and blow this dump.
Remember, Horror's Hand
is an artifact of unimaginable power.
But once we get close to it,
the hand will open...
and your worst nightmare
will spring forth.
It's only if you can overcome that fear,
that you get the hand.
So let me go first because...
I ain't afraid of nothin'!
What about spiders, yo?
- And clowns?
- And the mailman.
Let's make you a pony, little boy.
No one can help him now.
He must battle his own demons.
Gosh, that's scary, yo.
Who's gonna go up there next
'cause it ain't gonna be...
Oh, no!
Telling jokes to wild bears.
My worst nightmare!
So a bear and a rabbit,
they're pooping in the woods and...
Amateurs.
I'm looking for Horror's Hand.
Have you?
Hello, me.
I remember being your age...
when I was all gloom and doom...
instead of sunshine and lollipops!
But I was wrong.
I was wrong about a lot of things.
When I was your age...
I never told Billy and Grim
how important they really were to me.
Oh, egad!
I don't...
Why don't you come in
and have some brownies?
You're not me.
You can't be me.
I'm supposed to do something important.
Nothing is more important
than friendship.
Except maybe love.
Hey, little lady.
I see you met my wife, yo.
I told you,
you should have let me go first.
The Hand won't affect me.
I lived me worst nightmare
every day...
living with you two jerks!
Hand over the Hand
or we'll handle you roughly!
And now,
Mr. Former Grim Reaper...
I think I'll take this opportunity...
to scare you to pieces!
No, no, Boogey!
Not like this, not like this!
Mandy, this isn't fun anymore.
Billy, for once
I completely agree with you.
Yeah...
I wanna go home, yo.
Not so fast.
I'm sure I've got room for you
in my slave army.
I've done it!
I'm the scariest dude alive!
Now, all that's left is to rule...
with an iron fist!
Hi there.
What?
Hang on a minute.
I scared you to pieces!
No, really.
I totally blew meself up on purpose.
You couldn't scare
a puzzle to pieces!
I... don't understand! I'm scary.
The Hand!
It's making
my worst nightmare come true!
You've lost your edge, Boogey.
You're through!
Now that you mention it,
I don't know anyone un-scarier.
Creeper. No!
Wait, I'm supposed
to be afraid of that?
You're no spider clown mailman,
that's for sure!
You'd last two seconds with a bear.
I'm scary!
I'll just be taking that!
No, seriously, I'm scary.
I'm scary.
I've failed!
What do you say?
So the Boogey Man's
worst nightmare...
was realizing
that he's not scary at all.
That may have been his worst nightmare
but we can't blame the Hand.
I turned it off,
right after I picked it up. See?
So he really wasn't ever scary at all!
Nice one, Grim.
Hang on a second.
This means I'm acting captain.
I'll be taking that Hand now.
Nachos.
Work really burns me up.
Nice job.
But Fred Fredburger
so didn't deserve that.
Acceptable losses.
So you and me
can be friends now, right?
Suggestion.
Assimilate! Assimilate!
So, who gets the Hand?
With its powers
I could be someone again!
And I could scare people
into thinking I'm smart.
I could use it to...
make someone love me, yo.
- You'll never get it.
- It's mine!
Those nachos have hurt my tummy.
But if I had never eaten them...
I wouldn't have known
I could finish them all!
What the heck
is he talking about?
Nachos!
Wait! He's onto something.
- Really?
- Yes!
This whole voyage
has been like eating nachos.
- Yes!
- If we'd never come...
we never would have known
how far we'd go to get what we wanted.
- Nachos!
- And...
we would have never seen
that we had what we wanted all along.
Yes!
Grim, you still saved the day...
even without your powers.
Mandy still always gets her way.
Irwin got to kiss his true love.
And I'm gonna get
a new bike for Christmas!
And we all did it
without Horror's Hand.
And we did it together.
Now I am thirsty.
Did you come
to give me my job back?
No.
We came to finish
what the Boogey Man started.
Banishing you forever!
I don't think so.
Bonehead here
just saved all your butts...
from a future ruled
by the Boogey Man.
So I think you're going to say thank you...
get his scythe
and give him his job back.
Now!
OK.
Really?
I can be the Grim Reaper again?
Sorry, girlfriend.
You're just not working out.
I missed you so much.
Who's your daddy?
I'll get you for this, Grim,
if it's the last thing I do!
She was a heck of a reaper,
in her own way.
Stop right there!
Don't give her the Hand.
- My eyes!
- What the?
I come from a time
two weeks in the future.
A future where
the Lord of Horror reigns supreme.
Her!
Two weeks sounds about right.
A girl's gotta have goals.
It burns!
You look just like me!
But why are you naked?
Is it because clothes can't time-travel...
because nothing inorganic
can come through the time stream?
Nah, I just like to feel
the breeze on me.
Enough!
The Hand needs to stay
out of everyone's possession forever!
So I'm going to stow it in me trunk.
Yeah, because no one ever steals
anything from that trunk.
Suck eggs, Lord of Horror!
It's the Boogey Man!
Boogey Man? Where? Oh, no!
Did I leave the oven on?
You guys gotta help me, I...
Boogey's afraid of everything!
A few too many hits
on the noggin looks like.
A talking skeleton!
Poor Boogey!
I don't know.
I think I prefer him this way.
Well, all's well that ends well.
Not that anything
ever really ends well.
But I'm going to call this one a victory.
And the time has come for me to go.
Goodbye, future Billy.
I hope we meet again someday.
Can you tell me
what I'm having for lunch next Tuesday?
I could tell you,
but then I'd have to kill you.
I like that guy.
You know, I couldn't have gotten
me job back without you kids.
I mean, don't get to thinkin' I like you
or anything, 'cause clearly I don't.
If there's one thing
I learned down there...
it's that you shouldn't be
ashamed of your feelings, Grim.
- I have feelings too.
- You do?
Yeah. I'm feeling hungry.
Go whip us up some sandwiches!
I don't know
why I put up with you two.
Because we own you.
Because you love us.
Yeah, yeah.
Wow, that was lame.
I don't know why I put up with you two!
Because we own you.
Explanation.
Because you love us!
Yeah, yeah.
Temporal breach detected
in sector 33.
Unit 7 moving in after him.
Over.
It can't be!
Nothing's changed.
Who could've stolen the Hand?
It's you! I should've known.
My worst nightmare
is that I've run out of nachos.
I like nachos.
I can spell nachos too.
N-a-c-h-o-z.
Nachos! Yes!
www.moviesubtitles.org