[Music playing]
[Battle cry]
Die, barbarian pig.
Leave this land
and never return.
Doran?
Doran, is that you?
Who goes there?
Be you friend or foe?
Show yourself, coward.
Show yourself and do battle.
[Battle cry]
[Man laughing]
The amulet, it is not
protecting me from harm.
It knows you are safe.
Doran.
You know nothing of honor.
All is fair in love and
in war, my sweet Doran.
Now, the war is over.
Our bond is strong, my beloved.
I do love you.
I, too, love thee.
We shall always be
together, for eternity.
Doran, I'm worried
for our people.
There's so much evil
and pain in the land.
Thieves grow from every
tree and every stream.
The land is pure.
It is the hearts of
men that are evil.
This amulet shall
protect you from harm.
Power and strength fill me.
It is as if I, too,
am a great warrior.
Lystra, beware its power.
The Wizard made this
known to my grandfather.
Perhaps this wizard is
but a tale from your head.
Wizards are not to
be taken in jest,
But be posessed of powers of
the heavens and the underworld.
Where is this wizard,
then, and why does he
Not show his face to me?
He shows his face to none,
and he is a she, showing only
Her face to those she chooses.
A she?
My grandfather told me the
story when I was a young boy.
She appeared before his eyes
to save him from certain death.
He vowed never to lost
sight of the amulet.
And so it has been
bequeathed to me.
My vow is to use its power
to protect my people,
To teach them honesty and
bravery, to seek the truth.
And if this is done,
then the people of Armana
Shall be protected by its power.
So you have done.
They worship you, Doran.
Worship is not what I
seek, for I am not a god.
All I ask is that they
listen and follow.
Their lives, then,
are their own.
You become wiser with each day.
I am honored to be your queen.
My grandfather gave
me fair warning.
And you, too, must beware
its power, for with a thought
One can travel great
journeys to lands
Never seen by thine eyes, a
land where one may never return.
So dream not of lands
other than this, or you
Shall leave me forever.
The power shall make
us great warriors.
And with it, we shall build
a new world for our children.
[Music playing]
[Imitating bird sound]
Bartaga.
Kiss me, great warrior.
Kiss me.
I have come to
hunt with my king.
I have no time for
sexual foolishness.
Doran, my friend, today
is ripe for the hunt.
And so your wine shall speak.
She would make a great
wife for a warrior
For her bravery is more
than most men possess.
Bartaga is a
warrior, not a lover.
And I, my friend, am both.
Perhaps the boar are better
than a woman's tongue.
Yes, but what will
keep you warm at night?
[Inaudible] hunter.
[Laughter]
And it does not
screech in my ear.
Oh.
[Magical twinkling]
Mandrak.
I found a treasure, an
amulet of great wealth.
Oh.
Where?
A woman holds it,
a barbarian queen.
Her name is Lystra.
Lystra, the warrior's woman?
He warned us never to return.
We should go back.
Where is she?
By the stream at the edge
of the forest, not far.
They'll be sure to
kill us if we go there.
Coward.
She's very beautiful,
Mandrak, a tasty
Tidbit for a hungry man.
She's [inaudible].
He swore that if
we ever came back...
Silence!
Take me to her.
That amulet will
make us all rich men.
Ah, Lystra.
If a man truly loves a woman,
he will never leave her.
But you must have a tree, for
your man must leave to hunt
Or you shall go hungry.
You two speak with idle words.
If I had a man like Doran,
he could leave for years,
And I would wait for him.
But you do not
have him, do you?
Only Lystra has
that good fortune.
There.
[Whispering]
Are you mad?
Silence, Wolf.
You give me the women, or
I'll cut your tongues out.
There are no men that I
can see, just women and us.
[Quiet laughter]
Do thoughts of
sadness fill your head?
It is nothing, my lady.
Surely it is something, for
I can see it in your eyes.
I cannot hide from you.
You see into my very soul.
It is Bartaga.
He does not even
know that I am alive.
A man such as Bartaga
has a duty to himself
Before he can be with a woman.
He just needs to see the magic
inside you that he is missing.
You are right.
I am worthy.
It is he who has
not opened his eyes.
[Laughter]
[Yelling]
[Screaming]
She's only a woman.
Come now, barbarian.
You can do better than that.
Now, die.
Doran.
Oh, my head.
Nothing my wine cannot cure.
Lystra, she's in danger.
Come on.
The wife of the great warrior
Doran, the mightiest barbarian
Of them all.
Ha!
Where is he now?
How shall he save you?
Will he even want you after
I am finished with you?
You shall die by his sword.
No, no.
No.
Doran!
Do you not like the touch of
cold steel upon your cheek?
On your body?
Was it not as you
expected, barbarian queen?
Mandrak, we must leave
before Doran finds us,
Or we're doomed.
Doomed?
I will show you doomed.
Oh, I felt her spirit
pass through me.
It is as if I
possess a new life.
I have heard many
wondrous tales,
And now you will
make me a rich man.
Make us rich, Mandrak.
Tell me more of
the amulet's powers.
More?
Tell me.
I must know, or you will
die by my sword, jackal.
It has the power
of the heavens,
Master, the spirits of the
underworld, cursed strength.
It is said that...
Do you take me for a fool?
No, Mandrak, no,
it is the truth.
You know as well
as I. That crystal
Protects Doran and his people.
It could bring us a
talent of gold coins.
It will bring more
than that, [inaudible].
It will bring me
my salvation, what
I have desired all my life!
No.
No!
[Lamenting]
Prisal.
Who did this to you?
Mandrak.
Mandrak?
My prize of battle.
They did not die
without a fight.
He... he did this to my beloved.
I'll kill him
with my bare hands.
I swear, Doran.
No.
It is I who must
avenge her death.
I will not rest
until Mandrak dies.
I swear to you this.
Your thoughts must
be clear for battle.
My thoughts were clear
before you did that.
Come, we have no time.
Since my thoughts are
clear, what of the amulet?
Did not the Wizard give
your ancestors fair warning
Never to lose sight of it?
You speak the truth.
Will she not be a little angry?
It is I who lost the amulet.
It is I who must have to pay.
It was not you, my friend.
It was Lystra who
lost the amulet.
Surely the Wizard will look
upon this with a fair eye.
I have no fear of death.
A brave warrior, indeed...
Who, then, will I hunt with?
When the Wizard finds us,
we may never hunt again.
I will stand by your
side, Wizard or no Wizard.
[Birds calling]
Birds, only birds.
Come.
We must not stop.
[Birds calling angrily]
[Inaudible] I have awaited
this day, barbarian.
You die.
[Battle cry]
[Men shouting]
Stay back.
No!
[Crazy laughter]
[Howling]
[Laughter]
You are a brave one.
What do they call you?
Doran.
[Laughter]
The King of Armana?
Were you lost in the
forest like all of them?
He dies by my sword.
Moltar would be pleased.
Psst.
Psst, barbarian.
I know who you are.
Caught you the same way
they caught me, I wager.
What are you doing
in these parts?
I'm searching for a murderer.
Murderer?
Got plenty of 'em right here.
Bloodthirsty vermin, they are.
That one, watch out for him.
He'd just as soon rip the
heart right out of you if you
Look at him the wrong way.
[Men laughing and whooping]
Moltar, god of the underworld,
I send to you this sacrifice
Of flesh and blood.
[Cheering]
Tonight, you meet Moltar,
and I have the honor.
Strip him to the skin.
[Laughter]
Why do you look so
surprised, barbarian?
Have you never seen
a wizard before?
You are the Wizard?
I have heard only tales.
You must hide
before they see you.
They cannot see me.
Wizard, free me.
Free you?
Why should I do that?
You are a healthy-looking
mortal, aren't you?
It is a pity, being
captured by these heathens.
Where is my crystal amulet?
I lost it.
You lost it?
I saved your grandfather's life.
I gave him that amulet in the
hopes that one day one... one
Man in this putrid land would...
Would set an example of honor.
And all you can
say is you lost it.
That amulet was to protect his
descendants for many lifetimes.
You have broken
the chain, Doran.
So kill me now and
be done with it.
I do not deserve to live.
Oh, you are quick
to die, barbarian.
To kill you would be too easy.
To kill you would not replace
my amulet, now would it?
It has been with
me for centuries.
Your from this day forward is
to return the amulet to me.
If you do not, then I shall be
forced to curse your people.
You leave my
people out of this.
If you fail to
return it, then I
Shall cast an evil and wicked
plague over your tribe.
They will burn with
hatred and disease
Upon hearing Doran's name.
This is not my people's fault.
Their wounds festering
from their hate
For their king... oh, yes!
You will find the amulet.
You will find the
man that belongs
To that hand on your belt. The
man you seek is in this world
No longer.
You must travel to
another time to find him.
You must travel to a
land called the future.
It is very different
than the forest.
It is tomorrow's tomorrow.
But if you are quick of wit
and brave of heart and fight
With honor you may triumph.
But you must return
the amulet to me.
Mandrak has the amulet, and it
will make him a mighty warrior.
The amulet has no power in
the hands of evil, Doran.
Only in the presence
of honor and of a king
With a noble heart does
it have such magic.
Behold.
A sword.
It will take you
to your destination.
And for the love of
gods, do not lose it.
Enough chatter.
Be free, barbarian.
And heed this as
your last warning.
Your evil shall
end by my hands.
Penny, please, when are
you gonna listen to me?
I'm telling you.
You're asking for trouble.
Trust me on this.
Brice, just chill out.
Turn the camera
on, and no matter
What, just keep it rolling.
Cogs will have a brick
when he sees this.
Just remember, this
is all your idea.
Rolling.
I'm Penny Price,
Channel 5 Action News,
Reporting to you from the site
of a gang-related shooting
Which occurred earlier
today behind me.
Apparently, the warehouse
owner was threatened
To pay for what the street
gang, The Gladiators,
Calls safety insurance,
which means he pays
The gangs large sums
of money to stop
Them from destroying his door.
Well, as you can see, he didn't
make this week's payment.
This is just one gang-related
incident in over 239
That have happened in
our city this year.
What I would like to know is
whatever happened to morals,
Ethics, and common decency?
What we need is a positive role
model, a hero you might say,
Who could rally the
citizens to take
Action and make a difference.
Hey, everybody, I'm on TV.
Penny!
You sons of bitches.
Let go of me.
Come on, guys.
The witch.
Find the witch.
What do you want with me?
You know, every time me
and my pals turn on the TV,
There you are, giving us
a bad rap, Penny Price.
Consider this a warning.
Penny, I'm coming!
[Inaudible] keep
this camera rolling.
[Thunder]
Who is out here?
Free her.
What is this shit?
Get him, Crank, find out.
[Inaudible].
[Laughter]
You gotta be kidding.
Go on, kill the fuck.
Go on.
Get up.
Get up, [inaudible].
Your swords match your manhood.
You take him, Swank.
- What?
- Bye.
Hey.
You suck.
Now that you're
finished changing,
Can we get back to the station?
He looks like he's never
even seen a fence before.
So what's the big deal?
He's probably a convict.
Look at him.
He could be dangerous, Penny.
He saved my life, Brice.
Look, we've got a deadline, and
you're worried about this guy?
I don't believe it.
Penny, please, we gotta get back
to the station, so let's go.
Just go without me, Brice.
What?
Look, go without me.
Tell Cogs I got tied up.
All you need is the tape, right?
All right, but I don't like it.
Hey, wait a minute.
Where are you going?
Wait.
What's that thing you
carry around on your belt?
A hand.
I kind of figured that.
Whose hand is it?
Mandrak's, I've
come to find him.
Why do you have his
hand, and what are
You gonna do when you find him?
Battle.
Oh, don't tell me.
You're from some Nordic
country, and you're
Here to catch a criminal
and take him back with you.
The Wizard has given
me an impossible task.
Where do I find this
man in this land?
Is this the underworld?
Sometimes, it
sure seems like it.
Hey, where are you from, anyway?
Armana.
Armana?
I don't think I've
heard of that.
I've come to find Mandrak.
OK, well, welcome to LA.
LA?
What is LA?
Los Angeles?
I'm sure you've heard of it.
No.
Hey, wait.
THUG (ON RECORDING): Hey,
everybody, I'm on TV.
You're history, bitch.
[Crazy laughter]
What's going on here?
DORAN (ON RECORDING): Free her.
THUG (ON RECORDING):
What is this shit?
Get him, Crank, find out.
He's something, ain't he, Cogs?
I mean, he's like
a friggin Conan.
He saved Penny from
a real bad scene.
This is some kind of stunt
she's pulling, isn't it?
How can you say that?
Look, Cogs, I was there, too.
I'm telling ya.
We don't know who this guy is.
He came out of nowhere
and beat the shit
Out of those gang bangers.
He was incredible.
I haven't seen anything
like that since Superman.
Let me know when it's finished.
Right, whatever you say, Cogs.
Yes.
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
What is it, Brice?
I just wanted to make sure
that gorilla was in his cage.
He's not a gorilla,
and I'm fine.
In fact, we just went
shopping for some new clothes.
Is that all, Brie?
I just wanted to make
sure you were OK, OK?
I'll call you later.
Bye.
[Slow music playing]
May I have this dance?
So... so why do you want
this Mandrak so badly?
He murdered my wife.
Oh, I am sorry.
He killed her and stole
the crystal amulet.
I must return it to
the Wizard or my tribe
Will be cursed by a plague.
Well, there are treatments
and medications for that sort
Of thing, you know.
I cannot wait.
Hey, look, where...
Where do you think
You're gonna find this guy?
This is a big city.
You'll get lost.
I can help you.
We have ways of tracking
people, especially criminals.
[Sirens]
Hurry, you fool.
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
Brice, you're just the
person I wanted to talk to.
I knew that.
It's our karma.
Look, I need you to dig
up some information for me
From the computer.
Mandrak?
One hand?
Yeah, I... I got it.
I'll get on it as soon
as I finish the tape.
Oh, Penny.
What, Brice?
I just wanted to
tell you that, uh... I
Just wanted to... nothing.
Everything looks real good here.
Good, bye.
OK, now, I want to
do a story on you.
Come on.
Perfect.
Yes.
If I'm gonna get
this story, I might
As well go all the way, right?
I want you to tell
me about your home.
PENNY (ON TAPE): What we need
is a positive role model,
A hero you might say, who could
rally the citizens to take
Action and make a difference.
I'm Penny Price,
Channel 5 Action News.
So what do you think?
Air it, tonight, and I'd
better not regret this.
Not a chance, Cogs.
Not a chance.
What do you two want?
A drink, is there
a problem with that?
Yeah, you got a
problem with that?
The usual.
Let's see the cash.
That is the last of
our money, Mandrak.
A moment of pleasure.
Ah.
Destiny has cursed
us both, my friend.
We are no better off
here than we were at home.
We have no home but here.
There is no turning back.
You said the crystal
would make us rich.
It is not my fault the
crystal has lost its power.
My luck will change.
It must.
Oh, I must be a mess.
I'm going to take a shower.
Make yourself at home.
Listen to this,
and I'll be back.
Come to me.
I need a woman.
There ain't no way you're gonna
get me back in that dump again.
Hey, watch the
merchandise, honey.
Last time you did
that is the last time.
You're too rough for me, sugar.
And besides, if you
ain't got the money,
Then there ain't
nothing for you, honey.
Master, remember,
this is not the forest.
The forest.
[Evil laugh]
[Silly music playing]
Sorry, Penny, no luck.
[Busy signal]
Damn it, Penny,
get off the phone!
What we need is a positive role
model, a hero you might say,
Who could rally the
citizens to take
Action and make a difference.
I must be crazy.
Nah, this is exactly what gives
KPTC the cutting edge, Cogs.
It's about time
you got some balls.
Watch it, mister,
or I'll have your ass
On that sewer plant special
for the next four weeks.
Easy, Cogs, I was just joking.
PENNY (ON TV): He didn't
make this week's payment.
This is just one gang-related
incident in over 239
That have happened in
our city this year.
It appears that
man does not change.
PENNY (ON TV): Whatever
happened to morals,
Ethics, and common decency?
[Laughter]
Here it comes.
THUG (ON TV): What's
going on here?
Doran.
It can't be.
Why does it seem
like I know you?
It's almost frightening.
There is no reason for
you to fear when with me.
When you find him, what then?
If I am triumphant in
battle, I must return home.
Do not leave me, Doran.
Stay.
Please, stay.
That was him.
That was Doran.
I know who it was, you idiot.
How did he get here?
He's come for revenge.
By all the gods.
What are we going
to do about him?
Mandrak, what do we do?
Don't be a fool.
He does not know where we are.
It's only a matter of
time before he finds us,
And then he will
chop off my head.
We must kill him first.
Kill him before he finds us.
We kill him first.
Yes.
This Penny Price, she
will lead us to Doran.
You boys are in luck today.
I just got in a new shipment.
Yeah, anything you can
possibly want, I got.
Let's take a look.
Hmm, yeah, oh, M-16s,
AK-47s, Uzis, oh, look,
Magazines up the ying yang.
Hey, hey, special
grenades, boom, gentlemen,
Pick your poison.
Something simple,
but effective.
Oh, hmm, aha, here's a beauty.
Yeah, this'll take
on your barbarian.
Here, try it out.
I will take one of those.
Yes, watch.
Here.
You like 'em small, huh?
Well, you know what
they say, a guy's gun
Is as big as his prick.
Hey, just joking, you guys.
OK, we're gonna get
back down to business.
Uh, that'll be, uh,
four bills all together.
And I'm gonna tell
you right now,
You're not gonna get a better
deal anywhere on the streets.
Hey, watch where you guys
are pointing those things.
Have a nice day.
Who the hell are you?
Where is the
woman, Penny Price?
What do you want with her?
I ask the questions.
You answer.
Just tell us where she is.
Damn you, get out of
here, or I'll... I'll have
Every cop I know
up your ass pulling
Out your fucking [inaudible].
You will answer
now, or I will cut
Off your fingers one by one.
You go to hell.
No!
Very well.
Your daughter, it would be
a pity if she were to die.
Now, tell me where the woman is.
Cogs would kill me
if he knew I had this.
Cogs?
Is you OK?
They want Penny.
Who wants Penny?
Penny.
Don't worry, Penny, I'm coming.
This is yours.
My hand.
The amulet, where is it?
I don't have it.
You're a liar and a murderer.
It's hidden.
Where?
Somewhere close.
Hey, I'll take you there.
[Gunshot]
Give me the weapon.
Come on.
Now you die, barbarian.
PENNY: Doran?
Who are these men?
Stop.
Move away, barbarian,
or I'll kill
Her right before your eyes.
No.
Do as I say.
Your sword is no match
for these weapons.
I bid you farewell.
No.
Doran.
Kill him.
He has left you here to die.
Die?
I have this.
Doctor, come on!
Move it!
Come on.
Where is Mandrak?
Speak!
Where's Penny?
Mandrak has captured her.
He will lead me to him.
He looks dead to me.
He dies when I want him to die.
OK, OK.
I'll go with you.
You?
Yeah, me.
What?
You got a problem with that?
You do not look like a warrior.
Oh, yeah?
Let me tell you something, pal.
I can handle myself.
Then together we
shall do battle.
Battle?
Well, yeah, battle.
I think I know where
we can find this slime.
It's a little, nice
place you got here, huh?
What do you want?
I'm looking for a man,
a man with one hand.
Have you seen him here?
Yeah, I've seen him,
damn trouble maker.
Who the fuck are you?
Hey, look, don't
matter who I am.
Where can I find this guy?
How the hell would I know?
Look what he did to my TV.
Next time he comes in
here, I'm gonna kill him.
So beat it, before I do
the same thing to you.
All right, relax.
What?
For a minute there, I almost
thought you were a cop.
Look, I'm not
interested, all right?
You're looking for Mandrak.
You're interested.
All right, talk to me.
I'm gonna cost you, sugar.
You're beginning to
look familiar to me,
Someone I knew a long time ago.
You pig.
Let me down.
Perhaps you can put me on the
television, make me famous,
Like the movie stars.
If that's what you
want, I can rearrange it.
Just let me down.
That's not all that I want.
Allow me to introduce myself,
Mandrak the Magnificent,
At your service.
Mandrak?
You're the one he's...
The man with one hand.
It is indeed I.
Oh, God.
This place gives me the creeps.
It's a trap!
Mandrak.
There she is, barbarian.
Free her.
I give you this chance,
for I am a fair man.
No, Doran, don't
come any closer.
Let me nail him.
[Gun clicking]
Damn, I knew I forgot something.
By the gods.
Doran.
Wait.
Hey, are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Its out of control, Brice.
Maybe you should go.
Are you kidding me?
Show yourself, coward.
Stay here.
Run.
You took my hand, barbarian,
but gave me a weapon.
I'm gonna get you, creep.
She was delectable, barbarian.
Her body was all mine to
do with whatever I please.
That's really why you
came back, isn't it?
Well, the amulet is useless,
dead and lifeless, just
Like she was when I left her.
Your evil shall
end by my sword!
There is no way back
for you, barbarian.
Welcome to hell.
I wonder if hope is
lost for all mankind.
No, it's not.
You and I are no different.
It doesn't matter when
it is or where we are,
We'll both make damn sure
that hope stays where it
Belongs, in our hearts forever.
[Penny crying]
Our love shall be
for an eternity.
You OK, Penny?
He wasn't such a
bad guy after all.
OK, look, turn the camera
on, and no matter what...
No matter what,
keep it rolling.
Got it.
Rolling.
The end to a story of
gallantry and heroism, not
To mention sacrifice...
The streets
Are rid of one more malignancy.
And the world has only
the memory of a great man
Who some would consider a king.
This is Penny Price,
Channel 5 Action News.
[Music playing]