Slow down, Fred.
We wanna get there in one piece.
We're already late. It's the grand
re-opening of the Grimsley Mansion.
And we would've been there by now if
someone didn't have to stop us for take-out.
Two someones.
Like, let's dig in.
Fred, the mansion's been there
for over a 100 years. It's not going away.
I'm just anxious to take a crack
at finding its secret treasure.
- Maybe, we'll even see the ghost.
- Ghost?
It's supposedly haunted.
We better eat up, Scoob.
This might be our last meal.
Whoa!
Like, these sandwiches
could use a seat belt.
You may have recognized Grimsley Mansion
from several movie productions.
There are even films on its founder.
Augustus Grimsley. Fascinating man.
For example, did you know
that he was a Roman history buff?
An amateur astrologist
and a scratch bowler.
Who cares about all that stuff?
What about the treasure?
Yeah. And what about the ghost
that haunts this place?
Gentlemen, there is no real evidence
that there even is a treasure or a ghost.
Ghost!
- Please, don't drain my blood.
- Please, don't haunt my dreams.
No, dear. We didn't mean
to scare you that much.
I'm Charlie Grimsley and that's
my brother Kyle. We're your host.
Hi, there. Enjoying your stay?
We figured folks
would expect a little scare
while they are looking for our
great-great grandfather's treasure.
- So this is all a hoax?
- What's going on here?
I told you this was a terrible idea, Kyle.
The guests want real treasure.
- Not fake spooks.
- But there is no treasure, Charlie.
What do you mean no treasure?
My brother is just kidding.
There may be a treasure.
But nobody's ever found it yet.
Maybe you will.
- Then, join us for breakfast.
- Yeah, there's a waffle bar.
Nah, I wasn't really scared.
At least, we're done with that lecture.
Look at that.
Hey, the treasure could be inside.
Pulling some more tricks again, eh?
Phil, I don't think he's kidding.
No, comeback.
Fred, look out!
Is everyone okay?
Now we're going to have to find the treasure
to pay for the Mystery Machine.
Howdy-ho there travelers. Looks like you've
got yourself a smidgen of car trouble.
Wanda Grimsley. Groundskeeper, mechanic,
and and Jill of all trades.
I can handle this.
You can fix the mystery machine?
Well, I think I'm gonna upgrade you
from a smidgen to a scooch.
But not to worry,
I'll get it purring by morning.
Meanwhile,
my cousins can take care of you.
Monsters!
What? Oh, right. Sorry.
You see. It's all just for fun.
Phew.
Come on in. Welcome to Grimsley Mansion.
They were frightened by a suit of armor?
Yes, it's so silly. Their imaginations
must have run away with them.
- The black knight, it's gone!
- What do you mean gone?
I mean it's gone. It ran away.
This whole thing's been a disaster.
- There's no treasure and I never should...
- Kyle, please. Customers.
Oh, sorry.
Maybe we should hear more
about this black knight.
- I might be able to help you there.
- Oh, this is Adam, our house historian.
Is that a MENSA honors pin?
Why yes. Yes, it is.
- It's very impressive.
- You think?
- Uh, the uh, story?
- Yes, the story.
Well, it's all part of the legend
of Grimsley Mansion.
In the late 1800s,
Augustus Grimsley was a prospector.
A very lucky prospector.
Wealthy beyond his wildest dreams,
and not trusting banks,
he decided to build a huge mansion
where he would hoard his gold.
He also gave in to his rapacious appetite
for furnishings and antiquities
including his prized purchase...
a beautiful suit of black armor.
But all this wealth would take its toll.
Late at night,
Gus Grimsley start to hear noises.
Clanking noises.
Could only have been the suit of armor
marching down the halls.
The next day, he found out why.
The armor was once worn by the black knight
who tried to steal his king's riches.
But he was caught and thrown
into a dungeon never to be seen again.
Augustus was convinced the black knight
was now after his gold.
He had the armor taken away.
But he still feared the black knight
would return one day.
So, he hid the treasure vowing,
"Though the ghost may search forever,
"it's my family that shall find.
It's only a matter of time."
Will you guys stop fooling around?
- Like, sorry, we're just hungry.
- Yeah, hungry.
Kyle, why don't you take them to the dining
room? We have an all-you-can-eat buffet.
- They had an all-you-can-eat buffet.
- Oh? Yeah.
I don't understand. If the black knight
was in storage, how did it get back here?
Wanda brought it back in her obsession
to turn this place into a museum.
And what's wrong with that? It's not like
the treasure hunters bringing in the crowds.
- Excuse us. Family squabbles.
- What do you want, Wanda?
Well, it sure would make
my life a lot easier
if we could take those
heavy boxes out of the van.
Oh, those are my monster traps.
Will any of them catch a ghost?
Since we're staying,
might as well get the luggage.
Why don't I show you around?
This place has such a splendid history.
That would be sweet.
Good. That would be good.
Like, thanks for the buffet
and the midnight snack, Kyle.
What does it matter if we're out of food?
We don't seem to be getting
anymore customers.
My brother thought the lore
of a treasure would bring everyone.
And it's only brought disaster.
Huh? Like, what was that?
A booby-trap.
Our great-great granddad put in a bunch.
Wanda has been trying to remove them.
Like, Scoob, you almost saw stars.
Yeah, big ones.
Nah, this whole place is a trap.
Get out while you can.
He seems so sad.
Yeah, like, isn't it funny how sadness
can sometimes make you hungry?
Yeah.
Pretzel?
It's the black knight!
Yikes! Oh!
Shaggy! Come on!
Like, help!
Whoa!
Yikes!
Come on, Scoob. Let's get out of here.
Phew. I think we lost him, Scoob.
Yeah. And look what I picked up?
Like, halfsies, right, old buddy, old pal?
What was that?
Hey, where's my sandwich?
- Maybe you ate it.
- Maybe someone else ate it.
Like, dude. No way.
And that is my half.
- Hmm? Hmm.
- What happened to the rest of it?
- I don't know.
- I do.
Uh-oh.
- Shaggy!
- Like, hugs are not gonna help.
Yikes!
Even though Augustus chose
a Victorian sensibility for the house,
he included eccentric touches.
Like the death traps.
I hope I'm not being tiresome.
Jenkies, no. Coming from you
it doesn't sound boring at all.
- Boo!
- Ah.
Ha, it's just me.
Hey, did you guys find anything?
I think they have, Fred,
but it isn't clues.
You know, my great-great granddaddy
did leave a clue to the treasure in his will.
So, there really is a treasure.
Well, Augustus was a bit of a kidder
and crazy to boot.
He said that the clue would smack you
in the kisser when you saw it.
And I know where I'd look for it.
In his study.
Come on, I'll show you.
We'll join you in a minute.
I still wanna explore the lobby.
Yeah, uh-huh.
I don't think she thought
you were serious.
The truth is Adam, I'd much rather
spend a little more time with...
Oh, jenkies, what's that?
Oh, that's a painting
by Augustus Grimsley.
- I didn't know he was a painter.
- He wasn't.
This was the only picture he ever painted.
Right before he died.
I suppose it has a certain
primitive charm. What do you see?
I see a clue.
Here's the study.
- Are those Roman gladiators?
- Yup.
Uncle Augustus sure loved his Roman history.
Well, I gotta keep working.
Happy hunting.
What's wrong now?
- We're being stalked by a hungry hibiscus.
- And the black knight too.
- You saw the black knight?
- Yeah.
Like, someone's gotta tell that dude
that knights are the good guys.
Oh, no. The Romans are roaming.
Yikes!
We're locked in.
Whoa!
They are running on tracks.
If I could just time this right.
Oh, there you are.
Have I got something to show you.
According to the position in the picture,
this is Sirius. The morning star.
Morning star? What could it mean?
We saw a star. A big star.
Just down this hall.
Here it is.
Like, sorry.
Hmm.
A morning star. That's what they used to call
a spiked club like this in Medieval times.
Hey, there's an opening.
I can't see anything.
Wait. In the picture
the star was shining, right?
Right.
The key to the treasure.
Huh?
Like, what do you hear, Scoob?
Check it out.
It's crazy, old, great grandpa Grimsley.
Like, there's something written here.
"This thing runs but cannot walk,
"sometimes sings but never talks,
"lacks arms, has hands,
"lacks a head but has a face."
- It's a riddle.
- It's not very funny.
Let's see. It runs and it sings...
- And it has a face and hands.
- A clock!
Jeepers. Didn't Augustus also say something
about, "it's only a matter of time?"
It's in the clock tower. Come on.
Wait, don't worry, buddy.
I'll find a ladder.
I don't see any door that fits this key.
Maybe it's not for a door, Fred.
Maybe it's a key to the clock.
A-ha.
It fits.
The clock hands are moving.
It's unlocked.
- You did it. You've found it.
- We found it.
- Hey!
- No!
We're trapped.
Like, I hope there's
a snack machine up there.
'Cause this is one long climb.
Like, time to net the knight, Scoob.
Oh!
Yikes!
Over there, Scoob!
Go.
Oh.
- Yikes!
- Dude, what are you doing?
Black knight.
Oh, no!
Hmm?
- Whoa.
- No!
- Bye-bye.
- Scooby, I can't see.
It worked. These bars
are worth their weight in gold.
Like, do you think we lost him?
Hey, Scoob,
does this hallway look familiar?
Yeah.
- Uh-oh. Like, I think he knows.
- No!
Oh, no.
You did it. You caught the black knight.
What is that?
No, Eugene. Come here.
Who's a good fly-trap?
Who's a good baby boy?
You are. Yes, you are.
He's harmless.
One of uncle Augustus' exotic plants.
Raised him from a seed.
Didn't he baby? Yes, he did.
Okay. Now, let's see
who the black knight really is.
Like, it's nobody?
It's somebody, all right.
Kyle? Good heavens. What's going on?
It's pretty evident, Charlie. Your brother
wanted all the gold for himself.
That's why he was so insistent
that there was no treasure.
And when Wanda brought the black
knight armor back to the mansion
he saw his opportunity to scare away anyone
who might come looking for the gold.
Oh, and my plan would've worked too,
if it hadn't been for you meddling kids,
and your dog. And that stupid plant.
Oh.
You're not stupid.
Don't you listen to him. Don't you do it.
You know, deep down I never believed
there was a real treasure, but...
since you've found it, I guess
you should be the ones to have it.
That's okay, Charlie.
We know it belongs to your family.
We're just happy to have found it.
Oh, if you're gonna be that generous,
then the car repair is on the house.
I wanna come with you, Velma. I really do.
But I can't leave the mansion.
They need me here.
And my friends need me. Sometimes
it's such a curse to be the smart one.
We're on our way, Velma.
Where's Scooby?
Like, he's sharing his Scooby-Snacks
with his new friend.
Scooby-dooby-doo!