(BETTER DAYS PLAYING)
♪ I'm feeling of this change
That I'm on to something new
♪ There's something in the air
♪ Something that could
break our tune
♪ A spark of light is visible
from where I stand
♪ I can see it getting bright
♪ The time is getting
close at hand
♪ Pulled me to jump off
to the path that leads me
to the place
♪ I'm looking out
for better days ♪
(BELL RINGING)
NOLAN: I never understood
why I should care about
creatures that lived
60 million years ago,
had brains the size of Pez,
and happily crushed
the smaller and weaker
of their species
simply because,
well, they could.
Until the day I realized
that I was the weaker
of the species.
(SCREAMS)
Put me down!
NOLAN: And, for me,
it seemed there
was no escape.
(BELL RINGING)
It's terrible, but true.
Right here at Cedar
Valley Junior High,
a predator stalked the halls.
A beast more horrible
and cruel and smelly
than any creature
we ever learned about
in Mr. Green's class.
(BURPS LOUDLY)
Bubba Bixby was
the T. rex  of my world.
And I, Nolan Byrd,
was his lunch.
For someone who paid
zero attention in school,
Bubba Bixby
actually taught me a lot.
There's the noogie,
(SCREAMING)
purple nurples,
the fish hook,
(LAUGHS)
goober yo-yo,
the donkey dance,
the finger snap sap,
and the never-gets-old
classic, the atomic wedgie.
Where did this guy come from?
Did he crawl out
of the primordial ooze?
Or was the theory of nature
versus nurture to blame?
After all, Bubba's father,
the Sewage King
of Cedar Valley,
taught Bubba
everything he knew.
And none of it was good.
Searching for a solution
to my endless Bubba nightmare,
my parents forced me to meet
with the school principal,
Dr. Voss.
This little tiff
between yourself
and young Mr. Bixby
is just a good
life lesson, Nolan.
The world is full of
rambunctious people
like Bubba.
And... Well,
learning to deal with it
is all part of growing up.
You should be thanking him.
Thanking him?
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah, that helped.
My ex-best and only friend,
Max, ditched me for Bubba
to protect his own butt.
I guess he felt
being Bubba's right hand
was better than being
under his left foot.
(TAUNTING) Whoo!
Those of us who didn't
join forces with the enemy
were given nicknames.
I'm Weird-Eyed Wally.
Teeny the Weenie.
Art the Fart.
Dirt Wad Todd.
Man-Hands Miriam.
And, of course,
I was no exception.
Byrd Turd.
Here's Byrd Turd. Byrd Turd.
Something had to change.
Was this how it
was gonna be forever?
Here, ducky.
(QUACKING)
(NOLAN SCREAMS)
Byrd Turd.
(COUGHING)
(NOLAN SHUDDERS)
I hope not.
Thankfully, there was still
one place on Earth
where I could forget
about Bubba.
Emerald Pond
was the only place
I could perfect
the so-far impossible task
of piloting three
remote vehicles at once.
That's right. I said three.
(ZOOMING)
(ENGINE FALTERING)
(BEEPING)
(NOLAN GROANS)
History will have to
be made another day.
Okay, truth.
This isn't the only reason
I love hanging at the pond.
(NOLAN SIGHS)
I first saw Isabel here
when I was in kindergarten.
Hi, my name is Isabel.
I made my own kite.
Isabel was the kind
of girl who could smile
after eating a fudge brownie
and still look perfect.
And through all
we had in common,
our mutual love of the pond,
and the aerodynamics
of flying,
our relationship had blossomed
into nothing.
Oh!
(CRASHING)
(MACHINE BEEPING)
(MAN SCREAMS)
Oh!
Oh, just great.
Man!
(DOG BARKS)
Oh, your kite got...
Uh, the...
Do you...
Do you need, uh...
Okay, so you wanna help?
Thank you.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Oh... Yeah.
Thank you.
(GRUNTS)
NOLAN: Too high...
(GRUNTING)
Can't reach...
There were robin eggs
in the nest
and I didn't
wanna scramble eggs.
Well, thanks. I guess.
Nolan Byrd,
you are so weird.
(SIGHS)
I could've been a hero.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON TV)
Could. Have. Been.
STICKY: Sure,
you're a great hero, Gecko.
But maybe it's
time to surrender.
Surrender? The word
has no meaning to me.
Until now.
Give up? Never.
Together,
Sticky, we will defeat
the epicenter of injustice
and save the universe.
Together, we ride.
MOM:
Hey, kiddo, beautiful day.
Why aren't you out
playing hoops, or handball,
or catching something?
Bubonic plague would be nice.
Well, why don't you
fly your planes
over at the pond?
Hey, how's that
three-remote challenge
coming along?
A little slow since
my planes blew up.
Well, why don't you
hang out with Max?
He's embraced the dark side.
And just think,
you and Max
were going to get married
when you were five.
You know,
I still have the tape.
Nolan's my best friend,
and I love him.
We're gonna get married.
Yeah.
BOTH: We're gonna get married.
For the record,
he proposed.
Not me.
Bubba's on your back again.
I don't want to
talk about it.
No... On your back, there.
What?
(GRUNTS)
Why? How does he do that?
Maybe it's time
for another sit-down
with Principal Voss.
Oh, please.
I taught Sheila Voss.
She makes as much sense
as horns on a poodle.
Bullies versus nerds has been
an ongoing struggle
since cave nerds
invented fire,
and cave bullies thanked them
by burning their butts
with it.
Don't let Bubba get
under your skin, Nolan.
Not quite sure
that whole cave
nerd comparison
was the morale booster
you intended there, Dad.
Oh, your dad's not
saying you're a nerd.
He just means that
all of us go through
these awkward stages.
And well...
You know, back in the day,
your father was perceived
as some kind of a nerd and...
(LAUGHS)
Look at him now.
Semicolon.
(BELL RINGING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(BLOWS)
Sweet jet pen
you got there,
Byrd Turd.
Think I'm gonna
have to get me
one of these.
That's mine.
(EXHALES)
All right, guys,
if you could stop
text messaging each other
under your desks,
we can get our day started.
MR. GREEN: Thank you.
Whatever happened
to passing notes?
Anybody remember?
Paper, pen?
No? Okay, great.
All right,
well, as you all know,
today is the first
Monday of the month,
and that means...
(PLAYS ELECTRIC GUITAR)
♪ Project assignment day ♪
MR. GREEN: Yeah.
(APPLAUSE)
Yeah. Sweet.
You're my boy, Dirt Wad.
I expect a B.
Hey, you should
shred on this one.
You get to use your computer,
so have a good time with it.
Cool, Mr. Green.
Okay, everybody,
this month I want
you guys to do
a multimedia report
on an issue that
is important to you.
Anything goes
this month, okay?
You can use the Internet.
You can use your computer,
digital camera,
Ouija board,
two cans and a string.
Whatever you want.
Just take advantage
of the technology.
All right, everybody,
now close your eyes.
And think about
what gets you going.
It could be
a person or an issue.
The most important part is,
pick a topic that you
feel passionate about.
I want you to reach inside
and find that thing
that you care deeply about.
(SOFTLY) Nolan...
Or even that injustice
that you want to change.
Find your inner voice,
the one that is
screaming out,
and maybe you
can make a change.
NOLAN: Make a change.
That's it.
It's time for Nolan Byrd
to strike back.
(WALKIN' ON THE SUN PLAYING)
♪ It ain't no joke
I'd like to buy
the world a...
♪ And teach the world
to sing in perfect harmony
to snuff...
NOLAN: If I can't take
Bubba on face-to-face,
I'll do it
the only way I know how.
♪ This is a love attack
♪ I know it went out
but it's back
♪ It's just like any fad
it retracts before impact
NOLAN: I want the whole world
to see him in action,
and spying on him will be
the fastest, simplest
and, to be honest,
safest way to do it.
♪ Buy it just to
stay in the clique
♪ So don't delay act now
supplies are running out
♪ Allow if you're still alive
♪ Six to eight years to arrive
♪ And if you follow
there may be a tomorrow
♪ But if the offer is shun
You might as well be
walkin' on the sun
♪ Twenty-five years ago
♪ They spoke out
and they broke out
♪ Of recession and oppression
and together they...
♪ And they folked out
with guitars around a bonfire
♪ Just singin' and clappin'
man...
♪ Then some were spellbound...
Mr. Green wants us
to expose injustice.
It's time to expose
everyone to the epicenter
of injustice and
save the universe.
♪ Because fashion is smashin'
the true meaning of it
♪ So don't delay act now
supplies are running out
♪ Allow if you're still alive
six to eight years to arrive
♪ And if you follow
there may be a tomorrow
♪ But if the offer is shun
You might as well
be walkin' on the sun
Nolan, what're you doing?
Nothing.
What do you mean, "nothing"?
Oh, no. I didn't.
The absolute worst answer
you can give a parent
is "nothing."
Nolan, what are you doing?
Adjusting
the electrodes in Diego's head
so that he can speak German.
Okay, honey. Have fun.
Okay, Diego, it's time
for our moment of truth.
♪ It ain't no joke
When a mama's
handkerchief is soaked
♪ With her tears
because her baby's life
has been revoked
♪ The bond is broke up
so choke up and focus
on the close-up
♪ Mr. Wizard can't perform
no godlike hocus-pocus ♪
(GRUNTS)
Uh...
Mr. Green, can I get something
out of the back? I...
MR. GREEN: Yeah, go for it.
Did I get it?
Please say I got it.
(TAPE REWINDING)
NOLAN: Ew!
I'll never eat ham again.
What you looking at?
(STAMMERING)
Oh, I was just...
Learning about
my new backpack and how,
when you pull the zipper,
it opens.
Way cool, right?
I'll just stick it...
Dr. Simon says
we have the exact same
food allergies.
Well, it's a good thing
we're not having kids.
He said that
won't be a problem.
Oh?
You smell good.
It's tuna fish.
Yum.
Nolan. Miriam.
Would you guys
like to join us?
Wait.
Excuse me.
MR. GREEN: All right, I have
the results of last week's
test and, you know,
if some of you guys could
study a little bit harder,
it would be great.
That's yours.
By the way, FYI,
the first person
to circumnavigate
the globe
was not Santa Claus.
Oh, right.
Do you have gum
in your mouth?
No.
And some people
belong in high school.
Yeah. I do shred.
(BELL RINGING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
(FLUSHING)
(CAMERA WHIRRING)
(GRUNTS)
(LAUGHING)
Yes.
Nolan Byrd,
you've done it again.
Hey, just think, you did it
without Mommy to help you.
You're not just a nerd.
You're, like, a pervert, too.
He's a... He's like a...
Like a nerd-vert.
Yeah, that's what you are.
You nerd-vert.
It's funny, the way
you mixed "nerd" and "vert"
like peanut butter
and chocolate.
Well, I gotta go.
Wait a minute there,
Byrd Turd.
Looks a lot like my backpack.
What do you think, Max?
Yeah, what do you think, Max?
Um...
Yeah, yeah. Sort of.
No, it's mine.
I got the receipt
and everything, so bye.
Well, it sure does
look like mine.
How's about that?
Oh. I see what's different.
It doesn't have the...
The purple nurples.
(LAUGHING)
Hey, don't say
I never gave you anything.
Move it, maxi pad.
(BEEPING)
Nolito?
One sec.
Hey, Mom just told me
that you're pretty excited
about your
social studies project.
You know,
with my fairly impressive
newspaper contacts,
I could really
help you out.
It's okay, Dad.
I'm fine.
Well, Nole...
(SQUEAKING)
(CHUCKLING)
A fish on my tail.
Nole, come here, sit down.
Hey, Nolan, I want to
be an involved father
and be a part of your world.
And that means sharing.
I want us to
share everything.
No secrets, okay?
Okay. Got it.
But the truth is,
Mr. Green wants us
to do this one by ourselves.
Well, that makes sense.
After all, it's your name
that's going on it.
Exactly.
My name's going on it.
Mmm-hmm.
All over it.
Yeah.
Well, I just thought
I'd throw that out there.
If you need ol' Dad,
I'm here for you.
Hey, I love you, buddy.
Me, too.
If you need me...
Okay, okay, no need to panic.
We just need another name.
Something that
says Nolan Byrd,
then actually doesn't.
Something cool.
An alias.
Okay, think.
Messy Man.
What else?
Spare Parts Person.
That's pretty lame.
The goal is to shred Bubba
totally undetected.
Yeah. That's it.
I'll be the Shredder.
No, that sounds
like a slasher guy
who hangs up photos of people
with their eyes cut out.
Wait a minute.
I'll be...
Shredderman.
Grandma,
I need to ask you a favor.
I've been doing this
project for school,
and well,
it's for Mom and Dad,
and I really don't
want them to find out
about it. Like a surprise.
Uh-huh.
So I was wondering,
if I paid you back,
could I use your credit card
to get what I need online?
Is it a secure site?
Yeah. Totally.
Well, all righty, Nolan.
As long as it's safe.
I do like safe.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(WHOOPING)
Bubba. His name is Bubba.
Here's his brains.
Hubba hubba.
Let's watch Bubba.
So much to love-a.
Just watch him shove-a.
Break it down.
ROBOTIC VOICE:
♪ Bubba, his name is Bubba
♪ Bubba's busted
Shredderman rules
♪ Here's his brains
Hubba hubba
♪ Bubba's busted
Shredderman rules
♪ Let's watch Bubba
So much to love-a
♪ Bubba's busted
Shredderman rules
♪ His name is Bubba
Just watch him shove-a
♪ Bubba's busted
Shredderman rules
♪ Break it down
♪ Bubba's busted
Shredderman rules
♪ Break it down ♪
NOLAN: Now, how do I get
people to see it?
This is the Sewage King
reminding you
that a royal flush
always beats a full house.
MAN: Bixby's Royal Flush.
Call for a free estimate.
Yeah, advertising
can work for anyone.
But how?
ANNOUNCER: And now back
to Gecko and Sticky.
GECKO: The only way
we are gonna save the universe
is to climb to the top
of this building
and let the wind
spread the antidote
to all the citizens
of this fair city.
But, Gecko,
that's a huge undertaking.
If you're going to be
a superhero, Sticky,
then you have to
do superhero things.
He is so right.
NOLAN:
I know what I have to do.
(BELL RINGING)
That's all I got, man.
BUBBA: Yo, Byrd Turd.
What did your mommy
make me for lunch?
Brussels sprouts.
And onion pie.
Oh, and some radishes.
Gross.
Next time,
tell her to make me something
a little bit more refreshing.
Maybe some
springtime mangoes.
Cup and a half of grapes
with some cottage cheese.
Large curd.
MIRIAM: Nolan.
Oh, no.
I saved you a place.
(GROANS)
Thanks Miriam,
but I forgot to do
something. So...
I can do this.
I'm not afraid of heights.
I'm so afraid of heights.
But I can't give up.
I'm... I'm...
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
Never been so happy
to see a janitor
in my life.
No nausea. Good sign.
(GRUNTING)
Whoa!
...that you multiply
by a whole number.
For example,
take the digits zero, four
and one. If you multiply...
I'm not scared.
I can do this.
(EXHALES)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
"Is Bubba Bixby
causing you grief?"
"Try ShreddermanRules.com
for comic relief."
Come on,
let's check it out.
(LAUGHS) Yeah.
Yo. You see this, turdo?
Actually, Todd,
it's Nolan.
Just wanted to see
if you wanted to check out
this Bubba stuff with me.
Nolan.
Yeah.
(GIRL LAUGHING)
What is going on here?
What is this all about?
(KIDS LAUGHING)
TODD: Okay,
ShreddermanRules.com.
♪ Bubba's busted
Shredderman rules ♪
This really is a cool site.
Yeah, it's got over 600 ways
to get back at Bubba.
How'd you know that?
♪ Bubba's busted
Shredderman rules ♪
Lucky guess.
♪ Bubba's busted
Shredderman rules ♪
Gentlemen, the website
you are currently visiting
is not on Dr. Voss'
approved list.
Kindly exit
the website immediately
and proceed to your
next scheduled class.
Dude, Dr. Voss
doesn't approve.
If the man is trying to
stop us from looking at it,
it must be good.
♪ Bubba's busted
Shredderman rules ♪
(BELL RINGING)
I want everyone
back in the classroom
immediately. Go, go, go. Out!
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
Go, go!
(MAN EXCLAIMING ON COMPUTER)
This is hysterical.
Whoever made this site
is a genius.
Can you print it out?
Print it out.
Yeah.
♪ Bubba, his name is Bubba
♪ Bubba's busted
Shredderman rules ♪
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
(STATIC CRACKLING)
There will be
no more Internet
or cell phone use
in this school for
the remainder of the day.
(KIDS GROANING)
Man.
Dude, that's whack.
It's a conspiracy.
It's all right, guys.
Come on, let's get
back to work
on our projects.
It'll be fun.
Hey, Bubba.
Who do you think
did that website?
What, do you think
I can read minds?
Like I got PMS
or something?
How am I supposed
to know who made up
the website?
But when I find out...
All right, guys,
look, I was thinking
before lunch I would do a...
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Mr. Green,
may I speak with you please?
Sure. Excuse me.
Dr. Voss.
I hope Shredderman
doesn't get busted.
He's so cool.
Don't you think?
(CHUCKLING)
Nice. Yeah, cary vool.
Now.
Okay.
(HEARTBEAT THUMPING)
Dr. Voss would
like to have a word
with you, Mr. Bixby.
Word about what?
I didn't even do nothing.
Bubba's busted.
Shredderman rules.
He really does rule.
(WHOOPS)
I can't believe it.
Bubba's finally been busted.
Oh, I can't wait to see
what Shredderman's
gonna do next.
NOLAN: Turns out Bubba
wasn't the only one
doing bad things.
And my camera
caught them all.
Mr. Brown you get a...B.
Lucky you.
Keep moving, maggots.
Any of you puke or die
and I'm adding
10 more laps.
I'm glad I got
my degree in PE.
Miss Saltzer,
you get a... Oh, a D.
Not good, Miss Saltzer.
Not good at all.
All right.
Dear Shredderman,
I already loved the website
when you used it
to bring Bubba down,
but now, by exposing
all the injustices
in this school,
you're making life
better for everyone.
You're my hero.
"Keep up the good work."
This is too good.
Dear Isabel...
Bubba?
I know who you are,
Chicken Little.
And you'll be sorry
you were ever even hatched.
No.
No way he knows it's me.
He couldn't. Could he?
I have a firewall.
No, he's gotta be faking it.
He has to be.
No. I'm not falling for it.
Well, this Chicken Little
is dropping the sky
on your head, loser.
Take that, sucker.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Nole, everything
okay up there?
Yeah. Just doing
some homework.
It's actually kind of fun.
Homework, fun?
You want me to
come up there and...
No. No, thanks.
Fun's over.
Back to the grind.
Thanks, Dad.
Gotta hit the books.
What? No.
Where's my jet pen?
I definitely put it in here
before the bell.
(BEEPS)
(TAPE REWINDING)
All right, that's it.
There's no way
you're getting away
with this, this time.
Prepare to be shredded.
Hey, Nole,
it's awfully quiet up there,
what you doing?
Noth... I'm splitting atoms
with Mom's hairdryer.
Okay, buddy, keep it up.
Just hand over the jet pen
and no one gets hurt.
Hand over the jet pen
or I'll turn mashed
potatoes into your face.
I'll give you to
the count of three
before I have
to call in the sheriff
and the deputy.
Don't make me get backup.
MR. BIXBY: Come on,
let's take a spin
in the dumper.
I'll show you some
tricks of the trade.
Sweet.
Remember,
in the sewage business,
"Tide and time
wait for no man."
Yeah!
These are all things to know
if all this one day
is gonna be yours.
The truck?
No, you stupendously
misinformed child.
The business.
Right. Sorry.
Cool.
Let's go.
That Shredderman site's
just some stupid,
cruddy cartoon show
some no-life loser
at school made up.
And you don't know
who's behind it.
Oh, yeah...
No. No, I don't.
But when I do...
All right. All right.
Don't let it get you down.
Desperate little
people always take
cheap shots
at big people like us.
Bubba, they're jealous of us.
Yeah?
Look at the two of us.
Me, I'm good-looking,
I'm rich, I'm smart.
You, you take
after your mother.
Even now, Papa Bear
is working on a plan
to outsmart the entire town.
BUBBA: Yeah.
That's so great.
You are?
Yes.
I've generously
offered to rebuild
the old water
reclamation plant
down by the pond.
Once I have
the town's support
for my phony eco-mission,
I'll enact my real plan.
A plan that gives me
access to a pond.
A pond that I can use
for my own advantage,
if you catch my drift.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, yeah!
I don't catch it.
What's important
is that you understand
that your old man
is trying to build
a sewage dynasty
that stretches from
sea to shining sea.
And then one day,
one glorious day,
whenever anybody
hears the name Bixby,
they'll think of crap.
Yeah. Crap.
(BIXBYS LAUGHING)
So what're we doing
way out here?
Insurance.
We're gonna guarantee
that the contract
is awarded to us.
Yeah, but won't
we get in trouble
for dumping this
thing out here?
(LAUGHING)
No.
Gary will.
Oh, man.
I hope one day
I'm as smart as you.
That's really nice, Son.
You can hope. Let's go.
(WHIRRING)
What are you doing?
What are you doing? No!
Yes.
Okay.
(ENGINE STARTING)
Ugh...
(BELL RINGING)
Well, as many of you know,
Bubba Bixby has
been suspended
for two days
for the none-too-cool
incidents that appeared
on the Shredderman Rules
website.
Yeah.
(WHOOPS)
Don't take it so hard, kids.
Shredderman
really took out Bubba
like he promised.
Yeah, he did.
Mr. Green,
everyone thinks
you're Shredderman.
BOY: Yeah, are you?
GIRL: Yeah. Are you?
Is that true?
Well, I guess it's time
for me to tell the truth.
With music.
♪ Shredderman, Shredderman
Shredderman is watching you
♪ Shredderman
will show the world
All the evil that you can do
♪ He'll show
the world your evil plan
Expose you plain and simple
♪ And if you're
hurting people, man
♪ He'll squeeze
you like a pimple ♪
(ALL LAUGHING)
No, guys, I had nothing to do
with that awesome website.
But you know who
Shredderman is, right?
Well, I think Shredderman
put it best when he
or she said,
"Shredderman is all of us."
You sound like
you're defending the guy.
No.
But I think
that if we all knew
someone was watching us,
we'd be in the habit
of being a little bit
nicer to each other.
(BELL RINGING)
Kindness is cool, people.
Remember that.
All right, kindness is cool.
Kindness is cool.
Hey, Nole.
Yeah, Mr. Green?
You do know
that all the teachers
were asked to turn in names
of students who missed
the lunch period
the other day.
Uh...
You're being pretty cool
about this, Shredderman.
Relax. I didn't
turn your name in.
(EXHALES)
Mr. Green,
I'm not Shredderman.
Okay. Right.
Well, look at the time,
I better get to lunch.
Don't wanna get a low mark.
See you.
Right. Hey, Nolan.
You know you
have one week left
to turn in your report?
And you still haven't told me
what you're doing it on.
That's because, um,
the entirety of
the metamorphosis
of the overall thinking
of the evolution
of the hypothesis...
NOLAN: I've got no cover.
... it brought me back to...
On me? Me, Nolan?
You wanna do
your project on me?
Of course, yes.
Okay, Dad, calm down.
Calm down.
This is great.
This is super great, Nolan.
Okay, which one of my stories
do you wanna start with here?
Well, what's the story
with the pond?
Well, Mr. Bixby is
getting final approval
to renovate the historic
water reclamation plant
at the pond.
There's gonna be a big
groundbreaking ceremony.
The Mayor's going to be there.
It's gonna be quite a hoo-ha.
Hoo-ha?
Yeah, you know...
You see, Bixby says
he wants to give something
back to the town
and in exchange
the town will
grant him the deed
to the surrounding parkland,
which he'll beautify
as part of his
new eco-mission.
Bixby made his
money in sewage.
Since when is he into
making plants happy?
Something stinks.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I just burped
my anchovy pizza.
Something stinks
with the pond deal, Dad.
I mean, what if
his supposed reclamation
system hurts the pond?
Well, Nolan, he's got oodles
and oodles of studies here,
saying it's perfectly safe.
It's all right here
in black and white.
Look, Nolan,
I know how much
you love the pond.
And I also know
how much you
dislike the Bixbys.
But believe it or not,
Bob Bixby is doing
this town a favor.
A very expensive favor.
So, Nolan, just remember,
the first rule of journalism
is objectivity.
You see, you have
to maintain a certain...
Nolan?
(SCREAMS)
Why?
Sorry. Sorry.
It's not fair.
I mean,
we've been taking care
of this park for years,
and now Bixby gets it?
Someone like Bixby
shouldn't even be
allowed to walk by it,
much less have
responsibility for it.
I don't trust him.
And the sad part is,
we can yell and
scream all we want.
But the truth is,
Isabel Lopez or Tina Atkins
can't do a thing to stop Bixby
from taking over this place.
Yeah.
(MUMBLING)
Bixby... And the pond...
Sure, Nolan.
It's like what he said.
(SIGHS)
Isabel's right.
Nolan Byrd
can't save the pond
from Bixby's clutches.
But Shredderman can.
"Doesn't Mr. Bixby's
eco-mission stink
of yesterday's sewage?"
I love it.
Finally,
someone who's not afraid
to ask the tough questions.
TINA: No kidding.
Pond is mine! Pond is mine!
He's really got
Bubba's dad's number.
"Bixby smells of deceit,
and he who smelled it
dealt it."
I just hope Shredderman
knows what he's doing,
putting all those accusations
and stuff on the site.
Bixby's dad doesn't
seem all that nice.
I mean, Shredderman could
really be in trouble.
Are you kidding?
Shredderman can stand up
to a hack like Bixby.
Brains will always
conquer brawn.
If anyone thinks
that Shredderman
doesn't have brains,
they're going to get
their butt kicked by  moi.
(LAUGHING)
GIRL: That is so cool.
You guys want to see
something else cool?
(CELL PHONE SMASHING)
Well, as you all know,
tomorrow is our field trip
to the pond.
Yeah!
It's going to be great.
Now, don't forget to pack
your lunches, okay?
And just in case you care,
I love egg salad,
and whole grain is
good for the heart, too.
All right,
with that being said,
Isabel is in
the back of the room
with her pet guinea pig,
Claudette.
She's doing research
on how pets
reduce stress in
stressful situations.
She needs volunteers.
Claudette, say hi to Nolan.
Nolan, Claudette.
I like to have
my fuzzy stomach
rubbed, too.
No, no. My guinea pig, Diego,
he likes to have his
fuzzy stomach rubbed.
Well, then you should both
be nice and relaxed.
Okay, now think of something
that you care about.
Something that
calms you down.
I like the pond.
What?
Okay, now pet Claudette.
She really is
calming you down.
Thank you for volunteering.
Maybe, someday, you know,
if you ever want,
we can have
a guinea-pig play date.
You know, you, me,
the guinea pigs,
doing something?
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
Your eyes dance
when you laugh.
Uh...
Yeah, I was just thinking.
You were saying...
I was saying your eyes dance
when you laugh.
NOLAN: Mr. Bixby?
What's he want?
Mr. Green, I have an issue.
Can I go to the boys' room?
Yes, been there. Run.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
Look, there are
500 students here.
Unmasking the Shredderman
isn't as easy as it sounds.
You know how
important this project
is for me. For us.
Find me the Shredderman,
whatever it takes.
I will.
Show me.
Hello, this is Dr. Voss.
As most of you are aware,
a certain website is making
outlandish accusations
about one of our most
outstanding citizens,
Mr. Bixby.
I have no recourse
but to order
an immediate search
of every student's locker.
Will all students please
report to their lockers
now and wait there
for Mr. Bixby and myself?
Thank you.
What do I have in my locker?
Great grade.
I want hands open
and nothing in
your pockets.
MR. BIXBY: Clear. Clear.
Clear.
Nolan Byrd.
Oh, Nolan Byrd.
Of course.
My son, Bubba,
speaks of you often.
I'm sure.
What's in your locker, Nolan?
Nothing. I mean...
Show me.
I don't think Nolan
is anyone you'd be
interested in.
Oh, really? Really?
Is that because
you have some special
inside information
about this Shredderman
that you wanna
share with us?
Me? No.
I just think...
I want to see him
in your office.
Mr. Green?
Yes.
Unless there's a reason
that you can't help us
solve this problem.
NOLAN: Wait.
Mr. Green didn't do anything.
Nolan.
Nolan, Nolan, Nolan Byrd.
This really isn't
any of your business.
So just stay out of it.
Let's go.
You look so vulnerable.
Need someone to hold you?
(THUDDING)
NOLAN: Ow.
I can't believe they
searched our lockers.
Total invasion of privacy.
It was like the time
I was strip-searched
by airport security.
That must've been
really traumatic.
They'll get over it.
I mean, how would
Voss and Bixby like it
if people snooped
into their stuff?
I feel bad for Mr. Green.
He was humiliated
in front of the whole school.
That was like the time
I was in this dressing
room naked, and...
Okay, that's really enough.
I don't need to know that.
Nolan, what do you
think about all this?
I agree.
I don't wanna hear
about the dressing room.
I was talking
about Mr. Green.
I'm not sure what
I think anymore.
Well, here goes everything.
As we all know,
Mr. Green has been unfairly
removed from our school.
The truth is...
"...Mr. Green is
the most prepared, engaging
"and caring teacher
that we have."
"His methods may be
unconventional to some,
"but his ideas
and adventurous
field trips are
"the things we
will remember most
20 years from now."
"Mr. Green's
support of Shredderman
is proof,
"as opposed to certain
members of the faculty
and administration,
"he really does care
about how his students
are treated,
"and if Voss and Bixby
think invading privacy
and humiliation are okay,
"let them have a taste
of their own medicine"?
Why would you
take on those two?
Oh, no, Shredderman.
Sheila, by spring,
it'll all be over
and we'll be
sun-kissed in Florida.
(LAUGHS)
Oh! I hope you don't mind,
but I packed a little early.
Oh, Sheila.
I love when you pack light.
You are such
a little vixen.
Shredderman.
What?
"In 1997, Bob Bixby lost
his license to do business
in three states..."
"...after his Wonder Vitamins
were proven to be merely gel
caps stuffed with dirt."
There's minerals in dirt.
(EXCLAIMS)
"In 1985,
Sheila Voss was asked to quit
her cheerleading squad
"because her cheers came
from the wrong end."
(FARTS)
(EXCLAIMS)
Isn't that crazy?
(GROWLS)
Shredderman.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Okay, Diego,
no embarrassing me
in front of Isabel.
No gnawing or
licking yourself. Got it?
Here! Here!
Yes.
Hey, Todd.
Why are you playing
football with a boot?
And why are they playing
street hockey with mops?
Voss took away all
the sports equipment.
Punishment for
what Shredderman did.
He went for
the nuclear option
and now we're all
paying for it.
Man, Voss is so burned,
she even turned off
the handicap elevator.
(CLATTERING)
BOY: I'm okay.
Shredderman's
ruining everything.
Diego's really excited
about meeting Claudette.
Oh, too bad.
The field trip is canceled.
What?
Voss canceled it because
it's a Mr. Green activity,
and since he's been put
on administrative leave,
she says it's
not gonna happen.
Huh?
Maybe this
Shredderman should've
weighed the repercussions
before he got Mr. Green
in even more trouble.
I mean, telling everyone
that Green supports him...
It made him look
like he knows something.
What an impulsive goon.
At least now we know
Shredderman's a guy.
I thought Shredderman
was different.
Somebody who gave us hope
that things could change,
but he's just
like the Bixbys.
TODD'S VOICE: ♪ Shredderman's
a deader man ♪
Now, what I'm trying
to say is, he's a loser.
(MAX'S VOICE)
(RANDY'S VOICE)
(MIRIAM VOICE)
Nolan, what are you
doing up there?
Nothing.
Look, when you say
you're doing nothing,
you're...doing nothing.
You all right?
You don't look too good.
Yeah, I think I might
be getting sick.
Headache? Cough? Vomiting?
Yes.
Hmm.
Well, maybe you should
stay home tomorrow.
I'm a little dizzy, too.
That's it then.
No school. Maybe for
the rest of the week.
It's been,
like, two days now,
and nothing from Shredderman.
What do you people expect?
He made one mistake
and you all turned on him.
Like pitchfork
wielding villagers
on Frankenstein.
He has feelings,
too, you know.
How do you know,
Man-Hands?
I've been interfacing
with His Shredderness.
We're like this.
Really?
I just don't understand why
he made such a big deal
about the pond,
and how important it was,
and then just vanished?
Bixby's groundbreaking
is at the end of the week.
Why doesn't he care anymore?
Trust me,
he has his reasons.
I don't mean
anything by this, Miriam,
but it seems weird
that you're the only
person he's talking to.
Jealous, are we?
What do your friends say?
He's gone.
Done. Cooked. Toasted.
Shaked 'n baked.
Hey, what's wrong?
You seem tense.
No touchy.
All right.
This isn't over yet.
Yeah, but Dad,
I just told you
Shredderman's history.
Bubba, what do we
know about history?
That it's really hard.
History always
repeats itself.
So what do we do now?
Now, we're going to
have some real fun
with Shredderman.
(LAUGHING)
Yeah.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Here's what I want
you to do.
Good morning, students.
This is Dr. Voss.
And now for some school news
from Cedar Valley.
Greetings,
worms and wormettes.
What?
This is Shredderman.
Since you've all betrayed me,
I think it's time
I return the favor.
(SHREDDERMAN LAUGHING)
(AIR HISSING)
(SQUEAKING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hi, Mrs. Byrd.
I'm a friend of Nolan's.
Isabel from school.
Mr. Green wanted me
to give him his assignments.
Wow. You're a girl.
(CHUCKLING)
Yep.
And a friend of Nolan's?
Uh-huh.
Can I just leave
this 'cause I...
Oh, no, no, don't be silly.
Come in. Come in.
He's right upstairs.
Hey, would you
like a snack?
I've got waffles.
They're right here
in the freezer.
Just toast 'em up.
It's just...
No. No. No.
You don't have to.
Okay, well,
he's upstairs.
It would really do him
good to see a girl...
Friend.
I mean a girlfriend
who's, you know...
He's bored
to tears up there.
For wrecking my life,
prepare to have your booty
kicked, Bubbabeard.
Why, Gecko?
Why have we been banished
to the Cavern of Isolation
when all we tried
to do is help?
All superheroes are outcasts
at some point, Sticky,
until the ungrateful citizens
realize they need them again
and the superheroes
rise to the task.
Now, eat your cave moss
and get some sleep.
Let me tell him you're here.
Come here.
Nolan. Isabel's here.
Huh? What?
MRS. BYRD: Isabel.
She's here in the kitchen.
Shall I send her up?
How great is that?
No. No. No.
Don't send her up.
I'll come down in a second,
the stairs are dangerous.
Room's a mess.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Hey, Nolan.
Hey.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Cool earring.
Oh.
Yeah, it's my grandma's.
I must've fallen on it
or something.
(CLATTERING)
Mr. Green wanted me
to give you
these assignments.
He's okay?
Yeah. He came back yesterday.
That's good.
I guess you heard
what Shredderman did?
Uh, no.
Haven't you been online?
No, I haven't been on
my computer in days.
He stole my guinea pig,
Claudette.
He couldn't have.
He even left a note saying
he was going to grill her.
He went from pond protector
to guinea-pig thief.
I just don't get it.
I don't really think
the real Shredderman
would do something like that.
I think he's being set up.
Look, I gotta go.
Isabel?
What?
I think the real
Shredderman will return.
Yeah, well,
tell him to make it quick.
I will. I mean...
I mean, I would if I could.
If I knew where he...
Or if he's a she,
or she's a he. Or...
Right.
Smooth.
Four hundred messages?
It's time for some
serious shredding.
See, that's why he's been
so mysterious lately.
He's got a girl.
It explains everything.
Feeling super.
Gonna go to school,
which I love.
What a great day.
Later, Mom. Bye, Dad.
(BELL RINGING)
MR. GREEN: No soap radio.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Hey, look who's back.
Hi, Nolan.
We were just talking
about the negatives and
positives of Shredderman.
Why are we still babbling
on about that cyber-fraud?
Hasn't he caused
enough trouble?
How do you know
Shredderman did
anything wrong, Bubba?
'Cause I know, turd.
Mr. Bixby.
Because he left his mark.
That's not proof.
Well, he doesn't
exactly have proof
that my dad did
anything bad, did he?
But he still babbles on
like he knows what
he's talking about.
Bubba has
a legitimate point there.
First time those two
words have been used
in the same sentence.
Nolan.
Look, why are you
defending Shredderjerk?
He's been dumping
on everybody.
Maybe because
he's Shredderman.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Who, me? Yeah, right.
I wish I was that ingenious.
I just think it's time
that Shreddergoon showed
some evidence.
Well, maybe he will.
NOLAN: Evidence.
Bubba's dad talks
all kinds of trash.
Point is,
I gotta catch him talking it.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Come on. Just give me that.
Give me the bag.
Come on.
Come on. Sharing is caring.
Sharing is caring, my friend.
(GRUNTS)
Sorry, buddy.
Okay, look, I was just...
Hey.
I might just have to take out
a restraining order against
you, Mr. Nolan Byrd.
Well,
I am a big lacrosse fan.
Thought you'd be
helping your girlfriend
find her pet weasel.
It's a guinea pig.
Whatever.
It's just a little
flea-carpet pee puppet.
Pets bite.
Well, you know,
until you have a pet,
you can't really understand
how they bring out
the best in a person.
If a pet will complete me,
then a pet it shall be.
I know it's risky,
but Bubba usually doesn't
open his own backpack.
(FLIES BUZZING)
Except of course to
put things in it. Yuck.
(SIGHS)
Now, I just need to find a way
to get Bixby ticked enough
so he'll say something
he shouldn't,
and I can post
it on the website.
All right? Yeah.
Hey.
Hey, Nolan.
Somehow I took
Bubba's backpack home
by mistake today.
So I'm just gonna go
over there and swap.
Oh, well, I'll give you
a ride over there, bucky.
I want to ask Bob
some questions anyway.
No, thanks, Dad.
I've been sitting in front
of that kooky computer
all afternoon.
I mean,
I could use the exercise.
Getting cottage-cheese butt,
if you know what I mean.
I'm gonna just take
Grandma's bike. Bye.
All right. Bye. See you.
Sorry.
Why me?
(DOORBELL RINGING)
Byrd Turd. You want a raisin?
Oh, come on,
it's nature's candy.
Why are you breathing my air
in front of my house?
I took the wrong backpack
by mistake today. Sorry.
You know,
you should talk to my father.
Why?
'Cause maybe he can pump out
what's ever inside your head.
I mean seriously,
what's your deal, No-lame?
My backpack?
MR. BIXBY:
Bubba, who's at the door?
It's nobody important.
I think it's only
fair I warn you.
Word on some of
the school's blogs say
Shredderman's
going to take down
your dad tomorrow.
He got the evidence.
If I were you,
I'd warn your father.
It's gonna get real ugly.
Look, mark my words,
Byrd Turd,
the Bixbys ain't busted
'cause Shredderman
is flusted.
(STAMMERING)
Or flustered, or whatever.
One last thing.
Spit it out. I got rice
pudding in the kitchen,
it's simmering
and I gotta add my raisins
before it starts to curdle.
Do you know where
Isabel's guinea pig is?
Last I heard,
Shredderman took her.
(BUBBA LAUGHING)
BUBBA: Hey, Dad, there's
some loser at the door...
MR. BIXBY:
What did you say?
I don't get it.
Of course you don't,
because it's just too simple.
The little people
are bringing me down.
Just like the big ape
with the little blonde
in the palm of his hand.
You mean Uncle Louie
at his wedding.
The movie.
Bubba, the movie.
The movie with
the big gorilla
climbing up
the side of the building,
and the stupid,
little people come by
in their stupid,
little-people planes,
(IMITATES MACHINE GUN)
and they shoot at him,
and they get to him.
They get to that big,
mighty ape.
They get under his skin
and those rotten,
little people take him down,
that big, beautiful ape,
with their picking, and their
pecking, and their pestering.
And then...
Bubbles.
(SOFTLY) I'm not gonna let
them make a dead monkey
out of me.
I'm gonna sue them.
I'm gonna sue them for libel.
Because what those
cheese balls are saying
is libel.
That's right. It is libel
because you had all
those studies done.
Bubba?
Yeah.
I'm not a drum.
Sorry.
I had many studies done.
But the studies are fixed.
Once my reclamation
plant is built
that pond is gonna be
a doody dumpster
full of dead animals.
And I have news for you,
we'd better be on our way
to sunny Florida
by the time
the idiot town council
figures it out!
You know who's
to blame for this?
Absolutely. Shredderman.
You. You are to blame for it.
You had one
simple thing to do.
Get rid of him.
And you blew it.
(DIALING PHONE)
WOMAN: Police department.
Hi, Sergeant Klubb...
Would you excuse me
one second?
Bubbles.
Yes, Sergeant Klubb,
Bob Bixby.
Say, I need a little help
from you and the Mayor.
I'm having a little
problem with a website.
Hey, Mrs. Smith.
Nolan, how nice to see you.
Mr. Smith and I
have been wondering
how you've been.
Fine. Just fine.
Is Max around?
Oh, sure. You know him,
doing his homework as usual.
Thanks.
Doing homework, huh?
Huh?
Never could beat me
at that game.
What're you doing here?
Oh, gee, you actually
said something to me.
Where's Isabel's guinea pig?
Dude, look, I don't have...
Don't "dude" me.
Must I remind you,
you proposed to me?
Do you want the whole school
to know about that?
Dude, that never happened.
I have the plastic ring.
We were five.
No one would
ever believe you.
I have it on video.
That is harsh.
Where's Claudette?
Help me. Help Isabel.
(SIGHS)
All right, I'll help.
I just hope
it's not too late.
Bubba brought
her here yesterday.
Hopefully she
hasn't been sold.
I hear that pets bring out
the best in a person.
And there's someone special
I want to be the best for.
You know what,
their spines can break
pretty easily, okay?
I need to go to
the cash machine.
Wrap it up.
Don't hate me.
I want that guinea pig.
Sorry, dude.
I just sold it.
Got a sweet sale
on ferrets.
Claudette didn't
have a black spot
on her head.
Magic Marker.
Bubba's idea.
This guinea pig
isn't yours.
If you sell it,
I'll report you.
Cool, man, no problem.
She's better off
with you anyway.
Take her.
And I'll need
one of those.
They're free today.
Got the money.
Where is it?
Some guys just took her.
It was mine.
I had to.
They said it was
someone else's pet.
I can't get arrested again.
How about something
a little more sturdy,
like a turtle?
Claudette!
(SQUEAKING)
No!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
So we meet again,
Byrd Turd.
My name is Nolan.
I'm sorry,
I didn't mean
to offend you.
I don't care what
anybody calls you.
You almost made me spill
5,000 gallons of raw sewage.
Have you any idea
what kind of mess
that would make?
Kind of like
what you're planning
to do to the pond
with your water
reclamation system.
Careful, Mr. Byrd.
You're in over your head.
And in the sewage business,
that's a bad place to be.
(SIGHS)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
Whoa, man,
that was intense.
You just got
right in Bixby's grill,
stared down that beast
and didn't even blink.
Nah.
No, man, you did.
Really. Seriously.
Thanks. And thanks
for helping get
Claudette back.
Hey, what are...
Uh...
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
No problem.
Hey...
You wanna walk to
school tomorrow?
I'll show you how to beat
Blaster Destroyers.
Wait, dude,
you can't beat me.
Don't know,
but we'll see.
Okay.
Don't even play.
You know I can beat you.
Come on, now.
I taught you.
(SQUEALING)
You guys, too, huh?
I'm starting to get
a bad feeling about this.
Things could get messy.
Real messy.
(SIGHS)
MR. BIXBY:
Get some rest, Byrd Turd.
You look pooped.
(LAUGHING)
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
Bubba, you're tardy.
BUBBA: That's right, Mr. G.
I am the party.
And the party has arrived.
Right, guys?
You know what I'm saying?
Before we get started today,
I just want to thank
whoever it was
for bringing back Claudette.
Mr. Green,
can I go to the bathroom?
You're fine,
but be safe out there.
(BELL RINGING)
MR. BIXBY ON TAPE:
But the studies are fixed.
Once my reclamation
plant is built
that pond is gonna be
a doody dumpster
full of dead animals.
And I have news for you...
Yes. Yes. I did it. I did it.
Still a thrill, huh?
Oh, yeah.
MR. BIXBY:
But the studies are fixed.
Once my reclamation
plant is built
that pond is gonna be
a doody dumpster
full of dead animals.
(BELL RINGING)
I'm really proud of you guys.
Good luck at the protest.
Don't forget your
protest signs, okay?
It's gonna be great.
So is everything cool?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Well, while you were out
trying to save the world,
Isabel and some of
your other classmates
decided to stage
an old-fashioned protest
at Bixby's groundbreaking
ceremony.
What's that going to do?
Well, it seems like
doing any more
at this point
is too much of a risk.
Don't you think?
Look at what they did to me
just for having my name
on that site.
These people are
not playing, Nolan.
Sometimes you
have to risk things
to get things.
Well, can't argue with that.
I know. 'Cause you're
the one who said it.
Mr. Green,
thanks for being
such a cool guy.
You're pretty cool yourself,
Shredderman.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
(GROANS)
Miriam, not now.
We're through.
We?
Uh...
Okay.
I found someone else.
Someone who knows
how to treat a woman.
That's great.
I'm very happy for you.
Don't you want to know who?
Sure.
Who's the lucky guy?
Oh, boy.
Come on, Bubba.
Here you go, man. Psych!
Man, these are fun.
Good times. Good times
with these bad puppies.
Give 'em to me.
Okay, you want 'em?
Yes.
There you go.
BUBBA: Yo, turd.
My dad says thanks.
For what?
For giving him the heads up
on Shredderman.
He got the cops and school
to shut the site down.
Huh?
The website is history.
We just checked it out
two minutes ago.
The Bixbys ain't busted
'cause Shredderman is dusted.
Nolan, are you all right?
Great, just great.
NOLAN: It was true.
Now no one will
hear Bixby's plan.
(DUCKS QUAKING)
Hello? Hello?
Aren't you gonna
stay for the protest?
No.
Don't you believe
what Shredderman is saying?
It doesn't really
matter anymore.
You know what?
I don't know if
it does either.
All I know is,
whoever Shredderman is,
he speaks with more passion
and intelligence
and love for this pond
than anyone else.
And that's who I'm with.
Besides, I know he was the one
who saved Claudette.
And I'll always
be thankful for that.
I just wish I
could thank him,
or help him in some way.
ANNOUNCER: Introducing
Shredderman and Shreddergirl.
Whoo!
Yeah.
It should be interesting
to hear what Bixby has
in mind for this place.
Who knows what'll
come out of his mouth?
What did you say?
I can't believe you.
Why are you always
so out of it?
It's just...
Never mind. I gotta go.
Nolan Byrd, you are so weird.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Welcome, all.
Well, I guess
it's just appropriate
that we have
such a beautiful day
in which to
celebrate Bob Bixby
and his generous
contribution to our town.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Bob's generosity will ensure
that the tranquility
of this park will endure
for generations to come.
(PROTESTERS BOOING)
BOY: Go away.
STUDENTS: (CHANTING)
Flush the plan.
(STUDENTS CHANTING)
Now, children...
We're not children.
We're citizens.
GIRL: Yeah.
STUDENTS: Yeah.
By legal definition,
if you're not old
enough to vote, zip it.
Actually, what Mr. Bixby meant
when he said, "Zip it,"
was that sometimes
people will confuse
change with something bad.
But I can assure you all
that what we do here today,
we will look back on
and be very, very proud of.
Amen.
We will rock the boat.
This is our pond.
And so,
without further delay,
let's sign this contract.
And...
(TOY PLANES ZOOMING)
Look.
Very funny.
Very funny. Cool toy.
Let's sign this thing.
(WHIRRING)
GIRL: Get away from me.
Good job. Good job, Son.
Everybody, that's Bubba Bixby,
future Sewage King.
I love that kid.
Move. Get out of the way.
How's the weather up there?
Don't worry, Mayor.
I'll get the contract.
Everybody, calm down.
Look at all
the pretty ponies.
We'll see who's laughing
when I sign that contract.
NOLAN: Yes, I got all three.
MR. BIXBY:
The studies are fixed.
Once my reclamation
plant is built
that pond is gonna be
a doody dumpster
full of dead animals.
The studies are fixed.
Once my reclamation
plant is built...
(TOY PLANES WHIRRING)
...a doody dumpster
full of dead animals.
That's Bob Bixby.
Well, that's a little boat,
but it's Bob Bixby's voice.
...studies are fixed.
Once my reclamation
plant is built...
Bubba.
Bubba, get off
your sorry fan-tootie,
and kill that boat. Now.
Coming to help you, Dad.
I'm gonna save the day.
Dude. Bubba's dad
is a total fake.
Totally exposed.
Exposed?
Reminds me of the time
I was at the doctor's
office naked.
I've done nothing wrong.
Nothing wrong.
You people are gonna be sorry.
Sorry.
STUDENTS: Bixby's busted.
Shredderman rules.
Bixby's busted.
ALL: Bixby's busted.
Shredderman rules.
Bixby's busted.
(ALL CHATTERING)
Hello, my meddlesome friend.
You can hide,
but you can't run.
"Support Shredderman's plight.
"Stop Dr. Voss.
"Just use your kite." Huh?
Shredderman?
Oh!
Shredderman,
I don't think so.
Say hello to my
little friend.
Yeah. Good stuff.
You're barking up
the wrong tree, my friend.
(SCREAMS)
Way to go, Isabel.
You can't stop me
with your puny planes.
Come on. Come to Bubba, boat.
(GRUNTING)
Gotcha.
(WHIRRING)
(SCREAMING)
Dad, I got it.
(ALL CLAMORING)
(ALL CHEERING)
Well, obviously, the town
and the council and I
will reconsider its options
regarding our beautiful pond.
(CROWD CHEERING)
This is your captain,
Shredderman, speaking,
champion of the little guy.
Have a nice day.
(ALL CHEERING)
Mr. Mayor.
Mr. Mayor, sir.
Bob Bixby, a man we thought
we could trust,
came this close
to turning one
of our city's
greatest treasures
into a virtual cesspool.
Any comment on what
you believe brought
the big man down?
Isn't it obvious,
Mr. Byrd?
'Twas doody killed the beast.
(SPUTTERS)
(HUMMING)
NOLAN: Nice.
Beautiful, honey.
Just like you.
Oh, you.
Okay.
(CAR HORN HONKS)
Well, that's my taxi.
Don't wanna miss my flight.
Flight?
Yeah, baby.
I'm off to London.
My boss thought
the Bixby article
was so good,
he's sending me to
cover the G8 summit.
No bonding?
What about sharing
our feelings over
my report on you?
Well, thanks, Nole,
I'll read this on
the plane. Thanks.
Well, pip-pip,
cheerio and all that.
Bye, honey.
Bye.
Well, I'll have
to see you later.
I'm gonna go
start my new project.
Which is?
Building a pool.
(SCOFFS)
NOLAN:
It would've been nice to bask
in the glow of hero worship,
but there was no way
I could reveal my
secret identity.
Hey, Nolan, you rule.
Good morning, Nolan.
Community service rocks.
At least, not yet.
BOY: Actually, Nolan,
Shredderman rules.
But you're nice, too.
Oh...
Well, hello, Nolan.
Have a nice semester.
I've been asked to take
an early, unpaid sabbatical.
Lucky me.
NOLAN: Things were even
different for Bubba.
Hey, Miriam,
I love your hair.
Would you like to
go out sometime?
NOLAN: Just kidding.
Hey, Miriam,
I hear guys keep
taking you out.
But you seem to find
your way back home.
(LAUGHS)
That is so funny.
Did you guys hear that?
So good. So good.
NOLAN: Bubba was gonna be
Bubba till the day he died.
But what had changed
was the way we all
dealt with him.
BUBBA: Good times.
And as for me? Well...
Nolan. Nolan. Guess what.
Claudette is pregnant.
Huh?
Claudette is
going to have babies.
Isn't that cool?
I just wish I knew
how that happened.
A miracle, I guess.
I'm so glad
Shredderman
saved the pond.
He showed up just in time,
in true superhero fashion.
Oh, you would
have loved it, Nolan.
You know, he seems
to care about all
the same things you do.
Really?
Funny how you
and Shredderman
are never around
at the same time.
Um...
Scheduling conflicts,
I guess.
Oh.
Well, see you later.
Isabel?
Yes?
(STAMMERING)
I was wondering...
Right...
If...
You...
I...
If you would...
You can do this.
If you'd like to go hang out
at the pond tomorrow?
I did it. I'm the man.
Nolan?
I've waited nine years
for this moment.
I asked Isabel out.
Yo.
I didn't even give
you an answer yet.
Oh, right.
So do you want to?
Yes.
Awesome.
Nolan Byrd,
you are so weird.
(REACH FOR ME PLAYING)
♪ When it felt
too good to be true
♪ 'Cause you've never said
♪ What you mean to say
♪ Anyway you look at it,
I'm confused
♪ If you can't see where
this is gonna lead,
♪ Reach for me
♪ Don't wanna wait
another day without you
♪ Take me to higher ground
♪ We'll be safe and sound
♪ Come on, reach for me
♪ I can't wait another day
without you
♪ Take me to higher ground
♪ We'll be safe and sound
♪ Reach for me
♪ Just reach for me
♪ I've got it all figured out
♪ You decide
what's best for you
♪ 'Cause you will build me up
♪ So don't let me down
♪ I can't make you do
What you don't want to
♪ If you can't see
where this is gonna lead
♪ Reach for me
♪ Don't wanna wait
another day without you
♪ Take me to higher ground
♪ We'll be safe and sound
♪ Come on, reach for me
♪ I can't wait another day
without you
♪ Take me to higher ground
♪ We'll be safe and sound
♪ Reach for me ♪