I love you.
Yeah, same same!
Stop saying that!
Why, it's true.
It doesn't sound real.
It's real.
How do you know for sure?
Because I feel it!
Then say it, say
it to me properly.
Okay, I love you.
Is he ready?
Get down, get down!
Don't move.
Or I'll blow your head off.
Remember.
Remember, remember...
Get him!
Go!
Hey, no ticket!
You give me the money, money!
I don't have any money!
Money, money, money, money!
There, there's your ticket.
Go come on, go!
Go!
Damn it!
Go on, move!
Hey, hey!
Over here.
How are you feeling?
Come and find me.
Find you?
You'll know where to look.
Pharmaceuticals is a
risky market, Michael.
Especially in the current
financial climate.
I beg your pardon?
Alan Williams, United Kingdom
Foreign & Commonwealth
Office.
We'd like to have a chat.
Then call my secretary.
I have a morning
meeting to prepare for.
A meeting?
To discuss your
company's disappointing
last quarter losses?
Who the hell
have you been talking to?
We know about your
research facility in Asia.
What of it, that facility
isn't doing anything illegal.
Clinical opportunities
in emerging markets?
Like it or not, we operate
within all local laws.
Michael, if the public
knew you were using
an offshore lab to
conduct clinical trials
on the poor!
I hardly think the
legal position matters.
Mister, what was it?
Williams.
Don't you guys have terrorists
to catch or wars to start
or something, instead
of harassing taxpayers?
So you want to
shut us down?
Actually, we'd like
to offer you a contract.
But it would be
good for you to know
where we stand.
A contract for what?
There is a product we
would like you to develop
for us.
We'll be in touch.
By the way.
You will need to
improve the security
at that laboratory, good day.
Get down, get down!
Don't move.
Or I'll blow your head off.
Remember.
Remember, remember...
Get him!
Where the hell did he go?
This way!
It should be quiet today.
Yeah.
Drop your weapons
and stand down.
Don't even think about it.
I don't give a damn
what else is going on.
I'm only here for him, get him.
Don't move.
What's that?
Get back.
Yeah.
Hey man, this
is my father's restaurant!
Then
tell him it's closed.
Keep
quiet, he's coming.
Don't
worry, I know kung fu.
He's on the roof!
Hey asshole, watch the ride.
Alex, what are you doing here?
Alex, then you know me?
What, you can't be serious.
You disappear for a month,
and you think you can just
show up outta nowhere?
I'm sorry, but do you know me?
Of course I know you,
what's wrong with you?
I really need your help.
Please.
Come on.
Can you cover for me?
Yeah.
So, where have you been?
I don't know, I just...
People are chasing me.
What people Alex,
what's going on?
Military or something, I
don't remember anything clearly.
Military, what on earth
have you gotten yourself
mixed up with?
I don't know, I don't
know anything, okay?
But they're gonna kill me.
Calm down, it's gonna be okay,
we'll work it all out.
Here, go to my room, 406,
I'll meet you up in a bit.
Yes, Dr. Garideb?
Do you have the file?
Great, yes meet me downstairs.
Okay.
Until what?
Hey.
How are you feeling?
All messed up,
like I'm drowning
in a sea full of oxygen.
Well at least no one's
come looking for you.
I think you're safe here.
We'd like your
help with locating
one of our missing patients.
We know he's in the area, and
is very confused right now.
And why do you
think he'd be here?
We're just taking
precautionary measures.
Letting people know
to look out for him.
Everyone's safety is
our primary concern.
Is he dangerous?
Dangerous, yes.
He's a delusional schizophrenic.
He escaped from
a secure facility
earlier this morning, he
has actually assaulted
several people already.
Well,
I've never even
met the guy before.
Yes, I'm sure.
Nevertheless, if you do see him,
don't approach him.
Or talk to him, because
you might say one thing,
and he might hear something
entirely different.
You don't know what
kinds of crazy things
these people can
get in their heads.
Just call us.
Can I see some ID please?
Yes, of course.
Dr. Garideb?
Garideb yes, and
this is Dr. Parsons.
Prevara, I've
never heard of it.
It's on the outskirts of town.
As you can imagine,
our patients require
a certain amount of isolation.
Well, if I see or hear
anything I'll be sure
to let you know.
You cut yourself.
Yeah, I'm such a klutz,
I was cutting vegetables.
You should really be
more careful next time.
Have a good day.
Who are you?
Jane, your girlfriend.
Well, ex-girlfriend.
Who am I?
What the hell have
they done to you?
Wait, this is yours.
A memberships for
a place called Jaika.
Jane we don't have much time.
You know where he is
Tell me where he is.
Okay...
Wait here.
Can I help you please?
This is a residential area.
Get out!
Where is he?
Hey.
Thanks for that.
It was really, sweet.
What's happening?
I don't know.
But we need answers.
Find them.
Where do I look?
We have a clue.
The doctors?
They're not real doctors.
So that was all a lie?
A part of the truth.
There was
something else.
My arm.
Are you in pain?
Yeah.
Yes, I am.
Check her out.
Hey sexy, where are you going?
My house is that way.
I've got this, I've got...
Save your breath,
you'll need it later
to blow up your doll.
Hey, what's going on?
Are you all right?
What are you doing out
at this time anyway?
Did you go to a nightclub?
No, I waitress
just down the road.
That's good to know.
I didn't think you
had any friends.
Stop it, and
there was I thinking
you were such a nice guy.
I normally get a lift back.
Boyfriend?
Yeah, he's amazing actually.
Tall, strong, handsome.
All right.
Good at ducking.
And sometimes his
boyfriend picks me up.
They're my flatmates.
We should go from this place.
Those guys will be back.
You're probably right.
Let me drop you home.
Get down, get down!
Don't move.
Or I'll blow your head off.
Remember.
Remember, remember...
Get him!
Put it down.
Or you're dead.
Out of the way.
Get him!
Goddammit, he's gone!
He can't escape.
Come on!
Alex, I thought that was you.
What was that chasing about.
Kelly, I'm a
member here right?
Well you work here.
But it's been a month or
so since you went off.
Where do I live?
How the hell should I know?
The computer, what
address do you have for me?
Do you have your card?
Number 47, yeah, I
know where that is.
It's the road that
comes around the back.
With the derelict buildings.
What is wrong with you?
Where's the back exit?
Over there.
Alex, what are you doing here?
I haven't seen you for a month.
Mate, buy me some time.
There are people chasing me.
He's gotta be
somewhere around here.
Excuse
me, can I help you?
There he is.
Hey buddy, I'm gonna
need to see some ID okay?
What the hell?
Pre...
Prevara?
What does it mean?
We're getting closer.
To what?
The answers are at home.
I long, as does
every human being,
to be at home wherever
I find myself.
Shut up.
Three months is a long time.
I'm gonna miss you like crazy.
I told you when
we started dating
that I'd have to go back
at the end of the summer.
My parents haven't
seen me in years.
What's it like out there?
It's smaller, less busy.
A lot hotter.
Why don't you come with me?
I can't just drop
everything and leave.
What about my job?
Working in the
gym is not a job.
There are gyms everywhere.
We can find you one out there.
Well, I'm sure someone
will need protecting.
Defenseless, delicate
girl like yourself.
Really?
Get down, get down!
Don't move.
Or I'll blow your head off.
Remember.
Remember, remember...
Get him!
Come on, get up!
Hello?
Yeah, all right
I'll check it out.
What?
Hey Sam?
Commander, we've seen
something happening,
now, come on!
Sounds like
you're out of luck.
I won't need bullets.
They're
dangerous people, Alex.
Why are they chasing me?
I don't know.
But why would a
team of armed guards
be chasing a lone guy
around a backwater town?
I have something they want.
Or something they want back.
Why don't I remember anything?
Maybe that's a part of it.
Hi, I'm Manny.
You said you had some
news about my sister.
Have a seat.
My name's Brink.
I've been working as a
doctor at the local hospital.
Gathering information about
what's been happening there.
So she was there?
Three people were
brought in from a car crash.
Two guys, and a girl.
That must be her.
She's a taxi driver.
They're all in
pretty bad shape.
Unconscious.
But not life threatening.
They should've made
a full recovery.
I'm really worried.
First they told me that
she'd never been there,
and then that she was dead.
I can't straight get
answers out of anybody.
I don't have all
the answers yet.
But I know where she is,
and who's responsible.
Where,
I need to see her.
Don't worry,
we'll get her back.
We'll get them all back.
It's gonna take some planning,
and some time.
Get down, get down!
Don't move.
Or I'll blow your head off.
Remember.
Remember, remember...
Get him!
Move it!
A disturbance
has been reported
at the train market.
With sounds of possible gunfire.
The suspect has fled the area,
and is believed to
be a Caucasian male,
mid-20s, wearing a gray overall.
Alex, my name is Brink.
And if you're watching this,
then I guess they got to me.
If it's not you, not to worry,
I'm long gone by now.
Now pay attention.
This video will erase
itself after just one play.
Now your memory is
either returning,
or by a chance, you
found your way home.
You and several others
have been held in
a military compound for
the last four weeks.
And this morning, we
managed to get you out.
During your time in
captivity, you've been fed
a drug which is
extremely powerful.
You've been sedated,
and the drug causes
memory loss.
Now you'll be feeling the
withdrawal symptoms of this.
Which are confusion,
headaches and fragmented
memory retrieval.
The effects can last
up to 30 minutes.
We have managed to obtain
a few samples of these,
the pill they have
been giving you.
Analysis has shown it to contain
biochemical agents.
Which we know are
linked to the military.
Thanks.
Jane, you're okay.
Alex, what
are you doing here?
I need to talk
to you, right now.
You can't be serious.
You think you can
just come waltzing in
after disappearing for a month?
How dare you!
Do you know what that did to me?
Two minutes.
Can you cover for me?
Yeah.
Let's hear it.
We need to get out of here
as soon as possible.
What?
I'm in some sort of trouble.
People are after me,
it's not safe here.
What are you talking about?
Where have you been?
I can show you.
Damn it!
It was all on here.
What was?
Okay, this is
gonna sound crazy.
But I think I'm
part of some sort of
military, pharmaceutical
experiment or something.
Are you kidding me?
No.
You think you can just show up
with some bullshit excuse
and I'm just gonna let
you walk back in my life?
It's true.
I don't care if it's
true, you left me!
Jane, they're
going to kill me.
Well why did you come here?
Because I need your help.
And I wanted to see you.
Okay.
Go to my room, 406,
I'll meet you in five minutes.
Yes, put me through
to Dr. Parsons
at once please.
There's been talk of a
disturbance at the lab,
what exactly is going on there?
What?
We have a situation.
We're not sure.
Well we'll probably pick
him up on the street
somewhere, dazed and confused.
Well, that is unless
he's collapsed already.
That is unlikely.
Prevara.
There are some people
that are asking questions
on the street.
Jane, we don't have much time.
Wait here.
Can I help you please?
Where is he?
I love you.
And I remember.
They'll be here any second.
Come on, come on, up,
let's go!
Come on, and you, come on!
Move, go!
This way, go!
And you, move!
Come on, now, go!
Go, move!
Go, go, go!
Go, go, the door's over there!
Come on, just go!
Come on, this way.
Come on!
Here, plan B, put these on.
We need to get out of
here, get lost in the town,
it's our only chance.
Where do I go?
You keep running, in
about another 10 minutes,
your memory's
gonna return, okay?
Then you find your way home.
You take these,
it's the pills, the evidence,
just in case I don't make it.
What do they do?
They affect your perception,
it's some form of
biochemical agent.
It taps into your hyper
conscious awareness.
Is that why I don't
remember anything?
No that's the side effect,
or possibly a safety measure.
It confuses you, it stops
you guys from escaping.
So whatever these
are, they're pretty
damn powerful.
Dangerous in the wrong hands.
We think it's an
experimental weapon,
being developed by
the British military.
Hence all the security measures.
Get out.
Move it!
Out!
Get out!
My orders are to
recover you unharmed.
To continue our work.
Unless you have become aware
of the nature of that work.
In which case, I'm
gonna kill you.
Enough running.
I'm tired of being chased around
like some sick animal in a lab.
So if you want me...
Here I am.
Just remember, sometimes,
a sick animal bites back.
The sick animal always dies.
It's me Brink.
How the hell did you do that?
You knew every move
before he made it.
That pill I took, it's like
I can see the future,
or versions of it.
But that's not possible.
When we were fighting,
all the events played
out in my mind,
like an echo of the future.
It was so real, I could
almost get lost in it.
Almost.
What a weapon.
Now I understand what
the memory blockers do.
If you can't remember
where you are,
then you won't find
a path out of there,
while they're testing you.
There they are!
Come on, they're coming,
let's go, let's go.
Stop!
I'm gonna kill him.
Let's go
Come on Alex, let's go, quick!
My head.
Now come on, try and remember.
Remember?
The pill, the evidence.
Look, here, take my watch.
Try to remember in 30 minutes,
everything will be clearer,
now run straight, I'm gonna
create a diversion, now go!
Back here again.
Everything that's
happened since,
has played out in your mind.
The boats, the buildings,
the gym.
It's all simulation.
The drug, that's how it works.
See you in the real world.
Don't move.
Or I'll blow your head off.
Goodbye my friend.
Remember.
Remember, remember...
Hey, asshole!
I need your help.
-Please.
-What?
Meet me here.
What the hell are you doing?
In 13 minutes.
-Why?
-I'll fix your roof.
Jane, I'm so glad I found you.
Alex, what
are you doing here?
I really
need your help.
Come on.
Can you cover me?
Yeah.
Here.
Go to my room, 406, I'll
meet you up in a bit.
Wait.
There are some people asking
questions in the street.
Tell me where he is!
You know where he is
Jane, we don't have much time.
Wait here.
Can I help you please?
This is a residential area.
There's no one here,
whoever you're looking for,
there's no one here, just...
Get out!
Where is he?
My roof, are you crazy?
Alex, Alex are you okay?
Go, they're going to kill us.
This road looks so familiar.
I feel like I've
been here before.
When?
I don't remember, a
long time ago perhaps.
No!
Someone...
Someone!
Help!
The drug!
That's how it works.
Fragmented.
Simulation.
Memory.
Remember!
Retrieval.
I feel like
I've been here before.
When?
Remember.
I love you.
Yeah, same same.
Stop saying that!
Why, it's true.
It doesn't sound real.
It's real.
How do you know for sure?
Because I feel it.
Then say it, say
it to me properly.
Okay.
I love you.
And I'll always love you.
Until the end of time...