If you're ever tucked
inside Laurel Canyon,
this is the street
my two sisters used to live on.
If you listen carefully,
you can almost always hear
a distant howling.
My name is Emily.
And I was born
without a heartbeat.
I'd have been
the middle sister.
Right between Elle,
the oldest,
and Joy,
the youngest.
The three of us
would have lived on Weepah Way.
This would have been
our neighborhood.
We would have been
three wild animals.
Subrip: Pix
WEEPAH WAY FOR NOW
I'm here to show you
the last week my sisters spent
on Weepah Way.
At the time,
Elle and Joy
were eight months removed
from moving in
to Laurel Canyon,
an historic neighborhood
between sunset and ventura.
Two years removed from moving
out of the family house
and in with our
newly divorced mother.
Three years from discovering
our father was cheating.
Four years removed from starting
anti-anxiety medication.
And eight years
since releasing
their last album
as recording artists.
Shit.
-Okay.
-God.
-Different bowl.
-What the shit?
Shit.
I think it's on fire.
Let me tell you
about them.
Elle liked making budgets,
but never kept them.
She loved knowing
what job paid
for every item
in her life.
Joy would report
Elle's spending to our mother.
The separation
from our parents
didn't trigger any addictions
or odd behavior.
There was
no real acting out.
Although the trauma
might have accentuated
the habits
my sisters already had.
This is my father, John.
This is my mother, Lynn.
On the rare occasions
Elle and Joy saw him,
they invariably went out
sailing on the canals
around his new
bachelor's retreat.
Mom claimed to enjoy
her freedom.
Especially her freedom to stop as
frequently as she wanted on car trips.
Joy, my younger sister,
was the last to let go
of the image of our father
as a great man.
Look at this one.
All of the ties to their
youth were slipping away.
This is Elle
at 24.
This is Joy
at 22.
This is the house
my mom shared with cowboy Lou,
her boyfriend of two weeks
who owned a winery
in Paso Robles.
She moved in with him
only days after discovering
she had two years before
her savings would run out.
Elle and Joy, tucked into the
hillside of Laurel Canyon
believed it would all
come together.
All of it for the good.
Elle, roadie threw up all over
herself on her Gandalf beard.
And it's dripping.
Here, stay in the shower.
Stay there, stay there. Stay!
Welcome to a typical morning
with my sisters.
What the fuck?
Were you just touching that?
You're vile,
why is that out?
-Why are you in here?
-I'm in here because I don't wanna
drain roadie's vomit beard
in my shower.
-That's nice.
-You okay, honey?
I'm sorry you had
to go through that.
You're disgusting, you should
be ashamed of yourself.
Mom warned me about this.
That it would be really hard
living together,
because I do all the work
around here
-while you sit here vibrating.
-She said that? That's interesting.
'Cause she said the
same thing about you.
Are you kidding me?
Why are you here?
I do so much and mom knows
I don't use a vibrator
-to distract me from everyday living.
-Great.
Don't use one
in the bath either,
you'll get electrocuted.
Don't even look at that.
Electrocuted?
It's battery operated.
And by the way,
that was not me.
No, that was some weird noise
in the house. Good night.
I really don't think
we should have the party here.
I think everything we've been doing
right now is destined to fail.
No, no, no. We are having
a party here. Stop.
I don't think
anyone is gonna show.
And last year
for Halloween,
we ordered 15 pumpkins
and carving stations,
and how many people came?
Just tell me.
Remind me, for fun.
Two. Hard to forget,
isn't it?
It doesn't matter, okay?
People are gonna show up.
They have to.
We're leaving the country.
They're gonna be asshole
friends if they don't.
They are asshole friends.
Half of them are musicians or
actors. They're not gonna show up.
By the way,
when does terminix come?
8:00-12:00. Fuckers never
give an exact time,
so the guy's window
is huge.
Who says 8:00-12:00?
That's like me saying "I'll show up
to an audition from 8:00-12:00."
What time are we expecting her?
I don't know, 8:00-12:00.
Could be 9:30...
Could be 10:15...
Could be 11:52...
Could be past 12:00.
Then that's
really fucked.
Yeah, no shit.
You gotta get up at 8:00
in case they come at 8:00.
Then you have to live your life staying
here just to wait for the Rat Man.
Shit.
Well, it's better that
than it comes out
during the party.
It's like...
It still smells like
something died in here.
It on...
Every time I walk in.
My thing
that I'm worried about
is that this house isn't going
to look good for our party.
'Cause when dad shows up
I don't want him doubting us.
I don't want him saying,
"There's Rats..."
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
"When dad comes?"
-I might've invited him.
-You told our father
-to come to our going away party?
-Yeah, 'cause he's our dad.
-That's so nice.
-He's blood, you know?
Thanks...
You fucked up.
Why?
You fucking invited him,
when you shouldn't have.
And I know why you did it.
Because in your little,
weird, strange, obsessive mind,
you're sitting there
in your room
and your mind is racing,
your heart is beating fast.
-You're like...
-You know what? He's blood.
And we need to just fucking
stop pussying out about dad
and getting scared about what
he's gonna do at a party.
Admit that you fucked up.
And I will let it go.
Just say,
"you know what, Elle?
You're right.
I did something wrong.
It's my issue."
Admit it right now,
you fucked up.
Was that just you?
Was that the smell of you?
Your life? Your being?
-Yes.
-It smells like an aquarium.
-Yeah, it smells nice...
-It smells like a fucking fish tank.
That is rude. And by the way,
who cares about my little...
-you made her pant harder.
-Who cares if I'm a little stinky.
That's disgusting.
You think my problems
of o. C.D. Are a problem.
You need
to fucking bathe.
I'm sorry, I sweat
like a normal human being.
-Do you wash?
-Shut up.
-Yes I do.
-Do you clean?
Really?
Are you asking that question?
Yeah, I am, because your
sister is very clean.
Clean skin, clean nails.
Clean face.
I... my vagina
is always clean.
-My breath never smells.
-Your vagina never...
how do you know that
your vagina never smells?
I got a physical.
-No, I don't go down and smell.
-Yep, mom!
-Vagina's clean. What?
-My nails are clean and always done.
My skin is clean.
I wash my feet
so they don't smell.
I don't sweat that much
because I have the ac on.
I think about these things.
Okay, let me fucking text
all of your ex-boyfriends
and ask if your vagina never smelled
the entire time you were with them.
Sure, they'll all have
the same answer.
Every once in a while
you'll have a bad day
because you're on your period
and it gets a little stinky.
All right, put the female stuff
aside. Clean, all the time.
Yeah, well, at least
I didn't lose my virginity
to a 33-year-old
fucking creep.
Yeah, that's right.
He was 33.
That's Christ's age. Okay?
That's a powerful age
right there
to lose your virginity.
"Powerful age to lose
your virginity to?"
Are you shitting me
right now?
That's a very important
age in the biblical times.
Is it?
So Christ was just 33 the entire
time he was in the Bible?
-I didn't know he was frozen in time.
-Not saying that.
Most famous age was 33.
Crucifixion.
Okay.
In my mind
I feel like maybe
when he was a baby
that was a pretty big deal.
When he was like, in a manger
in swaddling clothes
and Mary gave birth to him.
I think that was a big deal.
Most famous age
would be crucifixion.
-Anyone would tell you that, 33.
-Really? Is that right? Is that right?
-Is it, is it really that age?
-Yeah, it was 33.
Interesting.
Because I would say
that if the wise men were here,
they would probably agree
with me and say...
Would you talk
to the wise men like that,
with that
"valley girl" accent?
Yo, wise men, what was
the most famous age of Christ?
They would say, 100 percent
that it was when he was a baby.
-No, no, no. Get her.
-No, no, no.
No, no, she's fine.
I don't feel good
about what's been going on.
I'm... I'm fucking upset.
Because we keep getting
bad rejection.
And I feel like how
roadie looks right now.
Really?
What... yeah.
With barf on your face?
-Yes.
-Yeah, that's how I feel too.
I feel like we're just standing
there with barf and shit on our face,
like,
"here's our record."
These small comedies,
they don't work.
Just last week, I saw a few
that my clients were in.
I wanted
to poke my eyes out.
And now you want to make
a small, independent comedy,
heartfelt or not,
nobody's gonna see it.
Hello, down there.
Everyone's so little
from up here, aren't they?
Look at that lady.
She doesn't know
what's going on up here.
She doesn't know what's going on
up here in this office, does she?
It's crazy, right?
We're just up here
doing whatever we're doing,
and she's down there
walking her fucking kid.
What were we
talking about?
I really love
that you guys want to produce.
It's one of the reasons I was
interested in representing you.
This is not the one.
Let's put it on the table.
Let's focus on the things
that are working for you.
Would the indie financing department
be willing to take a look?
That's kinda
why we're here.
Can I ask you one more question
before we change the subject?
Yeah.
Can we talk
about the tour?
-Yeah.
-The tour...
Not a good idea.
Why did you change
your hair color?
How did that happen?
I mean,
this is for a role.
So it's been like this
for like a year.
-Like a role in a movie?
-In a film.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Like a studio pic?
No, no. This really great
little independent I did.
Fuck it.
Fuck that shit.
God damn it,
I need to pee.
I always wondered
if I could jump
from the top of this building
to the top of that building.
I think
I could make it.
I think I could make it.
Do like some parkour shit
down the side of the building
if I miss...
Only if I miss.
In the case
that I did miss,
but I think I could just...
Clear shot right over there.
Anyway, when can you change
your hair back?
Actually, first of all,
we're going to Turkey
is our first leg of the tour...
-We're going to Europe.
-Turkey...
Yeah, and then I also really...
Everybody in Turkey's poor.
There's no money there.
Go to Dubai.
So close. It's just... the
production sounds a little like a...
Dumbed...
Dumbed down.
It was...
It feels dumbed down.
That's hard to say,
"dumbed down."
Try that.
"Dumbed down."
Dumbed down.
Yeah, but see, you're
missing the second "d."
Say, "dumbed down."
-It's weird, it sounds...
-"Dumbed down."
I don't think...
Don't say it.
"Dumbed down. You guys
dumbed her down."
By the way, it's freezing in
here. Please turn the air off.
Look at me,
I'm fucking dripping.
You're gross.
You're like a miniature mom.
-I'm really hot.
-You're menopausing at 22 like her.
It would help you.
You wouldn't wake up
in a bath of aquarium water
if you actually turned on the AC
and helped yourself.
You know what? I'm gonna
have a house when I'm older.
When I'm an adult,
when I'm like a grown human,
I'm gonna have my children, that are
gonna be fucking adorable and hot.
-And guess what?
-Okay. Depends on who you marry.
We're not gonna
have any AC ever.
-Ever?
-No AC. Nope.
-Just fans.
-You live in California.
You can't come over
with mom
and turn the air conditioning
on, 'cause there isn't one.
That's fine.
I don't wanna be invited over.
Good, yeah, well,
guess what...
You're just really
a mean person.
-You don't care about your family.
-Unlike you, unlike you,
I can be by myself and not have a
panic attack in my own bed, like...
Really? We're gonna fucking talk
and joke about my panic attacks?
I'm a creative being.
I suffer with anxiety and OCD.
Just like people
like Beethoven and Mozart.
Those people had
the same fucking issues.
And they ended up
killing themselves because of...
So now you're wishing
that you're dead.
That's first of all,
really dark.
-Bye. Let's go there. I'm dead.
-Really bad. You're dead?
Okay, good night.
Good bye. Bye. I miss you.
Good night. Bye. I just died.
-I'll miss you. I'll think of you.
-Bye. I died of natural causes.
Okay. I don't know why you're still
talking because you're dead, right?
And you're gonna be
a terrible mother, very selfish.
-Go text mom about it.
-Maybe I will. You know what?
Mom, I ate a tuna
fish sandwich today.
Mom, I had steak for dinner.
Mom, I wiped my butt.
-I already left the room.
-Mom, I brushed my teeth.
I already left the room.
Your words can't hurt me.
I... mom,
I changed my underwear.
Should I change
my underwear again,
'cause I think there
was some ovulation in it.
-I'm gonna change it a third time.
-Okay... okay...
Come on. We both
went a little too far.
Look at me.
Look me in the eye.
You were rude and rude.
You were rude.
We need to treat
each other with respect,
we're all we got.
Who is it?
My gyno.
Hello?
Yes.
Don't forget to wash roadie.
I know. Go.
Hey, Claudia.
Yeah.
Okay, but is this actually
a serious thing?
'Cause last time
that I came over,
you guys lost
my pee sample.
Hey, Joy?
When's the last time
I had sex?
My son is my only one.
Claudia had cleaned
our family house
for more than a decade.
We'd been there
for the senseless deaths
of three of her family members.
She couldn't leave the country
for any of their funerals.
She told my sisters
about mom's drinking.
But before anyone intervened,
mom moved in with cowboy Lou and
no one ever brought it up again.
And then he
looking at me like...
Very bad...
Very mad to me.
He say,
"I don't want it, this kid."
I said, "you don't want it,
but I want my son."
You no want to be with us,
the door is open.
-You're out.
-Yeah.
-Lot of women, single mom.
-True.
He don't want my son. He don't
want to give it the last name.
I say, "no problem. My son
is gonna have my last name."
-No problem.
-What's the difference?
You don't wanna give it?
Okay. Keep it.
Anyway, when you die
you're gonna take it.
Who's gonna need it.
Yeah, what do you think?
Well, should we put
one up there?
No, no, no.
Because the bigger the cheese,
the more of an aroma
it sends off
and these rats
come sniffing.
Yeah, I mean we do,
let's kill 'em.
We wanna kill 'em.
You do or you don't.
I mean, I charge 120 to
extract a rat or a opossum...
All right, yeah.
No, we're gonna do it.
-You are?
-Yeah. I think we should, right?
How about you give me
your number and I'll call you
and then I'll
have your number.
It's always worked
in the past.
Don't fix it
if it's not broke.
-Right, okay.
-Right, right.
I don't have to worry
in case one of you are showering
or busy trying stuff on.
-You know what?
-That way we can always...
Let's get
both of yours.
-I'll do it. I'll do it.
-No, no, no.
We're gonna put our mom's cell.
I think... yeah, mom's
cell is the safest.
You'll get a hold
of her easy. It's fine.
She's a robust,
young, 39...4...
What would you say,
early 40s?
-No, she's in her 50s.
-Okay...
Yeah, but she's healthy.
She's doing good.
Yeah, she's great.
-That could work, I could do that.
-She'll be the one...
-Yeah, she'll let you know.
-She'll answer...
Yeah, she'll answer
any questions...
She's not...
Like tight around the waist?
I'm good, I'm good.
That's all I need.
Got a couple visuals.
That was interesting.
There's a date
right there for me.
What's mom doing?
Have you texted her yet?
Pfft, no. I don't know
what she's doing today.
I think she has
ballet class again.
So you haven't
heard from her then?
No.
You did a a tic after that.
Okay, well,
you have your own weird habits.
I know I do, Elle.
I have to do it.
-It makes me feel good.
-No, you don't have to do it.
You can have self control.
Well, we both do it.
It's our OCD.
Can't help it.
Okay, well,
your habits are getting worse.
Just saying.
Yours are.
-You're taking long showers again.
-No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
Because mine are getting cold.
And you're touching windows,
and doorknobs,
and fucking curtains and shit.
I don't do that any more.
So you're telling me
that you don't touch walls
or shampoo or conditioner.
Maybe the shampoo and
conditioner bottles sometimes.
Yeah.
-You just did it again.
-Yeah, well, you made me nervous.
Yeah, well,
that's too bad.
At least I'm not touching
random shit like this.
What, do you watch me
in the shower, you weirdo?
I don't do it
like that either.
I do it like this.
Okay.
That makes sense.
Not that you deserve to know.
What?
Dad texted us.
What did he say?
He wants to bring
Susan on friday.
Well, hell no.
This is exactly why we don't
invite him to things.
-Think about mom.
-When mom meets her, she'll be nice.
She's nice to everyone.
Okay, still,
fuck no.
I agree.
Sorry, okay?
I know, I did it again.
Fuck.
Okay. Yes. I know.
My gosh.
Stop. It's a problem.
Stop. Don't.
Don't. You'll make me
do it the whole ride.
Shit.
What did I start?
We could just have mom do it.
Wait...
Shit, I gotta get...
Really?
Smells like piss.
Didn't get my keys
on purpose.
Joy insisted on taking
all dry cleaning
to the commons
in calabasas.
The man who ran the store
always complimented
their taste in clothing.
Something Joy refused
to let go of.
It can be oddly important,
encouragement.
What's going on here?
With the drinking in the
middle of the day on tuesday?
I mean, I like it,
don't get me wrong.
It's cool.
But it's not like you.
We might as well be honest.
-We are...
-We're depressed.
-incredibly depressed.
-So you are sad.
I didn't know if you were
just like partying
or if you're actually sad.
Partying in calabasas?
Yeah.
No, we're upset.
We're hanging on.
This is Dan.
This is us upset.
Why, why do you feel...
What face are you doing?
He's one of my favorites.
It's like we're not getting support
when it comes to the record coming out,
help with this film
we wanna get made.
They don't want us to tour,
they want us to be here...
They don't want us to tour.
Auditioning for horrible
little slasher films.
Where you die naked
in a really weird scene.
-Like literally, shit like that.
-It's great... yeah...
-It's like...
-Okay, well let me ask you this.
You should've listened
to the audition
that we had to run
the other day
for a movie
called "the divide."
-It was appalling.
And this is like
a movie that literally
they would give their
left arm for us to book.
The den is a dark place.
I never wanna go back.
I can't believe
you really did fall.
What was captivity like?
I don't wanna go into it.
But Jessup,
he lost his arm.
And Jonah,
he has no leg...
Legs.
Those are always
the first to go.
That boy loved to climb.
Let me ask you,
what is your ultimate goal
would you say?
Like what if you had to tell
somebody in five to ten years
this is where I wanna be,
what is that?
I wanna be super legit.
For sure.
But can we like...
Narrow that down
a little bit.
Be more specific.
That's definitely...
Yeah, that's a wide...
I think just respected.
I wanna be the greatest
comedic actress of my time.
Of like, my age.
Well, shit.
I'll cheers to that.
Not something
I've never heard before
-but sure, I liked it.
-But you know what?
That, that's totally possible.
You could do that.
It's just about setting the
intention and moving towards it.
But people also don't really
have trust in women
-being able to make movies either.
-Right.
So that's, I think,
maybe the biggest part.
Honestly, I should've
been born with a dick.
-So we wanna be men.
-We'd be a lot happier.
We wanna be men.
That's what we wanna be.
-We missed you, Dan.
-I missed you guys.
You know what we need, is we
need a Dan, Elle, and Joy hang.
-A little smoky-smoke time.
-For sure.
-In your bed.
-Absolutely.
-With some chips.
-I miss that.
-Chip bed!
Then we'd smoke
and get the munchies
and the little chips
would be everywhere.
And the chips would... you guys
always thought that was weird.
It's strange. It was
abnormally crumb heavy.
It was a lot of crumbs.
Heavy on the crumbs.
It was almost kinda like you just
took the bag and just went...
It was almost... it's nice
to lay on a bed of crumbs.
There's almost
an erotic quality to it.
Does this affect women when you try
to bring them over to your house
-and they notice it too?
-What, all the chips? No.
Do they ever like get
in there and go like,
-"it hurts."
-A little crunchy.
Most girls like it.
It's intriguing.
You know, they don't know
what they're feeling.
It's a little bit of pain.
A little bit of pleasure.
They're like is...
Is that a chip in my ass or...
That's a chip in your ass, baby.
And I'ma get it.
I eat that chip.
No. No.
Is that a
tortilla or is that a...
Is that a...
We'll cross that bridge
when we come to it.
I'm just saying,
I know you got cute girls
that you could
throw my way.
-It won't come to that.
-No, we're not doing that.
Anyway...
I'm gonna hook up
with all your friends.
-You're a jerk.
-Whether you like it or not,
I'm gonna kiss
all your friends.
-You're already bad enough with us.
-How many female friends
-have you made out with?
-Since when?
-Since...
-In my life?
I don't know,
since chip bed.
What?
We kissed that night.
You don't remember?
What are you
talking about?
What are you talking about?
What are you talking about
that I'm talking about?
Have you... did you...
Have you told her that?
Or was that first... no,
it's coming out now I'm sorry.
We maybe...
-Had sex? What the fuck?
-No.
Got fingered with a chip?
I mean, what are you...
My gosh!
What? No.
We... we made out.
We had a little make-out
session on the chip bed.
-When you were asleep.
-Well yeah, I mean, it was years ago.
-It was like for a second...
-how many Dan?
-How many have you kissed?
-Why are you doing this?
-It's getting weird now.
-How many girls?
-It is...
-Just stop. Stop yourself.
You're getting a little weird.
How is your mom?
Mama Lynn.
It's been too long.
-It's good.
-She's good.
She's good. Thanks again.
That was the least
convincing, "she's great."
-She is dating a guy named, cowboy Lou.
-You know what, she's happy.
-And he's not a cowboy.
-Yeah...
He like works
at a winery, I think.
She's dating a cowboy that
works at a... that's cool.
They're living together.
-They're literally living together.
-She's known him for two weeks.
-Two weeks and they're living together?
-Yeah.
Is she happy?
She's really happy.
Well, then that's all
that matters, right?
I don't know.
Now bring it back.
Bring it back.
Yeah.
Can you please not
get on the freeway?
Go up the hill
to our old house.
Why?
'Cause I wanna be there
for memory purposes.
What? You're so weird.
And no.
You have to get past
the gate, dummy.
You think they're
gonna forget us?
Pervert Sam is probably
still working there,
he'll let us in.
-I'm serious.
-I wanna hop the fence and take a swim.
It'll feel adventurous,
and nice.
I wanna do it.
They're not in town right now.
They're in France in June.
You know that.
Yeah, but there's
probably somebody
there that's waiting,
watching the house.
There's no way they have
someone there that's waiting.
No way.
We can easily do this.
We talk about being spontaneous
all the fucking time.
And today
I wanna be spontaneous.
I wanna sit there
and feel like a kid.
Yeah...
I miss being a kid.
'Kay. This roundabout,
turn around.
-Fine.
-I knew that would work.
Do I have to show some
cleavage or something?
Yep.
-That's high-collared.
-Shit.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you're bait.
-Hi, hey.
-Hi, Sam.
-Hey.
-Yeah. It's so good to see you.
-How are you?
-Very nice to see you too. Go on in.
-I think we should do it now.
-Well, if we just... right now?
Yes, today.
We keep fucking putting it off.
My sisters found out our father
was cheating before our mom did.
Waiting for how much longer?
I don't know,
it's already been three weeks.
It was agonizing watching
them decide when to tell her.
It's frustrating.
Well, I'm sorry,
it's not the right time.
-When is the right time?
-In a half hour.
Okay...
I was more upset that they
had to tell her
than that he had done it
in the first place.
You know,
the worst part is that...
My dad can really be
a wonderful person.
Always when you
least expect.
Truly wonderful.
What if she just
finds out on her own?
No.
No, I'm saying, what if she
just fucking figures it out
because he starts to become
more lazy about it.
-Ready?
-Yep.
-Okay, on the count of three.
-Okay.
One... two...
Three!
It's too cold out
when you're holding it under.
The game's not the same.
A lot of people say my sisters
need to let go of the past
but I can see why
they don't want to.
This house is amazing.
-Elle?
-Yeah?
-You okay?
-Yeah, I'm okay. Are you?
-You with me?
-Yeah.
Shit, life was so much easier
when we lived here.
Yeah, no kidding.
You never realize it
in the moment, do you?
Never.
It's like, "mom, can you
make me a sandwich.
Dad, can you
wash my car?"
I just wanna be
a kid again.
No kidding.
It's the best.
It really is.
I want that feeling again,
you know?
It's gone. It's not
coming back anytime soon.
Shit.
When we have kids though,
we'll get it back.
And we'll live vicariously
through them.
Yeah...
I just wanna go back.
And all of a sudden, bam.
Our mom taught my sisters
how to train squirrels
but never had
a well-trained dog.
She arrived for flights
hours in advance.
She never packed sexy panties
on her trips with our dad.
She punished Joy for intentionally
stripping her vocal cords at school.
She encouraged her girls
to bring friends over
but never respected parents
who didn't introduce themselves.
She had my sisters stop eating
fast food at 18 and 16.
She loved to cook, but never
taught my sisters how.
Maybe she wanted
to be needed.
Gardening was a therapy that she
guilted them for not helping with.
She realized
when my sisters moved out
that she had
almost no friends.
-excuse me?
-Hi.
Are you guys supposed
to be here?
Don't you think it's kinda weird
that we go all the way
to calabasas for dry cleaning?
No, I like going
to the commons, it's sweet.
Yeah, we should probably find a
new place that's like closer.
I need to stop.
Hey, if I tell you something,
do you promise not to tell mom?
It kinda depends on what it is.
No, you just have to agree that
you're not going to tell mom.
Because this is
between you and I
and it's something private.
So... just say that.
I don't like that.
No, it's not a big deal,
just promise me
just to stay calm
and not freak out
-and not tell mom.
-No, I won't.
Can we stop up here, please?
Hold on, hold on.
I just gotta
catch my breath.
The fuck?
-You're out of shape.
-Gotta do more cardio.
Yeah, no kidding.
Okay, I need you to come
with me to the gyno tomorrow
because they think
I have cervical cancer.
Cancer?
Elle always ordered
what Joy did at restaurants.
Even though Joy was younger,
she was the first to kiss a boy,
first to have her period,
first to lose her virginity.
My sisters
truly believed
angels watched
over them as children.
I'm not sure
they still do.
That's cute.
-Right? Farewell, ladies.
-Yeah.
Seeing Dan made me think
that I haven't been
on a date in ten months.
-Come here.
-Yeah.
That's him on set.
He booked a fucking movie.
-With her?
-Yeah!
I guarantee
it's a small role.
Has to be.
Not listed in the trades.
No fan sites are
listing about it.
No blogs.
-Okay, you did your research.
-He looks horrible there.
That's bad. Who would part
their hair like that?
I like it,
it's kinda messy.
That's bad,
the teeth are really bad there.
Well, I think he kind of like
got them fixed a little bit.
He got caps.
No, I don't think so.
I think that's him.
They look like dentures.
No, I think he just got
them like shaved a little.
Shaved?
Yeah, you know how
they just even them out.
-They look bigger.
-No, it looks cute.
Just fucking agree with me
like I want you to.
I'm just being real with
you, bro. He looks good.
Fuck. No.
Most of these are bad.
They're probably dating.
They could be.
No, they're definitely dating.
You can tell.
-They have like a thing.
-Shut up.
-Are you a little jealous?
-I know what you're doing.
"They're dating."
-Yeah?
-See? That one's ugly.
He looks awesome.
-Say that one's bad.
-Hot.
Work with me.
Fine. He looks okay
in some of these.
Don't be bitter.
There, there.
No, I'm over it anyway.
That's what we all say.
Over it enough
to look it up.
Do I look good?
-I feel round.
-What do you mean?
My butt. It's full.
It likes to come out.
Dudes like that.
Yeah...
I shouldn't have
canceled Jerry.
I feel like shit.
Cancelling Jerry
for one session
is not gonna change
your entire body.
Hold on, though.
If you're saying that,
that means you kind
of agree.
-So I am. I look bigger.
-No, no, no, no, no.
I'm not.
No, I'm not.
I mean, what,
how much do you weigh?
I'm like five pounds
over what I usually am.
That's bad?
no.
That was a bad reaction.
-Sorry.
-It's muscle.
Please.
I hate when people say that.
I know, I hate it too
but it's kinda true.
That your butt is muscle.
No, that muscle
adds pounds.
So that's
most of it, I guess.
-I think you look great, more or less.
-"More or less?"
Actually we would probably
create the ultimate human being.
The perfect human being!
Yeah.
Visually it would have
our best attributes.
My eye shape
with your lashes,
with my lips,
with my teeth,
with your nose,
with your hair...
-I like that.
-With your butt.
Willow,
what do you think?
I think I know what she's
been thinking about.
She's been thinking about you
telling mom about your tests.
She told me.
"Elle, will you please
tell mommy about your testings."
She needs to know.
She really does.
And I feel like
if she comes
before the party
really gets going...
Joy, we're not telling mom
about my test.
-Really?
-No.
We're not gonna
tell her.
Joy, we're waiting
until she's here at the house
and by the way, she's gonna
be late like she always is.
No, no, no.
Tell her here at the party.
Set aside, go to another
room, and explain it to her.
Yeah, except then
she'll start drinking,
and she'll accidentally say
something to one of our friends
'cause she's like drunk
and having fun.
And she thinks
it's funny to say something.
I'm sorry,
I'm not doing that.
I don't know why you're so weird
about me having to tell her.
I know...
I don't...
Because you keep saying saturday
and that's the day we leave.
I mean, yeah,
I'll text her at the airport.
We can't just send you
on the road if there's an issue.
I don't think
the news is gonna be bad,
I'm just saying we should
be ready to tell mom soon.
Okay, well, I'm not...
I'm not telling mom, period.
You tell her every single
little detail about your life
and I don't have to do
the exact same thing too.
We're two
different people.
So don't say anything
until we know for sure.
Sorry.
She's mad at me.
The only thing Elle
really loved about the house
was the view of the canyon
from her bed.
It was a simple view
that you grew to love.
You can grow
to love almost anything.
It's god's gift.
Are you sad 'cause
your mommies fight?
Are you sad
because your mommies fight?
I'm sorry.
It's sad...
Joy wanted
Elle to demonstrate repeatedly
how much
she needed her.
Elle wanted Joy
not to need her so much.
-Elle, look at this.
-Yeah?
-What?
-It's like a big dick.
-Look it.
I can't find the power...
Shit!
We're good.
Yes! Yes!
Come to mama.
You're gonna fall.
-The gardeners are fired.
-No shit.
-Text them.
-I can't do that. It's rude.
Let's ask mom
what we should do.
Joy, we text mom
about everything
about 500 times a day.
I think we can
handle this on our own.
She's not gonna be
around forever
-for us to ask her questions.
-All right.
I'm sick of you fucking saying
things like that.
-Really?
-Yes, it's rude.
Because if I was her,
I would be super annoyed
with you.
-Really?
-Yeah, I'd fucking hate it.
How's this for annoying?
-Joy. Joy stop.
-Yeah, you like that?
Are you
out of your mind?
-That good?
-Joy, stop!
Good, you feel good?
You feel blown?
Stop.
You are a very disturbed
young woman.
Hey, John!
Did the gardeners
come for you?
Yeah, I think so.
What happened to your pants?
We're good, we're
gonna get rid of them.
You're in your underwear,
you freak.
-He's gay.
-So he's gay?
Okay, so that means it's fine
for you to be in your underwear?
Next time
terminix comes over,
why don't you just greet him
at the door in your underwear.
Ernie's different.
I'm a little
worried sometimes.
About what?
Me? The gyno stuff?
No, no, no, no.
I think you're gonna be fine.
-Thanks.
-I do.
I've been praying
about it.
I worry about mom.
Just her and cowboy Lou.
Like she tends to just
disappear and do her own thing.
-Yeah.
-I don't wanna lose her.
I feel like we've
already lost dad
and it's kinda redundant
and horrible if we lose both.
We're not
gonna lose mom.
We are doing the dance.
This is my cocktail.
My girl drinks heavy.
I... saw you sitting
at the bar.
And wanted you
to dance with me.
Do I know you?
-Gregory.
-Gregory?
-Pleasure. Janet.
-Pleasure.
That was too masculine,
I shouldn't do that move.
Yeah.
Shall we set down
our drinks?
What are you doing later?
-I'm going to Jimmy's bar?
-Jimmy's bar?
Yeah. You never heard of it?
I love that place.
My tits are shaking.
Does that ever
happen to you?
Only on the weekends
when I let 'em loose.
You're the guy,
you can't have boobs.
Yes, guys sometimes
have man titties.
-So Gregory's out of shape?
-Yes.
-All right.
-He's a little thick in the waist.
I know, it's good to know
for our story.
Gregory,
you work out often?
No, I just
drink whiskey.
I feel like you look
a little soft.
Sorry, that's rude,
we just met.
-Hey, Elle?
-Yeah.
You're killing me up here with the
nail Polish fumes and the smoke.
Why are you doing this?
I'm sorry. I'm stressed and I
want my nails to look nice.
We're getting ready for a party
and our mother is here.
Hold on! We're coming down.
-Can you get the gate?
-She always does this. She has a key.
-Please get the gate.
-I don't have a damn key.
-Mom, use your key.
-Mom, we're trying to get ready.
We gave you two keys.
I don't have
a key with me.
There's an extra key
in that pot.
We can't come down
right now.
I want somebody to come down
and let me in.
No, this is really rude.
I just drove all the way...
If you face the gate
to your left, there's a pot.
And in the pot there's a little hose
head that looks like it's fake.
I don't wanna have to dig
through it and look for it.
I just... we're here...
Okay, all right, all
right, all right, all right.
Just let me... Joy,
what is wrong with you?
I'm coming down.
She's been emotional.
Will you shut up, please?
What? You have.
And it was dumb to invite dad.
No, I'm sorry I like sharing
things with my family.
Like cancer tests.
Cancer tests?
Elle had a test this week
for cervical cancer.
They were worried
they found something.
It's nothing.
It's nothing. They just...
They wanna make sure that
it's an abnormal test result.
It was a follow up.
How do you not
tell me this?
Thanks for keeping
a secret, Joy.
I'm sorry, I don't like secrets
when it comes to family.
This is mom, okay?
No. Had to.
Well, she wants
to have her own life.
So I'm letting
her have it.
Well, Elle,
that's different.
-That is completely unfair.
-Yeah.
Well, you were the one that
said we come to you too much.
And you want this new era where
you're living your own life,
so there you go.
It's completely reasonable
that your mom would want
to make her own friends
and go on trips
and take care
of the things in her life.
My mom died when she was ten
years older than I am right now.
Ten years,
I have to live those ten years
as fully as I can.
And if that means,
horses and hiking
and spending time
with my lover,
then that's what
I need to do.
But that doesn't mean I'm not
concerned if you're in a hospital.
Mom, you're not gonna die
in ten years from now.
That's so young. How can you
say something like that?
And I'm not
in a hospital.
And this lover of yours
you've known
for two weeks.
-What did they say?
-That's true.
They don't know.
I'll find out tomorrow.
Don't get
carried away, god.
-Told her, she should tell you.
-Shut up, Joy.
Okay.
My heart did start to beat a little
too fast there for a minute.
Yeah. Mine too.
Now, Elle's right.
We shouldn't get worried.
Until we actually know that there's
something to be worried about.
Joy's worried you're
moving too fast with Lou.
We're getting married.
I know it,
he's the one.
I am totally in love.
-Mom...
-Okay, that's great mom...
But you've known this guy
for two weeks.
-Two weeks.
-Okay. And his name is Lou.
-Say it out loud, "Lou."
-"Lou."
I know, I know.
I get it.
I told him, if I'm gonna take your last
name, you have to change your first.
Okay. Wait. Hold on.
You're talking
about name changes
and marriage already.
What is going on?
If you guys could hear the
messages he leaves for me.
Your father isn't even capable
of kindness like this.
I know. We love
that Lou is sweet to you.
Mom, but we've
also noticed
you're drinking
a lot more with him.
Stop it. I hardly drink
at all with him.
No, no, no, no. No drinking
tonight. It's not happening.
You could say it
a little nicer.
Maybe I'll just bust out
the vaporizer.
Okay, see this is why
you have to be real with her.
-Don't... definitely don't do that.
-Or she doesn't listen.
I'm not drinking tonight.
Okay, just...
Just protect yourself.
That's all I'm saying.
Because who knows if all the
things he's telling you
end up actually
being true, mom.
Yeah, look at Syd. I didn't
know his issues right away.
Still invited
him tonight.
I still have
feelings for him.
-You invited Reed.
-Yeah, has no issues.
He's poor.
That is not why I
broke up with him, Joy.
You both like having
a man around.
That's okay.
It's normal.
Yeah, thank you.
Very normal.
Just don't fall
into bad habits.
Okay. Well let's agree to be cautious
with all men. How about that?
Yeah, but with Lou
I know...
I mean,
it's as clear as...
It's just love.
I know he's younger.
I mean, he is.
But not really.
I met his friends
and I look, you know,
pretty much as young as
they do for the most part.
Take your time, mom.
Just move slow.
'Cause right now, it's like
you're hanging out with him
and we feel like
we're kinda losing you.
And you're on your own.
And you don't call us as much.
Okay, mom.
That's all we're saying.
But this is the kind of love
I've been waiting for.
And he treats me so well.
Okay, well, that's great.
We're really happy for you.
But we're just saying,
that you don't know him
after just two weeks.
No, you don't.
So when you've known him
more, you can say that.
And stop talking about marriage.
It's not allowed. Okay?
I mean, you obviously didn't
know dad well enough.
So I can't trust you.
And that's the point. This is
already completely different.
And while we're there,
he was a great dad
to you guys.
He gave you
a great childhood.
It was good. It was good
when we were little.
Yeah, just that fun thing,
he just lost that.
-Whatever that thing was. Lost that.
-Completely.
Did he ever have it?
Yeah. No. He was
actually kind of adorable.
All I'm saying is, if you're
gonna get married again,
you better do it
the right way.
I knew what I was getting.
But... did you really?
'Cause then you should've
just gotten an annulment.
Yeah, I think I did.
You knew?
I think I did.
Look what
came out of it.
How could I
possibly regret that?
I guess, but you could've still
had really awesome children
with some other dude.
Yeah, but they wouldn't
be you guys.
-True. But you don't know.
-You don't know that.
-You would never know.
-No regrets.
-You would never know...
-no regrets.
-never any regrets.
-Shut up.
-I love you, mama.
No regrets.
I love you, baby.
So what are you guys
wearing tonight?
We are wearing
really cute dresses.
They're vintage.
And mine looks
kinda like a little...
Like a little sailor girl.
It's really cute.
Adorable.
And what about Joy?
Hers is... Like a heart
shaped little dress,
that is gray and has like
a little shift bottom.
Darlings, darling girls.
You requested some tea.
Is it tea time?
Is it about that time?
All right, this is what dad
would always do.
He'd come in
as Rogers, right?
He'd play
this really really
kind of frothy english
character.
And he had a horrible
accent and we were
these two little
girls he worked for.
And he'd come down
and he'd go,
"girls, it's time for tea. Would
you like a little tea before bed?"
And then he'd trip,
of course.
And then
we would be like,
"Rogers, you can't trip
all over our things.
This is
a very upscale bedroom.
You're working
for two princesses.
Don't get our things wet."
And so he'd come on the bed
and he'd go,
"I'm so sorry. Rogers has
just had a horrible day.
Very busy in the kitchen."
And he'd come sit down and he'd show us
his little array of different flavors.
He'd go, "there's one
that's hibiscus, hydrangea.
There's a Berry bliss
and a mandarin orange flavor.
Which one
are you feeling?
And we'd pick a flavor.
And of course we'd have
to fake that flavor and go,
"it's so good.
Rogers.
We love when you make us tea."
And he'd sit there and we'd kind
of talk about our days
just, I don't know,
school or just hanging out.
Or what we were up to.
And then at the end,
he would go,
"all right,
well, Rogers is off the clock.
It's been a very busy day.
My two little princesses
fall asleep now."
And he'd kind of walk
out of the room
and gather up his tea set
and trip on the way out.
And we'd go, "Rogers, you're
getting our things wet."
He'd go, "I'm so sorry,
I'm so sorry.
Rogers is a very clumsy man.
Thank you. Sorry."
And he'd do that thing
where he pulls his head back.
"Sorry.
I'm being pulled.
I'm being summoned
by my housekeeper."
-Man.
-And that's it, that's my story.
I wish Rogers was real.
You do know like
two or three people
are gonna show up
tonight, right?
Yeah... yep.
Foti fotat.
-That was beautiful.
-That's nice, that's nice.
-I love it. Don't stop.
-Nice, nice, nice.
-So cool.
-So pretty, Brian.
Wonderful.
So I was thinking
about, "boy" and
I'm not sure that we should
go with the intro first.
I think we should try
to pick up from the verse.
-Okay.
-Where we just start with the verse.
-Yeah. Instead of just going...
-Right on the vocal.
Yeah, I think it
kind of hits harder.
A little bit
more emotion.
-Okay, cool.
-Now...
So one, two, three, four.
I like that.
Nice.
Right into the chorus.
One more time.
Nice.
We changed that melody
actually going up.
-Which I think is better.
-It's better.
Okay. Okay. Cool.
I don't know why, we just...
it's not on the record.
-But who cares.
-Yeah, whatever.
But that's
the good thing about live,
is that you can do
whatever you want.
-It doesn't have to be like the record.
-Yeah, yeah.
And then not doing the intro
I think helped, as well.
I think so too.
-Yeah, you know what I mean?
-The energy immediately goes up.
And regardless of where
we place it in a set,
that doesn't affect anything
that it just goes right away.
No, you just don't
say anything for it.
Just a count off.
You just go right
in from another song.
Okay, cool, yeah.
-No.
-From the top, one more time.
I mean, even if I'm trying
to think what would be a...
Okay.
You know even ending
on a "hothouse" ending
and then going right into this
would be really pretty.
-Yeah, that would.
-Yeah.
'Cause in rehearsal
it didn't... it felt good
but it felt too relaxed
or something to intro it.
-It was kinda disjointed.
-Like it was, okay good night.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay. Let's start it
from there one more time.
All right here...
Here we go.
One, two, three, four.
Nice.
Nice. Again.
Nice. Now break down,
break down the hook.
Nice.
-And into the bridge, right?
-And into the bridge.
You can tell when somebody
is like vibing on your man.
Like you know what I mean?
-Yeah, that's like...
-Yeah, that's true.
You're kinda like,
"yeah, like you're friends,
but like she
would go for it."
-And that's... and I know.
-Yeah, right. That's weird.
-And mama knows.
-"Mama knows?"
"Mama knows.
Mama knows best."
Mama knows
and mama doesn't like that.
Has that ever happened to you,
like personally?
The guy that I was supposed
to lose my virginity to...
-Supposed to!
-My...
-In my house.
-Like it was very, it was planned...
-i planned it out.
-My room.
-I planned it out.
I kind of did do that
but then...
No, my best friend actually
had sex with him
underneath my nose, twice!
No, sweetheart.
The girls
are here for you
just as much
as for your sister.
-They're your friends, too.
-That's I think what it is.
Sometimes I feel like
we're just like a unit.
Like you get one,
you get the other.
But do you think... some
people don't want the other.
See, I think
it's coming from you.
I think other people perceive
you as a separate thing.
You are not your sister, you're
not an extension of your sister.
You're you. You're this glorious,
talented, beautiful girl.
And I think that's
what people see, honey.
Yeah.
Of course, I'm in here
with mom in the bathroom.
What could be better?
Had sex with her the
night before and was
about to have sex
with her that night.
-No.
-My god.
No, no, nothing with me.
We made out, I was like...
were you
devastated?
But you weren't like
official yet?
No, we were official.
He fully cheated on me.
Were you devastated?
Yeah, but I was so mad at
him because she told me...
Obviously...
-This ended the friendship.
-No. It ended the relationship.
She told me in the car
and she's like...
the way she did it
was so creepy...
and she looked at me
and she's like,
and she was the driver,
I didn't have a license yet,
and she's just like,
"I had sex with Richard."
And she was smiling.
She was like, "perfect.
She played right into it.
And like he was like crying,
it was very sad.
-He cried?
-Yeah, he was very upset.
-Well, why the fuck did he do it?
-Exactly.
Because he's just a stupid man.
Motherfucker.
I mean, he had like
played like this like...
I'm sorry.
Remember, John,
"share, care,
and beware."
You got this.
Thanks, babe.
John brought Susan to the party
against my sister's wishes.
Sometimes "John" feels better
than saying "dad."
Hey, man.
What's up?
Hi, Syd.
-Joy.
-Do you like my coat?
-I love it.
-Thank you.
Come on, take it off.
Why are you doing this?
It's cold.
I brought
a water slide.
-Water slide?
-You brought a water slide?
Yes, I brought a water slide.
Sorry, tight arms. You
got me too small of a size.
-Where are you gonna put a water slide?
-What the hell?
Books are different.
Yeah.
You wanna show me
around?
Yeah.
I'll show you
some other new things.
Here's my room.
It's lovely.
Don't need
to see that.
Come on, you pussies,
do a shot with me.
i haven't
even seen them.
Give them a break.
I was at pumpkin carving thing
a couple years ago.
The pumpkin
carving party.
-Yeah. Dan was there.
-That was so painful.
I wasn't invited
to a pumpkin carving...
That's 'cause only
two of us showed up.
Don't get all butthurt about the
pumpkin carving party, okay?
What... you didn't even know
them until like a year ago.
-A year and a half ago.
-We go back.
-We're the old friends.
-We're old school.
-You're new school.
-Well, you know what?
Who goes back,
me and Lynn.
-Don't get me started on Lynn.
-We go way, way back.
No, you can't
claim this woman
-this woman has known me...
-No, she's mine.
Since I was a toddler
practically.
Nice.
-Those are dudes'.
-Those are lady boxers.
I mean, really...
Yes.
Look,
all you have to do,
is try my slide
and I'll leave you alone.
You actually found
my favorite suit.
Believe it or not.
Turn around.
By the way, I hear you have a
new little man in your life.
Yeah, I do.
You guys would love him.
He's super grounded,
super down to earth.
He he wishes
he could be here.
-Where is he tonight?
-He had to work.
How long
you guys been dating?
It's been
a little while.
-Yeah?
-All right.
-Fun.
-Hey, where are the girls?
-My god.
-What? I've barely seen them.
I think Joy
is in her room.
Well, you know,
I will go and get them out.
But before I do,
does anybody want...
What?
-A smoke?
-Coming in hot.
This is why
I love you, Lynn.
You're the coolest mom
of all time.
I wish my mom was like you.
A little present, a
little present from mommy.
I thought I was the only one who
brought crack to this party.
Apparently not.
I'm in good company.
-No peeking.
-All right.
-Okay. Very good. My... okay.
-Move the long hair, just a little bit.
All right. Okay.
A little precaution.
Put up the shield
of protection.
Shield?
Are you kidding me
with the double doors?
Why am I
turned around then?
Because,
it's important to me.
No, no, no, no, no.
We're making a deal.
Now this is
definitely your bed.
Yes,
do you like the new artwork?
-I do.
-Good.
-It's a nice addition.
-Yeah, I agree.
Is it a little weird
that it's above my bed?
No, no.
It's completely normal.
It's...
Does that say
something bad about me?
My back has been
bothering me lately.
No.
You know what? When you're...
when you're first with somebody
and like, you just wanna be
doing it all the time.
And you wanna try
all these new positions.
And you know...
Like from the back,
and with the shoulders
and the hair...
I don't know,
I tweaked something in my hip
and I got
a little back spasm.
Shit.
I gotta meet this guy.
I'm not gonna stop
doing it.
This place is like camping.
I'm sorry.
You know
what that means.
This place is nothing
like camping, though.
Yes, it is.
Okay, I'm sorry,
I'm a little spoiled.
But I do not like bugs,
and creatures, and flies,
and fucking dead rats
and leaves falling
all over me on the patio.
That's just how I feel.
I don't know about you.
Everyone loves this place.
Yeah, I know they do.
But we didn't know what we were
getting ourselves into, okay?
If it was me, I would
still be living out
in calabasas, right now.
In the life of luxury.
Instead,
I'm in a fucking 1920s cottage
dealing with death
around every corner.
That is my life.
Well, trust me, Joy.
You haven't lost anything.
Really?
Yeah, really.
What makes you
say that?
You might've
even got hotter.
Happens with age.
Look, I'll tell you what.
I'll make a deal.
I won't make a move
on you all night,
just let me watch.
Does it look like that,
-or does it look like that?
-Or like that?
-The latter... no I said...
-So what's the confusion?
Well, no,
I was pretty sure.
I just, you know, I'm always a
little uncertain which is which.
-So...
-You don't know...
Like, is circumcised mean
it's been snipped or not?
Exactly.
But you know
what you are,
-you just don't know what the word is.
-Right.
It's like flammable
and inflammable.
They mean the same thing
actually.
They both mean flammable.
-I mean...
-It's tricky though.
How do you know? You haven't
had to deal with rat death.
Well, no.
But the smell's lingering.
I mean,
it's gotta be something.
-It's gotta be...
-clinging to the clothes?
-No.
-Maybe.
Check the rodarte dress.
Row-dente?
No, rodarte.
-Okay...
-That one.
-What does that mean?
-It's just...
It's a label.
It's a designer person.
Please.
No.
No that one on the right.
On the right.
On the right...
-Yeah.
-Smell that. Sniff it.
Go...
-Does it smell bad?
-I don't think so, actually.
Really? It doesn't?
Sorry.
That's good.
Have a seat.
Okay.
We're gonna make it a show
if that's what you want.
My god.
It's a miracle.
It's perfect.
-Happy?
-Yes.
It's not bad
in here.
It's not like
your calabasas closet.
Yeah, hello. This is what it's
like to be a poor person.
It's not as bad
as your closet, but...
I'm sorry.
-No, I nailed it.
-You did?
-I did.
-How did you do that?
Because I was... and I was
reading with him too.
My... well,
but that's why,
because he's so good
so you're like...
The chemistry was there.
Although like, we were supposed
to be brother and sister.
But that's okay.
There's always
that weird dynamic
-between brother and sisters.
-There's a couple Oscar movies
that have touched
on that issue I think.
-Issue?
-Yeah the... issue.
Incest is best.
Actually, I used to...
They... there's a...
-there's a...
-incest is best.
Put your sibling
to the test.
There, no...
Really.
-Did you ever find them?
-Yeah. They're coming.
Okay, you saw
this coming.
But when John arrived
at the party,
Joy was so surprised
to see Susan standing there
that she fell down.
Hi, dad.
Hey, sweetie...
I don't know about the water
slide out here at night.
It wasn't
our idea, I promise.
-Here you go, I know you like purple.
-Thank you.
-Yeah. Hey, Joy.
-Hi.
-Joy, this is susie, Susan.
-This is... This is Joy.
-Hi.
-Hello.
-I've heard so much about you.
-Thank you. Sorry, I'm kinda wet.
-Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
It's not nice
what happened next.
Let's skip ahead
and just say this.
Susan stayed in the car.
John went inside.
And Joy went upstairs
to change back into her dress.
Can you get the back?
-Is it weird seeing him?
-I mean...
I mean, yeah,
it was like awkward
when I came down
like the steps.
It was weird
because you know when you like
still have that...
That rapport or that...
-Right.
-I don't know, it's like...
It kind of floods back
all of a sudden.
So you kind
of miss him...
-Yeah.
-You have feelings for him still.
-You're like, yes...
-Yeah.
Sometimes you need it
from a man.
You know what I mean?
It's like...
And then he blamed it on,
"well you're just close
to your mom.
You know
what I mean?
That's all you, you guys
are like three musketeers.
And you leave me out."
And it's like,
no, like, I love my dad.
You know, I wanna be
in a relationship with him.
But did you see
her dress?
-It was so ugly.
-I know.
-It looked like...
-That thing was offensive.
Palm Springs meets Vegas.
-Hey, dada.
-Sweetie.
Hey, how are ya.
Look
at you creatures.
Look at you.
What's going on here?
What is that?
I almost let you kiss me.
What? What's wrong?
-It's okay, okay sweetie.
-What happened?
I think she just
threw up in her face.
Dad said it looked like
she was...
Honey.
Yeah, here.
There's some on the floor.
Honey.
That smells
like bleach.
-Really?
-No, this is cum.
What?
That's not...
No, that's not possible.
Where's my shotglass?
Dad brought Susan.
Dad what?
He fucking brought Susan.
I'm gonna lose it.
I'm gonna pass
the fuck out.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Where is she?
Outside. In the car.
Past the gate.
I told him
if he brought her in
that he wasn't
my dad anymore.
-Okay. That's great.
-My god.
-All right...
-I'm so hot.
I'm just...
It's fine, it's no big deal.
Elle, everything okay?
Elle, why the hell
is there cum on the floor?
-My god.
-There's what?
What the fuck?
-My god.
Wait, wait.
-I'm sorry.
-Hold on. Hold the fuckin' phone.
-There's cum on the floor?
-That's not really cum, right?
-It does look like cum.
-It is.
What?
-What?
-That's fucking cum?
-My god.
-What the fuck?
-I don't know. Maybe the dog came.
What the fuck?
You... you two... when the hell
did this fuckin' happen?
Not me.
Elle wasn't wearing panties,
and it leaked out.
Wasn't wearing pant... okay.
Thank you, Reed.
Thank you.
-Thank you for that.
-Shit happens.
We understand
how that happened.
-You weren't wearing a condom?
-Yeah, I mean,
your dad would never
even have sex with me
-if he didn't have a condom.
-Okay, mom, stop.
You get the fuck out
of here.
Okay, I'm gone.
You just go. Get some
panties on, harlot.
-Really, Reed?
-What's with not wearing a condom?
What...
-what is wrong with you?
-That smell...
My god.
You really...
Have to be
more responsible.
I'm sure she's on
the pill, but what?
You wanna get
herpes from her?
-I don't know if she has herpes or not.
-Mom, stop it.
She doesn't have herpes.
You're embarrassing him.
Well, you know, you wear
condoms for a reason.
-Ahem... after you.
-Thanks.
I'm actually just gonna
wait out here for a friend.
It's not 'cause
I have a sword, right?
It's not real.
It's...
It's actually for wine.
-Awesome.
-Dan.
Cool.
John's girlfriend Susan
had told her friends
that she was planning
to spend more time together
with John's family.
They wanted proof before they
would support the relationship.
Selfie.
That was so slutty of you.
I'm embarrassed.
And who changes?
Who changes right here in front of
this open door for everyone to see?
And who designed
this piece of shit?
Who... I mean,
it's literally open windows.
Hi. Hi, I'm naked.
Hello.
-I don't get it.
-Okay, very funny.
What are you...
What are you doing in here?
Are you getting
all freshened up?
Are you about to go round two?
What's going on?
-Yeah, I am,
-I mean, Lacey panties.
What...
What're you doing?
This is the time where you
get comfortable now, right?
You already had sex.
We get it, okay.
You trailed your business
all over the floor.
We understand
what happened.
Right?
No, I did not trail
all over the floor.
-It was in one spot.
-That we know of.
Who knows what dad saw.
Who knows what he heard.
Dad didn't see anything.
He already left.
No, he didn't.
He's still
fucking here?
No...
Unless the man out there
is... is...
Is not my father.
Get the broseph
to fucking leave.
He won't. And she's
still out here, too.
She's on the fucking
street in the car.
-Susan's still down here?
-Yes, she was smoking.
Okay, well,
what just happened, actually,
should have made him leave.
So, there you go.
You got anything left
to trail around?
Actually, yeah, I could
fucking squeeze it out for you.
-My god.
-You weirdo.
Okay, all right, we're done.
We can't...
I can't talk about your
sexual activity anymore.
-Were you safe?
-Wait, wait, wait. Hold on, hold on.
What does he hate?
He hates movies.
-He hates movies...
-He hates movies.
Well, that's a natural thing
to put on at a party.
We're too loud.
We're too fucking loud.
-Animated movies he hates.
-He hates animated movies.
And he hates
subtitled films.
If we put them on,
it'll give him a headache.
-Perfect.
-Will other people leave?
-Shit.
-What if our friends leave?
By the way, a shit ton
of people showed up.
-I know they did.
-You, me, mom, dad.
-Alice, Lauren, Reed...
-You can't count us. We live here.
Fuck, wait, hold on.
Yeah, we can.
You came.
You came twice.
Very funny.
Hold on. Brian...
You have to go pee?
Why are you like that?
A little bit.
You have to pee after sex.
I haven't done it yet.
Hold on.
The landlords.
They count. They're
still in our territory.
-The landlords.
-Yeah, yeah.
-They count.
-Wait. Do we count Susan?
Sure, count Susan.
Yeah, yeah, she's here.
She's on the street, we didn't
even let her in the house.
Susan, the landlords...
You don't fucking count
Susan, you dumbass!
-You're a fucking dumbass.
-Now, hurry up.
Shut up.
No more slutty behavior.
That was disgusting.
You weirdo.
This is open.
Anyone could do that.
-I know it is!
-Potentially, anyone could...
-Shuffle.
-Shuffled. He did it.
So basically there's
townspeople and there's mafia.
There's more
townspeople than mafia.
You have to figure out
who the mafia are.
-Preach it.
-Everyday you wake up
-and then you go back to sleep.
-I don't understand...
I'm not gonna
be able to do this.
The card picks
who's what.
So, so basically the mafia
has to lie to everyone else
and tell them
they're not the mafia.
And then if they get
to the end of the game
and nobody discovers
they are the mafia,
-then they win.
-Also...
So they basically
have to lie and deceive and...
Your dad would probably be
pretty good at this.
-That's probably true.
-That's true. He would.
He lied to us for
fucking, what, 20, 25 years.
If I was in the mafia,
I wouldn't want to be
adopted by your dad,
though, 'cause...
It's
a really good game.
Could you come here?
Dad, wait. Wait.
-Wait.
-Look.
This is all about Susan,
all right?
You shouldn't have
fuckin' brought her.
We told you not to.
Daddy, you've done
this multiple times.
-All the time, uninvited.
-You never let me
introduce this woman
to you. Okay?
-She's the woman in my life.
-She's not invited.
-You need to accept...
-This is the woman you were with
when you were with our mother.
We will not respect her.
I never hurt your mother
on purpose, ever.
Okay? You have no idea
what was happening.
You always make it
like we're the bad guy.
You have no idea
the things that she said.
The things that she would say.
Okay, I never touched her.
I was never physical with her.
Ever! I never hit her.
-That's a given!
-That's not the point.
You're not supposed to be physical
as a husband. You two talk to me
-like I'm a subcontractor!
-So you're still emotionally abusive.
I don't work for you! I don't
work for you! You look at me!
-Elle!
-Elle, help us out.
Was I ever physical?
Who gives a shit if
you would've cussed?
It would have been a lot
better than what you've done.
She would call me
a son of a bitch.
A motherfucker,
every single fucking day.
Okay? Fuck this, fuck that.
-She had a mouth like a sailor.
-Mom?
I wish you would have cussed
her out all the fucking time...
-Okay. Really?
-It would have been way better
than fucking another woman, dad.
I wish you would have fucking
swore at our whole family.
Cause at the end of the day,
that shit doesn't matter.
We're a family we're gonna
fucking do those things,
but you don't fuck
another woman.
That's what you don't do.
This is so fucking
embarrassing, I'm sorry.
If you knew
my younger sister,
you'd know this is something
she wouldn't get over,
honey, it's okay. It's okay.
It's just stressing me out
and I couldn't stay
much longer, anyway.
I know because I have to
get home and let rivers out.
Okay sweetie, I'm fine. I'll...
I'll call Lou on the way home,
-and get it out.
-I...
Okay, honey.
It's okay.
We're sorry we didn't...
I'll see you
in the morning.
-Okay.
-It's okay. I love you.
Okay.
-I love you, baby.
-I love you mom, I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
It's important,
I think, to say that
this is the last time Elle and
Joy saw our mother alive.
When she crashed
into a retaining wall,
at the base of the canyon
while texting Lou.
No one at the party heard the sound
reverberate through the canyon.
At the bottom
of the canyon...
Mom? Mom!
The girls didn't
go running down
to the scene
of the accident.
For a little while,
no one knew but me.
you seem to be pointing
it down, though.
-Don't even worry about that.
-The patio got real small...
-Well, I'm scared.
-Just right through it.
This cuts through
something you shouldn't...
Just go through it.
Just stroke through it.
It's like a weird scene
in "the notebook."
It's like a scene
that got cut...
Shit.
That was good.
My god, you took
half the bottle out.
That was amazing.
There's no point
in showing you the grief
Elle and Joy experienced
when they heard the news.
There's no point in showing
certain things, to anyone.
We can choose to focus on
other things if we want to.
It's god's gift.
Mom was on life support
for several weeks
before they had to decide
to let her go.
I'd like to tell you
there was a reconciliation
between Elle,
Joy, and John.
Sometimes, I imagine how it might
have gone if there had been.
You know, I really should
be going back to London.
Is this...
No!
Shit, it's just
a little too much for me.
Actually was, a,
a real trip.
Not fake
like it used to be,
anyways,
I have some delicious teas
that are herbal
from the deep,
dark, forests of...
Bombay,
you know that place.
And here
is your lovely tea,
just a little bit
of it spilled, my dear.
Let me just get it.
Some Joy always
replaces the hurt.
My sisters went back to praying
together like they had in calabasas.
This especially
pleased my mom.
She hoped they wouldn't
get married young,
or stop singing if
they couldn't sell records
sure, she wasn't on
their patio in the morning,
or, around to take
their phone calls,
she couldn't hold
their hands at appointments
or be there
at their first birth.
But almost
all of their choices
could still be
traced to her.
This image
is of my sisters
a few months after
my mother died.
It's my favorite image
of them because
it's the first time in months
that they smiled.
I'm not sure why
it happened here.
But it just did.
We understand you!
We speak your language!
You there!
Turkey was cancelled,
but their
team managed to set up
a more lucrative one
in Dubai.
So, they'd always have
that you know,
"that time in Dubai."
They said goodbye to the house like
they were leaving it for good.
Are we past it?
We can't keep doing
this every day.
I love my sisters.
I love everything
about them.
This is Elle, at 24.
This is Joy at, 22.