[Music playing]
[MUSIC JACK MARTIN AND THE TYREE
BROTHERS, "HOUND DOG"]
Y'all know why white
women PMS, right?
Because they deserve it, man.
Hell, boy, I don't care.
I pull that string
out with my teeth,
Flop it back and forth to
make me some red wings.
I ain't into that
crime scene sex.
Hell yeah.
Y'all some sick fucks.
I just like the extra lube, man.
Hell, boy, I don't care.
Bloody or not, here I come.
We ain't worried
about the women.
The only two things that
matter in the deer woods
Is cold beer and no
nagging old lades.
And weed.
REDNECK: Hell, yeah.
Careful, it's got a
bit of creep on it.
We're in for some
good hunting, boys.
[Typewriter sound]
[Bell]
[Air raid siren]
Fuck, what was that?
I thought you said
this was creeper.
You already freaking out.
I ain't freaking out.
Shut up.
[Gunshot]
Tower, this Ranger Willis.
I'm hearing some
gunfire out here.
I'm going to check it out.
Oh, shit!
Is he dead?
Y'all with me?
You saw that it was an accident.
What are we going to do?
[Growl]
Dude, man, are you all right?
[Gunshot]
[Music - doa, "already dead"]
Ahh!
What the hell?
[Gunshot]
[MUSIC GEIN AND
THE GRAVEROBBERS,
["CRYPT KEEPER'S HOLIDAY"]
[Music playing]
Good morning.
First of all, I'd like to
remind everybody of the exam, 9
O'clock Monday morning.
It's going to cover
all the material up to
And including what
we talk about today.
So open your text to chapter 13.
We're going to talk a
little bit about cost
Benefit analysis, which we
started discussing last week.
A major consideration
in assessment
Of feasibility of any
project that you undergo
Is the cost benefit analysis.
It would be foolish.
So cost benefit analysis is a
decisive step in the systems.
Roger, Stacy?
So nice of you to join us today.
I hope coming here
didn't (DISTORTED)
Put you out too much?
Sorry, Miss Gerlen.
Yeah, sorry we're late.
We, uh.
["Jeopardy" style music playing]
We had a flat tire.
Well, at least you're
creative with poor excuses.
Do you have your report
finished, you know,
The one on macroeconomic
analysis, the one
That's due this morning?
Uh, my cat ate it?
Class, please pass
up your reports.
[BREAKING NEWS STYLE MUSIC
PLAYING]
Good citizens, we have a
major epidemic on our hands.
Our sources have reported a new
virus has infected our people.
Scientists are baffled
by the recent deaths
Of three rednecks,
two yuppies, four
Trekkies, and some other
people not worth mentioning.
We have no idea how
this virus works.
And we're pretty sure
there is no cure.
So stay inside, people,
and remember stay clean.
(DISTORTED) Don't use drugs.
Avoid unsafe sex.
Stay in school.
And most of all,
don't have any fun.
I'm Elizabeth Quigly
reporting from COTW News.
[BREAKING NEWS STYLE MUSIC
PLAYING]
[Ominous music playing]
Roger?
Roger, wake up.
I don't appreciate you
sleeping in my class so get up.
[Ominous music playing]
[Squishing, spurting sounds]
(DISTORTED) Obey the wacky.
Obey the wacky.
[severely distorted voice]
[Classical music playing]
[CLASSICAL MUSIC, CLATTERING
SOUNDS]
[Classical music playing]
[MUSIC DOTTLES AND SKULLS,
"NIGHTMARE"]
[Severely distorted voice]
[Tinny voices chanting "la la"]
Yeah, do it.
[Ominous music playing]
[STATIC WHINE, BACKGROUND SOUNDS
FROM TV]
Wake and bake
time, motherfucker.
Shit, I'm starving.
Spark that bitch up, all right?
Dude, I hardly
remember last night.
(DISTORTED) Yeah, I know.
All I remember is you sticking
in a mayonnaise jar and going,
Look at me, look at me.
Yeah, then you passed
out like fucking jackass
Before I could even
finish naming the name.
So.
[Snort]
What do you guys of
calling the band Iron Dick?
Nah, no, that, that's,
that's horrible.
What about Cock Smurf.
That sucks.
[Cough]
What the fuck ever
happened to, uh, Weed Whore?
I thought we agreed on that.
We're not a fucking
chick band, dude.
You just, you don't
get it, do you?
[Muffled sound from TV]
I got it.
(DISTORTED) I got it.
[Sparking sound]
The name of the band,
Peda-feel-my-nuts.
Nah, no more weed
for you, dumbass.
Hey.
Hey, check it out.
It's the school we quit.
[BREAKING NEWS STYLE MUSIC
PLAYING]
Tragedy struck this morning,
at Henlaughter High School, when
Two students attacked and
cannibalized teachers,
Students, and school faculty.
We had a chance to speak
with a few of the students
That witnessed today's
tragic events unfold.
Yeah, I knew that Roger guy.
He was a weirdo.
You know always wearing
black and listening
To that devil worship music.
Yeah, but I know
where he is now.
Down there.
Oh, my god, it was so gross.
I tried to run away, but I
slipped on the blood. [Sobbing]
Ahh.
Eww.
Miss Stacy, I knew her.
Actually, now that Roger's
dead, I knew her real well.
I fucked her.
It was all right.
Well, as you can see, the kids
here are taking it pretty hard.
We'll keep you posted.
I'm Elizabeth Quigly
with COTW News.
[BREAKING NEWS STYLE MUSIC
PLAYING]
Oh, man.
Do you believe that?
Yeah, we should have
stayed in school.
No shit.
I totally want to
pork that news lady.
Let's call the band Butt Frog.
STONER: Dude, I'm
not feeling so hot.
Calm down, man.
The pizza will be here soon.
Pizza?
They deliver pizza this early?
Hey, dude, is it me or
does he look a little green?
Yeah, man.
Hey, dude, you
look kind of green.
You OK?
No, dude.
I feel a little weird.
Must be that cheap gin
you drank last night.
Yeah, I'm not feeling
too hot, either.
Going to the bathroom.
[Muffled sounds from TV]
[Ominous music playing]
[Comical music playing]
[Muffled sounds from TV]
[Doorbell]
[Comical music playing]
Whoa.
Pizza man.
Take it in.
It'll be quick a quick thing.
Thank you for choosing
Wedgies Pizza.
Thank you.
That's $16.68 for
the Wedgies Pizza.
I got to find money, man.
I got to find money.
Just come in and wait.
Thank you.
STONER: I'll get the money.
Don't forget to get tip.
This is a Wedgies Pizza.
Put it down here, man.
I got to find money.
I got to find some money.
Don't forget tip.
Tip.
OK.
Eh.
Yep.
Yep, nice magazine.
Hey, don't forget tip.
Better give me a big tip.
Then give me the big tip.
Boy, it, it didn't
like a Troma movie.
[Growls]
What's going on?
[Growl]
Now, I want that tip.
What?
What? [Screams]
[Screams]
[Laughs]
[Laughter]
[Alarm]
What time is it?
12:40.
Oh, shit, I'm late.
Jim, call me a cab.
Yeah, all right.
Hey, Vanessa, you should
try some of this weed
That Tim brought over.
I hadn't tried it
yet, but it's supposed
To be really fucking good.
Just call me the cab.
I'm just saying, if it was me
going to work, I'd toke it up.
Yeah, and if you were working
at all, it would be a miracle.
[Ominous music playing]
[Horn tooting]
Cab's here.
Well, you are
good for something.
Yeah, this is the other thing.
I'm taking this with me.
See you later.
Bye.
What, no blow job?
[MUSIC DUFUS, "OUTERSPACE
ODESSEY"]
[Ominous music playing]
[Rattling engine]
[MUSIC MISS HANA HOKES,
"BACKSIDE OF DALLAS"]
[Police scanner]
[Siren]
DISPATCH (ON RADIO): Any,
in the street unit, 97,
If you could type
your notes to batch
Number for this CHP officer.
Good, good morning,
uh, ossifer 1088.
POLICE OFFICER: Morning.
Um, was I speeding, sir?
No.
I pulled you over because
I don't like your kind.
Hippy shit is what you are.
[Sniff] Do I smell reefer?
HIPPY: No.
Have you been driving
around smoking a doobie?
Do have any drugs
in this vehicle?
Drugs?
No, no, sir.
I don't do drugs, man.
I used to do drugs.
But that whole drug scene, man,
that is like a bad trip man.
Like, you know, like
you go to the store,
Man, because you want
some chicken, right?
And you're looking
for the chicken,
And you see the
sign for chicken.
And so you go there and you
pick up the package, man,
And it says chicken on it.
But there is not like a
chicken in there, man.
There's just like this white
thing with this slime on it,
Man.
So you say, where's
the chicken, man?
And the guy with the
white coat, he says,
Well, that's the chicken, man.
And I'm like, why are you
fucking with my head, man?
I just want some
chicken, all right?
And I look around, and
everybody's looking at me, man.
I just wanted some chicken.
Why does this have to turn into
such a big hassle thing, man?
Hey, do you have any chicken?
Get your patchouli smelly
ass out of that car, now!
OK, man, see this, this
is turning into like
A whole authority thing, man.
And that's, that's
not good, man.
My counselor, she says I got
a problem with authority,
So I got to like, I got to stay
away from that sort of thing,
OK, man?
So look, look, let's just,
we got to just sit down,
All right.
All right, so what we got to
do, we just got to sit down.
And we got to talk
this over, OK, man?
Why don't I just take a look?
Look, man, we're just
like two people on the face
Of the planet Earth, OK, man?
And like the Earth,
it's like, it's just,
It's spinning around, man.
And we've just got
to like sit down
And like listen to
mother nature, OK, man?
We got to close our eyes and
just stand out there, man,
And listen to the wind.
Well, well, look
what we got here.
DISPATCH (ON RADIO): Negative,
West End, 605 in the valley.
(DISTORTED) Give me
that weed back, pig.
[MUSIC MUEZU, "PAPAL
DISCREPANCY"]
Hm?
DISPATCH (ON RADIO): Is this
going to be a scoop and run?
DISPATCH (ON RADIO):
Affirmative, they're aware.
(DISTORTED) Obey the wacky.
Obey the wacky.
[Music playing]
In 1988, I had this
tabby cat named Wanda.
Of course, my girlfriend, she
hated the cat at the time.
I loved that cat.
I still have that cat.
I lost the girl.
And in 1990, after
my hernia operation,
I was riding this
pony named Bugs
Right down to a swamp gully.
That's what it was,
a swamp gully, yeah.
And, anyway, that
thing was so fast,
It ran and it ran and it
ran right into the lake.
Drowned himself.
And then I got this other pony.
I, uh, forgot what his name was.
But we had it for my
six-year-old daughter's
Birthday party, because all of
the kids wanted to ride a pony.
So we got the pony,
and then, right
In the middle of that party,
that pony just dropped dead.
I thought that, oh, the kids
are going to be disappointed.
But I wasn't going
to let it happen.
I'm going to let them
kids ride that pony.
I let four of them sit
on that pony, and I drug
It around in a circle.
That's what I did.
That's when I realized
that ponies was stupid.
So I guess better just
stick with tabby cats.
What are you talking about?
That's the thing
about driving a cab.
Some days are good.
Some days are bad.
You got to roll with
the punches, you know,
Keep your head up.
And you can't go
looking for trouble
When trouble is spelled with
two T's and an eight-ball.
And in 1982, I was a clown
traveling with the circus.
Then I met this dude.
He was a lion tamer,
a big son of a bitch.
He was a big son of a bitch.
I'm telling you, he
would six-foot eight.
Yes, he was.
His name was C.J. Lerone.
Old C.J., he don't
take know guff.
He says, I like them lions.
And I liked him.
I liked him a lot.
That's when I got
my first cat, Barry.
He got hit by a train.
Flattened him out
like a pancake.
As you can imagine, I, I was
fairly distraught over it.
Oh, god, I feel like shit.
Oh, and one time,
I accidentally
Lit my cat, Jerry, on fire.
I didn't know what the cat was.
God, I was drunk.
Can I tell you what?
I feel like shit.
[Voice sped up and distorted]
Just let me out here.
Fucking zombies, always
messing up my cab.
Well, at least
she left her weed.
Oh.
[Music damage case, "red alert"]
[MUSIC ELECTRIC FRANKENSTEIN,
"MY WORLD"]
I thought you went away.
I've got some good shit.
From Dave?
Totally.
[Laughs]
Are we still going to the show?
They're already ripping it.
It's OK if you want.
Oh, let's just say here.
[Sexy music]
[MUSIC THE DWARVES, "WE MUST
HAVE BLOOD"]
[Farting sound]
And then I said, who
are you motherfuckers?
Right?
Whoa.
[Music playing]
[Chatter]
Hey, dude.
What's up, guys?
What's up, my man?
[Chatter]
What's up, guys?
Ow!
What's up, man?
What's up, Cool Breeze?
Stoney.
What's up?
Right on.
Man, I'm doing fucking good.
I'm drunk as fuck.
Oh, yeah, man, can
I get one of those?
Oh, shit, man, I'm
pretty tight right now.
I just can't be
giving the shit away.
Whatever, man,
you're already drunk.
Seriously.
No, seriously, man, we
going to get you high.
As shit?
Hell, yeah, man,
we got the killer
Shit, fucking demonic chronic.
Kick ass.
Hell yeah, man.
Cool.
[MUSIC THE DEADITES, "ACTION
HOUSE PARTY"]
Word is, this is the shit, man.
Yeah?
Dude, can I get another?
You said, a beer.
Come on, man, we're
getting you stoned.
Fuck.
All right, one more.
What a fucking bum.
No shit.
[MUSIC THE DEADITES, "ACTION
HOUSE PARTY"]
So, do you want to go get high?
Can my friends all come?
Who?
Sure.
[Ominous music playing]
Hey, dude, Jenny and her
friend wanted to come.
Hey, guys, what's going on?
- Guys.
- What's up?
Hey, nice orange.
[Music - blitz, "final hour"]
So what's been
going on, Preston?
It's Cool Breeze.
What?
Call me Cool Breeze.
But your name's Preston.
But everybody calls
me Cool Breeze.
Like who?
My dad calls me Cool Breeze.
Actually, my dad's the first
one to call me Cool Breeze.
Your dad is fucking gay.
What?
[Comical music playing]
Come on, boy.
It's time for your,
it's time for your bath.
Water, water, remember,
It's time for your bath.
It's not hot.
Not hot at all.
No, he's not.
Dude.
You all right?
Man, I feel like shit.
Dude, do you feel like shit?
I can't open my eyes.
I'm just drunk is all.
Well, I feel like shit.
Man, Stoney just doesn't
get stoned no matter
How much shit he smokes.
STONEY: Hey, you
do look like shit.
I got to get out of here
You guys, (DISTORTED)
Don't fuck with my shit.
[MUSIC THE DEADITES, "ACTION
HOUSE PARTY", PARTY SOUNDS]
Sue.
SUE: Mm hm
I feel like shit.
Yeah, I'm drunk off my ass.
Me, too.
But I feel like shit.
Ohh.
Hey, Brian.
Yeah.
Well, you know we've
friends for a long time.
Yeah.
And, well.
What?
I'm only saying this
because I'm real drunk.
But I like you.
I like you, too.
Oh, Brian.
[Romantic music playing]
[Ominous music playing]
What the fuck?
[Party sounds, music playing]
[Ominous music playing]
[MUSIC DIEMONSTERDIE, "1,000
CORPSES"]
[MUSIC HONKY, "LOVE TO SMOKE TO
SMOKE YOUR WEED"]
[Choking, gagging]
Ah, I drank it.
CREW: [laughter]
Cut, cut.
That's good.
[Laughs]
Oh, shit.
CREW: Go run at them.
Go run at them.
Ahh!
CREW: I'm going to
kill a lot of people.
[Background conversation]
[MUSIC LEFT LEG LIMPIN, "POT
ZOMBIES"]
[Scream]
God, yeah.
God, that's fucking gross.
CREW: You can't scream
when their getting it out.
You're already dead, OK?
OK.
[giggle, scream]
CREW: She's smoking a cigarette.
Quit it.
Oh, god, this sucks.
CREW: Fill her up.
Oh, shit.
[MUSIC LEFT LEG LIMPIN, "POT
ZOMBIES"]
But John looks when
the kid wakes up.
Oh, you can stick as much
gack up your beak as you like,
Brother.
No weed.
What, you got to put it
in the lens, like you're.
[Laughter]
I'm fine.
All right, last one for me.
I got to sing.
DWARF: Marty, seriously.
If you call that singing.
[Laughter]
DWARF: I have to save my chords.