MODERN ASTROLOGY IS BASED
ON THE NATAL CHART,
WHICH IS ESSENTIALLY
A GALACTIC SNAPSHOT
OF THE UNIVERSE AND THE
ALIGNMENT OF THE PLANETS
AND STARS RELATIVE
TO YOUR LOCATION ON EARTH
THE EXACT MOMENT
OF YOUR BIRTH.
(crying)
THE CORE BELIEF
IS THAT THIS INFORMATION
IS THEN INTERPRETED
USING THE 12 ZODIAC SIGNS
AS INDICATORS OF BEHAVIOR
TO PREDICT INDIVIDUAL
PERSONALITY TRAITS.
RIDICULOUS.
(laughs ) I ALMOST BELIEVED.
ALMOST.
ASTROLOGY, A PROPAGANDA
CAMPAIGN OF BULLSHIT.
(dryer buzzes)
YOUR PRESENTATION COUNTS
FOR 40% OF YOUR FINAL GRADE,
SO BE SURE
TO CLEARLY ILLUSTRATE
YOUR TOPIC'S SOCIAL RELEVANCE
WITHIN POP CULTURE.
NICE OF YOU TO JOIN US.
I KNEW YOU
WERE CONCERNED.
- SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF CLASS,
AND PRESENTATIONS
ARE ON MONDAY.
I KNOW, SORRY.
I CAN'T STAY.
NEVER UNDERESTIMATE
THE VITAL IMPORTANCE
OF ETHICS, MR. GIBSON.
EVERY DECISION WE MAKE
HAS SOME ETHICAL
COMPONENT TO IT.
LIKE YOUR DECISION
TO LEAVE CLASS EARLY...
EVEN THOUGH YOU MUST
SUCCESSFULLY PASS IT
IN ORDER TO GRADUATE.
I COMPLETELY AGREE.
.P
OKAY. MOVING ON.
WHEW.
P YOU SAY YOU WILL STAY P
P FORGOT WHAT I CAME HERE FOR P
♪  THERE'S SOME SIGNS
ON THE ROAD ♪
♪  TELLING ME
I'M FAR FROM HOME ♪
P THE TRENCHES OUT HERE P
P MYSELF, I DISAPPEAR P
.P
♪  YOUR FRIENDS,
THEY WERE SO CLOSE ♪
.P
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
AS WE PREPARE FOR TAKE-OFF,
PLEASE MAKE SURE YOUR SEAT
BELTS ARE SECURELY FASTENED
AND TRAY TABLES ARE IN THEIR
UPRIGHT AND LOCKED POSITION.
WE SHOULD BE
TAKING OFF SHORTLY.
P ONE OF THESE DAYS P
ALL RIGHT.
SO, UM, WHERE TO START?
ALL RIGHT, WELL, 75% PERCENT
OF ALL NEWSPAPERS
IN THE UNITED STATES
HAVE A DAILY HOROSCOPE COLUMN.
ACCORDING TO FOX NEWS,
29% PERCENT OF AMERICANS
SAY THAT THEY BELIEVE
IN ASTROLOGY,
EVEN THOUGH
THE SCIENTIFIC COMMUNITY
STILL CLASSIFIES ASTROLOGY
AS SUPERSTITION
AND NOT AN ACTUAL FORM
OF SCIENCE.
YET THE POPULATION
KEEPS BELIEVING.
(alarm clock buzzing )
(groans)
SO, WHY ASTROLOGY?
IT ALL STARTED
ON MY BIRTHDAY.
HAPPY BIRTH DAY, BABY.
MMM, I DON'T WANNA
GO TO WORK.
I WANNA STAY HERE.
(flushing)
P THESE AMERICAN DREAMS P
♪ THESE GIANT TELEVISION
SCREENS ♪
P THESE PLANES
THAT CAN'T BE SEEN P
P FLYING OVER EVERYTHING P
P THIS BROKEN FACTORY
THIS COCA-COLA RECIPE P
P THIS COUNTERFEITING MACHINE
COUNTERFEITING EVERYTHING P
♪  THIS INDUSTRY,
THESE ECONOMICS ♪
P THESE MAGAZINES,
THESE MARVEL COMICS P
♪  THE NEXT TIME HALEY'S COMET
COMES I'LL BE TURNING 93 ♪
♪  NOW, TELESCOPES,
THEY DON'T TELL LIES ♪
♪  AND GALAXIES
DON'T GIVE ADVICE ♪
♪  ENDLESSLY EXPANDING,
GROWING COLDER, GROWING OLDER ♪
P JUST LIKE ME P
MAJOR PLANETS GATHER
AT YOUR MID-HEAVEN TODAY
SPOTLIGHTING YOUR CAREER.
- HOW ARE YA?
- GOOD, GOOD.
YOUR HIGH PROFILE
SHOULD ATTRACT
AN EQUALLY SUCCESSFUL
RELATIONSHIP PATHWAY
- INTO YOUR ORBIT TODAY.
- ( moaning)
IN ADDITION,
YOUR HOME AND PERSONAL LIFE
WILL REVEAL GOALS
WELL WITHIN YOUR GRASP.
TAKE YOUR LIFE
TO NEW HEIGHTS
AS YOU EMBARK
ON A FIVE-STAR DAY.
(ding)
♪  THERE AIN'T NOTHING
YOU CAN DO ♪
- ♪  YOUR FOLKS WERE RIGHT ♪
- GOOD MORNING.
P YOUR FOLKS WERE RIGHT P
AH.
(phone ringing)
HELLO.
HEY, DID YOU
TOUCH MY BOARD?
NO, I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, WHEN EINSTEIN
DEVELOPED HIS FAMOUS THEORY
OF RELATIVITY,
HE WORKED FULL-TIME
AS A CLERK IN A PATENT OFFICE.
DON'T TOUCH MY BOARD.
MM-HMM.
HAPPY BIRTH DAY,
BY THE WAY, OLD MAN.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
OH, HEY, INSTEAD OF GETTING ME
A PRESENT THIS YEAR,
I WOULD REALLY LOVE
A NORMAL ROOMMATE.
YEAH, THAT'LL HAPPEN WHEN YOU STOP
TAKING A LEAK WITH THE SEAT DOWN.
OH, HEY, DON'T FORGET
TO ACT SURPRISED TONIGHT.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
- ( Phone beeps )
- ( button clicks)
YEP.
MR. PETERSON
WANTS TO SEE YOU.
ON MY WAY.
- HEY, JAKE.
- HEY.
COME ON IN, BUDDY.
SHUT THE DOOR
FOR ME, WILL YA?
OH, I HATE CONTROVERSY,
SO I AM GONNA MAKE THIS
REALLY SWEET,
REALLY, REALLY SIMPLE.
UM, I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'RE AWARE OR NOT,
BUT CORPORATE SAYS
THAT WE HAVE TO CUT
14% OUTTA THE BUDGET
THIS QUARTER.
AND UNFORTUNATELY,
YOUR DEPARTMENT
WAS IN THE CROSS HAIRS,
MY FRIEND, WHICH IS GRIM.
OH, WOW, THAT IS
NOT A GOOD SWING.
SO, I HAVE TO LET YOU GO.
BUT, UH, I DO HAVE
A TWO-WEEK SEVERANCE PACKAGE
FOR YA EFFECTIVE
IMMEDIATELY.
AND, UH, ALSO, YOU KNOW,
AFTER THAT TIME JAKE,
IF YOU WANNA FILE FOR
UNEMPLOYMENT, KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
GO AHEAD AND FILE 'CAUSE
YOU'VE EARNED IT, BUDDY.
OH, THAT WAS ACTUALLY
PRETTY GOOD.
I LIKE THAT ONE.
WHAT ABOUT SCHOOL?
I DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT SCHOOL, JAKE.
JUST CALL HR.
THEY'LL LET YOU KNOW.
BUT YOU'RE YOUNG,
YOU'RE BRIGHT, YOU KNOW?
TAKE A TRIP.
GO ON VACATION.
HEY, YOU WANT A SHOT?
HIT A FEW.
JAKE!
WHAT THE HELL?
- JAKE!
- GRRR!
( Panting )
NO, THANKS.
YOU GO AHEAD.
ALL RIGHT.
MAJOR PLANETS GATHER
AT YOUR MID-HEAVEN TODAY,
SPOTLIGHTING YOUR CAREER.
YOUR HIGH PROFILE
SHOULD ATTRACT AN EQUALLY
SUCCESSFUL RELATIONSHIP PATHWAY
INTO YOUR ORBIT TODAY.
(phone ringing)
(line ringing )
( beep)
( knocking )
COME IN.
(ding)
BABE?
P I HEARD YOU RING P
♪  YOU DIDN'T LEAVE
YOUR VOICE ♪
P I GOT THE MESSAGE P
P YOU WANTED ME P
MODERN ASTROLOGY IS BASED
ON THE NATAL CHART.
THE CORE BELIEF IS THAT THIS
INFORMATION IS THEN INTERPRETED
USING THE 12 ZODIAC SIGNS.
ASTROLOGY, A PROPAGANDA
CAMPAIGN OF BULLSHIT.
( Panting )
♪ YOU GOT WHAT
WAS LEFT OF ME ♪
SINCE WHEN
DO YOU SMOKE?
JAKE, IT JUST HAPPENED.
IT NEVER JUST HAPPENS.
YOU STILL HERE?
(door closes )
SURPRISE!
(laughter)
P HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU P
P HAPPY BIRTHDAY, DEAR JAKE P
P HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO... P
( retching )
(flushing)
OH! WHAT THE--?
COME ON, WHAT THE--?
(line ringing )
911 EMERGENCY.
YEAH, HEY, I'M NOT EVEN SURE
IF THIS IS AN EMERGENCY,
BUT MY, UH, WATER PIPE
JUST BROKE IN MY BATHROOM
AND I HAVE, UH, I HAVE
NO IDEA WHAT TO DO.
- WATER'S EVERYWHERE RIGHT NOW.
- OKAY, OKAY. WHOA, WHOA, STOP.
LISTEN, THERE SHOULD BE A MAIN
SHUT-OFF VALVE IN THE BUILDING.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE
THE MAINTENANCE ROOM IS?
OKAY, YEAH, YEAH, WHOA.
JUST BREATHE.
IT'S OKAY.
DON'T PANIC,
DON'T PANIC.
IT SHOULD BE RED
AND HAVE SOME SORT
OF SIGN NEAR IT.
OH, YEAH...
AH, THERE IT IS!
I GOT IT. I GOT IT.
I GOT IT.
MY NAME IS JAKE GIBSON.
I WAS BORN FEBRUARY 6th,
1982, AT 10:32 P.M.
AT ST. JOSEPH'S HOSPITAL,
CHICAGO, ILLINOIS.
THREE OTHER PEOPLE WERE
ALSO BORN ON THE SAME NIGHT,
AT THE SAME HOSPITAL,
WITHIN MINUTES OF 10:32 P.M.
HERE WE GOT SARAH REYNOLDS,
YVETTE MONTGOMERY,
AND WESLEY HENDERSON.
THE INTERNET IS KIND OF
AN AMAZING THING.
SO, BASED ON THE THEORY
OF ASTROLOGY,
ALL FOUR OF US SHARE
THE EXACT SAME HOROSCOPE,
AND THEREFORE WE SHOULD ALL
SHARE THE EXACT SAME FATE.
AND THAT'S BULLSHIT.
FOUR PEOPLE,
ONE HOROSCOPE.
FIRST UP,
SARAH REYNOLDS.
(honking)
(line ringing )
Child: HELLO, LUCY SPEAKING.
HELLO?
YEAH, UH,
IS SARAH THERE?
Woman: WHAT DID I TELL YOU
ABOUT PLAYING WITH THE BUZZER?
Child: BUT, MOMMY...
(dial tone)
(line ringing )
HELLO?
DELIVERY.
COME ON UP.
( Buzzes )
STAND UP, PLEASE.
HOLD ON.
WHO IS IT?
YEAH, I, UH, I'M LOOKING
FOR SARAH REYNOLDS.
STAY THERE.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE HE IS.
IF YOU'RE NOT OUT
OF HERE IN 30 SECONDS,
I'M GONNA CALL
THE COPS. OKAY?
NO, NO, NO, IT'S --
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
(door slams )
I JUST HAVE
Lucy:
YOU'RE CRAZY.
Sarah: IT WAS
THE MAILMAN GONE AWRY!
♪ HEY ♪
( beep)
SARAH REYNOLDS.
CHICAGO.
INITIAL MEETING
DID NOT GO AS PLANNED.
UNDERSTATEMENT.
♪ HEY ♪
SHIT.
P WHAT'S GOING ON P
P IN YOUR EYES P
P I SEE YOU SMILING P
P SUNLIGHT P
P POURING THROUGH THE CLOUDS P
♪  DAYLIGHT ♪
P SHINING ALL AROUND P
LUCE!
♪ I AM ♪
P RUNNING THROUGH THE CROWD P
WHOA! CAREFUL.
♪  TRYING TO ♪
P KEEP UP WITH THE NOW P
♪ HEY ♪
P WHAT'S GOING ON P
YOU OKAY?
LET'S TRY IT.
ALL RIGHT, READY?
SWING TO THE NEXT ONE!
P I HEAR YOU SINGING P
♪  DAYLIGHT ♪
THERE YOU GO.
WANNA DO SOMETHING ELSE?
UM, YEAH,
YOU CAN DO WHATEVER.
GO PLAY,
GET YOUR WILDS OUT.
.P
YEAH.
IT'S GONNA BE
TEN FOR BOTH.
LOOK, YOU DIDN'T EVEN
LET ME EXPLAIN.
WAIT A SECOND.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
ST. JOSEPH'S HOSPITAL, FEBRUARY
6th, 1982, AT 10:30 P.M.
LOOK, BUDDY,
YOU CAN'T BE IN HERE.
JUST GIVE ME
A MINUTE! PLEASE!
I ALREADY TOLD YOU
I DON'T KNOW WHERE HE IS,
AND IF YOU DO NOT TELL
WHOEVER YOU'RE WORKING FOR
TO LEAVE ME ALONE,
I AM GONNA CALL THE COPS.
- WAIT, WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?!
- AARON.
WHO IS AARON?
YOU'RE NOT LOOKING
FOR AARON?
NO.
THEN WHY...
WHY DID YOU COME
TO MY HOUSE?
THAT'S WHAT
I'M TRYING...
WE -- WE WERE BOTH BORN
AT ST. JOSEPH'S HOSPITAL
FEBRUARY 6th, 1982,
WITHIN FIVE MINUTES
OF EACH OTHER.
I'M TRYING TO DISPROVE
THE THEORY OF ASTROLOGY
FOR MY ETHICS CLASS.
I HAVE, UH,
SARAH REYNOLDS,
JAKE GIBSON,
YVETTE MONTGOMERY,
AND, UH,
A WESLEY HENDERSON.
OKAY?
WE WERE ALL BORN AT THE SAME
TIME AND THE SAME PLACE.
AND I'M JAKE,
BY THE WAY.
IT'S OKAY. YEAH,
IT'S FINE WITH ME.
YOU SURE?
YEAH, I CAN HANDLE IT.
THANK YOU.
I'M SORRY ABOUT FREAKING
YOU OUT AND EVERYTHING.
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S BEEN A ROUGH WEEK.
YEAH, TELL ME ABOUT IT.
I'M NOT CRAZY.
I'LL EVEN SHOW YOU MY
RESEARCH PAPERS, IF YOU WANT.
LOOK, I...
I JUST NEED TO ASK YOU
A FEW QUESTIONS,
THAT'S IT.
DOCUMENT WHAT HAPPENED ON YOUR
BIRTHDAY, AND THEN YOU'RE DONE.
MY BIRTHDAY?
YEAH, NOT INTERESTED.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
PLEASE, PLEASE.
LOOK, LOOK.
IN ORDER
TO DISPROVE ASTROLOGY,
I NEED TO COMPARE ALL OF OUR
EXPERIENCES ON THE SAME DAY,
AND A PERSON'S
STRONGEST ZODIAC DAY
OF THE YEAR
IS THEIR BIRTH DATE.
IT'S TOO PERSONAL.
YOU GOTTA GET
OUTTA HERE.
COME ON! FOR ALL I KNOW,
YOU'RE SOME KIND
OF STALKER OR SOMETHING.
.P
- GOOD EVENING, SIR.
- HELLO.
I'VE BEEN BUSTING
MY ASS AT WORK
FOR, WHAT,
SIX YEARS NOW?
AND FOR WHAT, EXACTLY?
TO BE ABLE TO PRACTICE
MY GOLF SWING ON COMPANY TIME?
THE MONEY ONE HAS,
GIVES YOU FREEDOM;
THE MONEY ONE PURSUES,
ENSLAVES YOU.
JEAN JACQUES ROUSSEAU.
HOW'S YOUR HOTEL'?
REALLY NICE, ACTUALLY.
COULD USE
A BETTER MINI BAR.
SO, HOW'S IT GOING?
SHE DOESN'T WANT
TO DO IT.
- WHICH ONE?
- SARAH REYNOLDS.
IN ORDER TO DRAW
CONCISE CONCLUSIONS,
ONE MUST HAVE
ACCURATE DATA.
I MEAN, I...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
GOT ANY IDEAS?
YEAH, IT'S SIMPLE.
YOU GOTTA GO BACK.
YOU HAVE TO TALK TO HER.
YEAH, YEAH, I KNOW,
YOU'RE TOTALLY RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, MAN,
GOOD LUCK.
YEAH, SAME TO YOU.
LATER.
( Beep)
(sighs)
YEAH.
RIGHT, THIS WHOLE
"I'M NOT A STALKER" THING,
IT'S NOT REALLY
WORKING OUT.
YEAH, I KNOW, I KNOW, I'M SORRY.
I COULDN'T SLEEP.
AND I WANTED TO MAKE SURE
YOU GOT HOME SAFE.
IT'S LATE, AND IT'S A
DANGEROUS NEIGHBORHOOD.
YOU COULD
BE DANGEROUS.
TRUE. I COULD.
BUT I'M NOT.
ONE CUP OF COFFEE,
PLEASE?
YOU SHOULDN'T SMOKE.
IT'S BAD FOR YOU.
HMM.
THAT'S WHY I QUIT.
UGH. WHAT TIME IS IT?
WE COULD DO
APPLE PIE, EVEN.
I CAN'T, I JUST --
I GOTTA GO.
COME ON, A CUP OF COFFEE,
THAT'S IT. PLEASE, LISTEN.
I'M DESPERATE HERE, OKAY?
IF I DON'T PASS THIS CLASS,
I DON'T GRADUATE.
JUST A FEW QUESTIONS,
PLEASE.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO ME.
AND WHO KNOWS?
IT MIGHT BE IMPORTANT TO YOU, TOO.
I MUST BE CRAZY.
FOLLOW ME.
.P
HEY, SARAH.
HI, PATTY,
HOW'S IT GOING?
AH, PRETTY GOOD. YOU?
(sighs) IT'S BEEN
A LONG NIGHT.
IT'S GOOD.
MAYBE THIS'LL
WARM YOU UP.
- THERE YA GO.
- THANK YOU.
HE DRIVES
A MERCEDES OR A BMW?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOUR WIFE IS A PROBLEM.
PORSCHE TURBO.
DEFINITELY.
INTERESTING.
YEAH, MAYBE
THAT'S HIS WIFE.
OR HIS DAUGHTER.
OR HIS DAUGHTER, YEAH.
SO, IS THAT GONNA
BE YOU ONE DAY'?
I DO DRIVE A PORSCHE.
IT'S A 1976914 I PAID
LESS THAN THREE GRAND FOR.
OH, WELL, NOT ENTIRELY.
THAT WAS UP UNTIL IT
WAS STOLEN YESTERDAY.
- HEY.
- I GOT IT. LET'S GO!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA. HEY!
GET BACK HERE!
(growls )
SORRY TO HEAR.
MM-HMM, SO I THINK
IT'S SAFE TO SAY,
AS BAD
AS YOUR DAY WAS,
I GOT YOU BEAT.
IT'S KIND OF HARD
TO BELIEVE.
I'LL MAKE YOU
A DEAL.
IF I CAN MAKE
YOU SMILE,
YOU TELL ME
ABOUT YOUR DAY.
IF I SMILE FIRST,
I WILL WALK OUT
THAT DOOR
AND NEVER BOTHER
YOU AGAIN.
LIKE A STARING CONTEST?
YOU KNOW...
- YEAH.
- SO, WHAT ARE THE RULES?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
UM, YOU CAN'T LOOK AWAY,
AND YOU CAN'T SMILE.
YOU FORGET I HAVE
A THREE-YEAR OLD.
OH...
BUT SURE, LET'S PLAY.
EITHER WAY,
I'LL PICK UP THE TAB.
AHEM!
- WE STARTED? THIS IS--?
- YEAH, NOW WE ARE.
WE CAN BLINK, RIGHT?
SORRY FOR THE WAIT.
SHOULD I COME BACK?
NO, ACTUALLY.
MY GIRLFRIEND AND I
WERE JUST WONDERING
IF YOU WOULD
BE INTERESTED
IN HAVING
A THREESOME WITH US,
A MENAGE A TROIS,
IF YOU WILL.
YEAH.
HE'S JOKING. IT'S NOT...
DON'T LISTEN TO HER.
SHE'S SHY ABOUT
THIS KIND OF THING.
ACTUALLY, WE ARE HERE ON
OUR THREE-YEAR ANNIVERSARY,
AND WE FIGURED YOU LOOKED
LIKE THE TYPE OF GIRL
THAT LIKES TO GET DOWN
AND PARTY. HEE HEE HEE!
HE'S JOKING,
IT'S JUST...
MM-HMM.
THAT'S A WINNER
RIGHT THERE.
- WELL, YOU CHEATED.
- NO.
I DIDN'T SAY
WE COULDN'T TALK.
I SAID
I WOULDN'T SMILE.
YES! ALL RIGHT.
I AM JUST
ABOUT... READY.
WELL, MY BIRTHDAY SUCKED.
YOU KNOW, I'VE MADE
A LOT OF MISTAKES IN MY LIFE,
SOME BAD DECISIONS,
YOU KNOW, BAD CHOICES.
BUT LUCY --
THAT'S MY DAUGHTER --
WAS NEVER ONE OF THEM.
THIS BAD CHOICE,
WHO I HADN'T SEEN IN TWO YEARS,
DECIDED TO CRASH
MY BIRTHDAY.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
YOU CANNOT BE HERE
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S NICE
TO SEE YOU, TOO.
NO, MY SOCIAL WORKER'S GONNA
BE HERE ANY MINUTE.
LOOK, I NEED TO BORROW
SOME MONEY.
IT'S NOT FOR DRUGS.
LOOK, I'M SERIOUS.
- YOU CANNOT BE HERE RIGHT NOW.
- I'M SERIOUS, OKAY?
I OWE THIS GUY MONEY YOU
DON'T WANT TO OWE MONEY TO.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
YOU CAN'T KEEP DOING THIS!
LOOK, I'M IN TROUBLE.
( Knocking )
UH!
I'LL -- I'LL BE
RIGHT THERE!
PULL YOURSELF
TOGETHER, OKAY?
AND IF YOU MESS WITH MY SOCIAL
WORKER, I WILL KILL YOU.
LUCY? LUCY, COME HERE.
COME HERE.
YOU OKAY?
( Knocking )
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
- HEY.
- HEY. HI.
- HOW'S IT GOING?
- OKAY.
WELL, COME ON IN.
WE'RE JUST, UH...
WE'RE, UH...
(door slams )
I HAVE A SOCIAL WORKER
TO SORT OF MONITOR...
MY ACTIONS WITH HER
BECAUSE IT HASN'T ALWAYS BEEN
AS REGULAR AND SAFE.
SO...
SHE CHECKS ON WHETHER
I'M BEING RESPONSIBLE
AND IF I AM
AN ADEQUATE MOTHER.
HERE YA GO.
I'M SORRY, SARAH, BUT I HAVE
TO REPORT THAT HE WAS HERE.
- BUT THEY MIGHT...
- I KNOW.
I'M SORRY, BUT IT DIDN'T HELP
THAT HE WAS WASTED.
I DIDN'T EVEN
LET HIM IN.
HE PUSHED HIS WAY IN,
I COULDN'T --
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
WHEN I GOT HERE
HE WAS LESS THAN TEN FEET
FROM LUCY, HIGH AS A KITE.
JUST TELL ME
WHAT I CAN DO.
WELL, YOU'LL PROBABLY HAVE
TO APPEAR BEFORE THE BOARD
AND EXPLAIN WHAT HAPPENED.
COULD THEY TAKE HER?
I DON'T KNOW.
THEY COULD, I GUESS.
I DON'T REALLY DEAL
WITH THE LEGAL DEPARTMENT.
ALL I'M SUPPOSED TO DO
IS OBSERVE AND REPORT.
IT'S LIKE
A WHOLE BATTLE NOW.
JUST MAKES EVERYTHING,
EVERYTHING, LIKE ME
PICKING UP THIS FORK,
IT MAKES EVERYTHING
MORE COMPLICATED.
MM-HMM.
AND THAT'S IT.
THAT'S, YOU KNOW, MY BIRTHDAY.
WOW.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT YOU ACTUALLY TOLD HER
THAT SHE LOOKED LIKE A GIRL
THAT LIKED TO GET DOWN
AND PARTY.
I COME HERE A LOT,
YOU KNOW.
READY THIS TIME?
AND NO OFFENSE, BUT NEITHER
OF YOU ARE MY TYPE.
YOU WANNA HEAR
THE SPECIALS?
YES, PLEASE.
SO, YOU SURE YOU DON'T
WANT ME TO WALK YOU HOME?
COULD BE A LITTLE DANGEROUS.
NO, STALKER...
YOU KNOW.
YEAH, THAT'S
WHAT I THOUGHT.
DAMN IT.
WHO, UH, WHO TAKES CARE OF
LUCY WHILE YOU'RE AT WORK?
MY MOM.
LET ME KNOW IF YOU FIND
THE OTHER TWO PEOPLE.
I'D BE INTERESTED TO SEE,
UM, WHAT THEY SAY, YOU KNOW?
♪  AND YOU FELL
INTO THIS BED HEADFIRST ♪
♪ EYES WIDE
AND DRUNKEN ♪
P YOUR ROCK 'N' ROLL SKIRT P
P LOCKED INTO AN EVENING P
P OF LONGING OR WORSE P
P OH, THIS ROMANTIC CURSE P
♪  THIS FORGOTTEN
LAND MINE ♪
P WE WERE DOING SO WELL
FOR SUCH A LONG TIME P
P YES, WE WERE
DOING SO WELL P
♪  FOR SUCH
A LONG, LONG TIME ♪
TV: RELATIONSHIP
BEDROOM BATTLES --
THE FIGHT OVER WHO
CONTROLS THE COVERS
OR HOW EARLY
THE ALARM IS SET.
...A WHOLE OTHER ASPECT,
AND THAT IS
FALLING ASLEEP TOGETHER...
(clicks off )
( beep)
OKAY, UM, SO...
THIS MORNING
I MET YVETTE MONTGOMERY.
TURNS OUT SHE WORKS
AT A YOUTH
DRUG REHABILITATION CENTER
IN THE SOUTH SIDE OF CHICAGO.
P.A.: DR. BURROWS,
PLEASE CALL...
HI, UM...
IS YVETTE MONTGOMERY
WORKING TODAY?
WHO WANTS TO KNOW?
UM, I DO.
AND YOU ARE?
HER COUSIN.
REALLY.
YEAH.
YEAH?
YVETTE, COME
TO THE FRONT.
YOUR COUSIN'S
HERE TO SEE YOU.
IT'LL JUST BE
A MINUTE.
THANK YOU.
HERE TO TAKE HER OUT
FOR HER BIRTHDAY.
- YEAH?
- SURPRISE.
YVETTE, THIS IS
YOUR COUSIN.
SORRY, I DIDN'T
CATCH YOUR NAME.
- COUSIN, HUH?
- SHIT.
- DO I KNOW YOU?
- NO, YOU DON'T,
UM, AND I'M NOT
YOUR COUSIN, OBVIOUSLY.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT, UM,
BUT I NEED TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING...
- OKAY.
- IT'S VERY IMPORTANT.
WELL, I'M HERE
TO LISTEN.
UM, OKAY.
GOOD. ALL RIGHT.
OR BECAUSE SHE REALLY THOUGHT THAT I WAS.
SIR, CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
ARE YOU ON SOMETHING?
AM I -- ( laughs)
AM I ON SOME SORT OF -- ?
AND LET'S JUST SAY
THAT SHE TAKES
HER JOB VERY SERIOUSLY.
.P
- ( arguing)
- ♪  MESSING AROUND ♪
♪  LOOKING FOR FLOWERS
AND DIAMONDS ♪
CODE RED!
♪  SPILLING OUR ICE CUBES
ON THE LAWN ♪
DO YOU NOT SEE THIS?
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT
SOMETHING, OKAY?
GUYS, BACK OFF,
EVERYBODY.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IN THE END
MY STORY DID CHECK OUT.
NOW I'M NOT SURE
IF IT WAS BECAUSE
SHE FELT BAD FOR ASSUMING
I WAS CRAZY
OR BECAUSE SHE REALLY
THOUGHT THAT I WAS.
LOOK AT THIS STUFF
RIGHT THERE.
BUT AFTER I GOT
TO TELL HER EVERYTHING,
SHE FINALLY AGREED TO LET ME
INTERVIEW HER, SO...
( beep)
OKAY, SO, WHENEVER
YOU ARE READY.
UH, FIRST OFF,
MY CAR'S IN THE SHOP.
I DON'T WANT THIS TO BE
SOME SLANTED DOCUMENTARY
WHERE ALL BLACK PEOPLE
RIDE THE TRAIN.
I PROMISE
IT WILL NOT BE THAT.
I HAVE A CAR.
IT'S JUST...
IT'S BROKEN RIGHT NOW.
LISTEN, YOU KNOW, WE DON'T
HAVE TO USE THE CAMERA.
IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER TO ME.
IT'S, IT'S FINE.
( Beep)
ALL RIGHT, MY NAME
IS YVETTE MONTGOMERY.
I WAS BORN FEBRUARY 6th,
1982, AT 10:34 P.M.
AT ST. JOSEPH'S HOSPITAL,
CHICAGO, ILLINOIS.
SAME PLACE AS YOU.
UM, I'M MARRIED
WITH TWO BEAUTIFUL CHILDREN.
MY SON IS EIGHT
AND MY DAUGHTER IS SIX.
AND I WORK
THE OVERNIGHT SHIFT
AT A RESIDENTIAL YOUTH TREATMENT
CENTER FOR TROUBLED TEENS.
( Beep)
AFTER WORK,
I GET MY KIDS READY FOR SCHOOL
AND PACK THEIR LUNCHES
AND SEND THEM
ON THEIR WAY.
I SLEEP
WHILE THEY'RE AT SCHOOL
AND WAKE UP IN TIME
TO FIX DINNER.
THEN MY HUSBAND
USUALLY COMES HOME
EXHAUSTED
FROM A 10-HOUR SHIFT,
AND AFTER DINNER
I HEAD BACK TO WORK
AND START IT ALL OVER.
OKAY, BUT WHAT HAPPENED
ON YOUR ACTUAL BIRTHDAY?
UM...
(sighs) MY BIRTHDAY.
BABY, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
ISO NEEDED THIS.
GOT A SITTER
AND WENT OUT TO DINNER
WITH MY HUSBAND
BEFORE WORK.
TYRONE MISSED CALL.
I HAD TO GO
IN EARLY, THOUGH,
'CAUSE WE HAD
A KID MISS CURFEW.
I NEED TO GO
CHECK ON HIM, BABE.
I NEED TO MAKE SURE
HE GETS IN.
- IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
- UH, I'LL CALL YOU, OKAY?
THE RESTAURANT WAS RIGHT DOWN
THE STREET FROM WHERE I WORK.
I WASN'T ORIGINALLY
SCHEDULED TO GO IN TILL 10:00.
OH, MY GOD!
I DIDN'T EVEN SEE HIM.
OH, MY GOD.
T.! OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY -- OH, MY GOD!
UM, I'M AT,
I'M AT THE CORNER. I JUST HIT --
OH, MY GOD,
WHAT DID I DO?
(dispatch radio buzzes,
sirens wail )
I WASN'T EVEN SUPPOSED
TO BE THERE.
IS HE GONNA BE OKAY?
A BROKEN ARM
AND A SLIGHT CONCUSSION.
THE DOCTOR SAID
HE WAS LUCKY.
THIS IS MY STOP.
TRANSFER TO METRO TRAINS
AT LA SALLE AND VAN BUREN.
THIS IS AN ORANGE LINE TRAIN
TO MIDWAY.
TAKE THE NEXT TRAIN.
IT'LL TAKE YOU
BACK TO YOUR CAR.
O KAY.
UM, AND GOOD LUCK
WITH YOUR PRESENTATION.
THANK YOU.
YEAH.
OH, AND HEY, TYRONE?
IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
THEN WHY DOES IT
STILL FEEL LIKE IT IS?
P YOU CAN BE HARMLESS P
P AND I WILL BE SHAMELESS P
P AND WE WILL FIND
SOME KIND OF PLACE P
♪  THAT WOULD
TAKE US IN ♪
P AND HAVE US
BACK AGAIN P
P WILL TAKE US IN P
P AND HAVE US
BACK AGAIN P
P WE GOT STUCK
IN THE MIDDLE P
P OF SOME MIDDLE ROAD P
P IF NOTHING HAPPENS NOW P
♪ THEN WHERE
00 WE GO FROM HERE ♪
♪  OH, ONCE THE WEATHER
HAS CLEARED ♪
P I WANNA KNOW WHERE
WE GO FROM HERE. WHOO! P
♪  OH, TAKE US IN
AND HAVE US BACK AGAIN ♪
AND HAVE US BACK ♪
♪  WAIT TILL
THE WARM-UP'S UNDERWAY ♪
♪ WAIT TILL OUR LIPS
HAVE MET ♪
♪  WAIT TILL YOU SEE
THAT SUNSHINE DAY ♪
♪  YOU AIN'T SEEN
NOTHIN' YET ♪
♪  THE BEST IS YET TO COME,
AND, BABE, WON'T THAT BE FINE ♪
P THE BEST IS YET TO COME P
P THE DAY YOU'RE MINE P
♪  OH, THE DAY YOU'RE MINE ♪
♪  WE'VE ONLY
TASTED THE WINE ♪
P WE'RE GONNA DRAIN
THAT BOTTLE DRY P
♪  I'M GONNA TEACH YOU
TO FLY ♪
♪  HIGH ♪
♪  WAIT TILL YOU CHARMS
ARE RIPE ♪
P FOR THESE ARMS
TO SURROUND P
♪  YOU THINK YOU'VE
FLOWN BEFORE, BUT, BABY ♪
♪  YOU AIN'T LEFT
THE GROUND ♪
♪  WAIT TILL YOU'RE LOCKED
IN MY EMBRACE ♪
P WAIT TILL I DRAW YOU NEAR P
♪  WAIT TILL YOU SEE
THAT SUNSHINE PLACE ♪
♪ AIN'T NOTHIN'
LIKE IT HERE ♪
P THE BEST IS YET TO COME P
♪ AND, BABE,
WON'T THAT BE FINE ♪
P THE BEST IS YET TO COME P
P THE DAY YOU'RE MINE P
♪  OH, THAT DAY YOU'RE MINE ♪
WELL, THANKS A LOT,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
THAT'S IT
FOR ME TONIGHT.
DRIVE FAST, TAKE CHANCES,
DON'T DO ANYTHING I WOULDN'T DO,
AND IF YOU DO, DO IT TWICE
AND NAME IT AFTER ME.
I'M WES KNIGHTLY,
AND WE'LL SEE YOU
TOMORROW NIGHT.
THANK YOU.
(applause)
HEY
THAT WAS
A GOOD SHOW.
IT WAS A GREAT SHOW, REALLY.
- WELL, THANKS.
- YEAH, NO PROBLEM.
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS
GONNA SOUND WEIRD,
BUT I HAVE TO, UH...
CAN I GET YOU
A DRINK, MAYBE?
- UH, YEAH.
- YEAH?
YEAH, AT THE, AT THE BAR
YEAH? WHAT DO YOU WANT?
A VODKA PRESS.
VODKA PRESS.
I WILL, UH...
I'LL MEET YOU OVER THERE
IN JUST A SEC.
YEAH, AT THE,
AT THE BAR.
HMM.
- HEY THERE.
- HEY.
NAME'S JAKE,
BY THE WAY.
- I'M WES.
- WES.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- VODKA PRESS.
- OH, YEAH, THANKS.
SO, I WALK DOWN THE HALL
AND FOLLOW THIS WHOLE CREW
OF PEOPLE
INTO THIS HOTEL SUITE.
YEAH, GO AHEAD.
AND, UH, I WALK IN THERE,
AND GUESS WHO'S
STANDING THERE?
BONO AND THE EDGE OF U2.
NO WAY.
GWEN STEFANI FROM NO
DOUBT WAS IN THERE,
NEIL DIAMOND
WAS IN THERE.
UNBELIEV -- I HUNG OUT FOR,
LIKE, AN HOUR AND A HALF.
THEY HAD NO IDEA WHO I WAS.
IT WAS GREAT.
WOW, THAT IS
A WILD STORY.
UNREAL. BONO AND
THE FUCKING EDGE.
HEY, UH, YOU SMOKE?
I MEAN,
I'M QUITTING, BUT...
COME ON, LET'S GET
OUTTA HERE.
HEY, ON MY TAB,
WILL YA?
NO, MAN!
NO, NO, COME ON.
JESUS.
(laughs)
EH.
IT'S YOUR LIFE.
YOUR CALL.
EH!
(coughing)
I CAN'T REMEMBER
THE LAST TIME I SMOKED.
WELL,
IT IS UNNATURAL
TO MAKE NATURE
AGAINST THE LAW.
THAT'S WHAT I THINK.
(laughs)
YOU'VE GOT
A GOOD VOICE.
- THANKS.
- YEAH.
- SERIOUSLY, YOU DO.
- THANKS, MAN.
- HEY, DO YOU LIKE JAZZ?
- YES.
OH, HELLO.
MMM!
P I LOVE MY HULA GIRL P
(laughs)
SO, UH, WHAT
BRINGS YOU TO A.C.?
YOU.
ME?
BY THE WAY,
HAPPY BELATED BIRTHDAY.
WAIT, HOW'D YOU KNOW
IT WAS MY BIRTHDAY?
BECAUSE YOU WERE BORN
FEBRUARY 6th, 1982,
CHICAGO, ILLINOIS,
ST. JOSEPH'S HOSPITAL.
NO?
HOW THE HELL
DO YOU KNOW THAT?
BECAUSE, UM,
SO WAS I.
GET THE FUCK OUT.
(laughs)
YOU GOT A GREEN
LIGHT.
I'M EITHER REALLY HIGH,
OR I'M TOTALLY CONFUSED.
I WILL EXPLAIN
EVERYTHING, I PROMISE.
JUST THE FACT THAT WE HAD
SHITTY FUCKING BIRTHDAYS,
THAT IS THE WEIRD PART,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
YEAH, THAT IS WEIRD.
I CAN'T EVEN --
ALL RIGHT, WHOA, HOLD ON.
OKAY, SHH.
HOW WAS YOUR BIRTHDAY?
FINE.
WHAT?
IT WAS FINE.
- IT WAS FINE?
- YEAH.
I JUST TREATED MYSELF TO
A NICE EVENING OUT, YOU KNOW?
.P
GOOD TIMES.
SON OF A BITCH.
COME ON.
.P
WOW.
GEORGE.
WHAT'S UP?
HEY, WHAT DO
YOU WANT?
UH, WHATEVER
YOU'RE HAVING IS FINE.
TWO.
- CHEERS.
OH! WOW.
IMPRESSIVE, HUH?
WHY ATLANTIC CITY?
UH, VEGAS
WAS TOO CROWDED.
SERIOUSLY.
UM, HEADED FOR BROADWAY,
ENDED UP ON BOARDWALK.
MOST OF THESE GUYS,
AS GREAT AS THEY ARE,
WILL PROBABLY NEVER MAKE
A LIVING MAKING MUSIC.
REALLY?
THAT'S THE WAY IT IS.
SOMETIMES IT'S
JUST ABOUT PLAYING.
(vocalizing )
Patron: YEAH!
THE SORTED ONES,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
GIVE IT UP!
GIVE IT UP, A.C.
COME ON NOW.
(laughs ) YES.
( Beeping )
O KAY.
- HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
- THANK YOU.
COME ON!
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
IT'S YOUR ZODIAC SIGN.
MY ZODIAC SIGN.
IT'LL KEEP YOU IN TOUCH WITH
YOUR INNER ZODIAC STRENGTHS.
THANK YOU.
IT'LL ALSO HELP YOU ALIGN
YOUR INTERNAL ZODIAC SPIRIT
AND CENTER
YOUR ASTROLOGICAL AWARENESS.
REALLY? MMM.
IT WORKS, TRUST ME.
- THERE HE IS.
- HEY THERE.
SORRY.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I'M GOOD.
AH!
THANK YOU.
GOING THIS WAY.
SEE YA.
MMM!
YES.
YOU KNOW WHY
ASTROLOGY IS BULLSHIT?
WHY?
SHE BELIEVES IN IT.
- YEAH?
- MM-HMM.
AND I...
AM GOING TO MAKE HER STUPID
FOR BELIEVING IN IT.
'CAUSE I AM NOT
THE STUPID ONE,
HA HA, FOR NOT
KNOWING THAT SHE...
WHOA! SON OF A GUN.
WE'RE GOOD,
WE'RE GOOD HERE.
- I FELL AGAIN.
- ( chuckles)
COME ON.
I THINK YOU DID
Yo:-u
- OOPSY DAISY.
- HEY, I GOT IT!
MAYBE SHE COULDN'T LOVE
THROUGH ALL THE MEDICATION...
- YOU KNOW WHAT'S WEIRD?
- ...THAT SHE WAS ON.
I WAS JUST THINKING
ABOUT THIS.
IN THE '60s, EVERYBODY TOOK
DRUGS TO MAKE THE WORLD
ALL PSYCHEDELIC
AND WEIRD.
NOW THE WORLD
IS ALL FUCKED UP
AND EVERYBODY'S
TAKING DRUGS
TO MAKE IT ALL
NORMAL AGAIN.
YES, AND YES.
I HAVE TO GET MY CAMERA.
WE HAVE
TO INTERVIEW YOU, YES!
HOLD UP.
STAND UP.
AND HERE WE GO.
OH, SHIT.
WHOA.
WATCH YOUR STEP.
- COME ON IN.
- YEAH.
- ALL RIGHT.
- THAT'S GOOD.
OH, WOW.
LET'S DO SOME
INTERVIEWAGE, YEAH?
HEY
WANT ME TO PUT
SOME MUSIC ON?
YEAH. INTERVIEWS
ARE STARTING.
MAKE YOURSELF AT HOME,
AND I SEE YOU HAVE.
- INTERVIEWS.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
HERE, LET ME HELP
YOU WITH THAT.
THERE YA GO.
MM! (giggles)
( beep)
(humming)
(ala Dr. Strangelove) MR.
PRESIDENT, A MOMENT, PLEASE!
HELLO, MY NAME IS
WESLEY HENDERSON.
I WAS BORN
FEBRUARY 6th
IN THE WINDY CITY
OF CHICAGO, ILLINOIS.
AND, UH, THE DOOMSDAY MACHINE
HAS BEEN ENGAGED.
(phone ringing)
(groans)
HELLO?
AND I'LL GET BACK TO YOU
AS SOON AS I CAN.
ROUGH NIGHT?
AH, MAN, YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
THE PLUMBER CALLED.
SAID OUR PLACE'LL
BE READY LATER TODAY.
OH, REALLY?
OKAY, COOL.
I GUESS I'LL SEE YOU
IN A FEW HOURS, THEN.
OH, WAIT. YOU READY
FOR YOUR PRESENTATION?
NO. BUT I WAS THINKING
THAT I COULD, UH, JUST WORK
ON IT ON THE PLANE, YOU KNOW?
RIGHT. LATER.
YEAH, LATER.
(snoring)
(chuckles )
WELL...
HEY
- HEY.
- WHAT?
ARE YOU, UH,
ARE YOU ALIVE?
UH, HEY, YEAH.
(grunts )
THANKS FOR
LETTING ME CRASH.
YEAH, GOOD TIMES.
GOOD TIMES.
(chuckles ) YEAH.
DO YOU, UM, DO YOU
RECORD YOUR OWN MUSIC?
OH, YEAH.
GRAB A CD.
I JUST GOT IT
MASTERED, FINALLY.
YEAH, AND LET ME KNOW HOW
EVERYTHING TURNS OUT.
YEAH, I WILL.
DID I, UH, DID I INTERVIEW
YOU LAST NIGHT?
I CAN'T
REMEMBER.
YEAH, YEAH,
IT WENT GREAT.
- ALL RIGHT.
- YEAH.
ALL RIGHT,
WELL, THANKS.
YOU NEED A RIDE
TO YOUR CAR?
NO. I'LL TAKE A CAB.
YOU JUST STAY THERE.
AWESOME.
- THANKS, MAN
- MM-HMM.
(man vocalizing )
♪ HEY ♪
P WHEN YOUR HEART
IS BARELY BREATHING P
♪  AND YOU'RE LYING NAKED
ON THE FLOOR ♪
♪  WHEN YOU CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE DYING ♪
♪ JUST LET IT OUT ♪
P THAT'S WHAT IT'S FOR P
P AND YOU CRY P
♪ WE CRY ♪
(phone ringing)
WANNA KNOW YOUR HOROSCOPE
FOR TODAY?
AH, NOT SO FUNNY.
UM, HEY, DO YOU STILL
HANG OUT WITH THAT GIRL
WHO, UH, WHO WORKS
AT THE SAN FRANCISCO CHRONICLE?
- YEAH, SURE. WHY?
- DO ME A FAVOR HERE.
GO ONLINE AND LISTEN
TO THIS GUY'S STUFF.
HIS NAME IS
WES HENDERSON,
OR MAYBE TRY
WES KNIGHTLY.
ALL RIGHT, COOL.
GIVE ME A CALL AFTER YOU
CHECK IT OUT, ALL RIGHT?
LATER, MAN.
COFFEE?
(phone ringing)
OKAY. OH, UH...
ALL RIGHT.
- HELLO?
- HEY, IT'S JAKE.
SO, I JUST WANTED
TO LET YOU KNOW
THAT I ACTUALLY, UH,
I FOUND YVETTE AND WES.
THAT'S NICE.
YOU OKAY?
I'M FINE.
I JUST FOUND OUT
THAT AARON...
WENT THROUGH MY PURSE
WHILE HE WAS HERE, SO...
AH, SHIT.
ADD THAT TO THE LIST
OF BAD STUFF
THAT HAPPENED
ON MY BIRTHDAY.
WHAT'D HE END UP TAKING?
RUNNING.
ONE, TWO.
COME ON, IT'S TIME TO GO.
(phone ringing)
I GOT A CALL FROM A LADY
IN THE FRAUD DEPARTMENT.
JUST ONE MORE TIME
DOWN THE SLIDE, OKAY?
- HELLO?
- IS THIS SARAH REYNOLDS?
YEAH.
HI, THIS IS PAM STEWART
FROM CONSUMER FRAUD PREVENTION.
I'M CALLING REGARDING
SOME RECENT ACTIVITY
ON YOUR VISA SELECT CARD.
FOR SECURITY PURPOSES,
COULD YOU PLEASE VERIFY
THE LAST FOUR DIGITS
OF YOUR SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER?
IT'S FOUR, SIX, SIX, TWO.
AND YOUR MOTHER'S
MAIDEN NAME?
MA'AM?
ARE YOU STILL THERE?
- Sn-arr!
- MA'AM'?
SORRY, NO, I'M STILL HERE.
LONG AGO THIS BELONGED
TO YOUR GRANDMOTHER.
FOR THE PAST 30 YEARS,
IT'S BELONGED TO ME.
NOW IT BELONGS TO YOU.
AND SOMEDAY, IN WHAT WILL FEEL
LIKE THE BLINK OF AN EYE,
IT WILL BELONG TO LUCY.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, SWEETHEART.
LOVE, MOM.
(chuckles )
DOESN'T IT LOOK NICE?
GRANDMA GAVE IT TO ME.
MA'AM? ARE YOU THERE?
I CAN'T, UM, I'M GONNA HAVE
TO CALL YOU BACK.
SHORTY, IT'S TIME TO GO.
COME ON. COME ON, WE GOTTA GO.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
( Knocking )
THE LADY SAID
HE PROBABLY SKIPPED TOWN,
BECAUSE THERE WERE CHARGES
AT THE HILTON
IN NEW YORK CITY.
- L-ll.
- HOW YOU DOING?
HOW'S IT GOING?
(door closes )
(door opens and closes)
I CAN'T EVEN BELIEVE
THAT SHIT.
THAT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
SO, WHEN ARE YOU
HEADING BACK TO CALIFORNIA?
I'M ON MY WAY
TO THE AIRPORT RIGHT NOW.
(giggling)
SO WHEN IS
YOUR PRESENTATION?
TONIGHT, ACTUALLY.
COME HERE,
YOU LITTLE ROUGH-KIN.
IT'S NOT THE MONEY,
IT'S JUST...
I MEAN, OBVIOUSLY,
IT'S IMPORTANT, YOU KNOW,
BUT, IT'S JUST, THE NECKLACE
IS IRREPLACEABLE.
YOU DON'T NEED TO HEAR
ABOUT ME AND MY LIFE--
(service cuts out)
HELLO? HELLO? SON OF A --
P DOING ALL THE WALKING P
P I'M STUCK HERE
IN THE MIDDLE P
GO FOR IT.
♪ ALONG WITH GOOD
AND EVIL ♪
P I CAN HEAR YOU TALKING P
♪  AND DOING
ALL THE WALKING NOW ♪
.P
- OH, HELLO, SIR.
- HI.
HOW MAY I HELP YOU'?
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE MEETING
A FRIEND HERE,
AND I JUST, AND I, AND I CAN'T
REMEMBER HER ROOM NUMBER.
SO, NO, NO, IT'S NOT,
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
I MEAN, I TRIED HER,
I TRIED HER CELL PHONE
LIKE, YOU KNOW, IT GOES
STRAIGHT TO VOICEMAIL.
I'M SORRY, SIR, BUT I CAN'T
GIVE CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION.
OKAY, LOOK, HER NAME
IS SARAH REYNOLDS.
I -- I KNOW SHE HAS
A ROOM HERE.
OH, WAIT. I BELIEVE HER
FIANCE JUST CALLED DOWN
A MOMENT AGO, SAID HE
WAS EXPECTING SOMEONE.
ONE MOMENT.
EXCUSE ME, SIR,
BUT I HAVE
A YOUNG GENTLEMAN
DOWN HERE
WHO'S AT
THE FRONT DESK.
RIGHT AWAY, SIR.
ROOM 470.
470. THANK YOU.
HAVE A NICE DAY, SIR.
SHIT.
(panting ) OH.
YEAH, LET'S QUIT SMOKING.
(muffled music)
HELLO?
YES! OH, I JUST TEXTED
YOU, THANK GOD.
YOU SHOULD BE
LIKE DOMINO'S,
30 MINUTES
OR YOUR ORDER'S FREE.
YOU MUST BE AARON.
YOU SEE
ANYBODY ELSE IN HERE?
YEAH, OF COURSE YOU ARE.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
NO, THIS ISN'T
FOR ME, UM...
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
THERE MUST BE SOME TYPE
OF MISCOMMUNICATION.
- WHAT? HELLO?
- I NEED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE.
YES, YOU NEED TO TALK
TO ME ABOUT THE BLOW
THAT YOU
ARE GONNA GIVE ME
AND GETTING THE FUCK
OUTTA MY ROOM.
WHAT?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
CAN I HELP YOU'?
WHAT, UH, THIS
IS MINE, MINE?
- NO, NO, THIS--
- AND WHY DOES HE HAVE THIS AND NOT YOU?
- OKAY, LOOK.
- GIVE ME THE MONEY. WHO THE FUCK ARE YOU?
WHO THE FUCK
IS THIS?
- THIS IS NOT GOOD!
- HOLY JESUS!
BACK UP. BACK UP.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
GIVE ME
THE FUCKING MONEY.
GIVE HIM THE MONEY!
(groans) OH!
OH! AH!
SHIT, SHIT, SHIT, SHIT, SHIT!
SHIT, SHIT, SHIT, SHIT!
YOU GOTTA CALL 911.
YOU GOTTA --
- COME ON!
- FUCKIN' JUNKIES.
(groaning)
FUCK. OH, FUCK.
COME ON!
(Siren)
HELP!
- WE GOT HIM.
YOU GOT HIM, NURSE?
( Panting )
( phone beeping )
(line ringing )
- HI, THIS IS SARAH.
- AND LUCY.
- PLEASE LEAVE A MESSAGE.
- LEAVE A MESSAGE.
- SARAH, IT'S JAKE.
- NOT SO HIGH!
I AM ACTUALLY IN NEW YORK,
AND AARON IS IN THE HOSPITAL.
-( Lucy thuds, cries )
- HE ODed, AND I'M JUST WAITING TO HEAR
TO SEE IF HE'S OKAY.
I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT THE STOLEN NECKLACE
OR THE MONEY OR ANYTHING.
YOU KNOW,
IT WASN'T MY PLACE.
- OKAY.
- THAT'S GOOD. ALL RIGHT.
I THINK YOU'RE GONNA BE
JUST FINE.
ANYWAYS, JUST, UH,
CALL ME BACK, I GUESS.
- BYE.
- LET'S MAKE A SAND CASTLE.
(Siren)
YOU BROUGHT
IN AARON GREENFIELD?
HE'S GONNA BE OKAY,
BUT HE HAD A PRETTY
MAJOR OVERDOSE.
AND CONSIDERING THE
AMOUNT OF NARCOTICS...
LOOK, I HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH...
LOOK, I'M NOT A COP.
HE'S HEAVILY SEDATED
RIGHT NOW.
WE'LL LET YOU KNOW
WHEN YOU CAN SEE HIM.
(phone ringing)
HEY, I LISTENED
TO THAT MUSIC.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
IT IS REALLY GOOD.
YEAH, I KNOW.
BUT, HEY, I DON'T THINK I'LL
MAKE IT BACK TILL LATER TONIGHT.
I'VE HAD
A BRUTAL FEW HOURS.
I'M ACTUALLY
AT A HOSPITAL.
WHAT?
HE ALMOST DIED, THOUGH.
ODed RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME.
- WAIT, WAIT. WHO ODed?
- AARON GREENFIELD.
WHO'S AARON GREEN FIELD?
LOOK, I'LL JUST
TELL YOU LATER.
WHAT ABOUT
YOUR PRESENTATION?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'LL HAVE TO FIGURE SOMETHING OUT.
BUT LOOK, I'LL JUST GIVE YOU
A CALL LATER, I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU CAN SEE HIM NOW.
PERSONAL EFFECTS.
HE'S RIGHT IN THERE.
P YOU'LL RUN WHEN YOU CAN P
P AND HOPE FOR A DAY P
P FAR AWAY FROM HERE P
♪ I KNOW ♪
YOU BRING ME HERE?
DO I KNOW YOU?
YOU GOT MY MONEY?
DON'T JUDGE ME.
YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW YOU.
I'M OKAY WITH THAT.
♪ YOU GET LOST ♪
P SOMETIMES P
P THEN YOU COME TO REALIZE P
P MAY BE NO BLUE SKIES P
- ( phone ringing)
- ♪ AHEAD ♪
HELLO.
HEY, SORRY,
I JUST GOT YOUR MESSAGE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HOW IS HE?
DON'T WORRY.
HE'S FINE, HE'S FINE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN NEW YORK?
I HAVE YOUR NECKLACE.
(chuckles )
ATTENTION, PASSENGERS.
WE WILL NOW COMMENCE
GENERAL BOARDING
FOR FLIGHT 543
NONSTOP TO OAKLAND.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU. I DON'T EVEN --
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW TO --
WELL, THEY
ARE BOARDING NOW,
SO I WILL, UH,
I DON'T KNOW, I GUESS,
WHAT, I'LL JUST CALL YOU
WHEN I GET HOME.
FIGURE OUT A WAY TO GET
YOU YOUR NECKLACE.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
HAVE A SAFE FLIGHT.
WELL, DON'T WORK
TOO HARD.
WILL DO, WILL DO.
THANKS.
P THIS ISN'T THE MIDDLE P
P THIS ISN'T THE ENDING P
WANNA DO SOMETHING ELSE?
UM, YEAH,
YOU CAN DO WHATEVER.
GO PLAY,
GET YOUR WILDS OUT.
♪ I PAID THE POLICE
TO REMIND ME ♪
♪  THAT THE RAY
WAS BEGINNING ♪
(typing)
P WELL, ALL OF YOUR COMRADES P
P SAILED SHIPS P
P AND SLIPPED
THROUGH TIME P
P THEY WERE WELL EQUIPPED P
.P
YOU HAVE EIGHT
NEW VOICE MESSAGES.
FIRST MESSAGE.
YEAH, THIS IS, UH,
SGT. RAMIREZ, OAKLAND P.D.
CALLING TO INFORM YOU
THAT WE'VE LOCATED
AND RETRIEVED YOUR VEHICLE.
YOU CAN PICK IT UP
AT ANY TIME.
GIVE us A CALL BACK.
(510) 555-678...
-(beep)
- Roommate: HEY MAN, IT'S ME.
I JUST WANTED
TO LET YOU KNOW
I'M GONNA BE A FEW MINUTES LATE
PICKING YOU UP.
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA BELIEVE IT.
I WENT OUT WITH THAT GIRL
FROM THE SAN FRANCISCO
CHRONICLE LAST NIGHT.
- IT WAS HUGE!
- RIGHT?
AHEM.
TWO MINUTES.
PLEASE.
(groans)
I LEFT YOU, LIKE,
20 MESSAGES.
THIS CAN'T BE IT.
I MEAN, WHAT COULD YOU...
WHAT COULD YOU SAY
THAT COULD MAKE THINGS OKAY?
YOU KNOW, THERE ARE
THINGS IN LIFE
THAT YOU JUST --
YOU CAN'T TAKE BACK.
I'M SORRY.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
(groans)
THANK YOU
FOR PICKING ME UP.
ALL RIGHT.
(ala Dr. Strangelove )
ST. JOSEPH'S HOSPITAL,
IN THE WINDY CITY
OF CHICAGO, ILLINOIS.
THE DOOMSDAY MACHINE
HAS BEEN ENGAGED.
THE DOOMSDAY...
OH...
THE DOOMSDAY MACHINE HAS...
BEEN ENGAGED.
I, UH, WASN'T EXACTLY HONEST
WHEN I TOLD YOU
ABOUT MY BIRTHDAY.
I THOUGHT I HAD THE FLU,
UM, IT TURNS OUT
I HAVE, UH, LYMPHOMA.
AND, UH, THEY TOLD ME
THAT I CAN'T, UH,
THAT THEY,
UH, THEY CAN'T, UM...
THERE'S NO...
SO, MAN, JAKE, UH...
(sniffles)
AH! JUST LIVE
LIKE YOU MEAN IT,
'CAUSE YOU NEVER KNOW.
SOAK UP ALL LIFE
HAS TO OFFER.
( Beep)
I DON'T GET IT.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW,
IF WE ALL HAVE
THE SAME HOROSCOPES
AND HE'S DYING,
WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
(door opens )
INTERESTING TOPIC CHOICE,
BY THE WAY.
YEAH, THANKS
FOR THE EXTENSION.
WELL, DON'T THANK ME YET.
YOU STILL NEED TO GET
AN "A" TO PASS THE COURSE.
GOD. SON OF A BITCH.
MM. HMM.
SOMETIMES
THE SIMPLE SOLUTION IS
TO FOLLOW THE PROBLEM
TO THE SOURCE.
AH, I SEE YOU'RE A FAN
OF THE COMIC BOOK.
GENTLER ON THE SOUL
THAN HEMINGWAY.
A CHILD'S ABILITY
TO DREAM HAS NO BOUNDARY.
IF WE LIMIT OUR CHOICES
TO THAT
THAT ONLY SEEMS POSSIBLE
OR TO WITHIN
SOCIETY'S VIEWPOINT
OF WHAT IS REALITY OR REASON,
WELL, THEN, THE ONLY DREAM LEFT
IS A COMPROMISE.
SO TRUE.
SO.
IS ASTROLOGY BULLSHIT?
SEEMS LIKE
AN ETHICAL DILEMMA, NO?
I GUESS LIKE
MOST THINGS IN LIFE
IT DEPENDS ON THE WAY
YOU LOOK AT IT.
RELATING TO ETHICS, OKAY?
A KEY COMPONENT OF ETHICS
IS THE CORE BELIEF
OF STRIVING
TO LIVE THE GOOD LIFE.
OKAY, AND SO, HAVING
THESE TWO IDEAS,
HAVING -- HAVING ASTROLOGY
AND ETHICS,
JUST BECAUSE PEOPLE SHARE
THE SAME HOROSCOPES,
WE CAN'T ASSUME
THAT THEY WOULD,
THEY WOULD SHARE
THE SAME FATE.
FATE IS NOT
A UNIVERSAL CONSTANT.
FATE CAN BE CHANGED,
ALTERED.
IF I COULD JUST GET YOU
TO SIGN RIGHT THERE.
- HAVE A GOOD ONE.
- THANKS.
I MEAN, IT IS HOW
WE RESPOND TO FATE,
THE DECISIONS THAT WE MAKE
THAT DETERMINES WHO WE ARE.
(chuckles )
I LOST MY JOB,
CAR, GIRLFRIEND,
AND APARTMENT IN ONE DAY.
YOU KNOW, BUT THEN,
HOW I RESPONDED TO THAT,
MY CHOICES AFTER THAT,
IT LED ME
TO SOMETHING THAT --
SOMEONE
THAT CHANGED MY LIFE.
WHETHER YOU CALL IT
LOVE OR FAITH,
AND WHATEVER
YOUR BELIEF SYSTEM IS,
SITUATIONS OCCUR
IN OUR LIVES
THAT ARE SOMETIMES
OUT OF OUR CONTROL.
IT'S HOW WE DEAL
WITH THE ADVERSITY
THAT'S IMPORTANT.
- ( Phone ringing )
- ♪  FORTUNES... ♪
HELLO?
HI, I'M LOOKING
FOR WES KNIGHTLY.
SPEAKING.
YEAH, I'M CALLING FROM
THE SAN FRANCISCO CHRONICLE.
I HEARD YOUR MUSIC.
IT'S -- IT'S REALLY GREAT.
I THOUGHT YOUR ALBUM WAS
REALLY STRONG,
AND I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT DOING AN ARTICLE
ON YOUR STUFF
- AND YOUR UPCOMING ALBUM.
- FOR REAL?
LET'S SET UP A TIME AND GET TOGETHER.
YOU INTERESTED?
MY ZODIAC SIGN, AQUARIUS,
IS AN, UH,
AN INTELLECTUAL AIR SIGN,
WHICH, ACCORDING
TO HOROSCOPES.COM,
IS SUPPOSED
TO ENCOURAGE US
TO REBEL AGAINST
SOCIAL INJUSTICES
AND SEEK FREEDOM OF EXPRESSION
IN OUR LIVES.
IF THAT IS THE CASE, SIGN ME UP
FOR THE AGE OF AQUARIUS.
DO I HAVE A DOLLAR?
I HAVE A DOLLAR.
"LINE IN NATURE
IS NOT FOUND."
"UNIT AND UNIVERSE
ARE ROUND.
"IN VAIN PRODUCED,
ALL RAYS RETURN.
"EVIL WILL BLESS,
ICE WILL BURN.
"AS URIEL SPOKE
WITH PIERCING EYE,
A SHUDDER RAN
AROUND THE SKY."
(airplane passes)
HERE.
TRY TO STAY WARM,
ALL RIGHT?
MAYBE WE'RE ASKING
THE WRONG QUESTIONS.
MAYBE THE QUESTION
SHOULD BE
WHY DO SO MANY PEOPLE
BELIEVE IN ASTROLOGY?
MAYBE IT'S BECAUSE
THEY'RE AFRAID TO ACCEPT
RESPONSIBILITY THAT WE CONTROL
OUR OWN DESTINY.
WHETHER YOU BELIEVE
IN CHANCE, FREE WILL,
FATE, OR DESTINY,
SOMETIMES WHEN YOU LOOK
INTO ANOTHER PERSON'S EYES...
YOU JUST KNOW.
IT'S ALL IN THE STARS.
I THINK THIS
IS YOURS.
THANK YOU.
P SHININ' LIKE A WORK OF ART P
♪ HANGIN' ON A WALL OF STARS ♪
♪  ARE YOU WHAT I THINK
YOU ARE? ♪
P YOU'RE MY SATELLITE P
♪ YOU'RE RIDIN'
WITH ME TONIGHT ♪
P PASSENGER SIDE,
LIGHTING THE SKY P
♪ ALWAYS THE FIRST STAR
THAT I FIND ♪
P YOU'RE MY SATELLITE P
P ELEVATOR TO THE MOON P
♪ WHISTLIN' OUR FAVORITE TUNE ♪
♪ TRYIN' TO GET A CLOSER VIEW ♪
P YOU'RE MY SATELLITE P
♪  YOU'RE RIDIN'
WITH ME TONIGHT ♪
P PASSENGER SIDE,
LIGHTING THE SKY P
♪ ALWAYS THE FIRST STAR
THAT I FIND ♪
P YOU'RE MY SATELLITE P
P MAYBE YOU WILL ALWAYS BE P
P JUST A LITTLE OUT OF REACH P
P YOU'RE MY SATELLITE P
♪  YOU'RE RIDIN'
WITH ME TONIGHT ♪
P PASSENGER SIDE,
LIGHTING THE SKY P
♪ ALWAYS THE FIRST STAR
THAT I FIND ♪
P YOU'RE MY SATELLITE P