(scratches)
(musical tones)
(rock music)
♫This to me is crucial, enough
that when I started thinking
♫It indicated something was on
♫In the morning I yawn,
take a look in the glass
♫Turn my toothbrush on
♫Excuse me if I refer to
this as it but it's soothing
♫And cooling and calming me down
♫When I feel like Michael
Douglas in "Falling Down"
♫Like Calgon it takes me away
♫101 nights of great flex
♫I like to keep the words
simple about something complex
♫I'm shifting into second gear
when I'm racing down the road
♫With my baby blue and a hole in my shoe
♫What is this, what is this
♫Things are happening, quite a bliss
♫The world is shifting
♫Let me out, let me out
♫What is this, what is this
♫Things that happen, don't wanna miss
♫The globe is shifting
♫When the fires burn, turn the knob
♫'Cause that's the way the world turns.
♫What is this, what is this
♫Things are happening, quite a bliss
♫The world is shifting
♫Let me out, let me out
♫What is this, what is this
♫Things that happen, don't wanna miss
♫The world is shifting
♫Let me out, let me out
♫What is this, what is this
♫Things that happen, don't wanna miss
♫The globe is shifting
♫When the fires burn, turn the knob
♫'Cause that's the way the world turns
♫That's the way the world turns
(rock music)
- Okay, would you rather
get caught masterbating
to gay porn, or picking
your nose and eating it.
- I think I'm gonna have
to take picking my nose.
- I'm gonna have to go with gay porn.
- Oh, Mason, dude really?
- Yeah, masterbating is
normal, and if you're gay
then masterbating to guys is normal.
I don't care who you are,
you know, eating your boogers
is just nasty.
- You're right, I'm gonna
have to jerk off to gay porn.
- Okay, I got one.
Would you rather get
caught fucking a sheep
or fucking your cousin?
- My first cousin?
- Of course.
- My first cousin being a girl?
- Yeah, sure.
- Well, who catches me?
Does like a relative catch me?
- I don't know, why does it matter?
- Well, as long as my mom never finds out,
yeah I'd fuck my cousin.
- Hey, if it;s good enough for Einstein.
- I'd fuck a sheep.
- [Bernard] What, ew really?
- What's wrong with you?
- You haven't seen my cousin, okay?
- You're a senior in highschool.
Would you rather get
caught making out with
the ugliest girl in the
freshman class or bust a woody
in a shower room full of naked guys?
- Dude, that happened to me one time.
No, no, no,no,no, no, no look
in gym class the hottest girl
in school she was wearing this
like tight little tee shirt.
What? Hey, fuck you guys.
Like that could never happen to you.
- [Bernard] I know,
what a way to start off
a movie right?
It would seem appropriate
if you knew these guys.
This is Leroy.
He likes structure in his
life, which makes sense
he's an architect.
He's also five years
into his ten year plan
which includes buying a
house, getting married,
having kids, and making
partner at his firm.
Although lately, I'm not
so sure if that plan's
working for him.
Mason and I played soccer in highschool.
He got all of these
scholarship offers senior year
and then what's he do?
He up and quits the team
saying he doesn't want to deal
with the bullshit anymore.
He's a good guy, but I think
he's afraid of anything
becoming too real.
I'm not even sure why
I'm friends with Victor.
He's kind of angry at the
world for fighting him,
which is odd because he started it.
He's great to at parties,
but keep him away from any
female family members.
Seriously.
- What are you bitching about?
You haven't even called
me since the last time
out at Atomic Cowboy.
- Atomic Cowboy was like what? Months ago?
- Yeah. So, what's doin' boys?
- Well,
- Shit, you go first.
- Yeah, you got first.
- Come on, what?
- That night we went
Barnapoli, that's where I met
that girl Lily, right?
We were debating Modern
Art, specifically--
- [Victor] Such a dork.
- [Leroy] Whatever.
We're also talking and
even though I thought
what she was saying was kind
of bullshit, I couldn't stop
thinking about how
absolutely beautiful she is.
- [Bernard] Wait, back up, who's Lily?
- [Victor] She's Crystal's friend.
- [Bernard] Crystal who?
- [Victor] Come on, I
told you about Crystal.
- [Bernard] No.
- [Victor] Crystal, the
craziest girl I ever met
in my entire life, Crystal.
- [Bernard] Dude, I haven't
talked to you in months.
I don't know who Crystal is.
- [Victor] Yes, you do,
I met her the same night
we were all over at Atomic
Cowboy and Mason met Angela.
- [Bernard] Angela?
Wait a second, back up,
all three of you guys,
including the guy who's got a girlfriend,
go out and meet chicks the same night
and come to (mumbles) I get nothing?
- [Bernard] Okay, so now you
can see we're getting into
this thing where we tell
the story in flashback
and pause it so you can
hear us here at the bar
talking things over.
And, if I'm also doing
this voiceover narration
it's gonna get really
confusing so now I'm gonna
leave you to watch the story.
But, I might be back at
the end to explain things
if you don't understand it all.
- Oh see, that's even better.
Tell 'em how you met
Angela and tell 'em about
the contest and what that girl--
- Maybe we shouldn't tell so
many people about the contest,
it kinda makes us look
like total assholes.
- Dude, what are you talking about man?
It's Bernard and Leroy, they already think
we're total assholes, come on tell 'em.
- All right, so that night
we were at Atomic Cowboy
and I met this girl Angela
who was just...
- [Victor] No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
It started off at we
were at our apartment,
so Mason and I are trying
to come up with this idea
for this competition.
This is so exciting, this
has probably got to be
the most genius thing we
have ever come up with.
So, okay, what's on the list so far?
- Okay, African, Arab.
- Yes.
- [Mason] Asian.
- Good.
- Wait a minute, wait a minute
we should put East Asians.
- What do you mean? That's Asian.
- No, cause Russia's in Asia.
- Oh perfect, Russian, put Russian down.
- No, no, no there's no
race that's called Russian.
They're Caucasian.
- All right, fine, fine,
fine, fine put Caucasian down.
- Isn't going to be pretty
easy to find a white girl
to sleep with us--
- So what? Who cares?
You know, that's the whole point
you gotta complete the set.
- Like Latino.
- You mean Latina, oh Latina.
- Yeah, whatever you fucking homophobe.
- Indian, now Indian as in Ghandi,
or Indian as in Geronimo?
- How about one of each?
- Yeah, I don't know man.
I mean I've seen girls
from India in Saint Louis,
but I've never seen any Native Americans.
- So what? It'll make
the game last longer.
- No, it'll make it impossible to win.
- ♫I don't want no 'tang
that's hard to find
♫Don't want no tang that's hard to find
- Okay, fine, fine, fine,
fine put Native American down,
we'll see.
- But, they gotta be over 50% none of this
half and half shit, it doesn't count.
You can't go bang Maria and call that your
fucking Latino girl.
- They've gotta be like
two thirds, or whatever,
perfect, good.
- How's somebody going
to be two thirds one race
and one third another you fucking dipshit?
- What do you mean how?
What do you mean how?
From like their...can I explain?
- [Mason] I'm sorry.
- Okay, from like their
grandparents or whatever.
If they got two grandparents
that are...listen to me.
that are one race
and they got another
grandparent that's another race,
okay, you're right it doesn't work.
It doesn't work.
- [Victor] No, wait I've been
thinking about this okay,
so listen, so, if you go
back to the grandparents'
grandparents' grandparents--
- [Mason] Listen idiot it
doesn't work, there's no exponent
of two that's also divisible by three.
- [Victor] Okay, wow since
I don't know what that means
I'm just gonna assume I'm right.
- Just making it a ketchup
sandwich, or something.
- This is your ketchup.
I can use this ketchup now?
- Guys, I think--
- Wait, wait, wait, what's
wrong? What's wrong?
- I think I have to go home?
- Wait why? Why, why, why, why, why?
Don't leave.
- My dick touched--
- What?
- Oh man look, I just gotta go.
- Whoa, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What's going on, what's wrong?
- All right look, I was in
the bathroom, all right.
- Yeah.
- And, I had to take a
crap, okay so look, I cased
the joint, I made sure
nobody was in there.
I double papered the seat,
I sat down on the toilet,
dropped it between my legs and--
- What?
- Well, the water must
have been really high up
in the toilet because my
hang down touched the--
- Huh?
- [Victor] I don't know.
- Look, my dick touched
the toilet water, dude.
- Okay.
- Okay, so.
- So?
Do you know how many people have taken
a shit in that toilet?
- Oh actually, well no not
off the top of my head.
I don't, sorry.
It's no big deal.
- I had to clean my penis off in the sink.
- Please tell me you
locked the bathroom door
first, Bernard.
- Oh yeah, I wish I had.
- Please tell me that someone in here
didn't catch you with your
penis in the bathroom sink.
- No.
- Oh, well then--
- No, I was still applying
the soap when they walked in.
(laughs)
I gotta go.
- Ow.
- I just don't understand why
you always have to do that.
- I mean I'm agreeing with you.
I guess I don't understand
what the problem--
- Well, you didn't even wait
to hear what I was gonna say.
- [Victor] Hey yo, fuck that.
- Cool.
- Do you want me to get you a drink?
- Sure.
(kiss)
- [Victor] Hey Denise,
I'll take a Schlafly.
- [Bernard] Oh, Glenmorangie, Denise.
- What's up buddy? How's it going fellas?
What's up, hey how's that
new teaching job going?
- It's good.
- You know, send Denise home, okay?
Can we please let's just go on safari.
- Safari? What's that?
- Bernard, tell him what safari is.
- It's a perilous adventure
through the concrete jungle
hunting and capturing the
elusive poonani beast.
- Yes, come on it'll be like college.
- He can't do that.
- Yeah man, I don't think I could do that.
- Yes, you can, Denise
does whatever you say.
I mean, you could show up tomorrow morning
with another girl's
panties around your neck
and you could just say, you know,
"Hey, don't worry about it."
And, she'd be like, "Oh,
okay yeah, I won't."
- [Mason] Dude, he can't do that.
It's against the rules,
he's got a girlfriend.
- So?
- So, I'll have to figure
out a way around it.
- A way around it?
- Yeah, yeah hold on.
- Why are we even talking about this?
- Go break up with Denise
and then come tag ass
with us tonight and then tomorrow you can
get back together with her.
It'll be great.
- What?
- [Mason] You know she'll take you back.
- No, why should he go
through all of that?
- Because, then he's still
a nice guy, unlike you.
- No, that would make me a dick.
- Oh, Jesus Christ why
are you such a pussy?
- I gotta go guys, I'll see you later.
- What's wrong with you?
- [Victor] Hey, hey man.
He's just upset that his johnson
fell into another person's
corn log water.
- If you're broken up with
Denise you're not cheating
on her and you're not lying
to the girl you're going to
get with that night when she asks you
if you have a girlfriend.
- What?
- You can get your freak
on without breaking
any relationship rules.
I know girls that like
to do dirty, kinky shit.
The other night this
girl licked my asshole.
- Oh, come on.
Why would I wanna do that?
- Give it a try, trust me you'll love it.
- [Leroy] I'll just take your word for it.
- Okay, all right, no
that's great I'm gonna get
another beer.
- Wait, wait, total dick, fucking shit.
- Man, those two.
- Yeah, I know they can't help themselves.
- You know what, screw this. I'm gonna go,
- Oh no, come on man, stick around.
- You know, I got papers to grade.
Just tell them I left, all right?
- Dude, come on man.
That's not enough cash, man.
That's not gonna cover
it, I'm just saying.
- [Victor] Oh, boo fucking
hoo, you shoulda stuck around.
The girl I was talking to
had some cute friends, man.
- [Bernard] Okay fine,
what happened after I left?
- [Mason] So, Victor's
trying to get on this Indian,
you know, from like India
chick and he's working on her
for like an hour.
- [VIctor] That is crazy.
- I know.
- Oh, oh, look who it
is, Mason this is Jaamini
Majaraja Perum.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hey, good pronunciation.
- Thank you so much, darling.
- Jaamini, nice.
- Who's ready for shots?
- Oh, look who it is, Sarah Redcloud,
meet my friend Victor and Jaamini.
- [Victor] You know, I still
don't believe that chick
was Native American.
- [Mason] God, you're a sore loser.
- [Victor] Look, she didn't even look.
Okay fine, what tribe was she?
- [Mason] You know what,
specifically she was Alaskan Inuit.
Like I was gonna ask her,
Christ just give it up already.
- Very nice to meet you
guys, there are from Mason.
- Thank you, Mason.
- [Sarah] Cheers.
- Cheers, thank you.
- All right, I've gotta
go to the bathroom.
- Okay, okay.
- I'm gonna go with you.
- Okay, we'll be right back.
- Okay, bye.
See you in a little bit.
I'm gonna what?
Take her to my teepee,
get up in her wigwam.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait
are you actually taking
that contest seriously?
- You're obviously taking it seriously.
- I totally forgot all about
it, I mean, the only reason
I was talking to that girl
was because she's cool man.
- So, you wanna forget about the contest
'cause you're striking out already.
- Oh, are you kidding?
I'm gonna nail her like a two by four.
- Like a two by four?
- Yes.
- [Mason] Sure.
- You know what Mason, you
know what I think you need
to grow up.
I mean that contest was a little
stupid and somewhat racist.
- Racist?
Nice, so what's my philosphy
when it comes to women?
They're all pink on the inside.
- Oh, Jesus Christ I can't
believe you just said that.
Look, I really don't care, okay?
This place is kind of boring
me, I think we should take off.
Let's go to Barnapoli, yes.
- Oh, yeah that's a great
idea so we can get there
and you can bitch about
how the whole place
is full of gold diggers all the time.
- Oh, I don't care
there's going to be a ton
of hot ass there, it'll be great.
- There's two really nice girls
here and I think it's just
a foolish thing to do.
- So, are you gonna come
with or are you going to
try and get with the Two Dogs Fucking,
or whatever her name is?
- Oh, I'm gonna stay man.
- All right, well I'm gonna
have Leroy go with me.
- Oh, what a combo.
- You're gonna be left her alone.
- Yeah, great.
- [Victor] Good bye.
- It's better that way.
- [Victor] Have a good time.
- So, where's your girl?
- I said I was hungry
so she's off trying to
find me some food.
- Wow okay, listen you
need to come have some fun
with me, okay?
Just leave her behind.
Just tell her you need a
night out with the guys.
- Dude, I'm not gonna go pick up--
- Hey listen, listen no
chasing women, all right?
Just, we're gonna go out, drink
heavily, just talk and shit.
Just you and me, come on.
- All right, I'll go.
(kiss)
- [Mason] You actually
believed this guy when he said
he wanted to go out and not chase women?
- [Leroy] No, I'm not that
stupid I knew what he was
up to, I just I wanted a change of pace.
- [Victor] Yeah, well it
wound out working out for you,
didn't it?
So, fuck both you guys.
- Lucky you met him,
he's such a great guy.
And, nice to meet you Sarah
- [Sarah] Nice to meet you.
- Oh, curious what percent
of Native American are you?
- Excuse me?
- Remember, it doesn't
count unless she's over 50%.
Thems are the rules.
Take care, pleasure.
- He's--
- Fuck you.
- What? Sarah, Sarah, Sarah,
Sarah, Sarah, Sarah, Sarah,
wait, wait, wait he's just joking.
He's a jokester, that's what he does.
- You think I'm gonna trust you now?
- Can I do something for
you just to get you to stay?
Just anything, I don't care.
- Yeah?
- What's on your top shelf?
- We've got some Hennessy XO Cognac.
- I'll have that.
Pay her.
- Thirty.
- Okay.
What?
- Oh my god, I can't believe that.
- Yeah, me neither.
What a bitch.
- No, I can't believe you let
yourself get played like that.
- [Victor] So, what
percent Japanese was she?
- [Mason] None, she's Korean asshole.
- Maybe I deserved it.
You know what, can I get
a Schlafly's and a pack
of soft ones please?
I'm Mason.
- Angela.
- Nice to meet you.
Would you ever do that to a guy if you got
really pissed at him?
- No, I'd hit him up for an entire dinner,
then walk out on him.
- So, I'd be running kind
of a big risk when I ask
you out to dinner?
- Only if you pissed me off.
- Do you wanna go out to dinner sometime?
- No.
- [Mason] Why not?
- I don't date guys who smoke?
- I don't smoke, never did.
- Okay listen, if I wind
up talking with a girl
in this place--
- Dude, I thought you
said you weren't gonna go
on a hunt tonight?
- Well yeah man, I mean not on purpose,
but the fact of the matter is, you know,
even when I'm not looking for it hot pussy
just tends to find me, so.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, it's a blessing and a curse.
Listen, girls always have
friends so if I wind up
with a girl who wants to get with me
you gotta take care of her friend, okay?
- Yeah, sure I'll take care of her friend.
- I mean, you know what
I mean when I say like
take care of her, right?
- Yeah, yeah I know buy her
a drink, fucking talk to her
all night long.
- No, no man come on.
- Dude, I have a girlfriend.
- So what?
- Okay, so I have a girlfriend.
- All right, listen if we
end up taking these girls
back to my place I can't get on my girl
if her friend's just sitting
there doing nothing, man.
- Dude, I'm not gonna
fuck the friend just--
- Listen, listen, listen you
don't have to fuck her, okay?
Just mess around with her a little bit.
- No.
- All right, all right
come on man, how 'bout
you just go down on her,
you know, you can do that.
Then she can suck you off, it'll be great.
- You lunatic, you really
think that's not cheating?
- Okay, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine.
If she doesn't make you blow your load
then that's not cheating
because you didn't get
any sex out of it.
- What?
- Mm-hmm, yeah.
It's great, just fucking munch
on her box, enjoy yourself
and when it's her turn to go down on you
fucking fall asleep, or you
know pretend like you can't
get it up or something.
- Dude, how is that not--
- Hey, you're gonna at
least finger bang someone
in this fucking bar, okay?
That's that.
- All right, but I--
- No, no, no, no.
No, don't try and haggle with me.
That's my final offer, let's
do this, let's do this.
- I'm a little mad at you right now.
- Good.
- I don't know maybe I
could've learned to love rap
if someone got me into, you
know, but the only chicks
I knew in highschool who
listened to rap were these
Barbie doll blondes who
were all, "I listen to Ice-T
"and I slept with a black guy
once, that means I'm hard."
(laughs)
- Hi.
- Oh, hey sorry I was just gonna say
I used to be really into rap, so.
- Oh yeah, so you can
help me out with that?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But, you know, I kinda
got burned out on it.
Now, I just mostly listen to Sting.
- [Mason] What a fucking
bullshitter you are.
You hate Sting.
- [Victor] Asshole, chicks
dig Sting, so you tell them
you like Sting so they'll like you.
Now, shut the fuck up I'm telling a story.
- Ah, I love Sting.
- [Victor] So, there you go dickhead.
- Oh yeah, what else do you listen to?
- Just about anything, really.
But, right now I have a big
collection of 80s music.
- Great.
- I like some reggae.
My dad used to play jazz so I
listen to Coltrane sometimes.
I like just about any kind of music.
Well, except country.
- Oh, that's cool.
I like blues, I like
funk, I like some techno.
- [Mason] Well, that one backfired on you,
didn't it ass face?
- I think there's something to appreciate
in every kind of music.
Except country, of course.
- Of course.
- [Bernard] Hey, what's
wrong with country?
(clears throat)
- I'm sorry, this is Lily.
- Hi, I'm Victor.
- Are you here by yourself, Victor?
- No, no I'm actually here
with a buddy of mine, Leroy.
You might just getta bang out of him.
- Oh my god, you're so
completely fucked in your head.
- Oh, okay you really think
a comic book full of crude
sketches about guys punching each other
counts as art?
- Have you ever even seen
Alex Ross' watercolor
to Kingdom Come?
- I really wouldn't know who that is.
- Yeah. Or David Mack's mix media?
- [Victor] Oh my god, Leroy
please, please tell me
you did not talk to her about comic books
the whole time.
- [Leroy] You know, comic
books are a great in
to the ladies, my man.
- [Victor] Oh shit, fine. Go ahead.
- Or Craig Thompson's
brilliant brush work?
Or the ridiculously
complex graphic matches
that Brian Bolland pulled
off in The Killing Joke?
- Using an artist medium
doesn't automatically
makes someone an artist.
- Okay, but when Lichtenstein
borrows the asthetic
of comic books for his pop
art paintings then he counts
as real artist?
- God no, no, no, no, no.
I hate all that neo-dotist crap
in the contemporary museum.
And, that ass ugly Pulitzer
building, ugh it's terrible.
- You did not just say that.
The Pulitzer foundation
building was designed by
Tadao Ando.
- So?
Okay, so what if I told
you that Caravaggio
only painted realism
because he had no sense
of imagination?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa easy there.
- Ooh, oh, see wait a minute.
- No, no, no Caravaggio's
use of light it was...
Hey, it was absolutely groundbreaking.
And you know what?
I'm sorry but it took a
whole lot more imagination
than writing pow and--
- Oh, nah wait now I don't
know I think Caravaggio
only used that intense
lighting so he could leave
half the canvas black.
- What?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah I read
that he thought that if
he only had to paint
half the picture he could
crank out paintings
faster and make more cash.
(laughs)
Read it.
- You read it?
Okay, yeah now you're
just messing with me.
- Yeah, but we're starting
to understand each other.
- Yes, we're starting to
understand each other.
And, I don't like it.
- I've got a date with Crystal.
- I assumed.
- So, what's up with that Lily girl, man?
- I don't know I had fun arguing with her,
but she's all uptight and snobby.
- She's hot.
- So?
- So, if I were you I'd plug
her like a bathtub drain.
- Okay dude, even if I didn't
have a girlfriend, which I do,
I could never go out with a
girl who's all rigid like that.
You know, I mean would you
wanna go out with a girl
who has to get out of the
shower if she has to pee?
- Fuck no.
- I know you don't get out of
the shower if you have to pee.
- Are you kidding?
I mean sometimes I take
a shit in the shower.
- [Leroy] Dude, you brought
your drink with you man.
- You know, you are the
best boyfriend a girl
could ask for, you know that?
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah, flowers, romantic
dinners almost every night,
sex twice a night.
- Isn't that what I'm supposed to do?
- Well yeah, but I mean
after two years you think
most guys kind of get
comfortable and stop making
the effort, but you're just the opposite.
- I just want you to know I love you.
- [Victor] Yeah, you love
her so much you went home
and banged her after meeting another girl
out at a bar.
- [Leroy] Look, it was a
complicated situation, okay?
Okay wait, fuck you, it was your idea.
- So, what are we doing tomorrow?
- Oh Sean Murphy's doing a signing down at
Star Clipper comics.
I'm gonna take some of his books down
and get 'em signed.
- [Victor] Oh good, more
comic books so I guess
that's just your go-to
subject with the ladies.
- [Leroy] Ladies like a
man who likes comic books.
Certain ladies, ladies I like.
- [Victor] Hold on, I just
wanna take some notes here.
- Okay, and I'll go?
- Well, do you really like comic books?
- Well yeah.
- Which ones?
- I mean, you've turned me onto Powers,
Y: The Last Man, Invincible.
- Yeah, I know those are the ones I like,
but you might like some
others that I don't.
- Well, I don't know, I
mean the ones you showed me
are good.
- Yeah, but well look around
next time we're in Star Clipper
and maybe you might find
something I hadn't noticed
and then we could show each
other new stuff we found.
- Well sure, I mean if
you want me to do that
I can do that.
- It's not a matter of
if I want you to or not.
I just thought you might actually like to
find something that you like.
- But, I like the ones that you showed me.
- Okay, that's cool.
- [Mason] Okay, so you
didn't go out with Lily.
- [Leroy] Well, that's
not the end of this story.
After Victor took Crystal on a date--
- [Victor] Yeah, yeah so I
take her out and it's all this
normal nice talk garbage.
And then, she goes, "You're
treating me like a girl."
- Huh?
- Is this how you talk
to your guy friends?
Would you like to get to know me better?
- Yeah, of course.
- All right, then let's
talk. Quit being so polite.
- Wow, okay.
How old are you?
- 25.
- How much do you weigh?
- Between 120 and 124 and three quarters,
depends on the day.
- Interesting.
What's your favorite position?
- [Leroy] And she said cowgirl, right?
- [Mason] I don't know, I
bet she said missionary.
- [Leroy] She said rum punch.
- [Mason] I always thought
she looked more like
a doggy style girl to me.
- [Leroy] Snotty princess.
- [Victor] No.
- [Leroy] Farmer's daughter?
- [Leroy] The Charlie Chaplin.
- [Victor] Okay, just stop okay?
- [Bernard] Wait, what's cowgirl?
- [Victor] Just listen.
- What's your favorite position?
- Making the guy call me
Daddy while I strap-on
fuck him in the ass.
If I really love a guy I might throw in
a reach around for him.
- You do that a lot?
- Yeah, with every guy I date.
You'll get your turn later tonight.
- [Mason] That explains so
much about your relationship.
(laughs)
- It doesn't seem like
there's much in that position
for you, though.
- There is if we do it in front
of a mirror so I can watch
the look on his face when I
jam it in with no lubrication.
(laughs)
- Oh man.
- [Bernard] There's no way she said that.
- [Victor] Leroy, am I lying?
- [Leroy] No Bernard,
you didn't meet Crystal.
- [Bernard] Okay, would
you rather get caught
being strap-on fucked in the ass--
- [Victor] Oh fuck, can I
just tell my fucking story?
- [Bernard] Okay, shit sorry go ahead.
- Okay, so I am up in
the stirrups waiting for
my gynecologist.
- Yeah so, and she keeps
looking over at me, right?
And, I'm trying to pretend
like nothing's going on.
- And, the nurse is all, "hmm".
And I'm like, "What?"
- I'm squeezing as hard
as I can, but the thing is
every time the car hits a
bump I'm positive I'm gonna
completely crap my pants.
- And, she just says, "Hang
on a second," and she walks
outta the room leaving
me there in the stirrups
with no clue what she saw
that caused this big, "Hmm".
- The thing is up until now
the date has just been going
really well, and it's our
second date and I'm sure she's
expecting me to walk
through her door and like
kiss her goodnight, I don't know.
- So, she's gone a good five
minutes which seems like
five hours because at this
point I'm seriously sweating.
- I'm thinking, okay, well
if I don't kiss her goodnight
she's gonna think I'm not
interested, but if I do
I mean I run the serious
risk of taking a dump
all over her doorstep.
- And, when she comes back
she's got another nurse
with her and she just points
between my spread out legs
and says, "What do you think?"
- You know, so this is it's
getting worse and worse.
- And, I swear the other nurse just goes,
"Hmm" with the exact same
expression on her face.
- And, I'm thinking you
know what, "Maybe if I get
"to her place quick enough I
might be able to hold it in
"and walk her to her door."
- And, I am so upset by this
point I'm like, I just yell
"What the hell is it?"
- But, if not I'm gonna
start peeing out my ass.
So, I'm just driving faster and faster.
- And, both the nurses look
up at me like they have
no idea what I'm so agitated
about and the first one
just casually goes, "I think
you might have Chlamydia,
"but don't worry about it."
- Until we're going at least
a hundred miles an hour
and I swear to god we're going
well over 90 at this point.
- Yeah, "Don't worry about
it because it can't cause
"death or sterility, the
doctor will be with you
" in a moment."
- And, she turns to me,
she's like, "Yeah, could you
"slow down, maybe?"
And, I turn to her I'm like, "No."
- And, they walk out of the
room and I'm just praying
that the doctor's gonna
come back in and say those
stupid fucking cunt nurses have no clue
what they're talking about.
- And then, all of a
sudden we hit this pothole
and I make this sound like, "Oh, shit."
- But, another five minutes
goes by, she still hasn't
come in and I'm totally freaking out.
- Oh no, and then there's
this long silence.
- Okay, then while I'm waiting
I notice that they have those
informational pamphlets on the wall.
So, I hop off the examination
table, I go over to the wall
I grab the one that's for Chlamydia.
- Which would be awkward
on any second date,
but here it's worse because--
- And, the first thing it says?
May cause death or sterility.
- I keep making these grunting
noises and I can feel it
starting to leak out.
- It was fortunate that the
nurses' diagnosis was wrong.
- No joke, it started to leak out.
- Unfortunate that it
took about three days
to get the test results back.
- And I'm afraid it's
gonna start getting smelly.
- And, by that time I'd
already kicked my boyfriend
in the balls for giving me VD.
- And, it just the worst experience.
Why am I telling you this story?
- He really didn't want to go
out with me much after that.
(laughs)
- Wow, well remind me never to
give you a venereal disease.
- You'd be better off if you didn't.
- Yeah, I don't know I just...
I keep trying to get the
spark back in the relationship
and it's not working and
I'm running out of ideas.
- You think she's up for a threesome?
- You can make her wear costumes and wigs
and shit like that, then you
can pretend you're banging
a whole bunch of different chicks.
- Then, she puts her leg
up in the air and you
bend over backwards and put
your dick between her tits.
Then, take an ice cube and
you rub it on her taint
in a counter-clockwise motion.
Make sure she's got a hand
free to pull on your balls
or it won't work right at all.
- Oh, I gotta write this down.
- Just fuck her more.
- Okay.
- Have sex with a guy
once, you'll really learn
to appreciate women more, trust me.
- You have to make her
feel really special, okay?
'Cause it's small day to
day things that creates
a loving bond between two people.
It's that bond of love and
trust that fills two hearts
and makes them beat as
one and creates a passion
that'll last for all of eternity.
If you truly love her and you
want to cherish her forever
you'll always pay attention
to the little things
that add up to a lifetime of love.
- [Leroy] Like what?
- Like, when she's about
to come stick your finger
in her ass.
- Oh, 'kay, stick it
right on in there, huh?
- [Bernard] Wait, does that really work?
- [Mason] Oh, totally, yeah
but when you're doing it
you gotta--
- [Leroy] Look, that's
not actually important
to the story, okay?
- Okay, good yeah, no good anything else?
(sentimental music)
Hey.
- Came up with a more convincing argument
that comic books are real art?
- [Victor] Oh, please god
Leroy tell me you did not
start talking to her
about comic books again.
- Oh, that's what it is, from the bar.
Yeah, you looked familiar
and I just couldn't place it.
No, I was just looking for
some pieces for my place.
- Oh really?
- Yeah, what a coincidence.
- Yeah, 'cause Crystal told
me that Victor was probing her
for information about me a few days ago.
- [Victor] Oh yeah, I was
probing her all right.
- [Leroy] Yeah, thanks for
being subtle about that
by the way, that was real
smooth, smooth operator.
- Victor said that?
- Yeah.
- That silly kid.
(laughs)
Yeah, I don't know I just
thought it was cool that we
had a real conversation, you know.
I don't know many people I can
have real conversations with.
I just thought maybe you
might wanna hang out or--
- Are you asking me out?
Don't you live with your fiance?
- Actually, we're not engaged.
I don't even know if
we're gonna get engaged.
It's kind of complicated.
- I don't think I could, I
don't do that kinda stuff.
- I know, I...this is not...I just...
I know this looks bad, but--
- But it's not like that, is
that what you're gonna tell me?
- Would you believe me if
I said I wasn't like that?
- No.
But, I might be willing to
suspend judgment for a night.
- [Victor] Dude, wait, wait
she knew you had a girlfriend
and she still went on a date with you?
(laughs)
You fucking stud.
- Really?
- But, only one night.
- You've got a deal, sister.
(laughs)
How late of a night?
Hey, we can talk about that later, okay.
I'm gonna go, and I'll see ya.
- Why don't you look around?
- I'm gonna.
- [Lily] Okay.
- You look great today, by the way.
(laughs)
- Thank you.
(funky music)
- [Victor] Oh my god,
you took a Japanese chick
to a sushi restaurant.
- [Mason] She's fucking Korean.
- [Victor] So what, I
mean those are hardly even
different countries.
- Is that okay?
- [Angela] - Go ahead.
- And then, there won't
be any awkward moments.
I'll just talk the whole
date it'll be great.
- Okay yeah, come on.
- But, I can't do that, can I?
- Do you feel like you
need to be constantly witty
and charming on a first date?
- No, I know whether or not
I'm gonna get a second date
is based entirely on
my sexual performance.
- Oh.
- I should watch my mouth, I'm sorry.
You might take some of
this crap I say seriously.
- I've always thought people
take sex far too seriously
and not seriously enough at the same time.
- What do you mean?
- Well, like this one time a few years ago
on break from college
a bunch of us got drunk
and went skinny dipping
in my friends mom's pool
'cause she was out of town.
- There's this girl that I had
a crush on so she transferred
half way through freshmen
year, so we talked
for three solid years.
I have not had the balls
to ask this girl out.
- Well, it was all couples
and it was pitch black
so eventually everbody starts making out.
- So, she ends up breaking
up with her boyfriend
at the time who graduated a year before.
- And, probably doing some
other stuff I didn't even
want to know about.
- So, now she's single in
this big way and we just kinda
fate has it we end up in the
same group history project.
- So, I'm naked with
my legs wrapped around
my boyfriend's waist, he was also naked
and we're making out.
- I plan it for a night
that my parents are gonna be
out of the house and I just
kinda conveniently forgot
to invite the other two people over.
- I guess he starts thinking,
"Hey, if everybody else
"is doing it in the pool why not us too?"
- So, I have no plans to make
a physical move on this girl.
I seriously was just
gonna ask her to dinner,
all gentlemen like.
- Which, I thought was
kind of presumptuous
considering we'd only been
going out for a couple weeks.
- I get myself all pumped up for it.
I mean I'm determined I'm gonna ask her
no matter what.
- Well, he starts trying to angle it,
but he's not having any success with it.
- We started on this thing,
this project and I say
something stupid out of
nervousness and she laughs.
- He's moving his hips
all around trying to get
some distance between our bodies
to get the right angle.
- I'm like okay, this is it, this is it.
And, just as I get the
words out, you know,
"Would you let me take you to dinner,"
I hear the garage door
open and it's my parents.
- Meanwhile, I'm tightening up my legs
to make sure that isn't going to happen.
- I introduce everyone
to everyone, no big deal.
My dad walks off, you know.
- Look, as a girl if you called
everything to a dead halt
everytime a guy was trying
to take off your clothes
you'd get like two
minutes of make out time
in your whole life.
- My mom decides to stick
around and start talking
to this girl.
- We keep making out and at
first he'd try to go for it
then back off, then try again.
- So,she kinda gives this
girl a look and she says,
"Do you think it's normal
for a 17 year old boy
"not to be sexually active?"
- But, eventually we get
to the point where both
of our hips are just in constant movement.
- "The fact that he's still
a virgin doesn't bother me.
"What bothers me is that
at his age, don't you think
"he should at least be fooling around?
"He's a good looking
boy, don't you think?"
- And he's getting
frustrated, which is making
the making out less
enjoyable, and I'm just
getting really pissed.
- And, this girl is just
too stunned to speak.
She's literally just
squirming in her chair.
- And, all I can think is
doesn't he get it by now?
- And, just when I think
my mom's gonna stop.
- And, I just get tot the
point where I don't even
wanna kiss him anymore.
- Finally, she says, "Tell
me doesn't your boyfriend
"try to copulate with you?"
- And eventually I just yell,
"I'm not going to fuck you."
- This girl she says,
"Oh, I gotta go," you know
and she takes her stuff
and literally just sprints
out the door.
- Yeah well, by that
point I'd kinda forgotten
there were like six
other people in the pool.
- So, after that I was just like screw it,
why take this stuff so
seriously, you know?
And, from that point on I
just kinda do whatever I want,
just refuse to put too
much thought into it.
- All the movement stops in the pool
and everybody just starts
laughing their asses off.
And, he get really embarassed
and he broke up with me.
- [Mason] Okay, she's not too uptight,
but she's not too slutty either.
I dig it.
- [Leroy] You know it's
important to walk that line
that fun in bed, but won't cheat on you.
- [Victor] I always preferred
it when girls cheated on me.
- [Leroy] What? Why?
- [Victor] 'Cause then
they can't bitch so much
when you sleep with other women.
Keep 'em closed.
- [Crystal] Come on.
- Okay, open, open, open.
- [Crystal] How and I gonna--
- Here, look, look.
Look, I got you something really special.
- Oh my god.
Vanilla rum, how did you even remember?
- Well--
- I have never seen this anywhere
other than the Carribean.
Where did you get it?
- I found a place across
river that special ordered it.
And then, went over and picked it up.
- You drove all the way to the east side
just to get this for me?
- [Leroy] Well that and to
get a lapdance at the Emerald.
- [Victor] Hey, they got
great lunch specials.
It's good food.
- Well, you know I mean I'm
there from time to time so.
- Yeah, I bet you are.
My god.
I can't believe how sweet you are.
Do you wanna get drunk and do it?
- Yes.
- [Bernard] Hmm, it's like another Victor,
only with breasts.
- [Victor] Oh, what could be better?
(slow tempo music)
- You know, I don't want you
to think I'm a certain way.
- What? I don't, I do not.
- I've only slept with
one guy in my entire life.
- [Victor] Bullshit.
- [Mason] Shut up, asshole,
she was telling the truth.
- No way, come on one guy?
- I'm only 23.
- Yeah, yeah, but one.
- Yeah.
- All right. One guy?
(laughs)
Sorry.
- [Victor] Oh Jesus, what the fuck?
- It's just the second date, you know?
- [Victor] And?
- I thought we had more
than a two date connection
going here.
- Are you kidding?
We have like 102 date vibe going here.
I just...I'm just...
You know what it is?
I'm just used to it kinda
being the other way around,
the whole who's trying to
get into whose pants game.
- [Victor] Hey, so consider
yourself lucky, dickweed.
- Yeah, me too.
- It just kinda threw me.
Come here, I'm sorry.
- [Victor] Oh, oh dude,
you better fuck her.
Seriously man, you better fuck her.
Oh, Jesus Christ, you have
got to fucking be kidding me.
- I should go.
- What?
Mason, what the hell is the matter?
- [Victor] Yeah, what
the hell is the matter?
- You know what, I don't know.
Maybe we're not entirely--
- [Victor] Not entirely what?
All right, she's an Asian
chick with big titties,
that never happens.
What entirely else do you need?
- What?
- I don't know okay?
I don't know how I feel.
I'm sorry.
- [Victor] I'm sorry my
penis is chronically limp.
- I'll call you or...bye.
- [VIctor] Oh, that's
it you're a homosexual.
- [Mason] You know what, fuck you?
Okay, maybe my interest
in this girl went deeper
than her vaginal cavity and I'm sorry
you can't understand that.
- [Victor] Hey, here's a
concept maybe you can be
in love with her and still sleep with her.
Hey buddy, let me tell
you how a heterosexual
handles this situation.
Whoa.
- Yeah.
- [Bernard] Stop liar, no
woman actually likes it rough
like that.
- [Victor] Look, they all
like it rough, all right?
Some girls just don't know it yet.
Yes.
(laughs)
(grunts)
You're so...
Hey, question where are
all of your vibrators?
- They're in the repair shop,
and I wear those things out.
- I'm sure you do, but
they didn't give you
like loaner or anything?
- Uh-huh, they didn't have any in stock
that met my sexual preference.
- I'm sorry, so you have it all
to lube this up right?
- Wait a minute, wait a minute.
You're not actually
going to try and stick it
in my butt are you?
- Oh god, of course not
what are you kidding?
You know, I heard that people
tend to, well you're welcome
like you people tend to
make jokes when they can't
admit to something, so in reality
I think you actually want
me to stick it in your butt.
- [Bernard] You know,
that's actually true.
It's a psychological phenomenon called--
- [Mason] Victor, you're the
one that keeps bringing it up.
I guess that means you want
her to stick it in your butt.
- [Victor] If you
interrupt me one more time
I'm gonna fucking smack you.
- No.
(groans)
- [Mason] Did you stick it in her butt?
- [Victor] Totally.
- [Bernard] Liar.
- [Victor] Yeah, okay I'm lying.
(laughs)
- So, I was a figure
skater in junior high.
I even did my own choreography.
- Wow.
- Yeah, so my parents
finally thought that was what
I was gonna settle into, but then I quit.
- Why'd you quit?
- I don't know, I saw
some people at the rink
speed skating so I did that for a while.
- And then, after that
you took up painting?
- Well, after playing cello
in the highschool orchestra
and studying Brazilian Jiu Jitsu.
- Oh my god.
- Yeah, when I get interested in something
I tend to jump in with both feet.
- Yeah, apparently.
(laughs)
So, how do you think
the date's going so far?
- Well, I thought that this wasn't a date.
- [Victor] Leroy, only you
would be a big enough pussy to
take a girl out to dinner and
then tell her it's not a date.
- [Leroy] Shut up, fuck face.
- Right, right.
How do you think
this-is-not-a-date is going?
(laughs)
- I think it's going pretty well.
I caught myself trying to
impress you once or twice,
which is usually a good sign.
- Well, if I don't try to
impress you don't take that
as a sign I don't like you.
I kicked myself of that
habit a long time ago.
When I was in highschool I always thought
the kids that were really
funny were really well liked.
- So, when you're in the
sixth grade you're what, 12?
- Yeah, sounds right.
- So, kids started experimenting
with kissing and such.
- So, I started trying to be
funny and it kinda worked.
- I don't really think that
my hormones had kicked in
because I really didn't
like kissing the first boy
that I kissed.
- And then, I asked out
this really pretty girl.
- But, somewhere in my mind
that I knew I was supposed
to like kissing someone, so I started
a little experimenting.
- And, she said, "Okay."
- Yeah, it's not as pervy
as you're probably thinking.
I was 12, it was just kissing.
- So, you know, then I
was all excited 'cause,
you know, I thought was really
going to have some friends
and a girlfriend, and actually be happy.
- Well, I kissed a boy with
tongue, but I thought that
was kinda gross.
- So, before my date with
this girl we had a field trip
to the like science center.
- Then, I kissed this
foreign exchange student
who really didn't speak any English.
- And, a bunch of us, including this girl,
are running around and
we're just, you know,
yukking it up and having fun.
- Then, I kissed a girl.
- You see these guys they're like making
a big, fake dinosaur skeleton.
- It wasn't too long after
that that my guidance counselor
had a meeting with my mother
who just absolutely lost it.
- And so, I run up to them
and I start pretending
that I'm mentally, well retarded.
- I remember I was
sitting outside the office
and I knew what they were talking about,
but I couldn't actually hear anything.
- So, I'm like walking funny
and drooling on myself.
And I've got my hand up like
this, like I've got some sort
of palsy or something.
- Until my mother starts shouting,
"Oh no, oh no, oh no."
- And, I start going,
"How do you do that?"
(laughs)
- Yeah, I'm pretty sure that
the last one was the girl.
- [Leroy] The girl, right.
- Yeah.
(laughs)
- And, my new friends are like dying.
They're about to pee themselves
they're laughing so hard.
- So, my mother she comes
bursting out of the office
and she grabs me by the hand without even
looking me in the eye and throws
me in the back of the car.
- And, I look back and
the girl's not there.
- She's driving down the
road like this maniac
holding this business card.
- I'm so bummed because
like everyone thought
I was so funny and she missed it.
- And, we pull up to this
building and then next thing
I know I'm in a psychiatrist's office.
- Then, someone says that they
saw her off crying somewhere.
- My mother was so convinced
that I was completely warped
and if she didn't intervene
I was gonna become like
a bisexual, nympho prostitute, you know.
- [Leroy] My god.
Yeah, and so I guess she
caught the first half
of the bit, but then she ran off.
- So, everytime she'd
take me in to see this guy
this doctor just kept
badgering me and asking me
if I knew that what I'd done was wrong.
- It turns out that
like when she was a kid
she had a hearing problem,
but that the doctor
diagnosed her as retarded.
- I just sat there with my
arms crossed and I refused
to answer 'cause, you
know, I didn't think that
I'd done anything wrong.
- So, I don't know I guess
her dad distanced himself
from her and the whole
thing really scarred her.
She didn't think my joke was so funny.
- And then, you know, finally
one day I was just fed up
with the whole thing so when he asked me
what was the right way to kiss someone
I said, "One boy that
you're in love with."
- And, she didn't want
to date me after that.
- And, then when he told that to my mother
she almost collapsed from
the release of tension
she was so relieved.
(laughs)
- And, all those people
that were laughing so hard
were friends with her
longer than me, you know,
so they all kinda gave me the boot.
- Yeah, she took me home and no aspect
of any of it was ever
mentioned by my family again.
- And, the only reason I
did it in the first place
is 'cause I wanted them to like me.
- [Bernard] I dunno if
I woulda told that story
on a first date.
- So, were you out with that
Angela chick last night?
- No, man no actually I wasn't.
After the first date, you
know, she started to get
all weird on me so...
- [Victor] Yeah, she wanted
to have sex with you.
That's just bizarre.
- I don't know, I mean
I really dig her, man.
Honestly, I think she's really
cool, but I just don't know.
Something, you know.
- So, who were you out with then?
- Just his girl I seriously
doubt I'll ever see her again.
- Why not?
- I don't know, so we go
back to her house, thanks,
after the first date
and, you know, I'm about
to like go down on her.
- [Leroy] Wait, you
thought it was too soon
to sleep with Angela after
two dates, but this other girl
you'll nail after one date?
- [Mason] Yeah, but the
other girl was a slut.
you can do whatever you
want with a chick like that.
It doesn't matter.
- And, there's just something
there that, I don't know,
kinda stopped me, I
couldn't go through with it.
- Okay, what was so off that
it stopped you from hitting it?
- Well, first off it was shaved.
- So, you never boffed a baldie before?
Come on, man.
- It was shaved so you
could see the tattoo.
- Oh, a tattoo.
- Yeah.
- Okay, what was it a picture of?
- Nothing, nothing.
- I mean man, it had to be something.
- Just two words, that was it.
- [VIctor] Okay, what did it say?
- Joe's box.
- Joe's box?
- Simple block letters,
you know J-O-E apostrophe S
next line box, B-O-X.
Joe's box, Joe's box.
- Who the fuck's Joe?
- I dunno, do you know him 'cause I don't.
- What I'm saying is like
why the hell is his name
tattooed on her...
- Well, it was probably
from an ex-boyfriend.
- Why would she get
her ex-boyfriend's name
tattooed on her pussy?
- Because they were probably
going out at the time.
- Right.
- Yeah, so after that,
you know, it just kinda
killed the moment for me.
- Man, what's wrong with you?
Okay, a hottie's going to
let you get all up inside her
you can't let a little
thing like a tattoo claim
vaginal ownership, stop it.
You gotta get it up, stick it in, work it
and fucking own it, man.
- I can't own it, Vic.
- Why not?
- Because
it's Joe's box.
- Man, the Mason I know and love
would have hit that and
made her call him Joe.
All right, what's with you man?
- Nothing.
- [Victor] That's bullshit
man, I didn't keep calling
Crystal, I called her like once.
- [Mason] Please, dude, you
called her like four times
just while we were at the bar.
- [Victor] Oh Jesus, that's amazing.
You know what, you're
like stoned and retarded
at the same time.
- [Mason] No, you just
didn't want to admit
you were lodged entirely up
her ass and couldn't crawl out.
- [Victor] Oh, okay, okay, yup that's it.
(smack)
- [Mason] Ow, fucking
- [Victor] Oh, I'm gonna
bitch slap you 'till you
fucking cry.
(smack)
- [Mason] Stop it.
- [Victor] Ouch.
(smack)
- [Mason] Fuck you.
(smacks)
- [Leroy] Hey, watch it.
(liquid pouring)
Okay, you two pansies
own me another drink.
- [Bernard] This better not stain.
- God, you see it went straight
to her voicemail, again.
- So, leave a message.
- Does she think she can play a player?
- Maybe she just--
- I mean she liked me, I know she did.
I mean, don't you think she liked me?
- Vic, I just met her that one time.
- I mean if she liked
me why would she go out
with another guy, it just
doesn't make sense, man.
- Oh dude, just because her
cellphone's turned off--
- Does she think I'm stupid? Huh?
I fucking invented that trick, bitch.
- Well, rockabilly.
Some folk music, Cat Stevens and such.
Oh, I love that old sixties Jamaican Ska.
- Oh cool, that's cool.
- I don't know I like just
about any type of music.
Well, except for country.
- Well, yeah of course.
- [Bernard] Seriously, I'd
like to know what's wrong
with country.
- Well, here we are back where we started.
- Yep.
- [Victor] Yes!
- I got no idea what to do next.
- What would you like to do?
- Come upstairs with you.
- [Mason] Oh, that's it you just blew it.
- [Victor] Oh no man, okay
she gave him an opening,
all right he had to try and get in there.
No hey, you made the right call, buddy.
But, next time say it like a man.
- Nice try big guy, I
gave you a date that's all
you're gonna get until you
break up with your fiance.
- I'm not engaged.
- Whatever, you're involved.
- [Victor] Yeah, this is where
you whip out your cell phone
and start dialing.
"Hey Denise, listen so
I met a hot redhead.
"Yeah, uh-huh we're done, okay."
Come on man, things like
this are the whole reason
they invented cell phones
in the first place.
- I just want to show you
something I've been working on.
- Working on?
- Yeah, I'm creating a
new style of architecture.
- [Victor] Oh Christ, you are killing me.
- [Mason] It's better
than comic books, right?
- [Victor] I guess.
- You're kidding.
- Uh-uh, and I brought my
blueprints, they're in my car.
And, I've never showed
them to anyone before.
- [Mason] Wait, you brought blueprints?
- You brought blueprints?
- Yeah.
(laughs)
'Cause, I knew we'd click, I knew it.
And, I knew when we did I'd
want to show 'em to you, so...
I don't know, you're artistic so I think
you'll understand it.
- Okay.
- Yeah?
- [Lily] Yeah.
- Okay cool, you hang
on I'm gonna go get 'em.
- Okay.
- [Leroy] Okay, excellent.
- [Leroy] Oh well looky there
guys, she's wants to see
my blueprints.
- [Victor] Wow, then I take
it all back, you're comic book
and blueprints panty
removal scheme is brilliant.
- [Mason] You had it planned
like that from the beginning,
didn't you buddy?
- [Bernard] I guess we all
failed to see the subtle workings
of an evil genius.
- [Leroy] Shut up you dickheads.
- Okay, so my original concept
was to create a new style
of architecture that would be geometric
bordering on organic.
Okay, for which I was using
early Distill paintings
as inspiration.
- Okay.
- Cool, okay so but everything
I was coming up with
was looking a lot like
Gehry's Guggenheim in Bilbao,
which is super cool but it
wouldn't be my own style.
So, I started thinking--
- Wait, wait I'm sorry
are you saying that you're
trying to create a new
style of architecture?
- Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
- Oh, I thought you meant that you were
experimenting.
You know, following a train of thought
and you stumbled across something unique.
- What does it matter?
- Well, it matters
because doing like this is
well, it's artificial.
- [Bernard] Oh shit, I
know what happens next.
- [Victor] Okay, you're
in her apartment man,
you're about to seal the deal.
All right, keep your eyes on the prize.
- Huh, you know what
I don't wanna show you
my blueprints anymore.
- [Mason] Oh shit, I knew it.
Couldn't stop yourself could you?
- [Bernard] Mister hypersensitive,
just like eighth grade.
- Oh, no, no, no don't be like that.
- No, you're saying my architecture's bad,
you haven't even seen it.
- No, I'm not saying your work is bad.
I'm stating an intellectual
opinion about your theory.
Look, maybe I'll like the designs.
- No, you may not see my blueprints.
I can't even believe i
thought you were open minded
enough to understand it.
- All right, yeah you know what fine.
Why don't you show them
to your girlfriend?
I'm sure she'll tell you
they're the greatest thing
she's ever seen.
- Yeah, I'm gonna.
- Well do that.
- Great, I bet she's gonna love 'em.
(clatter and thud)
- [Bernard] You're kind
of a baby, aren't you?
- [Leroy] Yeah, pretty
much, yes. Yes, I am.
- [Bernard] Wait, you didn't
break up with Denise, did you?
- [Leroy] You know, I walked home thinking
"I got it good with Denise.
"I'm going back to her where I was happy."
- [Bernard] But, you weren't happy.
- [Leroy] Nope.
- [Bernard] So, you broke up with her.
- [Leroy] Yep.
- [Bernard] How'd she take it?
- For the last two years,
two months, and 11 days
I've done everything for
you and yeah, you know what,
that includes counting the
days we've been together.
Because, that's how much this
relationship means to me.
I've hung out with your stupid,
asshole fucking friends.
I've watched football with you on Sunday,
and I even pretended to
give a shit every time
you got an autograph from
some bald comic book writer
in Cleveland.
I mean, I listen to
you go on and on and on
about your creative vision
and I even let you do
whatever you want in bed,
even when it got weird.
I mean, sticking your finger in my ass?
What was that about?
You know what?
You couldn't appreciate me,
fine, fine, just get out.
Just get out, all right.
I mean really, here take your jacket,
your guitar.
Don't forget your picture
of your asshole friends
in Vegas, take that, your
Frank Lloyd Wright book.
- Okay easy, okay, all right, all right.
Are you gonna be--
(door slams)
You know, by the way it was your sister
who told me to stick
my finger in your ass.
Evening, Ross. Lovely day.
- [Victor] So, hey could
you hook me up with
Denise's sister?
- Sorry, we're closing.
- Hi.
- What were you freaking out about?
- [Victor] I can't wait to hear this.
- [Mason] Well, shut the
fuck up and listen then.
- I don't know.
I mean honestly, maybe I was just scared
of ruining things by
moving too fast, you know?
- And, you thought by
humiliating me it was a good way
to avoid ruining things?
- I never said I was that smart, so.
(laughs)
- You're not gay, are you?
- [Victor] Yes!
- Well,
You know the Too Skinny
Jeds are coming to town,
you wanna go?
- Is that a band?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah they
mix up a bunch of sounds,
rap most of their lyrics.
It's kinda like this kickass blend of--
- Why should I go on
another date with you?
- Because I'm crazy about you.
- [Leroy] Good answer.
- I mean, how many
times are you gonna find
a 102 date connection
after just two dates?
- It is gonna be like 102
dates before you get laid.
- Oh, I think I'm okay with that.
- [Victor] Hey listen,
don't worry about it.
All right, you know what
I prefer men anyway.
- Yeah, okay I'll go.
- [Mason] Yeah?
- You don't have to sell me,
I'll go see any live show.
- All right, awesome.
- Well, except country.
- Right, I understand that
'cause country blows, you know.
- [Bernard] I like country music.
- Victor, move those pallets over there.
- Got it, Mister Gallagher.
- Psst.
- Yeah.
- Wow, yeah
that's all I get is yeah?
- Hey, what do you want me to say?
- Why don't you just say what's what?
I mean why don't you just
say now that I've slept
with you a couple of times
you're blowing me off.
- Okay, isn't that what
you should be saying to me?
- Why?
Because I'm sitting at home like an idiot
all weekend waiting for you to call me,
that's me blowing you off, right?
- Right, okay just how
stupid do you think I am?
You think I don't know you
were out with another guy?
Please.
- What?
Who told you that?
- Nobody had to tell me that.
I mean, I called your cell
phone what a dozen times
this weekend and each time
I called it went straight
to your voicemail which means
you turned off your phone.
- [Bernard] Yikes, you're paranoid.
- [Victor] Hey, look.
- [Leroy] Yeah mean, if
you're gonna get all neurotic
like that you should
learn to hide it better.
- [Victor] Fuck you, Leroy,
you're like the fucking king
of neurotic.
- [Leroy] I know man, I'm
delivering wisdom to you
from a place of experience.
- [Victor] Wait, wait, wait
this totally wasn't my fault
all right, just shut up and listen.
- No I didn't. I didn't turn
off my phone once all weekend.
Not even when I was sleeping.
- Bullshit, okay so why
didn't you pick up my calls?
- You never called.
- [Victor] I never called?
- Yeah, you never called me.
- I actually think you're
the last person here.
Your voicemail.
- Oh shit.
I don't know what happened,
my phone must be broken.
- [Victor] See, there
you go. Not my fault.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- Okay, so you weren't out with anybody?
- Okay, you know what you
can apologize to me too.
- For what?
- For accusing me of cheating on you.
I don't think I've done
anything to deserve that.
- Hey, you're right, you're right.
I'm sorry, hey, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I did not mean
for this whole, fuck it.
Can we just forget this whole
stupid phone thing happened?
Please, I'm sorry I'm an idiot.
You're adorable.
(kiss)
Yeah.
- Look at that.
You just got through our first big fight.
- Oh, yes.
- You know this relationship
is showing a lot of promise.
- So, because of that do
you think maybe I could
stick it in your bum now?
- [Crystal] Shh, shh, shh.
- I mean, not now, you know, eventually.
(laughs)
- Now that we're getting
so close to one another,
- Yes, yes.
- there's not a fucking
chance of that happening.
(sentimental music)
(phone tones)
- [Lily] Hello?
- Lilly, hi it's Leroy.
- Leroy, I'm not gonna let you--
- I broke up with her.
I spent the day looking for apartments
and I just put down a
first month's rent on one.
(buzzer)
- Well, now that's different.
- Will you just forgive
me for that tantrum?
- [Mason] Tell her if she
says yes you'll take her
to her to a comic book convention.
That should close the deal.
- It depends on how
expensive dinner is tonight.
(laughs)
- I got plans to make.
I'll pick you up at seven.
- You got it.
- Awesome.
(giggles)
(kisses)
- I'm going.
- [Lily] Okay, go.
(mumbles and giggles)
("All My Life" by DJ Harry)
♫I got fabric from my mother
♫And, I got fabric from my friend
♫I got fabric from my lover
♫It will take it to the end
♫I got fabric from my mother
♫And, I got fabric from my friend
♫I got fabric from my lover
♫It will take it to the end
♫If it's down there in my soul
♫Doubts they wander, push, and pull
♫I am waiting for the role
♫If it's down there in my soul
♫It's just right
♫Take flight
♫Might be waiting all my life
♫All my life
- [Bernard] I know, I
know a musical montage.
It's pretty cliche but
this is romantic comedy
so what are you gonna do?
What you need to know
is everybody's happy,
everbody's going on dates,
everybody's falling in love.
I'm between girlfriend's right now.
Look boys, and they all
lived happily ever after.
- [Mason] Once upon a...
- [Victor] Oh.
I doubt that.
- Why not?
- Oh, so what do you think?
- You know, I don't know.
I don't really know much about art, so.
- I don't either.
- But, it's cool how he
tends to use one color
that kind of pops out.
- [Crystal] Jonathan.
- Hey Crystal.
- [Victor] Oh this fucking
guy, okay Jesus, what a tool.
He was fucking all over Crystal.
- What are you up too?
- Nothing really, just stopped
by because someone said
they had free booze here, so.
- Hey, Victor.
Crystal's boyfriend.
- [Crystal] I'm so sorry.
Victor, this is Jonathan.
He and I we went to school together.
- Good to meet you Victor.
- Oh yeah.
- You know what, Victor's
friend Leroy he's here.
He's an architect too,
you guys should talk.
- Definitely.
- Hey, do you wanna get a drink?
- Yeah, can you grab
me a glass of red wine?
Thank you.
- [Victor] I mean, you
see how she's trying
to blow me off here, huh?
Yeah, could it be more
obvious she totally wanted
to just bang this guy?
- You saw (mumbles) okay?
- I mean, what do you think of this one?
- I don't know I'm not
able to think of anything
other than getting you back in bed.
- [Leroy] Hey, what'd she say?
- [Mason] I don't know, it was in Korean.
- [Leroy] Oh, come on you gotta tell us.
- [Victor] No, no she said, "I
wanna fuck your friend Victor
"'cause unlike you he's a
real man who likes boobies."
- [Mason] She said all
my friends are gossipy
sewing circle bitches, okay?
Can we move the fuck on already?
- Why don't we just catch
up with our friends first,
that might be an idea.
- Sorry, I thought the constant sex phase
of the relationship was supposed
to last more than two days.
- I just don't understand
what's wrong with it.
- Nothing.
- Then, why don't you like it?
- I think that you should
wear whatever you want
and not be so worried that I
absolutely adore your shirt.
- Well, it's your opening,
so I thought you'd want
your boyfriend to look nice for it.
I'm just trying to make you happy.
- [Mason] Holy shit, did
you go from the butch
to the bitch in like two seconds flat.
- You know what, fuck it
if I'm bringing her wine.
- Hey, hey, hey I'm in heels here.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- You know what, you've been
acting like an ass all night.
Maybe you need some alone time.
- Oh, really?
And, where are you going?
- Jane and Rashida said
they were going to Luna,
I think I'm going to meet up with them.
- Yeah, sure you are.
- You can call me tomorrow.
- You wanna play like that.
Okay, okay.
- Do you wanna go to Luna?
- I don't think so.
- Why do you wanna go there so badly?
I like this place.
- Yeah, and tomorrow they'd
find me dead in a ditch.
- Are you retarded?
- How big is your cock?
- I don't know you.
- I don't wanna know you.
- Do I look stupid?
- Go to hell.
- Suck my dick.
- What?
- Do you wanna go to Luna?
- Drive dollar big price car?
- Huh?
- American drive dollar big price car.
- What, oh yes, yeah some American's do.
I drive a Ford, no but you
know, that's just until
my Ferrari comes in, obviously.
- Ferrari?
- Yeah, I actually just
inherited the biggest fruit
and produce distributer in the Mid-west.
So, I figured, hey why not splurge.
- Inherit?
- Yeah.
- Buy Zivanka drink hunky hunk.
- Huh?
Yes, yes how 'bout I get you a drink
over at Luna?
That place is so much
better than here, let's go.
Yes?
- Must buy drink first, then marriage.
- What?
Okay, yes drink okay, other bar.
Drink, at the other bar yes?
Yes? Yes? Yes?
Yes.
- What's the matter?
- Could you, do you think maybe
we could just, or you could take a shower.
- Oh, you wanna take a
shower, okay I'm game.
- No, no, no I was
thinking like, you know,
you could take a shower.
Like, to get clean.
- I took a shower before we left.
- Yeah, but...
- I'm not clean now?
- Look Leroy, you're not the
only one in this relationship.
- Oh really, gee I didn't notice.
- You know what? Sometimes I wonder.
- You know, with all the shit you give me
I wonder why I'm in this relationship.
- Whoa wait, all the shit I give you?
- Yeah.
- On extremely rare
occasion I ask you really,
really nicely to think
about me from time to time.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah, you know what, I say,
"Hey, Leroy since you worked
"70 hours last week and
I didn't get to see you
"maybe we could go out for dinner
"instead of playing video
games all fucking night."
- Okay, wait a minute.
I have to work to advance in my--
- I never argued that.
- Do you realize how little
- [Lily] I never asked you
to work less hours.
- [Leroy] money lower
architects make, and then at
the end of a long work day
I wanna come home and relax.
- Well, having a drink
with me at a restaurant
should be relaxing.
- You know what, you don't
get it, you have no idea.
You've never worked to have to advance
in anything in your life.
You just go around being all
good at everything you do.
And now, you make me feel
guilty because I have to work.
No, just you know what,
this isn't working.
This isn't working, this
relationship is not what I
wanted it to be.
It just feels so fucked
up about it all the time.
(sentimental music)
I'm sorry.
- I know, shh.
(sentimental music)
- [Bernard] So that's it?
- [Leroy] Yep, that's it.
- [Bernard] I don't get it.
- [Leroy] I don't know man,
I just really like her.
And, I realized it was all worth it.
- [Bernard] Leroy, welcome to manhood.
- [Mason] Yeah, I got a question.
- [Bernard] You know actually,
I'm getting a little misty.
- [Mason] What's wrong
with playing video games
all fucking night?
(dance music)
- Buy Zivanka diamonds now?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah why don't we just start
with some drinks first, okay.
- All right, I'll be back in
a sec. Can you watch this?
- You're a doll.
- Victor.
- Oh, hey Crystal wow, I
totally forgot you were
gonna be here tonight.
What a coincidence.
- No bang, bang honeymoon till diamond.
- Yes.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- I'm grabbing a drink, same as you.
- Three carat.
- Three carats.
- Who is this girl?
- She's
- Mister hunky inherit dollar.
- Okay, okay.
Hey, why don't you go
get us some drinks, okay?
Thank you.
God, she's so cool, you know.
And, such a sweetheart,
I just love hanging out
with her, you know?
- [Zivanka] Not platinum card?
- Hey, it's a blue card
that's higher than platinum.
- What are you doing?
- What?
- What are you doing with her?
- Oh, oh come on we both know
we're seeing other people.
- Oh, we do?
- Well yeah, I mean, you
know, it was fun playing
the whole, "I love you" game,
but come on it gets old after a while.
- Why are you trying to be an asshole?
- I'm not, I'm just being me.
- Okay, by showing up to a
place you know I'm going to
be at with some bimbo
you just met tonight?
- Hey, hey I didn't just
meet her tonight, okay.
Honey, whenever I'm not with
you I'm drilling that girl
like a piece of, you
know, flat metal that I'm
drill a rivet--
- Stop, stop.
- I do.
- This is all the respect you have for me?
- Yeah.
(thud and grunt)
- [Bernard] And, that
was the end of Crystal?
- [Victor] Yeah, that's what
I get for falling for a girl
like that, a punch in the nose.
- [Bernard] You didn't try
to apologize or anything?
- [Victor] Apologize?
Okay, she was probably off
banging that guy from college.
Okay, why should I apologize to her?
- [Leroy] Okay wait, wait
a minute she actually
took a shower?
- [Mason] Yeah.
- [Victor] And, you didn't
get in there with her.
- Hey Angela, have you ever been tested?
- [Angela] Tested?
- Yeah, you know what I mean.
- [Angela] Never thought
I had a reason to.
- What do you mean? Everybody needs to.
- [Angela] I've only been with one guy,
and he was a virgin too.
- Yeah, he also could have been a liar.
- I really don't think--
- He could have been with
like a hundred women.
You could have all sorts
of like funk and viruses
and mitochondria and--
- What are you talking about?
- [Leroy] Yeah, what
are you talking about?
- [Mason] I don't know.
I was just trying to...
I don't know.
- [Bernard] You know,
mitochondria don't carry
diseases, per se.
And anyway, they're not contagious.
- I knew the guy for like--
- Yeah, and then wait then
there were the other guys.
I mean, how many were there?
- I told you that he was the only--
- Yeah, he's the only guy you
had sexual intercourse with.
That means you did other
stuff with other guys.
- Yeah, some fooling around, but not much.
- I'm sorry, I can't
have sex with you tonight
without a condom.
- You didn't think you needed a condom
the first time we slept together.
- Oh fuck.
- What?
- I have to go to a clinic right now.
- [Leroy] What?
- What?
What the hell is wrong with you?
- [Bernard] No seriously, what
the hell is wrong with you?
- It's just a bad idea,
I mean this whole thing
is just a bad idea.
- This whole thing, like sleeping with me
or even going out with
me in the first place?
You know what? This was a
bad idea, you should go.
- Okay.
- [Leroy] Wow, I...man I
don't even know what to say.
I thought I had issues, but
man you have serious issues.
- [Mason] Yeah, I'm starting to think so.
- [Leroy] Man, you need serious help.
I'm not just saying that,
like you really do need help.
- [Victor] Okay look, if
you're turning gay you can't
be in the bathroom shaving
when I'm in the shower anymore.
- [Bernard] So, did you
actually go to a clinic?
- Of course not.
- Did you get back together with Angela?
- Yeah, I called and
left a message, you know?
More than once, but she
never called me back, so.
- [Bernard] So, that's it.
Leroy figured it out and got the girl.
Victor didn't figure it
out and lost the girl.
Mason is finally starting
to clue in, so maybe
there's hope for him yet.
I know, I know there's no deep
lessons to be learned here,
just three guys, well four
guys, trying to figure out
their own shit.
What else do you want, iambic pentameter
and literary allusions
to the Canterbury tales?
- [Voiceover] Bar's
closed, get the fuck out.
- Oh, oh.
- All right, fellas.
- Let's go, dudes.
- Wait, well I mean, hey.
The bars are still open on the east side.
- No man, I'm going over to Lily's.
- Dude, I gotta give a final tomorrow.
- You'll come with me
Mason, right come on.
- Yeah, guess what, I'm
not really in the mood.
- No, I'm gonna go hit on the
bartender over at Emerald.
- Oh, is she cute, is she cute?
- Yeah, she's really
cute I'm gonna click her
like a ball point pen, let's do this.
- [Bernard] What the
hell does that even mean?
- Don't, 'cause it always
means the same thing.
♫Doctor please
♫Bring me anesthesia
♫Three more of these
♫I won't have to eat
♫I'll say goodnight
♫Shut your mouth
♫Try to keep your composure
♫Play along
♫Just like no one knows
♫Just say goodnight
♫Got so much time these days
♫Like I've got nothing else
♫With all my time these days
♫I just keep to myself
♫So much fun
♫I can't seem to deny me
♫Christmas time
♫It's the Fourth of July
♫Please say goodnight
♫Goodnight
(Board claps)
- Mark.
(gum snapping)
- So, hey, you know, do
you wanna go to maybe
the Pepper Lounge with me?
- Do you know Lydia's philosophy?
- What's that?
- I don't go no where 'till I'm paid for.
(laughs)
- [Voiceover] Okay, cut.