- Sorry to keep you waiting.
Traffic.
- Yeah, big game.
Milbrae is jammed.
- I've been here for,
it's been almost an hour.
- Yes, I'm sorry.
The broker will be here any minute.
It's all fine.
- I was here alone, what if...
- She said we'll be fine.
- Let's just calm down.
We're here now.
George, just sit okay?
- I don't know if I can
go through with this.
- What?
- Of course you can go through with this.
Of course, that's why we're all here.
Why you waited.
- It's just, what if something happens?
- It's gonna be fine.
Isn't that right?
- Right.
- You both have the money?
- Of course.
- We need to do this now, Bob.
If you want out.
- He doesn't want out,
do you Bob?
- He's coming Bob.
Let me have it.
It's all here, 25,000?
I'll be right back.
Gentlemen, this is Imran.
- Sorry to keep you.
Can I perhaps have a drink?
- The place is closed, it's just us.
- Is everything in order?
- You have the stones?
- Of course.
- I'm curious.
How can you offer to
sell these for such a...
- Low price?
Again.
- I did explain.
- I'd like to hear that again.
- Weight, quality, these are
fine stones, uncut stones.
Good quality.
My family has a license
to carry these stones.
The license describes the weight,
not quality, not quantity.
But who can judge quality
unless they're an expert?
So I fly once a month.
I come here with my stones
and I leave with my stones.
Same weight, but better quality.
You see?
- So they're, I don't...
- I get it.
You bring these here,
and you sell them to us,
and then you fly back with
what, different diamonds?
- Better.
- Better than these?
- Bigger.
But these are you understand, fine stones.
For this price.
- They're good.
I'm satisfied.
- But this isn't,
it's not legal?
- Bob, we talked, you told me.
- It's just,
I'll be right back.
- You assured me you had good buyers.
You assured me.
- Everything is fine.
Mister Walker simply,
he just needs a moment.
- I'll check on him.
He's always like this.
You all right there?
- I'm sorry, I just...
- It's fine, just take a moment.
- I can barely say.
- Yeah well, we're almost done.
You got our money, right?
- Right?
I'm sorry, it's such a big risk.
You know I just met him last week.
- Yeah, me too.
It's almost over, so why don't we.
Shut it.
Ah Christ.
- What's going on there?
- The police, fucking hell.
- The money!
- We need to get out of here.
- She's gone off with it.
She's got my money.
- Forget the fucking money,
the police are coming back here.
- It's still there, the
money's still there?
- The police are coming back.
- I can make it.
- It's not worth it.
- If something happens
of course I can make it.
I can get all into this.
- Stop right there, don't move.
- God, sorry I...
Turn round, I'm not
gonna tell you again sir.
Who do you think you're kidding pal?
You're under arrest.
You're not obliged to say...
I must caution you, you're
not obliged to say anything.
Anything you do say, will be noted down,
and used against you.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
- He's in a taxi.
- You think he knows any
fucking thing we're doing?
- English prick.
- Cara?
- The big called.
He's got another sucker
if you're interested.
- Maybe.
They didn't just sweeten the deal though,
you know front and back,
like we talked about.
- I'll see what they say.
Also, I just got a call
from Frank over at Bimmer's.
Some kid is asking for you.
- Kid?
- Says Joe sent him.
- My Joe?
- Yours.
- He's there now?
- Uh huh.
Said he needs to tell you something.
Wouldn't say what.
You heard anything from Joe?
- Not for a while.
This kid, he's Irish?
- Don't know, I can ask.
I'd assume.
You know him?
- Bring him over.
- To the house?
You're sure?
- Call when you're close.
Sure?
How's the old man?
You and I, we met at a dog track.
Because we had a mark, a Jamaican guy.
- Yeah, really drunk.
- I'd been feeding him vodka all day.
And Joe played inside
man, took him off for me.
- Yeah.
- Shame the prick came up empty.
- Joe was pissed.
- He was.
Haven't heard from his since.
Till now.
- I'm sorry.
- It's Joe that sent you?
- I didn't know where else to go.
I found him,
a few days ago.
Someone killed Joe.
- Who?
- The place was a mess.
- His place, he's still there?
- Yeah, I legged it out as, I'm sorry.
- He's still there?
Any idea who?
- We hadn't did anything
for weeks, a dry spell.
- A dry spell?
- Oh, who's this?
- Ian?
- Rob, long fucking time.
- Where are you?
- Are you in London?
- No I'm up home, in Glasgow.
- Wait, this is a bad time.
- I need a favor.
- What is that?
- I need you to check on Joe for me.
- What happened?
- I'm not sure, I need eyes over there.
And, he doesn't use a phone.
- He doesn't use a phone,
tell me did he catch one?
Have you tried the kid?
He's been running around
with this little Irish prick for months.
Fucking some wired little shit.
- He's right here.
He can hear you.
- It'll take me half an hour to get there.
- Take a cab.
It'll be faster.
Well, I've got some time.
Come on.
Close the door.
- You made that?
- Yes.
- Really is the country life.
- It's quiet.
Peaceful.
I rent a place in town.
A speakeasy with a car
house like.
- How long?
- Soon.
So,
a wire scam?
- What?
- You into something about a wire.
- Yeah, we used that
backroom in Chaplin Street.
- I know the place, why is that shuttered?
- No, it was a phone thing.
I found this kid could
text the race results
before anyone else got them, apparently.
And the marks would give
Joe money to make the bets.
- But he didn't?
Make the bets?
- He played the stall.
If the horse won he'd say
he couldn't get the bet down in time,
and give back the money.
- You lost me.
- You know Joe, like he
knows that inside track
and won a few races,
so all I had to do was
predict first or second place.
And this kid, the one with the text.
He would text those to the suckers,
but he'd flip 'em, right?
So say,
Folding Money come second
to Bagatelle, 2:15 Kempton.
Like that, like he makes
it really confusing.
- Okay, then what?
- So of course they check the text,
and then in comes Joe and they
send him to make the bets,
like big bets.
- Yes.
- More than half the time, Joe
was riding the money, right?
But the text we originally sent,
was flipped to make the
marks bet on the loser.
So the way we worded it,
the way the kid worded it,
was to make them bet on the horse
most likely to come fucking second.
- So they'd lose.
- Damn fucking right they'd lose.
Of course, Joe never pays the bets.
We kept all the money.
- The marks don't beef
when they see the result?
- Oh yeah, oh yeah, go crazy.
Like yell, and threaten me and stuff,
but that's until they check the texts.
See the text is the best part,
like the text is the scam.
Because this kid, is like genius.
He could hack these phones, send a text,
then later go in there delete
that text and replace it.
You know what I mean?
- The first tells them
to bet on Folding Money.
- The second tells them
Bagatelle come first.
The second goes to
Folding Money out of that.
- And Joe came up with this?
- No, with the scam sure but.
- How much did he take?
- A lot.
You know we had the system.
But he OD'ed a few weeks
ago and it all dried up.
- You think?
- Ah, no, no no no, he was our clover,
just a hacker.
And the suckers were all cooled out,
that was the beauty of it.
Joe had something else
going, something big.
- I'm sure he did.
No idea at all?
The something else?
Inside.
- He's still out.
No he's a funny old man.
The place is dark, Rob.
- Can you get in?
- Oh fucking hell,
okay give me a minute.
- He's uh...
- Don't speak.
Not one fucking word.
- I'm in.
Joe?
Sure I can smell him.
- Keep going and tell me what you can see.
- Fucking hell the place is a mess.
I see him.
He's, shit somebody's
beaten the shit out of him.
- Can you send a picture?
- What? Fuck off, I'm in a fucking game.
- Ian, send a picture.
- Okay okay, this is
our square now, right?
- Not even close.
- Right?
- Get out of there,
lock the place back up.
- Do you want me to call anyone?
- No leave as is, just walk away.
Did you get out?
- We done?
- No.
- Fucking kill all.
Why are you here?
- Joe, he told me.
He said you were the best grifter up here.
- Okay, and so?
- He turned you out before me.
- Answer the fucking question.
What the fuck do you want?
- Joe...
- Joe's dead.
- Yeah, but.
- So what the fuck are you doing here?
- He had a score.
A big one.
- Answer the fucking question.
- He had a score, a big one.
- And your fucking luck.
So what the fuck are you doing, here?
- He told me I could, that you, that...
- Now look at the fucking picture.
And Joe is dead.
Was that you?
Was that fucking you?
- It wasn't me, it wasn't me.
- Yeah.
Let's get our drink.
Now you sit on the marks for him,
learn the markets, take bets.
When Joe was the only one
pulling the old school scams,
Pitch and draw,
Jamaican switch,
we used to play the ring
game in bars, Essex.
- First thing he showed me
was how to attract brag.
It was pub games mostly, but,
it was good money.
- Yeah, for me it was gin.
He taught me how to pick
two and ghost a card.
Ever see that?
Just one extra card is
enough to beat most chumps.
But you've got to get at
the right card, right?
Now the dumb play is to palm it back
onto the deck of a stump,
because smart players,
they watch like hawks
and they mind all the
fucking cards, right?
But Joe had a way to clean up,
without palming anything.
Like, nothing to see.
A thing of beauty.
Tell me about the score.
What was he sitting on?
I think you wouldn't be here
if you didn't need my help.
- It's big.
- Right.
How big?
- Like half a rock,
maybe more, all scratch.
- Where are you staying?
- In the hotel, by the river.
- Hey Maggie.
Can you send a cab over?
Good.
Bill me.
I knew you'd be faint.
Well, thanks for letting me know.
Hope you get something going.
- It's not bullshit.
- Listen Tom, Joe never
made more than 20 grand
in a single week.
If he's told you he's
got a score that big,
he's blowing smoke up your ass, I promise.
- It's a card game.
Right, it's big money,
serious fucking money
up here in Glasgow.
Joe's been holding onto this for a while.
He needed the money, a lot of money,
to get into the game.
- There's only one game laid out up here.
There's only one, and there's no way in.
I should know.
- Joe had it, Joe had the in.
- Let's see,
sure this is real?
You called?
- No.
But you know who it is?
- If this number is real,
this is a fucking jackpot.
I'll need to check this.
You up for some luck?
Put some cash in your pocket?
- What's the gig?
- Well maybe you can learn something.
A beard said you had to
tell tomorrow at noon.
If I'm not there by 12:15, I'm not coming.
- Okay.
- How's it going?
- What's in the bag?
- Nothing.
- What's in it?
Your number's good.
That's a solid in.
Tell me something,
why do you think didn't
say anything to me?
- I don't know.
- I've been waiting for that
number for two fucking years.
I just don't understand.
- I don't know.
- How come?
Tell me a trick.
Can you keep your mouth shut?
Do what you're told?
Let's find out.
Mister Olin?
- Yes.
- I understood we would meet alone.
- These are my sons,
I'm afraid they insisted.
They treat me like an old man.
You are Mister Will?
- And this is my associate, Danny.
I'm afraid we only have a
little time before our flight.
You have the money?
- Yes, yes of course.
But I'm very sorry,
but you understand I must
be extremely careful.
- You spoke with Karl in Amsterdam, yes?
- Yes.
- And he explained to you how this works?
- Yes, you have chains, 24 karat,
and I may buy them at a fair price.
- Very fair.
- They are all of this quality.
- I don't have much time Mister Olin.
I'm sorry to say I don't have
a great deal of patience, either.
If you've spoken to Karl
you should already know
what you're buying.
- I do, I do.
Now, if I might test one
or two more, to be sure.
- Are you deliberately trying
to upset me Mister Olin?
And what time is your
flight back to London?
- I will not risk taking so
much gold through an airport.
We have a train.
- Well I do have a flight,
in just over an hour.
And I don't have time for you
to scratch every chain in this case.
- I only want to test a couple.
But random.
You understand, this is
a great deal of money.
- This is your first
transaction with us, correct?
You were made aware of why
we're selling these so,
reasonably?
- Please, please, do not be offended.
But I could not in all good conscience.
- The hell with it.
I think you wasted a journey,
and a good deal of my time.
- All I am asking
is to allow a simple caution on my part.
Please, Mister Will I mean no insult.
- In 20 minutes, no more.
- It'll only take a few moments.
- Not here, not in the open.
- Then where?
- Your room, I'll meet you upstairs.
Danny, Danny will stay with you.
- Perhaps we can save
some time, if I could?
I promise not to put any in my pocket.
It's fine, it's fine.
We will wait.
Martin.
You have it?
Do not take your eyes off those chains.
I told you, if they try something,
shoot him in the leg.
The other one too, you have a silencer.
- No.
I just bought these at the bus station.
- I thought they come with silencer.
- No, Papa.
- Come in.
- All set?
You have the money?
- Of course.
- Wait.
Mister Olin I came a long way,
and I'd hate to think I wasted my time.
- I don't understand.
- Karl explained to you that
this is a regular shipment,
that we do this several times each year.
- Yes.
- And Karl has done a
lot of business with me.
- So he says.
- He's a rich man.
- He seems so.
- And you trust this man, Karl?
- I do not distrust him.
- Now why don't we start again?
Do this properly.
In this case, I have 21.3
pounds of 24 karat gold,
and a very large sum of money.
And that bag which my
associate is holding,
you say is 100,000 pounds cash?
- Count it.
- I could, some say I should.
But this is not a
typical deal Mister Olin.
This is, as they say, under the table.
- Naturally.
- Then let's keep it that way.
Now you have the money,
which we would have accepted downstairs,
without checking or counting.
I have the chains which you
agreed to accept in good faith.
Now we're here in this room.
Now we can count your money,
you can test the chains,
as you wish.
- Yes, that's why...
- But what I'm saying is, don't.
You take the chains, we take the cash,
no checking, no counting, as agreed.
- Why would I do that?
- Business.
I'm not interested in selling
one case to you, but 100.
Over time you will make a staggering,
life-changing amount of
money from this deal.
But if you want to look at my stuff,
this is the only case for you.
You will double your money, once,
and that's it.
- You're right of course.
I'm very sorry.
But I must check the chains.
- Count the money.
- These are good.
- You're certain?
- All there?
- Checks out.
- Mister Olin, enjoy your gold.
And should we meet again,
do me the courtesy of
leaving these at home.
- What the hell just happened?
- We made a deal.
- But I don't understand, who got conned?
That case was full of chains, gold chains.
- Right.
- Like solid gold.
- Solid gold.
- They're real?
You're not gonna switch 'em?
- What for?
They'll all check out.
They can test 'em all
the way back to London.
- You switched the fuckin' tests.
- Easier to palm one of these,
then check your whole fuckin' suitcase.
It gives 'em the results
they're expecting,
the chains aren't even
worth half what they paid.
- And that's it?
- Just getting started.
Later on, the Blitch
Brothers will catch up
with Harold and his idiot sons,
before they get on the train.
Flash a few fake ID's,
and say they're all under arrest
for possession of stolen merchandise.
Suddenly, Harold's in the
middle of a big,
and he'll do anything to get out.
- Anything?
- And make a deal.
Harold agrees to set me up,
calls our man in Amsterdam,
fucking begs to buy another case.
Makes more money, his own money,
and he takes a case,
but this time he doesn't
check what's inside,
because he thinks if we start waiting
to field my call on the way out.
- You get him again.
- That's old Banky's animal scam.
Different story, but the
principle's the same.
Hit the same mark twice
with the same fucking scam.
- He doesn't go to the police?
- That's the best part.
We send the police down, the real police.
And he gets caught walking out the door,
with a couple of pounds of
cheap, hard-cut Colombian.
Goodbye Mister Olin, and good luck
explaining any of this shit to a judge.
- You got the chains,
do it all over again.
- This time next year.
- Now what?
- Take the money to Cara, get my split.
- What do I get?
- Educated.
- Have you worked it out yet?
What he really wants?
- Says he wants to learn.
- A bit cliched, no?
This won't end well, I promise.
- But I kind of safe for the boy.
- I just cut your end.
You can slice that, any way you like.
If he's not scamming
you now, he will soon.
What's really going on in there?
- Joe is dead.
Someone beat the old man to death.
The boy says he found him a few days ago.
- Then why come here to you?
- Apparently, Joe's been talking
about a score for months.
In our backyard.
Something big.
- That Joe never told you?
- How it works.
- He thinks you'll help him.
To take it down.
- That's what he thinks.
- So, what is it?
- It's a card game.
50K buy in.
- I know Matt.
- He's got the number.
Says Joe's been sitting on it,
for months.
- Months.
- That means,
you know what that means.
What will you do?
- Give him what he wants.
Up here, it's not like London.
It's too small to
racketeer in local money,
which is a good thing.
We're mostly moving outside marks.
Money coming in and out of the city.
Investors, gamblers, crooks.
Anyone worth cutting into.
The con we'll work,
it's not like a picking
pockets or rippin' off granny.
You want to con someone,
you get to figure at one thing,
and the rest is easy.
And some cons you throw in there,
the X box, medical cure, eternal
youth, watch 'em line up.
But others, you've got to
know something specific.
Art collector, I've got a Picasso.
Investor, I've got an inside deal.
Gambler, I've got a bet you can't lose.
Get it?
Once they're on the hook,
the game is yours to lose.
Make all suckers special for a reason.
Look at this guy,
what's he tellin' you?
- Banker.
Success.
- You can tell
that he wants some space.
Nice car, house, usual shit.
Should be wearin' a sign saying, I'm easy,
come get some.
What about her?
- Security?
Safety?
- Right.
If you get to her,
she'll do half the work.
People can't help being people.
Most of the time, they con themselves.
You show them what they want,
and they get what they deserve.
- What about them?
- Dignity, respect.
Give a taste of that.
Jesus, just fuckin' talk to
them and they'll hand it over.
It can be a hard deal
with married couples,
sometimes you know.
Usually they'll wait
until one of them cops it.
Loneliness can be our best friend.
And I bet you the pages in the Herald
make a crackin' read sometimes.
In the end, they miss our company
more than they'll ever miss their money.
Joe was smart,
kept it simple,
at the ultimate level,
short cons, betting joints,
and soft swindles at the track.
If the mark was too big,
he'd roll, and pass it to someone
further up the food chain.
- Like you.
- Or Alex and Paul,
sometimes bigger crews.
But he never overplayed his hand.
Never took any real risks.
A few years ago,
if I had anything in London
I started cutting him in.
Take off man, convincer,
you name it, Joe could do it.
He was solid.
Step up to anything,
as long as someone else did the leg work.
Tell him you know, and he'll teach you.
- Change race, the betting fixing,
passports thing, dealing from the bottom.
- What about the money?
- What about it?
- Is it just half?
You'd have kept it.
The one thing Joe taught
me, and I never forgot,
that all the old-timers do,
was to protect my stash.
I don't give a damn whose money I take,
but when it's mine, it fucking stays mine.
You can't always arrange
on buying working money.
Somewhere safe, you got a hold out,
and you fill that with cash.
18 grand, 20.
Something you might go if you need to.
Your bank, a deal stash,
that's something I'm working a hit.
Where did Joe keep his money, day to day?
- In his shoe, like a paper brick.
And he had his socks made to hold it.
- How much do you have right now?
You're not?
What about his hold out?
You have to keep that.
- He never.
- His bank?
He had to keep his deal stash.
Did you get it?
You don't know because
he didn't trust you.
You know why?
Because con men don't trust anyone,
especially each other.
This is how it works.
If I get conned or jammed up,
the bank roll's the first thing I get out.
The holder is a cherry
who has no other way out.
You know enough for some trip
to be bought or something.
But I never give up the bank.
You can carve my ass with a bacon slicer,
or put needles in my eyes,
you'll never get the deal stash.
Joe didn't teach you that?
He just did.
You do what I tell you, when I tell you.
You don't fucking think,
when it's already thought for you.
You got me?
- Yeah.
- This game is real.
Phone number is real.
We need a week to find
our way in, maybe more.
- How do I know you won't go without me?
- You don't.
That should keep you fed and washed.
You're paid until the end of the month.
- You are teaching me.
- Look at us, the gang's all here.
You know boys,
nice to see you all again,
without all the calls and ties.
You see me in there, sunshine?
Tonight we're gonna be
playing a different game.
It's called, where's my fucking money?
Now you chaps may not be
familiar with the rules to
where's my fucking money?
So permit me to give
you a little refresher.
Any objections?
- Fuck it off.
- I'm gonna ask, where's my fucking money?
You're gonna tell me,
where's my fucking money.
Then you're gonna tell me
where's your fucking money.
You see this is a fair game, boys.
First I get my money, then I get yours.
All of it at once, which'll
save us all some fucking time,
which reminds me,
my friend here's gonna be
asking most of the questions,
and if memory serves,
he is not a patient man.
So, I'm gonna cut one of you loose.
Two in the hand's worth one in the bush.
That's fair, right?
Let's see,
eenie, meenie,
minie, Moe,
catch a nigger
by the toe,
if it hollers
let it go
eenie,
meenie,
minie.
Take a moment,
have a think, remember
the name of the game's
where's my fucking money?
When I come back, we're gonna play.
- You Tom?
- Who are you?
- The game is on.
Wanna put your stuff away?
- No, I'm okay.
- Put that shit in your hotel.
Don't be taking stolen
goods to Rob's place.
He'll put your head in a fucking vice.
- It's called a nomad game,
different place every week.
Very high stakes.
The only way in is to have
the right phone number,
which we now have,
thanks to Joe.
- Thanks to Joe.
- This thing is started at 50 grand,
just to sit down.
And Joe never had the money.
Too rich for his blood.
What matters now, is that
this game is serious money.
And these are serious people.
Now we'll need all three
of us to pack it off.
- How?
- Cooler.
There's a sent in dealer,
but they offer a cut.
The deck is wide open
for about two seconds
before every deal.
- You've been?
- Twice.
Imran'll will play the
, I'll take the money,
and you're in the bag move.
- What? No, I can't do that.
- You deal the basement, right?
Cold deck's the same thing.
Just 52 times easier to get caught.
- I'm serious, I can't.
- Give me those.
Come on.
This might not be strictly legal,
but effective.
- Ho, ho.
Fuck me.
- This, I can teach.
Learn it and you don't
piss away all my money.
- How long have I got?
- Six days.
And if it's not perfect by then,
we're all dead.
- I don't like it over.
We could re a month.
- No, I'm already in.
I happen to know two seats
that are likely to open up.
We have to do it now.
You up to it?
The one I'm buying is 35 grand,
I'm going with more, and on 40,
you sell at five.
- Won't that look,
going in with the middle.
- That's 35 of my money.
Now, you want to top
off with pocket change,
be my guest.
Just don't fucking lose it
before we get our chance.
You get knocked out before the big switch,
I'll shoot you in the fucking face.
Now you may have brought this score,
but let's keep it as coming
out of my pocket, you get me?
- He gets it.
- Then get to work.
In five days, you need to be
rod the hot with this thing.
Take him to Slayer's.
Suit, shoes, the works.
He'll look money.
I'll see to that.
Now you can't polish a turd,
but you can roll it in glitter.
Keep him hot.
- Before we get started ladies,
I think I should explain
some of the rules.
One of you is gonna do the talking,
while the other, you'll see.
In my extensive experience,
people can't really
think straight you know,
through the pain, so I
tend to feel for lettin'
one of you deal with that,
while the other decides when to talk.
Motivation,
of course this was a foul assignment,
though others would
take no time at all but
you two jokers,
you kept the loot in
that one fucking night.
Better start.
Eenie, meenie,
minie.
Good enough.
What do you want?
- You don't need to do this.
Enough.
- I ask questions, you give answers.
Although he answers, he shows,
if you lie or hold out on me,
same old time.
You got that big boy?
- Hello.
Yeah, I got this number from Tom Shepherd.
That's correct, yeah.
Yeah, I am available on that day.
Yeah, I'm aware of the stakes.
My name, it's Thomas Dennis.
Okay?
- Okay, I'll go in first.
Wait a few minutes, then follow me.
If things go wrong, don't forget,
we don't know each other, okay?
How's the move.
- Run hop.
- Show me then.
Good, now glove box.
There is 35,000.
Just give 'em the envelope,
we don't give 'em cash in the open.
I know you're trying to con me.
I know it.
I've not figured it out yet, but I know.
Shit, I'd be disappointed if you weren't.
- That.
- Just don't fuck this up tonight, okay?
I've waited too long to get in this game.
That envelope, you take it, run with it,
if that's what you want.
Just don't go in there
tonight and fuck this up.
Hey, I'm a 100 grand up
in my balls in this shit,
but I understand it being over the table.
So if you're coming, come to win.
- Mister Shepherd sent me.
- Welcome to the nomad.
- He says, that lying motherfucker,
you've been bent off the
way we steal it last time.
Who's the kid here?
Did they check your age
before they let you in?
- No, I've got a fake ID.
I made it myself, it's a good one.
- Gentlemen, if we're ready, let's play.
- Bathroom.
What the fuck were you thinking?
- It's a good hand.
- It was only one hand.
Now go back in there,
stack the deck.
I'll take over and run
the next couple of rounds,
and we'll roll over everyone.
You make a switch from the bottom cards.
- Stack it now.
But I don't get to cut
for another four or five rounds.
- You'll know of a finger
fucking bottom card.
- Enjoy myself, huh?
This is the worst damn
luck I've had all year.
We could lose the action.
You should drink more,
and let me get better.
Please.
- Now that was a hand.
- Stop.
Fucking stop.
I see, that's one hell of a
fucking hand you had there.
- My time I guess.
- Wait, take your hands
off those fucking chips.
You're fucking Tom?
- Jackie.
- Don't fucking Jackie me.
What's his fucking bullshit?
Put down those fucking chips.
- You've been on a run of late.
Last week too.
Like I said, it's my turn.
- And like I said, don't
touch those fucking chips.
No this hand's fucked.
After he changed on this,
this prick cuts aceys.
- You have two kings, he has ace-king.
I don't see the problem Jackie.
- What is the problem?
What is it you see that we don't?
You think I cheated?
Okay, how the hell did I cheat?
He do it?
Or him?
Or did I rub a fucking lamp
and wish or a good hand?
- You know what I'm talking about.
- No, you know what you're talking about.
Why don't you tell everyone?
Hell with this.
I'd like to cash out please.
- Fuck that, you just took over.
- I think now will be fine,
given the situation.
Jackie, I think you
should stay at the table.
- You don't know who I am.
Gonna find out.
- Jackie, please, sit.
- Gentlemen.
Pleasure.
- Fuck, that was awesome.
- What are you doing?
- What?
- You're supposed to fucking wait.
- That's some shit,
that guy's fucking nuts.
- You're supposed to fucking
wait, if you need to get.
He just pulled something, get in the car.
- No, but I can.
- Get in the fucking car.
- I'm sorry I didn't even think.
- I know you didn't.
- We got the money.
I guess we can't go back.
- You've doubled that
deal, that's for sure.
- Did I fuck it up?
- No, he was too fast, that's all.
- How did he know we switched the deck?
- How did he know?
Let me see the cards.
The ones you switched out.
Shit.
He did know.
- No, I swear, he didn't see a thing.
No one saw it.
- No, but he did after it
was already done, it's paper,
the mount.
So your stick, professional,
takes months of practice,
you're out of luck.
- So it's a clip joint?
- No, just Jackie.
You were stepping on his scam,
that's why he didn't say anything.
Prick's probably got every
deck in the house painted,
and half the dealers in his pocket.
That's how we knew we switched decks.
The fucking marks disappeared.
- So that's why that
dealer with the one eyebrow
was staring at me.
Then we're in the clear.
- We're fucked.
We just called out one
of the most dangerous guys in Glasgow.
You think he'll tear that up?
- So what do we do?
- There's only one thing we can do.
Light out tomorrow.
Take the ferry or the train.
Buses are good too, but
don't go to the airport.
- What about the money?
- We're gonna need a
fixer, negotiate something.
After that, we'll chop up what's left.
Where will you go?
Back to London?
- Ireland, family.
If they'll have me.
A month, maybe.
- You did well tonight.
Until you almost got us killed.
- Sorry.
- You're green, but you're good.
I can tell.
- Can I ask you a favor?
- You're fucking serious?
- Yeah, just wait, two minutes?
Can you hold on to this for me?
- Why it's yours Tom.
- I've got 12,000 pounds
and Euros in here,
and a few personal belongings,
and my granddad's watch.
Like you said, I got to
take care of my stash.
I'd take it with me,
but I might lose it all.
- 12?
- I captured this, to keep me going.
I wouldn't ask,
but it's everything I've got in the world.
- Put it in the back, with the money.
- Yeah?
- The man's no.
This is gonna get nasty.
Hey, don't come back unless
you hear from me, all right?
You're sure you want me to bank that?
- That way you know I'm coming back.
- Fair enough.
- Come on, you can do it, come on!
Come on you can do it.
- All right.
Oh fuck off.
It's all been chopped.
I've got 60, 70 is mine.
- Well, that's a good start.
That could even make it.
- It's at the house.
- No it fuckin' hasn't.
Or have you been in the fucking game?
- One house, in the watch shop.
Under the bench, in the floor.
- Geez, they looked in the fucking shed.
You ladies will take.
- Hey, stay with me.
Tom, stay with me.
You'll hear when he comes back.
Even if he affects us.
He just affects us.
I've got a plan.
- Wakey.
It turns out you did know
how to tell the truth.
60,000.
Not bad.
Not even close to square.
I can get more.
- And I'm done with this guy.
Where have you got your winnings?
This guy's got his.
A car, fancy watch, and the suit.
You,
you've got nothin'.
I may have to pin the both of you cunts.
See the problem?
It might work, he's getting winced.
- No, wait wait.
I don't have nothin'.
- That's what you call a double negative.
If I don't have nothin',
if you don't have nothin',
you must have somethin'.
- What?
- If you don't have nothin',
you must have somethin'.
If you don't have nothin',
you must have somethin',
yes, I know.
- I have something.
- Ah, that's a point.
Unless you're bullshitting.
What is it?
- I know where he keeps
his money, his real money.
- That wasn't his real money.
- No no, the money he
gave you is just a front.
He's got a lot more somewhere else.
- And you know where?
- In my phone I can show you.
- Curiouser and curiouser.
- You said it yourself.
- Where?
- There's an app.
No, last page.
That one.
I gave him my bag, there
was a transmitter inside.
- And that's
where he keeps his money?
- Yeah.
- Just the fucking house.
You sure this is at?
- There, her name is Cara.
It's her house.
- It will only be.
I won't hit you then.
Good news.
Found the bag.
And now what will I do?
House belongs to some woman.
She wasn't there.
In fact, nothing was there.
That's the bad news.
You know what that means.
- No no, no!
No!
Help!
Fuck.
No, no.
Please.
- Do you have any fucking doubts?
- Please, please.
- I'm done waiting.
I've got shit to do.
- I'm sorry.
- I don't need your fucking sorry.
Let's give you a hit.
- No, wait wait wait wait.
There's a van,
in longterm parking.
- I don't do.
Where's my fucking money?
- Inside.
- My money's inside the van?
- Mine, my money,
is in the van.
- How much?
- A lot.
More than mister jelly donut over there?
- Uh, a lot.
- Okay, I'm gonna give you one last try.
If you waste my time I'm
gonna start on your feet,
turn you into chopped beef.
You understand?
I'm gonna ask once.
Ready?
Where?
- Walton Street.
It's floorage there.
It's a bag.
Under the floor.
- How much?
- Everything.
- Good boy.
- Hello, morning sunshine.
Best be going.
Nothing personal son but,
nice fuckin' ya.
You may want to wipe your asshole.
Sorry about that.
- See you in the morning Jackie.
- We all hit it too.
- Nice try, you little prick.
- You want me to make that call?
- Thanks Cara.
Stings don't it?
- How did you know?
- Which part?
- What?
- That you were going after my money?
Or that you killed the old man for his?
Joe told me.
- Joe's dead.
- Aye, he is.
But he sent a message.
Special delivery.
- How?
- You gave it to me.
- The game?
- The game.
- Nomad game.
The game that everybody wants in,
but only if you have the right number.
- My number was good.
- It's my game, Tom.
It's mine.
Been running it for years,
a rolling clip joint
for high stakes suckers.
Every seat loaded but one.
Grifters from all over the country
bring fresh meat into town
for a fair cut of the action.
Grifters like you.
- Clever.
Clever old man.
- When you told me about his big score,
A game that I'm sure he knew was mine.
Well,
message received and understood.
- You knew I had the money.
- After I went to London,
after I saw the old man.
I checked his hold out.
The first thing he'd give up in a pinch.
Untouched.
But his bank, empty.
Someone got close enough to figure out
the old man's stash,
but not his hold out.
Somehow you found it.
And you had to kill him.
Make it look like a bag,
or something random.
Beating an old man to death.
Somewhere I know that I'm guessing
Joe tries to bargain for his life.
But then he knows what's coming.
So he tells you about his big score.
Gives you a phone number.
Golden ticket.
Then you finished the job you started.
The one thing I couldn't figure out,
how you knew where he kept his bank.
You had to trick it out of him,
and no idea how.
Until you gave me that fucking bag.
- Nothing personal.
- You think?
- All this, torture room,
hammer, just for the money.
- A lot of money.
More than we expected even.
A lot more than Joe ever had.
How many grifters have you ripped into?
- You could have just beat it out of me.
- Joe deserved better.
- The con was the con.
- You ever see The Sting?
The film, The Sting?
- No.
- Two con men, Hooker and Gondorff.
Robert Redford, Paul Newman.
This big-time mobster,
a real dangerous guy,
kills their old man, their Joe.
So, they put together a big crew of guys,
guys who cared about the old man.
All they're ever gonna get is money.
A lot of money, but that's all.
So, Paul Newman says to
Robert Redford something like,
why are you doing this?
And you know, just for a bunch of cash.
What the fuck is that in return for?
Killing a friend, right?
And Redford says,
this is my favorite
line in the whole film.
Redford says,
because I don't know enough
about killing to kill him.
Of course,
it's just a movie.