Wash your windows, lady?
I don't do windows.
We have you surrounded.
Stay right where you are.
All units, code five.
Fire a warning shot.
That's no woman.
In that case, kill her!
Go back to the future,
you inhuman nymph from hell!
Holy shit!
No, no, cut it! Cut it.
God, this is completely unusable.
You effects guys
are gonna be the death of me.
- Hal? Hal!
- Yeah, talk to me.
Yeah, I'm gonna talk to you, all right.
It might be a good idea
if the car blows up before it does that...
So I messed up. It happened. It's done.
- For God's sake.
- My God!
Turn that thing off
- before I have a stroke.
- All right. I'm trying.
Is it off or not?
It's off! I don't know why it's doing this!
How can it be moving if it's off?
- Will you please answer me?
- It must be interference.
- Please handle this!
- I don't know. I only push the buttons.
I can't get this thing to stop.
My life is passing before my eyes, Fingers.
What the hell are you doing, buddy?
That's a quarter million dollar
piece of equipment!
Wow. Oh, my God.
Rollie Tyler. Rollie, it's me.
It's me, Marty Evans!
I was the third on Chainsaw Santa.
What's brings you here?
Well, the kid likes to see
movies being made.
Mr. Tyler, I'm a great fan.
Fingers, clean up the cyborg, all right?
Rollie, I have got
this primo new project I'd love to...
Sorry, I'm not in this game anymore.
But I tell you what.
If you need any toys for your kids,
give us a ring.
Come on, Chris. By the way,
next time you hire a special effects bloke,
make sure he's got all his fingers.
That might help. Good night.
- That was great, Rollie.
- That was schlock, Chris.
Why don't you work for that guy?
Because I like living too much, that's why.
Hey! Could I have some help
a little bit here with this piece of junk?
Rollie?
Rollie, we'll be late.
Did you hear me?
Yeah, I hear you.
You're not even dressed!
You are always doing this.
You forgot, didn't you?
No. I didn't forget.
Now, here. Try this on.
Come on.
I had to bribe the maitre d'
to get this reservation.
Well, I'd have been happy to just go
around the corner to Mario's.
Well, it's not your birthday, it's mine.
- You have good legs, you know?
- Shut up.
I like your dress.
What is this thing?
There we are. A telemetry suit.
I would have preferred a Ralph Lauren.
What are you doing?
Turning you on.
What do I do now?
Whatever you like.
Rollie.
You like it?
This is amazing.
Kids are gonna love this.
Kids that can afford it.
Oh, yeah.
Your index finger operates his eyes.
You're gonna have to give
a name for this thing.
I thought I might call it Bluey.
Bluey?
Well, at home,
if you've got red hair, you're called Blue.
What if you have blue hair?
Probably Grandma.
Whoops! Not 100 percent effective.
I think you'll find a screwdriver
in your pocket there.
- Can you hand it to me?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
What have we got there?
Wait a minute.
Thank you, Blue.
- Thank you.
- You like it?
I love it.
Oh, Bluey loves it, too.
Let me turn him off.
There we go.
Now, can I get out of this thing?
Unless you want to go to
the restaurant like that.
UP We go.
Yeah?
It's Mike.
Come on up, Mike.
Chris, I told you a million times,
no choppers in the house.
I think I got the hang Of it, Rollie.
You're doing well.
Nice light touch, remember?
Chris, cut it out.
Your father's on his way up.
I'm all packed, Mom.
Hello?
- Hi, Dad!
- Hey, there he is.
Hi, Mike.
- Hi.
- What time do you have?
I'm sorry. I was working on something
on my own.
I got hung up.
How's it going, slugger, huh?
Look what I nabbed from
the captain's desk.
What do you think? Like it?
Rollie made me a Dick Tracy watch.
Not the same thing, Chris.
Your dad's has got a lot more range.
- Mike.
- How are you?
Well, at least it's real.
Can I use your phone?
Yeah. It's right there.
Chris, go get your things.
Costume party, huh?
You'd look good in this.
Brandon here.
Come on!
For Christ's sake, I just put in 15 hours.
Yeah, I'm heading in. All right.
Shit.
Mike, you promised.
I'm sorry.
I'll take him with me.
Hey, champ! Wanna go to work with me?
- Great!
- All right.
Bet you thought I forgot, huh?
Bye.
Have a good time.
That guy's still in love with you.
No, he is not.
He just doesn't like you very much.
Well?
You know my middle name.
Hey, long time no see.
Okay, Chris.
Just make yourself at home over here.
All right? Stay out of trouble,
or I'll throw you in the cage.
- Mike?
- Yeah.
You play Scrabble?
I don't believe this, boss.
Look at all these unsolveds
and you want me to stake out a peeper?
For Christ's sake, give it to uniform.
We got a chance here
to prevent the crime from happening,
instead of cleaning up
the mess and pushing paper.
Who's the perp?
Did seven years
for cutting up a model in '82.
Take a look at this.
Oh, man.
When do we go?
- Yesterday.
- Typical.
You've waited up for us.
That's very nice of you.
I suppose a drink's
out of the question, is it?
Maybe one, before I get started.
Of course. You've got to grade
those midterms, haven't you?
Yup, they're due out on Monday.
Surprise, surprise.
That's so sweet.
Can't help yourself, can you?
A new gel. Bit smelly.
Make a wish.
What did you wish?
- I'm not gonna tell you.
- Go on, tell me.
No. 'Cause then it won't come true.
Mom!
Mike, what are you doing here?
Excuse me. I'm sorry. It's...
I got to talk to Rollie.
Yeah, sure.
Come here, Chris.
We want to bait a trap
for this slime bucket.
Make him think that the girl is alone
in the apartment,
except it won't be the girl, it'll be me.
That's where you come in.
What? You want me
to make you look like her?
Why not?
You need a miracle worker,
not an effects man.
My kid says you can create
any illusion you want to.
Listen, Mike,
you're talking to the wrong bloke.
Cop's work isn't my game.
You think I don't know
what went down a few years ago?
What do you mean?
Between you and your pal, Leo McCarthy?
Let's get one thing straight.
McCarthy and I were never pals.
The way I heard it,
he got kicked off the force
because of a case
he was involved in with you.
Looks to me, you guys did okay.
Maybe you also heard that the lady
I was living with at the time was killed.
This is a different thing, Rollie.
You'll be in and out of the place
before you break a sweat.
That's what they said the last time.
If there's one thing I've learned,
it's that nothing is as simple
as people say it is.
- You want a beer?
- No. No, I don't want a beer...
I'm asking you to work for the NYPD,
for Christ's sake.
It's a straight-up thing!
The only person I work for now is myself.
That way, I always know who to trust.
Sorry I can't help you, Mike.
All right. Let me ask you something.
If someone like this was coming after Kim,
what would you do?
Why not?
Hey, you degenerates.
Get out of here. Come on.
- Is that it?
- Yeah.
This is a new one. What do you think?
I'm truly flattered.
Okay? All right. Now.
The microphone is in the left breast.
You press here if you
want to talk to Silak.
Great, they talk.
And this is so you can hear Silak.
You put that in your ear.
Now?
And if you want to talk to me,
you use this watch.
On, off and I'll beep you.
- Right.
- Gotcha.
Here we go.
I don't know about this, Rollie.
Believe me, it'll work.
You're a knockout.
You want to come for a little drink...
Would you get out of here with that?
Just asking. Okay, now, Kylie.
Mike'll give you your cue,
and then you just do everything
that we've rehearsed.
You're not gonna be here?
In spirit.
Damn Silak!
You know, it'd be
a whole lot simpler, Rollie,
if you stuck around and worked this stuff.
Don't worry. I'll be keeping an eye on you.
What's that?
- Camera.
- You're kidding me.
Latest technology.
A little paranoid, huh?
If there's any problems,
I'll beep you on the watch.
My kid's right. You're all right.
I wish I could say the same about you.
Mike, you read me?
What's going on up there? Where's Tyler?
He's leaving now.
Mike? Mike, I'm telling you,
nothing goes down
until Tyler's ass is on the street.
Roger, boss. I'm out.
There he is.
Mike? Mike? Your man's on his way in.
Let's go.
McQuay? McQuay.
Santoni, you stay here.
Kill that bulb, will you?
Here we go.
All right.
Show time, Mikey. Play the cheap seats.
We got him.
What? What?
Good. Real good.
Get down and come on through.
Stay low, stay low. That's it, that's it.
Stay low. Great. You're doing good.
Come on. Come on. Let me help you up.
- How'd I do?
- You did great.
I'll put you in for a Tony.
Now it's my turn.
- Break a leg.
- Yeah.
- Bye.
- Mike?
Mike!
What?
What's the matter, Rollie?
There's too much smoke.
It's a shower, not a fire.
Yeah, so? What to I do?
Go to the panel at the back of the machine.
- Yeah?
- Turn the knob counterclockwise.
Gotcha.
Wrong way, Mike.
Something's wrong.
What's shaking, Mike?
I'm taking care of it.
We've lost him.
Shit.
Mike? Mike?
The man's coming your way.
And, Mikey, he's got a blade.
- How you doing?
- I'm still shaking.
No. Just relax. Everything's gonna be fine.
Hey, Rollie, dig this.
I'm a special effects man.
What do you think of that movie?
Come, Mike. Knock it off.
- Mike?
- All right, all right, keep your shirt on.
That's better.
Okay, Rollie, I'm signing off now.
In 10 minutes, I'll buy you a drink.
Mike, don't take the watch off. Mike!
Okay, big boy, come and get it.
Here he comes.
Too smoky. Too bloody smoky.
Glad you've got that gun.
Jesus Christ, Mike!
Kick it in!
Freeze, asshole!
No!
McQuay, get on the air.
Tell them we got a 10-13, cop down.
Get her out of here. Get her out!
Hey!
Where is everybody, Silak?
The bastard got away.
What the hell are you talking about?
I just iced the son of a bitch.
No. No.
There was someone else in the room.
How do you know?
I saw you leave the building.
He was on the back stairs.
Now, wait a minute.
Hold it. Hold it. Now, listen.
There were only two people in here,
Mike and this piece of shit.
Now if you saw somebody
on the back stairs,
he didn't come out of this place.
Mike is dead.
Too much smoke, Tyler.
He got to Mike first.
Now, would you get in there
and shut off that goddamn machine?
Lieutenant, backup's here.
Wagon's on the way.
I brought the girl to her neighbor's.
What a mess.
Jesus, Mike.
Why did this have to happen?
Shit. Why did this have to happen?
Oh, Christ.
Tyler.
I think you'd better get home.
Mike's kid is gonna need you.
What about my gear?
I'll see it gets back to you.
Let's talk tomorrow.
Okay.
Come on.
- Hello.
- Leo, it's Rollie...
This is Leo McCarthy.
I hope this machine's working.
Leave your name, your number,
- the time, a brief message.
- Come on. Come on.
I promise I'll get back to you. I promise.
Leo, it's Rollie.
Pick up if you're there, will you?
All right, you know where I am.
I need your help.
Get in touch. I'm in trouble.
Hey, how'd it go?
There's been an accident.
Chris, you don't have to do this.
I want to.
Hey, take a look at this.
You got a problem reading or what?
It says, "Do not enter."
It also says, "Crime scene."
What the hell is going on here?
Are you family, lady?
I'm Mike's ex-wife and this is his son.
We just came here to pick up a few things.
Nothing's gonna leave here
without an okay from downtown.
What exactly are you looking for,
if you don't mind my asking?
It's just a routine search procedure,
Miss Brandon.
You got a problem,
you talk to headquarters.
This is routine?
Mike was a victim, not the suspect.
Or does somebody see this differently?
When an officer's killed
in the line of duty,
it is our job to secure the premises
and all department property.
I'm sure you understand that.
Yeah, I understand.
I understand that that is a lot of baloney.
I can't believe this!
These are mine.
Bad blood, bar...
I'm still playing with those.
"Becker." Now, what kind of game is that?
Come on. You can see it's the kid's disk.
M♪am, you cannot take that.
Be reasonable. The boy
just lost his father.
Kim?
On, God, Ray.
I'm sorry.
Your father was a good cop, Chris.
The best I ever knew.
I'm gonna make sure
that you get his gold shield.
I know he'd want you to have it, okay?
Thank you.
Come on.
Tyler!
I called you this morning.
We're here to pick up a few things.
Oh, listen, Rollie, your equipment...
Oh, yeah.
Don't you worry about it. I know you blokes
got a lot on your mind. I'll get it later.
No, no. We'll deliver it.
Just give us a time.
Well, I got some things to do now,
but I'll be back home later this afternoon.
Fine. By the way, Rollie, is...
ls this something of yours?
Thanks. It's a remote transistor.
It goes with the projector.
Don't fool with me, Tyler.
It's a goddamn camera.
I want to know what it was doing there.
Mike wanted a camera. I got him a camera.
Mike didn't clear
any goddamn camera with me.
- It's not my problem, Silak.
- You're wrong, Tyler.
It is your problem.
And my problem.
What are you getting at?
The guy you say you saw on the stairs?
The guy you think killed Mike?
We're working on the possibility
that it might have been a cop.
- What makes you think that?
- I can't say now.
Did Mike ever talk about
any of his cases with you?
Any old, inactive files?
- No.
- Maybe with Kim, then.
Where are we going?
Jersey. I want you to spend
a couple of days with your sister.
Be great, wouldn't it, Chris?
See your cousin again?
I don't want to go to my sister's.
It's too dangerous to go home right now.
- Dangerous?
- Yes, dangerous.
How could it be dangerous?
I mean, where are you gonna go?
- I got a few things to sort out.
- What things?
Why Mike was set up and who set him up.
Don't worry about it.
Kim can borrow any
of my clothes that she needs.
Beth's gonna be here. Go on.
Now, don't go out.
Don't even answer the door.
Rollie, I can’t just disappear.
I have to go to work!
Trust me on this.
Rollie, I have a night class.
What if I can't get
anybody to cover for me?
Kim, it's not safe now.
What did you mean
about Mike being set up?
Silak thinks that Mike might have
been set up by some other cops.
- Hi!
- Hi, Beth.
Think you can look after your cousin
for a few days?
Yeah, okay.
I think I can help him.
I can't tell you any more.
Just do as I ask.
Leo, I don't know
if you're getting these messages,
but if you are,
stop farting about and contact me.
I'm in real trouble with the cops
and I need your help.
Okay. Now let's get a good look at you.
What are you doing?
Jesus, Silak.
Give me that tape.
Sure, take it. It's yours.
No. You get it.
How do you know I didn't make a copy?
Did you?
No, I wish I had.
Hiya, Rollie.
Are you gonna hang around
here all night, huh?
Great bloody timing, Leo.
Come on. Don't fuck up the roof of my car.
I'll lock the door, huh?
All right.
My little crash pad.
Jesus, and I thought I was paranoid.
Hey, you're the one that's looking for
a safe place.
What?
Jesus, what?
Christ! Jesus Christ!
Gotcha! I got you!
You bastard, Leo.
You bastard.
After what I've just been through?
I got you!
How could you do that to me?
Five years I've waited. I finally got you.
So you ended up with it.
What do you think, huh? Not bad, huh?
Always wanted my own gin mill.
Yeah.
- So who else knows about this place?
- Relax.
Nobody knows about this place.
Hell, nobody knew about it
when it was open.
I'm sorry it's a little messy.
The maid hasn't been in
in three or four years.
So, who'd you get to decorate the joint?
Rin Tin Tin?
I'm not gonna discuss fine art with you.
Get over here. Take your medicine.
You're telling me that this beacon
of journalistic accuracy
has got this cop-killing story all wrong?
It's bullshit, Leo. I'm telling you.
Silak must have set the whole thing up.
He's probably got the whole bloody
precinct out there now looking for me.
Why? Why would he do it?
He's got 25 years on the job.
He can retire anytime he wants to.
Why would he kill another cop,
one of his best friends?
I don't know why. You figure it out.
You tell me why those bastards were
going through Mike's place this morning.
Wait, what bastards?
The cops gave us a hard time.
Wanted to see everything we took out,
even Chris's toys.
Shit. That sounds like I.A.D.
What's I.A.D.?
Shooflies.
Cops who investigate other cops.
Internal affairs.
Yeah, that's what they were,
internal affairs.
- That's what Silak called them.
- Wait a minute.
Silak was at the apartment
with these guys?
You bet.
The only reason I.A.D. would be involved
in a cop-killing
is if they thought Mike was dirty.
Mike was not dirty.
No, I know he wasn't. That's the point.
Silak must've brought them in.
He's trying to deflect the investigation.
I think we're getting warm here, pal.
You might be getting warm.
These cops at the apartment,
did they ask you anything?
No, they just wanted us out of there, fast.
What about Silak?
Did he ask you anything?
Christ, Leo, I can't remember.
Rollie, this is important! Think!
Did he ask you anything at all?
He asked if Mike ever talked
about cases he was working on.
An inactive case, whatever that is.
That's it. It's a shit pile case.
What is a shit pile case?
It's a hobby case.
It's an old, unsolved, inactive case.
Cops pick them up, they screw around
with them on their own time.
That's what it's got to be.
So, what do we do now?
First, we have another drink.
Then we try to find the right shit pile.
Hi.
Surprise!
Leo! I can't believe it!
This is a restricted area
and you always just waltz right in.
How do you do it?
I lie.
Tell me about it.
You said you were gonna call me for dinner.
That was two years ago.
I thought you were supposed to call me.
I tried to call you, you bastard.
You look good.
Congratulations on your promotion.
Thank you.
How's your mother doing?
Spare me the Irish charm, Leo.
You didn't come up here
to ask about my mother or to see me.
And if you think
I'm going to risk my job again
by helping you find
some alimony cheat, you're crazy.
No, no, I don't do
matrimonial work anymore.
It's too dangerous.
Oh, yeah? What are you doing?
Actually, I'm working on
the Mike Brandon killing.
Forget it, Leo.
That's a high-profile investigation.
It's also a bullshit cover-up.
Who's your client?
Another sleazebag insurance company?
Actually, my client
is Brandon's 10-year-old son, Chris.
Hey, Velez.
I'm serious.
Damn. You sure know
how to push the right buttons.
Good girl.
Look, I'm interested in an old case
that Brandon was working on.
How far back?
Why don't you bring up
anything older than five years?
Do it like you never tapped in.
Don't worry.
Any luck?
How do you feel about
doing some telephone work?
Telephone work?
Hi, Ray.
Sergeant, I'll be back in an hour.
Listen, I'm a respectable citizen.
I want to file a complaint.
We got a new install and repair
for Lieutenant Shylock.
- You mean Silak.
- Silak? Yeah.
Yeah. You want the boxes
at the foot of the stairs.
- Great.
- Here's the key.
Don't return it, it's your ass.
No sweat.
Look at this!
Look at this, I really got it.
Almost got it.
You're wasting your time.
That thing hasn't worked in five years.
Hey!
Turn it down.
- Hello?
- Yeah, Silak? It's Neely.
Tomorrow, trial part 52, 100 Center.
Yeah.
Remember, Tony Vargas
was the button man.
Yeah, I got it.
Don't sweat the little stuff, all right?
Hey, I see from the dailies
you neutralized the problem.
- Nice work.
- Yeah,
but it didn't go down as clean as I want.
- How's the old man doing?
- Sliding fast.
Don't screw it up.
You do your end, I'll do mine.
Silak, you scumbag.
So, are you gonna tell me?
What was all that about?
It's about me spending the day
in court tomorrow.
Mr. Neely, is it a fact you're coming up
for a parole board hearing soon?
Yes.
Now, Mr. Neely, tell us, please,
how was it you learned
who ordered the murder of the decedent?
Tony Vargas told me.
And what did he say?
That Moore hired him as the button man.
That's a goddamn lie!
Objection, Your Honor. Hearsay.
Sustained.
You may continue, Miss Kennedy.
Where were you when
Vargas told you this?
In C-81 at Rikers.
He said Moore wanted him iced
because he knew too much about the...
Objection, Your Honor!
May we have a sidebar?
Approach the bench.
Judge, I object to this
line of questioning.
I'd like to know what promises have been
made to the witness for his testimony.
Miss Kennedy,
do you have any response to this?
Yes, we're sending a letter to the parole
board acknowledging his assistance
in this case
and counsel is well aware of this fact.
I don't want this to drag on.
Neither do I, Counselor. Neither do I.
'Hey, Leo!
- Hey.
I'm surprised to see you.
- Hey, long time.
- Yeah.
- You look wonderful.
- Thank you. And you.
No black eyes, no broken noses.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, you're doing divorce work now,
you know.
Somebody opens the door too quickly and
you're still peeking through the keyhole...
That's right. That's right.
Kick an old pal when he's down.
Well, you deserve it.
You were the best cop I ever worked with.
Just too goddamned bullheaded
to play by the rules.
Hey! Are we talking professional now?
Or personal?
Oh, believe me, Leo, I forgot about
that other stuff a long time ago.
You lose a bet?
Thank you. Bring me the Doolan file.
- It's on your desk.
- On my desk.
Leo, you want coffee?
Yeah, I'll take some coffee. Black, please.
Two black coffees! That'll take an hour.
- Where do you want this?
- Just there is great. Thank you.
Not bad.
Look at this.
Liz Kennedy, the smartest kid
ever to come out of St. Cecili♪s Parish.
How come you didn't go with
some big-time corporate law firm
up there on Madison Avenue or someplace.
Make yourself some serious money?
I like trench warfare.
Madison Avenue is advertising, Leo.
What can I do for you?
I want to talk to your witness, Neely.
Well, call legal aid.
Neely's not my client.
No.
Come on, Liz. This is
Leo you're talking to.
Neely's making you famous,
for Christ's sake.
You got two major convictions
already with his testimony.
So?
You probably eat your tuna fish sandwich
with the creep right up here every day.
What's the matter? You never used
stoolies when you were a cop?
Oh, yeah. Sure, I used stoolies.
I didn't actually sit down
and write out their dialog
for them to recite in court
in exchange for sentence reduction.
Hey, hey, I don't do that.
Everything he testified to
is in line with the information
we gathered before hand
in our own investigation.
Who was in charge of that investigation?
Lieutenant out of the 2-7
named Ray Silak. You know him?
Yeah, I know him a little.
Yeah, Silak's been all over the papers
lately with this cop-killing.
This Mike Brandon thing?
Yeah. That's nothing to
do with this office.
Now tell me Liz, you trust Silak?
What are you saying here? Silak's dirty?
If he is, you don't want it rubbing off
on you, do you, Senator?
I am not involved
in politics in any way, Leo.
No, I know, I know. You told me.
What have you got on Ray Silak?
Who are you working for, Leo?
I don't have to tell you who I'm
working for. You know that.
As far as Silak is concerned,
all I have right now are suspicions.
Now, you could be in big trouble here
and not even know it.
Maybe I can help you,
but you got to help me first.
Okay? Come on, come on, come on.
Fix it so I can talk to
this motor mouth Neely.
Get me Chambliss in parole.
Norm Chambliss is Neely's parole officer.
The nuns would be proud of you, darling.
I really appreciate your time.
It's a pleasure.
What can you tell me
about this asshole, anyway?
Well, Neely started off strictly
small-time, fencing shit in college.
Got popped a couple of times,
he rolled over,
earned his stoolie jacket.
That turned out to be his true vocation.
So now, they put him in
with the real bad guys, he gets them to...
Just shut your mouth.
He gets them to shoot off their mouths.
Then he testifies against them.
Baboom! He gets an early out.
All right. How come he's back in prison?
The dumb ass violated his parole.
It's like he wanted to get sent here.
So, is he being a good boy this time?
Listen to this...
Chambliss. State parole.
Want to see Neely.
Thank you.
A model inmate.
Oh, Jesus.
Works here in the infirmary
a couple times a week as a volunteer.
This guy's even a chaplain's clerk.
Another scumbag comes to jail
and finds the Lord, huh?
What are these guys? The choir?
Jesus, very butch.
What is he, a boy soprano?
There he is.
Yeah, yeah, I see him.
A regular St. Francis of Assisi, isn't he?
Yeah.
What's the story on the old con
he's talking to?
Oh, Carl. He's been here forever.
Dying of emphysema. Any day now.
Tough old bastard, though.
Another con sliced him up
some years back.
Carl stuck a shiv through the guy's throat.
So they gave him life.
"He, answering, said to his father..."
Looks like he's gonna do it all, too.
Chaplain says
that Carl has been very good for Neely.
That's great.
He says, he brought
the young man back to the church,
don't you know?
Becker treats the kid like a son.
Becker. What...
Carl Becker. Jesus Christ.
That's Carl Becker.
Yeah, that's what I said, Carl Becker.
Wait here.
"Thou art ever with me
and all that I have is thine."
Hey, Carl. Neely.
Got a Pl here named Leo McCarthy.
He wants five minutes of your time.
What do you think?
No. Absolutely not.
Five minutes of your time.
What's it gonna take?
"For this, thy brother
was dead and is alive again."
Thanks a lot.
"And was lost,
"and is found."
Hey. So, there you are.
Jesus Christ. You went
back to the apartment, didn't you?
Couldn't sit around all day.
God, you stubborn son of a bitch.
You're like a 10-year-old.
- Where you been?
- What is this shit, anyway?
What the hell is this?
Say good day to Bluey.
How are you, pal? Nice to meet you.
You're not eating that shit, are you?
It's been there for five years.
Do me a favor, will you?
Stay away from the pickled eggs.
I've been at the library. Pardon me,
would you, sir? Thank you very much.
I found out why Mike was killed.
All right, here.
Saint Peter's in Rome. The Vatican. Okay?
It's the Sistine Chapel.
These bronze-colored reliefs show scenes
from the Old Testament Book of Kings.
Okay? From here to here,
the gradual conversion
of the human soul to God.
When he finished the Sistine Chapel,
Michelangelo re-creates these reliefs
in solid gold.
Ten medallions about so big.
This is the case that Mike was working on.
About 20 years ago,
these medallions were part
of the Vatican exhibit
at the Metropolitan Museum.
A guy named Carl Becker, pretty good thief,
he sneaks in and he grabs them.
The dumb son of a bitch.
I don't know what he thought
he was gonna do with them.
Now Becker gets pinched
the very next day, but the medallions,
they never turn up.
Now, these are original, hand-minted,
solid gold Michelangelos.
You got any idea
what they'd be worth today?
What do you reckon, Blue?
Close enough, Bluey.
- Bye.
- Okay, bye.
- See you later, Miss Brandon.
- All right, I'll see you next week.
Becker. Jesus. I know I know that name.
It was a famous case.
It made all the papers.
No.
Oh, Christ. I know where I heard it.
- Where?
- Just a... Just a minute.
Who the hell you callin'?
Don't tell them where you are.
I'm not tellin' anyone. Just quiet.
Come on!
- Hello.
- Beth.
Hi. Rollie. Put Kim on, will you?
She's not here, Rollie.
Where is she?
She went to her class.
Put your mother on, then, will you?
She's shopping.
It's just Chris and me here now.
Then I'll speak to Chris.
What the hell is goin' on here? What?
Chris, it's for you.
I know where Mike's file is.
Becker was a name
on one of Chris's game disks.
Jesus Christ. If Silak finds that out...
Yeah? What?
You don't think he'll go after the kid?
- Hello?
- Chris, hi, it's Rollie. How are you?
Listen, I need your help.
Do you remember the name Becker
on one of your game disks?
What if I do?
Well, I need to know what was in that file.
They don't have a computer here.
Listen, Chris, how you doin'?
Look, my name is Leo.
I'm a friend of Rollie's.
Do you know anybody out there
who might have a computer?
Yeah, over at the mall.
Do you want me to send it to you
by modem?
Yeah, that's a good idea.
He's not to leave the house.
That's a good idea, Chris. Go to the mall.
I want you to send it to me.
He's not to leave the bloody house!
He'll be safer there. There's people there.
- Bullshit!
- Where the hell are you going?
To get Kim.
Listen, Chris. Yeah, it's okay. Listen.
Have you got a pencil?
Yeah.
- Hello?
- Beth, is Kim back yet?
No, she isn't, Rollie.
She went to pick up Chris at the mall.
She just left five minutes ago.
Thanks.
I hate waiting.
Me, too.
And I've had a lot of practice, believe me.
I know I'm gonna regret asking this,
but what is that supposed to mean?
Every once in my life you walk in,
use my computer, use me.
Then you disappear.
It's not right, Leo.
You're absolutely right, Velez.
You know what you need?
A vacation.
Leo. I can't believe it!
- Jamaica!
- Yeah.
Am I going alone?
Well, I don't know. What date does it say?
Let me see. It's open.
Really? The same as mine.
Leo, you shouldn't have.
Yes, I should have.
I should have a long time ago.
There are other things
I shouldn't have done,
but this I should have done.
Attention, shoppers.
The mall will be closing in 10 minutes.
Need any help, Chris?
No, I'm okay.
Okay, we gotta close in a minute.
Leo.
- Yeah.
- This is Chris. ls Leo there?
Yeah, Chris, this is Leo.
Hold on a second. Listen, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna put the expert on, okay?
Hi, Chris.
Have you ever used a modem before?
- Yeah.
- Ls your program up?
- Yup.
- Okay.
Press F1
and then type in the same phone number
you just called.
Okay, now hang up, press enter
and I'll talk to you on your screen, okay?
Okay-
Chris. What are you doing here?
I told you to stay in the house.
But, Mom, we found dad's file.
Give me the disk.
It's stuck.
Here we go.
Way to go, kid.
All right. My God, look at how fast it is.
Are we gonna get a printout on this?
- Yes.
- All right.
"Becker. Vatican medallions."
Okay. "Neely. Samson"?
That's a new one.
Samson. What the hell is that?
There's Samson again.
What's goin' on here? We got garbage.
Oh, no. The transmission's
been interrupted.
The kid screwed it up.
See if you can find out what's going on.
Okay.
I guess that's the end of it.
Well, print it out.
We'll take a closer look at it.
- Why don't we go get something to eat?
- Okay.
I know a great place. They serve
the best Chinese food in the city.
- Great.
- We'll celebrate, all right?
Attention, shoppers.
The West Side Mall is now closed.
We open again tomorrow
from 10:00 a.m. to 9:00 p.m.
And please note,
tomorrow, many stores are participating
in the one-day sale,
with discounts of up to...
Excuse me, sir. We're closed.
Yeah.
Hey! I said we're closed!
Hey, watch it, pal!
Kim? You all right?
Yeah.
What's your problem?
Leave me. He's got a gun.
Don't be...
- Kim, run!
- Chris!
Open up.
Get lost.
Here.
Yeah. Come on.
Kim, hair spray.
- It's locked.
- Damn!
You shouldn't believe everything you see!
Now, you bastard, I want some answers.
Let's start with Silak.
Silak, we have a problem.
Becker's taken a turn for the worse.
What do the doctors say?
He won't last the night.
You'd better have
a goddamn heart-to-heart,
and if you want out of there on Saturday,
don't screw it up.
Good night, Mom.
Chris wants to say good night to you.
Some day, eh?
Do you think they got the file?
I'm sure they did.
Your dad would have been
very proud of you today.
That man, did he kill my father?
I think you should get a little sleep.
I never really thought it was your fault.
I know that.
Is this great or what?
I was picturing something
a little different, you know?
Candles, a bottle of wine.
Maybe a table and a chair.
Come on. This place is the best.
Frenchie here is the best Chinese cook
in New York, right, Frenchie?
You bet.
You betcha. We're gonna take
a couple spring rolls to start, all right?
I'll tell you,
I keep reading this and reading it.
"Samson. Samson."
Samson must be the buyer.
It's probably a code name of some kind.
Thing I don't get is
why the hell Mike didn't figure out
Silak was involved in this thing
right from the get-go.
Obviously, he was getting very close.
He was in over his head.
He should have known it.
Okay. Two spring roll.
- Okay.
- Here you go. Ready?
- Some mustard.
No, don't, don't put that mustard on.
- No, that stuff is murder, really.
- Leo, you're such a wuss.
Come on. It'll take the roof
right off your mouth.
- Leave it alone.
- You're such a wuss.
That's plenty. That's plenty.
Okay.
I don't even want to watch this.
Velez!
Father, could I have a moment alone
with him, please?
Can you hear me, Carl?
I'm gonna die.
No, Carl.
You're going to meet God.
You once said that you wanted my help
to atone for your sins.
It's not too late, Carl.
Tell me where the medallions are
and I'll give them back to God.
Where's the music?
What happened to you?
Velez is dead.
They shot her about an hour ago.
Chinatown, for Christ sake.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, me, too.
She was...
She was a good cop.
They tried to get me, too.
It was a mob hit, Rollie.
There's more to this whole thing than
a dirty cop and 10 shitty pieces of gold.
I had a talk to the guy that killed Mike.
Yeah? ls he a cop?
No, just some thug.
Silak's got a chopper
ordered for this weekend.
There's some sort of rendezvous.
I know where.
We're gonna need backup.
I think I know someone who can help us.
- Oh, God!
- For God's sake.
- Hold still. Hold still.
- That stings! What is that?
Come on. Don't be such a baby.
Why don't you just leave this to NYPD?
Because somebody else in the department
could be involved in this thing.
Look, look, look. Either they followed me
and killing Velez
was some kind of an accident,
or they picked up on Velez
through the computer.
When she tapped in,
she left some kind of a trace, something!
Either way, I can't take any chances.
- Enough with the alcohol, please!
- Okay.
Unless you have
some of the drinking kind out there.
Excuse me. Where are my manners?
Just a second.
Look, if I have a choice,
I'll take a scotch.
Hey, if you have a single malt,
you could make it a triple.
Saves all that walking back and forth.
Jesus Christ.
What's wrong with your cat?
There's nothing wrong with my cat.
She's a Cornish Rex.
They don't shed.
Are you telling me that...
Are you telling me that
they look like this on purpose?
Looks like a big rat.
Leo, you want ice?
What, in this? No. You got to be kidding.
No, for your head.
No, my head's fine.
Look, Liz, you got to help me here, huh?
Maybe help yourself, too.
I mean, you could be
a real hero with this thing.
You know how many assistant D♪s
work their whole goddamn lives,
they never get an opportunity like this?
Don't hustle me, Leo.
Opportunity for what?
Wreck my career? Get killed, maybe?
What do you need?
I need backup. But local backup, okay?
Nassau County cops,
the sheriff's department, something.
No NYPD.
That's it? What else?
You got to be there.
Me? No. I'm...
I'm an assistant DA. I don't do that.
Hey, I'm a private investigator.
You think those country cops out there
are gonna do what I tell them to do?
No way.
No, you got to be there.
This could be your ticket, Liz.
Somebody's got to prosecute
these Bastards.
Somebody's got to talk to the press.
Who better?
Do I take that as a yes?
Keep your nose clean, Neely.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll see you, Neely.
Neely, over here.
Come on.
All right, we're stopped. Now, look.
Enough of this shit. Where we going?
Hey, relax. We're here.
- Where?
- Come on.
Let's confess our sins.
Thank God for the sacrament
of his love and forgiveness.
Place your confidence in Christ,
who died for you on the cross.
For your penance.
Say five Our Fathers and five Hail Marys.
He'll forgive your sins.
I absolve you of your sins in the name
of the Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit.
Go in peace.
Welcome to this sacrament of forgiveness.
Forgive me, Father, for I have sinned.
It has been one week
since my last confession.
Continue, my son.
I felt anger, Father,
towards an old man
who had been my friend.
It was unworthy.
I also lied three times in the past week.
Yeah, I had a couple of impure thoughts.
And I...
Feel very regretful.
Anything else, my son?
No, Father, that's it.
Oh. Sorry, Father. I was deep in thought.
The eleventh station of the cross.
Jesus is nailed to the cross.
We adore you, oh, Christ,
and we praise thee.
And they came to Golgotha,
the place called the Skull.
They crucified Jesus and the robbers
one on his right, the other on his left.
And Jesus said, "Father, forgive them
"for they do not know
what they are doing."
- Yeah.
- It's Rollie. ls Leo there?
Yeah. It's Rollie.
- Yeah.
- I'm all set, mate.
All right, good. We're on the way. Yeah.
We're expected.
Who says?
Samson.
Jesus. I don't think we asked for enough.
Hey-
Watch what you say in here.
Go. Go.
I hope Rollie's ready.
He should be. He's been setting
it up for a couple of days.
This is good right here.
Cue ball, corner pocket.
I warned you.
Can you see Rollie?
No, but he's got the dogs penned up.
The gardener hasn't noticed anything.
I didn't see any backup.
You're not supposed to, Leo.
Do me a favor, will you? Get on the horn.
Make sure they're in position.
Nassau one, this is LK.
We're all set. Over.
All right.
Did you bring any protection with you?
I mean, a gun?
No. You said there'd be plenty of artillery
when we got here.
This is New York.
There's no such thing
as too much artillery in New York.
- You ever use an automatic?
- No.
Okay. This is the way you cock the sucker,
so to speak.
- All right.
- All right?
There's your safety. On, off.
- Okay.
- Okay? Hold on to it.
Leo? It's Rollie.
Yeah, go ahead, Rollie.
Looking good.
Okay, buddy. Just wait for my signal.
Leo, please be careful.
You, too.
What?
Gotcha.
Hi, guys.
Now, everybody, just relax, okay?
- McCarthy.
- You know this man?
Yeah.
NYPD, retired. He's a private dick now.
Damn it, Silak, this is the guy that
was snooping around at the prison.
Hey, listen, fellows.
We'll all get acquainted
in a minute, all right?
Just stand easy.
I knew this was too good to be true.
Liz, it's Leo. Send in the cavalry.
Liz, come back.
Okay, Leo,
I've cocked the sucker. Take his gun.
You're a great disappointment to me.
Just move, Leo.
You were expecting this, Silak?
Shut up, Neely. Leave everything...
I suppose this means
that the backup's not coming, too.
You said there were two.
Tyler's out there somewhere.
Tyler? Who the hell is he?
What the hell is goin' on?
- Call him, Leo.
- Kiss my ass, sweetheart.
Never point a gun
unless you intend to use it.
This right with the safety? Little red dot?
Hey, be careful with those things,
all right? It's an automatic. Okay?
Rollie, this is Leo.
Look, it's, lions eight,
Christians nothing in here.
Somebody's pointing a gun at my head
even as we speak.
I think it's time to pack it up.
Rollie?
I guess he's out of range.
Wait. Who the hell are these guys, Silak?
Yes, she was a fine Catholic girl, Father.
I don't know
what could have happened to her.
Shut up, please, Leo.
Enjoy your trip?
You're going on another one.
Ben voyage.
- How long is this gonna take?
- Until it's over.
You got the medallions, so pay up.
You can put 'em in your vault
and look at 'em on rainy days.
- Shut up, will you?
- You screwed up, Silak.
What?
You didn't check out
who really owns this place, did you?
What does he mean?
You always were an asshole, McCarthy.
What, do you think this place
belongs to some fence, for Christ sake?
Huh? These guys look like
art collectors to you?
This is a mob safe house, Neely.
Nobody said nothin' about the mob.
Their money's the same as anybody else's,
or don't you think so?
So when do we see it?
All right.
Old bills, as you requested.
It'll take you a long while
to count to 10 million.
Ten?
Oh, Jesus, here we go.
What did he tell you, kid? Five?
Huh? Two and a half apiece?
Or was your end supposed to be
parole and car fare?
- You son of a bitch, Silak.
- Hold it. You were gonna get a full cut.
- Of what?
- Of the 10 million.
Bullshit! I was the one
who got Becker to talk!
If it wasn't for me,
you and that bitch would be nowhere.
The kid is absolutely right, Silak.
You deserve a 60/40 split.
Shut your foul trap!
Maybe it should be 70/30.
I mean, you're the one
who had to go back inside, right?
The words double-cross
definitely come to my mind.
- The word dead man comes to my mind.
- That's two words.
Please. Please.
I apologize for these interruptions.
It'll soon be over.
They are his work.
Michelangelo.
Very good.
You know where they have to go.
Boat's waiting for you.
Yes, sir.
May I go, too?
Yes. Thank you for your help.
Thank you.
How about that, Silak?
You tell the chopper noon,
the man's here right on the button.
Now all you gotta do
is get out of here alive.
You don't think they're gonna let you
walk with that cash, do you, kid?
Don't listen to him. The money's yours.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Sure.
Silak, wait, wait. Before we break up
the party here, answer me something.
Now that you got these medallions,
what the hell are you gonna do with 'em?
Who's the buyer?
There's no buyer.
They're being returned
to their rightful owner.
Wait a minute. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What, are you telling me
the Vatican is behind this?
No.
Our associates in Italy have
never condoned crimes against the church.
This is our way of righting a wrong.
Come on, Neely. Let's...
Silak, you dumb shit!
You go out that door,
they'll fill you full of holes.
Now, hold it a second.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Are we forgetting somebody here?
What about Liz?
Where's her share?
Who's supposed to pay you, anyway?
Mr. Pizza man here, or Moe and Larry?
I mean, they were gonna cut you in
on this deal, weren't they?
Don't be stupid, Leo.
I'm not in this for the money.
That's enough.
Son of a bitch. Of course.
You're gettin' into bed with the mob,
aren't you?
You're gonna be connected
to all that influence
and that power.
Well, tell me, Liz. What
do you get out of it?
What, the DA? US attorney?
Or was I right the first time?
You gonna be the next senator
from the state of pasta fazul?
Would you please just shut up, Leo?
- All right, game's over. Give me the gun.
- No.
Oh, bullshit! You're not gonna shoot me.
You guys, stay out of this.
It's between her and me.
Don't look at him. He's not gonna help you.
He wants you to do it. Sure!
Yeah. He wants you to make
your bones right here, right now, with me.
That way he owns your ass forever.
Is that what you want? Huh?
- Come on, give me the gun.
- Don't do this.
Jesus, God, please! Don't.
Give me the gun, come on.
Please!
Let's get out of here.
L...
Silak!
Damn!
Life's a bitch, Neely and then...
Jesus Christ.
You call that a small fire effect?
Well, it's not an exact bloody science.
Christ, I stink.
Let's go. Chopper's about to take off.
Yeah. I'll catch up with you in a minute.
Yeah, he's messy, but he's fun at parties.
When did you know?
I'm a good detective.
I got lucky.
Big name for a little cat.
Samson.
I wondered where the hell that thing went.
Okay, Leo, it's your call.
I wonder if I could kill you
as easily as you killed me.
Now, there's the backup you ordered.
I called them, too, just
in case you forgot.
Why don't you explain all this to them?
Come on, mate! I'm losin' him!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey, you're goin' the wrong way.
I said the Nassau County Airport.
Jesus Christ!
Where did you learn to drive?
Slow down! Slow down!
Down! Here, take this.
Now, keep it steady. Steady!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like before.
Look, Silak. No hands.
Oh, my God. What are you doing?
Don't let go of the wheel! Jesus Christ!
Where's the bloody thing? Get it!
My God, we're... We're going...
What's the matter with you?
You... Hey! Hey!
Geronimo!
There he goes.
Yeah!
Silak, you're on your own.
Let's go! Come on!
I don't know how to work this. Oh, my God!
Hey, can somebody help? Hey, some help!
Oh, God, stay up, now.
I think it's going down.
That's not supposed to happen.
Bluey sprung a leak.
You said the damn thing would float.
I thought it would.
Grab the bag.
Come on.
All right. Give me the bag.
Here. Take Bluey.
Screw Bluey. Give me the goddamn bag.
- All right.
- Got it?
Yeah.
Don't forget me.
Come on, mate.
Yeah!
Good on you, Bluey!
Look, look at Silak go.
I hear it's a bitch
to learn how to fly those things.
He's doin' all right.
For a clown!
We got a real problem here, Rollie.
You know how long it's gonna
take us to dry $10 million?
These are already dry!
Please tell me those aren't
the real medallions.
They are! I switched them.
Rollie, you dumb bastard.
The mob wasn't stealing 'em.
They were returning 'em to the Vatican!
Nobody told me.
I wonder if we can find
a decent restaurant in this town.
What do you say we exchange
some of our damp currency
and we try to find something to eat?
Good idea. What do you fancy?
How about Mexican?
You're all class, Leo, but I promised Kim
and Chris some real Italian pizza.
Hey, hey, hey,
there's only one city in the world
where you can get a decent pizza.
Yeah, Sydney.
Yeah, you're right.
Hey, how about a coin? You want a genuine
coin collection from the Vatican?
That's the last thing
he needs, mate, coins.
- Sorry, pal.
- Come on. Next trip. Come on.
Here we are. Let's get up in this.
That poor horse. We should be pullin' him.
Apologize to the horse, mate.
Wait a second. Wait!
Oh, my God, this... I got it.