Subtitle By - arunutv
Best In Business
♪ First things first,
I'm the realest ♪
♪ drop this and let
the whole world feel it ♪
♪ let 'em feel it ♪
♪ and I'm still
in the murda bizness ♪
♪ I could hold you down like
I'm givin' lessons in physics ♪
♪ I'm so fancy ♪
♪ you already know ♪
♪ I'm in the fast Lane ♪
♪ from L.A. to Tokyo ♪
♪ I'm so fancy  ♪
♪ can't you taste this gold? ♪
♪ remember my name ♪
♪  'bout to blow ♪
♪ I said, "baby, I do this, ♪
♪ I thought that you knew this" ♪
♪ can't stand no haters ♪
♪ and honest, the truth is ♪
Buenos Dias, cecelio!
Sir, I'm just sayin', your ad
says, "bad credit, no problem."
So can you define
"no problem?"
Because me not gettin' this loan
is a problem.
I'm sorry. That's why
I'm asking you to...
Sorry, daddy.
That's okay,
but that's just nasty.
No, no, no.
Not you, sir.
Okay, all right,
well, listen to this:
What if I have everything
I need except the $30,000?
Keep calm?
Sir. Sir.
Can you...?
Ma'am. Okay.
I-I couldn't tell.
Aren't you supposed to be
a predatory lender?
Then prey on me!
Okay?
You're a lion, I'm a gazelle.
Okay, fine. Fine.
Do you know what?
I'm puttin' my
daughter on the phone
so you can explain to her
why she has to go to school
in a gangbanger school district
where they're murdering kids.
Murdering!
Here, you tell her.
Hey, baby, do what I showed you.
Why do you want me
to get murdered?
- No.
- Murdered.
Why do you want me
to get murdered?"
They hung up.
Baby, because you're
not doing what I told you to do.
You are sick.
I'm not sick.
It's called desperate.
Baby, all we have to do
is keep saving.
I just need...
I just need some love.
Can you just hug me?
Just kiss me?
Mm. Any better?
Awkward.
Come on. Get your juice,
and your book bag.
I told you
to hit the bull's eye.
How hard is it to cry,
Makayla?
"Murder. Murder."
All right.
Watch out.
Move, old man.
Is that weed?
Hey, I want you
to be safe, okay?
Listen to me.
You're not gonna be
at this school forever.
Daddy's workin' on it.
I love you.
I love you, too.
All right.
Don't worry.
Kinda hard not to worry.
You're my daughter.
Come on, dear.
Hey, watch it!
Matter a time.
I kick, James!
Yeah.
Move!
Ha!
Ginga!
Hey, babe!
Watch this, honey.
Watch this.
Whoo!
Look at that kick!
Axé.
Good job, James!
You looked good out there,
my big strong fiancé.
Jaoa says I need to focus
on bringing my power
into the world.
Fuck!
Maybe I can help.
You...
Are a great man,
James King.
Do me on the new house.
Did it get bigger?
The King needs his castle,
James.
So powerful.
So you don't think
it's too much house, do you?
James, seriously?
I mean, you wanna raise a family
in this house?
Well, yes.
In this house?
No! No, this...
This house is a shithole!
Look...
There's winners
and there's losers, James.
It's what drives this country.
All right?
People look at what you have...
And they want it.
They want your huge house.
And they want...
Your hot, hot...
Wife.
So hot.
Who's the King?
I am.
Are you the King? How much money
you gonna make today?
Enough to choke a baby.
That's right.
Yeah, are you a winner?
Yes, I'm a winner.
Yeah?
Whose tits are these?
They're my tits.
These are the King's tits!
The King's titties.
That's right.
Is it a King's dick?
It's... it's slightly above average.
Yeah?
You gotta stake your claim,
James.
Yes!
You gotta stake it!
Stake my... my claim!
Oh, come on, baby.
Do me like a billionaire!
Oh!
You. You, right there,
with the hat.
♪ I got this feeling on the ♪
♪ summer day when you were gone ♪
♪ I crashed my car ♪
♪ into the bridge ♪
♪ I watched, I let it burn ♪
♪ I threw your shit into a bag  ♪
♪ and pushed it down ♪
♪ the stairs ♪
♪ I crashed my car ♪
♪ into the bridge ♪
♪ I don't care ♪
♪  I love it  ♪
♪  I don't care ♪
♪ I got this feeling on the ♪
♪ summer day when you were gone  ♪
♪ I crashed my car ♪
♪ into the bridge  ♪
♪ I watched, I let it burn  ♪
♪  I threw your shit into a bag ♪
♪ and pushed it down the stairs  ♪
♪ I crashed my car ♪
♪ into the bridge ♪
♪ I don't care  ♪
♪ I love it  ♪
♪ you're on a different road, ♪
♪ I'm in the milky way ♪
♪ you want me down on earth, ♪
♪ but I am up in space ♪
♪ you're so damn hard ♪
♪ to please ♪
♪ we gotta kill this witch ♪
♪ you're from the '70s, ♪
♪ but I'm a '90s bitch ♪
♪ I love it ♪
hey, boss man,
did ya get that text?
I sent ya a text yesterday.
♪ I got this feeling on the ♪
♪ summer day when you were gone ♪
surprise!
The boss is here.
Maybe it's time that we act
like we got work to do.
We got 40 cars
and we got eight hours
of the air down here!
James King,
Wealthrop Funds.
Transfer 100 million
from my client accounts.
I'd like to put a buy order
on Bradway Chemical,
up to 7.50.
I've got a good feeling
about clean coal.
Clean the roofs, Mike.
You don't think
people can see those?
I hired you to do one thing.
That's be tall.
♪ I don't care, I love it ♪
all right, great job.
Hey there, Jamesy,
that was quite a ride, man.
That was like
third quarter 2012.
It's a real pleasure
to watch you work, sir.
Thanks, Leo.
Yeah.
How 'bout that,
you knew my name!
I love it.
♪ I love it ♪
so I shorted gas
and went long on coal.
It wasn't quite the return
I was hoping for, but...
James.
You made my company
$28 million today.
Now, to celebrate,
I would like to give you
an early wedding present...
Partner.
Sir...
Thank you.
Gayle, a minute.
James, this is the moment
when you cross that threshold
and join America's
most elite.
Anything you desire,
anything you want is yours.
I'm ready for it.
You know, I bought an island
in Cape Verde?
An entire island.
You can, too.
I would love to.
We could be island neighbors.
You could swim over
and borrow a cup of gold.
Yeah.
You know, and to think it all
started with this.
I still have that computer.
It reminds me...
Of my humble beginnings.
How I built this company
with my own two hands.
Just me, that computer...
...and an $8 million loan
from my father.
You really did it all
on your own.
Very inspiring, sir.
Now, listen, I want you
to drop this "sir" nonsense.
You are marrying my daughter,
for Pete's sake.
I want you
to call me "Dad."
Really? Dad?
Mm-hmm.
That feels very good.
My... my real father
never had time for me.
He shipped me off to
boarding school in London
with the Murdochs
and the Bin Ladens.
Of course,
that was before...
I mean, we knew they cheated
in soccer, but had no idea...
You know...
But if I could choose a dad...
Hey, you know something,
you're family now, kid.
Okay, then.
Oh, boy.
Motherfucker.
Ah!
Mr. King.
Take whatever you want!
Please!
Oh, it's the hood.
Oh!
Hey! It's Darnell.
Help!
No. Stop!
Mr. King!
Help!
No!
Oh, dear lord.
Someone help me!
You're being ridiculous!
Stop!
Look at me.
It's me!
I got your keys!
Oh! Yes!
I see you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
Here you go.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Yeah.
And, just so you know,
I would have done the same thing
if you were white.
That's...
That's good to know.
Hey, Mr. King.
Um,
while I got you out here,
I just wanna... I just wanna
talk to you for a second.
I've... I've been washing
your car for two years now...
And, I mean, I can tell
that you're the type of man
who likes the best
of everything.
So as owner and CEO
of Hollywood Luxury Bubbles,
I wanted to offer you
an exclusive platinum
lifetime wash card...
For, um, for $30,000.
Now, before
you say anything,
think about the type of money
that you'll save
with this...
With this investment.
Well, actually the time value
of money is such that
if I were to put that same
amount in my own fund,
in 23 years time, I'd have
in excess of $3 million.
Wow. Yeah.
With that rate of return,
I could buy a new car every time
it gets dirty.
Isn't that impressive?
That's amazing, Mr. King.
You see, I didn't get to
the place where I am today
by asking for handouts...
But by hard work.
And today,
that hard work paid off...
As I was just named partner
in my firm.
Mr. King, that is... hey.
That is amazing.
Thank you so much.
That is...
Thank you.
That... that's amazing.
Mr. King,
we...
You see, everyone, whether
we're born rich or poor...
Or white...
Or miscellaneous...
Who we become...
Is based
on our own decisions.
It's simple as that.
And on that note...
No, Mr...
You don't have to give me
that much, Mr. King.
Hold on, hold on, hold on,
hold on.
Mr. King, you don't have
to give me that much.
Mr. King. Hold on.
There we go.
You really don't need...
There you go.
There's a start.
Mr. King, please.
I feel like you just
haven't given me...
Success is a mind-set!
Wow.
Hi, everyone!
Hi!
Thank you so much
for celebrating our engagement
with us.
James, I love you...
And I can't wait to be married
to you.
And because
you rock my world...
I got you this!
Oh! Hey! Wow!
Come on.
This is beautiful.
But not as beautiful
as you, Alissa.
Aww.
I love you.
Being with you and in front
of all of our friends
and family here...
I just wanna say, I'm the
luckiest man in the world!
Play something!
Oh.
Oh! Well, actually, there's one
more part to your present!
It's Mr. John Mayer!
John Mayer!
Thank you, thank you.
Hey, everybody!
Who's John Mayer?
I just wanna say, thank you,
James and Alissa,
for making me...
Shut up!
...a part of
your special night.
Thank you very much.
You ever seen a hundred women
get wet at the same time?
Watch this.
♪ Fathers be good ♪
♪ to your daughters ♪
♪ daughters will love ♪
♪ like you do ♪
♪ girls become lovers ♪
♪ who turn into mothers ♪
♪ so mothers be good ♪
♪ to your daughters too ♪
John, lay back.
I'm gonna take a few bars.
Hey! Step aside, FBI!
Back up!
Everybody, step aside!
James King.
Yeah?
You're under arrest
for 43 counts of fraud
and 30 counts of
embezzlement.
Well, that's impossible.
Yeah, that's what they all say.
Get him outta here!
I know.
This is some kind of joke.
Is this some kind of joke?
'Cause if this isn't, this is
the worst nightmare imaginable.
Yeah!
Finally.
Are you gettin' this?
Shit, yeah!
Get outta the way!
I swear I don't know what any
of this is about! Mm-hmm.
Don't worry, son!
I'll take care of it.
Let's go.
Gayle, call my lawyer.
My party!
The charges are securities fraud
and embezzlement.
These transaction records
prove you're guilty.
I've never seen these.
These are fakes!
Boy, if you go to court,
they're gonna kick your ass.
Take the plea.
Dad!
You'll be out in a year
and in the best
shape of your life.
No.
I have faith that
the justice system
will exonerate me.
And that the jury will
put aside their bias
and see the truth:
That I didn't steal money
from people.
I lost everything!
Fuck you!
I-I didn't do it!
Judge Carlyle: For too long,
wealthy white collar offenders
like you
have gotten a free pass
with light sentences
in minimum-security prison...
While working Americans
have suffered.
Well, that ends today,
Mr. King.
I sentence you to the harshest
penalty allowed:
Ten years in a
maximum-security prison.
You have 30 days to get
your affairs in order.
Just run them over!
I can't go to jail.
I'll die in there.
That's not gonna happen, James,
because I'm gonna put
my investigators on this 24/7
until we find out
who really did this.
Just make sure you stay within the
county lines with that thing on.
Otherwise, the U.S. Marshals
will be down there pronto.
Son, I want you to stay strong.
Do you hear me?
I will.
I'll be so strong for you, Dad.
Why me?!
Esquiva!
♪ I didn't have time
to tell my baby... ♪
I have to leave the country!
♪ Hey, hey, hey  ♪
♪ hey, hey, hey  ♪
♪ take her down  ♪
♪ hey, hey, hey, hey  ♪
It took so long to ring me up,
I had to miss my
waxing appointment.
I feel like a gorilla.
It's summer, too.
I can't believe this is
happening to me.
It's like they don't even
recognize you anymore.
Thank you. Yes.
Alissa! Hey!
It's me, James.
I know.
What are you doing?
Why do you look
like that?!
Just eat your fuckin' salads!
I'll fuckin' kill you
if you say anything.
Hi. Hi.
Hi.
I came up with a great idea.
Let's just run away!
Some place that no one would
ever think to find us.
Mexico.
Let's just leave
this material world behind.
Live in a one-bedroom shack.
Oh, God.
Yes. You could sell
chiclets on the road.
What?
Look, we'll work out
the details later.
We should get out of here.
No!
I already cut off
my ankle bracelet.
No! No!
No!
Let's go.
James, no.
What?
No! I'm leaving you!
Why?
But I thought
you loved me forever.
Well...
Now you know.
Alissa.
This is the U.S.
Marshal service.
James King, exit the building
and surrender to
custody immediately.
Oh shit!
Hey, guys.
He's in there.
Oh!
Why are you arresting me?!
Me llamo es
reagando Esteban.
I am but a simple bartender
from Belize.
Wait, no. Mexico.
Call my lawyer in Tijuana.
Oh, shit! Aah!
What the fuck is that?!
Get off!
It's me!
Mr. King?
Yes.
You scared the shit
outta me, man.
Whatcha doin' in the trunk?
I just needed... I just needed
a place to regroup.
You know, fresh start.
Okay. Hey.
Lemme help you out, man.
Ugh.
Fuck you, King!
I lost everything
because of you!
I didn't do it!
Fuck!
Fuck someone!
Fuck a tit!
Fuck a tit hard!
For the love of Alan Greenspan.
Fuck!
My life is ruined.
I venture you've heard
that I'm going to prison.
Yeah.
No, we... we all did.
I just didn't wanna bring it up
first, that's all.
Come on. They're probably sendin'
you to some club fed prison.
You'll be playin' tennis
and golf, you know.
I'm going to be attending
San Quentin.
They're sendin' you
to San Quentin?!
Oh!
What?
Oh, God!
Oh, they fuckin' in San Quentin.
Oh!
Everybody gets the dick.
They might as well call it
San fuckin', man.
I don't wish that
on my worst enemy.
You talkin' about bad?
That's bad.
You should know.
I-I'm sorry to remind you.
What are you...
What are you talkin' about?
Well, the fact
that you went to prison.
The fact
that I went to prison?
Yes.
Okay.
Just before I get to
another level of anger,
Mr. King,
just tell me for giggles,
how do you know
I went to prison?
It's really quite simple.
Statistical analysis
is what I do.
Here's the deal:
One out of three black men
will find themselves incarcerated
during their lifetime.
Imagine a pizza, okay?
Okay.
There are three pieces.
Three black pieces.
One of those pieces of pizza
will be thrown in jail
at some point
during its life.
You know what? Lemme give you
my statistical analysis.
You goin' to San Quentin...
There's 100% chance that you're
gonna be somebody's bitch.
Ten years of this:
You know what that is?
Mnh-mnh.
That's a big-ass black man
on your pale white ass.
You: "No!
I don't want any more!
"Stop! That's enough."
Too late.
He done tagged
the next guy in.
That's like a rabbit.
And you don't want him
no more,
so now here comes the guy
that wants to rub your face.
"Oh, I like his hair."
He's breathing on you.
That's disgustin'.
But guess what?
You can look forward
to 10 years of it!
What if I speak to all the
bitches and we organize...
Form a union, and we put our
feet down and say, "enough!"
There's gotta be more
of us than them.
Well, there's not.
You deserve everything
you're gettin'.
Good luck on survival, sir.
Better luck
on handling yourself!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Don't leave.
Don't leave, please.
I could use your help.
Help you with what?
Help me to not be
someone's bitch.
You expect me to help you?
I'm supposed
to teach you what?!
How to prevent this...
All right, stop.
You could train me.
You could be the Athena
to my Odysseus.
I don't even know what the fuck
that is, man!
I could pay you.
Whatever it takes.
I need $30,000.
Done.
O-okay.
Yup. Yeah.
Fantastic.
All right.
What're you doing?
I-I only know these two.
What are you trying to do?
Shake?
You wanna shake my hand?
Oh, yes.
Oh, regular.
It's a deal. We got a deal.
Excellent.
Thank you, Darnell.
I'll see you in the mornin',
convict.
What're you doin'?
What is that?
Tryin' to do this thing.
No.
Shake. It's fine.
Okay.
Mr. King, no.
I got that.
All right.
I appreciate it.
No problem.
Yes! Thank you!
Babe...
This does not make any sense.
Why would he hire you?
Because he thinks I went
to prison, babe.
See, that's the part
I don't get.
Why would you
tell him that?
I didn't tell him that.
He assumed that.
He assumed it?
Yes!
So what reason
did you give him
to assume that you went to jail?
I was bein' black.
This is nuts.
Okay. I don't get
what's nuts to you.
In 30 days,
we'll have the money,
the house'll be ours.
What is the problem?
The problem is
he is never going to believe
that you went to jail.
Look, babe.
I am your wife,
so I will put it
to you straight.
You are not exactly
a thug.
I don't have to be a thug
to portray a thug.
Okay?
Honestly, all I gotta do
is change my voice,
talk a little deeper.
Talk like this
and be every stereotype
he already thinks I am.
Right now, I'm thuggin'.
Yeah.
This is thuggin'.
You're so good at it,
sweetie.
Have a good night.
Bitch!
Don't walk away from me!
What the hell
did you just say to me?!
Girl, stop.
What is wrong with you?!
Stop! Stop!
What is that?!
I love you!
I was playin'!
Bitch.
What what what what?!
I didn't say nothin'!
Oh.
Man, I didn't say nothin'.
You wanna watch
"the notebook"?
I love you and Makayla.
Yeah, I love you, too.
Good night.
You've reached the voice
mailbox of Martin Clark.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
Hi, Dad?
It's James.
Just wondering if there's any
word from the investigators.
I still love you.
Uh, thank you. Bye.
Now, I heard a crazy story
about you.
This guy James King?
Yeah.
And I heard that you played
at the party
where he got arrested.
Yeah. I had no idea
that I was performing
for a monster.
I don't know how
to really explain
what it's like to take money
from someone like that.
It makes you wanna
give it back to them,
except that would be worse
because then they'd have it.
And it's that whole
helpless feeling that I have
about our creative process
being monetized,
and that's what inspired me
to write this song,
which is actually available on
iTunes tonight at midnight.
Oh, wow.
If I can play it.
Great.
Okay.
♪  I can't see ♪
♪ through walls  ♪
♪ and I can't read ♪
♪ your mind ♪
♪but if I did I'd find ♪
♪that man James King ♪
♪is a great big turd ♪
♪I mean, the small, ♪
♪small kinds  ♪
♪  but that sh- ♪
♪ James will fall ♪
♪  hands against ♪
♪ the prison wall  ♪
♪  choking on a mouthful ♪
♪ of balls ♪
♪  he'll be chokin' ♪
♪ on a mouthful of balls ♪
I hate to admit it,
but it's a good song.
Hey, Russell.
It's, uh, it's Darnell.
Your cousin.
Your cousin, Darnell, man.
Hey, listen, Russell...
How would you like to make $500
just for telling me
what prison was like?
Yeah. Well, I don't...
I don't wanna say that.
Russell,
I shouldn't have to say that.
For... for what?!
What is...?
Fine. Fine.
I'm a Cliff Huxtable
pussy-lookin' motherfucker.
No!
I'm not even wearing khakis.
Russell, can you please
just help me,
what I'm asking you for?
Just start from the beginnin'.
No, no. Like, the beginning
the beginning.
Like, the first day of prison.
On... on the first day?!
Oh! There's no warmup?
That's sad.
Russell, I'm sorry,
did I just hear a gunshot?
You gotta go.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Ready, mother...
That's it, that's it.
Coming!
Rita, Makayla, new house,
good school.
You ready, motherfucker?
Just a second!
Hello? Hello?
You ready, motherfucker?!
Aah!
Oh, it burns!
Pepper spray, bitch!
Rule number one: You always
be on guard, okay?
'Cause on the inside,
there's somebody
waiting around every
corner to fuck you up!
Prison school is in session,
bitch!
You already failin'.
Aah!
I'm so glad I hired you.
This is just what I need.
Ohh.
Okay.
Uh, what's next?
What the...
How many motherfuckers
live here?
All right.
Let's get started.
This right here is
my prison readiness program.
Now, if you follow this guide
and do exactly what I say
you will definitely survive
in prison.
"Keistering."
What's, uh, keistering?
Slow down!
You ain't ready for that.
You're the teacher.
And I just want you to know
I'll do whatever it takes to
survive and get my life back.
That's good, 'cause let me
tell you somethin':
You're gonna have
to work harder
than you ever
worked before.
You know, back when I was in
Harvard business school,
I was facing some
pretty long odds.
But I buckled down
and I succeeded.
When you was at Harvard,
did you ever get raped
for failing a test?
I think that's more
of a Yale thing.
"Yale."
I'm sorry.
Shut the fuck up!
Now from this point on,
this ain't your house no more.
This San Quentin!
You understand me?
Okay.
From now on
this will be your cell.
You do not leave this room
without my permission.
It's good.
For you to sleep on,
señor.
Go on, we ain't got time
for games.
Go upstairs, finish turning
this place into prison.
It will be our pleasure
to repay you for
your many kindnesses.
Put that in there in front of
the statues with the dicks.
James, listen to me.
The key to survival
in prison
lies in the following
simple questions:
Are you hard?
And can you handle yourself?
Well, this is a rare
moment for optimism
because the answer to that
is a resounding yes.
Well, that's good.
Let me see what your mad-dog
face look like.
I'm sorry.
What's a mad dog?
You a mad dog!
Oh, shit.
What's your what, nigger? Huh?
Take whatever you want!
Let me see that!
No!
Stop! I beg of you!
Like a pit bull
with no leash.
That's a mad dog.
Wow. I knew you were
the right guy for the job.
In prison, a mad-dog face is
essential to your survival.
Do you understand me, James?
So the idea is that
I make a face
that conveys the fact that
I would have no problem
hurting you.
Exactly what it is.
Now convey that shit.
Let me see it.
Okay.
Ha!
That's terrible.
No, that's horrible, man.
Anger.
You gotta show me anger.
Why you smilin'?
I'm not smiling.
I'm tense and I'm agitated.
Come on, man!
Huh?
That's your mad...
That's it?
Yeah.
Your fiancée left you.
Huh?
That's right!
Y-you happy about that?
No.
Then get mad!
She gonna leave you?
What is she doin'?
She probably on her knees
sucking somebody dick
in the backseat of a truck.
Show...
James.
Oh. Oh. Come on.
Come on.
I miss her so much.
Oh, what the fuck
are you doing, James?
I'm sad-dogging you.
James?
You think that's a strategy
that could work?
No, I don't. I don't think it's
a strategy that could work.
Hey, listen up, everyone.
I'm extremely sad.
Please don't
sexually assault me.
I'm already too sad.
Hey, fellas.
My heart's already been raped.
Wait. I don't wanna
do this anymore.
Let's move on. Okay? We're
movin' on from the mad dog.
James, can you fight?
Absolutely.
Esquiva.
What?
Esquiva. Esquiva.
You had to change your
clothes for this?
Entrada.
What the fuck are you doin',
man?
It's called Capoeira.
It's a Brazilian martial art.
But don't be fooled
by its beauty and grace.
It's actually quite deadly.
This is deadly?
That's deadly?
Stab.
Ow!
Stop.
Stab. Stab.
Guards!
What are you...
Stabbity stab, stab, stab!
Ow! Ow!
What the fuck
are you doin', man?
Shit ain't gonna save you
in San Quentin!
Well, that may not,
but you haven't seen
my bencao kick.
Your what?
My bencao kick.
Bencao!
Look what your dumb ass
done did.
Stab. Stab.
I'm dead.
Stab.
Stab, stab, stab, stab.
You're so bad.
Aw, James.
I gotta tell ya.
I just can't imagine what you
must be goin' through.
Ahh. It is so nice
to talk to you.
So, what's the latest
from the investigators?
The investigators?
Uh, Chinese hackers.
They're pretty sure.
Hey!
I know I'm not crazy.
Didn't I tell you
to get off the phone?
Get off the phone.
Hey, who are you
talkin' to?
It's, uh, it's Darnell.
He's helping me.
Get... your time is up!
I-I gotta go.
I'll call you back.
Hang it up!
Hopefully, if I get more phone time.
That was important to me!
Yeah, well, when you got
a long line of angry inmates
waitin' to use
the phone,
you do not wanna piss them off,
James.
I'm going to fuck you up,
Mr. James!
Rosa!
You watch your back
on the yard.
Puto.
I'm not a puto.
Great.
All right. We got a problem.
What's that?
James is talking
to somebody.
Oh, no, no,
h-he trusts you.
He'll never put
two and two together.
No, stop it, Peter!
Stop it!
This is your fault!
What?
Well, you couldn't get him to
take the plea deal, right?
Instead of him
goin' to prison,
you got him 30 days to be out
there, runnin' around...
Fucking things up!
I had to make it look good.
You throw a fight, you don't
go down in the first round.
It's fine.
I don't want him out there,
playin' detective with somebody.
You keep an eye on my ex
future son-in-law, would ya?
And find out
who this Darnell is.
I'm on it.
Right away.
There you go.
All right, James.
Look, you're gonna get in
a fight on the inside. Okay?
Now, you don't need to win
these fights,
but you need
to show these guys
that you're not afraid
to fight back.
Gotta get used
to fightin', man.
See those guys over there?
Wow.
Yes.
I want you to go over there and I
want you to fight one of them.
That's insane!
They're...
They're behemoths.
They would break my spine.
Yeah, well, those are
the type of guys
you're gonna see
in San Quentin.
So you gotta shake
that fear, man.
I want you to go over there
and punch that big-ass dude
in the mouth.
Oh, my God.
My heart is pounding.
Okay.
Hey, guys.
Who the fuck are you,
man?
I wanna fight you.
What?
You picked the wrong day
to come to the park.
Is this some kind
of joke, man?
You ever been
mad-dogged before?
You about to get some right now,
motherfucker.
What the fuck is that,
man?
It's the size of your dick.
I'm gonna break it off,
make you eat it.
You...
You fuck your mother
with that dick?
How do you know my mama?
You don't know my mama.
Oh, no.
Get him!
Get back here, bitch!
Oh, no!
Please don't hurt my body!
Aah!
No! My body!
Help! Help me!
You're breaking my spine!
Wait. What happened
to my tennis court?
James, you will no longer refer
to this area as a tennis court.
From this point on,
this is the yard.
Understand something, James.
The yard is the most deadliest
part of prison.
It's where you come to get
your few precious minutes
of fresh air
and sunlight.
Do you understand me?
Mm. Fresh air.
How many times did I breathe in
clean air,
fragrant with lavender,
and take it for granted?
James, I don't give a fuck
how many times.
I don't give a shit.
I'm just saying.
Shut up, James.
You gotta step carefully
because if you step in the wrong
place at the wrong time,
you'll end up
in the wrong territory.
For a person like you
that can't fight,
it's not a good thing, James.
It's not a good thing
at all.
Right now, you in the
brothas-only section, man.
You got two seconds to get
your white ass out,
before you get
mollywhopped.
Okay, Darnell.
Who's Darnell?
You are.
My name is Leroy!
Yeah, I suggest you walk,
white boy.
All right.
Walk!
I'm walkin'.
Turn around and walk!
Hey, ésse.
What?
You got a problem, gringo?
Darnell,
what are you doing?
Darnell?
Who's Darnell, ésse?
You're lookin' at Carlos.
I suggest you walk wherever
you came from, ésse,
before you
have a problem.
I just was trying
to leave that area.
Okay, well, you need to go back
over there with the negros, ésse.
With Leroy?
You go back over there
with the negros!
'Cause that's
where you belong.
I don't see anyone.
Yeah, you belong with the negros.
Go.
I'm going.
Fuck you callin' a negro,
Carlos?!
He was. I wasn't.
I told you, Carlos!
Keep that shit over there
on your side!
Take that Yankee with you!
I'll go with you!
Hey, I don't want him.
I don't want him.
He's a negro lover.
You take him.
Why don't I...
Motherfucker, car...
Say somethin' else, bro!
Hey!
Hey, I swear to God.
Guys, please!
I swear to God,
I'll cut you, ésse.
Let's just shake hands.
There is no shaking hands, gringo.
Friendship.
You go back where you belong.
I don't know
where I belong.
Leave him alone. I'll keep him.
You belong with me.
W-who are you?
I'm Dante.
Why don't you
leave him alone, Carlos!
Leave him alone, Leroy!
Are you a woman?
I am if you want me to be.
I don't want that.
No, okay, I know what you are.
Let me hold your pocket.
All right.
I claimed him!
He mine, Leroy!
Bitch! You got two seconds to
let his fuckin' pocket go.
Two!
Oh!
Motherfucker! You got two seconds, bitch!
Don't hit a woman!
Gonna knock your ass out!
You don't want my pocket.
You don't want it.
So what?
Why can't I be happy?
Hey, essé.
I don't like you
and this domestic shit
in front of me
and my crew.
I don't...
You think I like it?
You need to fuckin' take it
somewhere else, essé.
Huh? Gringo, you take you
and your dirty bitch elsewhere.
I'll just go all the way over there.
Don't call me dirty, Carlos.
I wasn't dirty
when you was up in it.
I wasn't dirty then, was I?
You were dirty then.
You're dirty now, bitch.
So what?
You should be...
He ain't complainin'.
You should get tested.
No, I'm not complaining
because we have yet to have
any sort of interaction.
Mnh-mnh.
Tonight will be our night.
No, we won't.
Tonight won't happen.
Hey. Be my white knight.
Save me.
Don't get your hopes up.
Let me ride you.
R-ride me?
Let me ride you into safety.
No! I don't feel comfortable
with that.
Don't let them fight you
like that.
Let go of me!
Leroy is going to be upset.
I knew you were
coming back.
Motherfucker!
I knew you were coming back.
You making me mad,
motherfucker!
I'm not doing anything!
Motherfucker, I'm about to whoop
your ass, white boy!
That's it! That's it.
That's it, gringo.
I swear to God, I'm
getting sick of this shit.
I'll fuckin' stab you.
I'm still confused as to what piece
you are in this puzzle, Carlos.
Hold on!
Huh? What?
Question, question.
Are there any French gangs?
I speak French.
I'm not fluent, but I can...
Uh, je m'appelle James?
Can I join the gang,
s'il vous plait?
You know what, James?
You can't fight.
Being that you can't fight,
that means I'm left
with one choice,
and that's to get
your stupid ass in shape.
God!
You're failing.
I've got a state-of-the-art gym
40 feet away.
Ain't no gyms
in San Quentin.
♪ Little Sally Walker, ♪
♪ sittin' in a saucer ♪
curl me, bitch!
Curl me!
Maybe I should start with a baby
at higher reps.
Come on!
Hey!
Hey, you!
I wanna fight you.
What'd you say, dickhead?
I wanna fight you,
asshole.
♪ What to say the least ♪
let's just rest here.
Look at his face.
He looks like he's getting
fucked right now.
Oh, come on!
You better not drop me!
Goddamn it!
Excuse me, sir.
I hate to bother you,
but I need to fight you.
I was in 'Nam!
And I fuckin' loved it!
James, you gotta throw
somethin' back!
Aah! Darnell!
No... ohh!
Save me!
♪ Oh, shit! ♪
your training's
not going well, man.
I mean, frankly, I don't feel
like you're givin' me 100%.
And as your incarceration
expert, that concerns me.
'Cause it's my job
to prepare you.
Fortunately, I got a plan.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, that's good.
You're gonna learn
how to suck dick.
What?!
Oh, God.
Listen up.
I said I want you to learn
how to suck dick.
I heard you!
That's your plan?
Yes.
All I'm sayin'
is that when life
puts a dick in your mouth,
you make dickade.
"Dickade" doesn't sound like
a significant improvement
over dick.
Okay.
Bottom line, James...
I know what
I'm talkin' about.
We're talkin' about survival.
I understand.
'Cause that's how
you survived. Right?
No, you shut your mouth.
No, it is not.
I survived with these.
Dual hand jobs.
No. No!
I kill with these.
That's the difference
between me and you.
Hence, why you need
to suck a dick.
Come on, man.
Where am I gonna find
someone who...
We're at
the Ivars Brasserie.
Look around you.
This is L.A.'s number-one
gay hookup scene.
Voted "flirtiest brunch"
three years in a row.
But what do I say?
What do I literally say?
You say,
"I wanna suck your dick."
Politely.
"Hey, hi. I'm James.
You mind if I could give you
a little... a little head?"
Hey, I'm James.
"I wanna suck your dick."
I wanna suck your dick.
There you go!
Just dive in!
That's what they do.
What if someone says no?
He ain't gonna say no.
It's a scientific fact.
According to who?
Dickapedia! I don't fuckin'...
Why do you care?
Is that a real site?
No.
James, it's a figure...
Get up.
You're gonna go...
You're gonna go to that bar.
That guy.
That guy right there.
Get up, go over there,
and politely ask that man,
can you suck his dick?
Oh, my gosh.
I can't believe
I'm about to do this.
Survival.
Go survive.
All right.
I'll just go do it.
Yes, go do it.
Okay. Come on.
Are we doing this
or not, okay?
Yes,
we're definitely doing it.
Hey, I was nervous the first
time I did karaoke, right?
Yeah.
Just get up there and sing.
This is terrible foreplay.
Come on.
I'm gonna put it in my mouth.
Yeah.
I'm gonna suck your di...
Your di...
Yeah,
that's what we're here for.
I'll gonna put your di...
In my mouth.
I'm gonna give you hea...
Facial.
Down the hatch! Ha.
Eating alone?
I just thought you could use
some company.
Oh. O-okay,
I see what this is.
You... you think that you can...
That you can get with me?
Ooh, interesting topic of conversation.
Wait. No.
That wasn't a sit-down
invitation.
You're like...
You're like a 6.
Thank you.
No, it's not a compliment.
That's not a...
That's not a good number.
I'm like a 9.
If I were to get
into this game...
You know, the gay game...
Uh-huh.
By the way, the gay game
is a game you can win.
No, I-it's not,
'cause I don't wanna play.
I'm saying "if."
If I were to...
There's a spot on the bench
for ya, if you decide to join.
No, I'm not... I'm not...
On the bench, man.
Okay, starter!
I'm not gay, man.
I'm here supportin' a friend,
doin'... doin' some gay stuff.
I'm sorry.
My name is Chris.
It's short for Christmas
came early this year.
Where are you at, man?
Come on, man.
This is gonna help me
in the long run.
Here. Right there.
Ooh.
Don't point it at me.
Just...
Hey!
Have fun with it, right?
Yeah.
Have fun with it.
Come on.
Three, two, one! In the mouth!
Aah!
Look, you're gonna find
you someone, man.
You just gotta
set your sights
on something more realistic,
you know?
This is what
I need to hear.
Yes! Yes.
I can't do it.
I really tried.
I just... I just can't!
You have to train me.
It's my last chance.
Are you ready to train harder
than you've ever trained before?
Because once we go,
we do not hold back.
We do it,
and we do it hard!
Are you ready
to get hard?
I am ready.
I'm ready to get hard!
You're gonna show me
that you can get hard!
I'm gonna show you!
I'm gonna get so hard!
'Cause I'm gonna show you how hard!
That's what I wanna hear.
Then let's go home
and get hard.
♪ Whoa-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ whoa-oh-oh-oh ♪
I want what they have.
Yeah!
Yeah, James!
♪ The window's down, ♪
♪ let the whole world see ♪
Yeah!
That's what
I'm talkin' about!
Sho' enough!
Fear of dick sucking
will give a man strength.
♪ Kill 'em all, ♪
♪ kill 'em all ♪
fuck you.
Fuck cock!
Shit!
Hey, back off!
You better get those tits
out of my face!
Or I'll show you my tits!
What're you doin'?
Working on my trash talk.
You know, to get respect
from the other inmates.
Let me hear some of it.
Uh, all right.
Hey, pal.
I'm about to tear you a new ass.
You gonna have to do a little
better than that, James.
Hey, I'm about to tear you
a new ass.
And sew up your old ass!
Okay. All right.
I'm gonna punch you
in the fuck!
I'm gonna make you
my bitch's bitch!
You're gonna be
my grand bitch!
Yeah. You're about to
get 20 likes on instafuck.
If I see you
around here again,
I'm gonna put a hashtag
on your ass
and see how many hits
it gets.
Hmm?
Oh, my God.
Hope you brought
your Costco card,
'cause you're about
to get dick in bulk!
What?
This is so dark.
You eat organic?
How about fresh farm-to-table,
a purée of my balls!
Yeah.
Merry dickmas,
Santa cock!
Hmm?
Okay.
All right, man.
Where is this stuff
comin' from, James?
Hey, son. You're a
disappointment to your parents.
Who I fucked!
Oh, shit.
James, this is sick.
You gotta be crazy
to think of this.
That crazy is good.
Thank you.
I've got about six hours more.
That's good, James.
That's really good.
Okay.
I like that.
Good.
I like that a lot.
All right.
I hope you brought
your dick punch-card
'cause the eighth
dick is free.
Stab!
Ah, shit!
That's not bad, James.
That's not bad at all.
Progress.
Peter Piper picked a peck
of pickled cocks!
Yes.
Hey, hey, hey!
You ready
to get to work today?
Huh?
Hello.
What's all this stuff?
Oh, these are shanks.
Or "shivs."
In Scotland, they're referred to
as "chibs."
In fact,
I made this one for you.
Really?
Yeah.
Just to say thank you
for all the hard work.
Ah, man.
That's nice.
That's cool.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't... don't hold it
by the blade.
Haven't you ever
held one before? Right here.
Yeah, no, no, my cellie
used to hold 'em all the time.
I don't like 'em. I feel like
they cause too much trouble.
You pull that out on the yard,
somebody come out attack you,
they can do this to you.
Now what do you do?
You know what I mean?
Huh!
What the hell?!
Where'd that come from?
I taught myself
how to keister.
How to... Keister?
Yeah.
Up the keister?
Look.
The electronic toothbrush part,
it still works.
Oh, no.
Okay, James.
James, cut it off.
Cut it off.
Get it outta my face, man.
I can turn it on
with no hands.
I don't want to see that.
I don't want to see
that trick.
It's okay.
Put it back.
God.
Put it back?
No. No, no.
Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
Please.
Do you want me
to teach you how?
Nah, I'mma pass on that.
It starts with a simple
inverse inhale.
James, stop it.
That, with a simultaneous
relaxing of the sphincter.
Okay, I don't...
I don't wanna know.
You sure?
James, I'm... I'm positive.
I just wanna ask you
one question.
I was over there,
and I was touchin'...
I was touchin' all those shanks.
Yeah.
Were... were they...
Keistered?
Yeah. Were they...
Were they keistered?
Most of 'em.
Yeah.
We're about to simulate
a prison riot.
Understand that this is the most
dangerous situation there is.
Prisoners are scared.
Guards are scared.
The key to survivin'
is to not freak out.
Good lord.
What's gonna happen?
Cecelio's just gonna throw
some stuff at you.
Some roosters,
some mangly homeless guys,
whatever he's got.
He's really excited
about this.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Wait,
don't I get body armor?
No. We don't have
that type of time.
Cecelio!
Why don't we have
enough time?
James, remember,
do not freak out.
Lights! Music!
Who wants to party?!
Go! Go! Go!
Cecelio!
Release the chickens!
No, no, no, James!
Don't freak out!
Darnell, there's a baboon!
You're in my world now!
Someone let me out!
Stop freaking out!
It's fuckin' beautiful!
Oh, shit!
Die! Die!
Cecelio, turn it off!
Turn it off!
James, I've lost control!
Cecelio! Pull back!
I have lost control!
Oh, my God!
Ah, God!
Oh, my God.
Shit!
Ah! I'm stabbed!
No!
I'm cut!
No, you cut me, man!
You stabbed me!
No, I didn't!
Yes, you did!
I told you, don't freak out!
You freaked out!
God! Wait.
No, I'm okay.
Hold up.
It's just the wine.
I see all the wine, man.
I totally feel fine.
Oh, fuck!
What?
Oh! Don't...
Don't... don't...
That's where
the other one went.
Yeah, okay, just sit down.
It's a shiv.
It's just a shiv.
Yes, I know.
Hey, don't freak out.
I know.
I'mma pull it.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
It's like a fishhook.
The more you pull,
the deeper it lodges.
All right. Okay.
Look, my wife's a nurse.
Let's get you to my wife.
Okay?
God.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
It's sticking
right out of my head.
James, listen.
I don't want to look at it
no more
because I'm startin' to...
Oh, shit.
I'm so scared.
I know.
I just don't wanna...
Can you fuckin' just keep
your head...
Ohh!
Oh, God!
You drove it in
a little deeper.
Oh, God.
Oh, James, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Is my eye twitching?
No!
Answer the question.
Is my eye twitching?
It look fine.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Does it look fine?
Yeah, fine, man.
There's nothing wrong.
Let's play a memory game,
okay? Engage.
Yes.
What up?
Give me 12 months.
Months. One, two...
No.
Four...
Summer, Christmas...
What?
Baked potato...
What is "baked potato"?
Wait.
Did I leave one out?
No. You're right.
You're right.
Those are the months.
Thanks for driving me
to college, Dad.
What?
What the fuck?
But don't start crying when you
drop me off at the dorm,
'cause then
I'll start crying.
I love you, Dad.
Love...
Love you, too, man.
This is where
I need to get out.
James! James! No!
Close the door!
Are we at Coachella?
No, James!
Rita, thank you once again
for taking the knife
out of my head.
Mm.
Makayla, what...
Young lady.
But he's doing it.
This is delicious.
Okay, James.
Stop. Stop.
You don't have to eat like that.
You're on furlough.
Mm. Sorry.
It's part of my training.
If you let someone mess with
your food, you're a punk.
It's delicious, though.
Look, you need to shut
this stuff down right now.
Do you understand you're gonna
get him killed
before he even gets to prison?
What're you talking about?
No. Darnell's doing
a wonderful job.
He's a great teacher.
See that?
And a great friend.
The only thing
I can't figure out
is how he ever went to jail
in the first place.
Gosh, me neither.
You know, Darnell, have you
every shared with James
the story of
how you went away?
No, he hasn't.
Well, he's not really ready
for that right now.
And I got... and I got Makayla
at the table.
I mean, she's the daughter
of a convicted felon.
She's strong.
Mm-hmm.
Good point.
Why don't you tell it.
And don't leave out any details.
I-I'd love to hear it.
I think it could
really help me.
Okay.
Uh, we was... we was just
some boys in the hood.
Me, my man Ricky,
and Doughboy.
Doughboy's real name
was Russell.
We was close, man.
Ricky, thing about Ricky,
Ricky was special,
'cause Ricky had
the ticket.
Ricky was
star quarterback.
You know,
he had a college future.
He was our golden boy,
you know?
We got into it
with some other guys.
You know,
some gangbang stuff.
On the way home
we decide to split up.
Me and Doughboy said
we'll go this way.
Ricky said
he'll go this way.
Me and Doughboy come around,
we see Ricky on the ground.
Ricky got shot.
I run over there.
I'm runnin', I'm runnin'.
I grab him.
I got his head on my arm.
I'm lookin'.
I'm like, "Ricky!"
Ricky!
Aah!
Ricky.
He...
He had the ticket!
They got him.
Doughboy's like,
"come on, man. Get up.
Let him be.
He's done."
I get up.
Doughboy says,
"you know what this mean.
This mean we gotta step up."
Oh, no.
I said,
"you damn right, it does."
So we strapped up.
I don't know
what that means.
It means we got the burners.
I don't know
what that means.
It means we went
and got the guns.
We saw those guys
later that night.
Three head shots.
Bop! Bop! Bop!
"That's for Ricky!"
For sure.
Cops came, man.
I told Doughboy
I'd take the rap.
I said, "you go ahead.
Live your life.
I'll tell 'em it was me."
Cops came. I said, "I did it."
I went to jail.
You gave your life
and your freedom for Russell.
Loyal to a fault.
It is what it is.
That's why I wash cars today.
'Cause I got blood
on my hands.
Just like Lady MacBeth.
Huh?
Like MacBeth.
Yes.
Phew!
Wow, what a story.
Almost sounds like a movie.
- Whew.
- Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Darnell,
why don't you tell him
about that time that that white
lady came and adopted you...
And turned you
into an offensive tackle.
I think we've talked
enough tonight.
Oh, there's my cab.
I'd better get back
before lockdown
or Cecelio will put me
in the hole.
He loves putting me
Well,
let me walk you out, man.
No, that's fine.
Thanks for everything.
James, it was wonderful
meeting you.
Great to meet you, too.
You know, growing up,
my family would never spend
any time together like this.
You guys are very lucky.
Bye, Makayla.
Bye, Mr. King.
Bye-bye.
Hey, your dad never went
to jail, okay?
I've seen "Boyz n the Hood."
Who showed you
"Boyz n the Hood"?
Daddy,
I don't think he did it.
Of course he didn't.
You need to do something
that's really gonna help him.
He will not last in prison.
He wouldn't even last
in my school.
Hello, this is James.
Hey.
It's me, Darnell.
Look, man,
I've been thinking it over,
and I think it might be
a good idea
to get you some extra protection
on the inside.
So tomorrow were gonna go over
to my cousin Russell's house.
Now listen to me, James.
My cousin Russell
and his friends,
they're a different
type of dudes, man.
Very suspicious
of outsiders.
I mean,
you walkin' in there,
they're probably gonna think you
a cop off the bat.
So I need you to do
something for me
so we don't create any
dangerous situations.
Dress more casually.
Blackface.
What the fuck was that?
Uh, s-see you tomorrow.
James. James.
James, don't...
Don't do nothing stupid.
Just dress casual.
♪ Bitches ain't shit ♪
♪ and they ain't sayin' nothin' ♪
♪ a hundred motherfuckers ♪
♪ can't tell me nothin' ♪
♪ I beez in the trap, ♪
♪ be-beez in the trap ♪
♪ damn, damn, ♪
♪ what they say about me? ♪
♪ I don't know, man, ♪
♪ fuck is on your biscuit ♪
♪ if I get hits swingin' ♪
♪ on a big bitch ♪
♪ I don't know, man, I'm ♪
♪ shittin' on your whole life ♪
♪ damn, damn, ♪
♪ what they say about me? ♪
♪ I don't know, man, ♪
♪ fuck is on your biscuit ♪
nice whip.
What the hell
are you doin'?
Who you supposed to be
dressed like, James?
Little Wayne.
It's what he wore
at his last runway show.
Oh, lil Wayne.
You told me I needed
to try to fit in,
so I stayed up all last night
studying your culture.
I'm sorry, what?
And to those who say jazz
is the only indigenous
American art form,
I say listen to a little Jay z,
my friend.
Oh!
I forgot the gin and juice.
Should I run back inside?
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ yeah, I'm paranoid, ♪
♪ I'm trippin' ♪
♪ I've been smokin' ♪
♪ and sippin' ♪
♪ I'm... Around with two... ♪
♪ but I never made them... ♪
♪ My misses ♪
will you stop?
I-I'm not trying to appropriate
your culture.
That's great.
I'll tell the others.
I'm just saying, hip-hop
is a very sophisticated,
multifaceted subculture
that speaks to all
different types of people.
The music, the... the fashions,
the attitudes, the beefs...
The more I read,
the more I listened,
the more I felt connected
to its rich cultural tapestry.
That is really great.
Now, can we please be done
with this conversation?
Please stop.
I think I know
who killed Tupac.
♪ Pretty boy baby ♪
I got next!
What the fuck?
Hello.
I'm gonna put a cap
in yo ass.
Who the fuck are you?!
Yo, he's good.
He with me.
And who the fuck are you,
nigger?
Hey, Russ... Russell!
Russell.
Russell!
'Scuse me.
Hello.
James King, senior fund manager,
Wealthrop Funds.
James, come on.
Excuse me.
Right through here.
Hell naw, man.
Is this the motherfucker
who you said you had to get
ready for prison, man?
Well, I-I need...
I need protection,
and I'm hoping to join
the Crenshaw Kings.
Are you?
Hey, I've seen
white people before.
My probation officer is white.
You know what I'm saying?
But you, motherfucker, man,
you...
You white as mayonnaise, man.
Oh, shit. Maybe in blackface.
Who knows?
Hey, listen.
I tell you what, though.
You damn sure got
your get-up right, man.
I mean, camouflage
and cheetah print,
that's straight out
the gangbanger's handbook.
Yeah, yeah,
like... like lil Wayne, right?
Exactly.
Thank you.
I love it.
Look, he's not trying
to be a member, okay?
H-he just wants you to protect
him while he's on the inside.
L-like you did for Darnell
when he took the rap for you.
What?
That's... we can talk about that
another time.
Yeah.
No.
So let's let that go.
Y-you remember.
You know.
With what Ricky did
and the ticket...
No.
And you freaked out
and Darnell took control
of the situation.
Stop.
Is this motherfuckin'...
"Boyz n the Hood," man.
This is a bad time.
Okay, I tell you what, man.
I tell you what: Humor me.
I'm a fair person.
And I'm a businessman.
Clear professional.
What's your life worth
to you?
How does a million dollars
sound?
"How does
a million dollars sound?"
Hold up, everybody.
Stand back.
I'll handle it.
How does a million dollars
sound?
Man, a million dollars sound
like a one with six zeros
behind it with two commas
separating them.
However, from the sound of CNN
and the looks of
The Wall Street Journal
and everybody else that people
with eyes and ears
go to get they news,
you broke, motherfucker.
Your assets have been frozen
with no chances of thawing
anytime soon.
So you probably got as much
or less
than this little no good,
manipulative,
degenerate motherfucker
right here next to you.
Which forces me
to ask the question,
"are you fuckin' with me?"
You think this
a motherfuckin' game?
You think I'm playin'?
Why would you come up
in my hood,
in my house, man, and present
yourself as somethin' you not,
offerin' shit you know
you can't deliver?
Did this motherfucker tell you
to lie to me?
Russ.
Shut the fuck up, man.
I think, real fast,
you need to tell me
what the fuck
you gonna do
to make me wanna keep
motherfuckers off your ass.
You're talking
to James King.
Let me create wealth
for you.
So the normal minimum buy-in to
the nexel fund is $5 million,
but I can get you guys in using
a brokerage pocket account.
In other words, liquidate
two bricks of cocaine
and park it right here.
Now, with the historical
performance of the fund,
that's gonna double
every three to five years,
and we're looking at
$1.2 million easy.
Ain't no way you're making
that much money
without committing a crime.
With apologies to Balzac.
You pussy.
What the fuck?
You talkin' about
my ballsack, nigger?
No.
W-what we're gonna do is we get
other people's money
who've made an opposite
prediction on the market.
Okay, we gonna roll on them
and take they money.
Just how strapped are
these loser motherfuckers?
Oh, I-I wouldn't worry.
I've taken millions from them,
and they haven't stepped
to me, yet.
Loser motherfuckers.
Damn.
Mayo is badass.
Stock market is gangster.
Take what's yours and fuck
the other guy, right?
Wall Street, man.
Those are the real criminals.
Those guys get away
with murder.
Wait, man. You murder people
all the time, black.
Oh, yeah.
Murder's my favorite.
You should know,
you did a'ight this time.
Your boy Mayo
is an earner.
Are you gonna get him some help
on the inside?
I'll help him.
But not with us.
You know,
inside it's all about color.
Dude need a white gang.
A very white gang.
But I'll put
the play together.
♪ We can't be stopped now ♪
♪ 'cause it's bad boy for life ♪
That's... that's the gang
I have to join?
They seem kind of racist.
Ain't no "kind of."
They are.
That's the alliance of whites.
That's also your only chance
of survival in prison,
so you need to go in there
and you need to make them
believe
that you're one of them.
Matter of fact,
call me the n-word.
But say it like you
mean it, though.
Let me hear it.
What?
No.
That's the wrong "n-word."
Come on, James, I'm giving you
a free pass right now.
In this truck,
the "n-word" is perfectly fine.
Just another word right now.
Go ahead.
That still doesn't feel...
All right, let's try this.
What's that place
where your leg bends?
My knee?
Okay.
And what noise does
a angry dog make?
Grr?
Put it together, though.
Knee. Knee grr.
Ow!
Oh, shit!
I'm sorry.
I am sorry, man,
that just... that happened.
That literally
just happened.
Wow, I got you good, too.
It just, like, jumped out, man.
It was a reflex.
I-I really can't tell you.
I didn't even say it.
I was saying two other words.
I apologize, James.
What do you want me to do?
Just get your ass out the car
and go in there, act hard.
Fit in, man.
Go ahead.
Cut the light off!
Shit!
Fuck yeah!
Spider, you're up.
Watch and learn, son.
Hi.
Uh, if I could have
your attention, please.
I'm just looking for someone
by the name of spider?
He's a narc!
Listen...
This relationship can't just be
built around him.
I mean, you got a right to be
happy, too, you know?
And I am, I am.
And I think I'm open to it
now because of our talk.
Yeah. That's good.
I love the fact that you're
listenin'. I love that.
You know, you're the best
boyfriend I never had.
Okay.
Yeah, well,
I'm not totally giving up.
There is time.
And things change with time.
No, no, they don't.
No. No, no.
That's never gonna happen.
You say that now.
No, no, no.
I'm always gonna say that.
Okay.
Aw, shit.
Hey, I... I gotta go, okay?
So I'll talk to you later.
Have fun.
Private club, Jew hair.
Good one, spider.
I walked right into that one.
Uh, James King.
Protestant.
But, uh, Russell,
from the Crenshaw Kings,
referred me?
Yeah, Russell said
you'd be by.
Anyway, I'm going to prison
and I need protection.
Well, welcome to the club,
Jimbo.
Great! Oh, good!
But you get protection from us,
we got rules.
Principles.
Rule number one:
When you're on the inside,
you don't hang out with
the niggers or the spics.
Now, do you have a problem
with that, brother?
Me?
O-of course not.
Spider...
What do you take me for?
I'm a big-time racist.
I hate the knee.
What?
What is this shit?
I mean, heck,
I'm such a racist
that my chess set,
I only have white pieces.
It's confusing, but I don't...
I won't give the blacks
a chance to win.
Oh, shit.
He's a fucking cop.
He's a cop!
I smell bacon.
I'm not a cop.
Fuckin' hate narcs.
We'll find out what he is.
Oh, God. Shit, shit, shit, shit,
shit. Oh, my God.
I'm just wondering if maybe
I'm not the best fit
for the Alliance of Whites.
You got anything to confess
before I rip your face off?
Fine! Go ahead!
Kill me!
But please tell the world
I'm not a thief!
I did not do the things
they said I did!
Promise me, spider!
Promise me!
Burn him.
Aah!
The fuck was that?!
That's right!
A black man just came in
with a flamethrower,
just like you
always knew would happen!
Yeah!
The devil in here, bitch!
And he's a black man.
Stay yo ass back!
Stay back!
James! Let's go!
Yeah.
You all right?
Yeah. Come on.
Come on.
Come on, let's go.
You know what?
I got something I wanna say
to y'all since I'm guessin'
this is the first time
that you've ever been forced
to listen to a black man.
You know, maybe you guys
should just calm the fuck down.
Black people ain't tryin'
to hurt you!
I mean, technically,
I am right now.
But that's only because of
what you were tryin' to do
to the white guy.
Think about that!
Google "I have a dream,"
assholes!
It's a teachable moment here,
people.
Should burn everybody
in here.
Run, James!
Oh, shit!
Bring me their fucking heads!
Run, James! Run!
What the fuck are you
knocking over the bike for?
Run!
Oh, God.
You just couldn't say
"nigger," huh?
What?!
You can't see the irony
in being mad at me about that?
No!
Motherfucker!
It's Nazi titties!
And they're huge!
Get out!
Oh, shit!
Bitch,
get your white ass off!
Goddamn it!
Oh, go, go, go!
You blew up my club,
Jew hair!
Oh, shit!
Post-racial America,
assholes!
Fuck you, Nazis!
Yeah!
I'm so glad to be back in
Crenshaw where it's safe.
My heart is just now
finally settling.
Yeah.
We're... we're alive.
How 'bout we make a toast
to escaping fucking Nazis.
Yes.
You really are innocent,
aren't you?
Yes. Absolutely.
Okay, so, James,
if that's the case,
then why aren't you tryin'
to find the guy that framed you?
We are.
Who are?
Now, Martin has a team
of investigators
working around the clock.
He's keeping me up to date.
But the million-dollar
question is:
Who falsified
my transaction records?
All right, lay it on me.
All right.
Now, this is very complicated
to follow.
I don't expect you to get it
on the first pass,
so listen very carefully.
The one thing you need
to understand
at the Wealthrop Fund
is that everything flows
through Martin.
Okay?
Okay.
Any sort of contact with the
clearing house, the traders,
access to trading records
and client information,
international accounts,
institutions,
and, of course, the doling out
of commissions
all goes through Martin.
So it's Martin.
No.
Are you fucking ki...
It's common sense, James.
Look!
All arrows point to Martin!
The only name on the board
is fuckin' Martin!
Martin! Martin! Martin!
Come on!
James, you need to focus.
You're goin' to prison
unless you can prove
that Martin did it.
Then we'd need to get a hold
of the master records,
which is a log of all
transactions made
by anyone in the firm.
Okay, how do we get it?
Martin has the original copy
on the same computer that he had
when he started the company.
You got to be the dumbest genius
I've... get up, James!
All right.
Fuck the board!
Let's go, James!
We're going to Martin's office.
Act natural, James.
You walkin' like you guilty.
Hey, big guy,
you catch the game?
Yeah.
Hey, big guy,
my name is Ken.
I work here.
Okay. Okay.
It's in this cabinet.
We just have to
figure out a way to
get the door open.
Watch out.
I got it.
Ah. There it is.
Same computer he had
when he started the company.
It's a good luck charm.
Good luck charm, my ass.
It has no connection
to the outside world.
No e-mails, no Internet,
no trace.
There it is!
The master records!
That's what we need.
This will clear my name.
Oh, well, then let's not waste
time. Get it.
Yes!
I'm not going to prison.
More importantly, I'm not gonna
be anyone's bitch.
Hey, you are livin' the dream,
my friend.
Darnell?
Yeah?
Look, you saved my life.
I don't know how I'll ever
repay you.
Oh, come on, man.
Just this once.
All right, break it up.
Leave the cart there
and back away.
Move away, come on.
Move, move.
I actually respect you
for trying,
but enough is enough, James.
All right.
What are you doin'?
James, what are you doing?
Don't mad-dog, James.
He's gonna shoot us.
What the fuck?
No.
He's gonna kill us, man.
Do you want some?
Oh, fuck!
Do you wanna step with me?!
Aw, God!
You'd better... don't...
Oh, shit!
The gun!
Grab the gun!
Huh?
Why don't you pick up
the gun!
Uh...
Grab it!
Yeah. I got it, I got it!
I got it.
Yeah, I got it.
You look a little nervous.
First time holdin' a gun?
Nope.
Motherfucker, freeze!
'Fore I pop yo ass!
"Pop"? Really?
I would listen to him.
This man's a dangerous felon.
Yeah, except
when I ran his record,
it was the cleanest one
I'd ever seen.
Not even a parking ticket.
Yeah.
What?
You didn't know?
Yeah.
Stop dickin' around
and give me the gun.
- Come on.
- Give me the gun.
I think you have
the safety on.
Shit!
See? Safety's on.
Safety off.
Martin was right.
You are a lucky little shit.
Don't give me reason
to find you again.
Either of ya.
Don't you mad-dog me,
James.
Listen, listen, I got some
explainin' to do.
James!
We can talk about this
after we go catch this guy.
You traitor!
"Traitor"?
Everything you taught me
was a lie!
And now I'm fucked
beyond all fucktitude!
M-my life's asshole
is... is fucked!
You stop with your unorthodox
style of cussin'!
You just remember:
Whatever happens to me in
there, it's your fault!
Oh, stop.
That's bullshit, man.
Okay, I may have lied to you
about goin' to jail,
but I did my job.
I got you ready!
Ready for what?!
Maximum-bullshit prison?
I almost sucked a dick
because of you!
I don't even give a shit.
It's my sign.
♪ The world is mine ♪
♪ nigger, get back ♪
♪  don't fuck with my stack  ♪
♪ the gauge is racked ♪
♪ about to drop the bomb, ♪
♪ I'm they motherfuckin' don ♪
I honestly don't
get the difference
between Roth and the
traditional IRA's.
Fuck is wrong wit' you?
The shit is pretax.
No, no, no, it's okay.
A lot of people get confused
by that.
No, this bitch is gonna mess
around and get us audited.
Say what you mean, son.
You got five years' receipts,
motherfucker?
And the strip club
ain't no home office!
That's a red flag, nigga!
Hey, hey, hey!
You big beanbag-build bitch!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
stop it! You all friends!
Right?
Now, Jojo,
you might be right.
A strip club
isn't a home office.
You're askin'
to be audited, son.
But is being right more
important than friendship?
Huh?
Take it from me.
I lost my black friend.
Don't lose yours.
Hug.
Hug, motherfuckas!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, man.
I'll love you forever.
Hey, bro, you
know, it's just talk.
Say, cuz, you ready to get put
on the hood?
I'm rollin'.
♪ Bow down ♪
♪ when I'm westward bound ♪
♪ bow down ♪
Mayo...
I need you to sink
your mind into this, cuz.
Once you step through
this threshold,
motherfuckers are ready
to kill for you.
I mean a whole fraternity
of motherfuckers
gonna have your back.
But there's only one way
outta this.
That's when your casket
drops into the ground.
So from this day forward,
you have eternal protection
until your eternal demise.
We dead-ass serious
about what we do.
And if you go through
that threshold
and you make it back,
we gonna be dead-ass serious
about you.
Time to smoke some fools.
Crenshaw Kings for life,
motherfucker.
Hmm. Almost.
Let's roll.
Hey.
You come back safe.
I will, Shonda.
We gotta go, Mayo.
Bye, baby.
Let's roll, cuz.
Ho! Hold up!
Oh, shit!
Wait, wait, wait!
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
Hey!
It's Darnell!
What the fuck
are you doin' here?
Shit, cousin! Man, tell 'em
to put their guns down!
Man, put 'em up.
God!
What is your problem, man?
What are you doin'?
Man, give us a second.
I'm bloodin' in.
Crenshaw Kings are gonna protect
me on the inside.
So you're gonna go
and kill somebody, James?
Have you lost
your fucking mind?
I have to.
I don't have a choice.
That is not true.
I came here to tell you...
We can clear your name, James.
But you gotta
trust me, man.
We gotta roll, Mayo.
"Mayo"?
Who... who the fuck is Mayo?
I'm Mayo.
It's my gang name.
It's short for "mayonnaise,"
on account of my skin color.
I came up with that.
Okay, you wanna go, then?
What?
You wanna go?
What are you doing?
Putting fingerprints all on your gun.
That way, if you go to jail,
I'm goin' to jail wit' you.
So before you go out there
and make a stupid-ass decision,
why don't you
think about that?
Yeah. There you go.
That's... that's it?
My fingerprints are off
that easy?
Yeah, pretty much.
Good as new.
Let's roll, Mayo.
James, you got a choice
right now.
You got the right path,
you got the wrong path.
Make the right decision,
James.
Follow your heart, man.
James, you gotta trust me
on this one.
Oh, my God!
I almost did it!
I almost killed a man!
And I was gonna use
this gun.
Hey, James,
put that away, man!
Stop!
What is your problem?
I don't know.
They just... they were
just encouraging me,
and they were
high-fiving me.
They're passing me
this sticky icky.
And between the pot
and the hos...
It was just an ambrosia
of primal sensations.
And for one brief moment,
I knew what my purpose was.
Okay, okay.
Not to mention Russell.
He's so charismatic.
Real natural leader.
Reminds me of a young
Ronald Reagan.
Hey.
Thank you for coming back
for me.
Thanks for not doin'
nothin' stupid, man.
Let's get out of here.
All right, so listen to this.
I figured out that the residue
on Martin's car was saltwater.
Then I remembered
the mileage.
Reason being,
I used to take a picture
of the odometer all the time
to keep people from accusing me
of joyridin'.
People do that?
That's awful.
Yeah, you did it
like three times.
You tried to get me fired,
but you thought my name
was Andre.
Anyway, look:
Martin used to drive
the same exact seven Miles
every day.
But last week, he started
driving 56 Miles every day.
56!
So, what I did was,
I checked the map.
Turns out
that's the exact distance
of a round trip
to San Pedro.
Saltwater,
ocean, San Pedro.
I just gotta figure out
why he's going to San Pedro.
That's the only thing
I don't know.
His yacht.
It's docked at the port.
Fucker's got a yacht?
Mm-hmm.
And an island in Cape Verde,
where there are no
extradition laws.
Fucker's got a yacht
and a island, James?
Fucking working for a villain
in a James Bond movie!
He's gonna make a run
for it.
Not if Mayo can stop him.
Mayo and chocolat.
"Chocolat"?
Chocolat.
Is that... is that supposed
to be my nickname?
That's your nickname.
I'll do better.
We have the whole car ride.
Mayo and... Coffee.
Mayo and fudge.
I don't want one.
Just call me Darnell.
Hit it, fudge!
There it is.
There's his boat.
The Sea Note.
The Sea Note?
What a dick.
Come on.
Get down, James.
You gotta get down.
Are those guards?
I think so.
There's a lot of 'em.
Yeah.
Oh, there's the computer.
I see it.
James, you gotta get low!
Oh, no.
They're gettin' ready to leave.
Shit.
We gotta jump.
All right.
What are you...
Get off my hand!
Sorry, I'm nervous.
Let's go!
Aah! Ohh.
Darnell!
I made it!
Ohh!
Let go of my face!
That's all you, James.
All you, James!
Okay.
Come on, this way.
Ah! There it is.
Come on.
Let's go.
Oh, shit!
Get off!
Damn it.
This is the end, guys.
You going down.
That's great.
I spend my whole life
in Crenshaw,
and now I'm about
to get killed
by some white guy
from Beverly Hills?
On a yacht!
I'm so sorry.
Hand over the computer,
James.
Come on. Just can't get it
through your head, hmm?
Guys like you will always be
the fall guy 'cause you're weak.
Are you... are you okay?
James? James?
No. James, please.
Goddamn, James.
Please, please, James.
I sentence you to ten years
in a maximum security prison.
You about to get this:
Oh, they be fuckin'
in San Quentin.
John Mayer in this house?
Mouth full of balls.
Come back, Mayo.
Take it all.
When life puts a dick
in your mouth,
you make dickade.
Go suck a dick.
Your Capoeira's strong!
Now you must bring your power
into the world.
What? James.
What are you doin'?
I've been pushed around
for too long.
Now it is time.
I can feel it.
Time for what, James?
Protect the computer!
Oh, shit!
I don't want the computer!
Bencao kick!
What?
Ataque!
Oh, God!
Leave me alone!
Stop! No!
James! James!
Tudo bem!
All right, get down there.
Come on.
Tudo bem!
Axé!
Mayo and chocolat,
motherfuckers!
James, you mean to tell me
you could do this shit
the whole time?
Capoeira must never be used
unless Capoeira is required.
Let's go.
Motherfuckers!
Okay!
Beleza!
Come here!
That's what we do!
Mother... get off!
James.
Do like we used to do
in the yard.
Yeah!
You got it, James.
Fuck yeah, James.
Get his ass, James.
God.
I got the computer.
Lifeboat. Come on.
All right.
Hey, that Capoeira shit
was amazing.
But you learned some-a
that shit from me too.
Right, James?
What's goin' on here?
What the hell did you do
to my boat?
Man, fuck this boat!
We taking the evidence
that you framed
your son-in-law with,
you sick son of a bitch.
How could you do this
to me, Martin?
Ten years in prison?!
James, you realize
that I didn't mean
to hurt you.
I'm very fond of you,
but Himalayan Tiger tanked
and I had to get the money
from somewhere.
I had no choice.
It was you or me.
That sounds like a choice!
James, fuck him.
We're leaving.
And next time you wanna store
some fraud shit, get an iPad.
Come on, James.
Oh, my damn.
Alissa.
James!
Daddy, what's he doing here?
It's fine, honey.
Uh, James.
I have a wonderful idea.
Why don't you come with us.
We'll start a whole new life
in Cape Verde,
and nobody has to go to prison.
Don't you want...
A big, big island?
Were you in on this?
No, not at first.
And when he told me about it,
I was really mad at him.
But then he explained
how he was
able to hide most
of the money, so, really,
there's no harm done.
James, now, there's still time
to get everything you want.
Everything.
No!
I don't want any of it.
And you got a white girl's ass.
Thattaboy.
Hey, James, do you wanna
switch off, man?
I got nothin' left up top.
Quick, throw it in the Zodiac.
Right. Then we can get the fuck
outta here.
Shit!
Goddamn it!
I am genuinely sorry it had
to end this way.
When we clear the breakwater,
shoot 'em.
You ain't got to do this, man.
You ain't got to do this.
Well, Dad,
looks like you thought of
everything, didn't you?
You were always
one step ahead of me.
Except you forgot
one little detail.
Where'd that come from?
First rule
in prison pat-downs:
Always check the anus.
Someone learned how to keister.
Ew.
That's right.
Nuts and butts.
You point? Okay.
That's how you wanna do it?
You point at him.
I'll point at Martin.
Either way.
So if I die, Martin's goin'.
So you figure it out.
Shoot me, Martin gets shot.
You're gonna...
Ball's in your court, Gayle.
Alissa? Huh?
Shoot her.
Sh-shoot her. You need to shoot
that bitch anyway.
You're not gonna shoot me.
You're wasting time.
Police'll be here any second.
That's right.
We're talkin' the real police.
The ones that's gonna
come here on boats...
Uh-huh.
With sirens on 'em...
That's got dogs that can swim.
Let me tell you somethin'
about swimmin' dogs.
Now, let me tell ya, you're
gonna bullshit a bullshitter,
just make the bullshit
plausible.
This is the U.S.
Marshal Service.
Prepare to be boarded.
You are carrying a fugitive.
Yes!
Hell yeah.
Oh, shit.
How?
Remember this bracelet
that crooked lawyer of yours
gave me?
By my calculation we should be
well outside the county line.
Prison school's in
session, bitch.
And somebody
just graduated.
That's perfect.
That's great, right?
Yeah.
Attention, Sea Note.
This is the U.S.
Marshal Service.
Where you goin'?
Yeah, where you goin?
Huh, Martin? What?!
Look at you, man!
I know.
God, look at you!
Where did you put...
That was in your ass.
Yep.
The computer proved
I was innocent.
Martin was arrested for fraud,
tampering with evidence,
and obstruction of justice.
And I will be contacting
my attorney. Daddy?
As for me, I was cleared
of all charges
related to the embezzlement.
So I guess we did it.
Mayo and chocolate.
Thank God we won't be needin'
this anymore.
This illegal, unlicensed gun.
Okay, James. You know, you should
really get rid of that thing.
- Gun!
- Drop it!
Oh, shit.
Uh...
I did end up getting six months
for carrying an
unlicensed weapon.
But, thanks to Darnell,
I was ready.
Martin didn't do as well.
But he learned
a valuable lesson, too.
They be fuckin' in San Quentin.
How ya doin'?
A whole lotta fuckin'.
Hey! Open up.
Open up.
♪ Bubble butt ♪
♪ bubble, bubble, bubble butt ♪
♪ bubble butt ♪
Shonda visited me every day.
I never thought prison
would be the place
I learned to love again...
But that's what happened.
No, no, no!
Wait!
She's not done.
She hasn't finished yet.
No, it's not what you think.
We're in love.
Yeah. I know.
Stand up.
I helped the FBI find and return
all the assets Martin stole.
In return, they unfroze
my bank accounts,
and I knew just where
to invest my money.
♪ Come on, come on ♪
♪ that's just the way it is ♪
It's good?
It's good, right?
♪ Things will never be the same ♪
Makayla,
you proud of daddy?
Daddy did good?
Gimme a hug.
♪ That's just the way it is ♪
♪ oh, yeah ♪
Daddy, I like your car wash.
I'm glad you like it, sweetie.
♪ That's just the way it is ♪
♪ things will never be the same ♪
♪ that's just the way it is ♪
♪ oh, yeah ♪
♪ you gotta make a change ♪
♪  it's time for us as a people ♪
♪ to start making some change ♪
I see you survived.
I guess you got hard, Mayo.
No.
You made me hard.
Come here, man.
So hard.
You got me so hard.
I'm happy to see you too,
big fella.
I'm happy to see you.
There was a moment
when I stopped being hard...
But I thought of you,
and it got me hard again.
And I can't ever thank you.
All right.
Welcome home, man.
Come on,
let's get in the car.
You look good, James.
♪ Come on, come on ♪
♪ that's just the way it is ♪
Welcome back to the
free world, James.
How you wanna celebrate?
You know what I'd like
to get my hands on?
A Wall Street Journal
and a 40.
Now that'd be
a perfect Sunday morning.
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ some things will never change ♪
♪ I go hard ♪
♪ seen you running down ♪
♪ the electric boulevard ♪
♪ get up out of my biz ♪
♪ before the problem starts ♪
♪ if you want to act tough, ♪
♪ then meet me in the yard ♪
♪ 'cause I go hard ♪
♪ Gotta angry mob ♪
♪ at your front door ♪
♪ commandin' 360 o's ♪
♪ at the condo ♪
♪ put all the jewelry ♪
♪ in the back with the bankroll ♪
♪ or else your momma gon' be ♪
♪ mourning like Alonzo ♪
♪ I go hard ♪
♪ seen you running down ♪
♪ the electric boulevard ♪
♪ get up put of my biz ♪
♪ before the problem starts ♪
♪ if you want to act tough, ♪
♪ then meet me in the yard ♪
♪ 'cause I go hard ♪
♪ What you think about it now? ♪
♪ never mind, ♪
♪ don't want to talk about it ♪
♪ never spit when I look ♪
♪ in the eyes of a man ♪
♪ and your words are as good ♪
♪ as the lies of a man ♪
♪ now, would you pardon me? ♪
♪ I go hard ♪
♪ seen you running down ♪
♪ the electric boulevard ♪
♪ get up out of biz ♪
♪ before the problem starts ♪
♪ if you want to act tough, ♪
♪ then meet me in the yard ♪
♪ 'cause I go hard ♪
♪ 'cause I go hard  ♪