Cash only.
Sybil 2007 (remake)
Based on the book of Flora Schreiber
*** *** Virtualnet translation and sync - rufino_castro Moroka San TAPC
Watch your step.
On February 26, 1998, a reclusive woman named
Shirley Ardell Manson, died of cancer in Lexington, Kentucky.
The contents of your home was sold at auction.
Three days later someone discovered his secret.
New York City, November 2, 1957.
Excuse me.
I am so sorry.
Do not worry. That things happen.
No. No. It was really my carelessness.
Be careful not to cut yourself.
You broke it.
You do not need to go.
MS. Dorsett?
Too late. Too late...
Philadelphia???
- Number? - Operator.
I would like to make a connection to the distance to the city of New York.
- Kondaic 50134 - Please insert 50 cents.
Please enter 50 cents.
- Hello? Hello, are you there? - Yes I am here.
Thank you.
Hello?
- Stan. - Sybil, what happened?
- I do not know, I'm sorry. - We should have dinner last night.
I went to his apartment,
- You do not ... - I'm in Philadelphia.
What are you doing there?
- I do not ... - Sybil?
Sybil?
MS. Dorsett? It has a message for you.
- November 7? - What did you say?
How long have I been here?
We will see.
You registered on the 2nd.
This is the sixth night.
Here, this is for you.
Now, when you go to your room, take a nice hot bath.
I was very worried about you out there with this storm.
I tried to warn you: do not go out there, but you would not listen.
broken glass?
I can not pay for it.
crystal Broken
Too late...
Sybil why you left school and gone for a week?
I was a little nervous, that's all.
If you are nervous school recommends that you see a psychiatrist ...
... before accepting you back.
I'm sorry.
You do not have to apologize Sybil. It is a matter of disease.
Disease?
It seems that you suffer from "Cat Syndrome" ...
... a woman's disease.
The Greeks describe how wild feeling.
Sometimes they call hysteria.
Do you suffer from amnesia, severe headaches.
In addition to his brilliance, his IQ is 170, it is very bright.
My mother was much brighter.
You nãopensa much of yourself ...
...first of all.
Have you thought about suicide?
Oh, I would never do that.
I do not want to go to hell. Because if I go to hell.
I will not see my mother in heaven my mother was a saint, you know?
Well, in short.
Nothing seems to be wrong with you physically.
So I suggest you do psychoanalysis.
Psychoanalysis?
I can not be more patient, but I have a colleague who would ...
- devil's work. - What?
My father does not approve of psychoanalysis.
Why that?
Doctors use drugs and hypnosis and all kinds of things ...
to make you say what they want you to say.
I do not believe that Dr. Wilbur would.
- It will ask you questions ... - She?
She.
Damn I have no time.
I have customers all I can handle.
I also have a commitment as a teacher.
Understand that I'm already full schedule the way it is.
What are you talking? Would only be 45 minutes per week.
You will like. She's from the Midwest, like you.
Montana is not in the Midwest.
Now let's Connie, you're the best lady, psychoanalyst, that time has created.
Oh, that's because I'm a lady, or I'll take care of ladies?
It's going to be easy. I promise.
It is only slightly hysterical. You're good with it.
I really need to go. I appreciate that.
If you have any problem just let me know.
Sybil?
Oh, how are you? I'm Dr.. Wilbur.
Please come in.
Here, sit down, sit down.
I like to record the sessions, for my own reference.
At the end all the tapes will be returned to you, of course.
You do not mind, right?
No problem.
Well, Dr. Atcheson came to me talk a little bit about you.
His family is from Wisconsin?
Little Conner.
It appears to be small.
And is.
I came to New York to study Arts.
A big change.
Yes. I bet you do.
Do you miss Little Conner?
Who should not.
It was perfectly wonderful.
I had a wonderful childhood.
And friends.
special friends as Tommy Ewold.
- Let's jump. - What?
It was my first great friend.
- Let's go. - No.
Do you still have family there?
My dad.
My mother died very recently, and I was an only child.
I'm sorry to hear that.
It must have been difficult for you?
Oh gone.
I took care of her and in the end ...
... we were never very close.
Even when...
... she was dying.
Peggy Louisiana!
What was Mom?
I am so sorry. I was very rude to you.
What she meant by that?
Sybil?
What she meant when she said ...
... so rude to you?
Well, I do not know.
She was a wonderful woman.
A saint. We were with sisters.
Oh, I thought you said you were not very close.
Oh, but we were.
She took me to all the places where she was going.
We were always together.
You see, my mother was over 40 when she had me ...
... right after the other baby died.
I almost died too. I weighed only 2.5 kilograms.
And she was worried about me all the time.
My father was also concerned. He was a busy man ...
... he was a builder in the city. He built the church we were going.
You believe in God?
You believe?
Of course.
Are you Catholic? My mother would not approve if you are not Catholic.
Why not?
I did not intend to offend ...
... is that my mother does not approve most people ...
... and I was very unhappy ...
... understand that I am far from being the perfect type ...
- ... friends do not want ... - Sybil!
You come telling me what you think ...
... of all things ...
... but I wonder how you feel about yourself.
Sybil ...
...how do you feel?
Not very well.
Since wee I've always been very sick, but not ...
What do you mean?
People said I was doing things I had not done.
Like what?
Well, sometimes I found people I had never seen before,
they said they knew me.
And sometimes I find clothes ...
I did not remember having bought hanging in my closet.
Or paintings ...
I began ...
... and when he came home, I found them completed,
but in a completely different style ...
...like this.
Who is Peggy Lou Baldwin?
I've never heard.
My mother used to call me Peggy Louisiana ...
... when I was a little girl.
And Mrs. Baldwin was my favorite teacher in school, but ...
I did not draw it.
And where did you come from then?
I found in my room in Philadelphia, when I ...
What were you doing in Philadelphia?
I do not know.
Excuse me.
- No, no, no. - Excuse me.
Get one.
Thanks.
Stan said I need to be more disciplined.
Who is Stan?
My boyfriend.
He is a mathematics graduate student.
He is wonderful and understanding, I know that when we get married ...
everything will be alright.
Will?
He does not want to see me.
I know it's my fault, but it still hurts a lot.
What are you talking about?
Stan ...
... he left me in the gentlest way possible ...
... because he's a wonderful man.
Sybil,
you noticed, that changed completely subject to ...
... we were talking about a minute ago?
He left me this letter.
Oh my God.
What's it?
- They did it again. - What?
Time ran. and does not do it for everyone, do?
Sybil, what do you mean by the time go?
- What happened? - I do not know.
I do not know what happened.
I'm here, then I'm not, then I'm new and all ...
... things are so different, people are different.
And you can not trust them, you can not ...
... you really, really ...
- I want to go out, let me out! - Sybil!
No!
Stop it.
Be careful, be careful.
Let me see your hands.
What about the window? You do not care about her?
Of course not.
The windows can be repaired, much more easily than people.
It's all right.
Are you alright. Come, sit down.
Sit down, dear.
-'s blood. - Where?
Sybil not, do not. See, there's no blood.
In Grandma's bed, just before she died.
And in the hay, the barn, where Tommy was killed.
Let's jump.
What?
- Let's jump. -. That's not silly, Tommy.
Thus.
Tommy !!!
He dropped the fork and he was dead.
And I stayed there until the doctor arrived, because I did not want to leave him ...
lying there like I did with my grandmother.
She was bleeding when I went to call for help ....
the doctor came and took me from there ...
would not let me see her when she died, oh dear God ...
Grandma, please do not leave me, do not leave me.
Sybil! Sybil!
Sybil?
Look at me.
Can you tell me more about your grandmother?
You can say how you felt when you were living with her?
Why do you care?
- You do not care. - Sybil, I care.
You're just trying to trick me.
Many people deceive me,
many people and they deceived.
I feel so bad when they deceive me.
Who are you?
Sybil.
No, you're not.
- You can see the differences? - Oh, you can bet.
You can bet I can.
What's your name?
Peggy. Peggy Lou Baldwin.
We are not similar but most people may think.
You did that drawing, Peggy?
Uhh. I like to draw in black and white because I do not ...
I know how to paint as well as she.
Oh, I think it's very good.
It is very, very good.
Tell me something.
If you and Sybil are not similar ...
... yet you relate?
- Do you have the same mother? - No, no.
No, she's not my mother. Do not say that.
Okay, I'm sorry, I ...
It's all right. I just wanted to know.
Can I talk to Sybil?
You can control it?
What happened?
Did I do that?
I am so sorry.
- I'll pay for it. - No Sybil.
Sybil, let it. Do not touch the glass.
Forget.
Sybil, have you broken glass before?
I do this all the time.
- But I do not remember how. - Do you have absences.
Since when does that happen?
Ever since I can remember.
Oh my God.
Do you know. Now everyone will know.
No, no. Of course not. I will not tell anyone.
When these absences happen?
Have you noticed some sort ...
- ... pattern that is repeated? - No, no.
- Something that triggered ... - What's wrong with me?
I do not know.
But you and I will find out.
You will not use drugs or hypnotize me.
No, no.
You will not send me to the hospital?
- Do not. - I do not want to go to a hospital.
Of course it will not. You need not go to a hospital.
Oh dear God ... I'm losing my mind.
No, Sybil.
You're not losing your head.
Think that's a start. Only a start.
OK?
I did some research,
probably know that a handful of cases have been recorded.
Connie, you know as well as I do ...
that there is no such thing as multiple personalities ...
the diagnostics menu does not even mention.
Oh I know, what the hell, if you could see it.
I did, it is a brilliant hysterical.
Suffering occasionally from some psychotic confusion ...
It turns out that is unconscious,
- very talented ... - You think I have not considered it?
Where's your objectivity, Connie?
- What? - hysteria is a female problem.
And that's why I sent for you.
Do not reduce this because we are women.
I'm not diminishing anything.
I just said, check the menstrual flow.
to a pheromone balance, maybe crazy.
This is no side effect.
If someone does not help this girl, then she will end up committing suicide ...
- or ending up in a mental hospital ... - I will not throw it in a mental institution.
No, no, listen.
Look. I know it sounds crazy,
but the standards and no one else cares.
I mean that something happened when this girl was young ...
that Paggy know, but Sybil refuses to face.
But that turns the night in hiding.
But in a way, Peggy may be necessary.
Look. It is to a new channel the water takes when it reaches the reservoir.
I do not know how and why it happens,
but she expressed anger that Sybil care.
- Honey, please. - What?
Harold, come on.
How do you know? I mean, we can ...
we can discover a new frontier here.
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
Hey Hey! This is my car!
No, it's not. This car is my father.
- Not in hell he is. - Hey! Take your hands off me!
IT IS? You'll pay for this glass.
I can hurt you.
What are you doing?
- I'm taking it for damage. - No, you will not.
The wasted time and fix it.
That's all the money we have!
Be careful, you stupid,
- stupid ... - Ah. mad cow.
Stupid! Stupid!...
It can not be angry because her mother does not.
It depends on me, and then I get myself in trouble.
Why her mother does not allow?
It is sin.
Anger is purple. See?
Who are you angry?
- Of people. - What people?
Of people, the angry people.
- With who? - As the Sybil's mother.
What have you done to make her angry?
Trees are not purple, stupid!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
I can not answer everything.
There are things I will not tell you and nobody can make me.
I'll break the glass.
- I'll break the glass and escape. - No!
- Even if you do not want me to do. - You do not need to break the glass.
You do not need to break the glass, you can walk out the door.
- I can not. - Yes you can.
It's not locked.
- Do not. - Go ahead, turn the knob,
- No! Do not open the door.
I will leave here the garage, I'll get the car of my father.
- Why do you need to do this? - I do not like people or anything.
- I do not like music. - Music. What music?
Nobody likes me.
- Nobody cares. - The hands hurt.
- it hurts a lot. - Your hands?
Other hands, hands that come get you.
- Hands who, who? - They will not say.
I will not say, but I will not say, I will not say.
No, you can tell me. Honey, can you tell me.
No, no. Does all get angry inside me,
she wants to break things, say things.
- Setting the glass! - No!
- I need to do this. - No, let go.
- Where else would I live? - No.
It's all right.
It's OK. You are OK.
No! No, no.
Dra. Wilbur?
Sybil?
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
About what?
About losing our sessions last week.
But you have not lost any session.
- Oh God. - Sybil.
I think I can explain a few things ...
... but first I would like to ask you some questions, right?
- What kind of questions? - Easy.
Like how you feel about the music?
I'm not very good, I had piano lessons as a child,
But mother was very critical.
- She was a good pianist. - And hands, and on his hands?
Hands ever came to pick her up?
I think not.
Anyone ever hurt you with their hands?
Do not.
You have a few glasses of memories?
Are you sure, you can not think of anything ...
You do not remember anything related to windows?
Mother had some lovely crystals.
Once my cousin Luana and I were washing dishes and her ...
Why did you do that?
- Who made this? - Sybil.
- Mother, I did not. - Clean it.
- But, but ... - I said to clean.
Because?
And blood. The blood signal leaves you disturbed?
Grandma died of cancer, the treatment bled enough.
I loved her, she was very good to me.
What about Tommy Ewold?
When he fell from the top of the barn, had a lot of blood?
How do you know what happened to Tommy?
Sybil ...
When you delete when you have these collapses ...
... of which we speak.
Someone else takes over and takes his place.
Who?
Someone who is well inside,
- someone who is called ... - Peggy Lou, I know.
So you know about her.
Just know, I know what everyone does, especially Sybil.
But you, you are not Sybil.
I'm not, I'm Victoria, Victoria Antoniete Shalom.
I was born in Paris, but I am Americanized, so, so ...
... please call me Vic.
How are you, Vic?
Very well, but only when it is not. Sybil worries all the time.
Like now, for example.
She does not like when I buy things.
Oh ... so these are yours.
I put on the credit card, but Sybil tries to get them back.
It's very funny.
How long have you been there, Vic?
From the beginning. I was the first, and the other came.
What other?
Sead, Marie, Peggy and Vany ...
Oh ... you do not know about them, right?
I met Peggy.
- How many more are there? - 16.
Are sixteen of us.
Good evening.
- Vic? - It is too late?
Well, actually I was ...
It is not alright. Come on in.
I was going out tonight ...
... but I wanted you to see how my real appearance.
Wow.
Ulala.
Her hair is very special.
Oh, it's very special, it is not. But it gives me a lot of work.
This cluster does not come easily, but I do not care.
I have a very refined taste.
But that's just my preciousness.
Oh. Oh, I did not look higher, but ...
Nevermind. It's just a candy curls to make it the way I like it.
Do you approve?
I, yes.
I do not allow that many people to see me like that way.
Most of the time, I have to disappear.
And others, they appear differently than yours?
But of course.
Would you like to see?
This is Peggy Lou and Peggy Ann.
- Peggy Ann? - Yes.
Peggy Lou is most of the time angry ...
and Peggy Ann fearful and shy virtuously.
You probably will not know 12 of them.
- Sybil knows them? - No.
She does not know any of us.
- Let me show you Mary. - Mary?
Yes, very sweet girl. But a little neurotic.
Well ... they are neurotic, all except me.
At least, I think I'm not, but in this chaotic situation you never know.
I'll let you know all eventually.
You're in charge?
I just a messenger. I communicate and control when they leave.
Two, I agree.
When they leave?
It depends, each specializes in something.
For example, Peggy Lou, who met, she is good with anger ...
and mathematics, she takes stock with checkbooks own.
16?
Like no other recorded case.
And I have to treat all individually.
Well. I hope each of you to pay separately.
Oh, very funny.
That's crazy Connie, I think you are reading many tales.
You think I'm playing it wrong, is not it?
I think you are being sucked into a very controlling patient.
This disease does not exist.
Nor is there a category for that diagnosis.
So we proposed a.
I write a story about it.
And I make a presentation at the next convention of the APA
We have created a category.
That's not wise Connie, I think they will withdraw you from the stage to laughter.
- You think so. - I'm sure.
She's hysterical high suggestion.
When she, me or you have created these types of characters to ...
justify analyzes ...
- that they were possibly created. - Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Do you think I created these people?
I think you might have suggested,
almost intentionally.
How often have you met her?
3? 4 She will not prove that short period of time.
Hal, Come. She spent all her life hiding the truth.
- She is good at acting. - Look. I see a lot of crazy people.
- What? Or hear me. - And I did not find it so unique.
And now you tell me that this covering ...
some iceberg of a psychiatric phenomenon ...
- no one believes there. - Yes. I see at least I ...
while you can not.
You keep going down this path Connie
It's a great opportunity, we may be making history.
- You will destroy all their work. - Yeah, so I'll take that chance.
- Bad day Doctor? - More or less.
A stab in the back, ...
... I scratched some ribs, but not quite.
Miki know.
Nobody cares what I have to say,
they just want me to not listen.
You have to be a bartender.
- Hey Connie? - Yes.
I have 16 cousins ​​looking for dating,
you know someone who should I contact?
- Men. - IT IS.
I used to be so proud to be the only woman in that department, but ...
Lately I've been feeling a professional who has been tolerated ...
... to be the one that will sweep the mess that nobody wants to deal with.
Yeah, I know a little of that.
- Miki, what is it? - That?
It is these pins.
Look at this.
- It's a cute, right? - Yes.
Give me one more.
Wow. Well well well.
I do not see what this has to do with me.
What do you think you're doing during his blackouts, Sybil?
I do not do anything.
And if people have inside you,
which they are not exactly people but consciousness levels.
Personalities that are activated, they go out and take control.
- This is impossible. - No, this is not.
They emerge when you are inferior.
They are functional in the outside world.
That's crazy!
You keep saying or doing something.
- Even if you are not aware ... - This is crazy.
- what you are saying or doing - Are you saying I'm crazy?
No, I'm not saying you're crazy.
And I'm afraid that there is not a great knowledge about this condition.
That's a lie. You are a liar.
Mother was right.
People like you try to control us, make us crazy.
- Perhaps your mother tried to control you. - No, no!
My mother was wonderful, she was the best mother ever.
She beat you,
- and punished you when you did not ... - That's because it was my fault!
No, it was because of her.
Now, I want to know more about it ...
I want to know everything that you remember about your mother.
She was very talented,
it could have been a concert pianist if her father permitted.
Why did she not?
He took her school, she had to work.
Did she ever got to talk about it?
She was not angry if that's what you're inducing.
Good...
Maybe at first she was.
She cut your favorite jacket, but God punished her.
- As? - He made it very, very sick.
She was so excited,
family dishes had to be placed with cloths because ...
She could not bear to see them.
This is very agitated. She was always so nervous?
No! It was much better when grown.
Except when ...
When what, Sybil?
When she tried to put the needle line.
But I could not do that, Dad had to do it. He did.
Everything and then he was a wonderful husband ... and a father.
He even took care of her after I was born.
She was so sad. He did not allow her to take me.
So I wept much, and ...
That's why Grandma appeared there.
Grandma made me sit on her lap.
When she was come, nothing hurt, nothing.
What you mean?
She never got angry with me.
I readied the table, she never said what I was doing wrong.
When she died, they were not allowed to see her.
Grandmother!
The next thing I realized, was in a classroom ...
and it was two years later. I did not recognize the teacher.
We were studying arithmetic and I had never learned math.
Yes, but someone else must obviously have learned.
It means your checkbook is accounted for, right.
This is not proof that when you're not here, that ...
someone else is taking care of you?
Who? Who would do that for me?
Her name is Peggy.
Stop trying to make her believe me that obviously ...
- do not want. - What?
I assumed because she was angry over the death of the grandmother.
His mother was not going to lift a finger, so I had to be angry with her.
I was out, really, for a long time, it was great.
So why did you come back inside, Peggy?
Nobody likes me.
I was angry all the time, because I did not like them.
Then Sybil returned and I left. That was when he met Tommy.
Tommy was the only friend. She could tell him everything.
Let's jump.
When Tommy died.
It was tragic, but I assumed.
It was the first time I allowed myself to come out.
even if it has remained inside for a long period.
Why, Vic?
Because people who loved, Sybil.
Grandma and Tommy died.
I was the only one who could handle myself.
Hurry up do not say.
I am glad that is not blue because her boyfriend died.
Father would not like to see her with him.
Because?
Why is it wrong to mix with people who are not of our religion.
Tommy sabia, is burning in hell right now.
This is so tragic.
How many times have I told you not to talk about this nonsense of French.
- Olá Rita ... - Hi.
- Wonderful night. - Oh yeah.
Going to the park?
It's time to go to the Kigui Park.
- Happy Christmas to you. - For you too.
Merry christmas, it's such a snob.
I'll show you. Look at this.
No, please.
She dedicated the wards of other people?
I found it so embarrassing. How are you today, Dr. Wilbur?
I do not believe we met. I'm Mary.
Mary Lucinda Dorsett, I received this name after my grandmother.
Do you like poetry? Grandma liked. Poetry relieves pain.
What pain, Mary?
I can not tell you, the death of the grandmother is very recent.
No darling. She's been dead for 20 years.
No, it is now passing that when this carry with you.
We try to be heroes.
Sybil try, I try, but it does not work.
Perhaps Sybil's mother, studying a way to try, Mary.
But now she died, you can talk about the pain.
Can? Can you tell me about it, Mary?
- No! - What?
- No, no, no ... - Listen to me.
What is going on?
When you listen to me?
Listen me!
What is going on? What do you see?
Do not hit me Mom. Do not hit me Mom. Sybil is dead.
Who are you? What is your name?
- Mom. Mom does things. - Are you Ruthy?
- Little girls. - What little girls?
- Mom puts blades inside. - She does what?
- It puts blades inside. - Within the little girls?
It does this to you, Ruthy?
Mom plays games, it hurts-the mama, mama makes promises.
Promise what?
Do not tell, do not tell, do not tell.
It also hurts you, Ruthy?
No, no, please Mommy, please do not hurt me.
Bad girl.
Mom I'll be a good girl, I'll be a good girl, I will not tell ...
I will not tell, I will not tell, I promise, I will not tell.
Bad girl!
- No! No! No! - She's guilty!
Stop it! Sybil.
No, no...
Sybil.
No, no.
Ruthy pare! Now! Ruthy not!
Alright, stop!
Let me go.
- Stop it! - Get away from me.
Sybil, listen to me.
- Stop it. Stop it! - you will not play with me.
Please stop.
Sybil, Sybil.
No! Sybil.
Stand back. No. You do not walk away from me, stay away from me.
- Listen to me, all is well. - No.
No!
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Ruthy, the one who attacked you only have six years of age.
Her relatives make love in front of her all the time.
Oh yeah.
Once the mother miscarried, Ruthy put blame on sex.
Her father defeated by bad luck, can you believe that?
Hey! Vanessa I really like your painting.
Thank March, its is also lovely.
Let me get this straight. This is your march?
This is my Doctor.
Oh ... right. So...
That's his march, and this is your Vanessa?
That's right.
Any one of you can tell me ...
more about Ruthy?
Her mother treated her badly.
The treated badly?
It also hurt the little girl when the baby was born?
She kept the worst for you.
What was she doing?
She raped her ... with the handle of a hook.
March, there is a concert tonight, I'd love to appear,
would you like to go?
Get out of here, Fetish stinks, you know, I do not like him.
Vanessa ...
Where were you when the Ruthy's mother did this to her?
I was there, I saw it.
We all saw it.
But you do not feel anything?
Why should we? We are all different people Doctor,
I'm March, and I'm Vanessa.
Now Mary, and now Peggy.
Not a sweetie.
Vic.
We are not the same people.
And none of us will disappear.
I had never seen anything like it.
This is not associated with some advanced type of amnesia.
It is more advanced than that.
Each character has its own standard memories, series of conflicts.
And relationships with anyone, and yet ...
None of them has the dimensions of separate individuals.
It's almost like I can say that she is acting.
And if I'm wrong? And if she's lying to me?
She's good at it.
God knows how good at it.
She spent a lifetime doing it.
I never felt so indecisive, with my own training.
I know that we should not get involved, but still ...
She needs ... a mother or a friend.
And I can not do it for her, so ...
What should I do?
And if it stops in a sanatorium because ...
I do not know what the hell I'm doing.
- Mom, please. - You'd better hang on.
Mommy please, please Mom.
Stop it! Stop it! That hurts! That hurts! That hurts!
I can not take it anymore, I can not, I can not!
I can not take it anymore, I can not. Please.
Oh, thank God it's you.
Sybil Oh, what happened?
I do not know.
I woke up in an ambulance when they tried to give me an injection,
I gave them your name. They would put me in a sanatorium for observation.
- You will not let them go? - No, no, no. Of course not.
Let's go. I'll get you out.
That's it, no big deal, but ...
please do not notice the mess.
- Would you like coffee or tea? - Yes Coffee, please, black..
Well, that's very, very kind Sybil.
Thanks.
Oh, I thought you did not play.
I do not play.
You think you might have something ...
in music that night that may have disturbed you?
I do not remember.
Maybe your father can tell us something.
Well, he would never come to New York, he calls Sharon the city of sin.
Saron.
He never set foot in that place.
He did not want me to live here, he wants me to come home.
Or maybe we can go see him.
- In Little Conner? - Yes.
Truth! You'd do that for me?
If you think he can get me.
Oh, he'll love to meet you.
I told him all about you.
It is cozy, charming, a wonderful man.
Hang on! Hang on!
Hang on!
What?
Mother, no!
- Dad. - Hello, my darling.
- Nice to see you. - Nice to see you too, honey.
This is Dr. Wilbur.
Mr. Dorsett, I was eager to meet him.
- Mrs. Wilbur.. - Dr. Wilbur..
Well, let's go.
You go to Dr. Wilbur church?
Oh ... Oh ... no, not often.
Done. The story of our life here.
My father was very active in preparing for the end of the world.
The Lord will destroy the earth and be blessed.
Feeling, for it is a sin. I think you disagree.
Feeling is inescapable as breathing Mr. Dorsett.
We all know what happens when you hold your breath.
Sybil wrote that you had questions about Hattie.
It's a wonderful woman.
Sybil said she was nervous.
We are all sometimes.
But we had financial difficulties. It was difficult for her.
Everyone has their own customs.
What kind of morals?
Hattie was a proud woman. She liked being on top.
And when the depression came, we lost our money.
- He hit it too hard. - In what sense?
He was bedridden and stopped talking.
I had to dress her, feed her.
I brought a man from the clinic and he said ...
What is the word? Esquizométrica.
Schizophrenic.
Would you like some milk with your tea Dra. Wilbur?
No darling. She was treated that?
We were not able to pay for treatment.
So...
We pray,
and one day she began to speak again.
She was healed.
- It was nothing. - Anything?
Santa is correct, it was perfectly fine.
Mr. Dorsett ...
Do you think we can talk alone, perhaps sometime this afternoon.
I do not see the purpose of it all.
Taking this time, Hattie was a perfectly healthy woman.
Sybil was lucky to have her as a mother.
Schizophrenia is not cured with prayers, Sybil.
At least none that I know of.
She could not help, you should not blame her.
Is there anything you remember here ...
back here to do it remember?
No, nothing bad, just nice things, like going to church ...
ice cream, and visit Dr. tailler, it was beautiful violins.
He promised to make me one so I ...
- What? What is? - I will not say I will not say ...
- Do you remember something, Peggy? - A broken bottle.
Sybil was visiting Dr. tailler and Sybil's mother came along.
And Sybil struck the medicine bottle that was on the desk ...
- but it was an accident. - You broke.
- You are a bad girl. - Mom.
- No, please. - What did she do?
- No mother. - Ruthy, it's okay.
Can you remember. I'm here with you, it's okay.
Tell me what she did.
- No, no, no! - Ruthy.
Ruthy!
She did not.
Do not, do not.
I will not, I'll be nice.
Ruthy, what she did to you?
She...
I have, I have to.
I have, I have to do.
I just want you to be a good little girl.
Your mother wants you to go to heaven ...
because the world is coming to an end and then it will be too late, too late.
How often she did it?
I was bad.
I behaved badly.
And then she ...
What?
She died on the piano.
- Mom, please. - You better hold.
It hurts.
I can no longer hold. I can not.
I can not, I can not ...
It is better to handle.
I can not, I can not handle ...
- Mom. - You're bad, bad girl.
Sybil?
Sybil ?!
What have you done with my daughter?
She was perfectly fine ...
before moving to New York and get to see you.
This is not true.
She was never quite right, Mr. Dorsett.
Why did you allow your daughter to be raised by a schizophrenic?
- Do not blame Hattie ... - And she was catatonic.
by Sybil problems. She loved her daughter.
And Sybil was truly happy to have her as a mother.
Even people like you talk to her and ...
They do believe in all sorts of crazy things.
- That never happened. - Excuse me, but this ...
This simply is not true.
What about injuries?
You never noticed any marks on it? Oossos broken?
For me just talk to you.
Hattie was abusing his daughter.
She never raised a hand on Sybil.
cold water and other things ...
It raped a cable with a hook.
How dare you...
- come to my house and do ... - She beat her, tortured ...
- these charges. - and even then you did not see anything.
Anything.
Dra. Wilbur is the mother of the obligation to create the daughter.
Oh God, what happened?
Who made this?
Dra. Wilbur?
Sybil? Are you alright? Do you need something?
- I did. - What? What did you do?
I straightened the apartment, before she went to Little Cornner.
I built shelves covered, and bought blankets for her to sleep.
I made Mike wash and dry, but I did all the hard work.
Sybil, dear. I'm a bit of a hurry, so walk with me.
Now...
- Who's Mike? - You have not met.
Well, it seems I have not met too.
I'm Sid.
- Sid? - Yes.
Sid, as Sybil Izabel Dorset?
Hey. I had not thought of that,
- Well ... - I am different from her.
I'm a young man, like my father.
It was built, I am also built.
Yes, but you are not exactly like his father, Sid.
I'm sorry, I have arms, legs and all.
But not everything.
Well, I never had it, but ...
When I get older, it will grow.
No! Now listen to me.
A boy in a woman's body does not grow to be a man.
This is not the body of a woman.
My mother was a woman and she was dirty.
- I'm not a girl. - Yeah, but ...
All the girls are not like your mother says.
But I told you, I'm like my father.
And Mike is like the grandpa, girls can have babies if we want.
- Not exactly, I do not think ... - Yes, we can.
What the hell you know.
You're just trying to make me be like all the others, and I will not be.
We are all different, can not see it?
- We will never be the same. - Sybil ?!
Sid!
What are you doing, you have a lot of talent.
Thanks.
I've been admiring his work for long.
So many different styles.
This is not exactly a compliment.
In my mind is.
I would go in an opening with me?
- I'm friends with a gallery ... - No, thank you.
Thank God she did not leave with him.
- Meeting is a case of sin. - That's your opinion, Mary.
But maybe if you were with the Sybil ...
you may find that you have different ideas about it.
I do not want to go along, I just want to be me.
But you will not lose who you are.
No, think of it as a democracy, each has ...
Not much freedom brings sin.
Freedom does not always sin.
It brings the release of God.
Do not confuse God with religion, Mary.
You blame the church for who we are.
No, I blame ignorance and repression.
And you try to get away from my religion.
I never said that.
But you think you want.
Because I go to church can not be right at the same time.
You do not realize. What I am is bad.
This is my punishment.
If I want to be better, God will punish me otherwise.
And what did you do to deserve this punishment?
Well, I must have done something,
why else would God allow this to happen?
I do not know Mary, but I know he wants you to improve.
Improving means killing me, it's a sin.
- It does not mean suicide. - The world will end ...
and I will burn in hell. I'll never see Grandma.
No, Mary, Mary ...
The end of the world that you are afraid.
It's the end, it's the end of the world you know now.
There is another world, a warm and free.
Like all those little Russian dolls, put together ...
A completely inside the other, you will not die.
You will grow.
Precisely what we have to do?
You have to enter the Sybil, Vanessa.
All you have to know.
Wait, wait, look at what it can do. She does not want to know us!
Look, I do not have time to explain, let me talk to Vic.
No, you will talk to me. We know that we are crazy Dra. Wilbur.
Put us together only make things worse.
Hal! Hal!
On here!
- Dr. Hi. - Why are you doing this?
Would you like to join me?
I would like to explain this letter?
- We'll talk later. - No, we speak now!
I mean everyone here know exactly ...
what you will speak at the convention, right?
- I just present the problem. - Simply?
After my presentation,
You will perform and read 25 pages of paper calling me a fool.
Look, I treated this woman first.
- No, you have not tried. - And I get the odds.
You did not treat you interviewed her, Hal?
I am Connielia, and am no longer his student ...
and if you disagree with me and tell me to my face, but ...
not humiliate me in front of all these people.
I'm not demeaning you, you're doing this to yourself.
Why is this so important to you?
Why do you think I'm forcing these personalities it?
You're getting hysterical, calm down.
There it is again, hysterical woman.
Stop this.
You think I'm overshadowing you, is not it?
- That's it, is not it? - Connie ...
This is not about understanding the psychology,
- I think you're taking advantage - or anything else.
- For yourself. - It's about me not knowing my place.
You're being an ambitious woman, Connie.
IT IS? What's wrong with that?
Oh, wait!
It has a big problem with that.
And the right word for this is: Woman.
Oh, come on, Connie.
Hello?
Ramon. Oh, thank God there's someone here I can talk to.
How are you, Sybil?
Do not call me that, call me Vanessa, it is a kind of nickname.
I'm bored, and I'm hungry.
Let's get something to eat, right?
You mean like a date?
Sure, and why not. Only three of us. Who knows maybe we'll get lucky.
I'm always there when they speak.
Vanessa Hey, want a hot dog?
Call me march.
Marchat? Do not tell me it's another nickname.
Yeah, I guess you can call it that.
You're kidding me, right?
No!
- What is so funny? - Two please.
Oh my God.
It is a rare animal, as my feeling for you is rare.
Thanks Ramon, it's beautiful.
I love you Sybil, or Vanessa is any name you want to call.
I wanna take you to my house, to Argentina to meet my family.
No! No, no...
- Sybil was just a kiss. - What is going on?
I do not remember anything in my mind that hurt you.
Did you really think it was me?
Pure and clear heart, they shall see God.
What is wrong?
Boys do not sleep with other guys.
- Of course not. - Stop it! What's happening to me?
Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid ...
- Please stop. - You stop!
For the love of God.
See what made me do!
I've never seen anything like it before.
It was horrible.
It was like I was talking to people who were not there.
But they were there.
All the people you told me.
- What I am? A freak? - No!
Sybil Oh, no.
No, you're not a freak.
You're making progress, believe it or not.
So how do I feel like I was worse.
As if these demons were taking control.
They are not demons, and they are not having you.
But they do, they do, they steal time ...
- No, listen to me. - They're taking my life.
Listen to me Sybil.
And if they were the only way ...
the little girl knows how to defend ...
pretending to be someone else.
But she had to pretend so intensely ...
the pretense became real.
You understand?
What choices you had, Sybil?
His mother abused you, your father was negligent, his grandmother died.
He left me, white man ... left me.
Who are you talking about?
He said...
She broke my arm ...
And he says...
How's my big girl today?
Good.
And I saw that his shirt was unbuttoned the cuff.
And then I asked him ...
if I could close to him as I did with my father.
Of course, melzinho he said.
No one had ever called me melzinho before.
And he said I was ready to go home.
And I did. I knew he would take me with him.
He would take me home and be my new father, and take care of myself as a daughter.
- But he turned and walked away. - Hang on! Hang on! Hang on!
He left me, and this was the first time.
I keep waiting.
But I'm a Doctor, Sybil, and I'm not leaving.
I'll be, right?
I want you to meet someone.
This is Peggy.
I hear the glass breaking ...
This reminds me of the cucumber dish.
I just had to run to the door ...
How did you get the voice of my mother. This is the voice of my mother.
Disconnect!
This is the voice of Peggy Lou, she's talking about ...
No! Do not turn off this thing!
Do not you realize, Sybil?
Peggy Lou took the anger you felt, but can not express ...
for having been unjustly accused of having broken the cucumber dish.
I do not want her to take my anger,
I do not want anything to do with her.
Therefore Peggy breaking glass.
Well, I want it to stop!
It's me much harm.
But it will stop ...
when you manage to get angry on their own.
- You want to hear more? - No!
This is Vic.
- French is terrible. - Yes.
I pray to God as Grandma did.
I will be a good Christian.
I try to forgive Mom when she hurts her.
The girls did the measurements, you have to give them credit.
But Mike and I did the rest.
They are useless without us.
She can play ...
- So beautiful. - Yes.
Vanessa is very talented.
Because? Why she can play and I can not play?
That's not fair. It's not fair to rob me, they took my life.
But once, since all are together again,
- you recover. - No, no I will not.
I will never recover, they are many.
- No ... Sybil. - No!
Do not.
- Stupid! Stupid! Stupid ... - What?
You can not trust them.
- No One Likes You. - You know who I am?
I'm Mary. Mary Lucinda Dorset,
Do you love poetry?
Best. I understand that you would get scared.
I quite like it.
You should listen to me, March.
But you do not want to hear anyone but you.
What do you know? You're just a girl.
- Girls do not understand anything. - Please stop! Please!
Please do not do that anymore. Please please.
No, no!
- Who stopped you? - They all stopped.
I do not want to go to hell Dr. Wilbur,
but it is better than living like this.
I want to live without hurting myself.
I want to live without nightmares, and crying, and ...
wake up not knowing where I was and what I did.
I want a friend.
I'm your friend, Sybil.
If you had killed tonight I would greatly miss her.
Sybil, I have an idea, do not know if it will work, but I think ...
Each inside you have an age, right?
Ruthy six years.
Sid 15 years, Vic 18 years.
Everyone is stuck in time, and I think ...
The first step to bring everyone together is doing all the same age.
- Your age. - As?
I want permission to hypnotize her.
I know, I know, I promised that we would never do this, but ...
I had so many things I did not understand before,
you do not know me and ...
I did not trust me, but now you trust, right?
- Yes, Doctor. - Good.
And I think we should start this weekend, we can ...
go to my house, the lake, and ...
It's very beautiful.
You are now in a deep state of rest ....
I want you to think on ...
when you were a child and a happy day.
Can you think of?
- Yes. - What was your age?
Three.
And why are you happy?
Because Mom is not bothering me.
It is comforting jacket.
She did not speak for long.
But that's okay, because I can do what I want.
Now, when I touch your hand ...
I want to talk to Ruthy, right?
Ruthy.
- You see the little Sybil? - Yes.
Do you see how the little Sybil is happy?
Yes.
You can be happy too.
- Would you like that? - Oh yeah.
You have to grow, you have to be an adult.
You have to have 8, 10, 12, 14, 16 years.
That's fine.
And then I can paint,
I can do all the things I can not do now.
Good. Are you ready?
You are growing and growing and growing.
Wow.
And now when you touch your hands I want to talk to Sid.
Right?
- Sid? - Yes.
- How old are you? - 15.
You would not want to grow up?
Right.
Except that if I grow up, I'm going to die, I do not want to die.
No, you will not die, Sid.
You will only see the world through different eyes.
- Is ready? - I guess.
Now you have 16, you now have 17, and has 18.
Oh my God. Is my age now.
Yes, Vic, and now it's your turn.
You should not have the age of Sybil?
Since you have the memory of all the years that make it age?
I think so.
If you put it that way.
Since you're the pastor, vic.
I want to meet with you all.
Ruthy and Sid, Vanessa and March.
I have to be the Sybil agent? I do not want to grow up.
Peggy, it's easy when all have the same age.
Mary, okay?
I will be able to do the things I like to do ...
none of the others go to church, just me?
Of course, you can still go to church.
I will not take anything from you.
Is that you? You'll still be my friend?
Of course I'll still be your friend.
Now you will wake up, and when you do,
all have the same age and share the same memories.
You understand?
You are ready?
All ready?
When I touch your hand, you awake.
Sybil?
How do you feel?
Different.
- I can not explain. - It's all right.
What do you remember?
I do not want to think about it.
But you remember a few things now.
But not all are bad memories, right?
It has some memories of good things, right?
Like, when you played to dress in the attic.
- When you were happy playing ... - I should not be happy.
- Because? - My mother was sick.
When someone has a mother, you must love her.
Bad girl.
She did not deserve. What she did to you was terrible.
She did not do those things.
Yes, she does.
Because? I do not understand, I loved it.
Mother loves you.
I tried to love her.
Even when...
but I could not, I, me, me. I did not.
I think I ...
I hated her.
When she hurt me I want to hurt her back.
God, she should not do those things!
I hate her! I wanted to kill her!
Even if he is my mother!
I want her dead! I want her dead! ...
Oh God.
It WAS CHATTING, FOR MANY YEARS, Sybil has transformed COMPLETELY.
DURING THAT TIME THE DIAGNOSIS, '' MULTIPLE DISORDER IDENTITIES "
It WAS ACEIT0 AS AVAILABLE FOR PSYCHOLOGICAL EVOLUTION.
TWO WOMEN CONTINUED INTIMATE FRIENDS.
BY DOCTOR 1992 WILBUR die.
COLLEAGUES CONTINUED ITS MANY BELIEVING
SHE HERSELF CREATED THOSE CHARACTERS
DESIGNATED BY HIS PATIENT.
IN 1998 WAS REVEALED THAT THE LONE living in HOME,
Shirley Ardell Mason, WAS THE WOMAN KNOWN AS THE WORLD "SYBIL".
THESE WORKS OF ART, OF DISCOVERED AFTER HIS DEATH,
They WERE RAISED IN SEVERAL STYLES, GIVING SUPPORT TO BELIEVE
WHAT WERE VERY DIFFERENT ARTISTS PAINT ...
... USING THE SAME HAND.