What is yours?
Hard or soft?
Tough.
I do not know. The last time
I checked was 6 inches,
but it was in the seventh grade
is likely to increase.
Oh.
It's probably sad
7, possibly as much as 8.
You want to measure it by now?
I did not boner.
Oh.
And you?
It's not.
What's yours?
About six and a half...
That's good.
Not bad.
Hey, did Emily
coming to the party?
Yes, I think so.
Uh believes will arise.
I masturbate thinking of her every day.
Yes, I do.
-John I’m lucky.
Would the fuck?
Are you seriously asking me?
Yes.
Um, yes.
How would you do that?
What would you say?
What are you thinking?
Like, if she was here now,
what would you tell her?
-Is More goals?
No, not yet.
Well,
I'd probably want
to have sex with her and said to her,
"You're so beautiful."
Then
-They're Off her shirt and I would, uh-
What is yours?
Yes, I'd removed my shirt
and then her and then,
and then our trunks -
So she is naked or
still has her bra?
No, she still has her bra and panties
or whatever.
Yes, I still have my
bokesrice or whatever.
I lay on the bed with her
And I start to love and to-
And then she took off those boxers?
Yes, and then I help her bra around
And her tits are legendary, you know?
- What did you say?
No, she's just a little moans.
What then?
Then she  I take off her panties
And her vagina was wet and everything to-
Are you hard?
Hard me like a stone.
What?
Yes if you want to take the socks?
What do you mean?
I mean, if you want to-
Oh, dude, no,
I do not want to sully these sock.
I'll give you dirty.
Do not look.
-Oh well.
I like
I love the body and stuff
I ask is "What do you want?"
And she says, take me back.
Do?
I'm doing,
It goes and I'm doing that the bomb
And she says, "Oh, yes,
harder, harder, fuck me harder."
I "like it, honey?" and she
"Oh yes, I really like it."
Yes...
Do you think about her now?
Are you going to cum?
Yes.
- I will too.
Oh, I listened to your podcast.
- Thank you.
I really like...
I bought the  Silver  album.
Oh, yeah? Do you like it?
Yes, he's cute.
Good, really good.
It's not as good as their first album,
But they are really good group.
Have you ever thought about
listen to a Christian band?
I did sometimes, but mostly bad.
I do not know, I like them.
Oh, yeah, I forgot,
We will have to listen to all night.
I'm sorry, it will be easier,
I put the classics there.
Oh, I can not wait.
Oh, hey,
Happy birthday.
Hey, thank you.
Create  Not to 10:02 morning.
Good night.
Dear God, thank you for
blessed this day.
Please help me
tomorrow be merry
I thank you for all the people in my life
to be here.
Give me strength to serve every
and fulfill your will.
Please let me wake up in the morning
Fresh and ready to start a new day.
Thank you for mom, dad
, Autumn and me.
I pray in Jesus' name, amen.
Here rođendandžije!
How did you sleep, guys?
Nice.
Great.
Happy birthday, honey.
Thank you, Mom.
Can I get
salt on a dish, please?
Of course you can, baby.
No, I got my
mix together.
So Gabe,
show them how it's done.
Autumn. Birthday breakfast!
FALL!
You look good on the news Pastor Bob.
Ha. Thank you, Gabe.
We are excited about the new building.
sloppy peace is being built.
Yes, we are blessed, for sure.
Sit soul. I'll do it.
- You sure?
- Yes.
In the fall, we'll eat it without you!
Mama.
You and me
rubs his head, Mrs. Gamble.
Gabe, do you have everything you need to celebrate
Or we'll run to your house?
No, everything's fine.
Oh, honey, we invited staff from the church
,
But you know, we did not have to.
- I know.
He likes to have grown close.
I called and Rosa, I hope that's okay.
Are you?
Yes.
I thought I told you.
I think it's good for her, right?
Course.
Riki will not come?
I'm sure he will not come.
Look who's up 11.
Welcome home to me.
- Happy birthday, Hen.
- Yes, and I have not even seen.
Welcome.
- Thank you.
The year is almost over,
I'm not used to this no.
How did you sleep, dear?
Good. What time is the party?
U 4, I think.
Can I call Cheyenne?
Ask your brother.
No.
Well, if someone sees something that he needs?
Shall we?
Oh, look, I'm just now born.
Yes, that's
My brother and friends, and people who work with my dad
Friends from the church or school?
Both, why?
So, can I? - Yes I asked.
I know yours. I'm a girl Pagan.
No, you did not. Come on.
Honey?
Wait! My God.
I just wanted to see
do you like the new curtains
I put them in.
What?
Oh. They are beautiful!
Hi, Logan. How are you?
I'm fine.
I'm glad you came. Henri and Gabe
in the back, join them.
Already bathe?
-To think.
You need to wear a bathing suit.
It can there.
Do you want me to take?
No, it's okay.
-Okay.
Stop Learning.
Come.
Henri stop.
Stop.
Exams, stop.
Please stop.
The pool later.
Hello...
Hi.
How's Logan?
Hi, Logan.
You can put a gift here.
Oh, well.
Honey, can you help her mother around
fruit?
-Fruit?
Yeah.
Sure.
Let's cut some fruit.
Hey, honey, we have a great pattern for college
prayer in the church
I can bring you
if you want to know anything.
Nice.
Have you finished one, what's his name?
In love with God ?
Yes. I'm still working on it.
Hello?
Yes, this is good.
-Džoooone!
What is.
Hi, Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Where's Em?
I do not know, it probably comes with his brother.
Someone wrote a new song.
Yes, I'll play tomorrow in the church
I thought
and you can hear it later.
I can not wait.
Shut up, man.
Hi, Logan.
Hi.
Do you want to sing backing vocals
tomorrow?
Yes.
Please.
Is there anyone at home?
Hey, there they are.
Hello folks!
-Hello!
- I did not know you were coming home.
- The younger brother of the full 17
This is a great thing.
Absolutely, how's school?
-Rasturam.
- I bet.
- Would you met at Columbia
Christian, are not you? -  Sure.
Miss us in the younger age group, autumn.
Thank you.
Okay, let's do this.
You already have some children here,
Good, good, good.
How are you?
Oh, you know.
I'm pregnant.
Oh, my God!
I'm pregnant !!
Uh oh, here I am.
I should not bring me presents.
These are for another celebration.
Happy birthday.
We have to go in five minutes.
Get in.
Kristin did not know how to swim.
Perhaps, though.
You do not swim ?!
I do not see the point.
Hey, Henry, look who I found.
Hi, folks.
Let's go in!
Okay, let's go.
-Yes.
Hide your diversity, ladies.
-The Best. Fuck. Celebration. Behavior.
-Oh my God.
Hey, what are you doing here?
At the celebration itself.
I did not know you were acquainted.
Yes, we go to church together.
How do you two know each other?
We are together in a group, you idiot.
Oh, yes, exactly.
You know Logan, right?
Yes, you were in the choir at
Gays and Dolls , is not it?
Yes.
Come on, Logan.
-Yes.
Well, what did you bring me?
Journal.
Wait, what do you mean?
Why should I brought journal?
What's up?
DO HERE IS KLOPE?
IT IS IMPORTANT!
Hi, folks.
Are you going to take a bath?
I do not know. Probably not.
Girl, you gotta
satisfy physical needs.
No matter what you tell me?
I'm the one who seduced
seven freshmen or twelve,
Whatever, and you look wonderful,
Where your esteemed freshman?
O, who is this boy?
When?
What do you mean who?
The guy in the red.
Gabe, this is Henry's best friend.
On the twelfth.
Is not he older than him?
Yeah, but he's
Two years younger than us.
Yet her.
How is the Bible school?
It's not a Bible school,
to a Christian college.
Are you seeing someone?
Yes.
Why do you say?
I'm not interested.
That's not true.
What's wrong?
Due to Arona?
Swap topic.
Why are you wearing that ring?
Cheyenne.
I'm sorry.
Well... Gabe.
We'll go for a coffee tomorrow in the church.
Perhaps, I have to work until 8:30,
, I think maybe 9
'll Let you know.
Yes.
Hello.
-Hello.
Hey, how's it going?
... It's going well.
Yes, I'm fine.
- So, how's your party?
- OK OK.
I listened to your podcast this morning,
beautiful.
Oh, thank you.
The group  Wall ?
Yes, they were great.
-Yes.
I heard you talk about them in your podcast,
So I looked at them and are really good.
Yes.
I think I could do without swearing,
I think they're really good.
Yes, totally.
Do you want to chorus for
Hi, baby! ?
I do not know.
My mom wants to
focus on learning.
I think I've never met your family
.
I saw your dad
when I was driving.
That's your dad, right?
Stepfather, yes.
-I Am so excited for you.
-Thank you.
That was a surprise.
That's fine.
And it was so.
Hey, guys, do not be
overeat, lunch soon.
Yes.
Here.
Take a deep breath.
Zlobne you.
Are you having fun, Henri. Beautifully
entertain there. The other children were there.
Hello, Bonnie, how are you?
Hello, Bob.
I'm fine. I'm glad to see you.
Hi, Grace.
Ket made a potato salad.
I love krpompir salad.
How are things going at Saive-Mart?
Great?
It is really progressing well.
-  Lari!
-Kendis!
Ket keeps asking me,
"What does Grace?"
-Food Looks really nice, Bob.
Hello, Grace.
Are children having a good time there?
Oh, here's Kate, this is about Henry,
It's nothing, just socks and wallet.
What do you mean?
I do not wanna talk about this!
Hello
Oh hello.
I really like your podcast.
Thank you.
Stop.
I'm sorry. Hey!
There he is.
Happy Birthday mate.
Thank you.
Hi, Logan, how are you?
I'm fine, how are you?
- How Mom and Tom?
- Okay.
I would love to see Tom often churches.
Yes.
Children having fun outdoors,
that's nice. Hey!
-Lari!
Hey, how are you?
Lari  Hey, get me a
piece or two, will you?
So you're a church?
I Church?
Yes, do you like to go to church?
Oh, no, I do not go to church.
Oh, you do not believe in anything, or...?
I do not... I believe in a lot of things...
For example, what?
Yeah, like what?
I do not know...
Love, kindness and friendship.
Yes, but I think something božansko-
Oh, divine?
-Yes.
Um... yeah, I do not know.
Probably not.
Well, you're welcome to
Kraljevo city at any time.
Um... Thank you.
Yes, totally, think about this, you know?
Think seriously, though.
Sure.
Nice.
Think about it.
We'll talk later.
Hi.
divine : a musical.
We will seriously burn in hell.
Do you think that we burn?
What?
You heard me.
Oh, I do not know.
What? Will.
-  Hey, can we play music?
- Sure.
Yes.
Sorry about that.
Yes. Sorry about that.
-What station you want, Silver Spirit?
No, please.
We can not let anything vulgar, I'm sorry.
Let's just listen to what they want, they will exceed
over it.
I have a mix here.
How do you call it?
Oh, I see.
-Zabavljaš Be?
-Yes.
Is it the pectoral muscles?
Yes, finally.
-Are You doing pushups?
I work what I can.
Okay, let's go.
Ljuljaj.
I'm going to jump in here
if not behave decently,
what do you think about this?
I do not know why you girls
nose so small bathing suit. Yes.
It looks like naked.
I mean I have a bikini, but-
You have a bikini?
Yes, but-
-For the name of the world, Candice.
It is quite modest.
I hear you're pregnant,
that's great.
Thank you.
I thought
to get there.
No, you will not do.
Candice, honey,
If you're familiar with the major problems
Sex trafficking that is going on?
not
Well, I'll throw this on the grill,
Unless you...
Are you okay?
Yes.
Yes, I'm fine.
Just a lot of thought.
Yes.
It's nice to have a family again in the house, though.
Yes, that's right.
Hey.
You look wonderful.
Thank you.
Can I do something to help?
-  No. not just enjoy it.
Are you sure?
If you'd like to slice the cheese
there, it would Bilobil®
No, no, it should be
teramo to do so.
She asked if she could...
With pleasure.
Believe it or not, Bob,
some people prefer to be at your service.
You do not know anything about it, right?
Ha!
Good.
Hello, Caitlin.
Welcome.
Thank you so much for inviting us.
I hate to intrude on
Henry's birthday party.
Oh, do not be crazy. Hey, Ricky, how are you?
- I'm fine thanks.
I hope it's okay that I'm here.
- Of course it is.
Who is this lovely lady
and handsome man?
Oh, Bob.
How you doing, buddy?
I'm fine, Pastor, thank you.
I do not know whether it is permissible
But I brought some wine.
Pst. We will not tell anyone.
Well, I'm not sure
we serve it
- Thank you passed.
Maybe I can smuggle it.
- Okay, sure.
- There are 4 bottles.
Really 4. In one box?
Unbelievable. Come in.
Hi, Mom.
Hello girls, how are you?
I bathe. - She's thirsty.
-  Oh, just because you do not want to bathe
does not mean that I'm pretty.
Hi, Ricky, how are you?
I'm fine.
Is it true that the
tried to kill himself?
Not sure what happened.
Hello.
I'm Cheyenne.
Let the celebration begin, right?
Roz, my dear, just wonderful.
-Hello Darling.
I'm glad to see you.
Oh, hi honey.
Oh, Grace, sit down.
Rozi, you look wonderful, soap
It's good to see you.
Guess who's pregnant?
Oh, the glory of God, that's wonderful!
Oh, we'll have something to look forward to.
You know, I do not.
- We will rejoice.
Oh!
Yeah you're right, Logan?
You okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm sorry, Logan.
It's okay.
Did he hit his head?
Oh, I put the "medicine"
under the sink,
You know.
Thank you, dear.
Oh, HB has always enjoyed
Spending time with young people.
Course.
Young people who like gentlemen,
he would certainly appreciate it.
Yes, ma'am.
I miss him, Bob.
Really.
I know.
I menu.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
I want to serve itself.
Yes, that's best.
You know, HB and is much appreciated.
He appreciated your help.
He was a wonderful man.
I had some spices here
I do not know where I put them?
Cute girl.
Oh, I frowned.
Where is my Riki?
Oh, there he is.
How is he, Rosie?
Oh, you know,
has good days and bad days.
Thank God for these children, though.
He just celebrated its
days of this youthful activities.
Hello. -Hello.
How's your head. He seemed very...
Pretty bad.
Good.
Hello, autumn.
Hello, Grace.
I'm sorry, I must have missed this earlier.
- It's fine.
I did not mean to interrupt
reading.
Oh, no, it's just a stupid magazine.
Kupaćeš be?
I do not know.
I'm thinking about it.
Yes, I do.
You should.
It's a nice day for it.
Mama hates swimming.
I'm not much of a swimmer, really.
No, I think
she hates swimming.
Sam thought of him.
Why?
I do not know.
All these bodies think it bothered her.
It is obvious that Lucy and Stefan
doing what. Severe.
No idea.
Yes, but when it works gently...
These are just ogovranja in the hallways, but...
Whatever.
Have you heard of Kevin and Jamal?
What about them?
Kevin Reynolds?
-Yes.
Apparently they had sex
on a trip with a group.
Stop, they're gay?
Yes.
Tyler Collins came out of the hall
I saw them in the hotel room to
doing what.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Strange.
Strange?
I'm gay.
Wait, what?
Seriously?
How do you know?
I do not know these things!
Wait, you have a problem with that?
Of course not.
Wait, what does that mean?
Logan, are you okay?
Yes.
New meat, you idiot.
Hey, how's your head?
It's not so bad.
I'm fine.
Please stop asking.
Sorry, mate.
Hey, do you
Wednesday to apply for jobs,
Sure your family know about this?
Yes, I know.
Are you going to go this year?
I do not know.
We'd like to come with us.
It will be better than last year.
Who goes there?
Almost everyone here, I think.
Gabe goes,
Emily is going, going, John,
trying to convince
Cup to go.
Nice.
Also interested to know whether you're interested
To go to Sunday school sometimes.
We hope to start
the whole youth group,
we all do.
Oh, I do not know.
You can choose any topic.
In addition to homosexuality,
I took it.
And I have vanity.
Yes, you do.
So how do you like Columbia Christianity?
I still try to find out
, but I like it. - Yes.
My cousin was there and he loves it.
You teach physics and biology, is not it?
Yes.
So, how exactly does it work?
- What do you mean?
-  Biology at the Christian school.
Do teach evolution... or...?
Well... Can you teach biology without evolution
.
Yes, you can teach math without numbers.
Yes, it's called logic.
My cousin took it.
So how exactly this
teach that life begins?
I think you they're--
Bypass around things?
Yes, it's a little strange, but
Yes to focus on...
No, this is not surprising.
This school is wonderful, do not listen to them.
I think I am capable of
to think for themselves, you know?
Yes, well.
Do it.
Hi, folks.
Yes, join us.
Yes.
Hello, Riki.
Hi, Happy birthday.
I could talk to you, you were in the pool.
Oh, thank you.
Hello Cup.
Rikster, how are you?
Are you ready for a camping
in a few weeks?
Yeah, we
talking about this.
We are trying to convince the Cup to go.
Yes, you should go.
It'll be great.
Totally.
I do not know, I'm not the type of camp.
You go, Riki?
If you Kate goes with me.
Yes we're still trying to come up
Situation with another person.
Usually we
a lot of fun, though.
It's mine.
Oh, I'm sorry.
And all these women
Practically kidnapped
Streets
Girls kidnapped from their beds -
And then sold to be sex slaves
And it is happening right here in America.
There is a wonderful organization
Called  In his hands
So I think
To Kraljevo town needs to be attached
I know Larry wants
to talk to Bob about that
because I think it's a crisis.
A few people talk about the global crisis.
Who would have said.
And then there's the porn.
I saw a show the other night
The entertainment industry for adults
But these girls and boys are
18, 19, 20 years
Are not much older than the children there,
And they get up every morning
i go to work,
And have sex with older men,
every day
daily
on najponižajuci,
terrible, unimaginable way...
No ketchup. - I'll get it, honey.
-  No, I'll do it.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I do not know, sometimes
I look at our sexual
US state
I know that God is coming.
I do not know anything
o tom, Boni.
I think that for some of these woman
the more economic need
than sex.
I have not followed.
I think for some social problem
Have to see where it arises and
it seems to me that these women
end up in prostitution,
For something else,
Be they economic difficulties
Or lack of opportunities for education.
Or inadequate sex education.
Do not be a democrat with us.
Barbara is printed
those programs for tomorrow?
Yes, I saw them at the office
When I was there before.
Good.
When an event opens tomorrow, yeah?
If you do not mind.
No, not at all.
I look forward to
First Korinćanskoj series this fall.
You get sick from the Old Testament?
No, he did not say that.
I can not wait the New Testament.
I heard this.
Oh no,
they're doing a great job.
I love this series.
Well, thanks.
I always feel that I could better prepare
, but-
No, you're doing great, as always.
Do you know who would be proud of you?
Mr. HB.
Well, thank you.
I know it's been difficult
lose such a mentor.
Yes. Thank you.
You do not have to talk about this.
No no no, it's okay.
Taj cancer, it's a terrible thing,
I'll tell you about that.
Yes.
And he was a young man.
I think relatively.
-Looking,
Good health.
He could not see that coming.
-I Do not know.
No, you never know.
Okay, here we are.
I ought to change the channel.
Hey, Coop.
I'm trying to change the channel, this is dirty.
I think the receiver.
Think the battery.
Here it is. We managed.
You need to get rid of these movie channels.
I do not know why they still have.
You know, I do not know how to
she works, but
Ket every day
looking better.
I would not have thought it possible
Because it certainly will not happen
Boni.
Not yet, anyway.
-Yes good.
Thank you.
She's a wonderful person, of course.
Excellent.
I do not know where the basket smeće-
Under the sink.
Oh.
Hey Bob!
-Please.
What's under the sink?
Oh, no no no, it's...
Rozi brought to.
She does not know that we do not drink.
Oh, well.
Why would you?
Oh, you know, such an opportunity.
Ah.
You know, Jesus drank.
Well, I guess I can not.
I already began to feel it.
Oh, I'll take and I can see how it is.
Oh, shit,
need to present the cake.
Do you think it's okay to
take it with me out?
I think I will if it's uncomfortable.
No no no, it's fine, of course.
Good.
Nice.
Do you like him?
Yes.
This is perfect.
Thank you very much.
You are officially hipster.
And now this.
Wait, this is-
The first movie we watched together.
Thank you very much.
You're the best.
Thank you. I know.
This is a book.
Nadzemljaski: Guide
how to become a man of Christ.
Thank you very much.
This is wonderful. I appreciate it.
Course.
You're the best.
Oh, that's me.
Oh, wonderful.
Oh, dear.
This is really nice.
My mother had found a
on diving in Costa Rica.
It's beautiful, thank you, great.
I really like.
Oh, come on, embraced him.
-  Yeah, come on.
-  What are you doing?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
-Thank you.
Uh, well, what's next?
Can you open my.
-  You'll love.
-  No, you know what, I'll leave that for later.
What is going on back here?
Oh, we have a little medicine.
Oh!
I'm sorry... Aaron.
-Gđo Gamble.
God, you surprise me.
-Sorry.
The door was open,
I do not mind.
No, do not bother.
Autumn is back, it will be...
surprised when he sees you.
Back to the pool!
Do you want to turn on music?
Yes, you can put the mix B, please?
Sure.
Yeah you're right, Dad?
Larry, what's in the cup?
Oh, hello, Aron.
What are you doing here?
-What do you mean?
You are not invited.
You're not Henry else
You are not my friend, what are you doing here?
I just came to say hello.
Since we are not friends?
Autumn, autumn
what hell are you doing?
Get away from me!
-OK OK!
Help!
Okay, go!
What is it?
You're gonna hit me!
Stop getting in my house!
I'm in your house?
Good.
Can we look at
our actions.
Just as I remember. Because I...
Before you went to school
I am sure that everything was fine
That everything was fine.
And then we say that we will not be together
, we're just friends.
But... I mean,
do you do not remember that?
You sent me sms.
We had lunch together.
You sent me sms three weeks ago.
You'll be home.
I thought so.
Well, what were you thinking?
What is wrong with you?
-Men's Nothing wrong with you, Aaron!
Ouch! Jesus!
What's this?
I do not understand.
Think, Aron.
You took something from me.
What, seriously?
It is because of this?
You... you made me feel...
What did I do?
I thought was nice.
It was not nice, it was...
What? What is it?!
It's... it's... it was
nice... it was terrible...
The way you printed
What kind of way, the autumn?
We both do,
it was our decision.
Am I wrong?
Do not uzajedno decide?
Stop!
Stop, please.
Please, stop!
Hey, come ovamo-
Get away from me!
I want to get back to
brother's birthday party.
Stop talking to me.
What are we doing?
I have no idea!
HOW HAS MODELLING ?!
What ?!
Hello.
Do you like this?
Yes.
Henri,
I just wanted you to know that...
I'm totally willing to
... fun with you.
If you're serious.
You look really liked
Since we were partners in prayer.
Can I...
to come back to you?
Honey,
Where you been?
I ran down the street for no reason,
He chased me and now I'm back.
Hey.
It's okay...
... Hey.
You want some wine?
Hi, Bob.
Hi, Ricky.
How are you?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Hey, Kate told me that you're not sure
The situation
companion in the camp.
So I did not know whether...
I mean, if something...
You know, you should sit down next week
I talk about this
what might be best.
OK?
OK.
I think we're all excited and Ricky.
What does it mean?
I'm not sure it's good for him
To go with a companion in the camp.
Oh, why, for what inidenta?
To be sure, I'm not sure
it was suicide
I think the guy liked pills.
I do not know.
A was the incident in
camp last summer.
What happened in
camp last summer?
I thought you-
What are we talking about here?
I think maybe now is not the time.
No no no no, come on.
What happened?
I think that was the situation in the showers.
What situation?
Well, according to a couple of our boys, Ricky...
On the shower with several boys
A
they thought that he looks...
He might have been challenged.
Oh my God.
Yes, but...
Man,
Certainly a lot of stories.
The plane flying
and I was sick .-
Well, when you're in a plane
six and a half hours.
Oh, my God, I cry.
Why?
I do not know... Mom...?
I'm... I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
You know, the problem with growing up
This is what has...
Never grow up.
You think you're an adult, your body
peaked,
But you still... grow up.
You really never ready.
You never actually... you're on your way.
Why is this a problem?
Because you have kids.
In the fall, I want you to... izvinim-
No, Mom.
No, I will not. I will.
Look at me.
I want to apologize
If I ever made
to be ashamed of their bodies.
What? What do you mean?
You did not.
No, no, I did.
I'm sorry.
Tell me that's fine.
It's okay.
Listen, autumn
I want to be honest with you.
Something happened to me
in the recent past.
Or, some time ago.
In fact, it was the series...
Something happened to me and...
I'm not sure what will happen to me.
-Bob?
One second!
Riki said.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Yes, I'm coming right away,
Just to porbinem
for something I forgot.
I need you to tell me
the next time you do it.
That's fine
No, that's not right.
They're a bunch of jerks.
- Yes, I do.
- I know.
Can not you go through
B wing to the library?
Maybe you should try it.
Yes, I think maybe.
After all, it's the end of the school year.
I think you can.
Hey.
It will be better.
Well, no, seriously!
He will.
I really think it will be better for us.
Hey Grace, have you seen Ricky?
He was looking for me?
No, sorry.
Do you remember when you
Do you remember when I went
i was with Mr. Matthew
When Rosie had some obligations?
Riki was still working in the best shopping,
And she needed help.
Yes, I think I remember.
That was before the
He went to the hospital
on the last cycle
treatment
before you went to school.
Oh, well, yes.
He was very ill,
but not so sick
You can not enjoy...
in the time he had left.
Yes.
At that time, your father
spend more time with him
than I do.
But the road with him...
we are very well socialized.
He was... a real pleasure.
However, at one point, a couple of weeks,
-Mr Matthew -
Can you call him BB.
No, I can not.
One day he looked at me
grinning and said,
"God, you you could be a movie star."
You know, he was a very handsome man
even at the end.
He was.
I think I'm flattered,
You know, I was careless.
Then, he continued to speak,
"God, it's true...".
And in that moment he began to
looking at me...
He started looking at me as if I
worth of attention.
The first nothing happened.
But then you eat.
A couple of times.
Wait.
Do you think...?
Oh, sorry.
No, it's okay.
No, it's not right,
I did not.
Does Dad know?
Yes.
How did that go?
It's not good.
But he's good, I think.
I think.
I do not know, autumn.
What about Rosie?
She does not know.
I will never know.
That's probably for the best.
-Yes.
Do you still love daddy?
I do not think he's gay,
I mean, he's just confused.
Delio's bed with him in the camp
last year, nothing happened.
Well, you've shared a bed with Logan
and nothing happened
But it does not change anything.
Comrade, Logan is not gay.
-Kuper.
What?
I'm not saying that's a bad thing,
I'm just saying that this is obvious.
It's not a good thing,
it is safe.
So, what do you think?
Well,
I think that Christ teaches us to love everyone,
Whether zavisinici,
criminals or gays.
Hate the sin, love the sinner.
Well, yes.
That surprises me.
Why?
I do not know.
I think I...
I think that's all people
immediately realized.
You think because I'm married?
Yeah.
It's not at all the same.
People do not choose your race
The way you choose to be gay.
Hello.
-Hi Dad.
Where have you been?
Oh, we're just talking.
Have you seen Ricky?
Yes.
You could be a little
with your brother, you know!
I
I'll be back!
It will be right back.
How are you?
-Okay.
You?
-I'm fine.
After
If you... yeah, I do not know...
If you want to go back, anyway,
Promise not to run away and scream.
Can you save me?
I can save you.
If you choked you, I would like,
I believe, I believe the...
Me, I
need resuscitation.
Thank you.
-You're welcome.
You're a great savior.
I did, always. It does not matter what.
Hey, Kate, can we talk for a moment
?
Well, I'll try to survive without you.
Okay, thanks a lot, try to...
I'm sorry, gentlemen,
forgive me, gentlemen,
Forgive me, Lord,
forgive me, gentlemen...
Stop.
I think that this is a much
things happening, you know,
Bad influence
Sexual confusion.
Well, comrade, the best we can
is to follow Christ's example.
That's it.
I do not know, it seems to me
this is very urgent.
It seems to me as if...
It seems to me that we are losing a whole generation.
Oh, well, that's what I'm talking about!
What were you doing, honey?
Watching TV.
I do not know why.
This is a beautiful night.
Do you want to leave her alone!
Do whatever you want, Grace!
Thank you, Dad.
What is it?
Well, I'm a little!
Well, I'm going to bring you, Miss Rosie.
Do you all drink alcohol?
Where is Aron went?
I do not know.
Do you know that I love you?
Of course I do.
Oh, thank you, dear.
Do you want some?
No, thank you.
Kathleen
I'm not sure for some of these
Henrijevih comrades.
What?
For those there.
Oh, Heather, and Kristina?
They are very good
Henry's girlfriend.
They are beautiful girls.
A Logan that he is safe
poor, right?
You know what, I think it's time
to change the channel, Bob?
Let's move on to the next level?
I'm not sure what that means, but-
In fact, I'll do it.
Hen!
What ?!
Our Miks?
Do it!
Does anybody want to take a swim?
I will.
Grace...
Come on, Grace, move!
Yes.
autumn
What?
Swimming?
Happy birthday, honey.
Thank you.
Hello.
Heather. Christina.
Keep shark.
Bring the shark here.
Welcome back to the pool.
It's nice to be back.
Well... hello everyone, hello...
Before we adjourn tonight
I'll ask Bob if it's okay that I somehow
blessed
i get into this house
i bless you
beautiful young man
whose birthday
we are celebrating today.
Amin.
I love you, buddy.
Mama.
Lord, I want to thank you
For this beautiful young man
that Henry has become.
Thank you gave him life,
and allowed us to enjoy the time with him.
As he enters
his late teenage years,
we ask you to stay with him
at every step of his way.
-Are He no longer works?
-Who knows that?
Lord, we ask you to bless his parents
,
Who raised him well.
Set to fulfill this house
strength, wisdom and love
And taking our friend Henry
into the future filled with love
And happiness and your words.
Thank you for this night
And for all those who made this possible.
One, two, three, four...
God, we thank you.
God love you.
We can hear you now,
Singing in our hearts... God ..
MAMA.
Oh my stars, my son!
I'm sorry, Mom.
Please, can we go home?
I want to go home.
- Oh!
- Let's go.
Come on.
We do everything wrong, folks
You, you're gay, that's good.
God has made such a,
OK, fuck it.
Let's go home.
I will come later.
Where are you going to take him,
St. Francis?
Yes, this is the nearest, is not it?
- Yes.
I do not know why he did it.
We will be on the line.
Good night, Henri.
Happy Birthday.
Happy birthday, Henry.
-I Got my purse?
Yes, he's here, Mom.
Hey, Logan, I will send sms
your mother. OK
Okay.
Oh, wait.
Do you want to spend the night here?
Hello.
Thank you for coming.
Happy birthday.
-Thank you.
Hello.
-Hello.
Hi, yeah, we'll see you in church.
Yes, we make in the church.
-Okay.
Hello.
Thank you for coming.
Enjoy Connect to kids.
In all of them.
Yes.
Waiting, can you let us obavestiš-
Yes, come to us for that guy
- Ricky
-Answer Us how he is.
-I want to.
Tell your mom that we welcomed.
Yes. I will.
Let's go to the movies soon?
Yes.
Good.
Good night, sweetheart.
Happy Birthday.
Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Good.
- Hello.
Hello.
-Hello.
Well, we go to bed.
Do not stay up late,
tomorrow morning, we go to church.
Logan, your mom will
come here tomorrow morning at 8:00.
Good.
Good night, buddy.
Good night.
I hope that the celebrations were good.
It was. Thank you.
Good night, I love you.
-I love you.
I love you.
Want to go up?
Yes, I can not stay
long, but of course.
Good night, kid.
Good night.
Thank you for coming.
No problem.
Good night, Logan.
-Goodnight.
You know that I forgive you.
I know.
You know that.
It's not about that.
I think it is, but it is not so.
Bob.
What?
I think I'll go away for a while...
Kathleen, please, do not do that...
I'm sorry.
Please...
I think
I'm going to see if Amy
may take me some time.
Listen...
-I'll church,
You do not have to say church.
But I will go to see if my Amy
Allow me to be with her for a while.
A ti...
You, Bob.
You should be more with your boyfriend.
But you he needs you.
No, you need it more.
He needs your blessing.
Hey, I listen to music when
go to sleep,
If it's wrong?
Yes, that's nice.
Well... What do you want to hear?
It's not important.
You have good taste, you dial.
Good.
Hey...
I want to apologize for...
I have not talked to you in school.
or...
What can I hung out with you.
I'm sorry.
That's fine.
Do you want to love?
What do you think?
I think... this.
Perhaps this is good.
Good.