Voice: Oh, no!
Here we go!
I told you!
It's started.
Meow.
Cat: Aunt Hilda,
Aunt Zelda, come quick!
There's trouble
in Sabrina's room.
Cat:
Come on!
Meow!
Oh, no, Hilda.
Good night.
We've got to get her down
before she hurts herself
on the roof beams.
Salem,
you were supposed
to be watching her!
First we have to
move her over the bed.
Okay, but careful
Don't wake her up.
Sail softly down,
like a feather borne,
down safe to bed
to greet the morn.
You know, her powers are
certainly beginning to bud.
As long as
they don't bloom
before the full moon.
[sneezes]
Mmm.
You are so good
at that, Zelda.
Well, we all have
our strengths.
Maybe we could give her
a teensy hint
- just so she's--
- Perish the thought.
Do you want her to
start off with a strike
against her from the Council?
The rule is clear.
No matter what,
she can't know
until the full moon
after her 16th birthday,
and then we can tell her.
I know.
Shh!
Zelda:
I just hope she doesn't have a
conniption when she finds out.
- A what?
- You know, freak.
Radio:
It's a beautiful sunny day
in Riverdale today.
We expect highs about
70 degrees.
You're listening to WITC
radio on your A.M. dial.
Coming up,
an oldie but goody.
Did something strange
happen last night?
No.
What's wrong?
Why do you ask?
Well, it's just so weird.
Did someone rearrange my
furniture while I was sleeping?
What?
My bed moved
at least three feet.
Well, maybe we
had an earthquake.
We don't get earthquakes
in Riverdale.
Nope, in case
you didn't notice,
I've been here three months,
and nothing ever happens
in Riverdale.
Besides, Salem
would have warned us.
Wouldn't you, Salem?
Everybody knows
cats are psychic.
[laughs]
They are?
Sometimes I swear
I can hear his thoughts.
Salem's such
a special cat.
I had the strangest
dream last night.
Really, dear?
What about?
Well, I dreamt I was flying.
I was high above the town
just floating.
Oh, I used to have
that same dream when I was--
[thump]
when I was dreaming.
Which I don't anymore.
Hilda:
Well, whatever.
Talking about dreams...
Did you ever have the one
where you realized
you were late for class?
Don't wig. I'm going.
I'm going.
- Here.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
Bye.
[purring]
Sometimes I think
there's something very odd
about those two.
Don't you, Salem?
[meows]
♪ [hip-hop] ♪
♪ Well, I'm the mac daddy
on the left-hand side... ♪
[chattering]
Mondo styling boots, man.
Those are cool.
Thanks.
What's up?
Do I seem
different to you?
Taller.
No, I'm serious.
Do you ever feel like
you don't fit in?
Every day of the week, man.
Every day of the week.
[bell ringing]
I mean that there
was something
really wrong with you.
Like I had a disease
or something weird?
No, not a disease.
Just something...different.
Well, look, why do you think
that they have a counselor
here at school?
Everybody thinks
they've got a problem.
We're the troubled
youth of today.
I mean, my parents can't wait
until I go away to college
and come back human.
Hey, Sabrina.
Hey, Harvey.
How's it going?
Good. Hey,
what happened to you?
What?
I don't know.
You seem different.
Hey, was it
something I said?
Yeah.
Nice.
[grunting]
You've got style, Harvard.
Anyone ever tell you that?
All the time.
- You got it?
- Yes, I have it.
Ethics 101.
You're going to get
a B+ on this paper.
I knew I could count on you.
Thanks a lot, buddy.
That's great.
Let's get out of here.
Seth, he's a sophomore.
Well, no one's perfect.
Whatever.
Just look at her.
Miss Best, All-World,
Katy Lemore.
Really, who says?
Her own imagination.
Whoa. Tres great foliage.
I've got stuff growing
out of my locker, too,
but I think it's mold
from an avocado sandwich,
or something.
You must have
a secret admirer.
Shh. You're the only one
who knows it's my birthday.
Your birthday.
Right, right.
Your birthday's on the 27th,
and that would make it today.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Let's go to class.
Yeah.
[bell rings]
[whistle blowing]
Focus, please, ladies.
Keep your eye
on the ball.
Sorry, Miss Jones.
Check that out, Sabrina.
Seth? He's okay, I guess.
Okay? Come on.
He's more than okay.
[whistle blowing]
[grunting]
[laughing]
You guys okay?
- Whoops.
- Did you see that?
Oh, my God.
Come on guys, keep the pace.
I'm dumping Seth.
What?
I thought you two
were madly in love.
We are.
Am I missing something?
Fran, you're so naive
when it comes to l'amour.
Huh?
Matters of the heart.
A stagnant relationship
is doomed to failure.
I just want to keep him
on his toes.
Hey.
So, where's the party?
Party?
Well, I'm invited, right?
We're pals, aren't we?
So who's it for?
Sabrina.
Sabrina?
Oh, you mean that good-looking
transfer student, right.
Right.
Where's Katy?
You didn't hear?
We broke up.
I'm a free man.
Hey, Mr. Dingle!
Hi, girls.
[engine starts]
Marnie, do you
believe in magic?
Well, the first time
Bobby Peterson kissed me,
it was magic.
Of course, I got nauseous
and felt like
I was gonna hurl, but...
That's not what I meant.
I was thinking more along
the lines of the supernatural.
You mean like
astral projection
and channeling and
the Psychic Network?
Sort of.
I mean, let me ask you this.
Are the aliens really the ones
who built the pyramids?
Come on, I'm serious.
Sure.
Absolutely positively not.
Anybody here?
I'm home.
Great, they've forgotten
my birthday.
Hmm.
Well, there's always pizza.
Sure.
All:
Surprise!
What?
Surprise, sweetheart!
You should've seen
the look on your face.
Happy birthday,
Sabrina!
Look, we even
have enough food.
Look at this.
Food! Food.
This is great.
You're the best.
Actually, I know
I'm incredible,
but this was all
Harvey's idea.
Harvey's?
Yeah, I just thought
it would be a nice way
for you to make
some new friends.
That was really sweet.
Forgot my birthday.
Really, Sabrina.
Yeah, it was nothing.
Of course, I had some
help from your aunts.
They're both
really something.
They're something, all right.
Harvey!
Your nachos are burning.
I'll be right back.
This party just
hit the big time.
- What?
- It's Seth.
Well, obviously
we were expected.
Cool.
Okay, he is sort of cute.
Oh, cute.
Come on, Sabrina.
You're sixteen, now.
This guy isn't cute.
He's a man.
[laughing]
Anyway, have a good time.
This is a great
party, Harvey.
You're--You're a genius.
She's having a great time.
Yeah, well,
she's a great kid.
A kid?
Come on.
In case you haven't noticed,
she's not really a kid anymore.
I've noticed.
Yeah, it's so obvious.
♪ [rock] ♪
♪ Don't ask no questions ♪
♪ I've got no answers ♪
♪ I've never felt
this way before ♪
♪ We've both got others ♪
You must be
the birthday girl.
Well, happy birthday.
I'm Seth.
I know.
So, how do you like
Riverdale so far?
Things are definitely
looking up.
You noticed.
Listen up!
Who wants to play
pin the tail on the donkey?
What is this, some kind
of time warp, or something?
Hey, lady,
this isn't 3rd grade.
Maybe it would be fun.
Yeah. Yeah, maybe it'd be cool.
Right?
Yeah, I guess.
Harvey:
Hey, can I help at all?
Yeah, thanks, Harvey.
Could you hold this?
Okay, turn around.
[laughing]
[phone dialing]
[phone ringing]
Yes?
It's Fran.
You'll never believe this.
What?
Seth is here
at Sabrina's party.
I can't believe it.
What's he doing there?
He's playing pin the tail
on the donkey,
and he looks like
he's having a good time.
[engine starts]
If anyone tries to steal him
from me, they're dead meat.
Do you hear me?
Dead meat.
[tires screeching]
[door opening]
Who's there?
You're not even close.
Wrong again.
Could you please move?
Say pretty please.
Pretty please
with sugar on top.
I don't think
it's going to work.
What did I tell you?
You weren't even close.
Have you two met?
Sabrina, this is Katy.
Katy, this is Sabrina.
Charmed.
Likewise.
It's Sabrina's birthday.
Oh, really?
I would never have guessed.
Sweet 16.
[CD skipping]
Oh, what's happening
to the CD player?
Katy, have a hat.
Join the festivities.
It goes on you head.
Okay, sweetheart.
- Coming through.
- Excuse me.
♪ For she's a
jolly good fellow ♪
♪ Which nobody
can deny ♪
[cheering]
Happy birthday!
Make a wish,
sweetheart.
And blow out the candles.
That's good.
Keep going, keep going.
You can do it.
The other one.
[insects buzzing]
Oh, Good.
Nice one. Look.
Somebody...
Excuse me.
You jerk!
I'm soaked!
I'm sorry,
but you were on fire!
I saved you life.
You hair was burning.
I thought it was
important to you.
And I just thought
I was helping.
Yes, you did.
Thanks, Harvey.
Are you okay?
No thanks to you.
Are you coming?
Well, no.
I thought I was a free man.
Suit yourself.
Well, um...
Who wants cake?
So, did you have
a good birthday?
It was great.
You know that friend
of yours, Katy?
She's really quite
the comedian.
She'll do anything for a laugh.
A real hot-head.
Yeah, she's something,
all right.
It was the strangest thing.
I thought that--
You know, your parents called
today from Sri Lanka.
More cake?
I can't believe
I missed them.
Did you get a number?
Oh, honey, it was
a terrible connection.
They're on the move, anyway.
Next stop, Venice
They'll call again.
We know you
miss them, sweetheart.
They sent their love.
Hey, Sabrina,
look on the bright side.
They're halfway through
their sabbatical.
I don't know what I'd do
without you two.
Ah, well, we're just glad
we could be here to guide you
through your special time.
My special time?
Your birthday.
She means your
special birthday.
Your special present.
My special present?
Well, where is it?
Well, it hasn't
arrived yet.
Your parents mailed it,
and you know how the mail is.
They are always so slow.
But don't fret, I have
a feeling it will be here
any day now.
If it gets here at all.
Oh, it'll get here, all right.
[owl hooting]
[meows]
[purring]
[footsteps]
[creaking]
[cover closing]
"For Sabrina,
Happy 16th.
"To be opened only
under the full moon.
Love, Mom and Dad."
There's nothing here.
It's blank.
[door opening]
[purring]
I'm losing it.
I'm definitely
losing it.
[meows]
[phone ringing]
Mmm.
Cool.
Look, you think they're talking
to their stock brokers?
Harvey, thanks for those
flowers in my locker
the other day.
You figured it out, huh?
Yeah, I figured it out.
You're a real pal, Harvey.
Anyone ever tell you that?
Yeah, all the time.
Boy:
Hey, there's the boys.
Hey!
He's a senior, Sabrina.
[laughing]
I said, he's a senior.
So that means he can't
be seen with a sophomore?
No, it means he doesn't
even see sophomores.
I wish I could change that.
Anyway, he came
to my party.
He just came for
the free food.
I don't think so.
What, what do we
have here?
See you later, dudes.
He called us dudes!
Both:
Ahh!
Yeah.
[hurdle falling]
[groaning]
Why are we here?
Oh, come on, we get
to check out the boys
on the track team
and target a date
for the Spring Fling
which is a very good reason
to want to get
on the track team
Seth's on it.
You're a genius.
I know.
Come on, ladies.
I want everyone to
try out for this event.
Yeah, right.
Katy Lemore's already
on this event
and she owns this event.
Nobody ever wants to
try out against her.
Katy Lemore thinks
she owns everything.
[chuckles]
That's how it's done, kids.
Have you thrown
a javelin before?
- Nope.
- You'll catch on fast.
First time for everything.
Okay, ladies, listen up.
You all saw how Katy did it.
Just follow her moves.
Okay, I'll show you
how to do it.
Come with me.
First, you take
the javelin,
and you hold it right here.
Now, there are
three different grips.
Wish I knew
what I was doing.
[tinkling chimes]
Did you, um...
Okay.
Let's go.
Don't just stand there.
At least try it.
Woo hoo!
Yeah!
Just proves there's such
thing as beginner's luck.
Coach:
You're a natural, Sabrina.
Do you want to
be on the team?
Well, okay.
Sure.
Great.
Okay, training starts
tomorrow after school.
That was great!
Sorry you didn't
get on the team.
Oh, it's okay.
I didn't expect to.
My house, this weekend.
The whole team
is invited.
And I will take it
as a personal insult if
everybody's not there.
What's going on?
Oh, it's Katy's annual
pool party for the track team.
Katy:
I mean everybody.
That means you, too,
Sabrina.
I want you to
make sure you're there.
I wouldn't miss it
for the world.
Great.
Well?
This and the Spring Fling
are, like the social events
of the year.
What do you
think this means?
It means we have
to go shopping!
♪ [rock] ♪
♪ Awesome lady,
fashion lover ♪
♪ Chews them up
and spits them out ♪
♪ Keeps her weapons
undercover ♪
♪ Never leaves me
with a doubt ♪
♪ Makes me do just
what she pleases ♪
♪ Everything just
seems so right ♪
♪ When she talks
she never teases ♪
♪ Keeps me up all
through the night ♪
♪ She's hot,
she's got ♪
♪ Personality,
personality ♪
♪ All right,
all night ♪
♪ Personality,
personality ♪
♪ Personality ♪
I think it
is the first time
Katy Lemore will know
the meaning of the word
competition.
$75?
I wish it was less.
Is that all?
Yeah.
[scanner beeps]
Oh. It's only $15.
It must be on sale.
That's strange.
Man, this is
your luck day.
I don't know
what's going on.
Yeah, I guess so.
[chattering]
♪ Personality,
personality ♪
♪ All right,
all night ♪
♪ Personality ♪
Oh!
Okay, would you
like us to wait?
Oh, no, thanks.
It's okay.
Well, call us, and
we'll pick you up, then.
We'll manage a ride home.
Are you sure?
Positive.
Well, then,
have a good time.
Yeah.
Zelda:
Yeah, have fun, girls.
Both:
Bye.
Zelda:
Fun, fun, lots of fun.
Okay? Fun, fun, fun.
Fun, fun.
Maybe we should spy on her.
- Salem?
- Meow.
You be good.
Stay out of trouble.
And keep an eye on her.
Salem: Meow.
Leave it to me.
Ahh!
♪ [reggae] ♪
What's wrong
with this picture?
You mean other than
the fact we're on
the lifestyles
of the rich and stupid?
Like, you noticed?
Like, totally.
Both:
Cool.
Wow. If this is how
the other half lives,
I could get used to this.
[no audible dialogue]
Katy:
Sabrina.
So glad you could make it.
Brought your little
friend along.
Hi, Marty.
Marnie.
Oh. Whatever.
Oh, listen, we're having
a big diving contest in a bit.
You do dive,
don't you?
She was a gold medalist
at her last school.
Is that true?
Actually, it was silver.
Great.
Well, we'll see you
in a bit.
Oh, the cabana's
over there.
Okay.
♪ And so I say ♪
♪ I've got you on my mind ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Every time that you go,
every time you go ♪
♪ Every time that you go ♪
Hello, Harvey.
Hi.
Katy.
Hey, the water's
great, you know.
Great party.
Since when are you
on the track team?
I'm not really on it,
but I'm near it.
Near it?
Yeah, coach wants me
to be the hurdle painter.
You know, hurdles
get beat up, and
need painting.
I'm considering the job.
Hey, you look
great, you know.
Stunning, really.
Just, wow.
Save it.
You can stay.
You'll probably enjoy
the festivities coming up.
I know how much you love
surprise parties.
Salem: Meow.
Nice hair cut.
[barks]
Come back.
I was just kidding.
This wax should
help her take off.
Sabrina!
Hey, great suit.
Thanks.
So Katy was telling us that
you're a fantastic diver.
Oh, well, I didn't exactly
say I was fantastic.
But everybody's waiting
to see you dive.
We can't wait.
The diving contest
is starting.
You're up first.
Everybody can't wait
to see your technique.
Seth especially.
[barks]
She's going to be
so embarrassed
she'll transfer right back to
wherever it was she came from
and never show her face again.
Fran:
You're jealous.
I'm not jealous.
I'm just going to make sure
there's nothing
to be jealous about.
Attention.
Attention please.
What are you doing?
I'm just making sure
everybody's watching.
Sabrina, Sabrina, Sabrina!
Sabrina, Sabrina, Sabrina.
Well, are you going
to dive, or not?
Holy cow.
[cheering]
Okay, you wanna play rough?
No more Mr. Nice Guy.
[barking and meowing]
[cat hisses,
dog whines]
Wimp.
You know, Sabrina,
I don't think it's
a very good idea to go
up against Katy Lemore.
Can I use your mic?
Sabrina:
She seems like
she's out to get me.
What'd I do?
Marnie:
C'mon, you've been
staring at Seth
like he's an hors d'oeuvre,
and you haven't eaten
for a week.
Have not.
Yeah, right.
Sabrina:
I think he's so gorgeous.
I mean he even makes
Brad Pitt look like a nerd.
Did you check out
his butt?
[applause, cheering]
I could watch those tight buns
run around the track all day.
[laughing]
He's so gorgeous.
Fran:
I could watch those buns
all day.
[jeering, laughing]
- That's too funny.
- That's hilarious.
♪ [cartoon music] ♪
Sabrina?
I can't ever
go back to school.
I want to go back
to Massachusetts.
What is it, sweetheart?
Weeping Sabrina, dry
your tears of concern.
Tonight, you have
great secrets to learn.
[owl hooting]
To be opened only
under the full moon.
[flames flickering]
Ah, we're just in time.
And I see you've already
found it by yourself.
This, dear, is your heritage.
You've probably been feeling
a bit odd lately.
Different?
Well, you are different.
You're a witch.
[giggles]
A witch?
[laughs]
Uh-huh.
I can't be a witch.
There's no such thing.
Oh, you're wrong, sweetheart.
We're witches, too.
[wind whipping]
Your javelin, dear.
This can't be happening.
This has got to
be a dream.
You're not dreaming,
Sabrina..
This special place exists
only for witches.
It's the world of magic.
Every new witch must come here
to receive the ancient book.
Why are you
doing this to me?
It's not something
we're doing to you.
It's something you are.
It's how you were born.
With the gift
of magic.
Magic?
Both:
Magic.
That's right.
This has got
to be a dream.
Morning.
Good morning.
Morning, sweetheart.
Salem:
No, it wasn't a dream.
It was real.
[spits]
You really can talk.
I'm hallucinating.
This is nuts.
No, no.
You're not crazy.
It all seems very strange,
but it's all very real.
My parents?
Yes, they're witches, too.
They had to go
on their sabbatical
because every witch must
be delivered to trainers
when they reach
their 16th birthday.
We'll be here to help you as
you learn to use your powers.
My powers?
Of course, dear.
What's the point of
being a witch
if you can't do magic?
- Salem.
- Now, wait a minute.
I don't want to be
your guinea pig.
Though you're handsome
as a cat,
not, not pig,
turn into rat.
[laughing]
Salem:
Very funny.
You've had your joke.
Cool.
Oh, that's nothing, dear.
When Hilda gets going,
she's really good.
You know that whole
Susan Lucci thing?
The actress?
She's lost 15 years in a row.
Hilda hates that show.
Wow.
Though you're handsome
as a rat,
Salem, change back
into a cat.
I don't know why
I put up with this.
Witches.
But every witch must
learn to harness her powers.
The decision of how
to use your power
is yours alone, Sabrina.
And Salem?
Salem is our
familiar, dear.
He's an animal
that help do our bidding.
[tinkling chimes]
Here's some extra homework.
[phone rings]
Your friends are calling.
I can't face them.
Why ever not?
The party last night,
Katy's party.
Everybody heard me talking,
my personal feelings about...
About what, dear?
Okay, Sabrina.
Just this once.
Sail the times
of wind and place
so poor Sabrina
can save face.
Time, begone.
- [phone ringing]
- What do you mean?
It never happened.
Hello?
Hey, Sabrina.
You okay?
I think so.
Must've been
the food, huh?
It was real nasty,
and you looked so sick.
Sick?
Yeah, and it's a shame, too,
'cause you missed
all those guys
in those little bathing suits
and diving competition.
I didn't even dive?
No one heard me talking?
Dive? You were only
there 10 minutes.
This is so great.
See you soon.
Okay.
Bye.
It worked.
It's true.
I'm a witch.
Salem:
Go ahead.
Cast a spell.
You know you want to.
We'll, I'm a witch,
so let's make a switch.
Stop.
Stop!
[chattering]
[bell rings]
Okay, folks,
put away your books.
Let's get to it.
Hi, Marnie.
Hello, Sabrina.
Not high.
That is going to be
my score on this test.
[sighs]
Let's get to it.
B...B, B, B, B.
No, no.
Photosynthesis...
C...B.
Yeah, yeah. B.
[groans]
No.
Is there a problem,
Miss Littlefield?
No, Mr. Dingle.
There's no problem.
No problem at all.
In my mind, in my sight, make
all of Marnie's answers right.
Hmm?
Is there a discussion
you two would like to share?
No, Mr. Dingle.
Okay, time's up.
Pass over your papers.
Maybe I'll look at
yours now, Marnie.
Sure, why not.
It seems you've
done very well.
I have?
Yes, you have.
I think I'll go lie down.
What's going on with him?
[murmuring]
Look at him.
He's gonzo.
[whispering]
Okay, here goes
the big one.
By the power of
all the stars above me,
I send this spell
for Seth to love me.
♪ [discordant tones] ♪
Hi.
What happened?
I don't know.
It didn't work.
What?
Nothing.
I've got news.
You know that guy,
the shot putter,
the guy I danced with?
He asked me
to the Spring Fling.
Plan worked.
I got a date.
Oh, you did.
That's great!
Yeah, I thought so.
So, all we have to do
is find you somebody,
and it's perfect.
That's not going
to be so easy.
Want some tea,
sweetheart?
What's wrong,
Sabrina?
I don't understand.
It was going so well!
What's that,
sweetheart?
The witchcraft.
It was working,
and then, nothing.
Zilch.
What happened?
Well, I was trying
some things out
and everything
was going fine,
except that...
well, I was concentrating
on this boy.
A boy?
Yeah, you know Seth.
He was at my party?
He's maybe the most popular
boy in the whole school?
Well, I cast a spell on him,
you know, to get him
to notice me--
You cast a spell for love.
Yeah, I cast
a spell for love.
Well, you saw him.
You know.
Yes, we know,
but you can't.
Can't what?
You can't cast
a spell for love.
No such thing
as a love potion?
Not anymore.
In the old days,
some witches,
some bad witches,
did cast spells for love.
And it always ended
in heartache.
So the Great Witches'
Council convened
and it was decided
to abdicate that power.
We got in a circle,
we held hands.
We promised.
Love is too precious
for anyone to tamper with.
I can't believe
you did that.
Hilda:
Well, it's true, dear.
Great, the one power
that might really be useful,
and I don't even have it.
Believe me, Sabrina,
it's better this way.
What's the point
of being a witch?
Maybe she'll be one who
doesn't appreciate her powers.
Oh, give her time.
It's not easy, growing up.
You never appreciated
your magic
until you were 200,
if I recall.
[bell rings]
As the flames engulfed her,
her screams grew louder.
Her struggle ceased,
a smile locked on
her twisted face.
Such was the fate
of Abby Lang, the witch.
Did she really cause
the storm that destroyed
the Isle of May
lighthouse in 1636?
We'll never know.
But they thought so.
Any comments, Sabrina?
No.
One more thought:
during the reign of
Queen Elizabeth I, 1558-1603,
any woman who lured a man into
marriage by the aid of makeup
high-heeled shoes or a wig
was subject to punishment
as a witch.
How many young ladies
in this room today
are guilty of the same
with the Spring Fling
just around the corner?
Class dismissed.
[chattering]
Sabrina, hi.
Hi.
Oh, it's too bad you had
to go home so early.
We had a great
surprise planned.
Well, my guess is I wouldn't
have liked it much, anyway
Well, maybe some other time.
So, I hear Carpenter's
renting a limousine
for the Spring Fling.
I guess my telling him how
cheap he is finally paid off.
I just hope he doesn't
get a white one.
They're so tacky.
Katy:
We're probably going
in Seth's Camaro.
Fran:
You're going with Seth?
When did he ask you?
He hasn't, yet.
But I know he'll ask me
when I win the All City.
And then I'll put him
out of his misery and accept.
Watch this princess
throw a fit.
Send her a humongous...
[boing]
Hey, what's that
on your face?
What?
Come here.
Ah!
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God!
Fran:
That's so gross!
Katy:
Oh!
Oh, God.
[laughing]
Katy, where are you going?
What are you going to do
with that thing?
Mm.
Remain...
Okay.
First, you take
a deep breath
and jump.
Then when you're on
your way back to the ground,
you simply miss.
Miss what?
Zelda:
You miss the ground.
Uh, I don't know about
this whole flying thing.
Oh, oh, Sabrina.
One of the greatest
treats of being a witch
is being able to fly.
What about that little
thing called gravity?
Magic, it's just a matter
of technique, practice,
and one other thing.
What?
When you feel good
about who you are,
being true to yourself,
then nothing
can keep you down.
[grunts]
Okay, um...
Bad luck.
Try again.
Okay?
Yeah.
Ready, girl?
Okay.
[grunts]
No, get--
[grunting]
Oh.
Um...
Okay, um...
Maybe you should
give it a rest.
She needs to
try this on her own.
I think you're right.
Okay.
[crash]
Salem:
Get off my tail!
Did they burn
real witches at the stake?
No, of course not.
Whoever told you that
was a liar and a fraud.
Usually, they were
drowned in a river.
- Or hung.
- Thanks, I feel
a lot better.
That was only
the bad witches.
You're a good witch.
You've got nothing
to worry about.
Trust me.
Well, I now know how to
get Seth to ask me
to the Spring Fling.
And it's not by using
a love spell.
I found a loophole.
Meow.
Do tell.
Don't be such
a nosy cat.
You'll just have to
wait and see.
Hey, Ward.
- Hey.
All right, we got--
Come on, Sabrina.
Get the lead out.
I want you
on the field now.
Every dog has his day,
every shark has his fin.
But I've got the sneakers
that can run like the wind.
- Hey, Sabrina.
- Hi, Marnie.
Okay, let's run
the 200.
Sabrina, are you okay?
Yeah, fine, great.
Runners,
take your marks.
Set.
Hey, Sophomore.
Ready to lose?
[starter pistol]
Harvey:
Go, Sabrina!
[cheers]
All right, my sister!
Go!
Woo!
Move it, Katy!
[panting]
[cheering]
Woo!
Great, race, Sabrina.
You made record time.
All right, all right.
Yeah!
Look at her!
Woo!
Wow!
Holy Moses.
Coach:
Sabrina,
you can stop now.
Sabrina.
Way to go.
Thanks.
Hey, Sabrina.
That was a great run.
- It was, really--
- Thanks.
Careful she doesn't
run over you, Harvey.
A little competition
never hurt anybody.
One race doesn't
make a winner.
Well, everybody has
an off day, huh, Katy?
Yeah, well, I'm just
saving myself for All City.
That's when we'll separate
the winners from the losers.
Okay.
[chattering]
Look, there's
Sabrina and Tonto.
You know, she's cool.
Hey, Sabrina.
Over here.
You talking to me?
Yeah, you.
Come on, join us.
It'll be fun.
Oh, I don't know.
Don't worry.
Katy went home
to lick her wounds.
There's space.
Oh, well.
Sure, why not?
Great.
Come on.
Come on, Marnie.
It'll be fun.
Sure, I mean, I don't think
there's much space
left at the table,
but, sure.
Actually, I just remembered
that I forgot something
at my locker, so--
I'm gonna go get that.
- But Marnie--
- Suit yourself.
Come on.
Better go, Sabrina.
There's only so much
room at the table.
Fran:
Hi, Sabrina.
- Hi.
Katy is so mad.
She thinks you
cheated somehow.
She's throwing a fit.
So we were just discussing
Freddi's new nose.
What do you think?
Very nice.
Nice?
It's a masterpiece.
I mean, it will be
when the swelling goes down.
Dr. Hoftedder is a genius.
He's going to do
my lips next.
What do you think?
Well, I think
they're fine now.
[chuckles]
You're kidding, right?
How can you be
all that you can be
if you're not willing
to look like someone else?
You know what I mean?
So, who does your hair?
I do.
Oh, that's okay.
We'll get you out of
your cocoon in no time.
So, are you going to beat Katy
at the All City race?
I'm sure going to try.
Sabrina, cut
the modesty shtick.
We're your friends now.
[chuckles]
[slurping]
Oh, sister.
We're made some
chili, sweetheart.
Would you like some?
No, no thanks.
I think it could
use some eye of newt.
Just kidding.
I knew that.
So, anything exciting
happen today?
Yeah. I finally got
Seth to notice me.
What do you mean, got him?
Well, I found a way around
that no love spell rule.
I put a spell
on my running shoes,
I beat Katy, and Seth
was so impressed,
I'm sure he's going to ask me--
Sabrina, didn't you
read the magic book?
Didn't Salem tell you?
Salem:
Uh-oh.
Tell me what?
You did tell her,
Salem, didn't you?
You are supposed
to be helping.
Well, not exactly.
Why didn't you tell her?
Isn't it obvious?
He wants her
all to himself.
What are you
talking about?
Hilda:
Shame on you, Salem.
Zelda:
Double shame.
Would somebody please tell me
what's going on here?
It's right here in the book.
Where's the book?
Here it is.
Witches and cows...
Humans.
Witches and humans.
Witches are forbidden
to use witchcraft to win love,
but if witchcraft is
used on a mortal
in any form to win his love,
then true love
is not in his heart,
and his kiss shall...
His kiss shall what?
His kiss shall turn you
into a witch's familiar.
You mean I'll be turned
into a cat?
For 90 years.
But if he loves you
with a pure heart,
then you're okay.
Oh, well...I know Seth
would love me that way.
You know,
with a pure heart.
Then there's no problem.
Love is something that's
given freely by others
because they want you
to have it.
And animal passion alone
begets animal passion,
just like Salem.
You mean Salem--
'Fraid so.
Salem was once
a misguided warlock.
But it was worth it.
Well, I know Seth
and he would never...
Oh, well...
Then you have
nothing to worry about.
Teenagers.
Hi.
Excuse me?
Did somebody say something?
Come on.
Don't take it
personally.
So how was your power lunch
with Katy's gang the other day?
It was no biggie.
Well, it was to me.
I mean, did you see
the way they looked at me?
No.
I didn't.
The truth of the matter is,
I didn't feel that comfortable
there either.
So?
So...
I just wanted
to tell you I'm sorry.
Go on.
You're not going to make
this easy, are you?
No way, sister.
Look, I know I've been
acting strange lately.
It's Seth.
I've never felt this way
about anyone before.
Does your heart
start pounding?
Yeah.
And you start to feel
a little faint when he's near?
Like I might
just fall over.
And your palms
get all sweaty?
Drenched.
Have you ever
felt like this?
Nope. No, I haven't.
So that's not how
you feel about Jeff?
No, that's not how
I feel about Jeff.
I'm going to the Fling
with Jeff
for one reason
and one reason only.
What's that?
He asked me.
He gets bonus points
for having a car,
but that's all I need.
Shouldn't sell
yourself short.
I'm not selling
myself at all.
I mean, I'm just
being realistic.
It's a dance.
It's not a marriage.
Jeff's fine.
So, you really have it
bad, though, don't you?
Yeah.
Poor kid.
But you know, once I win
All City for the school,
I know Seth will ask me
to the Spring Fling.
I just know it.
Well, then a girl's
gotta do what a girl's
gotta do, don't we?
Will you help me, Marnie?
Yeah, sure.
How?
I've got a plan.
Phase two.
Well, what was phase one?
Don't ask.
I'm gonna win him
on my own.
Well, of course you are.
With my help.
[chuckles]
Right.
So let's do this.
- Ready?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Woo!
On your mark,
get set,
Go!
Kick Katy's butt.
Go, go, go, go!
Woo!
Yay!
Yeah! Woo!
- Yeah!
Hey, Harvard.
You don't happen to have
an extra set
of those questions
for econ, do you?
What questions?
The ones on the test
I'm supposed to take
next period.
No, Seth, I don't.
Sorry.
Well, I guess I'll have to get
them from somebody else, then.
So, you and Katy
still history?
Well, I haven't
actually made up my mind.
But I'm probably going to
ask whoever wins All City.
Unless, well...
Unless maybe you
should ask Katy out.
Don't be ridiculous.
What's the matter?
Don't you like her?
Sure, I like her.
I mean, what's not to like?
Any guy would have to be
insane not to want to--
It's only that--
Yes?
She's not my type.
I see what you mean.
So you've got a babe lined up
for the Spring Fling,
don't you, Harvard?
I'm still working on it.
[cheering]
All:
Woo!
P.A.:
Would all contestants please
report to center field?
Coach:
Okay, ladies, this is it.
The big one.
Today, we are going
to be in competition
and the whole idea
behind competition
is to win.
All:
Yeah!
Am I making
myself clear?
All:
Yeah.
Good.
All right, so,
let's go, Riverdale!
[cheering]
Right on!
P.A.:
The owner of a brown Chevrolet,
you left your lights on.
Isn't that Sabrina's
friend, Harvey?
Yes, it is.
He's awfully cute.
He looks troubled.
Perhaps I'll just
see what he's thinking.
Zelda.
He looks so unhappy.
Okay, then be quick.
Okay.
Zelda:
Oh.
Hilda:
What?
Zelda:
He wants Sabrina to lose.
Why?
Well, haven't you
figured that out?
Here, listen.
Okay.
Oh.
- Oh, my.
- Uh-huh.
Love.
Can't live with it,
can't live without it.
Oh.
Thanks.
I'm on my own now,
win or lose,
so drain the magic
from my shoes.
And the plot thickens.
P.A.:
Ladies and gentlemen, please
stay clear of the track.
[trumpet fanfare, cheering]
[sighs]
[starter pistol]
[cheering]
Yeah!
Yes!
P.A.:
Katy Lemore of
Riverdale High
wins the sprint.
Well, couldn't stay
away, could you, Salem?
Salem:
I thought you'd be
interested to know
that Sabrina is not
going to use any magic.
She's testing
this boy's love.
Oh, Zelda.
Maybe she will be the witch
we expected her to be.
Ta-ta.
P.A.:
Ladies and Gentlemen,
the up to date results...
[cheering]
Oh.
Oh, yes!
Sabrina!
P.A.:
The winner of
the broad jump event
is Sabrina Sawyer
of Riverdale High.
Central High
comes in second
and Western in third.
Riverdale High
wins another event.
Sabrina Sawyer
wins the javelin throw.
Second place goes to Central.
Third, Western.
Come on.
P.A.:
Ladies and Gentlemen,
the winner of the All City meet
comes down to one event:
the 800-meter run.
Oh, God.
I can't watch.
[starter pistol]
Ugh!
[gasping]
No, she's got to
do this on her own.
Every dog has his day,
every shark has his fin.
And I've got
the sneakers that can win.
Sabrina.
So, do you want to go
to the Spring Fling, or what?
♪ [marching band] ♪
All:
Yay, Riverdale!
Hey, Harvey.
How's it going?
Hi, Sabrina.
So, Seth asked you
to the dance, huh?
Yeah.
You really like him,
don't you?
Him?
Seth?
Yeah, I do.
I guess every girl
in the school would say
the same thing.
Can I ask you a question?
What's he got--
What makes him so--
Perfect?
Well, first,
there's his smile--
No, no.
Sorry I asked.
What's wrong with you,
Harvey?
It's just that
I've been thinking
a lot about you and me.
There's something
I want to tell you.
What?
Aw, nothing.
Have a nice time
with Seth.
You'll save a dance
for me, right?
Sure.
You promise?
Of course.
Great.
[purring]
You can turn
around now.
Do you like it?
Wow.
I mean, meow!
You know what I mean.
Do you think Seth
will like it?
- Yeah.
- [car honking]
Unless someone slapped him
with a stupid stick.
Hilda:
Sabrina?
Are you coming down?
That must be him.
Wish me luck.
[sighs]
Is he here yet?
Well, he appears to
be waiting in his car.
Well, I better
get going.
If he was a gentleman,
he would come to the house,
introduce himself properly,
and escort you
to his nice car.
Maybe he's no gentleman.
She's in big trouble.
Maybe we should drive you.
No, that's okay.
See you later.
♪ [hip-hop] ♪
- Hey, Sabrina.
- Hi, Seth.
You don't mind if we give
these guys a lift, do you?
Oh, no.
That's okay.
- Wicked.
- Hi, guys.
Hiya.
Hockey's much
tougher than football.
What?
Have you ever seen
a Riverdale hockey player?
Maybe he'd like to
be turned into a mouse.
Oh, don't be silly.
She's so vulnerable.
We've got to help her.
Hilda, rules are rules.
There can be no intervention.
This is one lesson she's
just going to have
to learn on her own.
Hey, Seth,
what's going on?
Seth, man,
- Hilda.
- What?
- I'm not doing anything.
- Put the car down.
Put the car down.
C'mon, let's go,
let's go.
[tires squealing]
Another game of fish.
♪ [synthpop] ♪
Cool.
One for me, Harvey.
Actually, give us
the whole tray.
Okay.
This silver and white thing
is just brilliant.
You're so great.
Yeah, uh, thanks.
Hey, uh, listen.
Is Sabrina here yet?
Marnie:
I haven't seen her.
Hey, Seth.
♪ If you can be open ♪
♪ I can do without
the attitude ♪
♪ So just be straightforward,
that's all I ever ask of you ♪
Seth, over here!
Can you excuse me
for just a sec, Sabrina?
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Sure.
♪ Is there a lack of ♪
♪ Communication ♪
♪ It's just a lack of ♪
♪ Ooh, oh ♪
♪ You run and hide ♪
No, no.
What I mean is are
we going to hit the lookout
after the Fling, or what?
It's tradition, man.
Yeah, right.
Uh, Seth.
You know, I'm really
kind of thirsty.
Oh, you know what?
Me, too.
Get me a root beer, would you?
You guys thirsty?
- Nah.
- I don't want anything.
Get me a root beer.
Thanks.
Yeah, so, um...
How's it going,
Cinderella?
Fine. Can I get four colas
and a root beer
for Prince Charming?
So what's the prince like
up close and personal?
Well, there are a
lot of people around.
It's kind of loud.
I guess there isn't enough
of him to go around, huh?
Hey, look.
There's Marnie and Jeff.
Wow, she looks like
she's having a great time.
Go, Marnie!
♪ It's just a lack of ♪
♪ Communication ♪
♪ Is there a lack of ♪
♪ It's just a lack of ♪
♪ Communication ♪
♪ Whoa! ♪
♪ Is there a lack of ♪
♪ Communication ♪
Hey, remember,
one dance for me, right?
You promised.
Sure.
Really?
A promise is a promise.
Sabrina, Katy
needs to talk to you.
Alone.
It's very important.
Yeah, yeah.
We'll get one later.
Thanks.
Nice outfit.
What can I do for you?
I'm not falling for this
cutie pie act of yours.
You're not some innocent
little sophomore.
I'm onto you.
All this voodoo stuff.
I'm gonna tell everyone that
you're some kind of a witch.
I am?
That's ridiculous.
I'll get you, my pretty,
and your little dog, too.
[cackles]
You really are a witch,
and I'm gonna
tell everyone.
Wait, Katy.
Come back. You can't!
Come back!
You, who lives to impress,
change back into
your poodle pest.
[barks]
[whines and barks]
[dog barking]
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Hey, there you are.
There's a bunch of us
going up to Lookout Point.
Let's go.
It'll be fun.
I want us to get to know
each other a little better.
Well, I sort of promised Harvey
I'd have a dance with him.
We'll be back in lots of time.
I promise.
Scout's honor.
I don't know.
Don't know what?
Don't you trust me?
Well, sure.
Well, then, come on.
Hey, have you seen
Sabrina at all?
Both:
No.
[dog barking]
Hey, has anyone
seen Sabrina?
Uh, yeah. She went up
to Lookout Point with Seth.
Some guys have all the luck,
you know what I mean?
Later.
- So, what are you doing?
- Well--
Uh, hey, can I
borrow your bike?
Sure.
Thanks a lot.
What?
Wow.
It's beautiful.
Come on over.
I am over.
No, closer.
I thought you said
there were going to be
a lot of other people here.
Everybody that counts
is in this car right now.
But I think what
we need here is
a little less talk
and a little more action.
Relax.
I'm relaxed.
I want us to get
to know each other.
Sabrina.
It's getting late.
No, we have the whole night.
I mean, nobody comes back
from the Fling until dawn.
It'd be uncool.
It would?
Yes.
It would.
Seth, I want you
to take me back now.
You want me
to take you back?
Yeah. You promised.
I promised that?
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, yeah, that must have
been me trying to get you
to come to Lookout.
I, uh--
Oh, come on.
Just one kiss.
No.
Just come on.
You lied to me.
Then why'd you
come up here?
I don't know.
Don't know what?
Look, come on.
Where are you going?
The dance is almost over.
We won't make it
back now, anyway.
So get back in the car.
I wouldn't get back in that car
with you for anything.
You're no boy scout.
Fine. You can walk, then.
[engine starts]
[no audible dialogue]
[alarm, honking]
Oh, what now?
[honking]
What the--
Come here!
Stop!
[shouting]
Stupid car!
What's going on?
Come here!
Harvey, is that you?
[grunts]
Need a lift?
What are you
doing here?
I thought I'd get
some fresh air.
You know, check out the stars.
That sort of thing.
Yeah, right.
Come on.
Well, if you really want to
know, I came to rescue you.
But I can see
you're okay.
I'm not so sure.
I've been a real idiot.
Big time.
Don't be hard on yourself.
Can you forgive me?
Yeah, sure.
Friends?
Friends.
You know, I only
have one regret.
That we won't get to
have our dance.
Me, too.
You know, I've got an idea.
We can still make it.
Get on.
I've got a better idea.
Come here.
Close your eyes.
Harvey, my friend
he is so dear,
listen for music
only we two can hear.
Do you hear that?
[laughing]
Look!
What?
- What?
- Didn't you see that?
No.
But--
How did we get here?
You drove us.
On the bike.
Don't you remember?
Oh, yeah.
Right.
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ La, la, la,
la, la, la, la ♪
♪ If you ever need a friend ♪
♪ He'll be there for you,
he'll be there for you ♪
♪ If ever you're in trouble ♪
♪ He'll see you through,
he'll see you through ♪
[dog barking]
[laughs]
[chattering]
[barking]
[no audible dialogue]
Katy, what are you doing?
I have no idea.
What happened?
I don't know.
What are you all
staring at?
Seth.
- You all right?
- Oh, Seth.
Can you ever forgive me?
I only dumped you because
I wanted to improve the quality
of our love.
I'm so ashamed.
♪ He'll never leave
or forsake you ♪
Don't they make
a beautiful couple?
Just beautiful.
Oh!
Ha, ha, ha!
♪ You can call him up ♪
♪ Morning, noon,
night or day ♪
♪ There is no problem
too big for him to handle ♪
♪ He'll never leave
or forsake you ♪
♪ He'll be there ♪
What's the matter?
Do I seem different to you?
Have I changed?
Yes.
You're even more beautiful.
♪ Protection from all harm ♪
♪ If you need a hand to hold ♪