Ah! Damn!
Just once I wish they would
discover diamonds in Hawaii.
[Laughing]
Hustle it, Tanner!
Tanner, get outta there!
Let's go you guys.
Let's go!
[Work horn]
Come on!
They got some environmentalist
showing up from Washington,
And I sure as hell
don't want her to see
The way of setting
explosives below
the aquifer.
You set?
Let her rip, Tyee!
Fire in the hole!
[Beeping]
[Explosion]
Alright, let's go!
Alright, everybody, listen up!
The truckers are going
to make one more run!
But there's a bonus for
everyone if we get this process
Before our friend
from Washington arrives.
[Laughter]
You are talking my language,
boss.
Whoa!
Tanner?
What the hell just happened?
Must have fallen.
Tanner, where's Tanner?
Get rescue down here now!
Now, damn it!!!!
Come on Kruger, it's breakup.
You know I can't send
a truck up that road.
It's 34 degrees!
Ice melts at 32!
Thanks for the lift.
So 44 huh?
Just had to get one
more run in, didn't ya?
A guys gotta make
a living.
Yeah, yeah, save it.
[Laughing]
44 flip-flops each.
Makes it a tie for top dog,
Jack!
There's never been
a tie before.
First time for everything.
Uh-huh.
Come on, let's get paid.
You're killing me,
you know that, don't you?
Fine, fine, I'll see
what I can do.
Just hang tight.
Damn it!
Your name is on this thing
five times, Jack.
This was supposed
to be my year.
You know, the Japanese say
a tie is better than a win.
I'm not Japanese and this
sure ain't no geisha house.
Alright, before you rush off
to cash these
At the first bank you see
in Fairbanks,
I need one more delivery.
(All): Aww!!!!
Come on, Sparkman,
hand them over.
I got a hot date tonight with
this Swedish little seat-cover
You ever saw.
She calls me every day.
Yeah, it's his mom.
He's late on the rent.
[Laughter]
Listen, Kruger is desperate
for enough explosives
To hold him over 'till the
first boat gets through.
Explosives?
I wouldn't hold manure
through that slush.
You can count me out.
Count me out.
Come on.
Triple rate.
Come on, triple?
Take it or leave it,
Sparky.
Triple rate.
Jack, I need two rigs.
One more flip-flop makes me
top dog, Jack.
Triple rate, huh?
Just kill ya if I won this,
wouldn't it?
What do you say, Jack?
I say I'm a poor trucker
with alimony payments.
You got yourself
another rig.
Now you're talking.
One more convoy of 20 tons
of kaboom, my friend.
Don't get nervous
on me now...
Huh?
[Laughs]
I am going in.
Need light and steady.
Hang in there Tanner!
Coming down!
[Growls]
Holy Mother!!!
Run! Everybody run!!!!
Run! Go go!!!
[Growls]
Go, go!!!
Bombshell!!!
Radio for help!!!
I'll get the explosives!!
Can you move?!
Yeah!
[Growls]
[Screaming]
Okay, but no promises.
I appreciate your assistance.
Everybody appreciates.
You should appreciate crapping
on my already crappy day.
Welcome to my world.
[Screaming]
[Distant screams]
[Growls]
Mr. Kruger, thank god!
Get outta my way!
[Roar]
Ugh!!!!!!
Please... I don't want to die.
You're already dead.
Ahhhh!!!!!!!!!
What the hell is
that thing?!
Wentshu!
Wentshu!!!
I got keys,
I got keys!!!
[Gagging sounds]
Anybody call for help!
No!
Go, go, go!!!!
Come on, let me in!!
It's Kruger!!!
Let me in!!!!!!
You two make a break
for it.
I'll keep it busy.
You mean we let it eat
you while we run away?!
You don't get it, we
don't have a choice.
We need to get help now!
Go!
Hey! Haven't you loaded
up yet?
I hate hauling this stuff.
When it's on the trailer,
it's all dead weight to me.
Oh, god, that reminds me.
I knew this guy
in Oregon once,
Who was hauling this load of
explosives to this strip mine,
If this story ends with a bang,
spare me, will ya?
Oh, Jack, all my stories
end with a bang.
That's what makes them
so interesting.
Jack, got a hitchhiker
for you.
A what?
Rachel Harris.
Well, hello, Rachel.
I'm Neil Conroy, it's a pleasure
to meet you.
What's this about?
Some congressional
committee is demanding
An environmental assessment
of Arctic breeze.
So you're what...
a scientist?
Research analyst
actually.
Oooh.
Now, that's what I call
tax dollars at work.
She gets a ride up
there today
Or they're shutting
the mine down.
Oh, you're gonna love
the Arctic breeze doc.
It's got the charm of
a Siberian Gulag.
Why can't she take
the chopper?
Chopper is down, Jack.
Well, in that case you
never mind them, doc.
I'll be your chauffeur today.
Here, let me take
your bag for you.
You're riding with him, lady?
A trailer full of explosives
are the least of your worries.
You just shut your pie hole.
Honestly, ma'am, I'm a southern
gentleman.
Fine, she's all yours then.
You all set doc?
Let me give you the tour.
Now, if you come with me,
Let me introduce you
to my rig.
We got hot water, tunes.
Bye, bye Jack.
Have a good trip.
Well, welcome aboard doc.
This is my home away
from home here.
Nice.
Oh, yeah. She's a
nice '96 Peterbilt
With a big can 4-350,
got 3-90's and one
sweet air ride.
I have no idea
what you just said,
But I'll take your word
for it.
[Laughs]
She's also got 18 speed
floor transmission.
You know what that means?
No.
It means she may take
a little while,
But once she gets
warmed up
Oh, boy, she'll give you
one smooth ride
If you know what I mean.
Listen...
You're a smart gal,
aren't you?
Yeah.
Me too.
I lied, I'm a Pisces.
[Laughs]
I'll tell you what, doc,
tours not over.
I've got a whole big bedroom
back here.
Comfy mattress,
tons of videos,
Actually on second thought you
might not be into those videos.
I got satellite TV though,
HBO.
Appealing.
Want to give a lady a lift?
You know, you don't need
to worry about Neil.
He's all talk,
absolutely harmless.
I rode up here on a gravel
hauler with a teamster
That would not shut up.
I haven't really slept
in 24 hours.
So I could really use some...
Quiet.
You mind?
No, come on up.
[Country music]
***
Jack, you old dog!
You're one lucky suicide
jockey, you know that? 10-4.
Suicide jockey, huh?
That's a trucker's talk for
a driver hauling explosives.
Nice.
Hey doc,
Next 300 miles
there's nothing between us
And the cold blue sea except
a couple of feet of ice.
[Laughs]
Don't worry,
it's not that soft.
Don't listen to him, doc,
he's plenty soft.
You think someone got
a call out for help?
Wentshu took down
the satellite uplink.
That's the second time
I heard you call it that.
Wentshukumishiteu.
What are you talking about?
It's an Inuit legend.
Lives under the ice
and feeds on human flesh.
Wentshu.
No freaking legend
is taking me alive.
If it comes to it or us,
okay?
[Growls]
[Loud banging]
[Loud roar]
[Screaming]
Is this your daughter?
Yeah.
Are you married?
Divorced?
Messy, huh?
I thought you wanted
to sleep.
I was just trying
to make conversation.
*
What was that?
Hold on.
Are we turning around?
No, not when they're
paying triple we're not.
What do you say,
top dog?
Follow me
and stay close.
You're the expert.
10-4.
Open your door.
What?
If I tell you to jump you
do and ask no questions.
Okay.
Hold on.
Come on now.
I got your back.
Come on! Come on!
Come on now.
Come on.
Come on, baby.
There you go.
That's it.
We're good?
Yeah, we're good.
Welcome to life
on the ice road.
If I lost my rig,
You'd be hearing from
my insurance company.
Yeah, you wish, cowboy.
There really is nothing
out there, is there?
Well, not completely.
Do you want a coffee?
Don't tell me
there's a Starbucks.
Better.
Lowman's.
What's that?
Truck stop.
Lowman and his wife,
Beryl.
The best Java
for 300 miles.
Is that because it's the only
Java for 300 miles.
[Laughs]
You'll have to try it
someday.
No thanks.
I don't plan on spending
too much time on the ice road.
Yeah, I said that
once too.
Hey Jack, gate is up.
That's weird.
There is always somebody here.
[Laughs]
Something's not right.
They don't get
their explosives,
They just take
the day off?
No... this is something else.
Kruger!
Anybody here!!!
Oh, my god!
Oh, my god, Jack!!!
What the hell
happened here?
Oh, no.
Oh, my god!
Explosion?
If this is an accident, where
is the first response team?
Where is everybody?
I have to go find Kruger.
Kruger!!!!!
Jack!!!!
Oh, my god!
What happened here?
It's Reid.
I think I'm going
to be sick.
Jack, let's just get
outta here, man.
Okay?
Is anybody here!!!!!!!
No seriously Jack, let's just
get the hell out of here, okay?
Is anybody here!!!!!!!
Hello?!!!!
[Distant]
Over here!!!
Wait.
Did you hear that?
Over here!
It's coming from over there.
Jack!
Hello, over here!
Tyee!
Jack...
Did you see it?
The Wentshu?
The what?
Everyone always said
it was just a myth,
But I saw it.
It's true.
Tyee, where's everyone?
Dead.
Okay, let's get you back
to the truck.
You okay?
Can you walk?
Let's get outta here before
whatever that thing is returns.
You're gonna be fine,
alright?
We'll get you in the truck
and warmed up, alright?
[Growls]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!!!!
[Loud growls]
What the hell is that?
Wentshu.
Come on, come on, come on,
let's go.
Run, run, run!!!!!
We're not going
to make it Jack!!!!!
[Loud roar]
[Whisper]
That's it, go that way.
[Roar]
You go up and have a look and
make sure it doesn't come back.
Okay.
Tyee, what the hell
is that thing?
I told you...
it's Wentshu.
I thought it was just a story
to scare the kids,
But it's true.
What's the story?
It moves under rock, ice,
and on land and it eats...
What?
Us.
I saw it take Tanner
Krem, Reid.
Kruger too.
[Roars]
[Whispers]
It's crisscrossing
back and forth out there.
It can't see us...
Where did this thing
come from?
We set our charges deeper
into the permafrost
Than ever before.
The charge unearthed a ton
of high-grade diamonds.
It grabbed Tanner,
crawled out of the pit
And went wild.
[Loud roars]
Okay, okay.
So what do we do?
How did you survive?
I hid under this blanket.
The thermal blanket.
Kept me warm.
Well most of me.
[Roars]
Jack we can't stay
here, okay?
This thing is going
to find us.
[Truck engine starting]
Oh, my god,
that's my rig.
Someone just
started up my rig!
At least we know
we're not alone.
Alright, we're going to have
to make a run for it.
[Loud growls]
You ready?
Okay, now!!
Come on!!!
Come on! Come on!!!
Go, go, go!!!!
Nice of you to join
the party, Kruger!!!
Move over!
Go... Go... Go.
Good idea.
Alright.
Come on, baby.
Come on! Come on!!!
Come on!!!!
What the hell are
you doing?
Son of a bitch,
follow me!!
That's it!
Follow me,
leave them alone.
The road's that way.
Not leaving them behind.
This might be
our only chance!
Give me the wheel!!!
Shut up and sit down!!!!!!
I can't see him,
where is he?
I don't know!
I don't see it,
I don't see it!
Oh, geeze!
I think we lost it!
What the hell was
that thing?
I don't know.
Neil, I think we lost it.
Let's get the hell out
of here!
We're right behind you!
Kruger's with me!
He's seen better days,
but he'll make it!
Kruger's alive?
[Laughs]
I think we could go faster
if you unhook the trailer?
I'm not stopping until
there's a hundred miles
between us.
You don't understand...
It will never give up...
It will follow...
Unless that thing can do 45
miles an hour on the ice road,
It's not going to bother
us again.
Why is Neil pulling ahead?
Come on Neil,
give it more gas.
Come on Jack,
come on.
You okay back there?
Neil, I think we blew out
a couple tires.
I'll slow down so you can
keep up...
Slow down...
are you crazy?
Maybe you're used to
abandoning your men,
But I'm not leaving
him behind.
He needs my help!!!
Listen to me, what we need
is to get to Lowman's
He's got a ham radio.
We can call for help.
Jack can take care of
himself.
I'm not leaving him behind!!!
You don't like it,
feel free to walk!
Don't wait for us.
Get to Lowman's
and call for help.
Not leaving you behind, buddy,
I'll keep pace with you.
That cowboy doesn't know
what's good for him.
What would you do if
the situation was reversed?
Wentshu...
Try to rest, okay?
You think he could
be right?
Some kind of
Inuit legend?
I don't know.
It looked like a pliosaur
to me.
What, like a dinosaur?
Yeah.
In 2008, a Norwegian team of
scientists found a large skull
In the Arctic.
It had teeth 12-inches long.
No one seen anything like it.
They think it's the largest
marine predator that ever lived.
This give a name
to this thing?
Predator X.
[Loud noise]
Jack...
What the hell was that?
[Loud roars]
Nooooo!!!!!!!!!!
Noooooo!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
Ahhhhhhh!!!!!!!!!!
Stay back.
Oh my god!!!!
He just took him!!!!
[Loud roars]
Hold on! Hold on!!!
Fire!!!!!!!!
Fire!!!!!!!!!!!
What?!
We're on fire!!!!!!
Neil, we're on fire and
the thing is back!!!!!!
Yeah, I gotcha in
my mirrors.
You're lit up like a roman
candle, Jack!
Coming to get you, buddy!
Get ready to bail out.
What the hell are you doing?
Listen to him.
Jack knows what's right.
We have to warn others...
Trucker's don't
abandon truckers.
Going flaps down.
It's okay, it's okay.
You get ready to bail him out
when I pull up alongside.
Get ready to jump!
Cross my lap, come on!!!
When I say jump,
jump, alright!!
I got you!!!
What about you?
I'll be right behind you.
Hand!
Come on!!!
Don't worry, I'll catch you!!!!
Come on!
I'll catch you!!!
Come on, come on!!!
Come on!
Jump!
Jump!!!
Jump now!!!
Come on!!!!
Jack!
Ahhhhhhhh!!!!!!!!
Jack, nooooooo!!!!!!!!!
Did you get him?
It's too late!
Let's go! Let's go!
Nooooo! Jack!
Come on!!!!
Get in!
Noooo!!!!!!
I'm right here!
Jack, you're amazing!
Jack!!!
Good to see you again,
Jack.
Thanks.
Thanks for coming back.
Anytime.
You okay?
Yeah.
You?
Let me see.
Does it hurt?
A little bit.
I didn't know truckers
had such a low
tolerance for pain.
[Laughs]
I guess I owe you a beer.
I think you owe him
a six-pack.
You know what they say,
old truckers never die.
No, they just get
a new Peterbilt.
Wait a minute.
What's going on?
Why aren't' we going faster?
We'll jackknife.
We can't drive faster than
30 with that trailer.
Hang on, Doc.
You're about see the
fastest trailer drop
In trucking history.
Great!!!!!!!
Perfect!! Just perfect!!!!!
It's completely frozen!!!
Alright, let's see what
we knock loose.
Back there at the mine
I left Tyee all alone.
I hid while he was out there,
all alone...
Defenseless.
I heard him calling out,
I heard his voice
asking for help...
I could have
done something.
I should have
Survival is a strong
instinct.
Let me tell you something,
It had nothing to do
with survival,
It was fear,
plain and simple.
Sure, I saved myself,
but what about my men.
They were good men.
I worked with a lot of them
most of my life.
Good men with families
and I let them down.
And then when I saw
your trucks...
If I could have gotten
that truck started...
I would have left.
That's right.
I would have gotten away as far
as possible from the mine...
From that thing...
What Neil did back there...
Saving you guys...
I would never have
come back for you.
The ice, it's...
It's not the ice...
It's something underneath it.
What?
We've got to get
out of here, now!!
Run!!!!!!!
Run!!!!
Ahhhhhhh!!!!!!!!
Nooooo!!!!!!!!!
Come on, let's go! Noooo!!!
He's gone, he's gone!!!!!!
Come on, get in!!!!
Go, go, go!
Damn it!
Tail end's still dragging
like it's knee-deep in mud.
We didn't disconnect.
Hook-up must be iced over.
What if you swerve
from side-to-side
Wouldn't that make
the trailer drop.
Good thinking doc.
We'll make a trucker
out of you yet.
Look like our friend
wants to play.
You gotta be kidding me!
Won't this thing
give up?!
We're the only food source
for about 100 miles.
Well, guess who's coming
for dinner.
Let's see who
blinks first.
[Truck horn]
Come on, baby!
Alright, hang on tight!
[Laughing]
Now that's some driving!
We've got to rid
of that trailer.
It's Alamo time.
Keep it in gear.
I'll break the ice
off the hitch,
As soon as the trailer's
free you go!
You don't wait for me.
We're not going
to leave you.
Don't worry, I'll handle it.
Same goes for me,
buddy.
Jack!!!!!!!!
We gotta go!!!
Go, go!!!!!!
Get in the snow.
What?
[Snarls and growls]
Doc...
That was close.
Jack!
Where's Jack?
Jack, are you alright?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
[Loud roars]
Four more payments and it
would have been all mine.
You have insurance,
right?
Not sure if I took the
prehistoric monster coverage.
Let's get outta here before
it remembers we're here.
Lowman's is a few miles
away, let's go.
It shouldn't be too
much further.
We need to rest.
We can't, Rachel we can't.
If we stay here we're dead,
alright?
Either from hypothermia
or that thing out there.
Rachel, listen to me
please get up!!!
I need you to get up.
I need you to dig deep and find
something to live for.
Please just get up,
Rachel.
[Laughs]
That's deep, Jack.
Besides Doc, you don't want
our little friend back there
To see you down,
do you?
Come on, I'm freezing!!
What about you?
What's your reason?
Is it your daughter?
Maybe.
Do you ever see her?
Every summer for one week.
That's not very much.
No, it's not.
Why'd you leave?
What are you doing
all the way up here?
I was having trouble
making ends meet.
Supporting myself and...
Covering
child support payments.
Lost my house.
Sold pretty well everything
I owned, my rig.
Environmental regulations,
price of fuel,
I was barely
holding on to that.
One day, a friend of mine
tells me about the ice road.
Says it pays
the big bucks.
So I figured, what the hell,
I'll get out of town,
Try something new.
I only planned on doing
it for a few seasons
While I got on
my feet.
I guess one day I realized
I got nothing to go back to.
You don't know that unless
you go back, do you?
Do me a favor.
If we get out of this.
Go see your daughter.
Stop hiding up here.
I will.
Come on, about a mile left
to Lowman's.
You sure
he's gonna be there?
He'll be there.
He has to be.
Neil!!! Come on buddy.
We're almost there.
You don't want me to get
back without you.
I'll give you 45 trips.
You know what that means.
That'd makes me top dog.
Oh, god, I'd never
hear the end of it.
Don't worry man, we'll
collect that trophy together.
How you doing, Doc?
Never better.
Good to hear.
What's that smell?
It's Lowman's
He's still there!
Okay, doc.
[Car engine revving]
Hold up!!!! Hold up!!!!!!
Damn it!
How many times
I gotta tell you,
Don't back it in!
Olson's not coming all
the way out here
To tow you out again...
I know Olson isn't coming
all the way out here...
So try listening next time,
will ya?
You're pointing it out
isn't helping!
You're such a Nancy sometimes.
That's why you love me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You hear that?
What?
Doc says you need
hearing aids and now
You got super hearing?
Sounds like voices.
There's ain't nobody
for a hundred miles.
Lowman!
Lowman!!!
Lowman, who's that?
Lowman!!
Lowman!!!
It's Jack!
What?
Jack!
Jack.
What in the name of Sam?
Neil, is that you?
Beryl, you're a sight
for sore eyes.
You look like
death warmed over.
Come on, let's
get you inside.
Where are your trucks?
We need to call for help.
Something attacked the mine.
Let's get you inside.
Go inside.
Alright.
Lowman, it's some kind
of creature.
What's that you say?
Lowman, come on, let's
get that water boiling.
Lowman why don't you call
for the chopper.
Let's get these folks
out of here.
What the hell are
you guys doing?
Close these curtains
and stay out of sight.
There's something out there.
Is the back door locked.
Bolted.
This is Lowman, we need
a chopper.
[Static sounds]
Let me try.
Hello? Hello?
Beryl here, I got us
an emergency...
[Static sounds]
It's the aurora.
Plays havoc
with the radio.
You said you guys were attacked
by something?
Destroyed the mine,
my rig...
Jack's too.
Tyee said it was
a Went-shu.
A Wentshu?
Come on, Beryl.
It's just an ol' Eskimo
legend.
Inuit. It's an Inuit legend.
Same thing.
What do you know?
I have been living here
50 years
And I've never seen one.
[Rumbling sounds]
It's here.
How big is this thing?
Big enough.
Everyone hold
still.
You got a gun?
Gun, do you have a gun!!!!
Yeah, yeah, right here.
Come on, Jack,
we're not talking about
a coyote here.
I took down a black bear
with that thing once.
It was a cub with a limp.
Fiercest creature
you ever saw.
You don't understand.
Nothing stops a Wentshu
Not once it has
a human's scent.
Nothing.
Well, I'm sure as hell
going to try.
Neil, check the upstairs
window.
Great idea.
You don't have to worry.
I built this place
with my own hands.
Nothing's going to get in here.
We're safe.
Listen to you, the big hero.
Do you remember the storm
two seasons ago?
We had ten tons of snow...
Six tons.
On that roof
and we were fine.
This thing is a little
bigger than that.
[Roars]
Maybe we should
just hold up here
Until someone comes through.
Maybe you haven't
noticed, Doc.
That ice road is
melting out there.
Someone's gonna notice
if they don't hear
from the mine.
Someone's going to come
investigate.
We got food enough.
If we have to, we can wait
for first boat.
I am not waiting
for no boat, alright?
Neil's right.
We can't wait here.
We gotta go.
Wait, what are we all
complaining about?
I got a truck out there.
Two key words:
Out... There!
But it's close.
Not close enough.
[Loud roars]
Is it there?
Yeah, it's there.
I want to see it.
I've heard these stories
all my life.
[Roars]
Holy!
Believe us now?
My grandfather was right!
Lowman, that is a Wentshu.
The man-eater.
Just like the legend says.
Still think that little popgun
is going to do the job?
Eskimo mumbo jumbo.
Inuit.
I told you Inuit.
I have an idea.
I'd love to hear it.
Remember the blanket
and the snow?
It couldn't see.
I think it's vision is based on
some kind of thermal imaging.
It can only see heat.
Like warm bodies
Yeah.
We can use that to create
a diversion.
And then run to
the truck.
Sounds like a plan.
So how do we do it?
We have to wait.
We can't go at night,
it's too cold.
We'd be too easy
to find us.
We'll wait until morning.
Hate to break it to you, Doc,
But it doesn't get
too warm around here.
Not even during
the day time.
Every little bit will count.
Then we'll wait
until sunrise.
And then I'm going to stab
it right through the heart.
Where do you suppose
the heart is on that thing, doc?
Forget the heart,
aim for the eye.
Yeah, he's probably right.
If this thing survived
under the pressure
Of tons of rock and permafrost
for who knows how long
Just imagine how
thick its skin is?
Fine.
The eye it is.
You should talk to him.
What do you mean?
Don't give me that.
I might be stuck here
looking after this old dump,
Doesn't mean I don't remember
what it's like to fall in love.
Believe it or not, he was
once the most dashing,
Charming man in town.
The idea of going up to him
terrified me.
But I knew if I was going
to make him mine...
I just have to do it.
And you know what?
Not a day goes by that
I don't thank the stars
I took that chance.
Jack's a good man.
And you might not get
a chance later.
Go on.
This'll keep you awake.
Thank you.
I told you, best coffee
for 300 miles.
Of course it's the only coffee
[Laugh]
Thanks by the way.
For what?
Saving my life back there.
As I recall, you saved
mine a couple times too.
Who knew a bunch of
colliding charged particles
Could be so beautiful.
The Cree call it "the
Dance of the Spirits".
Dance of the Spirits.
I like that.
What brought you
up here?
A gravel hauler.
That's not what I meant.
Nobody comes up here
to the edge of the world
Without being pushed.
I was pushed.
A guy?
Yeah.
It was my career or him.
He lost?
You might say he won.
You know Alaska is
kind of the last stop
for social misfits.
After the lower 48,
there is no other place to go.
So it kind of makes us
kindred spirits.
You think so?
I hope so.
I came up here because
I wanted to get away
from anything
And anyone I knew.
I just figured if I didn't
know anyone,
No one would hurt me.
I could just disappear.
There is something
about living up here,
Isolated from the rest
of the world
Forces you to learn how
to live with yourself.
Alone...
Survive...
The only problem is
sometimes you learn
that lesson too well
And you forget
what it means...
To have other people
in your life.
I think I am starting
to remember.
Me too.
Alright, I am clear
on this side.
Here.
Try this.
Thank you.
When I start the truck,
you three come running.
Don't give it too much gas.
I'll be careful.
You better.
I ain't running
this place by myself.
Ready?
Yeah.
Now!
Once you start it,
put it in gear.
It's gonna take a while
to warm up.
He doc, I am going
to light you up.
Hopefully the heat
from this distracts it.
[Car engine attempting to start]
I told you, not too much gas!
Jack...
Keep trying!!!!
[Gunfire]
Lowman!!!!!
[Loud roars]
I'm working on it!
No!
They know what they're doing!
[Gunfire]
Go back in the house!!!!!
Go, go, go!!!!!
No, no, no!!
[Sobbing]
It's gone.
You go help Jack.
I'll find him.
Jack, Jack, Jack!!
Can you hear me?!
We got to get him inside!!!
Come on, buddy.
Get the spark.
Lowman!!
Lowman, please.
Jack!
Jack!!!
I thought I lost you.
You can't get rid of me
that easy.
Where's Lowman?
Beryl?
Where are they?
They are still outside.
I gotta go!
I gotta help.
I can't see Beryl anywhere.
I am going to go find her.
No, no, no.
Neil, wait, wait, wait!!!
[Growls]
I have an idea.
Can you hook this
to the generator...
Get some kind of current.
Yeah, yeah.
I can, uh...
Splice this extension cable
to the tech cable.
Give him the shock
of his life.
Rachel, find me
some tape, okay?
Give me the tape,
let's see.
This is what we're going
to do.
You get it hooked up.
I am going to throw it up
to the roof to distract it.
[Sobbing]
Ready?
Now!!!!!
[Squeals]
I knew you'd come.
He'd done the same for me.
Help me take him home.
Of course I will.
Come on.
[Squeals]
Beryl!!
Stay with me, okay.
Jack... Jack...
He's going.
Okay.
I'm here, I'm here...
I got you.
This was our home.
Let it be our coffin.
Don't talk like that.
It's what he would want.
Beryl, you're going
to be up
And making your trucker's
special before you know it.
Five eggs, five flap jacks
[Choking]
And shot of whiskey...
Try to relax, okay?
Don't let the Wentshu
take us.
Promise?
I promise, I promise.
I promise I won't.
[Growling]
We're ready now!
Jack?
Neil?
What??
Without your trucks you
lose all your courage?
Rachel, there is nothing
left to do.
There is no cavalry coming,
it's just us.
So you just want
to give up?
I believed in you, Jack.
We can't give up now.
What happened
to all that talk
About having something
to live for.
I don't have anyone
to live for
But I am not going
to die here.
We have to do something,
maybe radio.
Rachel...
Rachel!
Doc... the generator's dead.
Lowman's truck is
too far out there.
What the hell do you
expect from us!!!!!!!
Rachel, there is no way to keep
this thing out.
Well, maybe we're thinking
about it all wrong.
Maybe we shouldn't try
to keep it out.
Did anyone ever tell you
you have a crazy streak?
You think it will work?
It might.
What the hell am
I missing here?
What?!
We aren't going to be able
to stop it from getting in.
But if we make this place
hot enough, smoky enough
It may not be able to see us
when it does get in.
It's too big to turn around.
It will give us time to get out
and get to the truck.
It's time to heat things up.
I knew we brought you
along for a reason, Doc.
[Loud roars]
We got company.
Go, go!!!!!
Neil! Come on!!!
[Loud squeals]
Neil!!!!
Come on!!!
[Loud squeals]
Come on!
Get up there!!!
Go, go!!!!
Age before beauty, buddy.
Get your butt up
those stairs.
[Loud roars]
Jack!
No! No!!!
Grab my hand Neil!
Come on! Come on!!!
Ahhhhh!!!!!!!!!!
I have to go to him!
There's nothing you
can do!!!!
I can't leave him!
He's gone!!!!
Go, go!!!!!
Come on, get up!
Get in the truck!
Start it up!
I am going to break
the tire loose, alright?
Yeah.
Come on, come on,
come on!!!!
Not too much gas!!!
Not too much gas!!
Go get going!
[Roars]
Jack, it's coming!!!!!
Go, go. go!!!!!
Go!!!!
Come on!
We gotta make a run
for it!!!
There's nowhere to run.
What do we do?
You got a light?
Yeah.
Come on, come on!!!
Come on! Come on!!!!
Jack, it's coming!!
I know!!! Come on!!!!
Come on, come on,
come on!!!!!
You still want to play?!!!!
[Loud squeals]
Stay back!!!!!!
[Explosion]
You think it's over?
Yeah, it's over.
How about giving a girl
a lift?
I don't know, it all depends
where you're headed.
I was thinking about Seattle.
Seattle?
After that,
who knows where.
Thank you.
[Helicopter approaching]