Good. Thank you.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Right.
They're gonna be here
in 10, okay?
So, be ready.
Don't screw up.
Of course not, boss.
Go.
That's a big box.
Tiny tykes measured in
at well over 100 inches,
and I'd say 900 pounds each,
wouldn't you, Russ?
A hundred pounds
of beak and claws,
and the mangiest feathers you ever
laid your beautiful brown eyes on.
The male is a bit bigger
than the female
and a hell
of a lot more pissed off.
What's the matter?
You afraid of a big bird?
Harvey, maybe we should
rethink releasing
them in the aviary this quickly.
-Doing...
-Stop. Stop. Stop.
I did not hire you for advice.
I hired you
to be my bird watcher, okay?
Unacceptable.
Do you think
this is wise?
They could hurt themselves
in there.
Better than hurting us out here.
They will be fine.
All we need to do
is an initial check,
make sure my babies weren't
harmed in their voyage.
Do you realize what today is?
Do you realize?
Today is the day that the past
has collided with the future
in the pursuit of knowledge
that no one else has.
No one. Only us.
And you know
what that makes you?
What?
It makes you pioneers.
Like Lewis and Clark,
or Darwin, or Copernicus.
Now, there's a man
who changed the view of where we
stand in this universe today.
Right, Russ?
What he said.
Are they down?
Shut up, you idiot!
Hey!
You bastards awake?
All right, why don't you go join them?
Go join them.
Go. Go.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, I think we're good.
Open it up.
Are you sure about this?
What? Do you think
they're faking it?
They're freaking birds,
for Pete's sake.
There's a reason people coined
the term "bird brain."
Not much up there.
Maybe you should get in
the car just in case.
I think you're right.
How we doing?
We're good, boss.
All right, let's do this.
I think we're good.
Okay, let's drag
those bastards out of there.
Time for the good doctor to see
how Heckle and Jeckle are doing.
Okay, that's weird.
Hey, I hope
you didn't kill this...
one.
I'm gonna get in the car, too.
Get out of the way! Move it!
Don't shoot the bird!
Another weekend
with Mother Nature?
Yeah.
What you going in for this time?
Birdwatching.
I'm hoping I can find
a Falconidae caracara.
Falconacara what?
A Mexican eagle.
Another watcher spotted a nest
about four miles north of here.
What the hell is a Mexican eagle
nesting up in these parts anyhow?
They've been living in these
regions for hundreds of years.
No wonder San Antone
lost the Alamo?
Done planted a bunch of
spies up in the sky.
Yeah.
That cover it?
-Okay, you have a good weekend.
-Yeah.
You go out and find yourself
a big bird now.
Will do.
Come on, Dad. Pick up.
Hello, this is Keith Stern.
Sorry I can't come
to the phone right now.
But if you could
please leave a message,
I'll get back to you
as soon as I can.
Have a great day.
Hey, Dad, it's me,
your loving daughter.
I was just thinking about you.
I know you're probably on one
of your crazy bird adventures,
but give me a call.
It would have been
Mom's birthday next week,
so I'd like to do
something special.
Call me. I love you.
Look at that?
It's a thing of beauty.
So, Slater, she still
over at the compound?
-She only popped in for lunch.
-All right.
Speaking of lunch,
when's the next feeding?
Should be dropping in
any minute now.
What the hell kind of birds
are they feeding out here?
Hey.
How we doing?
-Any luck?
-Nope.
We'll have to start over.
What? What the hell
is going on?
I mean, this is the finest
incubation equipment on the market.
It's not the equipment.
Two of the eggs
had microbial contaminations.
Same as the last.
How can this be possible?
All it takes is one bad egg
to spoil the entire litter.
What's causing the
contamination this time?
-I think it's the soil.
-The soil?
By the time your men
are finding those litters,
primitive bacteria has
already contaminated them.
I mean, as you're aware,
those birds thrived...
They thrived in regions
this far north.
Soil now is different than it was
two and a half million years ago.
I think you would probably
have had better luck
trying to breed them on one of the
islands where you found them.
Well, that's not
gonna happen, is it?
You know, I hired you because you're
the best at what you do, right?
So if there's something to be
done with the soil, please do it,
because it's been
six months, okay?
Fix it! Fix it!
Well, unless your men are planning
to catch that hen's next litter
as it comes falling
from her rear,
I really don't see how you expect
me to make this happen overnight!
And I need more time.
Fine. Do it.
What the hell is that?
Gonna do me some fishing later.
Fishing?
Yes, sir.
Light one of those babies,
toss it in,
all the fish come bubbling up
to the surface. Easy as pie.
Here's your money.
Next time you come around, you leave
that stuff at home. You got it?
What is this?
It looks like someone's pet.
Looks like it's not your day,
Old Yeller?
You're bird food,
you mangy mutt.
Help!
Go! Go!
-Get to the gate!
-Where is it? I don't see it!
Get to the gate!
Keep going!
Don't touch the fence!
It's electrified!
Please!
-Quick!
-Get back!
-Let me out!
-I'm trying!
Let me do it!
What's the new combo?
Come on!
Get me out of here!
Let me out of here!
-Where's your gun?
-It's on the car.
Go get it!
-Hey, who are you calling?
-My dad.
He's going birdwatching
again this weekend.
Trying to get some prize photo for
this nature competition he entered.
Nature competition? Yeesh.
Thought I'd catch him before
he left the cabin, though.
Dude, your dad
seriously needs a girlfriend.
He loves his independence.
Nut doesn't fall
far from the tree.
How the hell
did neither of you see
that some schmuck got
into the aviary?
And how did you not see him get past
the compound fence in the first place?
We never saw him
on the feeds.
And I don't know how the hell
he got past the voltage fence,
but the main fence
anyone can hop right over.
Must have got in on the east
side, down by the river.
The birds never go there.
It's covered in trees.
I bet he went up over.
Yeah, you know, the birds mostly
stick to the western region anyhow.
That's where they've been
hunting these mutts. -Who cares?
He's in.
He clearly got through.
Now, we have a dead man
on our hands,
and what are we supposed
to do with this?
How are we supposed
to deal with this?
Could find his car.
Stage a crash somewhere.
That's a great idea.
Yeah, maybe we can just prop up
his half-eaten skeleton
and put it in the driver's seat.
What do you want us to do?
Shut up so I can think!
What's there to think about,
Harvey?
The jig is up.
Another man is dead.
And I doubt he's some ex-con no one
cares about like the last one.
Have you lost your mind?
They'll shut us down.
They'll take away my birds,
and god knows
what they'll do with them.
No, I found those birds on
my expedition. They're mine.
And they're dangerous.
Harvey, they're dangerous.
Why do we have to tell
the authorities anything?
They already think
this is a cat ranch.
We just tell them the man got mauled
by a big Bengal or something.
No, no, no. No, no, no, no no.
No, the rules change when an
animal kills a human being, okay?
Having a permit and a promise
to put them down is not enough.
They're gonna come
do an investigation.
They're gonna wanna
see the animal.
No, we say nothing to anyone.
-Got it?
-What?
Are you kidding?
That man could be married.
He could have a family.
He could have children.
You just can't dictate someone's
death like that, Harvey.
The man is a trespasser.
Think of the birds for a second, okay?
Think of the birds.
Think of what would happen if
those birds get into the hands
of this corrupt government.
Come on. We are this
close to hatching them.
Now, don't you think we at least
owe it to a dying species
to at least try?
This isn't
about the birds, Harvey.
It's never been
about the birds.
And your big,
archaeological expedition?
Just another notch
on an endless ego belt.
We all know
you're a money man, Harvey.
And when you hatch
an entire flock,
you'll do what you do best.
You'll take all the credit,
and you'll sell them
to the highest bidder.
Hey!
You don't walk out that door,
because you work for me,
and you do what I say.
Screw you, Sullivan.
I quit.
Let go. Come on.
Just... Just tell him
to let me go.
I gave you everything
that you wanted.
I gave you a house
in the Hamptons.
I gave you everything
that you asked for.
Well...
why don't you go get Dr. Slater's
car for her so she can leave?
Where's my car, Dale?
It's just down the drive there.
My keys.
Dale, don't do this.
Don't do this, Dale.
My things are ready.
Please have them picked up
in the morning.
I hate to see you go, Doc.
Me too.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Da...
Come on. Come on!
Dale!
All right, tranq 'em
and put 'em back in.
Hi, this is Keith Stern.
Pick up.
Sorry I can't come
to the phone right now.
But if you could
please leave a message,
I'll get back to you as soon as I can.
Have a great day.
Hey, here's
a little percolated roast
to perk up
my fave roomie's afternoon.
Thanks.
Hey, no word
from your pops yet?
You know what?
It's probably okay.
He's probably climbing
some mountain,
finding some bald eagle's
nest or something.
You know, it's gonna be okay.
It's Friday. He said he'd be
back Tuesday at the latest.
Yikes.
Well, what are you gonna do?
I...
am gonna look for him.
Have you thought about
maybe calling the police first?
Well, my dad keeps
a GPS tracker on him
whenever he goes
out into the wild.
My mom bought it
for his birthday two years ago
and made him promise
to always keep it in his gear.
The receiver is
at the cabin in the woods,
so I'm gonna start there.
Maddy, you can't traipse the backwoods
by yourself. That's insane.
Paige, I'm going.
End of story.
Fine, I'm coming with you.
Paige, you don't have to come.
No, you're crazy if you think I'm
letting you go out there by yourself.
Justin? Hey, it's Paige.
So, Maddy kind of needs a favor.
Yeah, you know that big,
bohunk friend of yours,
the one that's
into all the outdoorsy stuff?
Brett, yes!
So, we could
really use his help.
Maddy's dad is missing.
He went camping, and no one has
seen him since last week, so...
Really? Could you?
That would...
That would be amazing.
Of course you can come.
Maddy would really like that.
Yeah, we're packing right now.
I'll text you.
Thank you so much.
So, what makes you think
Maddy would like that?
'Cause Maddy does not.
Are we talking
about the same Maddie here?
'Cause the one I'm referring to
used to be totally in love
with her inseparable
best friend, Justin.
Yeah,
before he got a girlfriend.
Okay, how many times
do I have to repeat myself?
The guy obviously
started dating that sorostitute
in the first place
to make you jealous, okay?
-You're the one who went AWOL on him.
-Paige!
I'm stressed out enough
about my dad as it is.
I don't need any more
added anxiety, all right?
Now, just call him back and tell
him not to come, all right?
Maddy...
will it or will it not help us
to have an experienced hiker on
the trail help us look for him?
Okay, you said it yourself how
crazy-far your dad is willing to trek
in order to take some snapshots
of some strange species.
Okay, give me five to pack.
Looks like you bought yourself
a little time, my friends.
Chef has pulled the canine
cuisine from the menu.
The birds had themselves a nice,
little Slater soufflé last night.
Just get 'em out, Dale.
Hey, guys.
He did not bring
that slutosaurus.
Hey, are you okay?
Thanks, you guys, but you
really didn't have to do this.
Are you kidding? I would have been
pissed if you hadn't called me.
Anyway, besides...
it's the weekend, right?
We didn't have
anything better to do anyway.
Yeah, nothing better. Nope.
Look, it would have been the
same old beer pong and keggers.
My liver... could use a break
and a little fresh air.
Hop in.
Thanks, Rough and Tumble.
Taylor, so great to see you,
but you really
didn't have to come.
Two desperate girls
in the wild with my boyfriend?
Yes, I did.
Yikes.
Sorry. Window seats
give me the regurg.
I'm gonna need to sit bitch.
Fittingly.
All right, let's do this.
Fill her up, man.
I'll tell you what.
How about I put $4.50 in there
and take the rest
for you trying to punk me?
Turd.
My god.
Hi, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Hi. Yeah, where's
your nearest ladies' room?
Never again, Justin.
Excuse me.
Could you tell me?
My dad, he comes
through here all the time.
I don't know if you know him.
He, drives
this dirty, old jeep.
He's got a cabin
down by the river bend.
Yeah. Yeah.
He was just through here
last week.
Going out to find him
some kind of crazy bird.
Mexican barracuda or something.
But he hasn't come back through?
I ain't seen him.
He doesn't always stop
passing back neither.
-All right, thank you very much.
-Yeah.
-Hi.
-I'd like to pass please.
What's the magic word?
You wanna play?
Okay, well...
seeing that
we're all alone in here,
I'm gonna guess
the password is...
Lay a finger on me,
and I will kill you.
Get out of my way.
Hey, are you okay?
No, Justin,
and I won't be until I get a freaking
bar of service on my cell phone.
Gosh!
Did you hear those kids?
You know exactly who
they were talking about.
So, what happened to you?
What happened to my little baby?
Let me check that.
Russell to Sullivan.
You copy?
What?
We may have a little problemo.
The kid of our recent
bird fodder friend
is on the prowl with some kids
looking for him. Over.
Do they have any leads?
Nah, just asking questions to the
store clerk on the county road.
He's dumber than nails. Over.
Well, people go missing
in the woods all the time.
Copy that.
We're heading back now.
With my containment equipment.
Hood fumes and all, sir.
Over and out.
Do you know
where those kids went?
Can't say that I do.
I probably wouldn't tell you
if I did.
No.
That hot chick left her
cell in the bathroom.
I was hoping I could just catch
up with them and give it back.
They went east.
You best hurry.
This is it. Right up here.
Keep going.
Well, he definitely
hasn't come back.
That's his jeep.
Where in the world are we?
There he is.
Why isn't he moving?
Perhaps he got bored
and fell asleep.
What? I know I would.
Maddy, he's just birdwatching.
I imagine you have to sit pretty still
in order to not spook the birds.
About how far out is that?
Any idea?
I don't know. It looks like maybe...
seven, eight miles maybe.
All right,
that's where we'll start.
We're gonna need some maps.
Now, just in case he fell,
or got hurt, or something,
you got a first aid kit
around here too?
Yeah, I think he keeps one
under the bed in the bedroom.
Taylor,
would you grab it please?
Hogeye County, that's the one.
Right there. Looks about right.
Not bad, soldier.
Looks like
pretty rugged territory.
Yeah, the more remote
the better for my dad.
He can get closer to birds
that are unaccustomed to people.
Hey, check it.
This little blinking light thing
is fading out.
No! No, no, no, no!
Please! Please!
Please! Please! Please!
Why are we taking our bags?
Mother Nature
is unpredictable, Tay.
-It's always better to be prepared.
-For what?
You know, in case we have
to camp out or something.
Camp?
I don't understand why we
don't just call the police.
I mean, surely they're better
at handling this type of thing
than a bunch of kids
tramping around in the forest.
We report it, and then what?
They sit on it for 48 hours
until they do something?
No, thanks.
He's already been gone a week.
I'm not waiting around anymore.
Hey, Tay,
just think of it
as camping out overnight
for the newest handbag line
at Nordies.
Hey, there's the trail.
Hey.
Hey, we're gonna find him.
Okay, look,
we know his last location,
and he's gonna be all shocked when we barge
in there and interrupt his birdwatching.
Okay?
Come on.
What if he's not there?
So, how'd you know
I was into camping anyhow?
Get over yourself.
You know
your five-foot friend, Phil?
So, I work with him over
at the West Campus Coffeehouse.
He swoons every time he talks about
the way you handle a fishing rod.
I mean, no, it's not like I have a
problem with gay dudes or anything.
It's just that
we, like, lived together
in the same dorm room
freshman year.
I know.
I also know that you sleep nude.
-He told you that too?
-Yeah.
So...
So Phil digs me?
At least as much
as I dig chicks...
No, it's nothing like your web browser
history would lead you to believe.
So, sorry.
So, guys, I think
we should take a minute.
So...
Why didn't you call me?
I don't know. I guess I was just
so worried about my dad that I...
No, I don't mean this morning.
I mean, like, either of my
calls a few months back.
And then every time I text you, I
get this terse, one-word response
like, "Yes. No. Sure. Cool."
Like you feel obligated
to humor me or something.
No, it's not that.
It's just I've been busy.
With bio labs and stuff?
Yeah.
That's bull, Maddy,
and you know it.
You're, like, one of
the smartest people I know.
In fact,
our entire sophomore year,
you were finishing your papers
weeks before I did
when we had class together.
Well, yeah, that was before.
Before I had classes
for my major,
so you don't know how difficult
some of those labs can be.
Fine.
But I do know
when you're lying.
-Like you're lying now.
-I'm not lying.
You so are.
You're making
the exact same face you made
the night we double dipped
at the Dobie Theater
and then got busted by that
usher with the terrible breath.
He was like,
"May I see your ticket?"
God!
I didn't lie. You did.
Please.
I was too busy laughing
at your reaction, but...
you were a terrible liar then,
and you're a terrible liar now.
Maybe if you would have
been a better liar,
we wouldn't have gotten
kicked out.
My god!
"Sneaking into a second feature
"without paying is
a serious..."
Dude, like, so is your breath, so...
Ew. -Totally.
You know...
I've really missed you
this semester.
So, whatever I did
to make you mad,
I'm sorry.
Justin, it's not you.
It's just...
Guys, what's so funny?
Nothing.
Just reminiscing
our sophomore year.
Sophomore year.
Okay, that's the year
I was crowned homecoming queen
and became president
of the equestrian team, right?
I love that year.
Well, somebody's mood sure has
perked up since this afternoon.
Well, this wilderness girl selife I was
trying to post finally went through.
Random?
I think there must be, like, a tower
in the vicinity or something.
You guys wanna
take a picture together?
Have fun.
What's up with that?
I don't know. I'll take a
picture with you. -Okay.
Gosh, we look so good together.
It's, like, ridiculous.
Yeah.
Where's the bridge?
Ain't one.
So, how do we get across?
Seriously?
Brett, this is the backwater.
Do the words "gator bait"
mean anything to you?
Contrary to popular belief,
gators don't like to attack
anything they can't swallow.
And who told you that, little bitty
baby gator or big, fat papa gator?
You know, Brett,
she does have a point.
Taylor doesn't attack anything
she can't swallow either.
I mean, that's never stopped
you before, has it, Tay?
A lesbian comic,
what a novelty.
My god! My dad's watch!
My god! He must have
crossed the river right here.
That's why it was
hanging right there.
No, I'm sorry, Justin.
I cannot cross this water.
That's fine, babe.
That's cool.
You can stay here
and wait if you like.
You, look away.
Ew! something just touched me!
Something...
It's got me!
-Just hold on.
-It's got me! Justin, pull!
Justin, what is it?
What was that?
It was a branch, Tay.
Your panties got caught
on a big, fat branch.
A branch?
Okay, well...
Well, I haven't had
my panties pulled on that hard
since the back of Tommy Swanson's
pickup truck on prom night.
They feel dry enough.
Get dressed everyone.
Daylight's a-burning.
Is it weird that
there's stairs here?
Maybe somebody owns
a summer house or something.
Okay, summer house or not,
I do not wanna be stuck here
in the dark, okay?
How much farther
do we have to go?
Let's go another half mile.
That's where his GPS was.
Yeah.
At this point, it might be good
to start calling out his name.
See if he can hear us.
Keith.
His name is Keith.
Keith!
-Keith!
-Dad!
Keith!
-Keith!
Maddy's daddy!
-Genius!
-We must have taken a wrong turn.
-No.
No way.
According to the map,
the tracking signal was some
200 yards north of here...
which is right through there.
How would he have
gotten in there?
Maybe he knows people
who lived here
and stopped in for brunch.
Looks like some sort of
government-regulated facility.
Why would my dad be
in a government facility?
Maybe he's assisting special ops
for some sort of Mother
Nature-inspired biological warfare.
Hey, special ops over there,
why don't you cut
the conspiracy theory?
You're freaking out
bottle blond over here.
So what do you wanna do then?
I wanna find a gate and see
if anyone will let us in.
Guys, it's gonna be too dark to
walk back if we don't go now.
We can take this road so we don't
have to go through the woods.
Yeah, in the dark?
We have flashlights.
Hey, someone's standing
guard over there.
Excuse me.
Hello there.
Man. We're not terrorists.
We're just college kids.
This is private property.
Move along.
But wait. My dad...
We think my dad is
already on your property.
Come again?
My dad, he's somewhere in there.
We keep a guard posted here
around the clock.
I can assure you your father is not...
on these grounds.
But, sir, we tracked him here.
Are you guys on drugs?
Are you tripping on shrooms?
No. No, sir. We're sober.
But we're just looking
for our friend's father.
He was carrying a GPS tracking
device in his camping gear,
and that device is
somewhere in there,
and we think
her father might be, too.
Please, can we just come in
and look for him?
We're not gonna steal anything.
You can watch us.
Okay, you kids hang right there.
Sullivan.
Yes?
This is gate.
I know.
I've got a couple of kids here,
and one says her dad
is on the estate grounds. Over.
All right.
Maybe we should let them in,
and we can get this settled.
10-4. Would you like me
to escort them?
They're on foot. Over.
No, that won't be necessary. Just
have them come down the main road.
Have them wait for me at the
aviary fence. Thank you.
Guys, I really don't like this.
Doesn't anyone find it odd
that they're allowing us to just
waltz across their property
without an attendant?
It's obvious
some rich guy owns the place.
Probably has security cameras
in half these trees, too.
Yeah, not to mention the electrical
fence surrounding the entire property,
ensuring we couldn't escape even
if we did try and steal something.
Yeah, see,
that's what concerns me.
Rich people like
to keep their stuff safe.
Yeah, but what kind
of normal rich person
lives this far
out in the backwoods?
Finally, Tri Delt has
a valid point.
Thank you.
What do you think is in there?
Maybe horses.
What kind of horse needs
a fence that high?
Could have some exotic game.
Maybe ostriches
or water buffalo.
Guys, according to this, that GPS
device is right through there.
Can't we just go back
to Maddy's cabin,
and shower the filth
of this forest off of us,
and then come back
tomorrow maybe
when a third party knows
where to find us?
Taylor, we can't just bail
on Maddy's dad right now,
not when we've come
all this way already.
Justin,
do I have "suicide"
written in pink lip gloss
across my forehead?
No, I don't think so.
I'm not going any farther.
I'm sorry.
Taylor, this is exactly what I was
talking to you about last week.
Sometimes, you are
the most selfish...
Justin, wait.
I think Taylor is right.
I think we should go
and come back tomorrow.
You guys have done enough
for me already,
and it's getting late.
It's gonna be dark soon.
-What...
-Taylor! Taylor!
Taylor, wake up! Taylor!
Taylor, wake up.
Run! Run!
Paige!
Nice! Nice!
What happened?
We found another one
at the cabin,
out cold on the ground,
big knot on his forehead.
All right, so what do you think?
Do you think
he's with the other kids?
Well, when we saw him
at the gas station earlier,
we didn't think he was.
All right, good. Good.
So, what about the car?
We just took care of it.
All right, so we'll take care
of the vehicles later.
We'll put the...
We'll put the kids in the barn.
And that new kid, I want
you to give him a sedative
before you put him
with the other kids.
All right. I'm gonna need
a sleeper though. I'm out.
I'm loaded, buddy.
Don't let him get away! Come on!
No worries. I got this.
Woo wee!
I could get used to this!
Hey, don't be
such a Neanderthal, Dale.
We're not murderers!
We're doing this
because we have no choice.
Paige.
Wake up.
-Dude...
-Paige.
I got hit in the head
with a baseball bat.
Try knock-down
tranquilizer dart.
What the...
We were attacked.
And what is he doing here?
Dude, I think
I have a conclusion.
It's "contusion," half-baked.
I don't get it.
Why would the guys let us go?
Yeah, and where the hell are we?
Out by the river.
I can hear it down there.
Who were those guys?
Wait. What guys
are we talking about?
You didn't see them 'cause
you were first knocked down,
but there were two big guys coming
down the drive with dart guns.
How did you get here?
I was on my bike.
They kidnapped me when I stopped
on the side of the road.
Right. And why were you stopped
on the side of the road?
Take a piss.
You're an idiot.
Guys, stop.
We're in this together.
Well, do you remember
them saying anything,
or do you know where we are?
Maddy! Hey, Maddy!
Guys...
I think these are
my father's footprints.
I thought you said your dad was on the
other side of that big cage that we saw.
Yeah.
And my guess is we are too.
Wait.
Cage? What the hell cage
are you talking about?
I don't know. It was some sort
of electrical, fenced-in pen.
It was eight feet tall.
Well, what the hell
is in the pen?
What was that?
Some sort of bird.
It sounded more like a banshee.
Guys, come check this out.
So, maybe this is
an ostrich farm.
No. I ain't never seen
no ostrich with feet that big.
Maddy, where are you going?
I'm going to find my father.
In the same direction
as those big bird tracks?
Nope, I don't think so.
You can do whatever you want,
but I'm going to find my dad.
Maddy, come on.
Don't be crazy.
We are in here deep.
We need to get out of here now,
call the cops, and send someone
back after your dad, okay?
Maddy... that is the best way
to help your dad.
Fine.
Which way should we go?
I think the south fence line should
be somewhere right through there.
Everybody.
Do not make a move.
Do not take a step.
Do not make a noise.
Dude, we're sitting ducks
in this clearing, man.
Yeah, but if we can see them
coming from all four sides,
they can't spring
a surprise attack.
I'm getting
the hell out of here!
Where are you going?
-Maddy, what are you doing?
-We might need this.
What the hell is that thing?
Everybody back up very slowly.
Paige!
Everybody run!
-Over here!
-Come and get us! Hey!
-Here! Here!
-Maddy, look out! Come on!
-Hey! Over here!
-Come and get us, ugly!
Pull your legs up.
My god.
Maddy, are you okay?
Let me see the leg.
Let me see your leg.
It looks...
No. No, not so bad. Not so bad.
We do need
some disinfectant right away.
-Can you check your dad's bag?
-Yeah.
And we gotta
stop the bleeding too.
So now what are we gonna do?
Guys, any ideas?
Just hold on.
What's going on over there?
That thing plucked her leg.
Yeah, and I'm gonna pluck her
in the head.
Taylor, try your phone again.
Your dad's Swiss Army Knife.
I gave this to him...
last Christmas.
It was right
after my mom passed away.
She was always
against those things.
Too bad she didn't have one the
night she drowned in that car.
She might have been able
to cut herself from that belt.
Hey. Hey.
Hey, Maddy.
Be with me right now, okay?
Okay.
Can she walk?
Yeah, we think she can walk.
I'm not walking anywhere.
That thing is still out there,
and for all we know, there could
be 20 more of them running around.
And what the hell are they?
They're definitely
not ostriches.
And aren't
all the dodos extinct?
They're not dodos.
Well, then what the hell
are they?
I think they're
called terror birds.
Terror birds? That's light.
Try "scare the crap out of me, send
my ass into a pecan tree" bird.
I'm serious. I think they're
called terror birds or Titanis.
My dad knows everything about every
kind of animal that ever existed.
Growing up,
it's all he ever talked about.
Those birds should
be extinct, though.
Clearly, they're not.
Maybe they're genetic clones
like in that movie.
Who cares? They're real,
and they wanna eat us like some
salty, sweaty student skewers.
Now, how are we gonna
get out of here?
If we found a tree
that was tall enough,
I think we could get over that
electrical fence, easy-breezy.
Yeah, but how are
we gonna get there?
We're gonna need some bait.
Wait. What do you mean "bait"?
You don't really think
those guys that put us here
are gonna let us hang out
in these trees all day, do you?
We have Maddy's dad's water and
enough pecans to eat for days.
So let's see
who caves in first.
Kids are in the trees.
Birds are on the ground.
Kind of funny?
Yeah, that's really funny.
You wanna know
what's really funny?
You're the one that's gotta
get them out of the trees.
How are we supposed to do that?
Well, I don't know.
Why don't you just hit them
with a dart maybe?
I don't care what you gotta do.
Shoot them.
They're teasing my birds.
Go. Do it.
You want us... to go out
there in the aviary?
Do what you did before,
bring your tranqs.
Go on. Do it. Go!
Looks like
both the birds are back.
I think that's
the one that had Paige.
Yep, that's the one.
Hey, you!
You are one ugly creature!
You hear me? Yeah!
U-G-L-Y!
You ain't got no alibi!
You ugly! Yeah, yeah, you ugly!
Maybe you shouldn't
antagonize it like that, Taylor.
I'm sorry, Mr. Birdy Bird.
Did I insult your feelings?
Taylor.
My god.
Friends helping friends.
Ain't that cute?
All right, get down here,
all of you.
Justin, what are we going to do?
They have guns.
What else are we gonna do?
Hurry it up!
Let's go.
Come on!
Toss that pack
over here, sweetie.
What do you want from us?
Well, we were trying to make
you the birds' breakfast,
but clearly,
you're a bit more resourceful.
Well, most of you, anyway.
Clever little Polly's crackers,
ain't they?
A lot more clever than their
father was. That's for sure.
Just let us go, okay,
and we won't say
anything to anybody.
We'll just say that we got attacked
by some massive mountain lion.
You thought this speech out,
haven't you, hot stuff?
I bet you're
at the top of your class.
Or, you know... at least
working your way to the top.
Screw you,
you backwater bacteria.
Now, we're gonna give you
to the count of three
to head that way
back into the forest
before we start putting
bullets in your head.
How does that sound?
One...
Two...
No, no!
Everything! I gotta do
everything myself!
Are you in? Let's go.
I think the kids escaped.
Think so?
Well, so did my birds,
because you let those kids
get ahold of your keys.
Yeah, but who's gonna get
the birds back in the sanctuary?
After they're done feeding,
you're gonna load up on darts
and pray you don't miss.
Russ! Russ was dead.
Yes, I know.
Those damned birds
tore him apart.
Yes, I know. I saw the whole
show on the monitor, all right?
Now, what we're gonna do is I'm going
back to the laboratory where it's safe.
You're gonna stay here.
Keep an eye on that driveway.
Make sure the birds don't get
past the house. Understood?
Yeah, but I don't think...
Or you could go out and help
my babies finish their job.
-I'll be right here if you need anything.
-That's good.
How are we gonna get
through that gate?
We got his keys.
Well, I guess
it's our lucky day.
Guys, they're coming back.
Justin, you're never
gonna make it! Come on!
It stalled!
Maybe those keys work
on that barn over there.
Let's go.
Hell!
Base to Bio. Base to Bio.
You look good.
You look good there.
Base to Bio. Base to Bio.
Son of a...
Justin.
Justin, hurry.
I'm trying.
There's a lot of keys,
and there isn't one labeled
for the barn like the gate.
My god! They're coming!
Dude, you gotta
get that key right now.
Justin!
That's my swinging arm, baby.
That ugly beak of yours
is about to hit me a grand slam.
My god! Justin!
Boy, you kids,
you sure put a damper in
my afternoon, haven't you?
Six months, this ranch
has been a safe haven,
a place of peace
for my baby birds.
A safe haven?
You killed my father.
No, dear.
No, your father got himself
into this mess
when he trespassed
on my property
when natural selection
chose him as food.
No, I'm no murderer, dear.
You tried feeding us
to your giant parakeets.
Pretty sure some states
consider that murder.
I can't let anything interfere
with my operation,
at least not until
the little ones are hatched.
Are you kidding?
You really want
these things to reproduce?
You bet I do!
They're the last two
of their kind.
I'm just trying to help them
survive, save a species.
By sacrificing your own kind
to feed them? That's balanced!
You kids are the only ones
who cost innocent lives today.
Now I gotta spend the rest of the
afternoon trying to find new wranglers.
And you know how hard it is
to find new wranglers?
I mean, wranglers you can trust.
Look at me. Of course I do.
Okay, Blondie,
let me ask you this.
You know what it costs
to keep somebody's mouth shut?
Probably not any more than it costs
for your Italian import shoes.
Welcome to the food chain,
you bastard!
Get away!
No, no, no! No!
If there's one thing I know to do,
it's divert a guy's attention.
We need to make a move for it
now while they're still eating.
Where to?
What about in there?
Maybe there's a phone.
You don't know that.
But there will be one
at the house.
It's too far. You'll never be
able to outrun those birds.
Watch me.
I did track in high school.
Taylor!
Let me look at it.
I think we should find
a way out of here.
We're not going anywhere
until I look at your leg.
Besides, I don't think that thing
can get through that door.
I think you got
a lot of dirt in it.
I'm gonna have
to wrap it better.
Well, it looks like
we're in the right place.
What do you think
this place is anyway?
I don't know.
It looks like...
Like a hatchery or something.
So either they hatched them
in here or...
they were hoping
two of them would lay eggs.
Can I borrow your knife?
My god.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No, I should be sorry.
For Brett, and for getting all of you
into this mess in the first place.
-I am so sorry.
-No, no.
Maddy, it's not your fault.
Besides, I'm not the only one who
lost someone I cared about today.
We're gonna make it
through this, okay?
I hope Taylor is okay.
Me too.
But I gotta admit...
I'm thankful that the person
I care about the most...
is still right here
in front of me.
You do know I only dated her
to get my mind off you, right?
I never really had with her
what I have with you.
Justin, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I pushed you away.
But it's only because I felt the same
way about you, and I just didn't know...
Maddy, Maddy, I get it. I know
all your defense mechanisms.
And I now that it was hard for
you to get close to people
after your mom died.
But I let you push me away too,
and I never should have.
But that doesn't matter
anymore, right?
Because it's never
gonna happen again.
Yeah.
Thank god for that knife?
Looks like somebody has been looking
out for us today from afar.
Hey.
Hey. It's okay.
Do you think
that door is gonna hold?
I sure as hell hope so.
You've got to be kidding me!
That's weird.
Hello?
All right, all right.
Keep it down in there.
What the hell?
What's wrong with you mutts?
Hey.
Hey, so...
it looks like Sullivan
found the two birds
in these neighboring islands
in the Caribbean.
He was funding a dig in Trinidad
for some rumored buried treasure
all his yuppie friends in Barbados
caught legend of from locals.
What a better way to waste money than
to spend it all searching for more?
But what does the treasure
have to do with the birds?
Well, they didn't find
anything in Trinidad,
so they expanded the dig
to nearby islands, only...
the natives refused to take
them to two of the islands,
claiming they were home
to death birds.
Needless to say, Sullivan was
thrilled by the prospect.
I didn't think that there were
any uncharted islands left.
Well, these are charted,
Navassa and Caparo.
So, why didn't anybody know
that the birds were there?
Well, it seems like
they were pretty small islands.
Totally uninhabited too.
Only the natives did know.
They even claimed their ancestors
hunted down what was left of them.
But since no one of any
prominence had ever seen them,
everyone else just chalked
it up to local myth.
So if the birds were staying so
concealed, how did he find them?
Bait.
He put goats
all over the island,
monitored them for weeks to see
where they would disappear.
Clever bastard.
So Sullivan found
his buried treasure after all.
Only two in the world left
of its kind.
Just like he said.
Too bad we're gonna kill them.
Miss Biology!
You do realize
that we'd be responsible
for the extinction
of an entire species?
Sure do.
Good. Glad we're
on the same page.
My god! Crap!
Hey, don't move!
Where's Harvey?
He's in there.
We might be stuck.
There is no way that bird is
leaving if we're up here.
Well, his ranch house
is just up there.
All right, I mean,
if we find weapons in there,
we can maybe get
past that guard.
But what are we gonna do
about that?
I have an idea.
Hey, you big chicken,
come and get me!
See how excited it gets
when I scream?
Yeah, I don't like it.
So I record myself
screaming into my phone,
I press repeat, and I throw
it as far as I can that way.
You really think
that's gonna work?
It's worth a shot.
All right, but we're gonna
have to be quick.
If that bird goes
after the phone...
I mean, those things are clocking
in at well over 20 miles an hour.
Let's just hope my arm gives us
a good enough head-start.
All right.
Ready?
Hey, you big chicken,
come and get me!
I don't hear anything.
It's so far away
you can't hear it.
It worked.
Let's go.
Hey, you big chicken,
come and get me!
Come on! Move!
I can't. No keys!
My god!
You've got to be kidding me.
I don't see it. It must still be out...
in the field.
Okay, any sign of that thing
taking a step towards us,
and I'm back in the van, okay?
Okay.
Anything?
No. Let me try the other one.
-Still over there?
-Yeah.
Wait.
What do you mean "wait"?
Justin...
I think you should get
back into the van.
Right now.
Go! Go!
How are we gonna
open that thing?
-We're not.
-What?
We're gonna smash
right through it.
Are you crazy?
This isn't the movies! That could
be reinforced steel or something.
Justin, don't do it!
Damn it!
Look in the back.
Maybe they have another gun.
I don't see one.
There's dynamite.
Bring that over here.
Hey, you prehistoric, overblown
turkey, come and get me!
Okay, do it.
Here it comes!
Go! Go!
Roasted bird?
How much you wanna bet
it tastes just like chicken?