♪ A dream is a wish
♪ Your heart makes
♪ When you're fast asleep
♪ In dreams
You will lose your heartaches
♪ Whatever you wish for
You keep...
♪ Have faith in your dreams
And someday...
♪ Your rainbow will come
Smiling through...
♪ No matter how your heart
Is grieving...
♪ If you keep on believing...
♪ The dream that you wish
Will come... ♪
Pluto!
Now, to finish off
the perfect dream.
I'm coming,
my dream Min-nie-ee-ee!
Hey!
Keep it down up there!
Hey, Mick. It's Goofy.
I can't sleep tonight
and thought
you'd like to know.
You know, I think
it all started
when I was a kid.
My dad used to say
it was time for bed,
but I'd just lay there
and close my eyes.
Probably 'cause
I just want to dream!
Yes!
Yoo-hoo!
I'm coming, dream Minnie!
♪ The dream that you... ♪
Oh, I can't sing
with all this noise.
♪ A dream is a wish
Your heart makes
♪ When you're fast asleep...
♪ Your rainbow will come
Smiling through...
♪ No matter how your heart
Is grieving...
♪ If you keep on believing...
♪ The dream that you wish
Will come true ♪