No, come on now. Let's go. You promised.
- I'll make you like nature.
- It does not like me.
- The air is never so fresh in New York.
- Sure, if you say so, then.
Do you want to go back?
To the house, not to the town.
Does he think...
Va?
Tom! Empty!
Tom!
He does not breathe.
I'm calling for someone.
Stay here, I'll fix it.
Breathing.
- I think it needs sewing.
- It does not have to be sewn. Just put on...
- Do they even learn psychologists like that?
- You do not know what they are learning psychologists.
Turn it on.
Aj! I'm just kidding, it did not hurt.
Is it good?
Yes. I just...
- I'm thinking of that guy.
- I know it was close to the eye.
- You risked the life of a stranger.
- I had no choice.
You... If I had not been
such a fantastic swimmer-
- I would not have jumped in,
but now I'm and I managed.
Thank you.
What you did was very brave.
I was scared only.
I know.
- I take it to the dry cleaner.
- It is his. The healthcare providers were wrong.
I was going to stop at...
You, it's no danger. No problem.
Hi, Mary.
We almost wrote Dr. Thomas Seymour
before I saw it. Ian Wilkinson.
- Have you received any values?
- He had Temazepam in the blood. Ten pieces.
Hello. I thought you wanted this one.
It was me who pulled you out of the water.
My wife was right upset.
Doctor Seymour?
It's me.
- Danny? Danny Miller?
- Yes.
Sorry, I did not know you were out.
They kept quiet about it.
And Ian?
Ian was the director's first name,
Wilkinson was the pastor's last name.
- Now I am.
- Was it ten, twelve years ago?
- It feels twice as long.
- Obvious.
- Sorry, this is...
- Crazy, right?
It makes one think.
The pastor had said that the randomness is
the crack in the human where God comes in.
Yes, he would have done that.
You, I have to work.
Under circumstances
you look good.
Yes, according to the circumstances.
Take care of you.
My mom is a subba.
She does not believe he raped me.
She said I found it. She can pull
to hell. Does he get conditional two years?
She blames me and killed my dog.
She killed my damn dog.
Therefore I cut the subban. Little justice.
It's enough, Miss Demers.
- Can the lawyer and psychologist arrive?
Doctor Seymour.
Well, what do you say?
I'm so tired of this case.
"My dog, my dog, my dog."
- Do you think the mom's guy raped her?
- He broke his conditional judgment.
- Young people have reason to kill anyone.
- Not in that area. I invite you.
- Ian Wilkinson.
- Is he one of yours?
Yes, and you did a good deed.
- Did you mean to tell me?
- You know that I could not.
Does the police know that he is?
He was depressed and took a swim.
- A swim? Angie, Danny is...
- His name is Ian Wilkinson now, okay?
- When did we start with it?
- We do it occasionally.
He was an exceptional, but bad young man.
Smart. He has a chance if we keep
the police and the press outside.
- He thinks you can help him.
- It's not possible.
You should not tell anyone about this,
not even your wife.
Drunk, Tom. You have earned it.
The water was deep.
I have to go back to the right
and make it look like I'm working.
Think about the matter.
- When are you back on Thursday?
- No, I'm temporary for Bob this weekend.
You work fewer hours so we
need the money. You should come down.
Now this weekend? Is it
premiere or something?
I will finish the chapter on child abuse
and have not listened to the tape yet.
- No, it's just a good time.
- I get it.
I hate to discuss it like this,
with calendars and thermometers.
No, I want to. I do.
Whatever is required and how many times
is required, I'm the right one.
I'm trying to get ready
the next few days and come down, okay?
I'm driving you there.
We stay at a guesthouse and get started.
Stop. It's fine. Finish what you
must finish and try to get down.
You are beautiful, do you know that?
It's too simple to assume that Nicole lacks conscience.
Many children with problems...
Then the question becomes how to determine
the difference between access...
Danny, what are you doing here?
Hello. I was nearby and you forgot your
letter at the hospital the other day.
Your address was on it.
Did not you hear the doorbell?
- It looked important, as a bill.
- Thanks.
- You look better. How are you?
- When I came out, I slept like a death.
Okay. Thank you for this,
now I have to work on.
What?
You are the only one I can talk to
about what happened.
Can I come in?
Certainly. Obvious. Take a seat.
Danny, I can give you the name of someone
else who can help. What are you doing?
Please do not smoke here.
Anyone else, then?
I'm the knife that has been thrown into the ocean.
It's Sigmund Freud, the doctor.
I know, but you do not end up in that
category. Please wipe the cigarette.
- I want you to know... Can we...
- No. I'm not your therapist.
Forgive. Oh my God.
They sentenced me to a crime
I had not committed and you...
You judged me more or less.
Can you help me get on my feet?
I gave them my opinion, that is all.
You know I'm innocent.
Do you have to know?
No, I do not know and I want
that you leave my home now. Understood?
Now.
What the hell?
- Hi, Louis.
- I got you there.
Seriously? Good work.
See you, Louis.
- Hi, mom!
- Here I am.
Did Louis try to talk to you?
He comes in when he breaks and talks
about the past, it's so depressing.
- Soon I will hire a Mexican or something.
- Mom...
- Where is my daughter in law?
- In New York.
- Previously the men went on business trips.
- Do not start now again.
Even though the women did the whole job.
Wait a minute,
what have you done with your wrist?
I slipped and hit me. I can not
stay for dinner, should I fix something?
For God's sake, I can handle myself.
But thank you for shopping for me.
- I love you.
- Okay, kid. Bye.
My advice is to think less and fuck more.
Look at me, I have four children.
- I did not think of them.
- And three wives.
You look more distracted
and bleak than usual.
Do you remember Danny Miller? I ran on
him. He's out, under a different name.
He is not your patient?
Write about him instead, then.
You can sell that easily.
Nothing is more nasty than the truth?
It was a joke, for God's sake.
Do not talk to him at all.
- It's the past, leave it there.
- He said that my testimony judged him.
It's good to take a little?
He was no angel right away.
But it bother me.
He was my last case on that page.
I think of him. Maybe it went too fast.
Maybe we were too tough for him.
He acknowledged that he was there, put the
pillow over her face and took on her.
He did not have her skin under the nails.
There was no decisive evidence.
- His fingerprints were in the entire room.
- Take it easy now, hardding.
If we continue, I have to pay.
- And the chicken?
- I do not want to hear about the chicken.
The fact is that you did the right thing.
You did.
There are always questions.
I have one for you. Do you really think
he "ran on" you or did he find you?
- He said it was a coincidence.
- As if there is any chance.
- Say if you need a firearm.
- What's wrong with you?
Thank goodness, there are still
journalists who look like that.
- Sweetheart, are you?
- It's Angela.
- Enter? What?
- Ian.
Ian Wilkinson appeared at Morgan
Hamilton Prison and wanted to be locked.
He tried to hand in a guard.
They want to take him in.
Maybe they should?
They will take him unless his
supervisor or therapist fetches him.
- Okay, but I'm not his therapist.
- He told them.
I can not take it here.
Please help me with this.
- So... You have to joke.
- You are involved, no matter what you want.
I have to put on.
Hell.
Drive into the roadside, I have to pee.
Yes, okay.
- Sorry, was it okay?
- Yes, it did.
Do you know what? Give me a blow.
- I thought you might have been stuck.
- Yes maybe.
Remember your last therapy call?
That before trial?
I had your arms around your waist
and you looked at me.
You looked at me and went your way. I
neither heard of you or saw you again.
I was eleven years old, Tom.
Okay, but now you're out. You are here.
Do me a favor and open the window.
And no smoking in my office, okay?
Ever.
I started burning fingertips
in prison.
I do not know why I do.
It's clean in here, very stylish.
Like a hotel
Safe and nice.
No distractions.
Why did you try to get
back to prison again?
Yes, and I jumped in the river
to cool me down.
- Still taking Temazepam?
- Yes, 20 milligrams.
- Where do you live? Do you have any work?
- At the port.
- Is there anyone at home? Your mom?
- She's dead.
- I'm sorry.
- I had to visit her with handcuffs on.
The handcuffs killed my mother - and my dad
was not even there when she died.
He lives in Norwich and
has a narcissistic coma he calls a bar.
He visited Windsor and pretended
that I was in some nice internat.
But when they take one to prison...
When you reach 18
you know that life is over.
I did not know you ended up in prison.
- Do not lie, Doctor Seymour.
- I do not lie. It's not a dash.
Being sorry does not give me life back.
I did not do it!
- I did not, you know!
- The technical evidence was convincing.
Time is out.
ACHIEVEMENT
Kat Kennedy is with Lauren Seymour.
Do you know, you'll have your eyes open
while we do it.
- God, sorry. I...
- The book is work. This is going to be fun.
I know you're right.
- You should have come down.
- I know it was time to try.
No, no. Because it was fun.
It's fun in New York.
It is cloudy in New London.
Stop for a while. Wait.
I may be a little jealous
when I see you with all the young artists.
A jealous Thomas Seymour?
I like that.
Oh!
- Is everything okay?
- The thoughts are clear. Fall asleep, you.
- Sweetheart, do you move out a blackboard at a time?
- She has an exhibition.
We ran to each other on Pete's at the river.
It's Ian, do you remember him?
Yes, of course.
How are you, Ian?
He is going to apply for some schools.
I said we can call around a bit.
Sure, that sounds good. What is the
exhibition you are talking about?
Bob had set,
so I exhibited something.
- Sure, is it fun?
- It is an exhibition for the faculty.
That sounds great,
I'll definitely be there.
- Ian is working night shift, I drive him home.
- No, I'm pushing him.
- Are not you going to court today?
- Yes, but I let him down the road.
- I have to go back to town, quite crazy.
- Yes it is.
I'd rather drink a real mold.
There I work and there I drink.
- No kids, so?
- No.
Sometimes I wonder why my parents
got me. What were they looking for?
So your daddy does not
want to meet you at all?
Dad wants to delete me.
He never really wanted to meet me.
He made the garage to a workshop
and locked the door.
He sat most in there
and talked about Falluja.
About when he shot a hole in a boy's chest-
- and he slid down the wall
like a red spottloska.
Dad loved to chase. I hated it.
Once, I was maybe six years old-
- He drove in to the roadside, picked up a
gun and shot six deer in seconds.
As if we were in jail.
I stood right next to him.
They are so beautiful at close range.
He forced me to push one in his head,
so it ended up getting up.
Maybe because of the adrenaline,
but I could not stop crying.
The blood splashed in my face.
Dad saw it and got pissed off.
Continue forward, only.
I have read that we only use ten percent of the brain.
Have you thought about it?
Yes, actually.
It's like buying a big suit.
Like it's going to be a beautiful day.
- What do you think the other 90 percent are?
- I do not know.
I think it's animal.
Without the tiny portion
we are animals all.
Like when we sleep or when I was
in the river. No thoughts, just animalism.
- Did you revive me with CPR?
- Yes.
Was not your wife?
- Why do you ask?
- I am just curious.
Your wife is a friendly lady.
She's nice, you've been lucky.
She is handsome. Sorry.
I live in that damn rucklet.
Hi, handsome. Put down the boxes,
and I'll pick them up for you.
You are a prince, Ian.
Stop coming home to me, understood?
I want to help you,
but you do not stop, it's over.
- You're bad, Doctor Seymour.
- Is that understood?
Oh. Thank you, raring.
You have violated your conditional release.
You have the right to a lawyer.
If you can not afford a lawyer, will be
entitled to appoint a public defender.
- He tried to rape his niece.
- You were right about him.
- Do Nicky know about it?
- Probably. Lucky that she was in prison.
I say that too often now.
And Ian? Have you talked to him?
- You asked me to pick him up, remember?
- Yes. And thanks.
But since then?
- What is it?
- Has he said anything about me?
Because we have talked every night.
Deep conversation.
Recently he has been short.
Almost remote.
- I might have upset him.
- Angela, you are his supervisor.
- How did he get out?
- Windsor's rector was fighting for him.
She called out some services. Me too.
- So he has not mentioned me?
- Angela, look at me. What's going on?
- What?
- He's a job, a case.
I'm worried. He is a good guy.
- How can you be so sure?
- Tom, how many such cases do we see by day?
This kid is special.
- He may have a chance. Am I wrong?
- I do not know. I do not know where I think.
Young man from Connecticut
charged with murder of older woman.
He forced me to hold a hen.
When he came back, then.
He was different. Nasty.
He tied my hands to it.
- And hit the head of it.
I held it while it shook.
Then blew it.
And you understood that it was wrong?
You are safe here, Danny.
You understand that?
- Mrs. Green?
- Yes. Get up, Doctor Seymour.
- You are more stylish than the picture on your book.
- No thanks.
- Thank you for receiving with short notice.
- I do not know what I can tell.
- Do you treat Danny?
- Yes. Yes I do.
- So you taught him here at Windsor?
- He was one of my smartest students.
Nothing is like killing a brain that
extinguishes everything and asks for more.
- How old was he then?
- Thirteen and fourteen.
Was there anything more
with him at the time?
- What did you notice?
He made people think they helped him
until they tore themselves out.
Or worse yet.
Three in the staff, to be exact.
My husband is still feeling guilty.
- For what he did with the child.
- Yes, that's terrible.
- I know it's hard to talk about.
- I blame Mr McDonald.
I still want to forgive Danny.
The other boy was such a boy
who always posed problems.
But Danny...
He knives the boy. He walked
across the room and knivled him.
Thank God, the child survived.
My husband got crushed.
But I blame Angus, you understand.
- Because he made it happen?
- Ville. He wanted it to happen.
Angus McDonald came here as a teacher.
But he forced Danny
to write awful things about what happened.
Angus became too engaged.
- Continue.
- I've probably said enough.
This is Tom's mobile answer.
Enter a message and I will call.
Tom, I'm angry with you but I do not want to.
You should be here.
I should not leave this message,
but it goes well. Really good.
He from "The Times" is here.
She's a liar.
Why do not you believe me?
- She said you're kidding a guy.
- You do not know what I had to do there.
What they called me. What they did to me.
- And Angus?
- He is a pig, a stalker and a gay.
- Fan. You hate me. Why?
- I do not. Stop.
- I want to know what happened to Windsor.
- You still believe I killed her.
I did not. It was not me.
Someone else did, I do not know who.
I have to go to work!
I thought you would help me.
Can you calm down? Calm down.
Danny, calm down.
Danny, Danny, Danny.
They belonged to me, I do not know who
they belong to anymore. Damn table!
Can you tell me what happened to Windsor?
Why? So you can pretend to bother you?
Please wait a little. Danny!
Fan too.
Angie.
- Wait. I want to invite a glass.
- Tom...
- Come on. Sit down. Have a glass with me.
- A glass.
Well, have you heard of our guy?
He's home with me. On the sofa.
I do not know what you've said,
but he's trying to get on his feet.
Digging in the past
does not help him. Not in that way.
Going over there again, Tommy?
Come on.
- Leave your hesitation about the decision there.
- Angie, it's not about it.
What did he say to you?
Angela, what did he say?
If you do not help, you will be hurt.
Thanks for the liquor.
Do not say it. Do not say that word. "Job".
- I know, but I...
- What did I just say? Thanks, I'll take it.
- Why all the new bags?
- Did you listen to my message?
Whole message?
- Colin Waters. Colin Waters Gallery.
- I know. Colin Waters. Great fun.
- Do you know who Colin Waters is?
- Are you serious? Of course I know that.
He does not exist, a bunch of guys calls it.
They have a gallery in Bushwick.
They want to give me an exhibition and they
have a studio on top where I can work.
In Brooklyn?
Do you know how difficult
it is to get your own show?
No, I did not know. What good
news, honey. Congratulations. Really.
Herregud. They came before me.
I have to bring work
and other things down there.
You should have listened to the message.
Hello. This is Tom. My husband Tom.
Wait, how is the situation?
- The armchair?
- I must have somewhere to sit?
There is a one with kitchenette right now.
It is completely empty.
It feels like you move out.
Only if you do not follow me.
Tom. Town. A room.
A little like when we first met and did
not leave your apartment in a month.
The show is only in June, it's over
a month. Why are you shaking your head?
Shaking my head?
This book starts to affect you,
all stories about children.
You are right.
It's an incredible opportunity for you.
I'm so tired.
Close me, you're nice.
I want to bakery and buy those
muffins we love, to those in the gallery.
- Who was it?
- Ian. Crazy, huh?
- What did he want?
- I became too distracted by his charm.
- What fan should that mean?
- What's with you?
What's up with you? Can not you
spend time with peers sometimes?
Go to hell. For real.
Ladies and gentlemen,
train 179 at 20:17...
Wait, Lauren. Forgive me.
I have a lot of thoughts right now
and I think the book affects me.
To write about the kids all day long
on me. It feels like I'm losing...
Tom. It's time.
- For what?
- Everything. Good things. Everything we have talked about.
Tom?
- Tom?
- Yes I know. I know you're right.
See you in a couple of days.
She's okay, even though she's an artist.
You should go and spend more time with her.
- It's complicated, mom.
- Religion and politics are complicated.
- And daddy?
- Complicated. But not me, I was simple.
Do you see who's working out there?
You remember Neil?
There are little Neil Bridges.
You boys used to torture the stacker.
- What does he do here?
- He needed a job.
- That was the smallest I could do.
- I still hear his crying and screaming.
I do not know who jumped in
after him. It was not me or you.
It was my dad who jumped in.
- Do you think of what had happened...
- No, not directly.
- What do you have for tea?
- Black, Green, Chai, Mint, Earl Gray.
But nothing with caffeine, huh? Hi.
- Ian, hello.
- What are you doing in town?
- Some herbal tea will be good.
- I invite you.
- What are you doing in town?
- I have been on admission interview.
- Well, how fun.
- Yes.
- Thanks.
- What a coincidence. What clumsy.
Yes, exactly. I want people to see my works,
otherwise I would not have done them.
I had forgotten how loud it was here.
You have an eyelash loose.
Good. Do I have to blow it? Thanks.
I loved Enkaustik,
I want to re-introduce it.
You put bivax and resin on the cloth,
it gives depth. You can melt it.
- I have to say a thing.
- Yes?
It does not matter.
What? You should not do that.
You are an incredible
source of inspiration.
You make me feel that
everything is possible.
I pay.
Doctor Seymour has a great trip.
Yes.
- A hard night?
- I met old friends.
- And Lauren?
- She's in New York. What did you want?
Ian's father knows he's out. He called
prison and asked about his son.
Has he called you?
I'm afraid he will try to find Ian.
- Did not he stay with you?
- He moved home again, but is not there.
He is not at work. He missed our meeting
today, it has never happened before.
- Who is Angus McDonald?
- Has he talked about it?
For fan, Tom. Knife cuts happen even
in youth prisons. Do not blow it up.
- He has not applied for Angus?
- I do not know where he is.
I'm watching Angus.
He is at school. Which type.
The students come and go. He is always two
glasses away from his perverted thoughts.
- Angela, your involvement in the case...
- Do not Analyze Me.
- Think about your own involvement.
- He's probably not the one you want.
Who is it?
Think about who you want him to be.
- I do not want him to be anybody.
- Do me a favor. If he belongs...
Keep him. Hold him up.
Do nothing until I get there.
- Hi. Doctor Seymour?
- Yes.
Professor McDonald is in there.
First visit?
I have been to school a couple of times.
- Jeremy?
- Yes. Is there any coffee left?
Cold.
- He likes cold coffee.
Doctor Seymour. Be careful and shut down.
Worry is not for him,
he has been up all night.
Yes. Danny Miller, then.
- Yes.
- Where is he? Do you know that?
Actually not.
Everyone wants to know where Danny is.
Or is that who Danny is?
Angus has read your first book.
You have a very optimistic view on your profession
- Except for Danny. What do you want to know?
How did a writer's course
lead to a knife crash?
If I tell you,
do you give him my address then?
Do you want to?
As a therapist, you should know
that Danny is not the victim.
He can be a seductive young man and...
I do not know what he said, but nothing
happened between us. Nothing physical.
After all I did for him
I'm being accused.
You know what he is capable of,
I know. He wrote about you repeatedly.
Danny is gifted with a huge talent.
A good writer, but a black hole.
You are pulled in. He draws one.
- Jeremy!
The story Danny wrote to me, and apologize for words - but he
saw me in the eyes, crossed the room and showed me his captain.
But the thing is that
that he seemed to enjoy it.
- Danny seemed to enjoy the action itself.
- That bastard pretended to be my friend.
- Do not be alone with him.
- I'm not worried.
Lucky for you.
Doctor Seymour. Hi.
Excuse me. I know it seems cymbic,
but can you sign your book?
Sure, jump in.
- It's cold out there.
- I have not seen this for a while.
I have started reading it
and I really like it.
But the stories the children are talking
about is more for adults than for theirs?
- Maybe for boats. What was your name, now again?
- Rowena.
I saw you speaking at school.
You were great.
- Enter?
- We have problems.
- Have you heard of Danny?
- No why?
Danny's father has called my
private phone. He knows where Danny is.
I do not know what he wants. Can you talk
to him before he does anything stupid?
He is unstable.
I have tracked the phone to Norwich.
- Do you have an address?
- I'll call you.
Are you following me, your damn?
Do not you think I notice it?
- I know who you are, Dr. Seymour.
- I want to talk about your son.
My son is a wretch, a shame.
He must be in prison again.
- You have apparently tried to contact him.
- Certainly you have had contact.
You of all fools should understand
that it was good that he was in prison.
- He's out and we're trying to help him.
- He must stop, okay?
Do not you understand how difficult it
is for a father to say so about his son?
Do you know what? Stick from here, for the fan.
You are like all other bleak freaks.
You have no idea
what you are dealing with.
Hello. Sorry darling. I miss you.
Wait, I do not hear. I will turn off.
Where are you? With your parents?
- No, with us. I missed you.
- I'm on my way home now.
- How long are you leaving? We cook dinner.
- Oh, who's there?
- Ian. We drove home from town.
- He should not be home with us.
Have you never used a knife before?
Vegetables do not cut themselves.
- Lauren, I mean seriously. Listen.
- Do you listen to my private conversation?
- Lauren, enter another room now.
- Switch to music I do not get headache.
- We wait for the food until you arrive.
- No, Lauren! Lauren!
Come on. Come on!
Run!
Lauren? Lauren.
Did not you hear me calling?
- Hi, myself.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Sorry, we only ate dinner.
- Take it easy.
- Ian, leave my home now. Now.
- No danger. Okay.
Thanks for the good dinner.
- Why are you appealing to him?
- You know nothing about him.
Danny. Did we agree
that you would not come home to me anymore?
Have you seen the news?
An old man has been murdered in Danbury.
There were two kids who did.
- Everything will happen again, right?
- Have you talked to your father?
Why would I do it?
Have you done it?
Fan, they will bura me again.
They will blow me again.
You have no idea who the guy is.
And you do that? He is not a
mental diagnosis, he is a child.
Stay away from him.
Trust me, okay?
- Stay away.
- Okay. Certainly.
I have to quit this.
Doctor Seymour, can we talk to you?
We want to talk about the Danbury youths.
They are not my clients.
I'm not involved in the case.
No, but they have released Daniel Miller, who
killed Elisabeth Parks twelve years ago.
- He was patient.
- I do not comment on clients.
Some had traveled to North Fork
for rafting in fashion.
What do I do in North Fork,
where is the salmon wandering?
Remember where we were,
then we will continue.
Did you tell your journalist
that he was out? Did you do that?
She already knew. I just confirmed that.
His father tells to anyone who
wants to listen. Empty. Tommy.
Did you think that's the end of our part?
Just because we locked him in
he will not be left behind lock and boom.
I will return to my meeting.
If you want to take a glass together
- And forget that we were
indented in this shit, call me-
- but calm down you She is running
her story tonight or tomorrow.
Then it's over.
What we can count on are people.
And people's lack of ability to follow
up things and long-term memories.
Calm down, hell.
Danny. You, me and Angela
need to be seen and set up a plan.
We can try to solve this together,
then call me.
I'm taking time.
I went to Lizzie
to feed the cats. The kittens.
Mom was home
and dad was back in the war.
- Are you tired, Danny?
- No. I liked Lizzie.
She did not look so good.
She had stared in her eyes.
When I got there she was not there,
so I went upstairs.
She had pillows. Dampuder.
- It smelled of flowers and was sticky.
- Then, then?
Then I heard her.
She came in and walked up the stairs.
I ran to get past her, but
she stood in the way and did not move.
I kicked her down.
She pushed and sounded so I took the paddle
from the chair. She had pads from Boston.
I covered her face
to make her stop.
She continued to kick and kick.
And how did it feel?
Like a chicken with a cut head.
- Why did you go back?
- I do not know.
- Why, if you knew it was wrong?
- Your fingers were clean, the nails with.
- I do not know who that kid is.
- No danger. Tell me what happened.
- It does not play a damn role!
- You still do not believe me.
- No one believes you do not take responsibility.
Your responsibility, then?
Sorry, I took it.
It was wrong. She is very weird.
Return these to my father.
I do not want them anymore.
Danny, for your own sake
you must call Angela.
Danny!
Please, I found him in my office.
He just went.
- Why did not you keep him?
- He broke in. He has stolen from me.
He is not my case or my patient!
We do not know where Daniel Miller was
deployed, but we have talked to his father.
I do not understand why he was released.
Last I heard something where he was somewhere
in Connecticut, probably New London.
The release of juvenile criminals is on the
tape after the recent violent violations.
- I'm going to bed.
- Okay. I'll be right away.
- Is it okay with you?
- Yes. And with you?
I do not know.
I do not know if it's okay.
- Why did not you tell me he was?
- Because it was over 12 years ago, Lauren.
I did not want
that would affect you or us.
The kid needs your help.
I do not know if I can help him.
- Sorry?
- They locked him in.
Because I thought
that he was a bad person.
- Still believe it?
- I do not know anymore, that's the problem.
- I just tried to protect you.
- No, you tried to protect yourself.
Do you know what?
Things are good or bad.
With people it is not always as easy.
I'm going back to town for a while.
You know where I am.
Are you sure?
Do nothing until I get there.
How far away are you? I go there
before he does anything against himself.
Danny.
Her niece lived here for a while,
I have heard.
Danny, they're burying you for that gun.
Maybe that.
But that's crazy. I can not close
without seeing her face.
Up and down, right there. She stares at me.
Not even if they burned down the place.
- You can give me the weapon, Danny?
- No.
I thought my dad would come here first.
Search and destroy.
Mr. Miller. That was what he was good at.
Little Danny Miller came back here evenly
- Every time he did it
he thought...
I thought-
- Lizzie was going to walk around.
Feed their cats.
"on my feet" mother had said.
As if none of it had happened.
Neither Lizzie nor my mom.
When I was a boy I pushed
and some friends a boy in the water-
- And watched when he almost drowned.
Did you see? Tom, that's your big problem.
You like to look at.
You are a tourist. That's what the rich do.
- Dad saved him from drowning.
- You jumped in and saved me.
We could have gone together,
but you saved me, Dr. Seymour.
Did I tell you about the drowning sooner?
Did you know I was in the river?
I do not think so.
You like to watch,
until you do not do it anymore.
People I have no choice.
Why did not you help me?
- I thought I did.
- Do not lie!
Open it and pick it up.
Otherwise, I'll kill you and leave myself.
- Do it! Now! Do it! Open it!
- Okay, I'll!
Record it. Pick it up!
Hold it.
Danny, why are you doing this?
Danny.
Danny, do not do this.
Danny, does not.
Snooze.
- Blunda.
- Do not do it.
That's where to feel.
It's not to be seen, it's feeling.
Is that what you were afraid of?
The feeling that someone may like it?
Why? Because we are killer?
We're killer everyone, Tom.
But to like it's something
completely different.
- Did you like how it felt?
- No. No, I did not.
Not me either.
I kicked her.
She fell and started shaking and...
Forgive me.
- Forgive me!
- No problem.
So.
It's daddy. He knows where I am, Tom.
Okay. Everything will be okay.
Get upstairs and stay away.
Away from the car!
I'm so tired of your fucking idiots!
- Let him be!
- Who do you think was where he was?
Should it be a sneak peek?
Skitsnack?
He can trick you, but not me.
These are the stories.
The stories the children intimate
themselves after the event or the action.
We do not punish or accuse them-
- Helps them to redo
their story in a way that gives them hope-
Opportunities and a Future.
If you do not think a child
has a future, what should you believe in?
Excuse me, but do not you exploit
the children you try to help?
The only thing he exploits here is himself.
Worry is not for her.
She has had drugs.
- That's what she's famous for here.
- Go to hell.
- A good friend?
- I thought so.
I saw the newspaper ad.
This is really exciting, Tom.
But...
- You did not mention me in the book.
- No, not in this.
A chapter is not enough for you.
You deserve your own book.
- Portland, then?
- Yes, I'm stopping. We are kind of a million.
It's like prison, stuck with girls.
- So you enjoy the present and the past?
- Yes. I'm looking forward.
- Danny, there you are.
- Hello Darling.
- Rowena.
- Yesvisst.
You seem to feel good.
I moved here at the same time as Danny.
Sorry, I missed the lecture.
- Did you tell me about your story?
- No, he did not.
- He is very talented.
It ends in the quarterly newspaper.
It is good and strange.
It's about a boy who buy
toy soldiers made in China.
Okay, now it's enough.
- Hurry up, Rowe!
- See you soon.
Nice to meet again.
- Toy soldiers were from Walmart.
- Excuse me?
In my story
comes the toys from Walmart.
It's about a guy
who starts fucking with his psychiatrist.
His former psychiatrist,
he had as a child.
It's just a story, Tom.
I will send it to you. Read it.
- What is the story called?
- "Tourist."
But it's not you anymore, right?
No.
You hugged the trigger, right?
You almost killed him.
I thought you would do it.
What is it?
- What's so damn fun?
- Nothing. People like you, just.
Forgive me.
You, I have to go to the airport.
- Do you want to go somewhere?
- Yes.
How is Lauren?
Did she not join in the trip?
No, she works.
Is everything good between you?
She's gonna feed soon?
- Yes, she will.
- Oh.
What fun. I know you tried for a long time
and it was hard for her.
- Congratulations. I'm so happy for you.
- How did you know my wife was pregnant?
- I asked how you knew.
- Tom, she called me and we talked a little.
Has not she told you?
We have not spoken,
I saw it on Facebook.
Relax, you're so excited.
But it's a boy, huh? Did not
she just know that it's a son?
You will be dad, Tom. Incredible.
What are you going to baptize?
You do not have to answer directly,
you have time for you.
I have to say
I long for meeting him.
Translation: Emil P.W.S Holmgren