[MUSIC PLAYING]
[BACKGROUND VOICES]
CHILD: My uncle says if I
tell, he'll kill my mother.
But I have to tell somebody.
Can I tell you?
BART: Jacob, where are you?
Jacob, get out here right now.
JACOB'S MOTHER: Jacob,
please listen to your father.
BART: You know I
don't like to be mad.
CHILD: My stepdad,
he will just start
Coming after me with a belt.
CHILD: But I have
to tell someone.
CHILD: She gets out of control.
Jacob, don't you run from me.
Jacob, don't make things
worse than they are.
Jacob.
BART: Jacob, why do
you make me so mad?
I don't want to be mad.
And then you make me mad.
MICHAEL: Jacob.
BART: Jacob, you're
going to get it
If you don't come out right now.
JACOB'S MOTHER: Please.
You know what you've done.
You know you've been bad.
JACOB'S MOTHER: Jacob?
BART: Where are you?
JACOB'S MOTHER: Jacob.
Please don't hide
from your father.
BART: You know, I've
got things to do here.
[SHOUTING]
Jacob.
Get up here now.
[DIALING PHONE]
[PHONE RINGING]
HOTLINE: ChildHelp National news
hotline How can we help you?
Yvonne and I opened
our headquarters
Here in Scottsdale in '96-
- Sara and I consider it
the heart of the operation.
Child Help's National
Abuse Hotline.
It's the cadillac of hotlines.
All of our operators have
their master's degree.
Wow, that's impressive.
Yes.
Well, they have to be able
to handle whatever comes
Their way, right
Detective Carter?
Yeah.
Well, you never know
what a call will bring.
Detective Carter,
this is Annie Grayson.
She's going to be
working with us.
Welcome aboard.
Thank you.
Nice to be here.
Are you still there?
Hello?
My name is Grace.
Can't tell you tell me yours?
Can you tell me your name?
Jacob.
Do you need some help, Jacob?
Please don't hide
from your father.
Don't hang up.
We can only help you if
you stay on the line.
I lost him.
Caller ID was blocked.
Not enough time to do a trace.
How much time do they need?
About 45 seconds.
Come on Jacob, honey.
Call us back.
You know I have things to do.
Where are you?
[PHONE RINGING]
Childhelp.
National Abuse Hotline.
Jacob?
Keep talking.
Just keep the line on.
Jacob, is that you again?
You need to talk to me.
Can you do that?
Can you tell me what's wrong?
Are you hurt?
Do you need someone to help you?
Do you believe in angels?
Yes, I do.
I do believe in angels, Jacob.
Jacob needs an angel
right now, real bad.
BART: Jacob.
Jacob, get over here now.
I hear someone else with you.
Is it someone you know, Jacob.
Are you at home?
Do you know your address?
Can you tell me where you are?
Bart.
Please let me talk to him.
Jacob, get out here now.
Jacob, where are you?
[WHIMPERING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Jacob.
Daddy, please, no.
Please.
HOTLINE: Jacob?
BART: Come on.
Jacob?
Jake?
Got a phone number.
And it's local.
[SIRENS]
Our son makes prank
calls all the time.
Tell them, honey.
That's right.
He's only nine.
You know how children can be.
There's no problem
here, officers.
I understand
that, Mr. Fletcher.
We still need to speak with him.
He went out with friends.
At this hour?
The boy's nine, you said.
It's all right.
You'll be OK.
OFFICER: We found him
beaten, tied to his bed.
There were marks on the posts.
So this wasn't the first time.
Kid hasn't said a
word since then.
You left him with
our doctor, right?
Yes, ma'am.
He's in the exam room now.
Get the paperwork started.
I'll get to the scene.
Thank you.
How did Jacob ever find the
strength to make that call?
It's a miracle.
We've seen our share
of those over the years.
Remember Tokyo?
Our first miracle.
[SINGING]
So are you boys
having a great time
Over here on this
side of the Pacific?
[BOOS]
We heard you might
need some new recruits.
Think you could squeeze us in?
[CHEERING]
Well, in that
case, Private Sara.
And Private Yvonne
reporting for duty.
[CHEERING]
Could one of you boys
point me in the direction
Of the Air Force
beautiful parlor?
You don't need one.
Oh, aren't you boys so sweet.
Why can't the boys
at home be like you?
Move over here.
[CHEERING]
[SINGING]
[SIRENS]
Sorry.
Sorry, ladies.
We've got to cut
this short, ladies.
Are we under attack?
It's another siren.
We've got to get you
back to your hotel.
Come on.
Careful.
Let's go.
[BACKGROUND VOICES]
Welcome to typhoon season.
October in Japan.
How long do these storms last?
Anybody's guess.
But we have more shows.
They're expecting us in Korea.
We can't fight an act of God.
He maybe wants you to stay here.
[CAR SCREECHING]
Oh.
Sit tight.
I'll be right back.
Oh, Sara, look.
Oh, my goodness.
What are they doing out there?
You shouldn't be
dressed like that.
You'll catch your death.
Why aren't you guys at home?
You understand
home, your parents?
Mama-sahn.
Papa-sahn.
Oh, my lord.
Think they're orphans?
Are you hungry?
I have some candy in my pockets.
Oh, my goodness.
OK.
Bet they haven't had
a decent meal in days.
Come on, kids.
Come, come, come.
What are you doing?
We can't leave
them out her, Sara.
They'll freeze.
Come on, honeys.
Come on.
This is going to
lead to trouble.
Come on.
OK, that's it.
Let's go.
OK, come on.
Come on.
Let's go get dry.
Here we go.
Open the door.
That's it.
Spot's our mascot.
He won't let anything
bad happen to you.
My name is Dr. Riggs.
And I'm only here to
make sure you're OK.
Are you good with that?
OK.
Let's just have a look here.
This must have hurt.
You want to tell me about it?
Is it OK if I take a picture?
I thought you'd want
to see these, Detective.
These Polaroids
were in their room?
[POLICE RADIO]
Anything you might have seen?
Anything at all
could be helpful.
People in this neighborhood
keep to themselves, Detective.
Privacy is very important to us.
More important than
protecting a child?
That boy still needs your help.
Give it some thought.
Call me if anything
comes to mind.
I've seen your x-rays, Jacob.
You have some broken bones
that didn't heal very well.
Did you know that?
Can you tell me
how that happened?
Take your time.
There's no hurry.
The boy's still not talking.
Not a word so far.
Well, he called our hotline.
And he spoke to one
of the counselors.
So we knew he can talk.
Just from observation earlier,
he's about two years behind.
He can't read very well.
Typical for abused children.
His father's a
big shot attorney.
No police record
for him or his wife.
But Jacob's teacher did
file a report last month.
Too many sick days,
suspicious injuries.
Parents actually
documented their abuse.
What do you mean?
Polaroids.
Mrs. Fletcher's admitted
showing them to Jacob
And promising it
would all happen again
If he didn't do
what they told him.
No wonder the
boy's not talking.
He's terrified.
I've seen that in
private practice before.
But Polaroids?
Is there a spot for Jacob
at the Merv Griffin Village?
Wickenburg is at capacity.
And so is our Virginia facility.
What about
California, Beaumont?
Yvonne is already
working on that.
What's he holding back?
It's a secret, children.
No one should know you're here.
Uh, just a minute.
Aloha.
Hi.
Peek-a-boo.
What's Japanese for peek-a-boo?
I don't know.
Some of them can
barely say hello.
Down, down, down.
[CHILDREN GIGGLING]
Down.
Under, under, under.
Under.
What's he doing?
Yes?
Only two, ladies?
Yep.
So many towels.
Yes.
Well, we take a lot of showers.
And you know, could you
talk to room service for us?
We need some sandwiches.
About 20.
20.
Yeah.
And three or four
pitchers of milk.
We're just...
Starving.
Famished.
[GIGGLING]
So...
You have child-ah in here?
Where you go?
Ah!
So many children, ah!
Hotel should know.
Um.
My gosh.
Thank you for the towels.
Do you... have you ever seen
a cashmere sweater before?
See, it's soft.
Isn't... that's soft.
Um.
If, if you were not to say
anything at all about this,
You, you could
have this sweater.
All yours.
OK?
Our secret.
Yes.
Thank you.
Very generous, Yvonne,
considering it was my sweater.
Oh my god.
More towels?
You call.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
OK, before you say anything,
Colonel, we have... Sara
And I didn't have any choice.
They didn't have anywhere to go.
And, and they were freezing.
That is not the issue.
Well, no one with
a heart could have
Left these children
out in that storm.
It was terrible.
The fact is you
can't keep them.
It could be a diplomatic
problem for all of us.
So what do we do?
Toss them back onto the streets?
You need to do something.
And if you don't, I will.
Pffft.
[LAUGHTER]
It's OK.
In your wildest
dreams, could you
Have ever expected
anything like this?
What?
Coming here to sing
and dance and ending up
A mother hen to a
dozen little chicks?
Never.
[SOFT LAUGHTER]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
This will be your new
home for awhile, Jacob.
It's a Childhelp
Village, the first one
That Sara and Yvonne created.
And what that signs
says up there is true.
Can you read it?
It says, all who enter
here will find love.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MICHAEL: Don't be afraid.
You're going to like it here.
Jacob, this is Michael.
This is David.
You're going to be roommates.
Here's some new clothes
for you to start with.
And you'll be able to
pick out your own later.
You get a new bed too,
with your initials on it.
Every kid does.
This is my bed.
And this is my bed.
So keep off it.
David.
Well it's mine.
You get toys, too.
You can earn points to buy more.
You like it?
What is he?
Stupid?
Can he talk?
That's enough.
David, that's enough.
Jacob.
Jacob, listen.
I know it's a lot to take in.
All these boys have been in the
same shoes as to you've been.
And it's going to be OK.
If you let us, it's
going to be fine.
Jacob, look at me.
You could give us a
chance to help you.
Just let us help you.
You'll be fine.
Jacob, look at me.
Jacob.
No.
Look at me.
It's going to be OK.
You're going to be fine.
Jacob.
It's OK.
It's going to be fine.
So who's the new kid?
The kid the bus
brought in today.
What's his story?
You know I'm not going to
answer a question like that.
What's the big deal?
How'd you like if I talked
about you with the other kids?
Rusty, that's for the horses.
Never seen him take
anybody like he has to you.
We both been through a lot.
That's why.
If you mix red and
blue, you get purple.
You know that?
Yeah.
Like the color of a bruise.
Or a plum.
Or an eggplant.
I thought eggs
came from chickens.
It's a vegetable.
Nothing to do with eggs.
Yeah?
Huh.
Yeah, maybe you could plant
one in your garden patch.
Maybe.
How about using some of
those colors you've mixed,
Maybe painting a picture.
Do they pay you by the number
of pictures us kids turn out?
No.
Did you paint for your
last art instructor?
You're not an instructor.
You're a therapist.
I asked Mr. Ogly
about the new kid.
Oh?
And?
He wouldn't tell me anything.
Did you think he would?
I heard he freaked
out in his room.
I heard he doesn't talk.
And that's just creepy.
Creepy around here
is saying something.
I bet he got beat
up a lot of home.
I bet his mom had a boyfriend
who drank a lot, took drugs.
And cut it when he didn't
do what he was told.
Is there more red?
Yeah.
There's some right over
there on the table.
Serve it.
Looking at these
kids, it's pretty hard
To believe this could
be their last chance.
Most of them have been bounced
through a dozen foster homes
Before finding this place.
I wish my daughter
knew how lucky she is.
Having trouble
adjusting to the move.
Oh, yeah.
She misses her
friends from Seattle.
Complains about me
working too much.
How long you been divorced?
Um, six years.
Six years.
How about you?
Ever think of getting married?
Having kids?
Aaah.
I've got a whole
village of them, right.
Well, thank god
for the village.
Mhm.
God.
Yvonne and Sara.
Those gals, they never
take no for an answer.
No.
We are full here.
Every place full.
Typhoon has made
many new orphans.
But what about these children?
We've been to five
other orphanages.
And no one will take them.
How can you turn them away?
They are not ours.
Japanese, you mean?
They most certainly are.
Only part.
Other part American.
You won't take them because
they're a mixed race?
What difference does
their background make?
They're children.
Mm.
Children, yes.
Not ours.
I'm very sorry.
OK, honeys.
What have we gotten
ourselves into?
Come on, honey.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
[WHIMPERING]
I thought you might be cold.
Why don't you want
the covers on?
My Mom used to tuck
me in all the time.
She used to let me light
her cigarettes for her, too.
She's coming to get me soon.
I think.
I don't hear from her much.
That's because she's been sick.
I bet or something.
I should go back to bed.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Julia?
Sorry I'm late, honey.
Julia.
Honey?
Who are you?
This is Granger.
He's helping me study.
Oh.
Little old to be the
same class, aren't you?
I'm not actually in school.
We met at the mall.
Right.
Well, Granger.
It's a little late.
And my daughter's a little
young for all this help.
So maybe you could find
your way to the door.
Mom!
It's OK.
Some other time.
Right.
In about five years, Granger.
I won't forget this.
And neither will I.
Sometimes I think we try to
be too many places at once.
Did you call Bob
and let him know
That were going to
be late tonight?
After all these years,
if I ever showed up
At a decent hour, I
think he'd take me.
Hey.
Hello, honey.
Some interesting information on
the Jacob Fletcher case today.
Their Arizona record is clean.
But a neighbor called and
mentioned seeing a Colorado
License plate when
they moved in.
And as usual, without
a national database,
Their records didn't follow
them from state to state.
How many times have we
come up against this?
And somebody's got to
close that loophole.
That may just have to
be you and me, Yvonne.
Admit it.
You were wondering what to
do with all that spare time.
Remind me again why we
gave up show business.
At least now with these
records to back us up,
We can see those
parents do time.
How much time is
the next question.
Right.
Oh, a package came
for you from overseas.
Oh, from Tokyo.
Mama Ji.
Yvonne!
This can't be right.
There is barely a door.
But this is it... this is
the address he gave us.
Maybe they read their
numbers right to left
Like the newspaper.
Oh, excuse me.
Are you Mama Ji?
Yes.
Oh, you the ladies?
American ladies?
Yes.
A doctor with the gospel mission
told us about the children
You take, the ones that
no one else will help,
And what good work you do.
He tell me about you too, but
sorry to say, no room here.
It's OK.
Come see.
OK.
Come on, honeys.
Come on, sweetie.
Come see.
No clothes.
Too little food.
I can barely handle
children I got.
Then suppose we
get you some help.
If we can do that...
But give takes money and time.
Well, the time we have.
The rest...
We'll get.
How?
He say you sing?
Tell a joke?
People pay big money for that?
I don't think so.
She's obviously seen our act.
Nina.
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't know how we're
going to make this right.
If we don't, who will?
[BELL RINGING]
Bye.
Jacob?
Jacob.
So I just wanted
to let you know
And let you hear me say
how much me and your sister
Want to make this work again.
I know you're thinking
you heard it all before.
But I'm doing the
therapy every week.
Mrs. Grayson can tell you
that if you don't believe me.
Three months so far.
I haven't missed a meeting.
Is there something you
want to say to me, sweetie?
Laura, you can say
whatever's on your mind.
I don't know why I'm here.
You're here to get better.
I mean, why am I
here in this room?
I don't want to see you.
I hate you.
Sweetie, we're family.
I don't want that
family any more.
And if there was a way to
get Karen away from you,
I would do that too.
Is he still there?
No.
But when he's finished
his sentence...
It's Johnny's home too.
I've talked to him.
He's changed.
Do I have to stay here?
You don't have to do
anything you don't want to do.
Baby, no.
[DOOR CLOSING]
I've done everything
that they said to do.
I don't know what else.
You're still planning
a life with a man
Who hurt your daughter.
Johnny's been good to me.
And he won't lay
a hand on Karen.
He's promised.
I mean, he knows he did wrong.
And he swore to me.
If Laura would just
give him half a chance.
Mrs. Wade, this is the man who
has your daughter so terrified
That she still wets her
bed almost every night
So that he'll leave her alone.
This is the man who
repeatedly molested
Her, who took a
razor to her face.
The sex was never proved.
He's serving 10
months for it now.
Well, the razor...
That was an accident.
He didn't mean to hurt her.
Did you listen to
a word she said.
Did you hear her?
There is no chance
in hell that she's
Coming home until at the very
least you get that man out
Of your life.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what
else to say to you.
[SINGING]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
YVONNE: Thank you.
Thank you all.
You'd think you hadn't seen
women over here in awhile.
[CHEERING]
I guess they haven't
What with all
that's happened, we
Were in Japan a lot
longer than planned.
Sorry.
Well, I guess you all
know that feeling, right?
We want you to know
that we're just really
Happy we could be here for you.
[CHEERING]
If we could get serious
for just one minute.
We'd like you to be
there for us too.
Because we need some help.
We discovered some
children here in Tokyo.
And they need homes.
And no one will take them in
because they're of mixed race.
They're just kids
who desperately
Need a helping hand.
And you see, Sara and I, we
made a promise... a promise
That we intend to keep.
Yes, and we can't
do that alone.
And you're the only
friends we have over here.
YVONNE: Yeah.
So we're asking you
if you could find it
In your hearts to maybe
donate a few dollars.
Maybe help them out.
SARA: Could you do that for us?
Make their lives a
little bit easier.
Thank you.
Take your hat.
Thanks.
There you go, darlin'.
SARA: Thank you.
Thank you.
SOLDIER: I've got
some over here.
YVONNE: Thank you very much.
It's very kind of you.
Both countries are well
aware of the problem.
And both countries ignore it.
COLONEL: And you're
going to do what
Two major governments can't.
Well, we can certainly try.
COLONEL: Listen, I could
have you on a plane
And back to the States
with a single call.
Well, don't waste your dime.
We won't go.
Their fathers may have turned
their backs on these kids.
But Yvonne and I just can't.
Colonel, could you hand
me that blouse out there?
Don't make me pull rank.
Then don't make us... well,
please, just don't make us.
Look, you've got
television and movies
Waiting for you
back in Hollywood.
Why are you wasting your
time on a hopeless cause?
Hopeless?
It's only hopeless
if we give up on it.
Now that we're involved,
you'll have to...
Carry us kicking and screaming
to that plane of yours.
Yvonne and I believe that
every life has a purpose.
And ours seem to be
tangled up with these kids.
Do you have a family?
If these were your children,
what would you want us to do?
Dammit.
I hired entertainers,
not social workers.
We'll have the plane
waiting at 09:00 tomorrow.
You have your stuff
packed and be on it.
And that's an order.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[DOOR CLOSING]
Looking forward to showing
you the ranch, Jacob.
You're not shy around
animals, are you?
A lot of kids are.
But I'm willing
to bet that you're
Going to have a good time.
So what is it you
think you'd like to do?
There's a lot of choices.
There's gardening.
There's ah grooming,
feeding the animals.
Any thoughts?
Man of few words.
Not always a bad thing.
So uh hey, ever seen a cow?
Up close, personal?
That's Bessie.
Why don't you go on over
and introduce yourself.
There's no reason to be afraid.
She likes kids.
Go on.
Whoa.
Hey now.
That's not the... let go.
Let go.
That's not the way
we treat animals
Around here, especially Bessie.
She's been roughed up
enough, haven't you, girl?
Let me show you.
She's a prize cow... blue
ribbons, everything.
Then one day, someone
poured acid all over her.
See?
When she came to us,
she was half dead.
Afraid of people.
Always stayed in that
corner over there,
Even if it may get
real hot and thirsty.
But with love, attention,
a lot of patience,
Well, she's as good as gold now.
You think on that the next
time you feel like hitting her.
And she can't say it right
out, because she's a cow.
But all she really
needs is love.
[MOOING]
Take care of her for me.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOOING]
Jacob knows.
That's very good, Laura.
It's only a line.
Yeah, but it's a good line.
And every great painting
starts somewhere.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I didn't make them up.
They're just me.
All of them?
Yes.
Even this one?
Mom's boyfriend
cut all my hair off
So nobody else would
think I was pretty.
No offense, mom, but
all of this is just sad.
You never talk about
normal things anymore.
Well, we could talk
about your school work.
But that's been pretty
sad lately, too.
The teachers here
have it in for me.
No one has it in for you.
Maybe if you spent more time
at home, you could help me.
Oh, I see.
Your lousy grades are my fault.
My grades were fine in Seattle.
I hate my life here.
Oh, honey, Julia.
If you only knew how
good you have it.
As compared to what?
Your freaks?
Hey.
That's enough.
Sorry.
Can't Childhelp do like
plastic surgery or something
On this kid?
Yes, they can.
It has to be her choice.
She has to be ready.
If I had a face like this
I'd be ready last year.
Why do you and those women...
Sara and Yvonne.
Right.
Why do they care so
much about this kid?
It's not just this kid.
It's every kid.
That's what they fought
for their whole lives.
SARA: Are we going to leave
without a fight, Yvonne?
Those kids need us.
What about all that
money we collected?
It's not even enough to give
him a roof over their heads.
A couple of months of
food maybe, but what
Happens when... when that's gone?
You're right.
The easiest thing
for us to do would
Be to go back to Hollywood and
forget we ever met those kids.
That's the easiest
thing, all right.
Except for the forgetting part.
All they need is
a place to be safe.
Where's the baby?
In the nursery.
That's where he belongs.
Do you want to talk about
why the baby belongs there?
Well, today I thought we
could do a drawing of someone
Really special.
Of who?
Of you.
Of Jacob?
Come on, I'll show you.
Stand up here against the paper.
Put your arms out.
There we go.
Now we're going to start.
And I'm going to draw
around your arms,
You legs, and your head.
And now you get to fill it in.
Color it in any way you'd like.
Jacob can't draw very good.
Not like the other kids.
Well, you know.
That's what makes
this so special,
Is that it's just yours
and not like anyone else's.
OK.
That' great.
Big, beautiful eyes like yours.
Good nose.
How about ears?
You can't hear
anything without ears.
Jacob doesn't
like what he hears.
What about a mouth?
He always says the wrong thing.
He doesn't need a mouth.
Well, you can still color
in any of the other parts.
What would you
like to draw next?
Look at that.
It's stupid.
We should just cut it
off, it looks so stupid.
Jacob's bad.
Stupid.
Jacob's just stupid.
Too stupid to live.
Jacob.
You can't hide from
me forever, pal.
Why did you have
to be so bad, honey.
You know I can't help you now.
Did you really think
I wouldn't find you?
Uh, please!
No, please.
Jacob.
Please.
[CRYING] Stop.
Jacob?
Are you OK?
We wish it were more.
But it's all we could manage.
Ladies such a blessing.
So few even try.
This can go long way.
Can it go far enough?
Mama Ji, [SPEAKING JAPANESE]
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
What soldiers doing here?
Oh, they're not here for you.
They're here for us.
You asked me what I'd do
if they were my children?
I'll tell you what I'd do.
Better yet, I'll show you.
Gentleman.
They're all volunteers.
They're on their own time.
An answer to our prayers.
It's a miracle.
Well, God works
in mysterious ways.
Even through Colonel Johnson.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
YVONNE: Before we left Japan,
we had 100 children in our care.
We came back and
built four orphanages
That went on to help thousands.
By then, there was
a controversial war
Waging in Southeast Asia.
SARA: With lots of help, we
managed to build five more
Orphanages and a children's
hospital in Vietnam.
When the bombs began to fall, we
had no choice but to evacuate.
We became known as
Operation Babyland.
I know you're all frightened
and you don't even
Know what I'm saying right now.
The most important thing
is that you're safe now.
Hi.
Yvonne.
This one needs attention.
Oh, OK.
We have a medical
team downstairs.
It's OK here, honey.
Sara.
Let's look at you.
Oh.
Come here.
Angela, honey.
Can you take this one, please?
Let's get the sick ones and
the youngest ones off first.
Yvonne, Sara.
Yes?
I need to talk to you.
We were expecting more.
Did you get all the kids out
of the China Beach orphanage.
No.
The Viet Cong were
coming too fast.
We barely got the
plane off the ground.
There was fire all around us.
But the children...
We got as many as we could.
If we hadn't left when we did.
As we took off and banked
left over the beach,
We see the staff getting
the others out by bus.
When I looked back, I saw the
rest of the children being
Pulled out of their hiding
places out onto the beach.
They were lined up.
And they just shot them.
I'm sorry.
It's OK.
After all we did,
it wasn't enough.
So then we just
have to do more.
OK?
A few months in jail?
That's all for what those
people did to Jacob?
Hey, most child abusers
don't do any time.
Mr. And Mrs. Fletcher.
I want to see my son.
And I want you to
make that happen.
Jacob has had a very difficult
time adjusting and he...
Of course he's had a very
difficult time adjusting.
He's surrounded by strangers.
He needs to be home.
He needs to be safe.
The boy needs to know
that there are people who
Care about him, who
want the best for him.
Who Jacob is with
isn't your decision,
Not when it comes
right down to it.
He's not your son.
And he's not your property.
Will you arrange the visit.
Or do I bring the
courts into this?
We can't stop you
from seeing him.
But I swear I will walk through
fire to make sure you don't
Have control over
his life again.
Dig deeper.
Keep those people from ever
getting that boy back again.
Laura, would you help me
wash the brushes, please?
Sure.
Laura, are you OK?
No, don't hit me.
It's OK.
It's all right, Laura.
Come on.
Come sit down.
Where'd you go just now?
I was back home.
Sometimes if I did
something or didn't
Do something, my
mother's boyfriend...
Johnny.
He'd fill the tub
with hot water.
Only the hot.
He'd push me in.
My skin blistered sometimes.
Did he give you a reason why?
Maybe I didn't get him
a beer when he asked.
Or maybe he didn't like
the way I looked at him.
Sometimes he'd lock me
in the closet at night.
I couldn't get out to eat
or go to the bathroom.
My sister would shove food
in the crack under the door
If he didn't catch her.
Did he hurt her, too.
I'd sleep in front of
her on the bed at night,
Push her against the wall
so he couldn't reach her.
So he'd take me instead.
Where was your mother
when this was happening?
At work, I guess.
I don't know.
Did she know what was going on?
She says she didn't.
Did you ever tell her?
Did you ever ask
her to make it stop?
Johnny called me
a liar and said
That he would move out
if Mom took my side.
So she believed him.
Even after.
After?
Mrs. Grayson, if somebody
did this to your daughter,
Would you just let
them stay there?
This is all a misunderstanding.
I know my rights, Mr. Aubry.
Oh, good.
Have a seat.
Let's talk about those rights.
You can visit your son.
But only here and
with supervision,
Unless and until the
courts say otherwise.
And the courts,
they tend to listen
To what Chidhelp has to say.
So like it or not,
this is the beginning
Of a long, long process.
All I want is my child back.
Have you ever asked Jacob
how he feels about that?
He's a kid.
He wants to be home.
You do you want that,
don't you, sweetheart?
What are you doing?
Huh?
Jacob.
It looks like packing.
Are you packing?
Shh.
Jacob's going home.
They'll get him if he doesn't.
But if you go, you
won't meet my mom.
Don't you want to meet her?
Sorry.
Jacob's gotta go.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIRENS]
Ah, thought that might be you.
Come into town to check out
the night life, did you?
Jacob's waiting for a bus.
Bus, huh?
Yeah, it might be
a bit of a wait.
Next one doesn't come by
until tomorrow morning.
Can I give you a lift
back to your cottage?
If Jacob goes back,
something bad will happen.
Are you hungry?
Me, I'd go for a
burger and fries,
Maybe even a chocolate shake.
Hate to eat alone.
Think you might want
to keep me company?
Yup.
Sure.
Run away If you want.
You'd be missing a lot...
Parties and friends, school.
Teachers say that you're
doing real well lately.
Pass the ketchup there.
Jacob moved up a whole grade.
He can work a computer now.
Not many kids can accomplish
something like that so fast.
Uh, did I mention that
Bessie's been asking about you?
Cows don't talk.
Doesn't mean they don't
have something to say.
You weren't talking when
you came to us, either,
You remember?
But you had plenty on your mind.
Still do, I guess.
Hey, look.
I know.
This is tricky, huh?
Here's the bottom line.
You put your trust in me
and Annie, and your cottage
Supervisor, and
all the counselors
That are looking out for you.
We will never let you down.
You don't want to go home.
And we will do our best to make
sure that that doesn't happen.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Oh, boy.
You got any money on ya?
This one's on me.
You know, a bus is going
to cost you a few bucks.
You can't get that
far on charm alone.
Three million cases of child
abuse are reported every year.
It's more than 10,000 a day.
Ladies, we know the statistics.
It's what we do for a living.
Not very successfully if these
numbers are any indication.
We came here
because Mrs. Reagan
Asked us to meet with you.
She asked you to meet
with us because she agrees
That these children need a
safe and healing environment.
Instead of moving the children
from agency to agency,
Bring the professionals to them.
We want to approach the child
abuse problem from all sides...
Psychologically,
environmentally,
Educationally,
legally, spiritually.
Combine conventional
therapies with art
Therapy, animal therapy.
Just throw everything but
the kitchen sink at it.
To accomplish something
like that, you'd need a...
A village.
You'd need a village.
Eventually several.
If you had any
experience at all,
You know that wouldn't work.
Let me tell you
what won't work.
Ignoring the problem won't work.
Assuming there is no
solution won't work.
Sitting on your tail, admiring
your diploma won't work.
Don't you people ever get
tired of, of saying no?
Yvonne and I have
never been that way.
And we never will be.
We've asked all of you here
because we need your help.
But if you're not
up to it, we'll
Just go right
across this country
And knock on every door until
we put the right team together.
Yvonne, do you have
anything you'd like to add?
Yes, I do.
We'd like a commitment from
each of you, a promise to help.
Or else we won't let
you leave the room.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Can Jacob see Bessie?
Uh, I don't know, pal.
Uh, she's probably
still sleeping.
But, yeah.
I guess she'd like that.
Go ahead.
Hey there, Bess.
It's OK now.
It's OK.
I love you, Bessie.
No!
No covers.
OK.
Nice work, cowboy.
You're in awful
early, aren't you?
The hours it takes
are the hours it takes.
I saw you pull in.
Kid had a rough night.
Took til dawn to talk
him into coming back.
How did you know what
he needed to hear?
I was that kid once.
Yeah, my ma used
to hit the bottle.
And when she did, her
moods turned violent.
Damn near killed
me once or twice.
Is that why don't you
want to have children?
Family abuse runs in cycles.
It stops with me.
Well, from what I can see,
the cycle's already broken.
Well, if that's true,
I owe it to this place.
There's something about this
property that's healing.
Sara and Yvonne must
have felt that when
They first laid eyes on it.
This is a large
tract with buildings
Already here from our
recent boy's town.
You're offering us less
than half what we're asking.
If that's your final
offer, then I...
Well, actually,
Bishop O'Connor,
We are uh prepared to
offer more than that.
You see, the orphanage that
we helped build in Tokyo...
They baked cookies.
Mama Ji and all the children.
And they sold them on the
streets to raise money for us.
They raised almost $5,000.
Those must be some cookies.
Yes, they are.
We're talking millions.
It's all very touching, ladies.
But business is business.
All right then, well
then let's talk business.
You're never going to sell this
land for what you're asking.
And that's just a fact.
Sorry to be blunt, but it's
out in the middle of nowhere.
And it's of no use to anyone.
Anyone but us.
And when you look at it that
way, you actually need us.
We need you?
Am I hearing you correctly?
Bishop O'Connor, we
are looking for a place
That we can help undo the
damage that these children have
Suffered.
This could be that place.
But we only have 1.8
that we can offer.
Plus the cookies.
Well, then I suppose
we'll just have to take it.
Oh.
Oh, my gosh.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, really.
Appreciate it.
Where are you going, Rusty?
Where are you going?
Where's Mr. Aubry?
Getting some breakfast.
I'm keeping watch.
Well, Bessie and me.
Jacob had a late night.
I heard.
Can I sit with you?
Just til he wakes up?
Of course.
Come on.
Thank you.
Mrs. Grayson?
Mhm?
Am I pretty?
Yes.
Yes, you are.
Some of the kids
call me scar face.
Well, they just can't see what
I see, a beautiful girl who
Cares about other
kids like Jacob.
Sometimes I forget it's there.
And I look in the mirror
and it surprises me,
Like it's somebody
else looking back.
I wish it would go away.
We can make that happen.
But only if that's
what you really want.
It didn't use to be.
But I think maybe now it is.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOG WHINING]
[HOSPITAL PAGING]
Nervous?
Yeah, a little.
You look like
you're going to cry.
Is it that bad?
No, no.
It's not.
You can see for yourself.
You're like new.
Now, there's a little bit
of redness and some swelling.
But that's going to fade
over the next few weeks.
It's wonderful, Laura.
It really is.
When you were born,
you were the most
Beautiful baby I'd ever seen.
Your skin was pink and perfect.
And now you're that way again.
It's like you're born all over.
Take another look.
It's great.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[APPLAUSE AND CHEERING]
Hey, Mrs. Grayson.
Hey, Laura.
You're up next, all right.
Jacob.
Laura.
No more scar face, see.
That's great.
I got your card in hospital.
You made it yourself, right?
Yeah.
OK.
So next for our Halloween
entertainment, Laura Wade
Would like to read us something,
something she wrote herself.
[APPLAUSE]
I used to want to
be a bird away up
In a tree, or a fish
that swims forever,
In a world beneath the sea.
I wanted to be anyone
or anything that's free.
But I'm not hiding anymore.
And now at last I see.
That all I really wanted
was for me to just be me.
[APPLAUSE]
Wow, was that our Laura?
It's pretty amazing the
power they have to heal.
Trick or treat.
Thank you.
Michael?
That's my mom!
Mom!
Mommy!
I knew you'd come.
We're petitioning the
courts to regain custody.
Well, you're welcome
to try, Mr. Fletcher.
But it's our opinion
and the opinion
Of all the social workers
who know your case that will
Determine whether or not
Jacob can be returned to you.
You've kept him from
us without just cause.
We mean to prove that and
rectify the situation.
You both have children.
As mothers, you know what
a child means to a parent.
I know even better than
most, Mrs. Fletcher.
But I also know your
history with Jacob.
Yes, we've seen the
x-rays, and the bruises,
The photographs you yourself...
We've served our time.
Listen.
If you won't turn him
over to us yourselves,
We're prepared to let the
authorities do it for you.
Let's go
Things will be
different this time.
I promise.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[BELL RINGING]
Give me that bag, David.
Mrs. Grayson?
Yes?
That's David.
What's he doing?
He didn't tell you?
He's being adopted
today by a Childhelp
Chapter member family.
Oh, hey Jacob.
Bye!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHIMPERING]
That's it.
Good.
See, it's a lot easier than you
thought it would be, isn't it?
Yeah.
That's great, Jacob.
Good work.
[WHIMPERING]
Yeah, yeah.
Turn him.
Use your leg.
Use your... now we're talkin'.
That's it.
Good.
Great.
That's it.
Looking good.
[WHIMPERING]
Hey.
What are you working on?
Putting together
the best parts of me.
Well, there are lot of really
good parts, aren't there?
What do you think?
You like it?
I love it.
You hate it.
Did you think I wouldn't?
This isn't some new
shade of lipstick, Julia.
You should have asked me.
It's my body.
Not until you're 18, it's not.
This is so typical.
You tolerate the most freaky
behavior from these loser kids
Every day, and yet you come home
and expect me to be perfect.
Well, I'm tired of it.
You call this art?
I call it therapy.
Is this supposed to be a tree?
It's the project I start
new children off with.
Every kid knows what
a tree looks like.
But how they paint it reflects
what they've been through.
Well, what's that?
It's a trauma hole.
It's a mark of her molestation.
The closer to the top
it is, the more recent.
The larger it is,
the more invasive.
That was painted by
a seven-year-old boy.
That's him there.
He does spell peaces.
His mother used to cut
him with razor blades.
But only where his clothes
would cover his scars.
You know, Julia.
These are pictures of
lives that children
Shouldn't even have to imagine.
And these kids live them.
You should come to
the village sometime.
See for yourself.
Like I'd actually do that.
Bye, Michael.
Bye.
So how do you really feel
about Michael going home today?
On paper, his mother's
done everything
The judge demanded of her.
You don't really
trust her, do you?
Let's hope for the best.
I don't want you to leave.
It's all going to be great now.
It's all I ever wanted.
Really.
When you're afraid at
night, think of me.
OK?
OK.
And it'll all be better.
I'll write you.
I'll write you back, Michael.
You're the best
friend I've ever had.
You too.
Maybe we can go camping
sometime like we talked.
And maybe my mom will take us.
Yeah.
Well, goodbye.
We've got a long
drive ahead of us.
Let's get a move on now.
You call us if you
need us, OK Michael.
All I need's my mom.
Right.
OK.
I said get in the car, Michael.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Bye, Jacob.
Bye, Michael.
[WHIMPERING]
So I have a new budget here.
And there's an item
we need... Sara?
Little Michael's dead.
What?
From Beaumont?
Oh, that poor sweet little boy.
We should have never allowed
him to go back to that woman.
Honey, we had no choice.
We should have fought
harder, found ways, something.
It's like I'm losing
my own son again.
It's 20 years ago.
And I'm hearing about
the crash, knowing
There's nothing I can do.
If we can't save one small boy.
We have saved thousands, Sara.
Thousands aren't
enough, not today.
It should have been one more.
It should have been Michael.
Shh.
I know you must be missing
my chicken sandwiches.
They've got chicken here.
Not like mine, I bet.
Johnny's never coming back.
Did you know that?
I told him that
he wasn't welcome.
You were right.
It was thing to do,
to protect Karen.
And to prove to you that I
mean what I've been saying.
You're my life, Laura.
You and your sister.
Why should she
believe you, Mrs. Wade?
Well, I'm speaking
from my heart.
What about tomorrow, though.
Or next week, or next year.
Well, there's no
calendar on my love
For my daughter, Mrs. Grayson.
You can't just expect her to...
I don't expect
her to do anything
Except for to give me a chance.
I got a new job.
And we moved to an
apartment that's closer
To schools, right.
I really hope you
come home, Laura.
I miss you.
I miss you, too.
You know what, we don't
have to decide right now, OK?
Uh.
Let's just have our picnic.
And we can talk about
this more next time.
OK?
Mrs. Grayson.
I made extra.
No, thank you.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
Ah.
You OK?
Yeah.
After what happened to Michael,
I uh... I looked at Laura
And all I could
think was what might
Happen if that little
girl goes home.
And she might.
We don't have the final say.
We just have to accept that.
I can't lose another
one of these kids.
Right know you
can give Laura what
I know you give your own
daughter... the conviction
That she's worthy
of respect and love.
Yeah.
Julia.
Yes?
Honey, are you down here?
Yes.
You OK?
You checking up on me?
Just making sure you're safe.
What's safer than my own house?
Hm.
So you've been going
through my things.
Well, kind of.
Since you showed them to me, I
can't stop thinking about them.
And this one here, is this
a picture of how he feels?
Or how it really was?
Well, this was painted
by a girl, six years old,
Locked in the basement
most of her life.
Neighbors didn't
even know she existed
Until a relative
called child services.
You really care
about these kids.
Yeah, I do.
But that doesn't mean I
care any less about you.
I love you.
You know that, right?
I love you, too.
That's good to hear.
And you know it's good for both
of us to hear now and then,
Right?
Sure is.
Back to homework.
Uh, thanks.
These will be pretty.
I saw you coming out of
the chapel this morning.
Ah, well, I had some things I
needed to talk over with God.
Do you think he really listens?
I think he does.
Yes.
Why?
Is there something you
need to talk over with him?
I was wondering what God
thought about me going home.
I mean, I want to trust my
mother, but I'm not sure I can.
And I need to be
there for my sister.
Well, you know.
Those are good
questions to ask God.
I used to ask my mom
questions all the time.
When I asked about God, she
said he never made mistakes.
Hmm.
Then Johnny heard us talking.
And he said that God made
a mistake when he made me.
Well, you know,
there's a saying
My mother used to tell
me, consider the source.
Yeah.
Consider the source.
You got it.
[CRYING]
Jacob.
He needs to breathe.
Hey, what are you
doing out here?
He needs a straw
to breathe through.
Even then it's... it's hard.
What are you talking about?
The baby, the
baby in the ground.
The baby in the ground.
Tell me about the baby, Jacob.
The daddy, he digs a
hole in the backyard.
And he makes me do it.
And he was lying down in it.
He says if he if he screams
he'll be in there longer.
Well, Mommy, she
gives him a straw
To breathe through and and he
He fills the hole.
He woudn't have done it
if he hadn't been bad.
What's the baby's name, son?
Jacob.
[CRYING]
I know.
Yeah.
You're a good kid.
Good kid, Jacob.
I'm out late a lot, you
know, out walking my dog.
Every now and then, I'd see
the lights come on back here.
Over there, guys.
I mean, I thought it was a
bit strange being the middle
Of the night and all, but, uh...
Did you ever anything?
Like?
Like noises.
People talking.
Someone digging.
Digging?
Detective.
My god.
What were they doing to him?
I'm losing my patience
with you, Mr. Aubry.
I really am.
Has something happened
we should know about?
Yes.
Your case is about
to be reopened.
Nonsense.
We can't be tried twice for
the same supposed crimes.
This is a new
crime, Mr. Fletcher.
A new crime?
This time I hope they
throw away the key.
Bart?
Relax.
They found nothing.
Because there's nothing to find.
I'm here almost
15 years, Fletcher.
Thought I'd seen it all.
Whatever Jacob's told
you is all in his head.
He's always been a liar.
You know what kind
of trouble he causes.
What kind of trouble would
make you bury your son alive?
Oh, my god.
Not another word.
You'll be hearing
from me, you and
This whole damn organization.
Thanks to this damn
organization, the law
Sides with kids these days.
Mr. And Mrs. Fletcher.
You'll have to come with me.
It's just beautiful, sweetie.
It's the first one
she's let me put up.
I know Johnny hurt you, honey.
And if there was some way to go
back and take that pain away,
I would.
You let him do that to me.
How does that make you
any better than him?
It doesn't.
But I will find some way
to make it up to you.
I will prove it to you no
matter how long it takes.
OK.
I think they're all wonderful.
Picking a top three, ah...
Which are your favorites?
Do you like this one?
Yeah.
I think you did a great
job with this guy.
Look at him.
He's got a pretty fancy hairdo.
Julia.
You said this art show
was open to everybody.
So I thought I'd come
and check it out.
I'm glad.
I'm glad you came.
Listen, I know I've been
kind of a pain lately.
And...
Yeah, well.
You're a teenager.
It's part of the job
description, right?
But until the other
night, I didn't even
Really get what you
were doing here.
Anyway, um.
I was thinking maybe
there's some kid
Who could use a friend.
I could.
Julia, this is Jacob.
Jacob, this is my
daughter, Julia.
Hi.
You're lucky that you
have such a cool mom.
Oh, you think?
So Are any of these
paintings yours?
A couple.
You want to see?
Sure.
Give me the whole tour.
I'm not very good yet.
But Annie, I mean Mrs.
Grayson, your mom,
Says that's not the point.
[DOG BARK]
Ready.
Go get it, Rusty.
[DOG BARKING]
I don't know who's going to
miss you more, me or Rusty.
Or me.
Don't worry.
I'll come back when I can.
I really don't
want you to leave.
Jacob, you'll be fine.
And whatever happens,
you'll find a good home.
I already found a good home.
It's right here.
How lucky is that?
I guess we're both lucky
we found this place.
I'll keep it forever.
I might even send you a new
painting if it's good enough.
What are you talking
about, if it's good enough.
If it's from you, of course
it'll be good enough.
Besides, I couldn't let you
leave without a proper goodbye.
Laura, are you sure about this?
Going home, I mean.
No.
But it's important
to me to try again.
Then It's important to me, too.
Oh, I'm going to miss you.
I'll miss you, too.
[WHISTLING]
SARA: Hey, Jacob!
Sara and Yvonne!
[LAUGHTER]
SARA: Look at you.
Hello.
Well, I guess we don't have
to ask how you're doing.
Everything's great.
Oh, fantastic.
You look wonderful.
Thanks to all
you've done for me.
This is such a nice
surprise, Jacob.
We heard you're in college now.
Premed.
Good for you.
What brings you back here?
Couldn't stay away forever.
Oh.
Came back to volunteer.
I thought there might be someone
who needed a special friend.
Well, you know there is always.
Come with us.
He's right over here.
We'll introduce you.
His name is Andrew.
And he's had such
a rough time of it.
You'd be the perfect person
to make a difference,
Won't he, Sara?
SARA: Absolutely.
The perfect person.
And what's life all about if
you can't make a difference?
JACOB: Hey, Andrew.
I'm Jacob.
[MUSIC PLAYING]