For Christ's sake.
Get your vehicle under control
before you kill someone.
Kelly, do you remember when
I allowed my townspeople
to vote you into office?
Kind of gave them a
feeling of solidarity.
You remember that?
Well, you need to
remember one thing.
You work for me, and
you're on probation,
so I would tread lightly.
Look, mayor, I'm just
doing what you hired
me to do... enforce the law.
My rules, Kelly.
My rules.
Now, why don't you scurry back
and go protect my property.
Yes, ma'am.
ON THE BRAIN
Subrip: Pix
Cheers for mayor.
Only weeks until the town's wired
for internet and cell phones.
Town's a-sproutin' back.
Hey mayor, how about
a round on the house?
You bet.
Here you go.
What are you doing?
Come on.
You know mayor,
I really love what
you've done with this place.
You know, I just give
the people what they want.
A nice slow-cooked beef
that falls off the bone.
When you concoct a good recipe,
you don't go changing it.
You just keep it as it is.
Hi Rev. Tell you, that
new whitewash on the church
looks fantastic.
Now all you have
left to do is put up
the sign, Mayor's Church,
right above the door.
Our honor, mayor.
Say, you think you could rustle
up some chairs and desks?
Reverend, I'm a busy woman.
It takes a lot to get this
town back on its feet.
I'm going to delegate
that task to you.
I think the more effort
you put into the church,
the better you're going
to feel about yourself.
You know, I'm contemplating
getting our youth involved
in a book-selling carnival.
Well, you know
what I always say.
Less thinking, more action.
Go get 'em, Rev.
Thank you, mayor.
Jeez Murray!
You need to watch that
greasy palm of yours.
It might get you into
trouble one of these days.
Thank you, Betty.
I am swamped.
Hey!
So what's the 411 on that
foxy sheriff of yours?
He's from Frisco, right?
And those massive boots.
You know what they say about
a man and his boot size?
Yeah, I don't
have to tell you.
You're screwing him.
Who else knows?
Nobody cares.
Too busy calculating
how to survive.
How did you...
It's in the way
you gaze at him.
You could spot it a moon away.
Yeah, I tossed him a pass.
He didn't want
nothing to do with me.
I guess he digs the dark meat.
Surprising?
Well what did you expect?
You bitch.
I am so jealous!
I haven't had it in...
well masturbation
doesn't count, right?
All the good men have
skedaddled out of town...!
Does he have any cute friends?
Betty?
Why don't you get back to work.
So, your boyfriend
hasn't quite learned
the ways of Golden Torch yet.
Why, did he give you
a parking ticket again?
Sweetheart, he's not going
to be around for a long time,
so I wouldn't too used to him.
You can go ahead and pay
that when you're ready.
Jeez Kelly.
At least cover your
mouth, my God.
In some countries,
it's customary to let
one go after a hearty meal.
Well, we are in
America darling.
It's rude.
OK.
You want to drink that?
In a minute.
I love you, you know that?
Yes.
I don't say it
often enough, but you
are the best thing that's
happened to me in a long time.
Me too, baby.
A whole bunch.
Man, I feel like
some ice cream.
My God, OK.
I'm dry, you polished off the
last two cartons last time.
That's because
they're so small now.
They went from two
liters to one and a half,
in the same container.
Nobody seemed to notice.
Well you did.
Of course I did.
I'm a cop.
Sometimes the
smallest of details
can solve the biggest of cases.
OK.
Damn baby, you didn't take
that medicine I prescribed you,
did you?
Just getting used to
the new environment.
I'll be OK.
Romance and cop work don't
mix too well together.
What now?
You know, you're the only woman
I would blaze the wilderness
for to round up some junk food.
You and me forever, right?
I'm going to go get
some more coffee.
All right.
You want to come with me?
I'm going to run to Eddie's.
Get some ice cream.
At this hour?
Howdy, sheriff.
Hey.
Smoking will stunt
your growth, young lady.
These look stunted
to you, sheriff?
Run home, before
I call your father.
Hey sheriff.
McCreedy's mangy mutt
attacked me again.
Luckily I nabbed
him, or the bitch
would have bit my ball sack off.
I got a good dose of mace right
in the mutt's kisser, though.
Hey Eddie, you got
any Ben and Jerry's?
Just what you see, sheriff.
Ain't the big city, you know.
One night with me, sheriff,
will clear that cough right up.
Sheriff?
Sheriff!
There's something
wrong with Murray!
My head, my...
Sheriff!
Are you OK, Murray?
You don't look so good, man.
What is it?
You want me to call a doctor?
Murray, you all right?
What the hell?
Get off of her!
Get off of...
Damn it, Murray.
Damn it Murray,
you stay right here.
It's OK.
It's over now.
Look!
Behind you!
Murray, stop!
Murray, God damn it!
No!
My God, Kelly.
God.
Are you OK?
Yeah.
Sit down.
Are Eddie and
Murray really dead?
Yeah.
It's OK, it's OK.
It's OK.
They're both dead.
Murray... I don't know.
They both started
attacking Courtney.
No provocation.
God, the look on their
faces, the distortion.
I've never seen
anything like it.
How's Courtney doing?
She's shaken up.
Her father rushed
her out of town.
Did he take her to a hospital?
I don't know.
It's OK.
Let me see.
You killed Eddie?
And the mailman?
Do you have any
clue how hard it is
for me to find somebody
who's dedicated enough
to go out six days a week, rain
or shine, and deliver the mail?
Any idea?
Mayor, wait till
you get all the facts
before you start saying stuff.
Please, shut up.
Nobody is talking to you.
Mayor!
Don't speak to her that way.
She wasn't even there.
And I didn't kill Eddie.
He killed himself.
He... he...
give me your gun.
Are you firing me?
Your goddamn piece.
Now.
Unbelievable.
Go ahead and give
me the bullets, too.
Just take it.
Until I figure out what
the hell happened out there,
you're a cop without a weapon.
Now I want a detailed
report on my desk yesterday.
If it matches
what's on the tape,
then you can have your gun back.
Don't point that at me.
I'm sorry.
Is this better?
Fuck you, mayor.
I can't.
I'm busy.
I'll take the key to this, too.
Someone's here.
You think?
Sheriff, I need your help.
Jesus.
Now what?
Ms. McCreedy, is
everything all right?
I don't know what to do.
I didn't want to come here.
Is Gus here?
Where's Gus?
He's not here.
What is it?
What's wrong?
He's...
Is it Zeke?
Yeah.
Did he hit you?
No.
I fell.
He never hurt me.
Zeke loved me.
He loves me.
Zeke.
He couldn't move.
He couldn't speak.
His last words were,
"Something's in my head".
Something's in my head.
Why are you covered in blood?
No!
Where's Gus?
Gus!
Damn, that was weird.
Yeah.
I'm going to go check on her.
OK.
Start!
Start, God damn it, start!
Zeke!
Why are you doing this, Zeke?
Get it out of your head!
Get it out!
Zeke, you don't want to hurt me.
Zeke!
Somebody help me!
You don't want to
hurt me, please!
Zeke, stop it!
Stop it!
Start, start!
Please start, please!
Please, stop it!
Zeke, look.
Look at the ring.
Zeke, Zeke, you love me.
Zeke, no!
Zeke, stop it, stop it!
Zeke, get it out of your head!
Zeke, stop!
Zeke!
Stop it!
Zeke, I don't want to hurt you.
Zeke!
No!
Stop, Zeke!
Stop!
Help me!
Zeke.
Zeke?
Zeke, what happened to you?
Are you OK, Zeke?
Where's Louise, Zeke?
I killed her.
You did what, Zeke?
She's dead.
Put your hands in the
air right now, Zeke.
You hear me?
My head.
I'm warning you,
right now Zeke.
There's something in my head.
Kill me.
I cant believe there's
nothing on Murray or Eddie.
Just me being investigated.
What the hell is
wrong with this town?
Sheriff?
God, Christ, pick up!
Hurry!
What is it, Gus?
What's wrong?
Get over
to bloody McCreedy's, fast.
They're dead.
They're all dead.
What?
Dead?
How?
I don't know.
Just hurry.
Gus, secure the scene.
Don't touch anything.
I'm on my way.
Gus.
What the hell happened?
I'm not going up there.
You can't make me.
Why, what's up there?
It's Louise.
She's dead.
Stay here.
I'll be right back.
Gus.
I'm sorry about your friends.
Why did do it, sheriff?
He drank too much, but he didn't
have a mean bone in his body.
Him and Louise was
high-school sweethearts.
What happened?
Exactly, Gus.
You know, I don't get it.
Before you barreled
into this town,
things was peaceful around here.
I don't get it.
You brought a curse around
this town or something.
Kelly,
Kelly, please pick up.
Pick up.
What is it?
What's wrong?
She's dead.
Lock yourself in the car.
I'm on my way.
Stay here.
Don't make me.
Guard the God
damned bodies, Gus.
You're a cop.
Do your job.
God damned sheriff.
Mary Alma, you're
OK, aren't you?
No.
It's OK.
I'm here.
You don't have to do this.
I gotta do this for Betty.
Shorts ripped off.
Possible rape.
Potential murder weapon.
Who the hell is there?
Betty, it's
Reverend Peter Lamper.
Hold your water, dude.
I will attend to
you in a second.
Enter if you dare, darling.
I pray
I'm not intruding.
You want a beer or something?
You know what
the good book says.
Whatever
We missed you in
church this morning.
Really?
Is it Sunday already?
I came to share a passage
from today's sermon, Betty.
The Word of God does wonders.
Our father, who art in
heaven, hallowed be Thy name.
Peter?
What's going on?
You're scare... Peter?
You're scaring me, Peter.
Peter?
My God!
At least she was able
to make it to the phone.
Kelly, I took that call.
I'm sorry.
Did you hear any voices?
Anything in the background?
No, it was dead silence.
What is that by the door?
Crap.
It's Peter's bible.
I gotta get outta here.
Why is this happening?
I don't know.
Why Betty?
She never hurt anybody
in her whole life.
Why is this happening?
What was that?
Stay behind me.
Tight.
My God.
What the hell is he doing?
and forgive
us our trespasses...
Peter!
On the ground, now.
and lead us not
into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
No Mary Alma, stay back.
No!
It's OK.
My God, Peter.
No.
Here you go.
Sit anywhere you like, honey.
That's a good spot.
Welcome to the Mayor's Grill.
We're here to fill you up.
What can I get you?
What's good here?
Everything's fantastic,
but I tell you what.
I'd recommend the
prime rib, rare.
Sounds appetizing.
Hey are you, working on
that new expansion down on 36?
Yes ma'am.
It should put your
town on the map.
Fantastic.
I'll tell you, that's what
I've been praying for.
Well, make sure you
tell all your coworkers
and your friends
about Mayor's Grill.
Best eats in 40 miles.
My lucky day, then.
All right.
Anyway, I'll take
whatever you got on tap.
You got it.
What are you doing
here so early?
Where have you been?
I am so sick of that
damn cold of yours.
Please drink that.
Since you're not taking
your meds it might help.
It's good.
Mayor cleaned
out all the guns.
What, and you didn't
try and stop her?
She scares me sometimes.
Now without a gun, without
any way to protect us.
Damn it Kelly, I'm doing
the best I can here.
No cell phone, no internet.
Jesus, I can't believe
this damn town sometimes.
There's Peter's medical file.
This is justice done by
suicide, but what's the motive?
I don't get it.
One step at a time Mary Alma.
I'm doing the best I can.
I'm swimming in a pool
of dead bodies here.
The least you can do is
throw me a life vest.
Jesus.
Kelly, I'm overwhelmed too.
I've never been around some
much senseless killing.
Everyone we know
is dead, or will
be if we don't do
something about it.
It's not my fault.
I never said it was.
Say ma'am?
It's,
it's actually mayor.
I own this beautiful 'burb.
It's been in my
family since 1889.
Excuse me, mayor.
Is that lady OK over there?
That's Nancy.
She's a little
touched in the head,
but all small towns
have one of those.
Come on, eat up.
Nothing makes any sense.
Peter had a physical
three months ago.
An EKG, blood work, urine
test... they were all normal.
He didn't smoke or drink, and
he wasn't on any prescription
medicine either.
By all accounts, Peter, he...
he was a normal healthy guy.
Betty never said
anything to you, right?
No nothing about Peter.
Betty's tox screen shows a
blood alcohol content of.12.
Betty's murdered.
Peter's identified
by fingerprints,
physical evidence,
and blood transfers.
This is justice done by
suicide, but what's the motive?
I don't get it.
It's just that...
It might be the mayor.
I'll get it.
Mary Alma?
Get over here, now.
What the hell happened, Mayor?
God damn it Mary Alma,
what is he doing here?
City folk is what happened here.
He went after Nancy
for no reason,
and I had to show
him how we take
care of people around here.
Get off her, you sick bastard.
Get away from her.
Nancy, come on.
Wait a second.
This is a crime scene.
We need to interview
both of you.
Get away!
They'll kill us all!
Jesus Christ mayor, what
the hell are you doing?
Don't fuck with
me today, Kelly.
I have no problem
putting you down
like I put that asshole down.
Now put the body in a blanket
and in the back of your truck,
now.
We're contaminating a crime
scene, yuou know that.
I said now.
Go, Nancy.
Shit no.
Can't be.
What, you know him?
It's Greg Creighton.
God, don't like it here.
Where the hell is Kelly Jarvis?
Well spit it out, deputy.
It's a simple question.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
You are?
Ann Creighton,
from San Francisco.
My husband Greg Creighton
has just been murdered.
I'm sorry for your loss, ma'am.
It's Ms. Creighton.
Don't call me ma'am.
Do I really look like
a dried up old hag?
Yeah... I
mean, no ma'am... I mean, Mrs...
Ms. Creighton.
Sheriff will be back
here lickity-split.
Ma'am, there's no
smoking on the, premises,
Ms. Creighton.
I'm sure you can
afford a grieving
widow a little nicotine, yes?
Now, be a gentleman.
Fix me a drink.
Sheriff frowns upon
alcohol, Ms. Creighton.
That his office?
Yes it is.
His desk, bottom-right
drawer, and make it a double.
Yes, Ms. Creighton.
Sneaky sheriff.
Should have known.
So deputy, can you
please enlighten me
as to why my husband is dead?
Maybe we should wait until
the sheriff gets back here.
I don't have all the facts yet.
Kelly?
Yeah.
My God, Kell.
This can't be happening.
Why, Kelly?
Why?
Let's discuss this in my office.
Was Greg ever
violent towards you?
Wait.
Not, how have you been?
What have you been up to?
I'm sorry about
your dead husband.
I don't have time to
spar with you, Ann.
I've got a lot on my plate.
You have no idea.
Here, sign this.
What's this?
It's a consent form to do
an autopsy on Greg's body.
You want to carve out
what's left of my husband?
Jesus.
That's a ghastly request,
even coming from you.
It's important, Ann.
I need you to sign this.
So that's how you want to play?
You've lost your touch, Kelly.
You're not so much fun anymore.
You never answered my question.
The answer is no.
Greg was never violent, nor
did he act like that around me.
Even when he caught us fucking,
he wept like an infant.
It's disgusting.
Go back to San Francisco, Ann.
Today.
I always knew you still
held a torch for me, baby.
Doesn't work anymore, Ann.
Hello.
What?
Who the hell's that?
Greg Creighton's wife.
Well I see she's left
you with a calling card.
The ma... the mayor's here.
I need to have a little chat
with the Sheriff, Mary Alma.
And where's the
goddamn autopsy report?
We just got approval
from the victim's wife.
Then get to it.
What the hell did
you bring to my town?
How many dead people
are there, sheriff?
Enlighten me, because
I've lost track.
Where are all the guns?
I can't do my job
without a weapon.
You know, your report said
this Crichton, Creighton fellow,
that he's a buddy of yours?
Not a buddy, an acquaintance.
I'm watching you
very, very closely.
You need to be mindful of that.
I have your number.
Yes ma'am.
Hey.
I want to see the autopsy.
Kelly, what are you doing here?
I wanted to see Greg's
autopsy...
Come on.
I'm going to get you
something for that.
Come on.
I'm so sick of that damn cold.
Sit down.
Here.
I'll see you tonight, OK?
Can you stop doing that?
It's driving me crazy.
Helps me think.
You all right?
What's wrong?
It's my stomach.
I'm under so much
stress right now.
I have my period to top it off.
It's so excruciating.
Why didn't you let me in
Greg Creighton's autopsy?
Because an autopsy's
a very personal thing.
I think halting
the killing around
here is a little more important
than a dead man's feelings.
So this Ann Creighton
person... you were close?
Where'd that come from?
We have history.
Exactly what's that
supposed to mean?
It was a lifetime ago.
Forget about it.
You sleep with her?
What's with the fifth degree?
Just tell me about the autopsy.
How come you're not giving
me any straight answers?
Jesus.
You had an affair with her
while she was still married.
It's not what you think.
You still have feelings for her?
It's not like that.
I can't explain it.
Then let's just
leave this town.
Go somewhere. I don't care
where we go, anywhere.
How?
Where?
What?
You're upside-down
in your house.
I have a small
stash saved, and I'm
sure you have a rainy day fund.
You've lived here
your whole life.
Exactly Kelly, I'm
willing to leave it all.
You have no ties.
You've only been
here for two months.
You don't owe this
miserable place anything.
Mary Alma, we're professionals.
It's our job to
save people's lives.
Then we suck at out
jobs then, right?
I'll be right back.
I'm not going to say anything.
Damn it Kelly, I
told you to stop
slamming the door like that.
Gus?
Gus, what's wrong?
Gus, my God.
Kelly, Gus needs help!
Come here!
My God, Gus.
Stay back!
Gus, stay back.
Don't touch me Gus.
Stop, don't touch me!
Gus, stop!
No, leave me alone Gus!
Stop!
Get away from me!
Go away!
Stop it Gus!
My God!
Gus, get off her!
God damn it, Gus.
Not you too!
Kelly!
It's OK.
I'll tell you what Mary Alma,
I do not trust the sheriff.
I think he's hiding something.
Mayor, I'm going to need a
full blood and fecal sample
from your cows please,
as soon as possible,
and a full inspection
of the Grill.
Mary Alma.
You're not the FDA.
Besides, my cows are fine.
They're healthy, they
are not the problem here.
Now I'll tell you what though.
Listen.
Listen, listen.
Kelly.
That's who you need
to be investigating.
I have, Mayor.
I'm testing everyone,
including you.
You're not exempt from this.
I do love the feel and sound of
a cocking revolver in my hand.
It gives one such
feeling of power.
Now you need to
listen to me, bitch.
I know that you're
fucking the sheriff.
But you will aim your
investigation his way.
I got it, Mayor.
Good.
Because you know
I mean business.
Who else is here?
I don't know.
Besides the piles of dead
bodies, I don't know.
I hope you remember
what I said, Mary Alma.
Excuse me, ma'am.
How rude.
Doctor, I presume?
Please, sit down.
I'm very sorry for your
loss Miss Creighton... Ann...
but there is no smoking
in the building.
It's making a comeback, doc.
Get used to it.
Besides, without disease
you'd be unemployed, yes?
I hope my husband's body wasn't
too much trouble for you.
Did you find anything odd, apart
from his teensy-weensy dick?
I'm still putting the
pieces together, Ann.
If that's doctor humor, I don't
find it particularly funny.
Sorry.
It's been a long day.
Well, you'll have to give me a tour
of this lovely little town of yours.
It's not a good time, Ann.
You might be next.
This is really dangerous.
What did you say to me?
Was your husband around any
strange type of chemicals
or meat, foods, consume any meat
besides Mayor's Grill recently?
Well, he measured things.
Calculated junk.
That's all I know.
But yes, most people
do consume meat.
Except for those pansy vegans.
I'm going to need some blood
samples and fecal samples
from you, as soon as possible.
Here you are.
Well, if it's going
to move things along
to get this goddamn will sorted,
I'll give you your samples.
Why am I still here?
Come on Mary Alma, think.
Come on Mary Alma.
There has to be a connection.
Think.
Wait a second.
You know Mayor,
I really love what
you've done with this place.
You know, I just give
the people what they want.
A nice, well-cooked beef
that just falls off the bone.
Bone.
Betty Hays was
menstruating like I was.
Only the women are
being attacked.
The people are only
attacking after the eat
at the Mayor's Grill.
There has to be a
connection between the meat
and the women's menstruation.
That's it.
My God, that's it.
Kelly.
Kelly, pick up.
Shit.
You're safe, Gus.
Easy, Gus.
Easy.
We're not
going to hurt you.
Just tell me what happened.
My head... there's
others... it's crawling.
It's crawling away.
Why did you break in
and attack Mary Alma?
It's crawling.
Something... something was...
What did you smell, Gus?
What was it?
Get away from me.
You're safe now.
You're safe now, Gus.
Kelly?
What's wrong?
No.
Not you too.
Mary Alma!
Get me out of these cuffs!
Mary Alma, I'm not playing.
Kelly,
you became possessed
like the rest of them.
We should have left
when we had the chance.
Shit, Kelly!
Kelly, breathe.
Now you should breathe.
Breathe.
OK.
What's wrong with me?
Am I possessed?
OK, I need you to... Kelly!
It's like a, a scent.
It's like a scent.
A scent, OK.
Stomach felt really weird.
I felt... fear.
Desire.
It was primitive.
Almost animalistic.
OK, so now we have
a common denominator.
A scent.
What the hell are
you doing here?
Well... How did you get in here?
I have access to
everything in my town.
What in the hell
is on your face?
More importantly,
what are you going
to do to get my
town back on track?
Right now I've got nothing.
Nothing?
Kelly, I have rapes and
murders and suicides going on
out there, and you have
the fucking audacity
to say "nothing" to me?
What I mean is, I don't have
a criminal to lock up just yet.
I know.
How 'bout you?
What are you
talking about, Mayor?
I know a lot more
than you think I do.
You're not going to
slither out of this one
and go off and
collect unemployment.
Some of the women are
probably leaving a scent.
A scent?
A scent.
OK.
That's your lead then?
OK, yeah.
That's the best that a big city
cop like you can come up with?
That there's some scent out
there, and the men in my town
are going to wear this
stupid thing on their face,
and that's going to
stop the carnage.
Some of the men have parasites.
Mary Alma's doing a workup
on the women at the clinic.
Mary Alma.
OK, OK.
Have you noticed that
there's no townspeople?
I've looked everywhere.
I can't find anybody.
You know what I've noticed?
That this all started
happening when you happened
upon our peaceful little burg.
This is your mess.
Clean it up.
I'm not
done with you yet.
Kelly.
You should never touch
a woman in anger.
You know better than that.
Yes ma'am.
Wait, wait!
Wait.
Let me put on my mask.
Just keep some
space between us.
I don't trust you right now.
Sorry I had to cuff you.
Look, we need to talk.
Keep back, Kelly.
Did you find what
you're looking for?
Looks like I picked an
inopportune time to show up.
Did you find anything odd
about my samples, doc?
What the hell are you
doing back in town, Ann?
You left a message on my
phone saying that you needed
some information about Greg.
Yeah, on the phone.
Not in person.
You have no idea
what the hell you're
in the middle of here, Ann.
A threesome.
I like how your mind works.
If you knew what
was good for you,
you'd get your sexual
tail out of town.
Well maybe I'm not like you.
I enjoy a bit of danger.
You're a fool.
You need to come with me,
unless you'd prefer to be dead.
If you know what's good for
you, you will come with me.
I need to discuss some
things with the sheriff
if you don't mind.
I can't believe you too.
Born from the same bowel.
Mary Alma, wait.
Well she's the life
of the party?
What is this ridiculous
thing on your face?
Jesus Christ Ann,
what are you...
doing?
You want me out of harm's way?
Your place is the safest, right?
Just go with Mary Alma, please.
I'm not going anywhere.
My dead husband... God rest
his soul... has life insurance.
We can go anywhere.
You and me, like we
dreamed of years ago.
Ann, I just can't leave.
Not with everything that's
happening in the town.
You're so much more
than your job, Kell.
And this shit hole of a town.
We can do so much
better than this.
You're so far away, baby.
Come here.
I'm lonely.
Ann, I... I could kill you.
Take the mask off.
It doesn't look like
it does anything.
Besides, it looks stupid.
You've nuts, you know that?
I could kill you.
Well, let's play it
like an experiment.
Stop it, Ann.
Ann.
What the hell?
Let me go.
Now I've got you
right where I want you.
Damn it, Ann.
Ann, let me go.
Come on, that used
to drive you nuts.
Ann, I can't do this.
I'm gonna devour
you whole right now.
No...
Deep breaths.
Breath deep.
Nothing, right?
You feel OK?
I smell something.
What?
Perfume.
You bought this
for me, remember?
Yeah, I do.
Ann, don't.
Something's definitely
coming to life.
No.
Someone's coming, Ann.
Someone's here.
Ann, uncuff me.
Kelly, I found... what
the hell is going on here?
You're supposed to be
locking the men up!
Mary Alma, nothing happened.
I swear to God.
Keep that on.
I should hit you.
That stupid piece of paper
is always glued to your hand.
Is that some sort of fetish?
Shut your mouth, Ann.
Don't you dare look
at me like that.
Are you gonna
uncuff him or is he
going to sit there
the whole night?
Get fucked, Mary Alma.
Are you going to let
her talk to me like that?
Ann, shut it.
Mary Alma... wait.
I can't find any
of the townspeople.
Dead or alive.
Where are the bodies?
Get back, and don't touch me.
I thought I knew you.
How could you do this to me?
Look, I'm sorry,
but nothing happened.
I just haven't
been myself lately.
Are you on your period?
Excuse me?
Are you menstruating?
You know something.
What is it?
Tell me.
Tell me, Mary Alma.
Mary Alma?
Get over to the Grill.
I've got some...
Mayor, is that you?
Mayor, can you hear me?
Don't just stand there, asshole!
Get your shit together!
Mary Alma, wait.
What about me?
What should I do?
Kelly, get back here.
Kelly, don't leave
me, not again.
I hate this flea-bitten town.
Good God, Gus.
What have they done to you?
Damn it, now I gotta
get a new deputy.
Time to be proactive.
Hello?
Mayor?
How did you get out?
Stay right there, Gus.
Don't make me hit you.
Please.
Help me.
Mary Alma?
Mary Alma, you in here?
Where am I?
Exactly where you should be.
In custody.
I don't understand what
you're babbling about.
You're a scoundrel in the first
degree, Kelly, and you know it.
But you can redeem your soul
by signing this confession.
I'm not signing any of your
illegal documents, Jesus Mayor,
admit what you've done.
You're the cause
of all this carnage
I've been trying to stop.
I'm the one that's been trying
to put this town on the map,
and you ruined it in
less than two months.
You killed all
those people, Kelly,
and the forensics proves it.
You have
got to be kidding me.
Finally, thank you.
My damn cell phone has
no service out here.
It had to be you, didn't it?
What are you still doing, Ann?
Two words... no gas stations.
Get in.
Hell no.
Are you crazy?
I'm not leaving
my car out there.
Those rims?
They set me back more than
you make in a year, honey.
You don't get it, do you?
People have been
raped and killed.
You may be next.
Your husband and my best
friend... what are you doing?
You need to get in the
car, or else I'm leaving.
OK, but that lady-man
friend of yours
needs to invest in some
fucking gas stations.
You need to stop.
We should probably
go around back.
Where are you going?
I'm coming with you.
You know what?
Maybe it is better that you are.
You know, karma, or
something like it.
Kelly?
Kelly, are you in here?
Breaking and
entering, Mary Alma?
Didn't think
you had it in you.
These keys belong to my
friend who used to work here,
and she's dead.
Watch what you say.
Keep your eyes peeled for Mayor.
That big honky-tonk lady-man?
I don't like her much either.
Stinks in here.
Yeah Ann.
Death's been here.
Maybe I should go wait
in the car after all.
Park your ass right there
and don't touch anything.
Where's Kelly when I need him?
You have a thing for him?
That is none of
your business, Ann.
Besides, you are the last person
I would talk to about him.
You're in love with him.
I knew it.
I could tell in the bedroom.
There's a fine line between
hate and love, my dear.
Trust me, I know.
This is a crime
scene you idiot.
Put that damn thing out.
Well you're just a burst of
energy today then, aren't you?
Do you hear that?
No.
Hurry up.
Just rip it off.
Give me that.
Kelly?
Kelly, are you there?
Please pick up.
Kelly, please, I need you.
Good
evening Mary Alma.
Things aren't really
going your way, are they?
Well, it's gonna
get worse for ya.
Mayor, where's Kelly?
He's in custody.
So listen, I want you to
grab all your evidence...
and I mean all of it...
and bring it on down
to the sheriff's station.
Then we'll talk about
Kelly's release.
Or, his termination.
Mayor, it doesn't
have to be like this.
Mayor, please listen to me.
It doesn't have to be this way.
Mayor, can you hear me?
God damn it, Mayor!
It doesn't have to be this way.
Stop!
Mayor, can you hear me?
I'm on my way.
Let go of her.
Get up, get up.
OK, Ann!
Pay attention.
Have you been bit?
I don't know.
Come on, come on.
Come on, hurry.
Get in.
Go, get in.
Hasn't there been
enough death already?
Listen.
My great-granddaddy
established this town
on a lot of blood,
sweat, and tears,
and I'll be damned if I'm
going to let the economy
or you destroy it,
you son of a bitch.
What did you do to your cows?
Nothing illegal.
Mayor, people are dead.
Look, I souped up the
animals a little bit
to get a more delicious meat,
but it's done all the time.
It's even in vegetables
and other foods now.
Everything I bought... the
drugs, the ingredients...
it's all legal.
Well obviously,
something went very wrong.
Put down the gun.
Let's figure this out.
There's been enough killing.
Will you help me, Kelly?
Tell the authorities that
I didn't do anything wrong?
Be a witness for me?
I swear to God, I didn't know
what was causing all this.
That's why I was having you
guys work so hard on it.
Look, we can fix this together.
Some sheriff you are.
You just got done by
an old woman, pussy.
Just get me out
of here, Mary Alma.
I want to go home.
Did you fucking
see that crazy guy?
Did you fucking see his eyes?
I've never seen
anything like it.
Ann, I don't need
your shit right now.
I have nothing to do with this.
I'm not even fucking from this
stupid fucking creepy town.
Ann, I'm still trying
to figure things out, OK?
I need you to calm down.
Where is everybody, Mary Alma?
Where all the people?
There's no one around.
I want to go home, Mary Alma.
I want to go home.
I'm pulling over now.
Get me out of here.
Get me out of this fucking town.
Get me out of...
Stop!
Get me out of here.
I want to go home.
Look at me.
You're going... you're
going to need to calm down.
I can't do this without you.
I'm coming with you.
You're not coming with me.
You're staying here.
Don't leave me here, Mary Alma.
I'm coming fucking with you.
Ann, you need to stay here.
Are you kidding me?
Anything could be
hiding in those bushes.
Stop, Ann.
Shut up.
Stay behind me.
Kelly, are you in here?
Go back, Mary Alma.
It's a trap.
Mary Alma, get out of here.
Mayor, let them go.
They have nothing
to do with this.
For the record Mayor,
I'm not a part of this.
I'm a hostage.
What is this bitch doing here?
I am not a bitch.
God Mary Alma, you just have
to complicate everything,
don't you?
I've got all the evidence here.
Open it.
I said, open it.
First, let Kelly go.
Something doesn't seem right.
If you're deceiving
me, I will kill you.
Now get over here I
said get over here!
Is this what's
happening to all the men?
Where's the mask?
He's gonna die.
Because he deserves it.
He brought this to my town.
Mayor, you are the
cause of all of this.
Don't you see?
He's sick.
People are dying
because of your meat.
Your cows, they are infected.
Everybody is dying
from the meat.
Don't you see that?
Goddammit.
Just give me the mask.
Here, just take this.
Give me the mask.
Give it to me.
You think you're in
control, Mary Alma.
But you're not.
I'm in control.
What the hell did I do?
I'm not even from
this fucking town.
I'm fucking getting out of...
No!
Get right back over here.
Do you want the mask?
You think the mask is gonna
save your little boyfriend?
Here.
Take it.
He did this.
I'm not going to lose
my town, Mary Alma.
It's all over.
I don't know how it came
to this, but it did.
There's only one way out.
I'm not gonna lose my town.
This is everything to me.
Do you understand me?
Everything!
And then you come
in, and he comes in.
And I'm gonna lose it all!
But that's not gonna happen.
I'm gonna make sure
it doesn't happen.
Kelly?
Kelly.
Come on, have some
dignity you piece of shit.
Damn it.
Die, you piece of shit.
God.
Stay here.
Stay there.
Kelly?
Relax.
OK, OK.
Breathe.
It's OK.
Ann, I need your help.
Ann... what are you doing?
Put that gun down.
Put the gun down, Ann.
He's gone.
Look at him.
Look, he's healing.
He's got the mask
on and everything.
He's gonna be fine.
I'm going to need you to put
that gun down so we can get out
of here, OK?
Even if we try and save him,
I don't want him near me.
Put the gun down.
I need you to help me
get him out of here
so we can leave, OK?
Put the gun down.
I'm begging you,
put the gun down.
Kelly, just stay there.
Come and help me.
Come on Kelly.
Come on.
Come on baby, get up.
Come on honey.
It's OK, come on.
Come on.
You're going to be OK, honey.
Just hang in there.
We're gonna be just fine.
Thank God that fucking
crazy bitch is dead.
Ann, shut up.
We're going to get
you to the clinic, OK?
Just hang in there.
Just see if he's shot.
Just check to see if he's shot.
It's empty, Mary Alma.
The fluid's empty.
He's turning again.
We're going to the clinic, OK?
We've gotta get
him out of here.
We've gotta fucking
pull over, Mary Alma.
I can't stop it!
We've gotta just fucking
get out of this town, OK?
We've got to just
fucking get out of...
I'm trying!
We've gotta get
him out of here!
Pull over!
He's turning again, Mary Alma!
He's fucking turning again!
Stop!
Pull over!
Stop the fucking car.
No Kelly, what are you doing?
Give it to me.
My God, he's
got the fucking gun!
Kelly, stop it now.
Kelly, drop the gun.
Drop it.
Mary Alma, do something!
Stay with me, Kelly.
No, what are you...
My God!
My God, Kelly.
My God.
Kelly?
Kelly wake up!
Don't!
Kelly, no.
Kelly, please.
Come on baby, wake up.
Wake up.
Come on Kelly, wake up.
Please, Kelly.
Come and help me!
Ann!
My God, baby!
My God.
Ann, come and help me Ann.
Come and help me.
Kelly, wake up baby.
Wake up.
Come on, wake up.
Ann, what are you doing?
Ann, come and help me!
I'm sorry Mary Alma, but
I can't do it any more.
I'm so sorry.
Come on Kelly, come on.
Baby, come on.
I'm sorry Mary Alma, but
you brought this on yourself.
Ann, what are you doing?
Ann, no!
Come back and help me!