* I learned the truth
at seventeen *
* That love was meant *
Turn it off!
What are you,
the fucking music czar?
Okay, language, Ellen!
Please, this song can not be
playing when we drive up.
What is wrong with it?
Ellen, I'm begging you.
It's like announcing
you're a loser.
Oh, great. Then you'll fit
right in with the other weirdos.
I don't get what you're doing
at this creative arts camp
anyway.
Aren't you supposed to have
some sort of talent?
I thought she was a hoot
in "Bye, Bye, Birdie."
She played the mayor's wife.
She had no lines.
All she had to do was faint
and spread her legs.
I thought
she was very inventive.
Please! The only reason
Miss Liebman recommended her
for this stupid scholarship
is 'cause she felt sorry
for her that Daddy died.
Hey! Fuck you, Ellen!
At least I'm not working
at Carvel,
hanging out at the mall,
and stealing lip gloss.
Enough, both of you!
Put that down!
Turn it off, Ellen.
Enough!
Your sister is trying
something new.
Besides, after the year
we've had,
someone in this family
should have a little fun.
Welcome, campers.
If you haven't checked in yet.
Please report
to the dining room.
- Hey!
- Wow!
What a freak show.
You can still sign up
for tonight's talent show.
Sign-ups are
in the dance studio,
and each performer
is limited to 10 minutes.
Ooh, check out Paddington Bear
at 10:00.
There's your hot summer romance.
- Shut up.
- Ellen!
Help your sister schlep the
duffel bag up to her wigwam.
Teepee,
and I don't need any help.
Maybe you can ask that strong
boy over there to help you.
Oh, yeah, Julie, why don't you
go over and ask that strong boy?
Hi. Need a hand?
- No, thanks. I can do it.
- Cool.
- Ethan!
- My name's Ethan Figman.
If you need anything,
I'm at your service.
Listen, Mom, it's five hours
to Underhill,
and you'll have to stop
for lunch.
She wants us to go, Mom.
Okay.
- Have fun.
- Thanks.
- I love you.
- I love you too, Mom.
First time away from home.
You'll adjust.
It just takes time.
- Mom?
- I got this.
Mom!
* Don't you feel it growin' *
* Day by day *
* People gettin' ready
for the news *
* Some are happy *
* Some are sad *
* Oh, we got to let
the music play *
You think Goodman Wolf
would let me sculpt him?
I mean, naked?
This guy on the swim team
said his dick is so big
they nicknamed it Excalibur.
You know,
like Sword and the Stone?
Thank you, Sandy, now
I will never be able
to listen to Camelot
without imagining King Arthur
pulling his penis out of a rock.
It's not like they think
they're better than everyone.
They just sort of are,
you know?
You make them sound like
they're royalty or something.
Well, they are, sort of.
Everybody comes here
with big dreams,
thinking they've got
some great talent,
until Ash Wolf
blows them away onstage,
or they hear one
of Jonah Dey's songs,
which are twice as good
as his mother's.
- Corinna Dey is his mother?
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
He's gonna be twice as huge.
And Cathy Kiplinger?
She's been dancing
since she was three.
Deep down,
everyone knows those guys
are the only ones
that are really gonna do it.
and not just as a hobby
or for a summer, but for life.
Hmm, what smells so nice?
Um, it's Gee Your Hair
Smells Terrific.
Too bad it looks like
a Brillo pad.
- Oh, come on.
- It's perfect
for removing rust,
stripping paint,
scouring pots.
- You're funny.
- It's the hair.
I get it from a clown.
- I'm Ash Wolf.
- Oh, I know.
I mean, I'm Julie Jacobson.
- I know.
- You do?
We're in the same improv class.
You were hysterical
in that elevator exercise.
When you fainted,
and your legs spread wide open.
- I nearly peed myself laughing.
- Thanks.
It just came to me.
Listen, if you're not
doing anything later,
a few of us are getting
together, and maybe you'd
like to join us.
Um... Yeah.
- Sure. Cool.
- Great.
After lights out,
my brother's tent,
Teepee 3.
It's the one
that reeks of weed.
See you there.
I'm not even that stoned yet.
- Goodman, leave it alone.
- "The Tin Drum"
is a literary masterpiece.
"House of Incest"
is female porn!
It's feminist surrealism!
Where did you hear that?
From your fancy English teacher
with the Harvard PhD?
Günter Grass is basically God.
I think Anaïs Nin is God.
- Anaïs Nin?
- Yes.
She's so full
of pretentious girly shit.
She's literally one of
the worst writers to ever live.
Anaïs Nin and Günter Grass
both have umlauts.
Maybe that's the key
to their success.
I'm thinking of getting
one for myself.
Increase the velocity,
the natives are restless.
Voila.
Cannabis Perfectus.
What are you doing reading
Anaïs Nin anyway, Goodman?
- Um, Ash made me.
- Mm-hmm.
And I do everything
that my sister tells me.
Maybe Ash is God.
Ash-- Ash is definitely not God.
All right, she's way too much
of a perfectionist.
She'd never let a mistake
like Dick Nixon go unchecked.
I wish.
The thing is, he's just such
a bad actor. He's so obvious.
Why don't people see
when they're being lied to?
Because they don't wanna see.
- Just look at My Lai.
- You sound like your mother.
- Fuck you, Goodman.
- Yeah.
At least Corinna uses her music
to tell the truth to the world.
That's what art is for.
Right?
That's what "Spirit
in the Woods" is all about,
using your talent to tell
the truth to the world.
Gosh, Ash, maybe you are God.
- No, don't!
- Maybe you are God, Ash.
- Ooh!
- You're not ticklish anymore?
- Stop!
- I don't know.
I just dance because I love it.
I've never really wanted
to do anything else...
except I'm probably fucked
because of these sacks of mail.
I doubt your bodacious ta-tas
are gonna stand in your way.
It's not funny, Goodman.
How many ballerinas
do you know with big tits?
- Hey, calm down.
- What am I supposed to do?
Quit?
No, nothing should stand
in our way.
We should try to do
whatever we want to in life.
What is the point otherwise?
All right.
So, Jonah, have you given
any thought to a future career?
There's a girl in our cousin's
school in Pennsylvania
- named Crema Semens.
- No.
- You made that up.
- No, she didn't.
Ash never lies.
It's one of the most
irritating things about her.
- Crema Semens?
- Yes.
It's like...
it's, like, a soup
made from various strains
of semen.
- A medley of semen.
- Ew, Ethan, you're being
totally graphic.
Well, he is a graphic artist.
Hey, show her
some Planet Figman.
This is Wally Figman
and his horrible parents
before his mother runs off
with his pediatrician.
Any similarities between Wally's
life and my own
are purely intentional.
- The world according
to Ethan Figman.
- Can I see?
- **
- Which one's that?
I haven't seen that one.
I think we should all observe
a moment of silence
for Crema Semens.
Well, the girl
from Long Island speaks.
- Hey!
- You're being elitist.
Jacobson knows that I'm kidding.
Right, Long Island?
Oh, Crema Semens!
Wherever thou art!
Your life will be tragic.
It will be cut short
in an accident involving
animal de-semenizing equipment.
See? I told you there was
a reason I brought her in.
- Desemenizing! Go, Jules!
- Go, Jules!
- Here you go, Jules.
- You have definitely
earned another toke.
Every year we sit here
just like this.
Maybe we should name
ourselves something.
Why?
So everyone will know how
just how unbelievably
interesting we are?
The Interestings.
That works!
From this day forward,
because we are clearly
the most interesting people
- whoever fucking lived.
- Fuck, yes.
Because our lives
are so compelling.
Because our brains are
so swollen
with intellectual thoughts.
Let us henceforth be known
as the Interestings!
Let everyone who sees us
be blinded
by our brilliant
and scintillating lives.
- Come on.
- Oh, thank you.
- Toast to the Interestings!
- To our scintillating lives!
Whoo!
You sure you don't wanna come?
I can still get the sitter.
It'll be good
to get out, you know?
Get some air, see people.
I see people everyday
in the park with Rorie.
I'm on a first-name basis
with every nanny
and alcoholic mom
on the Upper West Side.
Everyone's gonna be
asking for you.
Jules, I've got
the interview tomorrow.
- I just want to veg.
- Veging's good.
Wish I could veg.
Probably gonna be
a snooze fest anyway.
You know how Ethan goes on
at these things.
You look nice.
Can you see it's ripped
in the shoulder?
- No, not at all.
- Thank God for safety pins.
Say hi to the gang
for me.
Tell them we'll
have dinner soon.
I'll cook.
Hey, listen. Be good and do
everything your daddy says.
Okay? I'll be home
when you wake up.
You forgot to kiss Daddy.
Pucker up, Daddy.
I love you.
Don't obsess, hmm?
I love you, too.
* Take a straight
and stronger course *
* To the corner
of your life *
* Make the white queen
run so fast *
I mean, Ethan is
a great guy, I know.
He is incredibly smart.
- And totally honest.
- So is Winnie the Pooh,
- but I wouldn't fuck him.
- You're horrible.
- I'm serious.
- Sorry.
Look, it's nothing personal.
It's just the truth.
People are attracted to their
own levels of attractiveness.
Like me and your brother,
and you and Jonah.
I mean, Ethan will probably
end up with someone
incredibly brilliant
and badly disfigured.
Cathy!
She's horrible.
Seriously, you wouldn't go out
with him if he asked you?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
- Would you?
- Ash and Ethan?
I mean that's
like Beauty and the Beast.
I don't know.
I can't imagine myself
with anyone other than Jonah.
- Yeah. Okay.
- We're just so right
for each other, you know?
Jesus, Jonah, get a room.
Guess who finally agreed
to move in with me?
- Who?
- Me. It's me.
Really? Oh, my God!
- It's about time.
- Some things can't be rushed.
I admire your perseverance.
If he had let you go,
we were all ready to have
an intervention again.
You've got
such fabulous friends.
God bless that faggot camp
you went to.
Congratulations to the winners
of our silent auction,
especially the new owner of--
...the Wally Figman
punching bag!
Certain to save you
thousands in therapy bills.
But if you leave here with
nothing but our gratitude,
just know that
what you're doing tonight
is making a real difference.
If you don't believe me,
ask the true conscience
of the Figman Foundation,
my beautiful wife, Ash Wolf.
Ash has seen firsthand what
Doctors Without Borders--
I can't believe
you guys were a thing.
It was never that sexual.
- We were more like--
- Sisters?
I was gonna say lesbians.
Lastly, I'd love to thank
the gang at Figland for
their generous support.
Pardon, good sirs,
the Queen of Figlandia beckons.
I shall return anon.
So, yeah, make sure
to eat the food.
I can personally recommend
the tiramisu.
Wow. This one's new.
"If only I were President
of Figland.
With respect, Bill."
Oh, I can't believe
I missed that weekend
because Rorie had
that 104 fever.
I should have just sold her
to gypsies and come anyway.
I have to go to Iceland.
Goodman's in trouble.
- What's going on?
- He's fucked up, Jules.
He's got no money.
For all I know,
he's living on the streets.
- He sounded confused.
- I think he's using again.
- Your parents gonna go?
- They can't.
The doctor says
my mom can't travel,
and my dad doesn't want
to leave her, so...
He's still making a mess
of his life and ours.
- I'm so sorry, Ash.
- She's desperate to see him.
It's so sad.
I told Ethan I had
to go to Bali
to research these masks for
a production of "Midsummer."
You told him you're going
to Indonesia
to get masks for
a play set in Greece
that you're doing
in Lower Manhattan?
I know. I told him
it was part of my concept.
I feel badly than I'm missing
this Museum of Broadcasting
thing they're doing
in his honor,
and I told him I'd see
if you could go in my place.
I hate this.
I really do.
- I--
- I do.
Just fucking tell him already.
I can't do that.
You know I can't.
He'd be devastated.
You should have told him
before you got married,
or I should have.
We couldn't take the chance.
You know how he is.
He's never really believed
Goodman was innocent.
It's fine.
I'll go.
What's one more lie
amongst friends, right?
- Was I that boring?
- No!
No, if I had any money
to spare,
I would have stayed
until the hat was passed,
but alas, I hate passing up
a passed hat.
I forgive you.
You get a pass for passing up
the passed hat
as long as it's in the past.
I really hate it
when you guys do this.
I know.
That's what makes it
so much fun.
I wish she'd let me
auction her off.
What? there are so many things
wrong with that sentence.
Strictly look but don't touch.
Just dinner and drinks
with the most beautiful woman
in Manhattan.
We'd make a killing.
We'd never have to throw one
of these awful things again.
What do you say?
Take one for the team.
Where's Dennis?
I thought he was coming.
Oh, Rorie has a cold,
but he sends his love.
Guess what?
Jules can go to the Museum
of Broadcasting with you.
Really? That's fantastic.
Oh, it will be just like
old times.
Just the two of us.
Yeah, and afterwards,
we can go to that restaurant
- that Robert De Niro
keeps talking about.
- No fair!
That's what you get for having
the gall to choose your career
over mine.
I mean, who goes to Indonesia
to get masks for a Greek play
she's doing in the Village?
It's a concept, right?
Well, we better get
back out there
while there are still pockets
to be picked.
Ah, yes.
These things are gonna kill me.
But that's what I get
for marrying a saint.
What would I do
without you?
The law is very clear.
Anyone who hinders or delays
The discovery of
Goodman Wolf's whereabouts
is guilty of harboring
a fugitive.
Detective, if we knew
where my son was,
we would insist
he turn himself in.
Good. 'Cause it doesn't get
any better for him.
Fugitive warrants
don't expire ever.
Until he comes back
to stand trial,
he will be considered
a wanted criminal.
Listen, did it ever occur
to you that we are missing
our son?
We've lost our son.
We don't know if he's alive.
Please try to find
a little compassion.
I'm sorry, Mr. Wolf.
I can see you're a close family,
which is probably why I think
you will hear from Goodman soon,
if you haven't already.
But just bear in mind
that when you do,
you are legally required
to contact us.
And if you don't,
you will go to jail.
God, they're like
the Gestapo.
Instead of barging into
your home and intimidating you,
they should be out there
trying to find Goodman.
We can handle this, Jules.
Thanks.
No, we can't.
- Ash.
- I can't.
You have Mom to talk to,
but who do I have?
- This is a family matter.
- Jules is family.
We can trust her.
- Ash, please.
- We've been in touch with
Goodman and we know where he is.
Jesus Christ, Ash!
I hope your happy!
'Cause now our lives are in
the hands of a 16-year-old!
No, I'll be careful,
Mr. Wolf, I promise.
You didn't tell Ethan?
No, I couldn't. I mean,
you know how he is.
He'd probably think he had
to report it or something.
No, you're the only one.
And nothing leaves
this room
until we can prove
Goodman's innocence.
- So what do you think?
- It's fantastic.
- Not too much?
- I'd hire you.
Or at least sleep with you.
You don't think
I'm too overdressed?
Maybe I should just wear jeans.
No!
I think you look really nice,
very professional.
I got a good feeling
about this, Jules.
I really do.
Me, too.
You're gonna be great.
Too many things about it
are just so right, you know?
- I do.
- The clinic's on the west side.
I'm great with
sonographic scanners.
And the fact that they're
looking for someone
who's had
experience with obstetric
and gynecologic ultrasounds.
They would be lucky
to have you, Dennis, really.
- Nothing to be nervous about.
- I'm not.
Good, 'cause
you shouldn't be.
Keep breathing and be yourself.
You look great, Den.
You really do.
I'm gonna nail this fucker.
- You said the "F" word.
- All right.
Don't have to be a wisenheimer.
Go give your daddy a kiss.
Wish him good luck.
* Baby, we can do it *
* Take the time,
do it right *
* We can do it, baby *
* Do it tonight *
* Baby, we can do it *
* Take the time,
do it right *
* We can do it, baby *
* Do it tonight *
Is it me, or is sex, like,
so much better than
when we were in college?
I'm not sure.
Maybe we should try it again
and confirm your hypothesis.
No!
No, you're amazing.
You have some serious skills.
But there are other factors
to consider, you know?
Okay, like what?
Well, look at us.
I'm looking.
I mean, our bodies, they
may not be perfect, perfect,
but they're probably more
perfect than they'll ever be
for the rest of our lives,
you know?
Okay. That's really
depressing, Jules.
Yeah, but it's true, right?
And we're not all insecure
and fumbling around,
like when we were in college,
you know?
Well, you know,
I've been practicing
a lot since graduation,
Of course,
most of it's been by myself.
But you know what
they say about practice.
I can't. I have to go.
I'm gonna be late
for work again.
So when am I gonna
see you again?
Um, I don't know.
I have to figure out
what my work schedule is
and prepare this thing
for acting class.
I bet you're a great actress.
I really admire you,
Jules, you know?
Going after your dream,
working your butt off.
Well, you're doing
the same thing, right?
I mean,
you're not gonna be a lab tech
for the rest of your life,
right?
I don't know.
The work's pretty cool,
and the hours are great,
you know?
I get to spend time
with my friends
and play ball with
some of the guys from work.
I think I actually
really lucked out.
I think that's great
that you're so content.
I mean, if a lab tech
is what you wanna be--
Is not what I wanna be,
it's just what I'm doing.
For now. It's my job.
Maybe one day
I'll wanna do something else,
but for the moment,
it really makes me happy,
you know?
- We can't all be Hackneys.
- Who?
That guy who's exhibit we went
to who paints all those swimming
pools.
- Hockney. David Hockney.
- Right. We can't
all be Hockneys.
Or Jacobsons.
Some of us have other gifts.
- Stop it.
- It's your fault.
You and your perfect body.
Hey, come by the park tomorrow.
We got a game
in the late afternoon.
I don't know.
I'll try.
Well, we will be thinking
of you.
So when are we
going to meet him?
What's wrong with him?
Is he married?
- No.
- Is he deformed?
Ethan.
He's Republican.
- Mm-hmm.
- Jesus.
He's a-- a fuck buddy.
Okay?
I'm sorry to be so crude,
but that's all he is.
Nobody cares, Jules.
It's just you've
been seeing him
for, like, three months,
which surpasses
the official
fuck buddy time limit.
What are you
talking about?
It's impossible
to allow someone
access to your vagina
for three consecutive
months
and not develop
some feelings for them.
Okay, no more
Dr. Ruth for you.
Look, he's a very nice guy,
but we have zero in common.
And he's a lab
technician, okay?
He's the guy who squirts
jelly on your belly
and takes X-rays.
He's not exactly Proust,
if you know what I mean.
- I've never read Proust.
- Me, either.
Okay, neither have I,
but the point is we could.
So he's blind?
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Ethan.
He's part of your life,
Jules, for however long.
Since when do we keep
secrets from each other?
Bring him to dinner next week
when we celebrate
Ethan's first paycheck.
Yeah, I've never met
a bona fide fuck buddy
before, so--
Look, I know I sound
like a big fat snob,
but I just think
I can do better, okay?
I mean, I want
to be with somebody
who wants to do something
important with his life, right?
I'm playing a mermaid
for one week
outside the New York Aquarium.
You are being paid to act.
And you just got a job
on a network television show.
It's an animated
piece of shit, Jules.
Have you seen it?
The point is you're
going somewhere,
and so am I.
Not getting there as fast
as you two, clearly,
but I'm aspiring,
and frankly, I don't want
to be with somebody who isn't.
I mean, we're artists, right?
What about your tits?
Your nipples.
Uh...
you do know where your
nipples are, don't you?
Do not look at Miss Wolf.
She can't help you.
You're the one
in the shower.
Now take the soap
and wash your asshole.
Your pussy.
Oh, excuse me.
Your vagina.
You know, I hope
that you really do wash
your private parts
on occasion.
You think that's funny?
Do you?
I don't. I think it's sad.
You want to be actors?
Why? To become stars?
Or to hold a mirror
up to nature,
to show what it means
to be human?
That's what
this exercise is about:
to be willing
to be brave enough
to be private in public,
to risk revealing
your own humanity.
The audience pays you
to show them who they
really are inside
because they're too busy
or they're too frightened
to look.
But if you walk on that stage
looking for approval,
you're cheating them.
You're not acting.
You're begging.
You, Ms. Jacobson,
are a beggar.
You don't want to be seen.
You just want to be liked.
You're an approval junkie.
To me, that is sad.
You care too much
what others think of you.
We know this.
It's what you think
that matters.
You need
to find your voice
and listen to it.
I'm leaving you.
I'm sorry.
I don't think talk therapy
is that effective--
for me, anyway.
Uh, I-- I think it's time
for me to try
something else.
Well, I think it's...
interesting
that you want to leave
just as we're
starting to understand
the underlying issues.
What's the point
of understanding
why you're miserable
if you're still miserable?
It's like the booby prize.
I disagree, Shauna.
I have seen tangible
behavioral improvement in you.
You've been
so much more confident
and more optimistic.
I'm taking Prozac.
My doctor
prescribed it for me.
Okay.
I wish you'd told me.
You obviously feel
it's helping?
Well, if I wasn't taking it,
I don't think I'd have
the courage to leave you.
Can I help you?
Uh, sure.
Is this good?
Good for what?
Uh, my husband. New job.
Is it paying six figures?
No.
Good enough.
Julie Jacobson.
You don't recognize me.
Maybe if I was mixing
a couple vodka Tangs.
Oh, my God. Cathy?
I didn't even--
Wow.
You look great.
Thank you.
I guess I'm just
blessed with good genes.
Oh, I trimmed
those mail bags down
when I was dancing with
Paul Taylor's company.
Didn't make the big difference
I was hoping for, though.
I'm in finance now,
but I don't miss them.
Although he might.
My big tits.
Ah.
This is Julie Jacobson.
Hi.
We were at camp
together.
She was
part of that group.
Huh.
So you and Ash
are still best buds?
Uh, I don't know about that,
but we do speak occasionally.
According to Ethan,
it's more than just
occasionally.
He calls me
every now and then.
It's been a few years,
but at least one of you
had the decency to care.
It's a complicated
time, Cathy.
Bullshit.
But then it must be
very hard to see clearly
with your lips glued
to Ash's ass.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
No, you're not.
You don't
give a shit how I feel.
So no one's ever heard
from Goodman?
I don't think so, no.
Amazing, huh?
He just disappeared.
No body found.
Never contacted anyone,
not even his nearest
and dearest.
I guess not.
Well,
it doesn't mean he won't,
does it?
I know you were all
goo-goo over him,
so maybe he'll come back
and carry you off
into the sunset,
or maybe he'll just
fuck up your life
like he did mine.
- You ready, hon?
- Yeah, yeah.
Let's get out of here.
We're, uh, celebrating
my big promotion.
Senior VP
at Kanter-Fitzgerald.
Just crashing through
the proverbial glass ceiling.
That's right.
Well...
your life doesn't look
that fucked up to me.
You never did understand.
Did you?
Your parents leave?
Hour ago.
Right after Ash's big show.
So what are you
doing here?
Fuck if I know.
They should fucking
outlaw visiting weekend.
Really.
Except your parents
seem so, you know...
Charming?
Intelligent?
Cosmo-fucking-politan?
I showed them my
urban planning project.
My mother smiled,
sort of confused,
and said
it was very nice.
My father asked me
if I figured out a way
to keep the buildings
from collapsing.
Oh, I'm sure he didn't
mean it like--
Oh, he meant it.
Great expectations suck.
Let me tell you.
It's hard
to live up to them
unless you're Ash.
You'll have the last
laugh, you know.
You're going to be another
Frank Lloyd Wright.
There's not a doubt
in my mind.
You're funny, Jacobson.
And you made it
to the inner circle.
Not many people do that.
Good for you.
Goodman?
Goodman,
where the fuck are you?
Keep your tits on.
I'm giving Jacobson here
a pep talk.
This never happened.
What did she
need a pep talk for?
Nothing.
Where's Rorie?
Downstairs with Sophie.
They're having Chinese.
I guess
it didn't go so well?
It was a fucking disaster.
What happened?
She asked me
why I left my last job
and what I'd been doing
in the interim.
You knew that would
probably come up.
You were prepared.
It was the first
thing that came up.
The only thing that came up.
She takes one look
at my résumé,
and she notices the huge gap
in my employment record.
How could she not?
And she asked me
why I left Medfair
and what I'd been doing.
I told her that I left
because I wanted
to take some time off
to be with my daughter
while my wife worked.
And she asked me who my boss
was when I was there.
"Was it Karen Wallace?"
she asked.
Whom she knows very well,
she said.
Basically letting me know
that she would call Karen
and find out what happened,
so I might as well
just tell her,
which I then proceeded to do.
I told her
about what happened,
the reason I was fired.
You should have
seen her face.
What did she say?
She said...
"Thank you for coming in
and for being so honest."
Well, I think it's great
that you went in.
I do.
I mean,
you got back out there,
which is a huge
accomplishment.
I think you should
feel good about that.
Is that how you talk
to your patients?
Like they're fucking
12 years old?
It's like I'm
some disabled child
that you're helping
to get through the day.
That's not how I feel.
Well,
that is how it sounds.
Oh, God.
I fucking hate it.
I never
should have married you.
You should have trusted
your instincts.
Mm.
May I have another?
Behold the bounty that
selling out hath wrought.
560 big ones.
We're rich!
- Rich.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
And all it took
was selling my soul.
Really? Where do I
sign up to sell mine?
To the sweet smell of success.
May we all reek of it soon.
Hey.
- Mm.
Slow down, Jules.
It's going to be fine.
I never should have
invited him.
Seriously,
it was a mistake.
- I know.
- Hey, hey. Relax.
All right? We're not
going to eat him alive.
It just sends
the wrong message.
It's not fair
to him, either.
Oh, God, he's here.
Oh, shit, I knew
he'd wear that.
Hey.
Hey, you made it.
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
I was, like,
glued to the TV.
Ewing just hit
a buzzer beater.
Put the Lakers away.
Ha ha!
That's another
20-point game.
Even if the Knicks
finish fifth,
there is no way this man
is not Rookie of the Year.
It's not the champagne
you get drunk on.
It's the friends
you get drunk with.
- Hey!
- Err!
- Hear, hear!
- Cheers.
I can't believe you guys
have all stayed friends
for so long. I mean,
I went to Boy Scout Camp.
I can't remember
a single name.
Then again,
no one at Camp Nayaki
exactly stood out.
Except
maybe this one kid----
who could burp for
ten straight minutes
without barfing.
Ten straight minutes?
And you forgot his name?
How the great
are soon forgotten.
Chris Gunther.
That was his name.
Like that guy
you're always
bugging me to read:
"Gunther" Grass.
Oh, forget about it,
Dennis,
unless you're Jonesing
for a 600-page book
about a German child
with an unhealthy
attachment to a toy drum
and a voice that
can shatter glass.
Wow. Ha ha.
I guess I'll miss it.
Unless Ethan makes it
into an animated movie.
So, Dennis, Jules says
you are an ultrasound
technician.
Yes, I am.
That sounds pretty cool.
How'd you get into that?
I just sort of fell
into it, actually.
After college,
I didn't really know
what I wanted to do.
I saw this ad
on the subway
about becoming
a lab technician.
Seemed like something
I could be good at.
- Huh.
- You make it sound
like you just flipped
a coin, Dennis.
You must have given it
a little more thought
than that.
Not really.
Do you like it?
I do, actually.
Yes.
The other techies
are great.
We got our own
basketball team.
The doctors are cool.
Also,
it's in Chinatown.
It's surrounded by all
these amazing vendors.
I like to cook,
so sometimes
on my way home
I pick up these really...
bizarre ingredients
like...
star anise or, like,
these twisted roots
that look like
wizard's hands.
- Yeah.
- How's your job, Jonah?
When are you going
to give that all up
and go back
in the family business?
His mother's Corinna Dey.
Oh. Right.
Jules was telling me
about what an amazing
musician you are.
I would love to hear you
play some time.
Yeah. Well, I guess
she forgot to mention
that was in a former life.
Yeah, actually, I design
tech innovations
for the disabled.
I just can't understand
how you could walk away
from so much talent.
Your music was
such a part of you.
A part.
Not the only part.
You could have been
a huge star.
Really, you should have
heard him.
There's more to life
than being famous.
At least I hope so,
or the rest of us
are screwed.
Besides, I don't think
recognition has that much
to do with happiness.
Like we say
at the clinic,
it's what's inside
that counts.
Words of wisdom from
the ultrasound technician.
Excuse me. I have
to use the restroom.
That was funnier
in my head.
He's great, Jules.
You're an asshole,
but he is great.
Fuck!
Some fancy
moves.
Thank you.
You didn't return
any of my phone calls.
My friends really liked you.
At this point,
it's safe to say
they like you a lot more
than they do me.
I'm so sorry, Dennis.
I was awful to you at dinner.
I don't even know
what came over me.
- I just--
- I do.
I'm not the right guy
for you, Jules.
You want this...
big life.
And you deserve it,
and you deserve
the right guy
to go along with it.
And that guy just isn't me.
- Dennis--
- Let me finish, Jules.
I'm regular.
You know?
And you're...
Irregular?
Special.
Big dreams.
I'm just an ordinary guy,
Jules.
I'm never going to read
Günter Grass.
I looked it up.
I can't offer you this
extraordinary life,
just a real one.
But...I don't know
if that's going to be
enough for you.
I don't think
that life with me
is the life that you want.
I don't think
you should settle.
You know what I really
want, Dennis?
I want to be like you.
I do.
I want to be able to walk
into a room full of strangers
and just be okay with myself,
to feel like who I am
is good enough.
The thing is the only time
I've ever felt like that
is when I'm with you.
So to me, real is looking
pretty extraordinary right now.
Here.
It's the "Hoya Destroya."
I feel like anyone
who leads Georgetown
to three final fours
deserves to be
immortalized in plastic.
You're not the only one
with an encyclopedia.
You look like a famous
actress, Mommy.
Oh.
Well, thank God I'm not
because they're all
miserable and unhappy.
Money does not
buy you happiness.
Remember that.
All right, go wash up
for supper, huh?
Wow.
You look amazing.
That's quite some dress.
Thanks.
I got it
at Alice's Underground.
It was practically
brand-new.
I figured if I was going
to go to this thing,
I might as well
get in the spirit.
Ash owes me big time.
This is--
I can't believe she still
hasn't told Ethan
about her brother.
That they've lived with this
gigantic lie between them
all this time.
It's shocking.
We may have our problems,
but at least what we have
isn't built on lies.
I'm going to get better,
Jules.
I know.
You'll figure it out.
Prozac isn't for everyone.
I don't want to lose you.
Hello.
Your date has arrived.
I'll be right down.
A limo. Wow.
Beats the subway.
Oh, they're perks he's given.
I don't think he really
cares about them that much.
- Um...
- Have fun.
Of course I know how much
you'd rather stay home
and play "Legend
of the Sword and the Fairy."
I would, actually.
I'm not really
looking that forward
to a bunch of bloated,
self-important people
congratulating
themselves
on how rich and
successful they are.
You could have said no.
I should go. He's waiting.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'll tell you all about it
in the morning.
Mm. Sorry.
Your chariot awaits,
my lady.
Wow. I mean, look at you.
You look like
a fairy princess.
**
Yes.
Oh, my God. Ethan,
this is amazing.
This could be
in a movie theater
or on TV right now.
Seriously, Ethan,
it's brilliant.
It's just so smart
and original, you know?
Thanks.
See, I knew--
I knew you'd get it,
that we--
that we shared
a certain sensibility
and that you might like it.
I love it.
Wow.
What do you know?
Jules Jacobson loves it.
Mm-mm. Uh, what--
what are you doing?
I'm s-- I'm sorry. I--
- I-- I just--
- No. It was my fault.
- Wow.
- Forget it, really.
- I-- I--
- It's fine.
I feel terrible.
No, no, no, no.
You've nothing
to feel terrible
about, Jules.
It's not a big deal.
Look, look, seriously,
I don't want this
to come between us.
People have been
rejected by other people
since the dawn of time.
W-W-We're--
We're just riding
the wave of history.
I've never rejected anyone
before in my life,
although I've never accepted
anyone before, either.
What I mean
is it's never come up.
Well, maybe the reason
that you don't want
to do this with me
isn't even because of me.
What do you mean?
Well, you say that you
haven't accepted
or rejected anyone
before, right?
So you are 100%
inexperienced.
Maybe
you're just nervous.
Your nervousness
could be masking
your real feelings.
Uh, maybe.
It happens to girls
sometimes.
I-- I have
a proposition for you.
Just reconsider.
Spend some more time
with me
and see what happens.
All right.
Sure. Why not?
Excellent.
To be continued.
You look sensational,
Jules, really.
It's hard not to
in Valentino.
I can't even imagine
what this thing costs.
Oh, come on.
Ash was adamant,
and she picked it out
before she left for Bali.
Well, it's very sweet,
both of you.
Here.
Come on. Tradition.
Tradition.
For special nights.
You've won
about a million awards.
What's special
about this one?
Because tonight
I'm spending it
with my oldest,
dearest friend.
No kids, no spouses.
Just the two of us,
like old times.
To us.
Two old friends
sharing our lives
together.
Jules.
Hey.
I don't think Dennis and I
are going to make it.
This is a final boarding
call for Flight--
Mom and Dad must have
paid a fortune for this.
Will you
keep your voice down?
It's really good.
How did they even
know where to go?
Dad invested something
for someone once.
I don't know.
He was owed a favor.
"Raymond Price."
I like the name.
It suits me, kind of.
Can we not talk
about this right now?
Hey, chill out, Ash.
You're acting like
a fucking criminal.
I am a fucking criminal.
You're not the only one
who'll go to jail
if we're caught. You realize
that, right, Goodman?
I'm touched, Ash, really.
It's fucking noble of you.
And it's Raymond.
I'm doing this for Mom.
You're all she talks about,
couldn't bear the idea
that she wouldn't see you
before she left.
How long did they say?
How about Jacobson?
She know about me being back?
No. She doesn't.
Neither does Ethan.
And you're not going
to be here long enough
for either of them
to find out.
Wow.
You still haven't
told him about me?
That is fucking
impressive, Ash.
Next.
Business or pleasure,
Mr. Price?
Sorry, what?
Your trip.
Was it business
or pleasure?
Uh, pleasure. Yeah.
Always
wanted to see Iceland.
Welcome home, Mr. Price.
Next.
Hmm.
Just not funny, Richard.