Same sex marriages will hurt American
birth rate and the economy...
I'll be right with you so sorry.
The government recently
compared homosexuality...
- How is this?
- It's great the color is good.
... Revolves around maternity leave.
What about paternity leave?
At this time American companies
have no legal obligation...
To give men any time off
after the children are born.
However third world companies
have recently doubled the time
Workers can take off for
maternity and paternity leave.
new moms getting 16 weeks and
new dads getting eight weeks.
Brett, excuse me but...
did new dads started lactating
and I did not get the memo?
I have no idea .
So what's with the 8 weeks ?
The women are the ones who do
all the work in the pregnancy
Why would men need 8 weeks off?
Oh my God, shut this bitch up!
... We started lactating too
- Is that so?
Your jump shots improved.
Oh Linda!
One day you will die.
And we will take you and
we will have your corpse ...
Burned at eighteen hundred degrees
for approximately twenty minutes.
And then we will gather your remains
and we will put them in a pretty vase.
Morbid.
Hey! Connie.
- Greg?
The fucking babysitter
just canceled!
My date is gonna be here
in like 1hour and 45 minutes.
Would you please come over?
No, Connie today is our anniversary
and Ken's in the shower right now.
Oh shit, goddamit!
Greg, please! I would
not ask, but I'm just...
I'm in a jam here.
No! Connie we have
reservations, we....
Wait.
Hi!
- Hi! Hey!
I'm sorry. My house smells
like the chicken market.
Oh dear
Alright how do I look?
And nobody says fat.
- Good.
- Astonishing.
- So who will you going out tonight?
- My neighbor.
What's he like?
He's really nice and we're not that worried
we're not interested in each other.
It's just a friendly neighbors
kind of date. He is old.
Sexy but old.
- How old?
- Seventy...?
- Connie! 70 years?!
- I know!
He could be in the sixty and it would be nasty!
All I know is he's got to be active because ...
He was in the FBI
like 40 years ago.
The Federal Bureau of Narcotics?
You sure he's not just
some age down druggie?
Oh honey! What is
that? It came out?
You know what you need to do?
Put under your pillow so the Tooth
fairy comes at night. Okay?
- Bye, Matt!
- I'll leave you some money for that.
Matt still believes
in the Tooth Fairy?
Tooth Fairy, Santa
claus, all of them.
Thank you.
- One dollar?
- Ciao. Don't worry about a thing.
You know it's ridiculous.
What?
My sister dating
a septagenarian?
No, she fillling Matt's
head with that stuff.
Santa Claus, The Easter
Bunny, Tooth Fairy?
Not to mention the fact that
she's ripping the kid off.
I mean, why force him
to believe in that stuff...
If then she's gonna make the Tooth
Fairy out to be a cheap bastard?
Listen, I agree with you, that's why I gave
him $ 5 dolars as opposed to one dolar.
- But....
- Nice work.
What should be for Mother Goose? Mother
Goose is never perceived to be real.
- Whatever.
- That's why they appear at night.
It's why adults had such a hard time separating
themselves from myths and religion.
You know, they never learn to tell the
differences between truth and fiction.
I believe in myths.
- I know you do.
What you're saying is that
if we have kids some day
You wouldn't want them to believe
in Santa claus or Easter Bunny?
I don't know, I mean.
Look, maybe my reasoning
will change with time.
Besides we said we wouldn't even
talk about adoption for ten years.
I know and we've been
together for four.
So check back with
me in five and a half.
- I'm sorry about tonight.
- No, don't be.
Matt is great and we're together.
That's all that matters.
- I got you something.
- You did?
- I did.
- A present?
For me?
Greg...?
Scales of Justice cufflinks?
- Do you like it?
- My Gosh, yes I love them!
All my clients are gonna be so jealous
they gonna want to steal these.
Good.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- I got you something too.
- Really?
It's In the bag there.
- You sneaked into my bag?
- Maybe.
You're so sneaky, yeah it's one of
my favorites things about you.
- Super Spy.
- What is it?
A Rose Anne biography
Remember when we've been
through the entire series?
We did not leave the
bedroom for a week.
Dan!
Oh my God, four years...
- I know... Makes you think.
FOUR YEARS BEFORE
It's hot out there.
- Yeah?
- Yep.
You're up for a run?
What?
You said you thought you gained some
weight, maybe we should go for a run.
I love how you waited for me
to disrobe to say that but...
Come on, I'm getting chubby
too, let's go for a run.
What's wrong with chubby?
Now I'm chubby?
Here, look at this
here, look at this.
This is going to check the mail,
that's all that this is from.
It's 102 degrees outside
and this is human.
Greg, come on we're just
walked there, I mean
Look at us, all we ever do is
watch movies and order in.
Baby it's so hot!
Let's turn back around
and go get some lunch?
No momma.
Yes.
It was just from
checking the mail.
No.
He got so fat.
Yeah.
No, I'm eating.
I love you.
I love you more, okay.
Okay, bye.
Okay.
Dan!
- Dan!
- What?
What is the second
part to this song?
"It's alarming how
charming I feel."'
Okay.
It's alarming how
charming I feel.
There's nothing to watch.
- That's not true, you just passed by like...
five things that I would watch or
I have watched and I love.
Like what?
Soapdish
- Never heard of it, who's in it?
- Sally field!
The woman with the cookies?
Cookies ?!
The cookies with the red and white
wrappers in the airport newstands.
- Airport newstands?
- Yeah.
Like "Everything that you were
saying is wrong"  Gidget?
She won an Oscar! "You like
me you really like me!"
She was the mom
in Mrs Doubtfire.
I don't "werk" with the males,
'cause I used to be one.
What?
You're a masochistic.
Explain.
How do you even find the time...
For this little lovely and
deceivable sexy kitten?
Why would you even want to after
the picture you painted of him?
Is this the way you
talk to your patients?
- No.
-That is really good.
Thank you, but...
I'll tell you what's
good for you.
A healthy dose of
breaking it off.
Would you bring another glass?
The heart wants what
it wants you know?
Sometimes you meet someone and you
fall in love, and that's all that is to it.
Yeah, but you're not in love...
You're tortured. And not
even in the good way.
But I'm sure the
sex is great, right?
But a healthy and equal
relationship this is not.
You are clearly doing
all the heavy lifting.
Gregory...
What you need from a man
is an intellectual equal.
Not some junior sales associate...
Who knows all the defining characteristics
of the washes of denim.
But if you're now interested in
servicers level right now
I should be pursuing
dermatology.
Hey, I resemble that remark.
Now it is serious.
You avoid the psychiatry
rotation like the plague.
There's obviously no room
for crazy and you know it.
And you wanna place
in radiation and oncology
Because you have this
Mother Teresa complex.
You love curing people but
you can't cure this kid
of his narcissism, Greg.
It's incurable.
-He might as well be mentally retarded.
- You know, Ernie?
You might have avoided your
psychiatry rotation too
If your very first patient
on the rotation
Her problem was
"I am the queen of Africa...
And I have the papers
to prove it.
Followed by her shouting:
"You can't have my pussy!"
So I have this friend I'd
like you to meet...
- Ernie...
- What?
I appreciate your concern
But I'm very much with
Alex for the moment.
You're very much tolerating
And besides
all I said was,
I have a friend I'd like you to meet
Not that I have a friend that I necessarily
want you to go out and fuck.
Just have a coffee and
see what happens.
- Who is he?
- His name is Ken.
He is a criminal defense attorney,
he's very good looking and...
I just texted you his number
like two minutes ago.
You were saying something...?
I shouldn't...
Look, I already talked you up to him you
would only disappoint by backing up now.
I wouldn't be backing out I haven't
made any plans with him so...
- There's not backing out.
- Greg, listen.
I know you. You're not happy.
And besides I'd rather
see you single than...
With someone who requires
a trip to the diamond district
Just so you can translate
his terms of endearment.
Okay, okay so talking
isn't our strong point
You think?
You gonna be a MD!
This kid can't even pronounce
the word anxiety.
Oh God...
Orchide no really, is orchide.
- Guys, give me a break, okay?
- You guys just don't know him.
- So really, what is it?
What is it? Wait...
What is the thing?
Yeah he's pretty.
What is it?
Well he got a 8-pound dick.
Jesus, were you shop
for a porn star?
- Why was the door locked?
- I don't know, habit?
... having such a good time.
I think that we should-
- Hey, Tad.
- Hey.
What was he doing here?
Well, watching the
Drags Race marathon.
Oh, yeah with the
deadbolt locked.
Oh my God would you drop
it? I said it was a mistake.
Okay.
Why did't you tell me
he was coming over?
I figured it wouldn't matter.
Not matters? It matters,
a lot Alex, I mean I...
Fuck... It's one thing
to come home
Expecting to see your boyfriend and
is another thing completely
Come home and see some guy that I
barely know sitting on my couch
With his feet up on my
furniture, eating my food.
Okay?
I own, all of the things in this apartment,
and that includes the leftovers.
Okay.
Well, you know what?
If that's how you gonna play maybe
I should just go home tonight.
Yeah, maybe you should.
- I wasn't being serious.
- Maybe I was.
It's like really late and I'll
probably wake my parents
- If I went home right now.
- So why did you suggested?
Is this your way of scolding
me like I'm your child?
I'm not scolding you but-
Fuck I hope this
is a wake up call.
No, of course obviously I don't wanna
to send you home at this hour but...
This is my place, okay?
And you can't just have people
coming in without me knowing
And you can not lock me out
in the middle of the night!
I did't lock you out!
- You locked the deadbolt with someone else here!
You know what? I don't
wanna stay here tonight.
You always get like this after
hanging out with your friends.
Like what? How do I get?
You talk to me like you
were better than me.
Alex, I don't think
that I am better...
... Than you.
- No?
I just think that
we're different.
I think that we
are too different.
- This isn't working.
- Fucking, I knew it!
Alex-
- What?
Come here let's talk
about this, okay?
No come here.
- Just sit down stop acting like a child.
Don't tell me I'm acting like a
child, I'm not acting like a child!
No, you are behaving like
a totaly mature adult.
I'll come tomorrow
to pick up my shit.
You know, if that's
convenient for you.
So Ernie told me you're
a medical student.
Yes, I'm bad Ernie only
told you that because I am...
Actually dropped out.
- You dropped out?
- Yeah. I haven't told him that yet.
I...
I know that's kind of a loser
thing to tell on the first date.
This is our first date?
I hoped this was
our first date yes.
And I hoped that it's
okay that I'm okay.
Hey you! My name is
Greg, nice to meet you.
I made a big decision this week.
And I'm probably out of med
school. I'm college drop out.
Sorry I'm a loser.
I hope I'm handsome enough.
You know, I think if you're feeling
pulled in a different direction
Then you should listen to that.
What?
Just what I said,
stick with your gut.
You know, instincts are
underrated nowadays but....
You gotta listen to them.
Do you want to...
Break the news to
my mom for me?
No, that is all to you.
Hey, what you're
thinking about?
Nothing.
Everything you know.
How we got together
and Sally field.
And how much I love fast
food and hate white wine.
Lots, lots of things.
No, no, no, you
know why.
I don't know why.
- No! No, we can't!
- Yes, I'll be quiet.
- No! Don't
- He's sleeping.
Don't start something
you can not finish.
I always end...
- And you can not finish this...
Because he's up there.
Just relax, relax.
I'll just kiss all of it, okay?
- Like the French did.
What with a cigarette
in your mouth?
- Baby, let me...?
- No
- Let you what?
- Come on I just want...
What? What do you want?
I want to...
Put myself inside you...?
Where did this come
from? Born again Top?
I don't know, I'm feeling...
adventurous, you know?
- Like a finger or two or...?
- No I, like with my penis.
Wow! Okay, okay, alright.
- What? Okay?
- Yeah okay.
You are gonna need to
get some lubricantion.
Because the last thing that went
up there was a colonoscopy.
When I was eight and before
that a baby thermometer so...
I'm gonna need
some lubrication.
- Happy anniversary.
- Okay.
I'm sure Connie has some
lube stashed here somewhere.
Oh, my god, okay.
Okay, I couldn't find any lube
but I got some petroleum jelly.
- Did you get condom?
- What?
- A condom.
- For what?
We're celebrating four years
of monogamous bliss
I don't think we need a condom.
I think it gets messy. I don't
want stuff get on you
Okay, but let's just
this time...
Okay, but we have to...We have
to do it somewhere else and ...
We have to get some towels,
- Why? why
Because I don't want the couch to get-
- Okay what about the floor?
Okay, alright.
I'll put this down here
To be nice and comfy. Okay.
Get this off.
- Easy, easy, easy.
- Okay.
You feel so good...
Was a good six minutes?
Six minutes? It was
more like two.
Well...
When you got a dick in
your ass time stand still.
Don't I know?
What is your fortune?
No adventures away
beyond the horizon.
You gonna climb many
mountains and be on top.
Again? Round two?
- Are you ready?
- I'm in, okay.
I don't know about what
the conversation was...
I just kept going in and out. I didn't
know what he was talking anyway.
I was so distracted by...
the pendulum swings
of his neck skin.
It kind of ... get to
a point I just gave up.
So... no second date?
I'm guessing.
Thursdays and Mondays.
Oh, yeah of course we do.
Her name was Linda,
she was a drunk pet.
She went to school but
just couldn't rack up.
Majored in ornithology.
Yes, that bird watching.
But she failed every test
cause she ate them.
That is her thing to do,
because she's a cat.
But then he went to Hollywood
and married James cameron
How is it going there baby?
Swimmingly. What about you?
Honestly? I am
ready for a break.
Yeah me too.
- Oh, yeah?
- Hum, Hum
- One of these breaks?
- Yeah, I think it's a good break.
I like these breaks.
No, don't get it. No, don't!
It might be the client, It might be
the client, It might be the client.
I'm sorry.
Hello! This is Greg.
Shouldn't you have said are you
sitting down first? Jesus!
No, no I'm in bed,
I'm in bed sorry.
What happened?
- Oh! My God!
- What?
Yeah, we'll...
We'll be there soon,
like ten minutes, okay?
Yeah, love you.
That was Richard.
- Ernie had a stroke.
- Oh my God!
- Hey baby.
- Hey.
You okay?
Yeah, I just ... thinking
about Ernie.
- Have you talked to him lately?
- No, I feel like such an asshole.
Baby, don't... I mean.
After the time when you called over that
his parents have turned you away. - True.
Max asleep already?
Yes, he's in bed thank you so
much for being cool about this.
It's fine.
- You're all sweaty.
- Yeah, I know, it's burning hot in here.
- Are you that hot?
- No, I'm fine.
I can turn on the air
a little bit to cool.
Thank you.
I didn't want to touch it because I
know how cold that you can get.
Bed time for us too.
No, I have to finish this.
- Come to bed...
- No.
- Yes.
- I can't, I can't.
I have to finish my work.
- Pay the bills.
- Fine.
Okay, I will.
- Oh, my God! What the fuck!
- I'm sorry.
- What the...
Get off of me!
Hey! I....
Why didn't you tell me that
you were weren't well?
Sorry I just didn't
think it was serious
It was so disgusting.
- I know.
- Seriously I can't-
- Hello?
- Hey. How you feeling?
Much better, better.
Well, did you have
anything to eat today?
Yes, everything. I had
everything to eat.
Okay, great.
So I guess we're officially
out of groceries now.
Well, there might be
some eggs with luck.
Or cans of tuna.
Okay, order in
the drive through.
Can we get like Chinese
food on top of the pizza?
- Hey this one looks good.
- What?
Oh don't mind it's subtitled.
And guessing you're not
in the mood to read a movie...
I've just take cheese off
of the remote control
Now I'm not on the mood
to read my movie?
Yeah I saw that.
How about a documentary?
I don't know... it's kind of boring to watch
something that we've seen a million times before.
Like Lulas.
Baby, we've just watched
that like three days ago.
Fine, watch what
you wanna watch.
I'm not gonna be able to pay
much attention my brain is fried.
- Hello Helene.
Oh, my God!
Seriously, if you roll around
any harder I gonna be sick.
I'm sorry but I'm tossing and turning
because I'm trying to keep from puking.
Again?
You know what? Tomorrow ...
You should really go see a doctor.
- For indigestion?
This isn't indigestion, I ate the same
things you ate and I'm not sick.
I don't have health insurance.
So what? Go Greg.
A general partition is gonna
cost next to nothing.
Go and see Dr.
Elliot she's great.
Plus she owes me a favor.
I've got her husband
office last year, didn't I?
Just go to bed quietly.
Don't move.
- Hello Greg, I'm Dr. Elliot.
- Hi Dr. Elliot, nice to meet you.
So what's been happening?
I've been dizzy, I get nauseous
have recurring headaches...
Well, something is wrongs.
Let's take a look, shall we?
You're fine, Greg.
Your tests came back fine.
Your blood test is fine, HIV is negative,
You probably just got a flu bug.
Just gonna have
to switch it out.
This is not the flu.
Of course it's the flu, throwing up is
what happens when you have the flu.
Not only throwing up happens
when you have the flu.
But a lot of other stuff
also happens like
Sore throat, and aching
muscles, and coughing.
And I don't have any of those, plus
when was the last time both of
your feet went numb
when you had the flu?
I'm sure Dr. Elliot knows
what she's talking about.
What?
- Am I fat? Am I hideous?
- What? No!
I saw that you looked at me, I know
that that's what you were thinking.
Baby, I wasn't even
looking at you.
- You weren't?
- No, I was ...
Looking at myself in the mirror, with my
back turned to you much like it is now.
I just thought I saw you looking at
me out of the corner of his eyes
Honey, I think you're sorrow.
You're starting to sound like every
other husband on the face of the earth.
How is that?
You are so agreeable!
"Yes, dear", "No dear"
You don't likethat about me?
That I'm agreeable?
No I love that
you're agreeable.
But I just wanna make sure that
you're being sincere, okay?
Don't take this the
wrong way, dear but ...
You're beginning to sound like any
other wife in the face of the planet.
I thought you were the wife.
According to your chart,
everything is normal.
No, everything is not normal.
I got heartburn, cramps, almost
constant nausea, swelling.
My feet are swelling inside
my shoes right now, so.
- Any acne?
- Yes, thank you for noticing.
He's also having a
lot of mood swings.
- You're hungry all the time?
- Yes. Okay.
Greg I'd like to recommend
you seeing an specialist.
- An specialist?
- What kind of specialist?
Well, you're not suffering
from any illness.
So whatever it is, it's unusual.
And what you said that means
Swelling, blossoming...
- It's if you were...
- Becoming doctor Hulk?
It's if you were
expecting a baby.
- Excuse me, what?
- I know it sounds ridiculous.
But Greg what you
are describing...
Is what I'd expect to hear from a
woman who was four months pregnant.
And outside of that, you
couldn't be in better shape.
So I don't think there's anything
that I can do for you.
But I do want you to consult
with this friend of mine.
I'd also like to put
you on a strict diet.
Starting immediately.
What...? I was going...
It's still good.
Have you made the appointment
with that especialist yet?
No, I...
Isn't it obvious that she
just thinks that-
That's diet okay?
- Greg I'm serious.
- Just think that I have
A weight problem, okay?
- I am serious.
I'll go on the diet.
I'll go on the diet
And then we'll see what happens.
- Yes Yes.
You'll go on the diet and you're also making
an appointment with the especialist , okay?
I'd throw myself out the window
if anything ever happen to you.
You can't be that serious.
Doctor's Office
One possible reason for
Dr. Elliot send me here?
I don't know.
There it is.
What it is?
Is that a ... tumor?
- No, it's not a tumor.
This is closer to his
abdominal cavity here.
Thank you.
- You two are sexually active?
- Yes
Do you use protection?
No, not anymore, we've been
together for a very long time.
Alright I need to
make a phone call.
Would you two mind
waiting in my office?
I wonder what he saw? Like, have
you seen the look on his eyes?
- Dr. Elliot? Hi guys.
- Oh my god is this serious?
You are pregnant.
What?
Okay, alright.
- Alright.
- Greg?
You guys!!
Greg?
I'm gonna say this as plainly
as I possibly can.
You have a human fetus growing
withing your abdominal cavity.
Just as it would grow
within a woman's uterus.
Your baby has fingernails.
Okay, guys, like that was,
that was funny but...
You're welcomed to seek a second
opinion or third in this case
We... We would encourage that.
Is this... I mean, could medication
have caused this?
It has taken sleeping pills? Maybe
we're elegible for legal recourse.
You should really
look into this.
I've never seen a
pill create a womb.
In fact I've never seen anything
remotely like this. Neither does he.
Greg, at this point you
are a medical miracle.
49 million years of evolution and I am the
first man in the history of the world
To ever get pregnant! Why?! Why me ?!
- Greg, please just try and relax.
Oh yes! Just try and relax
with a baby inside of you!
Are you in Valium?
Is that an option?
You know, technically you're the second.
Don't forget about Thomas baby?
Except you know Greg was
actually born a man so...
How could this happen? I could
never do anything right...
That's your mother talking.
- Is it?
Stop torturing yourself, you
can't help it, is not your fault.
Of course it's my fault! I was
the idiot that let him top!
- So now it's my fault?
- Yes! Yes it's your fault!
You were the person that just had to
have and you were so insistent...
That we have sex right there on
Connie's living room floor!
Wait, what ?! You had
sex in my house?
Oh yeah. Right there, next to the couch.
- Greg stop please!
What the fuck! When?
- When you were walking the neighbor!
Were in the neighbor...?
Oh my God! You guys had sex
while you were babysitting?!
Where was Max?
We were very quite quiet,
he was upstairs...
I don't have any health insurance! How
anyone has a baby without health insurance?
Greg, we sign up. Come on
I've been you to sign up.
What happens if it's deformed?
- Someone will find that charming.
- That's not charming.
It could be a gold medal
gymnastics. It could be a...
Or could bag groceries or could
be addicted to black tar heroin...?
So... So what? Look, anything can
happen, anything can happen?
Yes, I have a girl friend who is a
personal incontinence consultant .
She takes orders for adult
diapers over the phone.
Thank god for baby boomers.
What? I'm just
agreeing with you.
Anything can happen.
My friend, she's married,
she has a kid... in a therapy.
She's happy!
There are so many
great little boy names...
Hank Fisher, Matt,
everybody loves a Matt.
I can't be responsible for the way
some kid's life turns out okay?
I can't.
That's what you're thinking?
- Yeah, that's what I'm thinking.
What...
What about our apartment? Like
we don't have enough room?
- For what?
- For a kid!
We barely have enough room
for Linda and she is a cat so...
Okay, you're right.
Changes are gonna happen
when we have a baby but...
I mean, who cares?
We'll redecorate.
Don't you want this?
Can't you feel it?
Yeah, I can feel it. Yeah,
absolutely I can feel it...
I can feel it moving around, and kicking
and sharpening its little fingernails
And sending emails and playing cards
because it's living inside of me.
It's living inside of ME!
Baby, it is because you
are a medical miracle!
I don't wanna be a
medical miracle!
I DON'T WANT TO BE
A MEDICAL MIRACLE!
I didn't even want
to be a doctor!
That night, remember?
When you told me that you're gonna
drop out of medical school...?
What did I say to you?
Said that if I was being pulled
in a different direction
I should go with it. I
should follow my instincts.
And what is this?
Sure, maybe it is more
of a thrust than a pull
But baby, this is a
different direction!
And my guts is telling me that
this is what supposed to happen!
You bottom one night
out of hundreds!
Okay, thousands and
bam, you were pregnant!
- Don't you think that's amazing?
- Yeah, lucky me...
I don't think there
is anyone answer
It is multilayer ...
A man in Los Angeles,
was the first pioneer
of this revolutionary
social transformation
What is this?
An overweight gay man, apparently
gave birth to a healthy baby girl
In a West Hollywood
toilet last night.
What...?
I think the question on everyone's
mind is: What caused this?
could be a random genetic strain that
mutates among the male species?
perhaps there is some
common food on the market
Some product which would
further this on the males?
A sort of counter
contraceptive pill?
Now members of the medical
community like yourself
Are coming forward
saying they see
Millions of men
experiencing...
It's on every channel.
... the very foundation
of what it is to be a man
And what it is to be a woman...
What is wrong?
Nothing...
It's just that I...
You know I'm not religious or
spiritual or any of that I just...
I can not help but feel
let down by all of this.
Why?
Because I thought what we had
between us was special, you know?
Something...
Giving meaning to our lives.
Yeah if you're talking
about our unborn child.
Then there is something
special between us.
I'm talking about the pregnancy
that it even happened at all.
I mean...
I thought this was a miracle. It turns
out that's a goddamn epidemic!
So...?
So?! We're not gonna
matter, okay?
Our baby is not gonna matter.
We're just like everybody else.
Anyone can make a baby.
Is that... Is that all you
care about? The attention?
You just want people
to come by and-
Greg, of course not. No I just...
I thought we were the first.
We were like the Neil Armstrong
of male on male conception.
One small step for a man
One giant fucking
leap for mankind!
Well, with great hopes comes
high disappointment.
I'm upset. Can't I be upset?
Sure, sure. You can be
upset. Absolutely, but...
Frankly I'm excited that
we won't have news cameras
Pointed at our
door 24 hours a day.
Right.
Ken has been acting
strange recently.
Well, men have been known to act
strangely in pregnancy.
It's too different for them.
They're not actually going through it.
- Yeah, I know, I know I'm through it.
Yeah, right, and now
if you go throught it...
You have to.
You deal with it, and you'll never
forget what your child mean to you.
Yeah, what my
child means to me...
It's a completely fucking
pain the ass.
No, your children
are meaningful.
I don't talk a mere contribution
to the world.
I have an appointment. I need to go
check on my little contribution.
- Thanks for the insight.
- You're welcome.
- Look at you. Need help?
- No, I'm fine.
I would reel you in.
Are you here to
pick up your wife?
No.
So I just been feeling
a little hot lately.
In hot flashes, do you
think that's possible?
You're not 32 years old!
Yeah, but the women in my family
we all start things earlier.
I hit puberty at nine.
Hormones in chicken? Did you
grew up eating a lot of fast food?
Excuse me? Do I look like I grew
up eating a lot of Fast food?
I didn't mean anything by it I just-
You know what Doctor?
I think we are done here.
Just forget about it.
I appreciate your time.
Greg, I will see you now.
The baby will be
due October 18th.
Okay. So what do we
do on the due day?
Well it's a surgical procedure
similar to a C- section.
Okay, doctor but I saw the guy
on TV and he had his in a toilet.
Why do you have to cut me open?
- Greg, this is so new.
To everyone, to medical
professionals everywhere.
And frankly I'd like
to play this safe.
I'm sorry I can't help it notice
the hair on your hoodie...
- Do you have an animal?
- Yeah, I got a cat.
No, no cats have worms and it
could get the baby toxoplasmosis.
Linda doesn't have worms.
Well, a cat could suffocate
the baby or claw the baby.
Fuck him! Don't let him make you think for
one second that you need to get rid of that cat.
I'm not. I will not. But...
All that talk of let's
cut the baby out...
- I don't know, it's a downer.
- Don't listen him Greg...
Do what you want.
You saw that guy who
gave birth in the toilet?
You think he exactly marked
this way over there?
Doubtful.
Have the baby however you
want, this is YOUR child!
Thank you.
Listen, I...
I'm sorry that I've been such an
asshole since this pregnancy.
How's Ernie? How is he doing?
Hot mess.
He texted me last week and asked
if I thought Oscar the Grouch writers...
For living in such a tight conditions.
- Really?
His hall of questions had something to do
with the Kate Blanchet being a half breed...
Well, I'm glad that this stroke has opened
up Ernie's mind for the bigger picture.
Wow! It's quite the breakfast
you got going here baby.
So you have your appetite back.
Yep. No more nausea.
No more insomnia.
I feel great.
- That's great.
- Yeah.
Actually... I was thinking ...
That we might be able to
fool around a little bit...
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
I bumped out against
the oven handle earlier ...
And I think I got wood.
It's been too long, hasn't been?
- Far too long.
I'm gonna find that spot
that makes you growl...
You're not on top now.
Wait, wait, wait
- What? you're not ready?
- No, no, no,
He moved.
Yeah it's generally what penises do when excited.
- No, no the baby.
- Where are you going?
- I should clean up the kitchen.
He's scared of this baby I can tell you,
you can see when you look in his eyes.
He's afraid to grow up.
Connie
I don't know if I wanna
have this baby.
Of course you do!
This is a blessing.
People spend thousands of
dollars trying to get pregnant.
Or paying for a surrogate or
paying to buy a baby from China.
Look, I get it.
I know that's hard.
- Have you heard of the Doulas?
- No. Who is she?
Not a she. A Doula.
It's like a stress therapist.
They're there for the expecting mother
during the pregnancy and then at birth.
- It may be worth looking into.
- Yeah, that's fine.
But what about after the birth?
I just wanna make sure that
this baby has a family.
Right.
We are going to need to get a new car.
- What?
A new car, we gonna need one.
- Why?
Because we have to fit a car sit
into it and we need four seats.
- Yours has four seats.
- And mine is also a piece of shit.
Greg, come on, you know I bought
That car for myself as a present
when I graduated at law school .
I know you bought that car
for yourself because you liked
Looking in the park
lot as the hot lawyer.
Excuse me?
Listen, I know that this baby was
unexpected and I know that ...
For the last if you even
enjoyed the ride,
But I just think that-
- Enjoy the ride?
That's what you think of me?
You know how hard I work.
That's what you think?
I think that you don't look like someone
who wants to become a father.
Okay, maybe I don't know how
to be a dad, maybe I, maybe I...
Maybe I can't be a dad. Maybe
I just don't wanna be a dad.
- There it is.
- There what is?
The truth that we've been waiting
for, you don't want this baby.
Maybe I don't Greg.
Maybe I'm scared.
Scared? Maybe I'm scared
too.  I'm scared too and...
And who was the one to
talk me out of that? It was you.
You were the one. Because you said that it
was gonna be a blessing, a new direction.
And that's so easy for you to say,
that is so easy for you to say.
When you are not you the person
who has to carry it around, okay?
You're not the person who's gotten fat
and is getting fatter every single second.
You're not the person who's
gonna up shoes size and half
You're not the person who bumps up against
kitchen appliances and gets horny.
And you're not the person whose hormones
had turned the man into a 15 years old girl.
Yes nod your head, go
ahead, nod your head.
But you...
I don't have the energy to
hold you up okay?
I don't have the energy to be
your rock when you didn't...
You just go.
- Go where?
- Just go.
Okay. Really?
Fine.
That's what you want, Greg?
Is it?
Is this what you want?
I'll be sleeping at the office.
So, what I have here is my Doula
bag. That I have for many years.
So if is okay with you I'lI show
you the kind of things I carry in it.
That'd be great.
So this right here are hard candies.
And I really just carry
this in case you
Wanna get a little sugar
buzz during labor.
I don't know, just something
to comfort you.
Let's see...
Well my swimming suit.
This is a water birth and
I can get in it with you.
Plastic bag for my wet
swimming suit.
- Nice to meet you!
- It's nice to meet you.
Okay, so.... let's see here...
I have...
A pad. If it's those
days of the month.
These right here, these
are essential oils.
What are those for exactly?
You'll find out which aroma
resonates with you.
A mirror.
If you want to see what's
going on down there.
That sounds awful.
I have some... gum.
What... what is... that?
That's marijuana. Afterwards
you are welcome to use some.
That is very kind of you.
- Nice.
So did you brought anything that would
be like... Hey this is helpful!
While you're pushing a
human out of you?
Yes.
So, would you like one?
They're so good.
Good to see you.
Well, we usually have just a
few meetings before the birth.
You know, to discuss things
like your emotional needs,
Your mental condition,
birth plan.
Just getting ready to push
when it comes time to push.
Thomas that's the best thing
that I've heard all day.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- So you're set for October?
- For the moment yeah.
Okay,then I guess that the
only thing I will need to do is
Come by and check out your
place whenever you'd like.
Just to access the conditions
of your home.
The conditions of my home...
Mostly, it's an apartment but
it's not sanctioned for anything.
I have a nice scream maker so
That's good, that's good.
- Pretentious.
No, probably it's fine.
I would just need to make
sure it's appropriate.
You know, no mould, clean air
filters, planty of  space.
- That sort of stuff.
- Yeah.
No stacks of  dirty
dishes, I got it.
So? This is it.
- Wow! This is great.
- Yeah, thank you, thank you.
I should probably
check the boiler.
- Oh! Yeah this...
- Back here?
Yeah, to the left.
Hot water is important.
We need a lot of  hot
water for the birth.
That's what I would go.
You'd neeed a lot space
in your tub too.
Oh! Yeah.
I don't know about the tub
I barely fit in it now.
What about your bed?
I still fit in it.
I know I meant what
size is your bed?
Oh, it's a California King.
- It's perfect.
- Yes
You can always purchase
an inflatable portable pool.
- This is Ken?
- Yeah.
- Handsome guy.
Where are you guys here?
Ken was deep sea fishing and
He thrown his harpoon and it
popped out of the water so...
You're alright?
No, no.
Not alright.
I'm huge.
I'm like a brand
new Greg and I...
I got this thing growing
inside of me...
And my nipples are sore
and my back hurts...
And my feet are swollen
and I am constipated and I...
I haven't seen my
dick... in weeks.
And you know, Ken is
basically moved out.
Which I get, I don't blame
him I don't blame him but...
He's not ready for this and I'm not
ready for it either you know...
Sometimes I just can't help but
thinking that I don't want this baby.
I've been drinking tap water.
Because I'd heard that it sometimes
causes miscarriages in women  what...
Or maybe you know it's just the single
isolated incident in West Virginia.
I don't know, I followed so many
news out some social medias.
And I'd just been
looking for someone.
Anyone who is not a falling
complete crazy that could...
Help me through this, through
the delivery at least.
Because I'm 31 years old and I am a
web designer who until very recently...
Did not have any
health care and I'm...
I'm a top usually
by the way and...
I just don't know how I'm gonna be a
parent, how I'm gonna have a family...
My family is a complete train wreck,
my mother is vain and self-absorbed.
And my father has never been in the
picture and my half sister, Connie, she's...
She's wonderful actually, she's  wonderful
but has her own problems.
My best friend, Ernie...
He is basically in life long
prison sentence for his...
Fucking psychotic christian
fundamentalist parents.
And he is in a wheelchair
right now by the way.
He is confined to one
And he has the mental
capacity a preschool
Constantly tweeting about
like sharp wigs
Or whether or not the Cookie
Monster has an ants problem.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Look...
I know that most of my responsibility
happens at birth but...
Greg, looks like you're under
A considerable amount of stress and
stress is not good for the baby.
And yes, in some areas
either is tap water.
... But hey, why
don't we do this...
Why don't we schedule an appointment
each week from here on now?
That i's very nice of you, Thomas,
but I can't afford that.
I just can't. So thank
you, thank you, though.
It's what, it's what
needs to be done.
And if you still want me to be
your Doula, what I hope you do,
That's what we gonna do.
Okay.
Don't worry about the money.
God, I'm happy to help.
So happy to help.
Hormones...
Well, today I thought I'd
start off simple.
Okay.
After your outburst
the other day.
I thought it would be a very good idea
for you to get your feelings out.
Awesome.
- How do you feel?
- Fat.
I feel fat like Marlon Brandon
in The Island of Dr Monroe.
It's like I have a
gravitational pull.
I have a solution, I think.
Have you ever seen that music video about
Britney Spears Dear Diary?
No, I haven't.
Well, you gonna Dear Diary
the shit out of this notebook.
A Dear diary, I'm
fat and disgusting,
Dear diary, where my penis go?
And so and so forth, okay?
Okay.
- Oh you hated it!
- Kind of.
It's merely a suggestion,
this is all about you.
Hello?
Greg, hi. Brett Roberts
from the Local News.
I just wanted to get back with you
about schedule your interview.
Schedule? I didn't scheduled
an interview.
Well, it must have been
your partner, Ken.
Apparently Ken called
a few weeks ago and,
This is the first opportunity I have
to get back with you, I'm so sorry.
Is this... Is this about
my pregnancy?
Yes, it is! And congratulations
by the way.
You might have won me over by saying my
condolences, the way that I'm feeling right now.
Hello?
So I brought you two things
that gonna improve your mood.
This is a test,
a bag of essentials
Oh shit! No...
This is to watch Clueless.
- Whatever the edition...
- That's a better test.
That's a test.
- And...
There's this. Which
one do you want?
- Dulce de Leche.
- Nice. I'll have the strawberry.
Listen, did you actually...?
The essentials were just a
joke, right? Like you didn't...?
Or did you actually intended to bring some essentials?
- I did.
But I... I left it on my
counter before I left.
No, it's good to like
soak in absence...
- That's okay.
- It's for...
Like most relaxation
and stuff like that.
Yeah I have some.
How many births
did you assisted on?
- Four.
- So I'm your fifth.
Yes, well...
Technically...
Or the forth I guess. Depending
on how you  look at it.
One of my clients
miscarried, so.
That's terrible, I'm so orry.
It's okay. She was...
I mean, she was...
It was not good but...
So what is you...
What is you do regularly, or
what you wanna do regularly?
I like to be making music actually.
- Yeah?
Yeah, I mean, that's what
led me to Nashville, so...
Alright.
- But since I don't have...
Anything too cling to just yet.
Like your fortunate sister does.
I mostly do ... figure modeling
For Art classes.
Some of the colleges
around town..?
Really?
Like... Like figure...?
Like... figure... like naked...?
- Naked?
- Nude. They call it nude.
- I did not take you for an exhibitionist.
- I'm not!
- It seems like you might be an exhibitionist.
- I'm definitely not.
Really? Is it not uncomfortable?
The first or second time...
Yeah, yes, but I...
I don't know. I guess it grown
on me. Like most things do.
Ew.
You know,  just kept
stick with it long enough.
But...
Some of the fucking poses
they make me do? Suck!
Suck so bad! It's
so uncomfortable!
And I start like...
Individually resenting each
and every student in the class.
Because you know
they're comfortable.
But I don't know
after it passes,
It's pretty freeing.
You should try it.
Belly and all.
- That would be beautiful.
I just kinda zone out and...
I write songs in my head. And
they can't really do that.
An attempt job or sling drinks.
Which I've tried before.
I can definitely see
you raking the booze,
Behing a bar.
Yeah, I did it for a while.
But that is definitely something
that did not grown on me.
I'm just really not
that social actually.
Really?
- Yeah.
And that's kind of what
I like about the art classes.
Yes?
You don't have to talk
to anybody, you know?
Just sort of... judge
them on silently.
But you know, sometimes after
classe I'll get up and walk around,
And look at people's sculptures
and the drawings.
And chat a little bit, but inevitably
I just kind of zone out and...
And I play music in
my head, you know?
Unless I have a big
ass cramp in my toe.
So what's your agenda?
In Pop music?
- Yeah.
Sing a song that stuck.
So what kind of are you trying like...
Are you trying about Britney or Adele?
You gave me pretty little
kisses on my face
Your arms enlace me, we
cuddle in the right place
In every time I look at
you, you smile on like
You know what it do to me
It doen't hurt that you have
the most perfect teeth
And when you hold my hand
you sweep me off my feet
Because every time I'm around
you, I can barely breathe
You see what you do to me
I won't forget you
when you leave me
I know it's coming shortly
That I just have to let you know
It's what you do to me
I can barely breathe
Hello.
Hi Greg, Brett Roberts from the
Local News please don't hang up.
I'll get it.
- Thank you.
- Hi.
Brett Roberts good to see you.
- Nice to meet you.
I wanna go over a few bullet points first
before we get started if that's okay.
Sure.
Is paternity leave, it's
that an option for you?
No, no I'm self-employed.
Alright. Well, we'll just
inscribe as unknow.
What are your
plans for delivery?
Greg has decided
to do a home birth.
And we gonna get an inflatable pool and
do a water birth right here in the livingroom.
Okay.
Oh, my god Brett
hit me up on Grindr!
When? When he was here
or was after he left?
No! No, yuck! Not gonna happen.
Ages ago. Like before
he was on TV.
Yes, but I doubt
he remembers.
Although he did give me this weird
look when he walked in did you see it?
He did, he did give you a low weird
look. But did you two ever...?
Did you meet him after...?
- No, no.
If memory serves
he was apprehensive.
Oh, like he was cautious about
meeting because he's still...
- Yes.
-Yes.
His profile was Brett
spelled backwards and...
And his profile pic was on that area
between the neck and the nipples?
The memory does
serves I guess...
Maybe he was new in town
and went hunting, you know?
It was what you were doing?
- No, no.
I feel like I only ever checked
that stuff when I'm feeling lonely.
I get.
Hi.
Ken this is Thomas
he's my Doula.
Hi.
Yes, I just came
by to drop stuff.
You can stay if you want...
- No, no I can't.  I have a meeting.
Nice to meet you.
Okay, Greg, today I want
you to pick a room
Any room in the apartment.
Walk into it and find five things
that you could live without.
Okay.
And then throw them away.
And what purpose
does this serve?
Maybe it's just to feel
a little less overwhelmed?
And I mean not in the I feel
soft and life is too hard,
There's so much to it, kind of way I mean why
do we have three lemon shakers by the way?
How did you know about
the lemon shakers?
- A bunch.
- Yeah.
- So you do know what I mean.
- No I know, I know exactly what you mean.
My grandparents are...
They are... They were...
Richer than Ben Folds. Not
as rich as the Kardashians.
They had an Antiques
obsession anyway.
When they passed on...
I was left in their will so I know
exactly what you're talking about.
- Nice.
- Yuck.
-Who got the loop?
- My sister, thank goodness.
She got the house and
most of the stuff so.
Alright, I will purge.
I'm sorry you may not remember me
completely but we've seen each other.
- Greg! Oh my God!
- Hi Alex!
- Hi! How are you?
- I'm well, I'm well, how are you?
I'm ...
- I'm good...
- Good.
- Are you ... Are you pregnant?
- Yes, I'm pregnant.
Oh! my God! Who is the father?
Ken, Ken is.
- Wow!
- Yeah.
That... You...
That... that lasted a long time.
- Yeah.
- Good for you...
- Well, not that good for me now...
- Oh, I'm sorry...
- That's okay. That's okay.
What are you up to?
I... I don't know I'm ...
A little of this, a little...
I'm sorry, is that a weird
question to ask? I'm sorry.
- I didn't mean to pry.
- No, I... I'm in school.
I'm taking night classes at
the Art college Downtown.
- That's great! Congratulations!
- Yeah I...
I mean...
I still don't know what I'll be when
I grow up but it's a start I guess...
Sure.
And I never really
had the drive you did.
Yes, my drive...
By the way, I dropped
out of med school.
- So... why? You didn't...?
- Yeah.
- Because of the baby?
- Oh, no, no, no this happened way before the baby.
Way long.
What made you decide to quit?
You don't care
about this. It's okay.
Yes I do. Of course I do!
Your future was always
so important to you!
Well, things change.
You look great.
- You, you  look great.
- No I don't.
- Yes, you do.
- No, I am fat.
You are pregnant.
That's true, Yes.
Well, I'm pregnant.
Well...
Hey, do you... what are you doing right
now? Do you wanna grab some coffee?
- Can you even drink coffee?
- Oh no. Yeah. No. I can't.
But I can drink tea,
I can have a tea.
Okay.
Great. Well, good, good. I'll tell
you, it's so great to see you.
It was great seeing you too.
Alright I'll gonna check out my albums
and then we head out, sounds good?
Yeah. Alright.
I am so glad I run into you.
Yeah. It's so sweet,
yeah, wow! Good.
BUY 3 USED ITEMS GET
THE 4TH ONE FREE.
Hi.
I...
- Why are you here?
- I just came by to say hi.
See how you were.
Impressing you .
I really missed you.
I really missed you too.
Hey, did you see the new car?
- It's yours?
- Ours.
When I pulled in the
front I saw a Volvo,
And that the lights were on inside I
thought I was about to be a victim
Of middle-class, some
middle-class crime.
You were right.
I'm sad to say you were
right about everything.
I was... scared.
Scared and I...
I was so wrapped up in how
it was gonna affect me that...
I acted like the big prick
we both know I can be.
I wasn't even thinking about
how you should be feeling.
And you deserve a lot
better than that, Greg.
So I'm here to be better.
If you let me. I really
wanna be better and...
I'm gonna be better.
You know the best news?
- What?
- I'm really a father.
I'm so glad you're here!
Me too. I missed you.
I missed you so much!
You know I've been eating like
from snacks machine at work?
- Yeah?
- So like two weeks that count.
That's number one,
it's expensive.
Yeah, and they are loaded with
salted peanuts, it's horrible!
- What?
- I'm just...
I'm afraid I'm gonna
crush the baby.
People have sex when they're
pregnant all the time.
What if...if I just milked you?
I know that I look like a
cow but that is another.
I want you to fuck me.
Listen to you born again bottom.
Alright.
Ken?
Ken? It's time.
-Time for what?
- Time to get chicken out of  the oven.
- Ken, it's time to have the baby!
- What?!
Time to have the baby, Ken!
- Okay, okay, okay.
Here we go. Alright.
I don't... I can walk.
I can walk, I'm okay.
I can't believe
this is happening.
Yeah...
I had a long time to
get used to the idea.
Hello!
I've heard a baby is on the way!
PLEASE DO NOT DISTURB
Are you ready to come out?
Today is the day.
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine, I'm fine.
Okay, yeah, easy, easy
Yeah, I'm okay.
- Am I pretty?
- You are beautiful.
Come over here.
Over here, Greg.
Okay, Greg. You're doing well.
God! Shit!
Motherfucker!
Greg, I can see the head.
- What? What?
- Is he coming?
You're almost there, sweetie.
You're nearly there, okay?
- Okay, okay.
- Now, you can push.
Come on.
According to medical experts,
Since the first man
became pregnant,
An estimated fifty thousand babies
worlwide have been born to men
Miraculously the
number of C-sections
Have been unparalled with
the number of natural births.
Suggesting that men's
bodies have adapted,
Some point in the last
twenty five thousand years.
And that men giving birth
is just another bullet point
On the impressive timeline
of homo sapiens evolution.
Today, the Republican Congress
Which includes six nearly
pregnant legislators
Has rushed through a bill
proposing that pregnant men
Been paid paternity leave
Which is expected to
easily pass the house
Should be on the president's
desk early next week.
Awaiting his signature.
English Subtitles:
Pinky and the Brain
More after the credits
Today we are here with the
new Nashville transplant,
All the way from sunny
west Hollywood California.
Mr. Gino Ollie. He's recently
had his third baby.
The first which was
born in a toilet.
He just came out so unexpectedly.
I was at the club T and I thought,
I had got some food poisoning
from the crab leg,
I've had on a Chinese
buffet earlier.
You had no idea at all you were
pregnant. No signs, nothing.
No, no I mean,
I'm a large girl, so...
And everything went smoothly after
that, the baby was good and healthy?
What I mean, you know,
he has some issues
But you know he alright,
he run around,
He kinda talk sometimes.
And your second and
third children they...?
Oh they're fine. Trey,
Trey Trey, and Japanda.
- Lord, days are long.
- Japanda?
- Beautiful, beautiful name.
- Her daddy pick it.
Her daddy pick it.
We were at that
japanese restaurant,
You know what I'm saying?
He picked it right out Japanda.
- I loved it.
- You sound very proud.
What about the father or
fathers of these... babies?
Well, you know, they're fathers,
They're there. They're
around. They're around.
So they're helping you
take care of your children?
Their pay checks are helping
me take care of my children.
So they're not raising
your children...?
Well, you know, I mean...
How... I don't mean,
What does raising children
really mean anyway?
You know, I saying...
That's a good question Nashville what
does raising children really mean?