My generation,
we were born into war.
Giant monsters attacked our world.
We called them 'Kaiju'.
They came through the breach.
A gateway to another dimension, at
the bottom of the Pacific Ocean.
They were sent by an alien race
on the other side...
the Precursors.
We fought back...
built in our own monsters.
Jaegers, giant robots.
So big they needed
two pilots to run them.
My father was one of them.
He sacrificed himself
to help save the world.
I am not my father.
It's been 10 years since we won the
war and closed the breach.
Most of the world has recovered...
but few coastal cities never did.
And the world is still
picking up the pieces.
But some of us live
better in a broken world.
And squatting in half a mansion...
is better than paying for
some crappy apartment.
Now in the relief zones
you have to get creative,
you have to hustle.
Somebody else might eat
your breakfast.
And your cookies.
And your damn hot sauce.
You know out here we place a
different value on things.
The Pan Pacific Defense Corps
usually looks the other way...
as long as you don't go poking
around where you don't belong.
Say like a, decommissioned
Jaeger scrape yard.
Big risks mean big rewards...
and nothing pays more
than stolen Jaegertech.
Plenty of nutcases out here
trying to make their own Jaegers.
But they need the parts to do it.
So if you can steal what
no one else can steal...
you can live like a king.
Are you sure it's in here?
Power cords are stripped before
they get decommissioned...
but sometimes they miss the
tertiary plasma capacitors.
And that's a big score.
This one is still holding the charge.
You better hope so.
OK. Just calm down.
Just not get excited.
I'm just playing the odds here.
You cheated Barada and while you
escaped another Chau in Hong Kong.
- That was a misunderstanding.
- And stole from me, my own backyard.
Now I'm stealing for you.
Cycle of life.
- You good?
- You deliver...
Yeah.
- We good.
- Okay.
- Let's get rich.
- Nice.
Target locked.
Where is it?
Hey man, uh...
Just a little situation.
It says it's here.
It is supposed to be right there.
Well, you know what,
Let me just figure this out.
Somebody please kill this guy for me.
Target moving.
No, it's here. You wait, wait.
Some one else is in here.
Someone else has the capacitor.
Now, let's go. Come on!
Jake! Jake! Wait!
Son of a.
Go, go, go!
Spread out.
Come on, Jake!
- Boss, he went through here!
- Hurry up.
I see him. I see him.
Jake, Jake, Jake. Nice try.
- Yeah. We're good!
- Jake.
Jake, you son of a...
Target locked.
Hey. Get back here.
Target moving
HELP WIN THIS WAR.
END OF THE KAIJU WAR.
KAIJU WAR IS OVER.
SHAO PLANS TECH TAKE-OVER.
Jaeger MARK VI.
- How old are you?
- Old enough to kick your ass.
Let's take a second.
Back off. Back off.
- You build this to yourself?
- What do you think?
I think I can sell your
little toy for a whole lot of money.
Scrapper is not a toy
and she is not for sale.
The man holding
the pipe says yes.
So listen up...
- You led them here?
- It's impossible.
What the hell now?
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Yes. It works!
Hey! Get out!
What are you doing?
- No no. Stop.
- Where is it?
Don't touch that.
Hey! What are you doing?
- Where is the other one?
- The other what?
The other cray door,
A Jaeger needs two pilots.
Scrapper is small enough
to run on a single neural lobe.
Either you get out or you let me pilot it.
- Get out.
- Screw that.
- Told you she is not a toy.
- You're gonna get us killed.
- I can get us out of here.
- I just got us out.
Oh my God.
That's November Ajax.
Pilots of unregistered Jaeger,
this is the Pan Pacific Defense Corp.
Power down and exit your comm pod.
No, no, don't give up.
You give up way too easy.
That's what they think.
Stop.
You are in violation of
code ten, section 14,
operation of an unregistered Jaeger.
- Hang on.
- I am hanging on.
Hang tighter.
Seriously?
Stop.
See?
I just outplayed with November Ajax.
- No you didn't.
- I did.
Didn't.
OK. What do you got?
And I'm not getting out.
- One of those ion cells redundant?
- No.
- They are now.
- But we need that.
Get up to Ajax's head.
- What?
- Go!
Power down...
Low power warning.
Twelve percent.
- I told you we needed that.
- It worked didn't it?
Eleven percent.
How long before Ajax can
reboot its systems?
About that long.
Power down.
This is your final warning.
Alright! Lets go.
Look what you did
to my Jaeger you jerk.
You should have let me pilot it.
Oh like this is my fault.
You compromised my command center.
Wow. Your command center?
Sorry, sorry to hear that.
And you had no place to come in
and try to tell me what to do.
I go where I want.
This is different world.
Look where we're at.
Your top lip and your bottom lip
need then need to meet and become friend.
They need to close up. Alright?
Shut up! Shut up! Conversation done.
Junkyard baby.
- Why did you build it?
- What happened to the shutting up?
Says you wasn't gonna sell it.
What the hell was you gonna do?
Rob a bank or something?
I built her because one day
they are gonna come back.
The Kaiju.
And then do I'm not
gonna be stuck waiting
for some one else
to come save my ass.
Not like before.
You, let's go.
I do not wanna talk about it.
It's ridiculous.
I have the right to silence...
Hello, Jake.
Here we are again.
Just a stretch of bad luck I figure out.
Your father used to say
we make our own luck.
Yeah, well. Dad said a lot of things.
You were arrested in a rogue Jaeger.
Hold on a second. That wasn't my Jaeger.
This little kid, she's about...
You have priors.
This is serious.
That's why I need my big sis
to help me get
the hell out of here.
Just one last time.
They are not going to
let you just walk.
But there might be another way.
OK. See, that's what I wanna
hear, let's talk about.
The other way. Lay it on me.
What do I gotta do?
Re enlist and finish what you started.
I am not doing that.
I am too old to be a cadet.
I don't want you to be a cadet.
I want you to help train them.
Train who? Train what?
I am not training no damn kids.
The transport is standing by to
bring both of you to Moyulan.
Both of us?
You and your new recruit.
Mako.
I can't believe she
just hologramed me.
PPDC PILOT ACADEMY.
MOYULAN SHATTERDOME
CHINA.
Yeah. Look, I didn't have a choice.
I know I get it, but why me?
Why do they want me for the program?
You built and piloted
your own Jaeger.
These people like
that kind of stuff.
So then why am I just a cadet
and you get to be a ranger.
Valor Omega.
Oh my God, that is Valor Omega.
Scrapper.
You gotta be kidding me.
I didn't believe it when they
told me you were inbound.
- How you doing, Nate?
- It's Ranger Lambert.
Yeah, with love.
Well, This is a military base.
You remember how that works..
Ranger Pentecost.
- And you must be Amara Namani.
- Yes sir. Ranger, sir.
Let's get you squared away.
And and, try not to steal
anything while you're here.
Did that haircut just call you Pentecost?
As in 'Bad ass Stacker Pentecost'?
Pilot of Coyote Tango, hero
of basically the whole world?
- It's just a name.
- Yeah, really cool name.
Simtraining starts at 0600. If
you are late, you miss the day.
You fall behind,
you'll be on the next transport
back to wherever they found you.
That's Titan Redeemer.
And Bracer Phoenix.
She is a 3 man rig.
Saber Athena. I love Saber Athena.
She is the fastest in the fleet.
Did you know that?
Warning: stay clear of lift.
Which one is yours?
Gipsy.
- You pilot Gipsy Avenger?
- He used to.
Until his co-pilot got a better
offer in the private sector.
Jules Reyes, J-Tech.
Amara, cadet.
Jake.
- Ranger, apparently.
- Heard a lot about you, Pentecost.
- You know you still hold the record.
- What record? Shut up.
So how did they lure you back?
I mean it couldn't have been the pay.
Oh yes, it's a long story,
but if you
if you want to talk about it,
then we can meet up...
She is busy.
Eyes front, Pentecost.
- Come on, Renata, not the face.
- Sorry man.
I raise you, two shower chips.
Fold, Ilya. You need all the
showers you can getting there.
I have musk.
What you smell is musk.
Ranger on deck.
Audio system deactivated.
Cadets, this is Amara Namani.
She will be joining you in sim
training right and early.
And this is ranger Pentecost.
He will be helping me instruct you...
until I can find a new co-pilot
to replace Ranger Burke.
Anything you like to add?
Nothing you want to hear.
Malikova, get Namani squared
in and prepped for training.
- Yes sir!
- As you were.
Pentecost.
We are gonna be trained by a Pentecost.
So? Not like he was the one who died
helping close the breach.
He has never been in an combat.
Renata, ready for round two.
Yo. Ilya, do you see this?
- So, where should I...
- Heard you built your own real Jaeger.
Yeah, actually Scrapper.
I operated her too,
with this solo unit...
If you want to put junk together, be
a mechanic. Moyulan is for pilots.
- Hey come on. I got you.
- Thanks.
Jinhai. Ou-yang Jinhai.
So you and Vik, already buddies huh?
Vik is short for Viktoriya, but
you don't wanna call her that.
Yo, what's her problem?
Took her 3 shots to
pass the entrance test.
Don't think she likes
how you landed here.
Hey, it's not my fault.
Recruiters never come
around back home.
- Hey. Do you know any Russian?
- No.
I'll teach you something.
Calms her down.
Come on, let's get you squared away.
Hemispheres out of alignment. Warning.
- We need to reconnect.
- I know! I'm trying!
MAGLEV deactivated.
- I just can't get this.
- That sucked.
Drift simulation terminated.
AMARA FAIL
SURESH FAIL.
You know, when I heard you gave
November Ajax a run for his money
I thought we might have something here.
Now I'm not so sure.
How am I supposed to drift in this thing?
It smells like feet.
I didn't ask for excuses, cadet.
You put her up against Kaiju that
almost killed veteran pilots.
Doesn't make any sense.
Well maybe, she is not the only
one who doesn't belong here.
See Nate, I know you have
a problem with me,
but come on, she is just a kid.
So were we. That's the point.
You make stronger connections
when you are young.
And that kind up on makes
a better drift pilot.
Yeah, I remember the pitch. Thanks.
Ryoichi, Renata, you're up.
Show our new recruit how it's done.
What the hell are you wearing?
Jules loves it. Yeah she
told me it's nice to
finally have someone
with style around here.
Can't blame the girl.
I am sexy.
- You want a drink?
- Sure.
Thanks.
- Ice cream is up top.
- Yes.
So one more time around huh?
Prove your old man wrong?
No, I just came back to see if
your chin implant ever settled in.
Oh I think it settled
in quite nicely.
Yeah, it's very commanding.
Kids must love it.
Jake. These kids,
they look upto us.
We gotta show them that
we can work together.
Well... The war ended ten years ago.
You might just need to let that go.
Just whoosha...
After you understand,
you gotta make your...
Yeah...
Sorry me.
You have to understand
your enemy's objective...
to know you defeated them.
We still don't.
No, I can help you out with that.
See I'm thinking it has
something to do with them
sending giant monsters to
kick the crap out of us.
No, the Precursors won't
send Kaiju to flatten a
few cities if they were
trying to wipe us all out.
Look, me,
I don't have a problem with you man,
but I had to make a choice.
It was between your
pretty face and prison,
I chose your pretty face.
Well, I'm touched.
How many damn
toppings do you need?
Leave my toppings be man.
Don't mess my damn toppings.
So the cadets got like what?
Couple of months
before they graduate?
- Six.
- OK. I tell you what...
Every time you want to say
something soldiery to them,
I'll just nod...
or like "Yep, what he said".
Then before you know it,
they get to be pilots.
- And I get to get back to my life.
- Great!
You may get sooner what you think.
- How's come?
- Big dog and pony show tomorrow.
SHAO and her team are presenting
this new drone program they have.
- Could make us all obsolete.
- Sounds like my get out of jail free card.
You know, you confront all you want...
but you and I both know you
could have been great.
She doesn't do the
whole handshaking thing.
Doctor Newton Geiszler,
head of research and development
for SHAO Industries.
That's a nice firm grip you got there.
That's a much better look on you.
I guess it is better than
prison stripes. Barely.
I'm sorry? Is this him?
It's gotta be him. Right?
You're Stacker's kid.
Hey! I am Newt. I was a
big fan of your fathers.
Amazing speechwriter by the way.
Do you ever hear one where
he canceled the apocalypse.
- Newton.
- Hermann.
I was hoping you would be tagging along.
I could use your help in
an experiment I'm working on.
This will only take a moment.
I know how busy you are.
I do not want to impose, but...
Come on. You can't
impose on me. I mean...
We have been inside
each others heads right?
We saved the world.
We have drifted with a Kaiju.
You know, if we hadn't yanked that
Intel right of Kaiju's brain
Raleigh would have never been
able to close the breach.
That was you and that was me.
Technically more me, but we can
make this quick, or...
Deployment.
Of Jaegers. Their deployment to battle
it takes too much time, you know
The amount of damage a Kaiju
can inflict before they even...
Ah here. I think I found a solution.
You know I can never read
your...
Rocket thrusters? Huh.
Yeah, no.
There is no fuel in the world with
that kind of boost-to-mass ratio.
Not from this world.
- Now.
- Is that Kaiju blood?
Exactly.
I've discovered Kaiju
blood is highly reactive
when it's combined with
rare earth's elements.
- Cerium, lanthanum, gadolinium.
- I know that.
You can't be fooling
around with stuff.
You're gonna blow yourself up.
No one knows more about Kaiju
morphology than you.
- If you could just take a look.
- No, Hermann. I gotta stop you.
Look, none of this matters.
Once my boss's drones
are approved, deployment time.
This is gonna be a non issue.
Within a year buddy, we're
gonna have drones everywhere.
So you won't help me?
Look, why don't we talk it
over dinner in my place, OK?
You can finally meet Alice.
I don't need a hot meal Newt. What I need
is a solution, to a specific problem.
That's me. Bud,
I'm sorry. Duty calls.
It's been nice catching up.
Newton.
I still get nightmares
about what we saw
when we drifted with that
disgusting Kaiju brain.
But it was hell of rush, wasn't it?
I know, I'm terrible.
Yes, we shared a lab together.
Oh some crazy idea about
thruster pods on a Jaeger.
The man is completely harmless.
Could you say that again, and this
time about 80 percent slower?
I said, don't make me question
your loyalty. Understand?
What's to question?
Look I barely talk to that guy anyway.
My drones are the next
step in Jaeger evolution.
The system I designed process its commands
through a quantum data core.
This means that a single pilot can
operate the drone remotely...
from anywhere in the world.
As soon as the council
approves the deployment,
based on Secretary General
Mori's final report...
the days of struggling
to find and train drift
compatible pilots will
be a thing of the past.
And you think a bunch of
desk jockeys are better than us?
We are not here to shut you down.
Cooperation between our programs
has never been more vital.
- If there are any questions?
- Yeah, I got a question.
We are pilots, not a
bunch of office workers.
And now we're shouting.
There is no need to shout.
That was slick.
So how long till they order
the shutdown so I can go home.
I don't trust that tech.
Not yet at least.
Oh. It looked
pretty good to me.
Remote systems can be
hacked or compromised.
You got the key vote right?
So there you go,
it's your decision.
I wish I could just
go ahead and approve them.
Nearly half the counsel is backing Liwen.
They aren't going to like my decision.
Who cares what they like,
and what they don't like?
I tell you what?
I'm gonna go with you.
For moral support. Plus I
wanna get out of this place.
I'm glad you offered,
because I already requested
Gipsy Avenger as honor guard
at the counsel summit.
You know Gipsy is Nate's right.
His co-pilot works for Liwen now.
He needs a new one.
One that you already know
is drift compatible.
Alright, I'll do it.
I've got your back.
But I wanna be there when
you tell Nate, cause I
just want to see his face.
He's gonna be so pissed.
You see he's gonna stand there like
"Yeah, I don't think you
belong in a Jaeger, Jake.
Get out of my Jaeger. I
am handsome and sexy."
He is handsome. He is sexy.
Thank you, Jake.
SYDNEY
AUSTRALIA.
Welcome back. Lots of sunshine today.
The kick of the weekend, the city...
Good afternoon everyone.
Peter Overton broadcasting
from the Nine Studios in
Sydney with the latest...
So far police say at least, 49
officers injured.
Kaiju-worshipers in black
masks throwing bottles and rocks.
PPDC security in right gear
are attempting to weaken...
FLAGSHIP Jaeger ARRIVES
AT PPDC SUMMIT.
Gipsy Avenger, this is Marshal Chan.
All you
have to do is stand
there and look pretty.
- Stay focused and try not to fall over.
- Roger that sir.
Go for drop.
In three, two, one.
Drop it.
Jake.
Drift alignment unstable.
Relax. It's coming back to me.
You sure?
Ion cells activated.
Hey Nate.
We're in each other's head, remember?
So I would appreciate it if
you'd stop thinking about Jules.
Not gonna happen.
Well,
you still thinking about kicking my ass.
Not gonna happen either.
It's gonna be a long day.
Incoming transport.
- Warning.
- Gipsy to Command. You reading this?
Gipsy, this is Command.
Be advised that we have a rogue Jaeger.
Pilots of unregistered Jaeger,
power down and exit your
comm pod immediately.
I repeat: power down and
exit your comm pods now.
Missiles fired.
- Low powe warning.
- We are loosing power.
Jake, that Jaeger's power
reading is same as yours.
It's jamming our comms.
- Nate.
- Power's up.
- What do we do?
- Follow my lead.
Mako is hit.
- We gotta move.
- Activate the gravity split.
Mayday, mayday, mayday.
This is Charlie 052.
We have been hit and
we are going down.
- Going down!
- Sending.
- Mako.
- Jake. Wait!
Drift alignment failing.
Come on, Sarah. Do something.
This stupid brain thing.
So I'm not really good at
emotional stuff, but...
I really am sorry about your sister.
Half-sister?
Yeah, her family died during
the Onibaba attack.
My dad took her in.
And she was my sister, my family.
Why are you out of uniform?
Just had a lot in my mind after Sydney.
Guess I just wanted to be comfortable.
Don't let Ranger Lambert see you in that.
He might take the stick out of
his butt and beat you with it.
I think I'm safe.
So they still using Sarah.
I can't drift with her for some reason.
All the other cadets have
been training for years and I...
- I hate feeling like the slow keg.
- You gotta relax.
Or you're just grinding gears.
I'll help you out.
Got it, coach.
- Do not call me a coach.
- Alright, sensei.
Concentrate.
You have to make a good connection.
You can't do that if
you're yapping your gums.
- You ready?
- Ready.
All right.
See if we are drift compatible.
Come on girls. Get it.
Shoot. Come on.
Neural load is exceeding limit.
Stay focused Amara.
Remember: the stronger your
connection, the better you fight.
That's it.
Jump to me, honey.
Jump. Come on.
Don't hang on to the memory.
Just let it flow back through you.
Amara, jump in there.
Yeah come on. Get together.
Ready? One, two, cheese.
Got it. Wanna see?
Wait a sec.
Amara, you have to let it go.
Just listen to my voice.
Amara!
- Amara!
- Daddy.
Come on Jump.
- Amara!
Amara! We need to break the drift.
- Jump to me. Come on!
- I'm scared.
Baby. I'll catch you.
I promise. Come on.
- Come on, Amara.
- Jump.
Take it off.
You okay?
I was there.
I felt it.
I felt it too.
Jake, it's me. You there?
Yeah, I'm here.
Meet me in the lab right away.
The marshal wants to see us.
Alright, on my way.
You okay?
- What is it?
- A message from Mako.
She was trying to
send it from her copter
right before it went down.
It's a data package. High density.
Obsidian Fury was jamming comms.
How could her
signal get through?
- It didn't. At least not intact.
- So it's gone.
Gone is relative in digital round mate.
Running a modified factorial algorithm
I might be able to reconstruct
a few megabytes.
There.
Is that a Kaiju?
I am checking with PPDC Kaiju archives.
No matching in the database.
Keep looking. Whatever it is,
it was important to her.
I want to know why.
And I want to know who was
piloting that rogue Jaeger.
SHAO INDUSTRIES
SHANGHAI, CHINA
Hey, sorry I'm late.
I thought you were still in Sydney.
That's great.
I thought you'd be a
little more enthusiastic.
Yeah, no, I am calm.
This is great.
It's the timing of everything.
With that attack and
all it feels a little...
I was there.
I know what happened.
Neural connection terminated.
Yeah, I guess they do.
If you look at it sideways in
they maybe you can say that.
Sorry, what are you...
What is going on here?
48 is a...
Get it done.
Not a problem. Which...
You don't think there's a way?
Alright. Well, then you're fired.
OK. How about that?
Or maybe you are promoted.
I don't know.
We'll see how it goes.
Just get it done.
Give me this.
Hey honey, I'm home.
Sorry I'm late. Things were...
Things were crazy today, with
what happened in Sydney.
All those people.
It was not pretty.
My boss almost got killed.
That could have been bad.
Maybe I guess. I don't know.
That would have been great
actually, that one is
all over me. I mean I can't
get a break from her.
I am ranting. Enough
about work and enough
about her. Really I
should be focused on you.
How about we have a little
fun in the bedroom?
How was your day?
Oh that's great.
Yeah that's exciting.
What's that?
A little pick-me-up?
What can I say?
You are right by mine.
They are calling it Obsidian Fury.
He's never been a rogue like this.
News feeds they are posting
a dozen Jaegers at the memorial.
When I die, I want
that many send me off.
Your pops gonna make you work
with boobs when you wash out.
Jaegers do not show up
when the boob guy does.
- Your dad works with boobs?
- He is a plastic surgeon.
He does not just work with...
I'm not gonna wash out.
I'm gonna be a pilot.
Still, you die, man, they post
one Jaeger on your funeral.
Maybe half a Jaeger.
I heard this is where they found Amara
in half a Jaeger.
It was a whole Jaeger.
It just wasn't very big, Viktoriya.
Bigger is better.
- Kiss my ass.
- What did you say?
Kiss my ass.
Am I saying that right?
I have worked everyday in my
life to be here. You didn't do
anything. You are just picked
up from street like garbage.
Do you know where I learned that?
- On the street, you bitch...
- Ranger on deck.
- She jumped me.
- She does not belong here.
I don't care.
When I first joined the
Corps, I was like you.
Worse, I was nobody.
But that woman we lay to rest today, Mako
Mori, she said, "Whoever you are..."
"the minute you enter this
program, you join a family."
"And no matter what they do, no matter
how stupid they may act sometimes..."
"you forgive them and you move on."
So you start believing in that, in here.
Then you will start
believing it in a Jaeger.
The marshal is looking for you guys.
Says Gottlieb has found something.
It isn't something,
it's somewhere.
Severnaya Zemlya,
of Siberia's tiny peninsula.
- What is in Zemlya?
- Nothing anymore.
A facility roughly in this location was
used to manufacture Jaeger power core...
during war
but it was decommissioned years ago.
Why would Mako be trying
to tell us about an
abandoned factory in
the middle of nowhere?
Sir, a mission to take Gipsy avenger
to see what the hell is out there.
SEVERNAYA ZEMLYA SIBERIA
Scanning.
Looks like Mako's message was a dead end.
This place is abandoned.
Wait a second.
- Getting some weird readings.
- Incoming.
Take out his legs.
We gotta get out of here.
Plasma canon.
- I think we've pissed him off.
- Good.
- You remember our old move?
- Hell yeah.
- He looks hurt.
- Go for his power core.
Warning.
Pilots of Obsidian Fury,
Get the hell out of your comm-pod.
What the hell is that?
It's definitely Kaiju.
A secondary brain used to
control the hind quarters.
- How do they get into our world?
- There hasn't been a breach in 10 years.
The sensors would have pick that up.
I don't think there was a breach.
Kaiju flesh has a distinct radioactive
signature particularly to the anti-verse.
This specimen does not.
So... You saying that
it's from our universe.
The genetic fingerprints indicate
terrestrial modification techniques...
probably engineered from Kaiju
flesh left over from the war.
Precursors didn't do this...
Humans did.
That punk of slimy crap
was piloting obsidian fury?
We gotta get a look inside.
- Inside?
- That thing is part Kaiju.
Come on guys.
When are we ever gonna get a chance
to see something like this again?
Never, never would be good.
- You guys can stay here, I am going.
- No I'm not. Amara!
Guys, we should not be in here.
It's fused all the way to the system.
Like muscle tissue.
That's how it was able
to move like. Cool.
Yeah cool.
Working with boobs are
sounding better and better.
You shine the light over here.
Yes, just pull on the
guts of that weird Kaiju.
- What is it?
- I think it's some kind of...
- I told you not to...
- Go get help.
We are so screwed.
The security takes over.
We are done.
Is Jinhai OK?
He's got some scar,
but yeah, he'll live.
The Marshal plan on probation,
Meilin and Suresh too.
- They bleak wrong, all of them are out.
- No it's not their fault.
- I talked them into...
- Sorry, I talked to the marshal, but
you are dismissed from the program.
- Never belonged to here anyway.
- Really?
I used to say the same
thing a long time ago.
Still don't.
- Why did you sign up?
- We were at war.
My dad was leading the charge
and I thought
maybe I could see more of him.
Maybe even drift with him.
One night me and Nate got into it.
It was over something stupid. I can't
even remember what.
So, I climbed in an old Mark 4
just to show him,
I didn't him to be a great pilot.
- That is pretty dumb.
- Yeah.
How far did you get?
- Seven steps take or leave.
- How far did you get?
About 2 steps. And I blacked
out from the strain.
And the first thing I saw when
I woke up, was my dad.
He's standing right in front
of me looking stunned.
What did he say?
He said that I was out of the
program, he said I didn't
deserve to be in a Jaeger.
Look he said a lot of things.
A year later, my dad was gone.
I didn't get a chance to prove him wrong.
And more importantly, I could not
get a chance to prove it to myself.
You listen to me.
Don't let what other people
think of you define who you are.
You won't like where that takes you.
Do you understand?
And keep your head up,
then you might just be as
good looking as me in
this type of situation.
This face is set up well.
Beauty is a burden.
You will be alright.
SHAO Industries.
What?
Obsidian Fury has tech in it
made by SHAO Industries.
That's impossible.
Jules and her team scanned every
centimeter of that Jaeger.
Insulating meta-materials wound
counterclockwise in the shunt cabling.
SHAO is the only company
that winds in that way.
Amara, are you sure about what
you're telling me right now?
I stole a ton to make scrapper.
I thought it might be important.
Yeah. Thank you.
SHAO Industries.
- They don't even have a bio division.
- Not that we know of.
The cabling could have been
stolen, just like in Amara's
Jaeger. We're gonna need more
than that to connect it to SHAO.
What about Newt?
He'd have access to internal
records and shipping manifests.
Alright. Go see him,
keep a low profile.
I have a mission? Finally.
We will take over
Newt to the Marshal.
SHAO INDUSTRIES.
This isn't fair.
I'm sorry. You don't deserve this.
It was my fault.
This is on me.
Amara.
The next Jaeger you build,
make it a big one.
System online.
And we have delivery
at 100%, people.
A 100%. That's the way
that it's done. OK?
I told you we could do it and we did it.
- Malfunction.
- I losing up link to drone 375.
Why? Figure out why.
We will take what we know to the
council in person. Prepare transport.
Give me a second.
Get to Gipsy. Go!
All pilots, man your Jaegers
and engage the hostiles.
You can do it. You cool?
Yeah, super cool. Just stay calm.
I know. I'm heading up.
On my way.
Hermann, what are you doing here?
How did you get in?
I do have PPDC credentials, and besides
everyone else seemed to be little
bit preocupied occupied with the
killer drones your boss just set off.
- She used you.
- No.
She lured you with
money and a fancy title.
And while you were
basking in the glow,
she took your research
and she twisted it.
Help me stop her, Newton.
Help me save the world, like old times.
Sorry, technically you
helped me last time.
Let's get that straight.
Fine. Help me help you save the world.
What do you say?
I say... I say. Don't shoot!
Damn it, why can't
I get this language?
What is happening?
- Are those Jaegers?
- No they are Drones of SHAO Industries.
- What are they doing?
- I don't know. They just went crazy.
Get back to your quarters right now.
Yes sir.
Go, go, go!
- Get the hell out of here.
- Come on, get up.
Really? Now?
- Come on hurry!
- Little help, Hermann?
Learn how to use a gun.
Thank you, Newton.
You're done grabbing me,
let's take care of the drones right?
Everyone get out of the
lab, or I'll shoot you.
I'll shoot you twice.
You are officially fired.
Get out.
- What do we do? How do we stop this?
- There is a back door Hermaan.
- To what?
- To the drone sub routine.
I added a sub routine
just in case I wanna
get in here and poke
around down the road.
Sneaky bastard.
I know right.
CONFIRMED
INITIATING BREACH PROTOCOL
What did you just do?
What I have been planning
the last ten years.
I am ending the world.
HONOLULU, USA.
HONOLULU, HAWAII
BREACH DETECTED.
HONG KONG, CHINA
ANCHORAGE, ALASKA
BREACH DETECTED.
All pilots, breaches detected.
Drones in the field are opening multiple
breaches across the pacific rim.
Why would you do this?
Why would I do this?
Well, I guess I want it.
Normally, it's not really my style.
I don't know. Maybe I
hate you over treating
me like an insignificant
little joke of a man.
Maybe that's why he
did it, Hermann. I did it.
That's it. There you go.
There is the problem.
I am not just feeling
totally myself these days.
You.
Precursors.
Very good, Hermann.
You figured it out.
And as usual a step behind.
Newton, you are a good man.
You must stop.
- Hermann.
- You must stop it.
- Please, you must fight back, Newton.
- I am not strong enough.
He is not strong enough.
None of you is strong enough.
I'm sorry, Hermann.
They are in my head.
Oh hey, boss.
What the hell are you doing here?
I told you to get to quarters.
- All the doors are blocked.
- What do we do?
I mean 38% of your company
is fully automated.
It really wasn't very hard to
re allocate a little over here
and a little over there.
And slipping a little Kaiju
surprise without you noticing.
Stop. Wait. Newt has
no control over himself.
It isn't him. It's the precursors.
They must have
infected his mind when we
drifted with the Kaiju. Shut up.
Stay here. We are gonna
try and get to Gipsy.
- Are you ready for this?
- No you?
- On three. One two...
- Hello anyone there?
- Gottlieb?
- Jake, thank god.
We are under attack.
It isn't her, it isn't Liwen.
It was Newt.
The precursors. They infected him.
They are controlling his mind.
Gottlieb,
can you get him to disable the drones?
No, he got away.
Gottlieb, shut them down.
- It is trying to lock you out.
- Feedback loop.
What the hell is going on, Gottlieb?
Gottlieb, Shut them down,
or we're gonna die.
Shut them down.
Liwen has disabled the drones.
The breaches are closed.
I repeat the breaches are closed.
- Oh no.
- Oh no, what?
Three Kaijus have gotten through.
South Korea, Russian coast
and the East China Sea.
- Two Cat fours and a Cat 5.
- Copy that.
Get back to the dome.
We need all the help we can get.
- You guys okay?
- Yes Ma'am.
What do we got?
The reports are still coming in
but the drones attacked Jaegers
in SHATTERDOME across the rim.
Alright! How many
Jaegers do we have here?
Operational? Gipsy avenger, barely.
That's it?
- Yeah.
We need more Jaegers up and running
or this is gonna be a short fight.
Even if we can, all of our pilots
are dead or severely injured.
One disaster at a time. Let's
just focus on those Jaegers.
Namani. Come over here.
I need you to help Jules with
the repairs. Can you do that?
Said I was kicked out.
I'm kicking you back in.
She's pretty good at turning junk
into Jaegers. You good with that?
Hell yeah.
Right we got a lot work to do.
And not a lot of time.
We got incoming.
I brought some help.
Hakuja, Shrikethorn and
the big fellow... Raijin.
I took the liberty of
assigning the designations.
Well the spiky guy and the
big idiot are moving away
from the cities towards the ocean.
What does that mean?
Maybe they are trying to link up
with Hakuja in the East China Sea.
I bet Newt would know
what they are up to.
If we can get it out of him.
Yeah but we have to find him first.
Any Jaegers closer to
those Kaijus than us?
What was left of the
Chin-do and Sakhalinsk
drones tried to intercept.
Emphasis on tried.
- I am afraid we are all alone.
- There is gotta be something here...
Something in the East China Sea.
Maybe that's not
where they are headed.
Pull up a map of Kaiju
movement from the war.
- Pushing data to main display.
- Well you know something we don't?
You said we need to understand
our enemy's objective,
to know we've beaten them.
What if the Kaiju weren't blindly
attacking our city during the war?
What if we were just in their way?
Right here.
Mount Fuji, Japan.
Extrapolate for Hakuja,
Shrikethorn and Raijin.
- Mount Fuji? But why?
- Rare earth elements.
Mount Fuji is a volcano rich
in rare earth elements.
Kaiju blood reacts extremely
violently with rare earth
elements is the basis of my
fuel thruster experiment.
- That sounds bad. That's bad, right?
- Very.
Mount Fuji is active. A
geological pressure point.
Based on their blood
to mass ratio, the
Kaiju reaction would
cause a cascade event.
Igniting the Ring of
Fire around the Pacific Rim.
Billions of tons of toxic gas
and ash will spill into the atmosphere...
wiping out all life.
And finish terraforming the earth
for the Precursors.
We can't let them
reach Mount Fuji.
I'm gonna check with Jules
for the Jaeger repairs.
Even if we had a hundred Jaegers,
there is no way to intercept in time.
- What bout your thruster pods?
- No no no. They are not ready.
Can they be?
Well in theory. Maybe with your help.
Gottlieb, what does that mean
'in theory'?
Today...
it means 'yes'.
Power partially restored in sector 2.
Saber Athena, Guardian Bravo
and Bracer Phoenix are good to go.
Not a lot to work with.
Liwen keep passing fury-tech
in Gipsy that might help.
- Prep everything we got for deployment.
- OK. Don't get yourself killed.
You either.
Well that's confusing.
Let's just stay focused.
We got four Jaegers against
two Category-4s and a five.
It's better than just Gipsy.
- We still need pilots.
- We have them.
If my dad was here,
he would probably give you a big speech,
make you feel invincible.
I am not my father.
I am not a hero like he was.
Like Raleigh Becket
and Mako Mori.
But they didn't start out that way.
They started out as cadets,
just like you.
We remember them as giants
because they stood tall
because they stood together.
It does not matter who your
parents are, where you
came from who believed
in you and who didn't.
We are a family now, and we
are earth's last defense.
This is our time. This is our
chance to make a difference.
Now let's mount up and get
it done, do you understand?
Yes sir.
- Jaeger pilots, do you understand?
- Yes sir.
- Do you understood?
Then help me save the world.
Let's do this.
- System online.
- Initiating neural handshake.
- Establishing neural link.
- Amara, jump in there.
Neural handshake strong and steady.
So... How does it feel
to be in a real Jaeger?
Bigger is not bad.
All Jaegers, sound up.
Go and go for launch.
- Guardian Bravo, go.
- Saber Athena, go.
- Bracer Phoenix, let's go already.
- Copy that.
- Command, we are go for launch.
- Roger, Gipsy Avenger.
Ignition in ten seconds,
nine, eight...
seven, six, five, four...
three, two, one...
ignition.
Warning:
Exceeding structural limits.
What the hell?
My grandmother used to play it for me.
Keeps me calm.
What about me?
I am not calm, man.
I knew it would work.
TOKYO, JAPAN.
- Gipsy to Command, targets acquired.
- Roger that, Gipsy.
Everyone in the city is
secured in underground
shelters. You are
clear to engage..
Solid copy, going hard.
Bracer Phoenix, on me.
We'll take Raijin.
Roger that, Gipsy.
Saber Athena, Guardian
Bravo, you take the other two.
Copy that. It's our
turn to save the world.
- Let's hope so.
- On my mark. Three, two, one, mark.
Fire!
Gipsy, Raijin's face
plates are absorbing the
hits and throwing the
energy back at you.
Let's see it absorb this.
How many buildings
can this thing take?
Shrikethorn inbound.
Guys, we could use some
of the help over here.
- Right Now.
- Copy that, Saber.
- Vik, take out Shrikethorn.
- On it.
Saber Athena, Guardian Bravo coming
to assist. Activate the Arc Whip.
Yeah. That's nice.
You better run.
These things ain't that tough.
Bracer Phoenix, watch your six.
Hostiles inbound.
Copy that.
OK. Giant robots again. Alright.
Real original guys.
I am not impressed.
We've got movements,
multiple hostiles,
three kilometers south-east.
- Liwen, are you reading this?
- That is one of my automatic factories.
It was Newt. He is in Tokyo.
Locating his position.
- Hostiles, one foot away and closing fast.
- All Jaegers, brace for contact.
Disengage and brace for contact.
Let's go alright.
Go, go, go. Go baby.
Where are they going?
Well. He's pretty big.
All Jaegers, advance and
fire everything you got. On my command.
Go.
- Guardian, stand down.
- We have got this.
Negative. That is an order.
Freaking teenagers.
Go for the eyes.
- Which ones?
- All of them.
Ilya, Suresh, report.
Do you copy?
Come on guys.
Guardian Bravo, give me a sit rep.
You guys okay?
Guardian is down.
I'm here in the comm-pod. Suresh...
- Suresh didn't make it.
- Copy, Guardian.
Just stay put. We'll send you help
as soon as we can.
Bracer Phoenix, report.
You guys okay?
Little bit duped, but
we are still in the fight.
Us too, Saber.
I mean Saber Athena sir.
Saber, Bracer, prepare to intercept
to the following co ordinates.
Let's finish this, move
your ass and don't be late.
Copy. Bracer
Phoenix hauling ass.
Gipsy to Command, do you have
a tactical scan of the hostile?
Assessing data from the sensors.
We have it Gipsy, but
it's still compiling.
No time. Can you locate the brains?
Hostile's central brain
mass is heavily armored.
Your weapons won't be
able to penetrate.
What about a secondary brain?
This son of bitch has one of those?
Hostile has three secondary brain,
one for each component Kaiju.
Sending Intel.
Package confirmed from Saber Athena.
Confirmed from Bracer Phoenix.
Alright team, follow
my lead and stay alert.
Fire up some of that
Fury-tech Liwen grabbed us?
Read my mind, partner.
- Eject eject.
- Damage detected.
All pilots eject.
Warning:
Neural power exceeded limit.
Nate. Stay with me, Nate.
Get up, Nate.
Pilot down.
Get up from that, you pile of junk.
Bye.
Liwen, is there anything
that you can do to help?
I need more time.
We don't have any. If the
hostile reaches Mount Fuji...
Understood. I'm not
gonna let that happen.
You can not operate Gipsy
without a co-pilot.
The strain will tear
your mind apart.
- What do we do now?
- Regroup with the others.
Gipsy Avenger, this is Amara Namani.
Stand by for assist.
- Amara don't.
- You won't make it.
- Shut up.
- Don't. Don't.
- I told you.
- Since when do I listen?
Amara, you're up..
What are you doing?
Getting the hell out of your way.
You got this, brother.
Ejection sequence initiated.
Ejection sequence successful.
- Are you ready for this?
- Only way to find out.
Standby, Command.
Initiating neural handshake.
That was supposed to
be epic, but it was not.
Definitely not.
Warning: test kit failure
Multiple systems offline.
- Reboot.
- Yeah OK. I'm on it.
Command to Gipsy. Hostile
is two kilometers
from the summit of mount
Fuji and closing fast.
Gottlieb, do you have
enough fuel left in your
thrusters to launch us
into the atmosphere.
- The Atmosphere?
- Yeah.
Possibly, but there won't be
enough to slow your re entry.
We don't need to slow down.
We're gonna drop gipsy
right on top of that thing.
- I just ejected my escape pod.
- You have to use mine.
Jake, there is only one thruster
with enough fuel remaining.
- Sending location.
- Alright, checking.
We are too far away.
We are not gonna make it.
Gipsy Avenger, transport inbound.
Remote systems are online.
Sending help.
Scrapper.
I have located the
thruster pod. Stand-by.
Come, move them little leg.
The thruster's way too strong.
There is no way we could hold onto it.
- Liwen, what do you got?
- I can weld it to your hand.
- I have upgraded Scrappers weapons.
- Nice. I was actually gonna do that.
- No you wasn't.
- Yes I was.
- We only got one shot at this.
- Yeah. Let's make it count.
I'm stuck.
Stay there. Extra weight
we can drop on that thing.
- She's falling apart.
- We are almost there.
- We're drifting off course.
- Use the plasma canon.
- Disengaging safety protocol.
- Plasma canon engaged.
Warning:
Exceeding structural limits.
- It's working.
- Structural failure.
Hold on.
- Come on.
- Target left.
Jake, Amara, you need to eject.
Disconnect, Amara. Disconnect.
I'll catch you, I promise.
Come on.
I have got you.
Gipsy to Command,
we're getting the hell out of here.
Escape pod failure.
I'm sorry.
For what?
We gotta save the world.
Your dad would be proud.
Scrapper, come here.
Hurry up.
Move.
20 kilometers to impact.
Get out of there.
Go. Go.
We are in. Close the door.
- Hang on.
- I am hanging on.
Hang tighter!
OK. You know what? Plan B.
Always a plan B.
Anyone who's listening,
this is ranger Lambert.
- Be advised, we just got ourselves a Newt.
- Copy that.
There he is. I'm glad
to see you okay man.
You too, brother.
I knew you could do it.
Well, I had a little of help.
- Nice work, ranger Namani.
- Thank you sir.
I have never seen snow before.
About all the things you know this
right now, you know since snow.
Big dead Kaiju is right over
there and I do not know...
Is this the part where you're gonna
give me one of those big dumb speeches?
Did everyone think it was
dumb, or it was just your opinion?
How many times did you practice
that in front of the mirror?
It was motivational. You can
be who ever you want to be.
- Fire.
- OK. Now are we going to play that?
- I am a natural. Give me a break.
- No you're not a natural.
There you go boom.
We did it.
Subtitled by Clarity.
Previo: RQ & Mandy.
You think this is over huh? You think
you saved your crappy little world?
We are gonna keep coming.
We are never going to stop,
and sooner or later your
luck is going to run out.
The things in your head,
the Precursors?
Tell them we are not afraid.
Tell them next time,
they will need to worry
about coming for us.
Because we are gonna
come for them.