REPORTER: Coach Royal, I'm Casey
Addison from The Daily Texan.
ROYAL: Hello. Hey, sit down.
REPORTER: Thanks
for meeting with me.
Sure. Sure.
Coach, I'm writing a story
about legendary
Texas football players,
and you're a legend yourself.
Was I a player?
Why,yes.
You were a great
football player
for the Oklahoma Sooners
in the late 1940s.
I'll be doggone.
I knew that.
But you coached UT
and won three
national championships.
Yes.
Texas had 30
All-American players
while you were coaching.
Which one had the
greatest impact on you
and the program?
Freddie.
Freddie Steinmark.
I'm sorry, Coach,
but Freddie Steinmark
wasn't an All-American.
No.
But he was my
All-American.
You see,
a player's skills
and character
are influenced years
before I ever meet him.
I gain the benefit from
all the other coaches
who instilled fight
and grit in their hearts.
MUZZY: The Rough
Riders' creed,
"I will play hard and clean,
and I will not be a quitter!"
(19605 MUSIC PLAYING)
What's most important
is courage.
It's not a disgrace
to be beaten.
The greatest disgrace is
to quit or to turn yellow.
You got that?
ALL: Yes, sir.
Let me hear it again.
Yes, sir!
Now, get your butts out
there and practice hard.
Steinmark.
Stay here.
(SIGHS)
You did good last game.
You scored a lot
of touchdowns.
But you would have done better
if you'd run in a straight line.
You get to the
end zone quicker.
You zigzag too much.
My dad taught me
to run that way.
When you play for
your father's team
on Tuesdays and Fridays,
you can zigzag.
On Mondays and Saturdays,
you run a straight line.
You got that?
Yes, sir!
Get out there.
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
Wind sprints, let's go!
GLORIA: Oh, look, Sammy
wants some peas. Come on.
You want a little pea?
FRED: Come on, Sammy.
GLORIA: All right, I want you to
finish the whole thing for me. Okay?
If you're gonna
be a great player,
you gotta get some meat
on those little bones.
How did my boy do
at practice today?
I scored five touchdowns.
Six.
Our guy's gotta work
a little bit harder
out there on the field
because he's always
the smallest one.
Isn't that right?
I try as hard as I can.
What makes a winner
is learning that they
can always try harder.
Is that enough
Parmigiano?
Yes, Mama.
Maybe a little
bit more. Hmm?
We gotta get you
to Notre Dame.
That's right. Great education
and great football.
Give me a kiss.
Huh? Come on.
That's my QUV-
RED: When I took this job,
they told me that
you haven't won
a division championship
in 25 years.
Haven't beaten
Lakewood in 15 years.
The pure and simple fact
is you all are pathetic.
But not for damn long.
We will beat Lakewood,
we will win the
conference championship,
and we're not
stopping there.
Anybody who doesn't get
on board with my plan
can move your sad sorry ass
out of my eyesight
now and forever!
Are there any questions? Good!
Now, we got a new kid
here from California.
And he may be
just what the doctor
ordered for this team.
He's gonna be carrying the
rock a lot for us this season.
Any questions?
I didn't think SO.
Now we prepare for war.
Out on the field! Now!
Now! Now!
Not a minute to waste.
ASSISTANT COACH 1: Let's go.
Go!
ASSISTANT COACH 22 Hustle up!
Finish strong!
ASSISTANT COACH 1: Let's go,
gentlemen. Pick it up!
Freddie Steinmark. Glad
you're part of the team.
You'll really
help us this year.
I wish I was back
in California.
It's pretty nice
here in Colorado.
This team's nowhere
near as good
as the one I was on there.
It Will be.
Yeah, sure it will.
Now that you're on the team,
I say state championship.
You haven't won your
division in 25 years.
You're talking
state championship?
You're nuts.
(19605 MUSIC PLAYING)
Go!
(PLAYERS CHEERING)
ASSISTANT COACH 2:
Atta boy, Freddie!
(PLAYERS APPLAUDING)
(BOTH PANTING)
You're really fast
for a big guy.
We can use you this year.
DEBBIE: Just pretend like you've
gone to school here all your life.
Like anywhere else,
the jocks and the
cheerleaders rule the school.
And the jocks
are mostly jerks.
Except one.
Freddie Steinmark.
He's sweet, he goes
to mass every day,
and he is, by far, the cutest
boy you will ever see.
He broke every
scoring record
both in basketball
and football.
I don't like sports.
You don't have to like sports
to have a crush on Freddie.
You just need a pulse.
MALE STUDENT: Hey, Freddie!
He looked at you.
He's okay.
FRED: Go.
DEBBIE: He's here every day
after his regular practice.
His dad trains
him pretty hard.
Time!
Maybe it's not his dad.
Maybe it's what he wants
to do to get better.
All I know
is he is
exceptionally dreamy.
Time!
(PANTING)
11.9. Great! Great!
Do it again.
He stares at you every day
and never says a word.
Maybe he's shy.
The most popular kid
in school is shy?
I doubt that.
Well, what do
you think it is?
Maybe it has something to do
with him being so religious.
No.
Boys that go to mass every
morning can't talk to girls?
I don't know.
Hustle up. We still
got five more.
Be right back.
(STAMMERING) You have
to start the car.
Here.
No, I can't.
(CAR ENGINE STALLING)
No, I don't want them.
Debbie!
This is so embarrassing.
Hi.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
(STAMMERING) You know,
we were just looking for a...
Picnic.
Picnic area for
a bunch of girls...
Surprise party.
For a surprise party
for a bunch of girls.
Do you wanna go
out sometime?
What?
Do you wanna go out?
Go out with me?
Yeah.
Okay. Yeah. Yeah,
that would be great.
Great. When?
I don't know.
How about tonight?
If I run about 20 more
reps, I might get the car.
Tonight.
I'll just have to ask...
All right.
Some other time.
No, tonight will
be fine. Right?
Yeah?
Hmm?
Yeah.
Great. What's your address?
It's 2678 Pear Blossom.
Oh. Nice area.
Thank you.
How about 7:00?
7:00 is perfect.
It's perfect.
Great.
Thanks, Debbie.
Uh-huh.
Okay, I'll see you then.
Okay.
Please start the car.
(19605 MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
LINDA: Is this your car?
No, no, it's my dad's.
I have to get it back
by 8:00 tonight.
He has to be
at work at 9:00.
What does he do?
He's a Denver policeman.
Oh.
At least, that's
his nightjob.
During the day,
he's a security guard.
Hard worker.
Very.
My mom, too. She's a
clerk in the hospital.
I'm gonna take you
to my favorite spot.
Okay.
FREDDIE: I can see
my whole life,
present and future,
from right here.
Look, there's Wheat Ridge High
field, where I'm playing.
Yeah.
There's Boulder,
University of Colorado,
where I might be playing
if Notre Dame
doesn't offer me.
And there's Denver,
the Broncos.
That is, if the Chicago
Bears don't draft me.
I don't know that
much about football.
You Will.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(MARCHING BAND PLAYING)
MALE FAN 1: Let's go, farmers!
Let's go, Freddie!
Fifteen straight times
you mullets have
lost to this team.
The tide will turn tonight.
This game.
Now,
get out there and
kick their butts!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(WHOOPING)
PLAYER 13 Nice hit, Freddie!
(CHEERING)
There we go.
LAKEWOOD QUARTERBACK:
Set, hut!
PLAYER 22 Go, Bobby!
Come on. Come on!
Come on, Bobby!
That's it.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Yeah!
PLAYER 3: Come on, Freddie!
MALE FAN 23 Yeah!
(CROWD BOOING)
Come on. Get him.
This is your team.
Get them ready.
Offense! Huddle up!
FREDDIE: (PANTING)
All right, guys.
We will not lose this game.
This streak ends now.
We have 57 seconds
to go 82 yards.
Not a problem.
Right?
ALL: Right.
(LOUDLY) Right?
ALL; Right!
Let's go out and do it!
(ALL CHEERING)
Come on!
What do I do?
Just give the damn
ball to Freddie.
Down. Set. Hut!
Come on, Freddie!
Go!Go!Go!
Freddie, go!
Go! Go! GO!
Run! Freddie, run!
(PANTING)
(BUZZER SOUNDING)
Oh, my God!
(ALL CHEERING)
Yeah! That's all right!
Well done, young man.
Good game.
Thank you, sir.
Neverseen
anybody your size
do as much damage
as you do out there.
Thanks. You do a lot
of damage yourself.
Wish I had your size.
You'd be dangerous.
Hey, you want a ride?
Nah.
Your dad's always
there, watching.
Every practice,
every game.
All my life.
(LAUGHS)
Did he play when
he was younger?
He was an amazing athlete,
the best in every
sport he ever tried.
If he hadn't gotten
in a car accident
and banged up his knee,
he would have been
a Major League Baseball
player for sure.
So he's like one
of those dads
living his failed
dreams through you.
He just wants me to
give everything I have
in whatever I do,
all the time.
School, sports. It's
all the same to him.
I've seen a lot
of dads like that.
What matters to us both is
for me to get a scholarship.
We don't have a lot
of money for tuition.
I'm sure you're gonna
get plenty of offers.
So far, nothing.
I bet you don't
have that problem.
So many, I don't know
what to do with them all.
Must be nice.
Hey, you ever hear of Army's
two great running backs,
Doc Blanchard
and Glenn Davis?
They were called Mr. Inside and Mr.
Outside.
That's us.
Sounds good,
Mr. Outside.
Okay, Mr. Inside.
Hey, one more thing.
Lakewood used to be the
number one team in the state.
You know we're not
gonna lose a game
for the rest of the year.
Sounds good.
FRED: I appreciate you taking
my call, Coach Crowder.
Just wanted to make sure
you got my letters.
Well, I will tell him you said that, sir.
Thank you.
(FRED LAUGHS)
Tell him he's also
a 4.0 student.
165, with room
to put on more.
Well, I assure you, sir.
He weighs more
than 145 pounds.
A junior college.
Well, thank you anyway.
Who's next?
The Air Force. They
recruit smaller players.
I have to study.
(SIGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
You wanted to
see me, Coach?
The University of Texas.
What about it?
Mike Campbell, their
defensive coordinator,
is somebody who
trusts my word.
And he thinks a little
different than most coaches.
University of Texas? Me?
No guarantees, of course.
Did they show
any interest?
Well, he came up yesterday
to recruit Bobby.
Oh, well, that's why.
(SCOFFS)
Hold on now.
I made Iron Mike watch
a season worth of film.
You got his attention.
Okay. What do I do now?
They want you and Bobby
to fly to Austin this weekend
to meet Coach Royal.
You need to sit down, son?
No, I have to go.
I have to tell my dad.
Now, wait.
I'd be careful about
getting hopes up.
They meet with a lot of kids
without making them an offer.
Right.
It means a lot they
want to see me.
Thanks, Coach.
University of Texas.
Doesn't look real.
Been a lot of great football
played here over the years.
Never thought
I'd see this place.
If I have anything
to do with it,
you'll be playing here.
But it's not up to me.
You ready to go meet him?
Yes, sir.
All right.
Freddie Steinmark.
Yes, Coach, that's me.
Watched film on you
again this morning.
You run like you got a school
of minnows in your pants.
Thanks.
I like the way
you attack.
I try to teach my kids
to drive through
the ball carrier.
Notjust lay him
on the ground.
Looks like that just
comes natural to you.
I'm thinking about you
playing some safety
and maybe returning punts.
How's that sound to you?
Maybe you need
some time to decide.
Um...
No. No, sir.
What is it, son?
Well, every other
coach just thought
I was too small to play.
ROYAL: (CHUCKLING) Too small.
Well, I'm 5'10".
I was an okay
college football player.
Okay? (LAUGHS)
He quarterbacked the
University of Oklahoma
to an undefeated
season in 1949.
ROYAL: Mike.
You want me to
play here for you?
Son, I'm offering you
a scholarship
to attend the University
of Texas and play football.
How can I be more plain?
You will not regret
giving me the chance, sir.
Becoming a Longhorn
and part of this football team
is a dream come true.
Give me my hand
back now, son.
Sorry.
As for you.
(SIGHS)
Well, I figure you Colorado
boys can be roommates.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
All right. That's
all for today,boys.
We'll be seeing you back here
in two months. All right?
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
Sir, Coach.
Thank you very much.
Thank you. Thank you.
(LAUGHS) Wait for it.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(FREDDIE AND BOBBY WHOOPING)
Never gets old.
(CHUCKLES)
Thanks for the ride.
Why didn't you call?
I kind of wanted to
tell you in person.
So, what happened?
I can't believe that place.
Everything is bigger
and better in Texas.
And that means?
Coach Royal, he, um...
He offered me
a full scholarship.
What?
I'm so happy for you, son.
You worked so hard for this.
Answered prayers.
Yes.
FREDDIE: So now,
lhavetolook at everything
in a totally different way.
Over there, Wheat Ridge
is where I used to play.
University of Colorado.
No, thanks.
You had your chance.
Nope.
And None Dame had
the“ chance, too.
You know, I wanted to
go there all my life.
Till now.
My dream is to
play them some day
and show 'em what a
terrible mistake they made.
You know what?
Forget the Broncos.
I'm going with my
first choice now,
Chicago Bears.
Coach Royal believing
in me makes me think
anything is possible.
I have a surprise for you.
Uh-oh.
Oh, no. It's a good surprise.
Uh-huh?
Actually, it's a great one.
It's too dark.
It's an acceptance letter.
From Texas.
What? How'd that happen?
I applied and was accepted.
Well, what about your
plans to go to CU?
No. You and I are
part of a bigger plan.
Well, I know, but I didn't
know you were going to...
No, no. Spanish is my major.
They have the biggest
department in the country.
Ithoughtyour
parents said
there was no way they
would ever let you...
lam very persuasive.
(LAUGHING)
Yes, you are.
Yes.
(LAUGHS) You're going.
We're going to have
the best time in Austin.
Icanfivwmt to get started. Yeah?
FREDDIE: Texas!
LINDA: Yeah!
FREDDIE: Wh00!
Gentlemen,
impress me.
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
CAMPBELL: Drop it! Drop!
Come on, move those feet.
You can do better than that.
Come on, pOP UP-
Hope Coach is
right about you.
Yes, sir.
Better keep up
with your Colorado
buddy, Mitchell.
He's here because of you.
Come on! Move those feet now.
Come on, Mitchell!
Quit dogging it.
That was awesome, Bobby.
Doing great, buddy.
Steinmark, you're up.
Let's go. Come on.
Let's see some hitting.
UT FOOTBALL PLAYER 1:
Let's go, now!
Set, hut!
(ALL CHEERING)
CAMPBELL: Who's next?
Reynolds, go!
Nice pop for
a Colorado boy.
UT FOOTBALL PLAYER 2:
Set, hut!
There you go, Freddie.
Good hit.
Oh.
(PANTING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Hey. Want a burger?
BOBBY: No.
What's the matter?
My brother Mark
joined the army.
Why are you so upset?
You ever hear of a little
place called Vietnam?
Yeah, but not everyone who
joins the army is sent there.
He's training to be
a helicopter pilot.
I'm going to get a beer
at the rectory.
You want to come?
A beer at the rectory?
Yeah.
Some priest named
Father Bomar
invites the football players
over to get away, relax.
Have some brews.
A Priest?
(SCOFFS)
Yes, altar boy, a priest.
(DOOR CLOSES)
They use the freshmen
as cannon fodder.
Since we aren't eligible
till sophomore year,
they don't care how much
the varsity pounds us.
I'm worried about
you getting hurt.
Me? I'm invincible. Never
been hurt in my life.
My roommates tell me
that football players
are the targets for
every girl in this campus.
You can't possibly
be worried about me.
Well, you were treated
special in high school.
And if you end up being
a star on the team,
which I know you will,
they're going to
treat you like a god.
♪ I can't see me
loving nobody but you
♪ For all my... 4“
Stop. That's too much, stop.
(MUFFLED smenue)
Freddie! Freddie!
They moved me to a more
advanced Spanish class.
Congratulations.
My teacher, very
good-looking.
Really?
Yeah. Jealous?
Hey, Captain.
Good to see you.
Do I know you?
Freddie Steinmark.
I'm a freshman.
I'm on the team.
Welcome aboard,
young pup.
It's Bill Bradley.
One of the top quarterbacks
in the country.
He's going to lead us
to a National Championship.
(LAUGHS) Young pup?
Upperclassmen don't normally
even talk to freshmen
till spring practice
next year.
Oh, so he honored you?
Yeah, I guess he did.
Let me lay this out
as plain as I can.
A 6-4 record is unacceptable
for Texas football.
This year, things are going
to be a little different.
No, a lot different than anything
we've ever done here before.
Gentlemen, football
doesn't build character,
it eliminates the weak ones.
We're about to
weed out the weak.
Come on, come on, come on.
Let's go, boys. Get them up.
ROYAL: We got 200 players
fighting for a spot
on a 100-man roster.
CAMPBELL: Come on.
Get that butt down, Mitchell.
ROYAL: That means, by the end of this
two weeks' spring practice session,
100 of you are going to quit,
get hurt,
or we'll kick your
ass out of here
for not being good enough
or not working hard enough.
Faster. Double. Double time.
Let's go! Double time.
We are going to
stay here all day.
ROYAL: No one is guaranteed
a spot or a starting position.
Each week, you will be rated.
Come on, Steinmark,
get up there!
Let's go, ladies!
Come on. Let's go!
ROYAL: Some of you
who played this week
won't be in the same
spot next week.
Move! Move! Faster.
Let's go! Faster!
ROYAL: Last spring,
we didn't wear pads
until the second week.
Or get into the nutcrackers or
eye-openers until ten days in.
This spring, we start now.
(PLAYERS CHEERING)
CAMPBELL". Come on,
come on, come on, come on.
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
Happy hour.
I don't think I'm pushing
these boys hard enough.
(CHUCKLES)
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
ROYAL: You ran 30 off
this week alone.
That Steinmark kid.
I can't make him sweat.
The more I push him,
the more he answers the call.
I don't know what they're putting
in the water up there in Colorado,
but we could sure use
some of that down here.
(CHUCKLES) Okay,
Frank, we'll do that.
(19605 MUSIC PLAYING)
FREDDIE: All right.
Let's see what you got.
Show me. Yeah, that's right.
Lighten your feet.
Yeah, I'm ready.
Oh! Wheeler's pass,
intercepted by Steinmark,
takes it back all the way!
Oh, it's a monster tackle!
Wheeler takes Steinmark down.
The last-ditch saving tackle.
(YELLING)
LINDA: Stop. Stop.
Steinmark is down.
(LAUGHING)
This summer went by too fast.
Mmm. Not fast enough.
I can't wait to start
practice and play for real.
You know, you got nothing
but football on your mind.
That's not true.
Hmm?
It's not.
Gentlemen, we're going to
implement a new offensive set.
It's called
"the triple option."
Now that means we're primarily
going to be a running team.
And I guarantee you
no one we play this year
will have ever
seen this offense.
Now, quarterbacks.
Bradley, Norvvood,
Street, Phillips.
How you read the defense
and make instantaneous
decisions
will determine whether
this system works or not.
So, we're going
to try you all.
And whoever can best
handle this challenge,
runs the show.
Okay?
All right, let's give
our quarterbacks three.
Let's get to work.
PLAYER: Let's do it, come on!
Down, set, hut!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Bill, where are you going?
Down, set, hut!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Smart play, James.
Set, hut!
Man, that kid's
got an arm.
Yeah, he's a little
slow on the read,
but he can throw.
Set, hut!
We're either going
to go 10-0 or 0-10.
We sure as heck
ain't gonna go 6-4.
(JAMES SINGING)
Fast Freddie.
Hey, slick.
Boy, you showed them how it's
done out there, little dink.
Little dink?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hey, you and me need
to stick together.
You lead the defense, I'm
going to lead the offense.
I'm a long way from
leading anybody.
Hey,bubba,
I know a gamer when I
see one, all right?
Give us a couple years,
you and me are going
to be running the show.
I won't be
running the show.
And you got the number one
quarterback in the nation
in front of you.
Ooh!
Just a matter of
time, Fast Freddie.
FREDDIE: Hey, Bobby. Hey.
Hey, what's the matter?
They're moving me
to offensive line.
Guess they're trying
to make me quit.
Look, I don't want your
Pollyanna bullshit now.
Okay.
But you're not
going to quit.
Why is that?
Because you promised
your brother you wouldn't.
CAMPBELL: Steinmark.
Coach Royal wants to see you.
In his office.
Yes, sir.
Come on in, Freddie.
Sit down.
We don't have
a defensive back,
including upperclassmen,
who understands their
position as well as you do.
Hell, it's like you
got a second sense
of where the damn
ball is going
before it even gets there.
(LAUGHS)
We think you may
be the toughest kid
we got on the team.
Thank you, sir.
We're moving you up.
Starting safety.
You'll be the first
sophomore starter
I've had since
Tommy Nobis.
And he was the greatest
player I ever coached.
I'm honored, sir.
ROYAL; All right.
Now, there's
a lot on you, son.
We wouldn't be
making this move
unless we knew
you could handle it.
Yes, I can.
I definitely can.
ROYAL: Good.
Because this season it's going to
be Texas smash-mouth football.
Offense and defense.
Can't wait.
Glad to hear it.
(CROWD CHEERING)
JOE: After a very
disappointing first contest
with Houston,
we'll see if the Longhorns
and their newfangled
triple option offense
can get untracked
here at Tech.
That was a bold gamble
which did not pan out.
No question.
Coach Royal
is on the hot seat.
PHIL: The fact is,
the fans are restless.
If they don't win
this game today,
you can just about
write this season off.
Here you go.
BILL: Set, hut.
JOE: Bill Bradley is really
struggling with this offense.
PHIL: And yet
another turnover.
Oh, my God.
BELLARD: 86, cover the flat.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
One, two.
(G ROANS)
ROYAL: Take a knee.
MEDINA: Listen up.
ROYAL: You are
embarrassing me,
the coaching staff,
your family,
the University of Texas,
its fans.
But most of all,
you're embarrassing
yourselves.
Where in God's good earth
is your pride, gentlemen?
Is that how you want people
to remember you? Mediocre?
There is a hell of a fight
going on out there.
We ought to get in it.
CAMPBELL: Let's g0!
(PLAYERS AGREEING)
BILL: Down. Set, hut!
Aw! Damn it!
JOE: More of the same here
in the second half, Phil.
I don't know what Coach Royal
was thinking
with this offense.
PHIL: It's a bit of
a train wreck, Joe.
(SIGHS)
Where's Street?
Street!
16!
CAMPBELL: Street!
Yes, sir?
Get your helmet on.
Yes, sir.
CAMPBELL: Defense, get ready.
Get in there.
Yes, sir.
Hell, he can't
do much worse.
What is this? We've
got a change here, Phil.
New quarterback?
Coach called you out.
PHIL: Joe, it looks like
a desperation move to me.
James Street is
raw and unproven.
JAMES: What the hell
are you doing? Let's go.
Y'all want to play
some Texas football?
All right. All I ask is you guys
stick with me one play
at a time, all right?
Can we do that?
PLAYERS: Yeah.
Down. Set, hut!
JOE: Street pitches it to Koy.
For a big gain!
There you go.
JOE". There goes Street.
Spin move.
Touchdown, James Street.
FREDDIE: He got it.
Set, hut!
JOE: Touchdown, Steve Worster.
I guess he just needed
the right quarterback
to make the triple
option work.
Good read, James.
JOE: That might be the end
of Super Bill Bradley,
one of the top quarterbacks
in the country.
Replaced by a
fourth-string quarterback
we've never seen before.
JOE: Despite
a strong second half,
Texas is winless in
the first two games
of the last two seasons.
And that hasn't happened
in 72 years.
First to arrive,
last to leave.
I like how quiet it is
before everybody gets here.
What you reading there?
Chemical Engineering.
You are one of the darnedest
players I've ever seen.
Sure wish I had
a lot more like you.
Yes, sir.
Looks like we're the only
ones left on the team
that still get our
hair cut every week.
(LAUGHS) Yeah, yeah.
You could be right.
Who is that young woman
I see you with all the time?
That's Linda,
my girlfriend.
We've been together
since herjunior year.
Hmm.
I first laid eyes on
Edith in high school.
Fell in love faster
than a hiccup.
Well, I hope we
end up together
as happy as you
and Mrs. Royal.
Thank you, Freddie.
(LAUGHS)
I need to stop by
and see you every day.
You just make me feel
better about things.
Anytime, Coach.
My office.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Bradley's not here.
Probably already transferred.
(PLAYERS MURMURING)
(PLAYERS QUIET)
BILL: Come on, slick.
Throw me a pass.
I'm looking for
a new position.
Let's go, gunslinger.
Run her to post.
Hit me.
Yes, sir.
Hut.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING)
(PLAYERS CHEERING)
You all right, bubba?
Our quarterback!
Hook 'em!
(ALL CHEERING)
Let's get to work.
(PLAYING UPBEAT MUSIC)
JOE: It's Steinmark again.
Up and over.
Touchdown, Bertelsen.
PHIL: Steinmark on the return.
He's got blockers, Joe.
He's out to the 50.
He could go all the way!
Touchdown!
Whoo!
JOE: Street with a keeper.
He gets hit. Spins!
Oh, another touchdown
for the Longhorns!
This triple option offense,
which sportswriters are now
calling "the wishbone,"
has changed this Texas team.
PHIL: And defenses don't know
how to stop this offense.
The Longhorns
will not be denied.
JOE". Street to Speyrer.
On the end-around.
He breaks it upfield.
Touchdown, Cotton Speyrer.
Amen.
PHIL: Another vicious hit
by Steinmark at the
line for no gain.
JOE: Well, after
a horrendous start,
Texas have outscored
their opponents 320 to 134.
PHIL: And has won the Southwest
Conference championship.
JOE: What an amazing
season for Steinmark.
Leading the league
at interceptions
and being named all Southwest
Conference safety.
PHIL: And if it was my vote,
Texas would be number
one in the country.
(GRUNTS)
I've been looking for you.
What is it?
Bobbyjust found out his
brother got killed in Vietnam.
(SIGHS)
(19605 MUSIC PLAYING)
...in the name of
freedom must stop.
End the war.
PROTEST LEADER:
We are sick and tired
of our brothers dying
thousands of miles away
fighting useless wars.
Hey, man!
First Amendment.
Right to free speech.
To hell with
your free speech.
Let him go.
We've got plenty more.
Hey, war lover.
War lover.
FREDDIE: Bobby! Bobby!
Bobby! Hey! Hey!
Hey, it's me. Hey.
Mark's...
I know.
(SOBBING)
I'm so sorry.
Come on, let's go.
ALL: (CHANTING) No more war!
No more war!
He had such great
plans for his life.
He was everything
I wanted to be.
And nothing has
ever hurt this much.
(SNIFFLES)
Tell me why God takes
my brother so young
with such a great
life ahead of him.
I don't think anybody
can answer that question.
You know,
just because you're not
a religious person
doesn't mean you can't
pray at a time like this.
If I did pray,
it would be to ask God
to bring my brother back!
I understand.
Look, I'm sorry. I didn't
meant to yell at you.
Don't be sorry.
You have every right to be
mad and yell all you want.
Doesn't do any good.
Nothing does any good.
FREDDIE: Can you believe
a man just walked on the moon?
No.
It didn't even seem real.
Everything's
changing so fast.
Yeah. In two years
we'll be graduating.
And then?
NFL.
And?
What do you mean "and"?
Is it still a boy and a girl?
No, it's three
boys and a girl.
(LAUGHING)
Three?
All right, fine.
How about four?
No. Three.
Four
Thirsty.
Ow!
You okay?
(GROANS) Yeah,
it's nothing.
You sure?
Bruised it playing softball.
ROYAL: I hope you don't
read this bullcrap.
We do not care what other
people write about us.
We don't care what people
think we can and can't do.
Only those of you right
here can tell that story.
And, gentlemen,
I'm counting on it
being a great story.
(CROWD CHEERING)
PHIL: The University
of California
should be a good first test.
JOE: There hasn't been
this much excitement
about Texas football
in a long while.
Even ABC is anticipating
a number one versus
number two showdown
at the end of the season.
And right now that would be
Texas versus Arkansas
for the 100-year anniversary
of college football.
JOE: Steinmark!
A loss of three.
PHIL: The Campbell twins
join up on a tackle!
JOE: Street, scrambling again.
He's in trouble,
but he gets out of it!
Touchdown!
JAMES: Yeah, baby.
(PLAYERS PANTING)
You all right?
Fine.
JOE: Final score.
Texas, 17 to nothing.
A great defensive effort
led by Freddie Steinmark.
Your leg's still
bothering you.
It'll be okay.
You got to see Medina.
He never healed anybody.
His whole job is to tape you
up and send you back out.
I'd hate to see
you play at 90%.
Good stuff, man.
PHIL: Texas Tech has
gotten the better
of the Longhorns
in the last two years,
but with James Street
at the helm
and Freddie Steinmark
in the secondary,
this Longhorn team has
a completely different look.
JOE: It's 28!
Steinmark again with
another interception.
Revenge is sweet.
Texas crushes Tech 49 to 7.
PHIL: And they'll next
face archrival Oklahoma,
led by power back
Steve Owens.
JOE: It's a war of wills now.
Power versus power.
PHIL: And the Sooners
are counting on Owens
to carry the bulk of the load
but Freddie's got something
to say about that.
Come on!
(CROWD CHEERING)
JOE: And the Longhorns prevail
in a slugfest. 27 to 17.
Smell that?
Yeah.
Wait, isn't that illegal?
Why are you still
limping so badly?
I'm not.
Don't act like you're not
in pain. I know you.
I'm getting better.
It's not getting better.
You have to go see a doctor.
I'm doing all right
out there.
I see you. Trying to hide
your limp on the field, too.
Look, if I wasn't
doing the job,
I wouldn't be playing.
If it's still a problem
after the Arkansas game,
I'll have someone
take a look at it.
That's not for
another month.
I'm not going to miss
this season, Linda.
It's going to be special.
I know it.
Stubborn.
Stubborn boy.
JOE: It's Speyrer
on the reverse.
He's going to throw it.
It's a long one to Peschel.
What a grab. Touchdown!
(FREDDIE GROANING)
PHIL: Steinmark took
a big hit there, Joe.
It looks like
he might be hurt.
He's going to shake it off.
JOE: Well, he's a tough kid.
JAMES: Set, hut!
JOE: Street with a keeper.
Scrambling again. Touchdown!
Steinmark on the coverage.
PHIL: Freddie got beat
on that one, Joe.
How's it feeling?
It's fine.
JOE: What a catch! Touchdown!
Texas has this
wrapped up 49 to 12.
PHIL: And now they are the
number one team in the land.
JOE: Arkansas' number two.
Phil, this could be the
game of the century.
Hey, Freddie.
Didn't know you
came in this early.
What happened to you?
You look like you've been
run over by a truck.
It's this way
after every game.
You know what it's
like out there.
It's different for me. I'm the
one who's doing the hitting.
Yeah, I got 11 of you bastards
coming at me every play.
And most a hell of
a lot bigger than you.
(STEVE GROANING)
How's that leg of yours?
Pain is pain.
Comes with the territory.
You got that right.
All I care about now
is the Arkansas game.
That's why we're here.
To play for all the marbles.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(BOTH SIGHING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
How's the leg, Freddie?
It's not bad.
It just keeps getting
banged up. I'll be fine.
Seems like it's
getting worse.
Everyone is a little beat up
this time of the season.
Montgomery is the best
quarterback we play against.
When he watches the film,
he's going to see
that you're vulnerable.
And he will attack.
I know all
his tendencies.
I'll be in the right
place at the right time.
I promise! Coach,
I will not let you down.
(SIGHS)
Even at 90% I want
you out there.
You're the heart
of our defense.
And hell, you boys
only allowed
three touchdowns
all year.
After we win this game,
we'll have three weeks
before the Cotton Bowl.
If it still hurts,
you see a doctor, okay?
Yes, sir.
My leg will be perfect
New Year's Day.
PHIL: Welcome to
The Big Shootout!
Or as many have been saying,
college football's
Game of the Century.
FANS: (CHANTING) Texas! Fight!
There's not an empty seat here
in hostile Razorback Stadium.
Two undefeated teams,
number one Texas versus
number two Arkansas,
battle for the
National Championship.
(CHEERING)
JOE: Arkansas present
the Longhorn defense
with their toughest
challenge of the year.
PHIL: But no team this
year has figured out
how to stop the potent
wishbone offense.
What we got here, Joe,
is two great offenses
versus two great defenses.
JOE: And despite
the bitter rivalry,
coaches Darrell Royal
and Frank Broyles
are good friends.
PHIL: Maybe not from
the opening kickoff
to the final gun today, Joe.
And this game has received
so much attention
that even the President
is expected at any moment.
JOE: I have never
seen one game
receive so much publicity.
Hey.
Can you hold up one
more game, little dink?
Wouldn't be if I couldn't.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
If you want to help, keep their
defense on the field, huh?
I'll see what I can do.
(BOTHLAUGH)
PHIL: The helicopter,
Marine One, is landing.
President Nixon will soon be
joining this raucous crowd.
Here we are.
Wheat Ridge boys.
(WHOOPS)
Playing in front
of the President
of the United States in the
biggest damn game ever!
All part of the plan.
(LAUGHS)
I wouldn't be here
if it wasn't for you.
Let's go, boys!
I'm going to set
the tone of this game
right here, right now.
(FANS CHANTING)
On three. One, two, three.
PLAYE RSI Texas!
JOE: And here we go. Texas,
first series on offense.
Set. Hut!
JOE: James Street.
Hands off to... Fumble!
Arkansas recovers!
PHIL: Holy cow. First play
right off the scrimmage.
I'd hate to say the crowd
was already a factor,
but maybe they are.
And just as the
President arrives.
Glad he didn't see that.
I wish I hadn't seen it.
Unbelievable.
(PLAYERS GRUNTING)
JOE: Touchdown!
Arkansas draws first blood.
JAMES: Hut!
JOE: Street going back
for his first pass of the day.
Going for Speyrer.
Underthrown. And intercepted!
(CHEERING)
Street rolls to his left.
Completion to Speyrer.
Fumble!
A scramble for the ball,
and Arkansas recovers again.
Steinmark with a big hit.
Street, going for Speyrer.
And again,
another interception!
PHIL: What a disastrous start
for the Longhorns, Joe.
Damnfll PHH;Thm@Sfwo
interceptions and two fumbles,
and the first half
isn't even over.
(CHEERING)
(PLAYERS GRUNTING)
JOE: And Texas, stuffed
once again at the line.
MONTGOMERY: Set, hut!
JOE: Montgomery
to Johnny Rees.
Tackled by Steinmark.
A gain of five.
There you go.
Nice hit, Freddie.
Nice hit.
Darrell, Steinmark
is really struggling.
I'm thinking about it.
JOE: Third and 10
on the Texas 22.
Down!
Set! Hut!
JOE: Montgomery.
He's looking downfield.
Great protection.
Dicus is right there,
wide open!
And he lets it go!
Touchdown,
Arkansas Razorbacks.
PHIL: There is
nothing going right
for Texas right now, Joe.
Mr. Referee,
he was blocking on me
when the ball was in the air,
and that's against the rules.
JOE: Now, hold on
a minute there, Phil.
I see a flag.
Flag. It's coming back.
ARKANSAS PLAYER: Come On!
PHIL: You know what, Joe?
I believe Tom Campbell
convinced the referee
that he was interfered with.
How does he get to call that?
REFEREE: He was blocking...
ARKANSAS COACH:
They're the number one team
in the nation. I understand.
But you don't make
a call like that
with something like this.
(BOOING)
Not in a game like this,
you can't make that call.
PHIL: Worst half of football
the Longhorns have
played all year.
Arkansas have figured out
how to stop this wishbone.
JOE: And at the end
of the first half,
it's Arkansas 7,
Texas nothing.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
RANDY: I'm wide open
after every five yards.
Hey, slick. I can get open
out there. I promise.
All right. Well,
if your number's called
and you're open,
I'll get you the ball.
You going to
be all right?
One more half.
CAMPBELL: Listen up!
Everybody UP-
I'm not gonna stand
here and tell you
what you're doing wrong,
what you're doing right.
By God, you wouldn't be playing
if you didn't know that.
Men, I want you to think about
all the years
we spent together.
The practices.
The weight room.
The heat.
The sweat.
The vomit.
The Medina drills.
So difficult, every one of you
at some point wanted to quit.
As you see,
it was all for a purpose.
To get ourselves
to this place,
for this great battle.
Don't let all those hours
you put into this
endeavor go to waste.
In about one hour,
a gun is going to go
off and end the game.
And at that point,
the world will know
that the 1969
National Champions
were the University
of Texas Longhorns.
FREDDIE: That's right.
Now give me three.
TOM: Come on, let's go!
(PLAYERS CHATTERING)
What you say, DOYS?
All right. One by one, let's go.
Play by play, let's 9°-
Hey, let's go get them,
Fast Freddie.
PHIL: They've spotted the ball
inside the Texas 30-yard line.
So that was a pickup of two
on that last
running play, Joe.
JOE: And it's Arkansas.
Second down and eight
on the Texas 29.
Dicus and Rees
split through the left.
Montgomery, back to pass.
And he hits Dicus
on a crossing pattern.
He's got some running room.
He's on the ten, five.
Arkansas, touchdown!
The Razorbacks strike
first in the second half.
PHIL: Steinmark had
a shot at him,
but he couldn't
get there in time.
Freddie's a step behind.
PHIL: A demoralizing score
for the Longhorns,
who are now down
14 to nothing.
Hey! It's your time, slick.
BELLARD: Let's go, Texas.
Just watch me.
JOE: Second and nine
for Texas on the Arkansas 44.
Street goes back.
He's in trouble.
He breaks free.
He almost goes down.
And there he goes.
He's at the 30, the 20, 10.
Touchdown, James Street.
What a run!
PHIL: You can't hold
a good man down, Joe.
We've been seeing
that scrambling artistry
from James Street
for the last two years.
And now we can pull
within seven.
JOE: Wait a minute, Phil.
Look there. Texas is going
for the two-point conversion.
PHIL: That's a big risk.
If they fail, that makes it
a two-possession game
instead of one.
JOE: Coach Royal rolling
the dice on this one.
It's Street, he fakes left.
Spins, goes right.
And he's in there!
Two points, Texas.
Arkansas 14, Texas 8.
PHIL: Darrell Royal,
the riverboat gambler,
wins that bet.
The number one team in
the land is back in the game.
Let's go, come on.
JOE: Montgomery goes back
and hits Dicus again!
A 21-yard gain.
(GROANING SOFTLY)
Down.
Set! Hut!
JOE: There's the throw.
And it's too long.
But we have a flag.
PHIL: There was a hold.
Steinmark was
going to get beat,
and he grabbed his jersey
to save a touchdown.
I've got holding, number 28.
PHIL: So, with that penalty,
that's going to
be a 15-yarder.
That's going to move it
all the way from the 24
down inside the 10-yard
line to the 9, Joe.
JOE: I've never seen
him do that before.
He's finished.
Take him out.
Get in there.
Freddie!
FREDDIE: You can do it, Rick.
JOE: Rick Nabors,
the backup safety is in.
PHIL: Joe, I believe that's
the first time I can remember
he's being pulled from the
game for not doing his job.
At least he
saved a touchdown.
I'm sorry, son.
I hated to do it.
The right call.
Bring your kinnies!
Come on, now.
Stiff it up!
JAMES: Set! Hut!
JOE: Montgomery, looking
for Dicus. He throws it.
Interception!
Danny Lester.
He breaks the tackle
and returns it back
all the way to the 25.
PHIL: That's a big break
for the Longhorns.
They dodged a bullet.
Montgomery and Dicus
were on a roll.
Offense, on the field.
JOE: And here we go.
With six minutes to go,
Texas needs to make
something happen.
Time's running out.
And it's Street to Speyrer
on the end-around.
He breaks it up field
to the 40, 45,
into Arkansas territory.
Set! Hut!
JOE: Koy, with a quick
hit to the inside.
A gain of a couple.
Worster again, off tackle.
Maybe three yards at the most.
Third and five. Worster again.
They didn't make it.
PHIL: Now it's fourth down
and the clock is
still running, Joe.
Damn it.
Ref!
JOE: Time out, Texas. Fourth
at about two and a half.
PHIL: Oh, this is going
to be Coach Royal's
biggest call of the game,
if not the season.
JOE: No doubt.
That veer should be there.
Fourth and two and a half.
But with this field
position, if we go for this
and don't make it,
and give it back to them,
that's it, game's over.
We got four
minutes left.
Right 53 veer pass.
Hey, Coach! Right 53
veer pass. You sure?
Hell yes, I'm sure.
Run the play.
Yes, sir.
Yeah, I might be wrong,
but I'm not confused.
Defense, get ready.
All right. Get in tight.
Randy, this one's
coming to you.
Right 53 veer pass. On one.
You better be open.
I'm always open.
All right.
On one, on one! Ready?
PLAYERS: Break!
Carry out your fate!
JOE: Here we go. James
Street, over center.
Everybody on their feet here
at Razorback Stadium.
Set! Hut!
(GRUNTS)
JOE: Randy Peschel!
It's caught!
PHIL: He somehow came
up with the ball.
Yeah, baby! (LAUGHS)
Atta boy, Randy!
PHIL: Coach Royal gambling
it all on that play.
(CHEERING)
How in the hell did
he get behind them?
JOE: James Street and Randy
Peschel coming through.
James!
JOE: They're now in scoring
position on the 13.
PHIL: They're now in National
Championship position, Joe.
JAMES: Huddle up! Huddle up!
All right, Darrell,
you're a genius.
JAMES: Set! Hut!
JOE: Hand off to Ted Koy,
and he pounds his way
to the two-yard line.
An 11-yard gain.
(ALL CHEERING)
And Bertelsen rams his way
into the end zone.
Touchdown, Texas!
A 14-14 tie!
PHIL: And that's why
Coach Royal went for two.
To set up kick and a simple
extra point
in taking the lead.
He wasn't planning on
playing for no tie.
JOE: And here's the kick.
It's up. It's good!
Texas leads 15-14.
PHIL: But there's
still 3:58 left.
Plenty of time for Arkansas
to get back in
scoring position.
Rick! Rick!
Keep Dicus on the inside.
Don't bite on
his post move.
Got you.
You're doing great.
One more stop.
I want Freddie
in the game.
You sure?
All right.
We got three minutes
to hold them.
Coach wants you
back in there.
Come on, defense!
Saddle up!
Freddie's going back in.
Let's go, Freddie.
Come on, son.
LONGHORNS FAN 1:
You can do it, Freddie!
LONGHORNS FAN 2: Longhorns!
MIKE: Hey, welcome
back, Freddie.
Hold them right here.
Let's go!
JOE: Montgomery, back to pass.
Spots his favorite
target Dicus.
And completes it again.
Hell, you can take
Dicus, baby. Let's go!
JOE: Now the Razorbacks
in Texas territory
at the 46, first and ten.
CAMPBELL: Steinmark! Hey!
Man, 80, man!
Guys, we have got
to shut Dicus down!
I got him.
Drop somebody.
PHIL: Joe, all Arkansas
needs is another 20 yards,
and they can kick a field
goal and win this game.
MONTGOMERY: Down!
Set! Hut!
JOE: Montgomery rolling
left looking for Dicus.
He's covered tight
by Steinmark.
He's got to throw it away.
PHIL: Great coverage
by Steinmark.
That's it, Freddie!
That's my boy.
FRED: Yes!
JOE: Second and 10 on the 46.
Set!
Hut!
JOE: Montgomery,
looking downfield.
Dicus not open.
He goes for Rees.
PHIL: Interception!
Tom Campbell! What a grab!
Right there!
(ALL CHEERING)
(CHEERING)
FREDDIE: Yeah! Yeah!
Texas!
(CHEERING)
PHIL: That's it,
they've done it!
JOE: Number one Texas wins
the National Championship,
15 to 14!
It's like a dream, right?
National Championship!
It's why we came to Texas!
Congratulations, Darrell.
Heck of a good game.
It's a game for the ages.
Could have gone either way.
It could have, it could have.
Good luck to you guys.
Got it!
BOBBY: Number one, baby!
Fast Freddie!
(BOTH WHOOPING)
PHIL: A game for
the ages, Joe.
JOE: No doubt about that.
PHIL: What a battle it was.
They'll be celebrating
in Austin tonight!
ALL: Longhorns!
(ALL WHOOPING)
(MARCHING BAND PLAYING)
(WHOOPS)
(WHOOPING)
Freddie!
Hey! (SQUEALS)
(LAUGHING)
You were right,
National Champion!
Meant to be!
I know. All part
of the plan, right?
I'm proud of you.
(GROANS)
The doctor, tomorrow.
And don't even mention
the Cotton Bowl.
We're gonna be
playing Notre Dame!
It's the first time they ever
accepted a Bowl invitation.
They wanna prove they can
beat the National Champions.
The doctor. Tomorrow.
That's it. No more interviews.
We've got to start
preparing for Notre Dame.
Come on in, Freddie.
I'll talk to you later.
(EXHALES) Sit down.
Your leg.
It's worse.
I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
I wanna play in
the Cotton Bowl.
I think we have to have somebody
good take a look at it.
Yeah. I know.
Everything I've done to make
it better hasn't worked.
I don't know, maybe I
should have held you out
a couple of games.
No way, Coach.
I wouldn't have missed
one minute of one game.
I know.
Let me be clear.
We would not be
National Champions
if you had not been
out on that field.
You hear me?
Lance, will you get me
Dr. Julian, please?
Dr. Julian,
it's Darrell.
Listen, I need you
to clear the decks.
Give my Freddie Steinmark
the VIP treatment.
No, now.
Thank you.
He'll be right over.
Dr. Julian's the best bone
and joint doctor we have here.
He'll take good care of you.
I'm going to New York
to collect the MacArthur Bowl.
Oh, yeah.
You gonna be okay?
Yes, Coach.
Thank you.
You're welcome, Freddie.
You ready to get right to it?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
This area, here,
is the problem.
There are a couple
of possibilities.
Bone spurs, coagulated edema.
But the most likely
is that it's a tumor.
A tumor?
Tumors can be benign.
We've decided that the
best course of action
is to send you to Houston M.D.
Anderson Hospital.
It's part of the University
of Texas Medical Center.
There are good hospitals here.
Why go to Houston?
Because they got the best
oncology department in Texas.
Oncology?
The study of cancer.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
FRED: Hello?
FREDDIE: Dad.
I just talked to the doctor.
They're sending me to a
cancer hospital in Houston.
I think my leg
is bad. Real bad.
Please don't tell Ma.
Okay, well, I have to
tell your mother, son.
We're coming down there.
No, you don't
have to go,
I'll call after
I know anything.
When's your appointment?
5:00, tomorrow afternoon.
Okay. We'll see you there.
No, you don't have to go.
It would be a waste
of time and money
if it turns out
to be benign.
Son, we're coming.
How are you?
I'm okay.
We are gonna come and
see you real soon, champ.
Tonight, we'll say
our prayers together.
(SNIFFLING) Yes,
Mama, we'll do that.
We'll do that.
Okay.
Good-bye.
(EXHALES)
(APPLAUSE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
MAN: Since 1959,
the MacArthur Bowl has been
presented by the National
Football Foundation...
(WHISPERS) Coach Royal, you have a phone
oall in the vestibule, it's urgent.
MAN: it is annually awarded
by the National
Football Foundation
to the outstanding college
football team of the season.
Since it was first
offered in 1959,
the trophy is looked upon as
one of the most celebrated...
Thank you.
Doctor, it's Darrell.
Are you sure?
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Okay. Well, let's get him
there as soon as possible.
We'll charter
a plane, we'll...
No, I'm scheduled to come
back tomorrow night.
Forget that. I'm going
to the airport right now.
Yes, thank you.
Somebody here to see you.
Why didn't you call me?
How did you get here?
I drove.
When I didn't hear from you,
I found out from
the football office
that they flew you here.
I just didn't want you
involved with all this.
Involved?
I'm a little more than
involved, don't you think?
I'm sorry, I knew
you'd wanna be here,
and it's a three-hour
drive, I...
I would drive across
the country for you.
You know that.
Whatever you're going
through, I'm going through.
I know.
I'm sorry.
No.
It's gonna be okay.
(SNIFFLING) Your
parents are flying in.
I'm picking them up
in a couple of hours.
Thanks.
I'll be outside.
Love you.
I love you.
How are you, Linda?
Coach.
I thought you were
in New York.
Ah, hell, I never liked
those big cities.
If Coach is here,
it must be serious.
DR. MARTIN: Well, Freddie, I'm
going to lay it out to you,
as simple as possible.
We're going to
biopsy your tumor.
Best scenario is that it's
benign, we can drain it,
and you'll be out
of here in no time.
But the chance
of that happening,
based on my reading of the
X-ray, is quite small.
It's most likely an
osteogenic sarcoma.
Bone cancer.
If that's the case,
I'm going to have to
amputate your leg.
We have no other choice.
Okay.
How far up?
DR. MARTINI The hip.
Okay.
We'll see you first
thing in the morning.
Yeah.
Thanks,Doc.
Thank you, Doctor.
(EXHALES)
Freddie, you and I
have been through
some tough spots together.
Both of us have
been behind in life,
and we've come back.
We've never given up.
You can't give up now.
Okay, Coach.
Whatever it is,
you will meet the challenge.
And I'll be here for you.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
Yeah.
Thank you.
Freddie, don't get up.
Let me do it now.
(GRUNTS)
I may not get another chance.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
You know why we're
having this meeting?
I think it's about Freddie.
Has anybody heard anything?
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
ROYAL: Sit down. Sit down.
Everybody sit down.
As you're all aware,
Freddie's surgery was today.
I want you all to
know the outcome
before you heard it
from somewhere else.
They found a cancerous tumor,
the size of a baseball,
on his femur.
Doctors told me
they didn't know
how he could
walk on that leg,
much less play football.
Of course, I'm sure
that wouldn't surprise
anybody here.
They amputated his leg...
Damn.
...at the hip.
Men, your teammate is in
the fight of his life.
And if there's anybody I know,
or have ever known,
who's up to it,
it's Freddie Joe Steinmark.
That boy has never backed down
against nothing or nobody,
and he won't now.
But he's gonna
need all of you.
Your thoughts,
VOW prayers,
Your support.
Hey, Coach.
Are they gonna let him
out of the hospital
to come and be with all
of us at the Cotton Bowl?
I'm afraid not.
Doctor said a minimum 3O
days before he can leave.
But, men, he will be
there with us in spirit.
He will be there with us.
(sesame)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
I'll never play again.
I won't be able
to show Notre Dame
what they missed out on.
None of that matters now.
Look at me.
There is nothing
my boy can't do.
You will beat this.
We'll do it together.
(SWALLOWS)
Okay, Mama.
GLORIA: (WHISPERING)
You are so strong.
You're gonna be okay.
Love you, son.
FREDDIE: I love you.
GLORIA: Get some sleep.
Hey, hot dog.
When you get out
of the hospital,
we're gonna go to our
favorite parking spot.
That may be a while.
They said at least a month.
I've got nothing but time.
We're gonna get back to our
normal lives. I promise.
Normal? (SCOFFS)
Yes, normal.
We got plans, mister.
I can see our future
from right here.
Right here.
There's Austin,
where we'll graduate May,
a year from now.
(SIGHS)
Right there is Denver,
where you're
gonna be coaching.
And there's our
little house in Aurora,
where we're gonna live
with our one girl
and three boys.
(SNIFFLING)
(BOTH WEEPING)
You're making a fast recovery.
That doesn't surprise me.
Hey, Dr. Martin, this is my
best friend, Bobby Mitchell.
Hi.
BOBBY: Hi.
What are those for?
Oh, Freddie.
He's gonna be with us
at the Cotton Bowl.
(CHUCKLES) Not on
those, he's not.
FREDDIE: Please, Doctor.
No, I'm sorry, Freddie.
It's out of the question.
Uh, you know...
Only way we could let you
go is in a wheelchair.
Even that's doubtful.
You just had a major
traumatic surgery.
I won't go in
a wheelchair.
Then you're not
leaving the hospital.
Can't you just let me
try the crutches?
No.
Your system will be
in recovery for weeks.
Just being upright puts
too much pressure
on all your stitches.
I'd just like to try.
I'm sorry, Freddie, this
is not up for discussion.
I'll be back to check
on you tomorrow.
Nice to meet you, Bobby.
Doctor.
Hey, Bobby.
Let's prove him wrong.
BOBBY: Easy, easy.
No, I'm good.
One, two.
Yeah. Okay.
(GROANING)
All right, come on.
Maybe this isn't
such a good idea.
Let's try it one more time.
Okay.
One, two.
ROYAL: Excuse me, Nurse.
I just went to Freddie
Steinmark's room,
and he's not there.
ls there something wrong?
Yes, there sure is.
We can hardly
keep track of him.
He's constantly
on the move.
Those two practice
every day for hours.
I know some doctors
do not support this,
but I think it's great.
There it is.
Thank you, Nurse.
Absolutely.
All right, end
of this hallway,
then I'll get a break.
(GRUNTING) Okay.
All right. Okay.
Yeah.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
DR. MARTIN: There's
a rumor going around
that you've gone
renegade on me.
FREDDIE: I don't know
what you're talking about.
Well, this isn't
the military,
and I can't order you
off the crutches.
I can only strongly
advise against it.
Dr. Martin.
How many patients of
yours have lost limbs
due to bone cancer?
Well, I don't have
the statistics.
There are many variances.
Please. I wanna
know where I stand.
I read an article
on how bone cancer
is one of the deadliest.
Hardest to cure.
Well, that's true, it is.
But I've had a number
of success stories.
I'm asking you to
be straight with me.
I need to know.
The survival rates
for your form
of osteogenic sarcoma
are not high.
Doctor,
I'm gonna ask you
one more time,
and I'm begging you
to tell me the truth.
How many patients
who lost a limb
from my kind of cancer
lived more than a year?
Very few.
(SIGHS)
Thank you.
(PLAYERS CHATTERING)
Bob.
Hey, little buddy.
McCoy's nothing.
You're gonna own him.
I will.
It's your game, Woo Woo.
Tom.
I'm counting on you
to shut down Theismann.
I'm planning on it.
Street.
Hey, Freddie.
You know, their left cornefls slow.
Attack on his side.
You got it.
Welcome back, Freddie.
Hey, Mr. Inside.
Mr. Outside.
(SIGHS)
Hey.
Give 'em hell.
Yeah, I'll take care of it.
All right, men,
let's listen up.
I don't need to say this,
because I know it's all
in your heads anyway.
Let's go out there and
win Freddie a game ball.
Yeah.
(ALL CLAPPING)
Yeah!
(CROWD CHEERING IN DISTANCE)
(CROWD CHEERING)
There he is!
You ready? Let's go
get 'em, boys!
(PLAYERS SHOUTING)
(WHOOPING)
(CROWD CHEERING LOUDLY)
Yeah, boy!
(CAMERA CLICKS)
ROYAL: We won that game.
And Freddie did
get the game ball.
That kid had a tub-full
of guts and courage.
And defying the
doctor's odds,
he lived another
year and a half.
He died on June 6,1971.
His family and Linda
by his side.
But he still lives
in our hearts.
We honor his spirit
before every game.
(PLAYERS SHOUTING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Let' s gm!
I don't know if I tell you
how proud I am of you.
It'd be kind of, you know,
an understatement.
Afraid if I talk too damn
long, I'm gonna choke up.
But we've got a guy
that we love a lot.
Freddie, here it is for ya.
(ALL CHEERING)