Computer: Condition three,
anomaly alert status.
Gen lab four. Level nine.
Sector Amber 11,
please investigate.
Camera A7
double LL,
sector Amber 11,
remote zoom-in.
Condition three,
anomaly alert status.
- (electronic beeping)
- Sector Amber 11.
(loud buzzing)
Access denied.
Warning: This area
is under condition three
anomaly alert status.
Please use caution.
(door struggling to open)
Biosensors indicate
viral and bacterial levels
within acceptable norm.
Access denied.
Pneumatic pressure
seal engaged.
Damn.
Access denied.
Warning: This area is
now at condition three
anomaly alert status.
Please use caution.
(alarm blaring within)
Oh my God.
Condition three alert status.
Bio-filters engaged.
No contamination detected.
Please use caution.
Halon compression
system at standby.
(feet pattering)
(cans clanging)
(screaming)
All infectious biological
levels nominal.
Please use caution.
M5 and GH4 indicators
at standard OPC.
(screaming)
Brian!
TV: Something grabbed him.
It was horrible.
Brian!
What did you see, Butch?
I don't know.
But one thing's for sure,
it wasn't human.
I found this
next to VanDoren's helmet.
My God! It's huge!
For God's sakes, don't touch it!
It's growing!
- Is that your hair? Sorry.
- Yeah...
Give me a pair
of rubber gloves.
I want to check this out.
Ow!
You're not going to stick
your hand in there!
What's that green stuff
oozing from the tip?
Whoa! Get it on, sis!
What the hell was that?
Where the hell have you been?
It's 11:00.
Chill out, sis.
I was out with Billy.
I was in good hands.
Oh my God, we're
not going to make it.
Looks like you were in pretty
good hands yourself tonight.
Hi, Brian.
Fire, fire!
Oh, that's real romantic.
Daddy's going to kill you
if he finds out
you were out this late
with that delinquent.
Billy is not a delinquent.
He's got problems at home.
He's got problems all right.
You're just jealous, that's all.
Thank you, Kim.
Oh, I'm sorry, handsome.
You get to bed right now,
missy, it's a school night.
And you stay there,
you hear me?
Lighten up.
What are you, my mother?
I'm sorry, Sherry.
I didn't mean...
Just go to bed.
- Good night, Brian.
- Good night, Kim.
She didn't mean it, Sherry.
She's just a kid.
I don't know what's
happened to us, Brian.
Kim and I used to be so close.
Relax.
- Come on, Sherry.
- Not now, Brian.
Ooh, brrr!
Computer: Warning: You are
entering a condition three
anomaly status area.
Please use caution.
Michael?
All biological systems
functioning
within acceptable
zeta parameters.
Elliot?
Damn!
Emergency override
code L374 engaged.
(clattering)
Atmospheric sensors
indicate trace levels
of ammonia, methane,
hydrochloric acid,
all less than
one part per million.
- (squishes)
- (gasps)
Warning: This area is
now at condition three
anomaly alert status.
Please use caution.
Well, where is he?
I don't know.
He must have escaped.
Mitchell!
I want you and Jarrett
here immediately.
We've got a problem.
DJ: Hey it's 7:42 Thursday
morning, the sun is shining,
coffee's brewing,
- do you know where your parents are?
- Hurry up, Kim. We're both late.
First period's English.
I'm always late.
Mr. Gunther doesn't mind.
Well, I mind. You're never going
to get anywhere in life
unless you start taking some
responsibility for yourself.
Do something productive.
Hey, I'm doing
all right, so far.
God, I'll never make it.
If you want a ride you
better get ready right now.
All right, mellow out.
DJ: You wanna keep it down out there?
I'm trying to sleep.
But seriously folks,
we got a real racket
comin' at you now from the boys
down at Mute Jam Records...
Seymour and the New Mutants
singing "Baby, You've Changed."
- Where's Dad?
- Lay it on me!
What do you mean, where's Dad?
Isn't he in bed?
Nope.
His car's not there.
You sure he's not in his room?
I may not be a college girl like you,
but I'm not an idiot.
He's not in bed.
I wonder where he could be.
We've got to do something.
Call someone in.
Nancy, you're not thinking logically.
We're fully prepared to handle
this situation within Talos.
But this situation
is out of control.
He's killed two people already
and now he's disappeared.
He couldn't have gotten
out of the complex.
He has to be somewhere
in the building.
I've got two men
searching for him right now.
I don't want him killed.
Elliot and I have devised a way
to get him back to normal.
I won't stand for it.
Do you hear me?
Sit down, Doctor.
What would you have me do?
Call in the police?
Or better yet,
the National Guard?
I'm not sure
they would share
the compassion
and understanding
you feel for Dr. Foster.
They don't share the same
romantic past as you and he.
You saw what that
creature is capable of.
That creature is
still Michael Foster.
- I'm doing what I can.
- It's not enough, damn it!
What about Elliot?
What about John Griffen?
What are you going
to do about them?
That has already
been taken care of.
You're a cold bastard.
(intercom buzzing)
Yes? Send them in.
I'll ignore
that last remark, Doctor.
Now you know
as well as I that
this entire project has been
highly illegal from the start.
And you have been
a willing part of it.
I feel terrible about
what has happened.
But we must keep
this within the family
or everything we've done
and learned will be for nothing.
Michael Foster will be
worse off than he is now.
Please, trust me.
(knocking)
Come.
Mitchell, Jarrett,
this is Dr. Kane.
Nancy, I think you'd better
explain to these gentlemen
exactly what's going on.
Um, Doctor, I don't think
we should explain...
It's all right, Doctor.
They've a level six clearance.
They answer
only to myself. Proceed.
As I'm sure you're aware,
a number of research
and development programs here
at Talos are subsidized
by the government.
Some, how shall I say it...
do not exactly fall within
the safety guidelines and regulations
outlined and normally
enforced by the government,
particularly in the field
of nuclear research and genetics.
A few months ago,
Talos was assigned
a research grant
by the Defense Department...
a very strange request.
We were given tissue samples,
alien tissue samples.
- Alien?
- Yes, alien.
From another planet, apparently.
We were skeptical ourselves.
They were vague, almost tight-lipped
about the sample's origin.
Which led us to suspect
it was, in fact,
some genetically-altered
biological substance from Earth.
If that was the case,
why would they tell you it
came from another planet?
We thought perhaps they developed
this material for biological warfare
and were using Talos to test
what would be their alibi.
This type of biological engineering
is expressly forbidden under
the UN germ warfare pact.
If they could fool
Talos into believing
that the origin of this material
was, in fact, from outer space,
they could fool
anyone and avoid...
Avoid indictment
for violation of the pact.
Exactly.
Unfortunately,
they were not lying.
Dr. Michael Foster,
head of the entire genetic
research sector,
was put in charge...
myself,
as Dr. Foster's assistant,
and Dr. Viallini being
the only three people
with any knowledge
of the research.
Our problem
started on May 4th,
approximately 6:45 p.m.
Michael was working with some
cell cultures from the alien tissue.
(harpsichord music playing
on headphones)
Computer: Containment seal secure,
all functions normal.
- Guess who?
- Ahh!
Don't do that to me.
Don't tell me the doctor's
actually getting
- paranoid about his little monsters.
- (music shuts off)
You're a little monster.
Come here.
Please, dear,
not in front of the mutants.
Computer:
Cryo-interlock engaged.
Are we still on
for dinner tonight?
I don't know what time
I'm going to be getting out of here.
Hello, Checkers.
Hello, baby.
Hello.
- (screams)
- (growling)
Well, Checkers is
certainly energetic today.
Mm-hmm.
Computer: Intermediate microbe
distention filter...
- at 98%.
- How far have you gotten?
Well, I'm introducing some of the alien
cell cultures into Spot's ovaries.
The problem is, I can't find
any plasmas in the alien cells.
There do not appear
to be any structures
that contain identifiable
genetic material.
How can the cells replicate
if there's no genetic code?
As far as I can tell,
the cells don't reproduce
by fission
as normal cells do.
They seem to accumulate
polyp-like growths
which just mass
together to form tissue.
I don't think even using
the term "cell" is applicable.
I tell you, Nancy, I'm stumped.
Well, you better get un-stumped.
Viallini wants a report
by the end of the week.
- Well, you can tell Viallini...
- Hey...
You can tell him
whatever you want.
I've got to go.
(screaming)
Michael!
- Oh God!
- Michael!
Computer:
Emergency alert.
Biological contamination.
Quarantine restriction
code seven.
- Oh, shit!
- Michael!
- Are you all right?
- Oh my God!
The cells!
Michael, what do we do?
Nancy, come here.
Hurry!
- Pour this on my hand!
- Michael, that's sulfuric acid!
Damn it, don't argue with me!
Just do it!
Do you think that did it?
I don't know.
Oh my God.
Michael!
Oh, shit!
Michael! Michael!
Elliot!
Please answer.
- Computer: Emergency alert.
- Please!
Emergency alert.
Biological contamination.
Quarantine restriction
code seven.
Elliot.
Dr. Elliot Stein?
Yes, Elliot...
Dr. Stein is
staff physician...
Dr. Elliot Stein:
Age 33;
single; father dead;
mother still alive,
living in Chaplin, Nebraska;
graduate, Harvard Medical,
class of '77.
Stein is staff physician,
assistant to Dr. Marcus,
head of pharmaceutical
and chemical research.
Yes, that Dr. Stein.
May I continue?
Thank God Elliot
was still there.
You know, I usually
don't make house calls.
He was working on
one of the mutants and it bit him.
Michael, can you hear me?
Michael! Michael!
Elliot, he was working with some
really strange cell cultures.
They got into his...
Holy Jesus.
What the hell was
he working with?
Elliot, they were cell samples
from another planet.
What?!
The cells come from a creature
from another planet.
Nancy, have you
been drinking?
Elliot, don't argue with me.
I know it sounds crazy,
but it's true.
The cells come from a...
I don't have time to stand
here and explain this to you.
Just help him!
From another planet?
Elliot!
All right, all right.
Jesus Christ,
cells from outer space.
I outta change
my name to Dr. McCoy.
Have you noticed any pods?
Elliot!
I'm sorry, it's just...
- I don't know where to start.
- (growling)
Elliot!
Nancy, come here. Help me.
Hold that in.
You gotta hold him steady.
I'll give him a sedative.
(growling stops)
Help me get him up.
We've got to get him to a hospital.
That will not do,
Dr. Stein.
Dr. Viallini, we've got
to get Michael to a hospital.
That won't be necessary, Doctor.
We have the facilities here
to deal with this situation.
I don't mean to disagree, Doctor,
but this man has got to be...
Dr. Kane will explain to you
why it is imperative
that we deal with this problem
within the confines
of this establishment.
Nancy.
Naturally, I explained the...
situation to Dr. Stein
and he apparently agreed
that we should keep it...
in the family.
I'm sure whatever Dr. Viallini
is using to black...
was using to blackmail Elliot
is in that little folder of yours.
That will be enough, Doctor.
It is not enough, damn it.
You've had it in for Michael
ever since the ICV incident.
- Dr. Kane...
- You've been waiting...
for an opportunity like this
to get rid of Michael
so that he couldn't...
he's been looking for an excuse...
a few months back, Michael Foster
developed a retro-clonal virus...
a virus with the ability
to seek out
specific chromosomes
within certain organ cells.
This virus could have
been used to hunt down
and destroy malignantly
mutated genes.
Ultimately, it might
one day have rid
mankind of most
inheritable diseases.
Dr. Viallini had other plans.
Son of a bitch!
You had no right to call
the Defense Department in on this one.
This is my project.
It's my work, my responsibility.
You are an employee
of the Talos Corporation.
Any materials you develop,
any research
you undertake is funded
by this corporation.
Hence, it is owned
solely by this corporation.
It is the board
of trustees who determine
when, where and to whom
we offer the results of our research.
Not some pig-headed
Ph.D. With delusions of...
- You incredible bastard!
- Michael.
We are not discussing
some secret recipe here.
We are talking about
a search-and-destroy virus
that could be perverted
and manipulated
to wipe out selected
populations of the human race!
- I will not be responsible!
- You're not that naive, Doctor,
nor that innocent.
You've taken a willing
part in many projects
whose objectives were
less than altruistic.
This is no different.
I'm not going to let you
get away with this.
I'll destroy all the data,
all the samples.
Do not make irrational threats
you'll be sorry for.
This is no threat.
I'll blow the whistle on you
and your little mutant
freak show downstairs.
I'm sure the National Genetic Council
would have a field day in this place.
Subpoenas will be flying around
here like a ticker-tape parade.
You are
just as much responsible.
You'll be cutting
your own throat.
I may go down, Doctor,
but I swear to Christ,
I'll drag you with me.
You wouldn't.
You want to play hardball?
You just try me.
Michael. Michael!
He's a very stupid man.
I suggest
you speak with him,
set him straight,
before I'm forced to take
more drastic measures.
You're wasting
valuable time, Doctor.
Mr. Jarrett and Mr. Mitchell
are not interested
in your accusations
or your fantasies.
They work for me.
If any harm comes
to Michael Foster,
I will see to it personally
that the NGC strings
you up by the balls.
Mr. Mitchell
and Mr. Jarrett are waiting.
Please continue.
Within hours, Michael's entire
body had been infected.
(groaning)
Elliot set up the lab facilities
for treating Michael,
but the mutations
were too rapid,
and research led
only to dead ends.
As the days passed,
Michael changed even more,
as if his entire cellular
structure was being rearranged...
redefined by the alien tissue.
Nancy, come here.
I'll need your help.
Hold that open
while I get a sample.
(screeches)
What the hell was that?
(screeching)
Elliot!
Are you trying to give me
a heart attack?
Stand back.
Come here,
you little son of a...
(screeching)
What in God's name
is that... thing?
I don't know, but I'm
not taking its temperature.
Look at this thing.
Jesus Christ!
Freakin' thing's
pissing on me.
Elliot's theory was
not quite accurate.
These small masses of flesh
contained a caustic venom,
ejected through a hollow quill
in its mouth, I suppose.
But like a bumblebee, once
the stinger has spent its venom,
the mass dies and virtually
decomposes within minutes.
It is not a pleasant sight.
(intercom buzzes)
Yes?
Who?
I see.
Give me a moment
and then send her in.
Wait outside for a moment.
It appears that Officer Griffen's
daughter is here asking questions.
She hasn't seen
her father all day and she's...
Ah, Miss Griffen.
Come in.
I'd like you to meet
Dr. Nancy Kane.
- Doctor, this is Stephanie.
- Sherry.
Hello, how do you do?
Your father has talked
about you quite often, Sherry.
I understand you are
a very smart young lady.
You're studying
computers, is it?
Micro-circuit design
and engineering.
Very impressive.
Very impressive, indeed.
When you graduate
I hope you come see me.
I'm sure we can find
a spot here at Talos
for somebody
with your talents.
Thank you, sir.
I'd like to ask you
about my father.
Ah, yes? A fine man!
One of our most trusted
and loyal employees.
Dr. Viallini...
my father's been gone
since last night.
I haven't seen
or heard from him since.
I'm very worried.
It's not like him.
I see.
Well, according to our log...
your father didn't work
here last night.
Wait. You mean
he wasn't here?
No, it says here
he called in sick.
Yes.
That's confirmed.
Another security guard
is listed on his shift.
This is very strange.
It's not like him to leave
Kim and me without calling.
I wouldn't worry.
I'm sure there's
some explanation.
I'll keep my ears open.
And if he doesn't
show up soon,
I'll personally see to it
that my people find out
where he is.
Thank you so much
for stopping by.
Feel free to stop by anytime
you have a problem
we can help you with.
We may have trouble with her.
The question is,
where could it be hiding?
Where would it be hiding?
I would appreciate it
if you would stop saying "it."
That is still Michael Foster,
no matter what
he's turned into.
I'm sorry, Doctor,
I forgot how close you two were.
Well, when I saw him last
he looked pretty slimy.
He'd begun to resemble
some sort of garden bug
or slug, or leach.
(groaning)
(groaning continues)
Dr. Stein!
Thank you,
very much, Doctors.
Now would either one of you
care to retrieve my probe,
or shall I just take
a reimbursement out of petty cash?
Elliot!
This is no time for levity.
(screaming)
Ta-da!
For my next trick...
By this time, even his internal
physiology had transformed.
His blood became
highly caustic,
his heart enlarged
by nearly twice its original size,
and he was becoming
less and less responsive
to the medications.
Finally, after four weeks
of dead ends,
Elliot made
a major breakthrough.
Computer: Nucleic IVM:
One part per billion.
Cellular engraination
reaching MD T threshold.
(groaning)
Temperature:
58° Celsius.
Michael.
(screaming)
Elliot!
Michael!
Computer: Microbiotic enzyme
distention at 47%.
I think we've got it.
RNA factor:
0.936 IMP.
Take a look.
A few minutes ago that sample
was completely infected
by the alien cells.
But this shows
no sign of infection.
- Thank you very much.
- Elliot, you're wonderful!
Yes, I know.
How did you do it?
Elementary, my dear.
I'd been noticing strange
molecular behavior
whenever I exposed samples
through the electron microscope.
The reaction
to negative pulse phasing
caused rampant destabilization
of the molecular bonding,
but only at specific
wavelengths.
As it turns out,
cellular and biological activity
is halted for a period of time
when electricity is introduced.
I can't be that simple.
You've received
total remission.
When his heart
stopped, we gave him
electro-shock resuscitation...
it did nothing.
You're talking about
normal AC current.
You got two problems there.
One, there's no way
to control or focus it
at specific enough
wavelengths.
Secondly, the amount
of energy required
to stop and reverse Michael's
metamorphosis would fry him.
Well?
Well, what?
Well, how did you manage it?
- Wow!
- Elliot!
I, uh...
I borrowed this little machine
from the boys down
in particle acceleration.
- An atom smasher?
- That's right.
But it's not atom smashing
I'm interested in.
You see, the particles are accelerated
through a series of electromagnets.
As they travel and build up speed
around its curved course,
electrons fly off, sort of like
tires screeching when
you take a turn very fast.
But these electrons can be focused
and manipulated to any wavelength.
So, I can control the output.
And this way we can
reverse the process
and still keep
Michael alive.
That's what
I'm hoping for, yeah.
Well what are we waiting for?
Come on, let's give it a try.
Nancy, hold on. Calm down.
I still need to do
a few more tests.
Besides, this machine isn't nearly
powerful enough to do the job.
We can use Agnes.
My thinking exactly.
A cyclotron the size of Agnes will
put out 10 times the power we need.
We'll have to construct a terminal
in a room nearby
the accelerator tunnel.
Let's schedule the first test
next week sometime.
If we can keep Michael
alive until then...
I'll talk to Viallini right away.
Tell me exactly what's required,
and I'll have him
take care of it.
The particles
are accelerated...
Within a week the terminal
was constructed.
We called it
the atomic shotgun.
Let me see that.
Agnes, this cyclotron,
it's never been tested?
Construction has only
just been completed.
We expect a full-power
test firing tonight in...
less than six hours,
as a matter of fact.
And the engineers,
they have no knowledge
of this shotgun's purpose?
Only the four of us
in this room.
Go on, Doctor.
Michael's transformation
continued
while we conducted more
tests preparing for tonight...
unfortunately.
Computer: Bio-scan
of frequency shutdown.
All systems at standby.
Warning:
Patient's heart rate rising.
Blood pressure
230 over 110 and increasing.
252 over 140 and increasing.
Blood pressure
286 over 190 and increasing.
303 over 215 and increasing.
Nancy, I think
he wants to talk to you.
What?
Warning:
Heart rate critical.
Blood pressure
310 over 250 and increasing.
383 over 290 and increasing.
Elliot, do something!
Oh my God.
- (screeching)
- (mutants growling)
You better get Viallini.
We can't wait until tomorrow.
We gotta fire up Agnes now.
Nancy, go now! Find Viallini.
And get right back here... I'm gonna
need help getting Michael downstairs.
(flatlines)
(screaming)
Doctor, it's Michael.
(buzzing)
Computer: Warning: This area
is now at condition three
anomaly alert status.
(screaming)
Please use caution.
Red alert. Red alert.
Emergency override
condition three.
Red alert.
Halon compression
system at standby.
Red alert. Red alert.
And this was last night?
Last night, early this morning.
So, you really have no idea
what this thing looks like.
My God, it doesn't
matter what he looks like.
Believe me,
there will be no doubt
in your mind when you see him.
Sherry, you're
acting ridiculous.
You are really paranoid.
He was lying to me.
He told me my father never even
showed up for work last night,
that he called in sick.
All right, all right,
so maybe your father did call in sick.
Maybe he had other plans,
personal plans that Viallini
wouldn't let him off work for.
He would have told me.
He would never leave Kim
and me this long without calling.
Maybe he did call.
You've been gone all day.
You're leaving the room.
I didn't even think about
the answering machine.
I just got it
a few days ago.
Answering machine:
Hi, handsome.
I just wanted to make sure
you're still going to stop by.
I've got the martinis chilling.
I'll be waiting. Ciao.
See, what did I tell you?
Your father probably got lucky...
Shh!
Hi, honey. I guess
you're still at the movies.
I stopped off at Susan's
for a drink before work.
I left my ID pass at home.
I was going
to ask you to bring it.
Don't worry about it.
I'll use Jerry's pass tonight.
I'm running late.
Gotta get to work.
Make sure Kim
gets to bed early.
See you tomorrow.
I love you.
They've got him.
They're holding him there.
What are you talking about?
He's been telling me about all the weird
things going on at that place.
Now they've got him.
Don't you think you're
being a little ridiculous?
He said he wanted to quit,
that they were making him nervous
with all the dangerous experiments
they've been doing
on animals and stuff.
They're probably
experimenting on him.
Sherry, Sherry, this is absurd.
Calm down.
Do you hear
what you're saying?
They don't do
experiments on people.
- I'm going out there.
- Out where?
Sherry!
Sherry, will you slow down a minute?
You're not thinking straight.
Hey, dude.
Where are you all off to?
Have you heard from Daddy yet?
They've got him.
I'm sure of it.
God knows what
they're doing to him.
Sherry, stop it.
You're going to scare Kim.
What's going on, Sherry?
Where's Dad?
We're gonna go find him.
He may be in trouble.
We don't know that, Sherry.
Kim, I want you to stay here.
He might call.
Screw that!
I'm going with you.
You're not going anywhere.
Someone's got to stay here
in case he calls.
Besides,
you'd never get in there.
You wanna bet?
Don't argue with me, Kim.
Just stay here.
- Screw you, Sherry.
- Sherry...
- Here, put this on.
- For what?
Do you think we're going to get in
because of these white coats?
No... because of this.
This is a security card.
Level five clearance.
This'll open
any door in the place.
Sher... Sherry!
We cannot afford
to make any mistakes...
any leaks outside of Talos.
When you find this thing,
I want you to destroy it.
I want there to be
no trace of its existence.
What about the woman, Dr. Kane?
If she cannot be
persuaded to cooperate,
to remain silent,
you shall have to arrange
an accident.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
(tires screech)
I can't believe
we're doing this.
Look, if you don't want
to go in, just tell me.
I mean if our relationship
means that little to you.
All right, all right,
all right, let's go.
Brian, this is my father.
I know.
Let's do it.
What a bitch!
Will you calm down?
You're making me nervous.
My God, he's enormous!
This is it. We're dead.
Will you act normal?
This isn't the mafia.
- (door buzzes)
- Access allowed.
Where are you going?
Come on, just act natural.
There'll be no problem.
- Late night tonight.
- Hi.
Hold it right there.
You forgot to sign in.
Sorry, million things on my mind.
Yeah, you know how it is
in the mutant business.
See you later.
Bye.
- (growling)
- Oh, shit!
(yelps)
You sure you got him?
TV: The people
of Penguin Computer
have given me just 15 seconds
to tell you about their new PC
the Puffin XL,
before they drop me into
this pit of poisonous vipers.
The Puffin XL cuts
data processing
and peripheral
download time in half,
allowing you extra time
for that creative touch.
And when you've got a deadline
to meet, you can't afford downtime.
- (man screams)
- The Puffin XL.
Don't let a deadline
get you down.
Man #1: The name of the game
is Stud. Ante up.
Man #2: Wait a minute.
What's the limit?
Man #1: Same as always, Ernie.
High-low, ante up.
Ernie: Wait a minute.
What are the chips for?
Man: Same as always, Ernie.
The whites are 50¢,
the reds are a buck
and the blues
are $5, okay? Ante up.
- (door buzzes)
- Ernie: Wait a minute...
Hey!
- (beeps)
- (door buzzes)
Son of a bitch!
What the hell's
the matter with you, anyway?
Making jokes like that?
What if he asked you for real ID?
- Then what would you have done?
- Relax, we made it through, didn't we?
That guy was
so stupid he probably... ahh!
Jesus Christ,
what the hell is that?
I don't know.
Let's just get
to Viallini's office.
- I don't believe this.
- Shh! Will you be quiet?
(falls down)
Shit!
Will you stop
fooling around?
What the hell exactly are
we looking for anyway?
Clues, evidence.
You're quite
the dick aren't you?
What?
Uh... a private dick.
Detective, I mean.
How do you expect
to access any information?
A system like this has got
to require security clearance.
You forget you're dealing
with the Princeton computer
cryptography champion
two years running.
There isn't a system
or circuit I can't break into.
Pardon me,
Miss Summa Cum Silicon Chip.
It's just going
to take some time.
- Wonderful.
- Computer: Access deni...
Access denied.
Brian, come here.
I think I've got it.
Access allowed.
These are the records
from last night?
He was here, Brian.
He logged in.
This proves it.
They have him, I know it.
It'll be all right.
We'll find him, I promise.
Ahh!
All right, what are
you two doing here?
We were just playing
"Star Trek" on the computer and...
Oh, a comedian.
You're the girl
who was here this afternoon.
- You're Griffin's daughter.
- What have you done with my father?
Where is he,
you bastards?
She's just a little upset.
She doesn't really mean "bastards."
Where is he?
I know you have him.
Shut her up!
Hey you son of a...
You punk.
Sherry, run, get help!
Call the police!
Call Viallini.
I'll get the girl.
(screams, grunts)
Ow!
Shit.
(screaming)
What the hell?
(gasps)
Jesus Christ.
Get the hell out of here.
(Mitchell screaming)
- (screams)
- Who are you?
- What are you doing here?
- Let go of me!
It's all right, I'm not going
to hurt you. Just calm down.
It's all right.
Just tell me who you are
and what you're doing here.
- I'm looking for my father.
- Your father?
You're John Griffen's daughter.
That's right.
And what have you done
with my father, you bitch?
Is your sister here, too?
No, just me.
- What's your name?
- Kim.
Kim. It's very dangerous
for you to be
running around
these hallways by yourself.
You're telling me.
What the fuck was that thing?
What thing?
What did you see, Kim?
It was this huge...
like, really gross...
I don't know what.
It ate some guy.
Jesus Christ, what the hell is
going on around here?
(screaming)
Now, Kim, I want you
to wait here. Don't be afraid.
I'm going to lock the door
so nothing can come in, okay?
Wait. I...
My sister Sherry,
she's here, too.
She may be in trouble.
I have to find her.
It's all right, Kim.
I'll find her. I promise.
Please, just wait here and keep
the door locked until I get back.
(Sherry screams)
Brian!
Computer: Syntax error.
Please enter reset code.
Information
does not compute.
Non sequitur.
Input is uncorrelated.
(screaming)
Kim, what the hell
are you doing here?
Kim, are you all right?
- (roars)
- (screams)
What the hell are
you doing out here?
I...
Oh, never mind.
Get out of my way.
Access allowed.
Come with me.
Kim, stay right here.
- Don't move.
- Where are you going?
There's some acid in
that cabinet over there,
if I can get to it.
- Be careful!
- (roars)
(screams)
Sherry!
Look out!
(screaming)
Come on, Sherry!
No!
(screaming)
Come on, Sherry,
move your ass!
Red alert. Red alert.
Where is it?
Back there in the lab.
You can't stop it,
not with that gun.
We have to get out
of here and get help.
Mitchell:
There is no way out.
The whole sector
is sealed off.
Quarantine status.
What in the hell are
we supposed to do?
Sherry, can we go home now?
You're not going anywhere.
- Red alert. Red alert.
- I've got a job to finish.
And you're going to help me.
Mitchell: Now get down
to blue sector double-zero.
Wait for me there.
Sherry, Sherry!
This is like, really insane.
Let's just get the hell out of here!
You heard what he said, the place
is sealed off. We're trapped in here.
There's got to be a way out.
Let's just go!
Kim, listen to me.
That thing in there...
it killed Daddy,
I'm sure of it.
Red alert. Red alert.
I'm sorry, Kim,
but if there's a way to stop it,
to kill it, I have...
we both have to do something,
at least to try.
Then can we go home?
(pounding)
Red alert. Red alert.
(pounding continues)
Warning:
Contamination alert.
All right, you ugly fucker,
come and get me.
I must be nuts.
Red alert. Red alert.
Blue sector.
Come on, Kim.
Red alert. Red alert.
This is it.
Oh, no. My security pass.
Kim, you wait here.
Sherry.
Be careful.
Red alert. Red alert.
Where are you going?
Come on, it's right behind me.
Damn!
- Kid, you got a pass?
- No.
Perfect.
Kim: What are
you doing?
Computer: Denied.
Access... access denied.
Come on, Sherry!
What the hell are you doing?
Mitchell: Here it is,
you'd better hurry.
Kim:
Hurry, Sherry!
(screams)
Access denied.
- Access allowed.
- That's it!
- (pounding)
- (screams)
Come on, this way.
Computer:
Primary control systems activated.
Damn it, Jarrett,
where the hell are you?
You dragged us down here,
don't you know how to use this thing?
I'm working on it.
Let me see that.
You understand this shit?
A little.
What the hell is
this thing, anyway?
A way for us to stop
that thing out there.
(typing)
Computer:
Please enter access code.
Release magnetic lock
to open accelerator doors.
That's it.
Accelerator engaged.
Particle flux:
10 to the 26th power.
They'll be test firing
in exactly two minutes.
Kim:
Test firing?
The particle accelerator that runs
in a two-mile arc just below us.
Please enter coupler
interface code now.
There it is.
Electron coupler.
Activated by this access code.
I got it.
- Hydraulic systems set.
- Okay, go.
Throttle control engaged.
Electron coupler deployed.
Magnetic stasis grid
locked and operational.
Don't touch those!
Who the...
- Negative flux phase shift C -2.38°.
- Wavelength.
97.42 megawatts?
I don't know
what this means.
Well, figure it out.
We've got less than a minute.
Hey, get off her back.
She's doing the best she can.
In 30 seconds that
won't be good enough.
I got it. I've got it.
Power output, magnetic coupling.
This is it!
You better be damn sure,
sweetheart.
It's gonna be
my ass out there.
What are you
talking about?
Someone has to draw him
beneath the dispersion plates.
I don't get paid
enough for this shit.
Are you crazy?
You can't go out there!
You want the job?
No screwing around.
When I get that thing
under that grid, you hit it.
I hope you've got
health insurance.
There's going to be
enough radioactivity
out there to microwave
half of Newark.
Don't remind me.
- Well, what should I do?
- Pray for me.
You're sure?
I've got it.
Error, error.
System shutdown.
- Please reset.
- I've got it!
System shutdown.
Please reset.
All right, open the door.
Come on.
- Shit!
- (both scream)
Come on.
Sit, you ugly mother...
Come to papa.
Flux capacitors engaged.
Now, hit it.
Get out of there!
Don't argue with me,
goddamn it!
Just do it!
(screaming)
Beam crash.
For Christ sakes,
what are you waiting for?
It's not working, damn it!
Please allow 1 minute,
52 seconds to recharge.
Kim, what are you doing?
- He saved my life!
- Kim, don't!
Sherry: Kim!
Kim!
No!
Kid, no!
Oh, come on!
No! No!
Over here!
No!
All right, you fucker,
try and swallow this.
20 seconds
to discharge capacity.
No!
10 seconds,
nine...
eight, seven, six...
five, four, three...
two, one.
Electron coupler at...
Turn it off!
Turn it off, it worked.
Electron flow terminated.
Radiation levels normal.
Neutron dispersion at 46%.
What the hell were
you waiting for?
You stupid bitch.
And you, you miserable fuck.
- What are you doing?
- Don't shoot him.
Sorry, girls.
Gotta tie up some loose ends.
Now get back in there.
Now!
Sorry, pally.
Doctor's orders.
Yeah, I'm gonna enjoy this.
That's right,
you son of a bitch, smile.
What the?
(screaming)
- (roars)
- (screams)
Accelerator at mid-cyle.
Please allow 27 seconds...
Danger. Danger.
- What are you doing?
- I don't know.
Overload status.
Warning. Warning.
Electron continuity terminated.
Magnetic stress
function nominal.
Electron depletion
at minus 26,000 RMS.
Neutron absorption:
12 billion KTS per cubic centimeter.
Radiation level acceptable.
Is it over?
I certainly hope so.
Let's go home.
Primary path
systems online.
- (screams)
- Ahh!
Brian!
We thought you were dead.
The creature...
how did you escape?
Just lucky, I guess.
- Oh!
- Ah, sorry.
Quarantine status lifted.
All sectors secured.
Have a nice day.
Sherry!
- (squealing)
- (screaming)
(rumbling)
(growling)
♪ I was used to you, baby ♪
♪ Used to be anyhow ♪
♪ How you used to do me, baby ♪
♪ Ain't the way you do me now ♪
♪ You were nice to me, baby ♪
♪ Baby, must've been
like you ♪
♪ But, sugar, you turned
to spice on me, baby ♪
♪ What am I supposed to believe? ♪
♪ You're like someone
new to me, baby ♪
♪ You've changed,
changed, changed ♪
♪ What you want
to do to me, baby? ♪
♪ It's strange, so strange ♪
♪ You don't seem
like you to me, baby ♪
♪ You've cha-aanged ♪
♪ Seems impossible, baby ♪
♪ You don't even look
the same ♪
♪ A whole new kind
of animal, baby ♪
♪ But too wild to tame ♪
♪ You're like someone
new to me, baby ♪
♪ You've changed,
changed, changed ♪
♪ What you want
to do to me, baby? ♪
♪ It's strange, so strange ♪
♪ You don't seem
like you to me, baby ♪
♪ You've cha-aanged ♪
♪ You're like someone
new to me, baby ♪
♪ You've changed,
changed, changed ♪
♪ What you want
to do to me, baby? ♪
♪ It's strange, so strange ♪
♪ You're like someone
new to me, baby ♪
♪ You've changed,
changed, changed ♪
♪ The crazy things
you do to me, baby ♪
♪ They're strange, so strange ♪
♪ You don't seem
like you to me, baby ♪
♪ You've cha-aanged ♪
♪ Changed, changed, changed ♪
♪ You don't seem
like you to me, baby ♪
♪ You've changed,
changed, changed ♪
♪ You're like someone new to me ♪
♪ You've changed,
changed, changed ♪
♪ Oh, the crazy things
you do to me, baby ♪
♪ You've changed,
changed, changed ♪
♪ I was used to you. ♪
(harpsichord music playing)
(music stops)