(MUSIC)
- Go, go, go!
- (BOTH WHOOPING)
Oh, I love racing! (LAUGHS)
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh, here we go!
No, that's the queen, Craig. Just let it go.
What? Let it go?
Yes. Let... it... go.
- But they...
- I said let it go!
- ANNA: We can't lose to my sister!
- (KRISTOFF WHOOPING)
Hang on tight, Olaf.
We're in for a bumpy ride.
(WHOOPING)
Oh, look, I'm defying gravity.
Go, go, go! Come on, Sven!
Move that furry tail!
(GROANS)
(BOTH WHOOPING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(GRUNTS)
Did we win?
Yay, we tied!
Everyone's a winner and a loser.
Wow, look!
It's the...
sky!
Was I supposed to just see the sky?
You guys need to get out more.
Father's weather glass says today
should be the day of the first sighting.
I was hoping we would see them. Together.
Oh, why? (ECHOING) Why?
I know you're the queen, but let's try
not to be a drama queen, okay?
What exactly are the northern lights?
- Hey, my nose!
- (CHUCKLES)
Everyone knows the northern lights are
the Valkyries moving across the night,
while others say
they're nature's night-light.
SVEN: Wrong again, Kristoff. The northern
lights are the result of collisions
between numerously electrically
charged particles from the sun
entering the Earth's atmosphere.
Everybody get that?
Okay. I'm taking away your library card.
So, we need a plan of action.
If the northern lights won't come to us,
then we'll go to the northern lights.
Let's pack it up and get going.
- Go, go, go!
- Where?
To wherever the northern lights come from.
You're "Mr. Mountain Man," you must know.
(SCOFFS)
Mr. Mountain Man was my father, please.
Just Mountain Man will do. And I have
no idea where they are. I'm not magic.
Sometimes, you gotta make your own magic.
Welcome home.
I know one person who knows all about magic.
Please, not the trolls.
ALL: He's gone!
(CHEERING)
- (LAUGHING)
- (MUSIC)
(LAUGHING)
What do you mean Grand Pabbie isn't here?
- Oh, he headed out on the northern trail.
- (GASPS)
- We should go find him!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait a second.
A sister-sister adventure!
Filled with sing-a-longs
and near-death experiences. Hooray!
Okay. Sounds like it'll take
a true mountain man and...
since I'm the only one here with a degree
from Mountain Man University,
I'll lead the way.
(CHANGES VOICE) Nothing's safer than being
alone in the woods with a mountain man.
Have he and Sven always had... conversations?
Yeah. Started quite a while ago.
Sven, should I have
another piece of carrot cake?
(CHANGES VOICE) Carrot cake is healthy.
Well, looks like you have
everything you need.
(LAUGHING)
Ooh, sorry about that.
(CHUCKLES)
- What are these, Anna?
- Uh...
Don't worry,
there's always a few extra pieces.
So, how many miles does this thing do?
Is it hard to look at the back
of a reindeer all day?
This is a hybrid, right?
So, how much reindeer power
does this thing have?
- (SLURPING)
- One.
Okay, I've got some ideas for our adventure.
- Uh, Anna...
- Actually, I have close to 100 ideas...
Oh, no!
Ideas might be the wrong word,
more like springboards.
Just... just... just...
Wow, if you need to sing about, okay,
but we'll find the northern lights.
It's my new mission.
You know how I am when I'm on a mission.
I'm not talking about that, Anna.
I'm talking about that!
Avalanche! Run, Sven, run!
Oh, no!
Anyone else feel that breeze?
- Watch out!
- Whoa!
Thunderous hurricane
of destruction wants to say hello!
Hello, Mr. Ava... Oh!
(GRUNTS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Come on. Come on. Give me a hand here.
- (BELL DINGING)
- Whoa, Pistachio!
- Whoa, Cannonball!
- You've got to be kidding me!
I told ya, we should have taken the Polar
Expressway. We'd already be there.
- Zip it. Zip it, Craig. Zip it.
- (TRAIN HORN BLOWING)
OLAF: Oh, look, we're in a snow globe!
Now it's snowing, now it's not.
I can do this all day.
(ALL SHOUTING)
That was... weird.
My powers were a bit too strong?
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(THUD)
I'm all right! Good thing I'm boneless, huh?
(CHUCKLES)
Wait! (GASPS)
Arm... ageddon!
Whew! Huh?
See guys? Mountain man.
Great! Now let's get your sleigh
up and running.
(GRUNTS)
Uh, what was up with that, sis?
Yeah, my powers seem a bit, um...
off, don't they?
(SIGHS) I think getting upset
about it will only make it worse.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Don't get upset.
If I didn't have
mad survival skills out here,
Sven and I would have been in trouble.
Watch. I'll show you how to build a fire.
There are at least 56 different ways
of rubbing sticks together to create fire.
- (GASPS) My arms!
- (GROANS)
I'm armed and dangerous.
ELSA:
Oh, Kristoff, don't worry about the fire.
The cold never bothered me anyway. (CHUCKLES)
Get it? Okay, we have to finish
rebuilding the sleigh and keep moving.
I know a place with the best view in town.
The northern lights are barely visible.
Even from here. This is terrible.
I still haven't seem them
in all their amazingness.
We need to get to them
before they all disappear.
No worries, Olaf. I'll create an ice slide
so we can quickly get back to the trail.
OLAF: Ooh, that's resourceful.
A slide! Huh?
OLAF: Ooh, an exploding slide.
Hmm. Okay, alternate approaches.
This is my department.
I think we can kayak farther north. Hm.
Uh, no. I think we should
kayak farther north.
She literally just said that.
Stop "man-splaining."
Oh. Well, uh... good idea, Anna.
- (GIGGLING) Little brothers!
- Wait a minute.
I bet little brothers
could give us a little help.
Okay, guys, it's go time!
(GROWLING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
- (KRISTOFF GROANS)
- (LAUGHTER)
Oh, we're safe.
(ALL SHOUTING)
Well, looks like it's just you
and me, big guy.
(ALL SHOUTING)
(MUSIC)
(CAMERA CLICKS)
- (ALL SHOUTING)
- (CAMERA CLICKS)
(ALL SHOUTING)
Ow! Ow!
(PANTING) Oh! That feels nice.
Huh, that one came out a little weird.
The ears are way too big. Try again.
- Oh, I bet Sven likes that one.
- (SVEN GRUNTS)
I don't know what's happening
to me, this is so strange.
Whoa, boy! Steady.
- (GASPS)
- Um, what are you doing?
Well, there's a fjord in front of us,
and mountain men don't swim.
But we need to get there,
to the Great Glacier.
- To see the northern lights.
- We'll never make it.
I think we need to think positive.
Hooray! We'll never make it! (CLEARS THROAT)
Was that positive enough?
It's no use,
we'll never see the northern lights.
Oh! Look, she's gonna sing. I know this one.
(MUSIC STARTS)
(MUSIC STOPS)
I don't feel like singing right now.
Just not feeling it.
Good news!
I think I've solved all our problems.
(FRENCH ACCENT)
Welcome to Château du Kristoff.
(NORMAL VOICE) Complete with a 24-hour
salad buffet and complementary ratatouille.
We can stay here
until the fjord freezes over.
Sitting in an ice palace does us no good.
- We need to get over there.
- Yeah, but... (SIGHS)
Fine. The birds can use this one.
(BIRDS SQUAWKING)
No problem, I'll scout ahead.
Didn't... think... that... through!
- Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
- Probably. Not.
- But I'm sure it'll be inventive.
- Oh, it is. You're gonna love it!
Wow! Impressive redesign.
But, uh... how do you expect
to go anywhere without a motor?
I've never felt so close to nature before.
(LAUGHS)
It's nice to have this adventure with you,
Elsa. Just like when we were little.
And now we're big.
We can have bigger adventures.
I think we're close.
(GRUNTS)
Yup, we're pretty close. (LAUGHING)
- Wow! Look!
- (GASPS) The northern lights?
No. Another incredibly difficult obstacle.
(LAUGHING)
Looks like we're gonna have
to do some climbing. Okay.
So, we can make our way up this crevasse,
then transition farther up the glacier.
We don't even have climbing gear,
feisty boots.
And if you think there's a store within
50 miles of here, you're going cuckoo.
Yoo-hoo! Did I hear somebody
needs some climbing gear?
Seriously?
So, you're the first customers here
in my new store. (CHUCKLES LIGHTLY)
- Sauna?
- I feel like letting off a little steam.
(GASPS) Olaf, don't. Bad idea!
But it's so... warm.
(SHOUTING)
Big sale on frozen goods.
Tasty snow cone or fish sticks. Or ice cubes.
In this cold?
Who in their right mind would want...
Oh, snow cones!
Look at the pretty little colors.
Blue, green... ooh, yellow.
Yellow... wait, yellow snow!
Oh, no! No!
Going to see the lights, yeah.
I got the climbing gear you need.
Big winter blowout. Still, a bit pricey.
You know, supply and demand.
Pricey, eh? Look, pal,
you can't just jack up your prices...
(GROWLS)
...advantage of people!
(GROANS)
Chill out, everybody. I'm okay, I'm cool.
- A bit too cool, actually.
- (SCOFFING)
Also sell fishing rods.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
Whew! That... was quite the climb.
You know something,
it really didn't feel that bad.
(GASPS)
The northern lights! Aren't they beautiful?
Wow!
They look tiny.
Maybe I need to get my eyes checked, huh?
Ooh. No, now they're tinier.
Oh, pretty!
But why are they here
and not over our kingdom?
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
- You're going on a diet, Sven.
- (BELLOWS)
Kristoff, hold on! Elsa, can you do anything?
You, again. We have to find a name for you.
Ouch!
Not helping.
- Ooh, frozen carrots.
- Mm!
- (SCREAMING)
- (GROANS)
Okay, really not helping.
I know. I'm trying!
But I'm just worried about the northern
lights and the kingdom, the past.
So cold.
Elsa, the past is in the past.
My powers are all out of whack.
It makes me so distraught.
- Oh, what can I do? What can I do?
- You can just let it go.
(GRUNTS)
Slipping, still slipping.
You guys, still slipp... ah!
That's the sound
of a mountain man in distress.
- But you promised me pancakes!
- Ah, we promise a lot.
- And syrup!
- Yeah. Let's ride!
Hang on there, Sven, you're doing great!
I second that, hang on!
I wish I had a tongue like that.
I wish I had a tongue.
- Anna!
- Kristoff!
Uh, you guys do realize you're only,
like, three feet apart, right?
Well, yeah, okay.
But how are we gonna save them?
Stretching, stretching. Really stretching!
(SCREAMING)
Got it! (GRUNTING, SHOUTING)
Gross, tongue!
(GASPS)
Grand Pabbie! It's so good to see you!
We have this question
about the northern lights.
- Not now.
- Huh?
Now, we must... (STRAINING) pull.
- Oh, right.
- (GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING) A little bit... more!
Whew!
Wow, I guess I didn't know my own strength.
And they call me twig arms.
Technically that is true.
Grand Pabbie, we finally found you!
- What are you doing up here?
- Something very important.
Please tell me you brought your crystals?
Right, crystals. Uh, I am definitely
pretty mostly sure I brought those.
I think I stuck them in...
Yes! Oh, yes, we have them.
Oh, those things.
GRAND PABBIE: Good.
Every 500 years I must come here
to where the earth touches the sky.
Then, yadda-yadda-yadda,
mystical stuff happens and voila,
northern lights.
Enjoy!
The four crystals will refract
the light to each corner of Arendelle.
Don't worry.
- (LAUGHS) Oh, we weren't worried.
- Hm.
Okay, we were a little worried.
I'm just so, so happy
to see the northern lights again.
It feels like... the first time in forever.
- (GIGGLES) That sounds familiar.
- (LAUGHTER)
GRAND PABBIE: My job is done.
500 years and they almost
didn't bring their crystals.
(MUSIC)
All right, all right, everyone.
Party is over.
Oh! Already? Come on!
No! It's early.
(GROWLING)
(SIGHS)
Well, well, well.
Thought we'd never catch ya, huh?
(GASPS)
Wow. Gorgeous. Incredible.
Uh, sir? The... he's, um...
Darn it, Craig, you had one job to do.
- One job. One job.
- He was right there.
- I had my arm around him.
- Oh, Craig.
(SIGHS) We had quite the adventure.
I know. I don't think I've ever seen
the northern lights brighter.
I don't think I've ever seen
the northern lights. Wait a second.
Yes, I have! The sky is awake.
The sky is awake. Remember Anna?
That's how we used to call them.
(GASPS) Happy thoughts,
happy thoughts. Puppies, kittens.
(LAUGHS)
Your magic is back.
(CHUCKLES) Wow!
We need a place to sit and watch the show.
Oh, impressive.
But, ooh, you know,
it's a bit chilly on my buns.
Maybe a cushion made of eagle feathers,
bear claws, and tree fungus.
Something with some smelly mountain man musk.
This looks great though.
And tonight, as an added bonus,
I get my first frozen hot chocolate.
- There you go.
- Mm!
(SIGHS)
Like a cup of fresh mountain air.
(GRUNTS) And I got to share
all of this with my little sister.
And I got to share it with my big sister.
- Go on, Elsa. Sing it.
- (MUSIC STARTS)