(silence)
[Bus Driver] Last stop, Cawdor.
(bus engine running)
Subrip by DanDee
(train horn blowing)
(wind howling)
[First Witch] Beware the man
that swings from the rafters!
[Second Witch] Beware
the man that swings.
[Third Witch] Beware!
[First Witch] Who never
lets go, can't let go, beware!
(eerie music)
[Vivian] Have
you been here long?
Not really.
Maybe awhile, I'm not sure.
Feels like I've
been here forever,
my ride will be
here soon though.
Where are you going?
Not far, the
Cawdor Barn Theater.
I love the theater.
Something really special
about it, don't you think?
I've never been to the theater,
it's just something
that I have to do.
You'll like it.
Oh, my ride really
needs to hurry up,
I'm tired of waiting.
(sobbing)
Hey, are you okay?
(cans clanging)
[Roddy] Morning, Miss!
Good day for
collecting cans, huh?
You just get off the bus?
Uh yeah, yeah.
All right, well
welcome to Cawdor.
Nice having you in town,
you visiting friends?
No, working, at
The Barn Theater?
Oh, The Barn Theater,
that's such a great place.
It's been here as long
as I can remember.
But, you know, I
always stop in there
and say hi, they really like me.
You know what, I'll
come by and visit you.
Who are you?
I'm Roddy.
Vivian.
You going home after?
Home?
Nope, no, there is no home.
(car honking)
Oh, that's my ride.
See ya later, Vivian.
Wait, Roddy, did you
see where that girl...
Went?
Vivian, I am so
sorry, I am so behind.
(wind howling)
(soft piano music)
¶ When the night speaks
far in the corridor
¶ Asleep, the wind,
lullaby baby dear
¶ Here in the dark, this lullaby
¶ La la la, la la la ¶
(song distorts and fades)
(blows whistle)
Everybody, tighten it up!
Eyes front, roll call!
You hear your name, I
wanna hear a yes sir!
Lance Cole.
Yes, sir.
[Charles] Brian Daly.
Yup!
I said I wanna hear a yes sir,
you get it right!
Yes, sir.
Gary Baines.
Michael Cross.
Yes, sir!
Neil Stams.
Yezzir.
Tina Bailey.
Yes, sir.
Mackenzie Cane.
Yes, sir!
Teri Welles.
Yes, sir.
Lisa LaFontaine.
Vivian Miller.
Yes, sir.
Okay, I wanna introduce you to
the Camp Coordinator and
Theater Owner, Mr.
Lawrence O'Neil.
Thank you, Chuck.
Welcome to The Barn Theater.
Because you've
earned enough points
for good behavior from the camps
you were are, we
were able to strike
a deal with your
Probation Officers
for you to complete
your phase three
work release program here.
Now as you've probably surmised,
this place is not
like any other camp.
In fact, we don't even
like to call it a camp.
The State does mandate
that we run it like one.
I won't lie to you,
there's tough chores ahead,
and you will need
to continue your
GED studies while
under our supervision.
In between, we will put on
a stage play for the locals
which falls under the category
of behavioral therapy.
Now it's a special
year, an anniversary.
After 20 long years,
we're gonna do
a play that's close to my heart.
Superstition says
that we never say
its name in the
theater, instead,
we refer to it as
The Scottish Play.
Participation is mandatory,
and you will get to
perform dual roles as well
as rotate backstage duties.
A word about security.
I want you to look around you.
Go ahead, look.
As you can see, there
are no fences here.
No barbed wire, no watchtower.
That's because
they're not necessary.
We're over 20 miles
from the nearest town,
you will be caught,
so put the idea
of escape out of your minds.
Our staff, Mr. Kosack will be in
charge of your work duties,
Mr. Seals, head of
our studies, and
I of course run the
theater program.
Make the most of your time here
and it will pass quickly.
Mr. Kosack will now give
you your orientation.
Thank you, Chuck.
[Charles] What, Brian?
I've never really acted before.
I'll chip in here,
fundraise or something,
I could maybe sell some weed.
It's kinda how I
came to be here.
I'll bet you're a fine actor.
Shit, you've been acting like a
fucking asshole for
a long time, right?
Unlike the courts, we don't do a
three strikes and
you're out around here.
One rule violation
and you're gone.
The judge will double your time.
You will be behind
bars until the
snow flies next
Christmas, any questions?
Yup.
Seriously, I'm no actress,
so what am I supposed to do?
Well, you can address
me as Sir, little girl,
and when it comes
time for the play
you can stand in the back
and be a fucking tree.
I don't really care.
Meantime, you can
clean the shitters.
Now let me be perfectly clear.
I can't make you do anything
you don't want to do,
but I can make you wish you had.
Trust me.
Let's go!
(dramatic music)
Welcome to your new home
for the next three months.
By day, it's a working
scene shop for set building,
we got your paint
room, my tools which
will be locked up,
and by night you
got your sleeping quarters.
Big curtain on the
ceiling comes down
every night for
a little privacy.
Men over there,
women on this side.
Yeah.
It's gonna get
cold pretty soon,
you got any heaters
to keep it warm?
We got some space heaters
if it gets too cold.
Some barn fans
for some air flow.
Up at 6 AM for roll
call, calisthenics,
breakfast, and then
the fun begins.
Paintings, grounds striders,
(creaking)
set building, and
rehearsals for Macbeth.
[Tina] Thought
that was bad luck.
Ah, that's just theater folk.
I apprenticed at
Chino State Prison.
We didn't worry about no
Shakespeare curse up in there.
Moving on!
(dramatic music)
All right, everybody
grab a seat.
All right.
Back there, dressing
room for the guys,
women's on the
opposite side, got
lockers and showers inside.
TV room for a couple hours
after dinner for fun.
No cable, but all the plays
we've ever done on DVD.
(groaning)
With cable down here, you
little shits would never leave.
It's a couple hours after
dinner and then lights out.
Ladies, stay put.
Men, follow me.
Come on, all right, let's go.
Let's go, let's go!
All right.
Your name, padlock, and key are
on your locker, lose your key,
you run a couple extra
miles in the morning.
If I catch you
stealing, I call your
probation officer after
I kick your sorry ass.
Hey!
You feel me?
Work clothes are in your locker.
Dress and be out front in 15.
Man, love that guy!
Dude, he'd just as soon
shiv ya as look at ya.
Chino State Prison,
man, he'll mess you up.
Go get him, man, we'll
all be right behind you.
How?
Big slow bastard, wouldn't
know what hit him.
Cool down, sweetheart, or it's
gonna be a long three months.
(chuckling)
All right, dress and
be out front in 10.
Well, we're not waking up from
this nightmare anytime soon.
Let's go.
Hey.
I think I need to get in there.
Oh, sorry.
No problem.
I don't think we've met yet.
I'm Tina.
Possession of a controlled
substance and a DUI.
Hell of a night.
I'm Vivian.
What, no sharing
your rap sheet?
Oh, shoplifting, I got
caught one too many time.
Life in the big city.
(eerie music)
(loud bang)
(ghostly whispers)
Number 10, late!
Sorry, sir.
Okay, work details.
On this board each
morning, start
your day looking at it.
It's already past noon,
be a short one today.
All right, dinner
bell rings at 6 PM,
after that Mr. O'Neil
will talk to you
about the show and
tomorrow's auditions.
Okay, find your
job, get to work!
Let's go!
Brush clearing?
Bunch of shit.
What the hell are
you bitching about,
me and Vivian gotta
clean toilets.
Well ladies, you get bored in
there, I could entertain you.
Oh dream on!
Let's go.
(wood chipper running)
Don't stand there,
dummy, it's dangerous!
Pay attention, huh?
All right, there's
the wood pile.
I want you to finish
that before dinner.
You're kidding, anything else?
Yeah, watch out for snakes.
(wood chipper revs)
Snakes?
Supplies are here.
Mmmm, I'm gonna go check
out the girl's bathroom.
I'll be right back.
(door opening)
(stall doors
opening and closing)
[Roddy] Hey!
(laughing)
What are you doing here?
I told you, I come
by here sometimes,
I saw your name
on the board and,
you know, saw
where they put you.
I'm sorry, are you okay?
Yes.
Anyway, hi.
Hi.
Kind of stinks in here.
It wasn't me.
Yeah, well I've cleaned worse.
Roddy, maybe you
shouldn't hang around,
Charles might not like visitors.
They like me
here, it's all good.
When did you work here?
(wood chipper running)
You know what, I don't
wanna get you in trouble.
Oh.
Charles might be off his meds.
(laughs)
I'll be around this Fall.
Now I got a reason to visit.
Bye.
Help!
Help me please, help me!
Somebody!
Hurry, it's Brian!
[Charles] What
the hell happened?!
Goddamn chipper!
Almost chewed me up
is what happened!
I told you, you
gotta pay attention.
You're lucky I saw you
and hit that kill switch.
Could have had Brian
chips all over.
(laughing)
It's not funny!
I nearly died!
Goddamn chipper
tried to kill me.
Okay guys, hang back.
Ladies first.
Our meals are a
little different here
than what you get in Juvie.
This is food you
can actually eat.
Go ahead.
Tonight, we got beef stroganoff,
fresh lake trout, some kind of
vegetable, strawberry shortcake.
I got my eye on you.
(classical music)
Well what kind of
group we got this year?
Eh, nothing I can't handle.
Eyes front!
[Lawrence] Let's see what
these kids are made of.
All right, who here...
Has heard of
William Shakespeare?
Anyone?
No?
Well William Shakespeare
is considered
to be the greatest
playwright known to mankind.
In fact, every 12
minutes one of his
plays is being performed
somewhere in the world.
Now why is that, hmm?
Why?
400 years ago, he
was writing about
things that still matter,
that still resonate today.
War, sex, violence, betrayal,
ambition, lust, murder.
Things that I'm sure some
of you can relate to.
Frank.
Now this play...
This play is about a man's...
Ultimate quest for power.
And his wife's driving
ambition to achieve
their dreams at any cost.
It's perhaps the most
violent of his plays
and includes all
the things I just
mentioned including witchcraft.
OooOooOoo.
Which accounts for
the superstition
associated with the play.
Now I don't want you to be
intimidated by the text.
Don't overanalyze it, okay?
All the answers you need
are right there on the page.
Now of course if you
have any questions,
you can always come
to me or to Frank.
We'll be happy to help you.
I will bend and twist
you band of misfits
and delinquents into
the most marvelous
characters ever
written for the stage.
We start tomorrow,
so hit the script,
and I'll see you all
in the morning, okay?
Chuck.
[Charles] Okay, wrap it up!
Lights out at nine.
Hey, we're all gonna go watch
old plays in the TV
room, wanna come?
Sure.
So on a scale of
one to 10, how bad
do you think this run's
gonna be in the morning?
(laughing)
[Brian} Uhh, Man of La Mancha?
[Lance] No!
Booo!
[Brian] A Flea in Her Ear!
[Lance] Oh sweet Jesus, no!
[Brian] Richard the Third.
[Tina] Oh come on, blech!
Yeah, here we go, crazy kids,
stabbing horses, nudity!
Equus it is!
[Voiceover] Have you never
seen a DVD player before?
You know (mumble).
[Tina] Okay, all right.
(neighs)
This one particular horse
called Nugget, he embraces.
The animal digs his snout into
his cheek, and in the dark.
[Melissa] (on TV screen)
Take your sweater off.
[Kevin] (on TV screen) What?
I will if you will.
(eerie music)
(door lock clicks)
(ghostly whispers)
I put it in her.
(mumble).
(door creaks open)
(whispers intensify)
[Voiceover] (on TV
screen) He was in the way.
[Kevin] (on TV screen) No!
No more!
Equus, thou God seeth nothing!
(groaning)
Kill me, kill me, kill me!
[Tina] Well that was
some fucked up shit.
(laughing)
Yeah.
So 'cause the guy
couldn't get it on with
the girl, he just stabbed
the horse's eyes out?
It's not that simple.
Religion and God and sex are all
mixed up for the
kid, plus he saw
his old man coming
out of a porno show,
that'd give anybody limp dick.
(laughing)
You're smarter than you look.
Sexy.
Hey big boy, that
was a compliment.
Hey Mackenzie,
walk with me and
I'll show you exactly
how smart I am.
Let's go!
Charles'll be busting
our chops soon anyway.
(laughs) All right,
well I'm hitting the hay.
Ha, no pun intended.
Me and the comedian are
gonna get out of here.
Goodnight, Vivian.
Yeah, I get it.
You don't like me.
But maybe you're frigid?
You don't know me.
I know your type.
The hot girl, thinks she's
better than everybody else.
Thinks that perfect
guy is going to
come along and take her
away from her shitty life.
Well that guy don't want
you, you're damaged goods.
You say you're in
here for shoplifting?
I say bullshit!
Whatever you really
did, you better
get used to guys like me 'cause
I'm all you're gonna get.
(dramatic music)
Macbeth, 1994.
(thunder booming)
Help me!
Help me, Vivian!
(gate slams shut)
Jesus, Roddy, what the hell?
That's how my mother
used to greet me.
Sorry, I just,
you surprised me,
but what are you doing here?
I was looking for
some part time work,
but I think Lawrence
is already in bed,
so I'm just gonna have
to keep coming back.
[Charles] (blows whistle) Hey!
You two in the bushes!
Knock it off, lights out!
I think that's my "cue".
(laughs) You get
it, 'cause we're,
'cause it's a theater, right?
Because in the th.
(footsteps approaching)
Come on, Vivian.
You follow the rules
like everybody else.
Didn't you hear my whistle?
Yes, sorry, I just,
I lost track of time.
(gate closes)
What was that?
Okay, Vivian.
Hey, just do what you're told,
these next three months
will fly right by, okay?
Okay.
Okay, now get.
(static sounds)
[Mackenzie] (sharp
inhale) Oh, you are bad.
Real bad.
[Lance] Shhh.
(door lock clicks)
(eerie noises)
(ghostly whispers)
[Vivian] No, stop please!
[Charles] (blows
whistle) Okay smokeys!
Rise and shine!
Time for the morning run,
get that blood flowing, huh?!
(blows whistle multiple times)
[Tina] We're up!
Come on, I want to see
those feet on the ground,
that's it, ladies, now
you see how it works!
(blows whistle) Come
on, wakie wakie!
I stop blowing when I see
all your pretty
feet on the ground!
You'll always blow!
(blows whistle loudly)
Shit!
Did you just shit me?
You don't give me shit!
I give you shit!
Now drop and give me 10!
One, two, three,
four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine,
nine, nine, nine, 10!
Suit up for roll call!
(blows whistle)
Come on, assholes,
try and keep up, let's go!
(dramatic music)
Can I help you?
Mr. O'Neil.
Yes?
Good morning,
I'm Doctor Lazarus.
Oh, hi.
I wanted to talk to you about
a woman in your
care, Vivian Miller?
Sure.
This'll only
take a few minutes.
- Yeah, come on in my office.
- Thanks.
Where did you drive in from?
Oh, Ann Arbor.
Oh, nice.
Beautiful place here.
Thank you.
Excuse the mess, I wasn't
expecting visitors.
Where would you like me?
Sofa is fine.
Want some coffee?
Yeah, that'll be great, thanks.
Milk, sugar?
Black please.
A Tony Award.
Oh, heh.
Pretty heady
stuffy, you must have
been the toast of Broadway.
Well for a moment.
You know what they say.
You're only as good
as your last hit.
Three straight bombs and your
table at Sardi's is gone.
In fact, you're
lucky to get a table
at the Carnegie Deli with
three bombs in a row.
Yup, Broadway loves
a winner, but it
crosses on the other side
of the street for a loser.
You know what most people don't
understand is that
art can be like,
like a popularity
contest, you know?
You do what you feel
is your best work,
love what you do,
but if the audience
doesn't show up then
you're out of a job.
Most people don't work
under those conditions.
But enough about me,
you're here about Vivian.
I've been her
Psychiatrist for six years
the entire time
she's been locked up.
I thought it'd be best if I
gathered some info for you.
What is it exactly
that you do here?
Oh, we focus mainly
on behavioral therapy,
psychodrama, we get the kids to
act out their issues on stage
and break their bad habits,
form better relationships,
and hopefully in the
process broaden their
horizons a little.
We feel if we've gotten
through to at least one
of them that we've
accomplished something.
Do you know what
Vivian was in for?
No, I haven't gotten
to her file yet.
Murder.
She was 15, abuse was going on.
Got a plea deal down
to Manslaughter,
but she's been in and out
of psych wards ever since.
The court request that
I meet with Vivian on a
regular basis to review how
she's doing before the release.
I'd like to see Vivian
right now if it's okay.
Yeah, sure, should just
be finishing up her run.
(vomiting)
Oh come on!
Vivian, someone here
wants to speak with you.
Hi, Doctor Lazarus.
Can we talk once
you've cleaned up?
[Charles] You filthy pig!
Sure, yeah, after
breakfast in the Dining Hall?
Dining Hall is right through
those double doors, Doc.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[Charles] Breakfast
in half an hour!
Ladies, your
auditions are today!
Men, your duties
are on the board!
How you holding up?
I'm getting too
old for this shit.
You and me both.
So there any lady
queens in this group?
We've got a few queens in this
group, if you know what I mean.
(laughing)
Why don't you go shower up and
I'll see you after breakfast.
Yeah.
Kind of noisy last
night, weren't you?
What are you talking about?
Like shooting fish in
a barrel around here.
So guess your aim is off then.
You didn't shoot nothing, right?
[Gary] Or he's shooting blanks.
(laughing)
Kiss my ass, bee-yatch!
So did you hear
about the first screw?
Yeah, we know it was
Lance, we're just
trying to narrow down the ho.
Yeah, my money's on Mackenzie.
Oh well, we'll figure it out.
It's gonna be a
long 90 days, hmm?
[Jeanette] (ghostly
wail) Help me!
(classical music)
Hi.
It's good to see you, Vivian.
How's this place treating you?
It's better than a
normal camp, I guess.
You look tired, are
you getting enough sleep?
A little.
I...
I think I need to be
back on my meds though.
Okay, I left some
with Mr. O'Neil.
A small dose, I want to
start weening you off of it.
No no, I need to be
on my regular dose.
Is the OCD getting worse?
No, it's not, it's not,
it's not getting worse,
it's just, it's there, you know?
What else?
I've been hearing things.
What kind of things?
Things that may not be real?
Okay, like what?
Well earlier by
my locker there
was this tapping sound.
Are you sure there's
no construction
going on upstairs,
maybe sets being built?
Yeah, maybe
there was, but then
I swear I heard a voice.
What'd the voice say?
It asked for help.
Okay.
Anything else?
Yeah, just yesterday
at the bus depot,
I saw this girl and she was just
so different, it was
like I knew her somehow?
Where from?
I don't know, I'm
probably wrong, never mind.
You know Vivian,
you had a real
tough time not too long ago.
I really feel that
our time together
has improved your situation, I'm
not saying that
there's not work left.
But I agree with the
court, in less than
90 days you can re-enter
society, live a normal life.
I'll never be normal.
You will.
I feel that the
anxiety or stress
of your transitioning
from the juvenile
then prison system are
causing these problems.
You'll be okay, I promise.
You'll be okay, Vivian.
Hey, who's the stiff?
Proby Officer?
Yeah, kind of.
So do you wanna look over this
Lady Macbeth chick, 'cause
she was kinda bat-shit crazy.
Sure.
Morning everyone,
sorry I'm late.
Ladies, front and center.
Okay, I take it
all of you have read
the play and none of you
understood a word, right?
I remember the first
time I read Shakespeare,
I felt the same way.
I promise you, it'll get
easier with time, all right?
You guys ready to do this?
Yeah?
All right, let's have some fun.
Ladies.
All right Chuck, who's first?
[Charles] Mackenzie,
front and center.
Okay, Mackenzie, let
me give you the setting.
We are in the Scottish moors
sometime in the 11th century.
Do you know what period that is?
It was a long
time ago, I get it.
This Macbeth dude was all.
Stop stop stop stop
stop, outside, let's go.
[Charles] Everyone
out, let's get, let's go!
Come on, let's go, let's go!
Come on, come on,
ladies, outside!
(suspenseful music)
[Lawrence] Come on,
outside, outside, come on.
All right, once, twice, thrice.
Now spit.
What?!
Just do it, spit
on the ground.
Just do it.
All right, now curse.
Why?
Because it's the
only known remedy
for saying the
play's name in the
theater, curse, go on.
This is fucking bullshit!
Good enough, okay,
inside, inside.
Thank you, Chuck.
And don't do it again!
The curse can only be kept back
so long if you keep
summoning it, okay?
Okay, Mackenzie.
The lady queen is the
devilish wife of our hero
and her deadly
ambition drives him to
murder so that he can be
king and she can be queen.
Subsequently, their murders
drive her to madness.
Now let me ask you
something, Mackenzie.
Have you ever wanted
anything in life so badly
that you would go to
any extreme to get it?
Yeah.
This one time.
No no, don't tell
us, don't tell us.
Use the secret inside of you.
If you share too
much, you lose all
that magic and power,
you understand?
Just use the words, okay?
Whenever you're ready.
I have given suck
and know how tender
'tis to love the
babe that milks me.
I would, while it
was smiling in my
face, have plucked my nipple.
Um, okay, okay,
hold it right there.
Chuck, if I could have all
the ladies on stage please.
Life happens from the inside and
leaves you from your pores.
It's the same with acting.
You absorb it
inside and only then
can we see the affect outside.
Understand?
Never say result.
I'm sorry, what's
your name again?
Tina.
Thank you, Tina,
how did you feel
about Mackenzie's reading?
It sucked.
Fuck you.
Okay, Mackenzie, how did that
make you feel when
she said that?
You feel what, regret?
Humiliation?
Embarrassment, anger?
Right?
Same things I feel
every time I look
in the mirror in the morning.
That's oozing out of
your pores right now.
That's what we
want, don't act, be.
Okay?
You all have the potential
to do something great,
you just feel it inside, use it.
Don't fight it, just let it be.
You have a very expressive
face, you're very free.
Give it another shot?
Okay, all right,
Chuck, who's next?
[Charles] Teri.
[Lawrence] Okay, Teri,
let's give it a go.
I have given suck,
and know how tender
'tis to love the
babe that milks me.
I would, while it was
smiling in my face,
have plucked my nipple from his
boneless gums and
dashed the brains
out had I so sworn as
you have done to this.
Okay, Teri, you
have just told your
husband you would
pull your newborn baby
off your nipple, while
it was still feeding,
and kill it by
smashing its skull.
I want you to go
back and look at
that sense with
that in mind, okay?
Thank you.
All right Chuck, next please.
Vivian, front and center.
Okay Vivian,
whenever you're ready.
Come, you spirits that
tend on mortal thoughts.
Unsex me here, and
fill me from the
crown to the toe, top-full
of direst cruelty;
make thick my blood,
stop up the access,
and passage to remorse
that no compunctious
visitings of nature
shake my fell purpose,
nor keep peace between
the effect and it.
Come to my woman's breasts
and take my milk for gall,
you murdering ministers,
wherever in your
sightless substances you
wait on nature's mischief.
That was...
That was very good, Jeannette.
Vivian, sir.
Oh, Vivian, I meant Vivian.
Yeah.
Chuck, give me a
moment here please.
What's going on?
Why?
Not here, Tess, let's
talk outside, okay?
Come on, let's talk outside.
You're really gonna
do this play again?
Are you sick?
Have you finally snapped?
No I haven't.
I need to open this up,
we need to open this up.
Nothing needs to be opened up.
Nothing!
I forbid you to do it.
What are you
talking about forbid,
you're not in any position
to forbid anything.
You know the agreement, I
keep creative control here.
You're gonna cast
that young girl
as the queen, aren't you?
Yeah, I think so.
Because you're fucking her?
Hey, that is way out of line!
I maintain a
professional relationship
with these kids
and you know that!
Like the kind you
had with Jeannette?
Are you gonna
drag that up again?!
Nothing happened, all right?!
She just had an infatuation
with me, that's all!
This play is cursed, Larry!
Oh come on, that's
just superstition.
It cursed us!
We can't keep living
in the past, Tess.
We need new memories.
I need to do this.
Okay, Larry.
But what's done
cannot be undone.
We're all going to regret this.
(dramatic music)
(car revs)
[Vivian] Jeanette.
(eerie music)
(thunder booming)
- Please, Vivian!
Find me!
Help me!
(thunder booming)
(dramatic sting)
Help me, Vivian.
I want you to know I'm
not a big fan of medication.
Why?
Well they tend to
dull your senses.
You read very well
the other day.
This is an important
role for you.
Why do you say that?
Because of all the things
you're holding onto inside.
What do you mean?
Doctor Lazarus
told me everything.
Everything?
Mmmhm.
Wanna talk about it?
No.
How am I supposed
to get through to you,
Vivian, if you
don't let me inside?
The whole point of
this process is to
get you guys to
lower your defenses.
It's all about honesty, sharing.
I can't help you if
you don't help me.
You know, the theater
is a lot like therapy.
You can express
yourself and say things
on stage that you don't
get to do in real life.
You can show a side
to yourself that
even your best friends
have never seen.
I don't have any best friends.
I know.
I think this part
can give you a chance
to communicate your feelings.
Let those demons go
that torment you.
And they do torment
you, don't they, Vivian?
I want you to know...
We can get through
this together.
It's what I'm here for.
Thank you.
Can I go now?
Mmhm, sure.
[Charles] Hey
George, you wanna take
the ladies out for
some yard work?
Men, go wait in the wings.
[George] Come on,
girls, let's go.
Come on, move it!
Chuck, can you send Vivian
Miller down here please?
As the queen, she needs
to watch the auditions.
Let's go!
All right Chuck, who's first?
[Charles] Brian.
Just read any part.
Okay Brian, which part
will you be reading?
Malcolm.
Whenever you're ready.
What I believe
I'll wail, what know
believe and what I can redress,
as I shall find the
time to friend, I will.
What you have spoke,
it may be so perchance.
This tyrant, whose
sole name blisters
our tongues, was
once thought honest.
You have loved him well; he
hath not touched you yet.
I am young, but
something you may deserve
of him through me and
wisdom to offer up a
weak, poor, innocent lamb,
I appease an angry god.
Okay, thank you, Brian,
that was very nice, thank you.
Was that it?
Yeah.
Did I get the part?
Well all the
roles will be posted
on the work board outside.
Shakespeare's shit.
I'm sorry, what did you say?
I said Shakespeare's shit!
Oh really?
Let me tell you
something, Brian.
Shakespeare died
over 300 years ago,
but he's still being
talked about today.
Who will remember
you three minutes
after you're dead, huh?
Will you have
accomplished anything
of any value or
worth in your life?
The system and
everybody else has
given up on you, but
I haven't, not yet.
All right Chuck, who's next?
(dramatic music)
(no audio)
(heavy breathing)
(knocking)
Password?
Open the damn door!
(laughs) About damn time.
Hey, take it easy!
Jesus, rough day at the castle?
You don't know the half of it.
What's up?
(new wave music)
[Charles] (PA system) Everybody
to sleeping quarters,
lights out in 10 minutes!
[Tina] You sure you're okay?
Yeah, I think I am.
[Tina] Wait up!
Gary, Teri...
Boy, you guys look guilty.
I know nothing.
Uh huh.
Goodnight, chuckle heads!
(dramatic music)
[First witch] Is this
a dagger I see before me?
A dagger, a dagger.
The handle toward my hand?
Come, let me clutch thee.
(dramatic sting)
(toilet flushing)
(screaming)
(dramatic music)
Okay, okay.
(Vivian hyperventilating)
Okay okay okay.
What the hell happened, Vivian?
He was in my
bed, he was wear...
He was wearing a cloak
and he was choking me.
Who was it?
I don't know.
How did anyone get in here?
Couldn't have.
No goddamn way.
Who did this?!
All right, everybody
back in bed!
Now!
Put her to bed.
[Lance] How now, what news?
He has almost sucked, why
have you left the chamber?
Hath he asked for me?
Know you not he has?
We will proceed no
further in this business.
He hath honored me of late.
Whoa, wait, wait,
hold on guys, hold on.
Chuck?!
Yeah?
Where's our sound cue?
[Charles] Gary called it.
Come on, guys!
Pay attention!
[Lawrence] What's going on?
There's something
wrong with the deck.
There's no power.
How long will it
take you to fix it?
It's gonna be a
few minutes for sure.
All right Chuck,
let's take five.
May I get some water, sir?
[Charles] Yeah, two minutes.
Shit!
Roddy, you can't sneak
up on me like that!
Well I can't stay long.
I just, you know,
wanted to say hi.
It's been a little while.
Yeah, I thought you
were gonna get some
part time work here
and hang out some more.
Why, you miss me?
Well I, no, it's just that I.
Relax, I'm kidding.
Nah, they don't need me.
It kind of pisses me off, I mean
I wanted to hang out here more.
Looks like you're
playing the lead.
Yeah.
Lawrence is the greatest,
he's the best teacher.
[Lawrence] Places everyone!
So.
Listen, I actually,
I need to get back,
I don't want
Lawrence to get mad.
This play is so much
fun, but I'll see you.
We have got to
call the electrician.
We need this fixed by tomorrow.
Okay, I'm on it.
Let's get everybody up front.
Everybody, front and center!
Okay everyone,
unfortunately the
sound deck problem is actually a
booth electrical problem.
It can't be fixed right
away, so you're all excused.
I'm sure Mr. Kosack
has some things to
keep your minds
occupied, thank you
for a great day's work and
we'll see you all tomorrow.
Okay, thank you.
[Charles] Okay everybody,
in your work clothes,
let's get some yard work in!
(group groaning)
Shut it, come on,
let's go, let's go.
(eerie music)
(door creaking)
(ghostly whispers)
(dramatic music)
[Lawrence] All
the world's a stage.
And all the men and
women are merely players.
There's magic in
an empty theater.
All the possibilities.
Wouldn't you agree?
I know so little
about the theater.
Only what you've taught me.
Well you know about
life, don't you?
Yeah.
Isn't the unknown
more exciting...
More intriguing than the known?
Sometimes, I guess.
It's why people think
they can get up on the
stage and entertain a
thousand people at a time.
Make them laugh, make them cry.
Without ever knowing their name.
But you have to be
willing to fail,
take chances, be bold.
And bury your past
in the theater.
Recreate yourself, start anew.
That's what I did.
I...
I never really thought
of it like that,
I've always been afraid
of what I didn't know.
I was the same way.
So how did you get out
of your morning run?
I started in the back
and just dropped off.
(chuckles) Well you
must not be too afraid
of life 'cause Chuck
is gonna be on you
like thunder when he finds out.
You know, actually
I've been feeling
kind of lightheaded.
Maybe I should go lay down.
I'll square it away with him.
Thank you.
(ghostly whispers)
(eerie music)
(music intensifies)
Hey!
What the fuck are you doing?!
I...
You are in deep
trouble, young lady!
Skipping out on the run is
a serious rule violation!
I did, I wasn't, I didn't feel.
[Lawrence] It's okay, Chuck.
I told her she
could miss the run.
She wasn't feeling well.
Can we talk in my office?
Sure.
So what's on your mind?
Look.
I've been here 20 years.
I owe you everything,
we both know that.
And I've always backed you up.
It's just, I gotta tell
you, I'm a little worried.
About what?
That kid has got
some serious problems.
Come on, Chuck,
they've all got serious
problems, that's
why they're here.
You really think
it's a good idea to
cast her in the role of
a psychotic murderer?
Yeah, she gave
the best reading.
You read her file, Larry.
You don't think
that's kinda risky,
putting her in
that state of mind?
I mean look at her.
She looks like she's
ready to crack.
That's the whole
point, Chuck, is to get
these kids to work through their
trauma on the stage, remember?
I don't know, man.
I know what I'm doing, okay?
Okay.
I mean, you're the boss.
Is there anything else?
Nope.
Okay.
See you at rehearsal.
Yeah.
[Lawrence] So we
have the lady queen
going slowly insane
from the murders,
she imagines that
she cannot get rid
of the blood stains
on her hands which
leads to her death
by suicide, okay?
All right, you guys are ready?
Let's do this.
Places everyone!
Chuck, ready?
And lights up!
[Mike] Look how
she rubs her hands.
And here is a spot.
Hark, she speaks!
I will write down
what comes from her
to satisfy my remembrance
the more the better.
Out.
Damn spot, out I say!
One, two, why...
'Tis time to do it.
Hell is murky.
Fie, my lord, fie!
A solider and afeard?
What need we fear who knows it
when none can call
our power to account?
Yet, who would have thought the
old man to have so
much blood in him?
(wire snaps)
Move!
Holy shit!
Are you okay?
What was that?!
[Voiceover] Mike,
are you all right?
[Lawrence] Stand back,
stand back, stand back!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
You sure?
Yeah, I think so.
All right, let's
get her to her feet.
Clear the stage
please, everyone.
Chuck, deal with this.
[Charles] Where's
the damn safety cable?
There's a first aid
kit in the dressing room,
you might wanna
take a look at that.
(dramatic music)
Ow.
(dramatic sting)
(dramatic music)
[Witches] Enter
his world, Vivian.
You must enter his world.
[Group] Hey!
(cheering)
Get your ass over
here and have a drink.
All right.
[Mike] How you doing?
Better, thank you.
Glad I saw her coming!
Ha ha, ha ha ha,
that's so funny.
(cheering)
So how do you do
this, what do I do?
I just have it like this?
Okay.
I can't...
[Tina] Aw, you're so close.
[Vivian] Oh, I did it!
[Mike] First try.
[Vivian] Oh my God, I
bet I can't do it again.
I should not...
That's awesome.
Oh my God.
What the fuck, don't
fucking touch me!
What, you've never
been touched before?
Fuck you!
- Fuck you!
- What the fuck is wrong?!
Get the fuck off me, Lance!
[Tina] Get out, asshole!
[Vivian] Get out of here!
Get the fuck out!
Fuck this place and fuck you!
[Vivian] Fuck you!
[Tina] You okay?
[Vivian] Yeah, I'm fine.
(eerie music)
[Charles] (PA system)
Everybody to sleeping quarters,
lights out in 10 minutes.
All right, come on.
Right here, right
here right here.
(urinating)
(dramatic sting)
Where's Brian?
Brian!
Anybody seen Brian?
[Group] No.
Not since dinner.
Damn it.
Okay, we gotta find him.
Let's go, let's go!
Two teams.
You guys go around the front,
we'll go around the back.
Brian!
(dramatic music)
Anything?
- Have you seen anything?
- No, nothing.
Get everybody inside right now.
(music intensifies)
Oh my God!
[Teri] He's not moving!
(screaming)
Oh my God.
What's going on?
Get inside right
now, ladies, go go!
Oh my God!
Everybody get the
fuck inside right now!
I'm not fucking around!
Guys, it's Brian.
What's going on?
[Lance] Come on, come on!
What the fuck do
you mean it's Brian?
[Neil] Lance!
Hey!
I'll just be a minute.
[Witches] What's
done cannot be undone.
What the fuck?
Jesus Christ.
(thunder booming)
(dramatic music)
Vivian, please help
me, I'm so scared!
What's done cannot be undone.
(music intensifies)
(thunder booming)
Vivian, you have to
leave, he'll kill us both,
you have to leave, Vivian!
(mumble) come on, we
need to leave right now.
(mumble) Vivian,
(mumble), oh my God!
(screaming)
Please, please just
let me go, (mumble).
(gagging noises)
(thunder booming)
Hey!
Let me in!
Open the door!
The hell do you want?
The police want to question you.
Why?
Brian's dead.
Oh my God.
I'm gonna lose everything.
What?
They're gonna shut
this place down.
I can't believe it.
After all that hard work...
For nothing.
This play is cursed.
Who killed Jeannette?
Jeannette.
That poor, sweet girl.
You did it, didn't you?
You made me trust
you and I haven't
trusted a man in a
really long time.
You killed her,
you sick bastard!
You have an
overactive imagination.
No, you called me
Jeannette at my audition.
What, were you fucking her?!
You're not well, Vivian.
I'm gonna call
Doctor Lazarus and
have him come over right now.
Jeannette was murdered!
No she wasn't, she ran away.
You said no one
could escape from here!
Well she did.
Liar!
You are not telling
me everything!
My whole world ended that day.
No!
No, that is not
possible, that is not
possible, that is not possible!
For a long time I just
went through the motions.
This year felt
different, I felt alive.
I thought I could
finally exorcise
my demons and maybe help
your exorcise yours.
No, no, Roddy is not dead!
He is not, I saw him
and I talked to him
and he was there, he was
there at the bus stop,
and he was there at the theater,
you are lying, you are lying!
What are you talking about?!
You are lying!
My boy is dead!
He's dead!
- No he's not, no!
He killed himself.
No, no, no, no, no.
I cut him from
the rafters myself.
He's dead.
No, no he's not!
He's...
He's right there,
he's right there!
He killed Jeannette.
I loved Jeannette.
She loved him.
You all fall in love with him.
No.
(sobs) I tried to breathe life
into him, but I
couldn't save him.
(sobs) No, I...
(sobbing)
I couldn't save him.
[Roddy] Goodbye, father.
(suspenseful music)
[Witches] Is this a
dagger I see before me?
A dagger, a dagger.
Come, let me clutch thee.
(music intensifies)
Okay, no no no, why
won't you fucking work?
What's wrong with me, Vivian?
I just want to
love a pretty girl.
But you all fall
for him, my dad.
Oh my God, I don't
love your fucking dad!
You shut up!
Don't you lie to me.
It's too late for that.
You're just like
Jeannette, aren't you?
I have a lot to offer.
I mean I'm just as
good as Lawrence,
all I ever needed was a chance.
Then let Jeannette go.
Roddy, just stop,
just stop killing her.
You keep playing the tape!
You're making me kill her!
Now it's your turn.
Vivian, I can kill you here
or in my world with Jeannette.
The choice is yours.
What's done cannot be undone.
No!
Damn you!
(thunder booming)
Jeannette?
Vivian, he's coming!
(shrieking)
(coughing)
Why won't you love me?!
You're just like her!
Why?!
(clenched screaming)
Ahhh!
(gagging)
(angelic choir music)
Charles, I found her,
she's on the stage!
Vivian!
George, call 911!
Vivian?
(police radio feed)
Twice in one day?
What the hell is
going on around here?
I don't know, I...
Is she taking any medication?
Yes, but under supervision.
Have you been drinking, sir?
A little, yeah, why?
Okay, we're gonna
have to forget
about tomorrow's sit
down, Mr. O'Neil.
You need to come to
the station right now.
Nobody leaves!
I want a statement
from everybody,
lock this place down now!
Detective, we
have a video camera.
[Jones] I don't know, tag it.
Whoa whoa whoa,
who are you?
I'm Vivian's doctor.
What are you treating her for?
PTSD.
She's been severely
abused for years.
My God, was she attacked?
[EMT] I've done
a rapid trauma exam
and found no severe
lacerations on her body.
She's unconscious, but
her vitals are stable.
[Jones] Doctor, please, I
need to ask you a few questions.
I'm so sorry.
It's all my fault.
I gotta go.
(dramatic music)
(heart monitor beeping)
[Charles] Candace Malone.
[Candace] Here, sir.
[Charles] Natasha Gloden.
[Natasha] Here, sir.
Franklin Lee?
[Franklin] Here, sir.
[Charles] Theater Owner and
Camp Coordinator
Lawrence O'Neil.
Good morning.
Welcome to The Barn Theater.
My name is Lawrence O'Neil.
Because you've earned enough
points for good behavior
from the camps you were
at, we were able to
strike a deal with the
courts and your probation...
We're just going through
the tape again one more time.
I don't know, I just don't
think there's anything on it.
Okay, bye.
Anything?
[Taylor] Just static.
[Jones] It's a cold case then.
[Taylor] Yes, sir.
(dramatic sting)
(thunder booming)
Subrip by DanDee
(soft piano music)
¶ When the night speaks
far in the corridor
¶ Sleep, the wind,
lullaby baby dear
¶ Here in the dark, this lullaby
¶ La la la, la la la
¶ La la ¶
(electronic synthesizer music)
¶ Memories burn, bruises fade
¶ I want to purge
all possessions
¶ It's hard to clean up messes
¶ And if we lose all connections
¶ Will you hold on to me sweetly
¶ On to me sweetly
¶ I can make room
for this moment ¶