- OH.
[Sighs]
YOU WANT ME TO MAKE THIS PLACE
READY FOR A PARTY IN TWO WEEKS?
- NOT JUST A PARTY.
THE PARTY.
- MADISON, MAYBE WE SHOULD FIND
SOMEWHERE ELSE
TO HAVE YOUR SWEET 16.
- YEAH, LISTEN TO
YOUR OLD MAN HERE.
I MEAN, I CAN GET YOU THE RITZ
ALL DAY LONG.
- THE RITZ?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WHEN I WAS LITTLE,
THIS PLACE WAS THE BOMB.
AND THEN THEY CLOSED IT.
- MADDIE, HORRIBLE THINGS
HAPPENED HERE.
- I DON'T CARE IF THE TITANIC
SANK HERE.
YOU SAID I COULD HAVE
ANY SWEET 16 I WANT,
AND I WANT A SKATING PARTY.
- HOW MUCH?
- [Laughs]
MAN, THIS IS
A MASSIVE JOB.
- WELL, IF YOU CAN'T DO IT,
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO FIND SOMEONE
WHO'S UP FOR THE CHALLENGE.
- I'M UP FOR IT.
IT'S JUST GONNA COST YOU.
- THAT'S OKAY.
WE'RE VERY RICH.
MY FRIENDS ARE GONNA FREAK
WHEN THEY FIND OUT I REOPENED
THE ROLLERDOME.
[Exhales]
- MAKE IT HAPPEN.
[Clatter]
- SOMEBODY THERE?
[Cell phone rings]
AH, WHAT UP, PETE?
YEAH, NO.
I'M LEAVING THE ROLLERDOME.
I DON'T KNOW.
A FEW MINUTES.
[Electrical buzzing]
[Chumbawamba's Tubthumping]
- ¶ PISSING THE NIGHT AWAY ¶
- ¶ HE DRINKS A WHISKY DRINK,
HE DRINKS A VODKA DRINK ¶
¶ HE DRINKS A LAGER DRINK,
HE DRINKS A CIDER DRINK ¶
¶ HE SINGS THE SONGS THAT
REMIND HIM OF THE GOOD TIMES ¶
¶ HE SINGS THE SONGS THAT REMIND
HIM OF THE BETTER TIMES ¶
- ¶ OH, DANNY BOY ¶
¶ DANNY BOY ¶
¶ I GET KNOCKED DOWN
BUT I GET UP AGAIN ¶
¶ YOU'RE NEVER
GOING TO KEEP ME DOWN ¶
¶ I GET KNOCKED DOWN
BUT I GET UP AGAIN ¶
¶ YOU'RE NEVER GOING TO
KEEP ME DOWN ¶
¶ I GET KNOCKED DOWN
BUT I GET UP AGAIN ¶
¶ YOU'RE NEVER
GOING TO KEEP ME DOWN ¶
¶ I GET KNOCKED DOWN
BUT I GET UP AGAIN... ¶
- YOU READY?
[Intercom feedback]
- ATTENTION, ROLLERDOME,
ANYONE HERE
FOR CRAIG'S BIRTHDAY BASH,
ROLL ON OVER
TO THE SNACK BAR.
IT'S CAKE TIME.
[Click]
HERE WE GO.
- SO WHEN AM I GETTING
MY PRESENT, BABY?
[Musical fanfare]
WHAT THE HELL?
- I AM LORD OF THE RINK.
- KAREN, CHECK OUT
THIS FREAK SHOW.
- HERE TO MAKE SURE THAT YOU
HAVE A SUPER BIRTHDAY.
[Laughter]
- WOW, DAD, YOU PAID
15 BUCKS FOR THIS DUDE?
[Laughter]
[laughter]
- OH!
[Laughter]
- SORRY, YOUR MAJESTY.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE CAKE DROPPED.
MY BAD.
[Gasps]
DUDE, LET GO OF ME.
WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH YOU?
I'M GONNA KICK YOUR ASS.
[Laughter]
I DON'T NEED THIS.
- LOSER.
[Electrical buzzing]
- [giggles]
- OH, THIS IS
GONNA BE SICK.
[Glass shatters]
DUDE, SWEET.
WHAT IS THIS
SUPPOSED TO BE LIKE,
A JOUSTING STICK POOL CUE?
[Laughs]
- [giggles]
- YOU LIKE THAT?
- YEAH.
COME ON, LET'S GO
HAVE SOME FUN.
- ALL RIGHT.
[Heavy metal music]
¶ ¶
- [giggles]
- AW, COME BACK, KAREN.
- CATCH ME.
- OH, SO WE'RE
PLAYING GAMES NOW.
- [Giggles]
- I WIN.
- NOT YET.
MISSED ME.
- DON'T BE LIKE THAT,
BABY.
KAREN?
[Electrical buzzing]
- [screaming]
[whimpering]
- DADDY!
- STAY ON THE LINE.
THEY'LL BE THERE ANY SECOND.
HELLO? HELLO?
[Indistinct
radio dispatch]
- I GAVE THEM
WHAT THEY DESERVED.
[Groans]
- DON'T HURT HIM!
- [Laughs]
[groans]
- STOP IT!
I HAD TO, DADDY.
I'M SORRY.
- [Groans]
MY GOD.
- IT'S THE CASE THAT STUNNED
A COMMUNITY.
ROLLERDOME EMPLOYEE
CHARLIE ROTTER,
WHO PLAYED THE LORD OF THE RINK
TO COUNTLESS KIDS' PARTIES,
HAS BEEN CHARGED WITH SIX COUNTS
OF FIRST-DEGREE MURDER.
- TWO 16-YEAR-OLDS SLAUGHTERED
ON THE RINK FLOOR,
FOUR MORE DISMEMBERED
AND STUFFED INTO AN OIL BARREL
IN THE BASEMENT.
- POLICE RESPONDING
TO A 911 CALL
MADE A GRUESOME DISCOVERY.
ROTTER, THE MANAGER
OF THE ROLLERDOME,
WHO LIVED ON THE PREMISES
AND PERFORMED AS THE POPULAR
LORD OF THE RINK,
WAS TURNED IN
BY HIS YOUNG DAUGHTER.
- OUR TOP STORY TONIGHT,
TRAGEDY AT A LOCAL SKATING RINK.
THE BODIES OF SIX TEENAGERS
DISCOVERED LATE THIS EVENING
AS POLICE RAIDED THE POPULAR
TEEN HANGOUT, THE ROLLERDOME.
- THE ROLLERDOME HAS BEEN
SHUT DOWN BY POLICE.
IT IS NOT KNOWN WHEN
OR IF IT WILL REOPEN.
- WHAT THEY FOUND
HAS BEEN DESCRIBED
AS THE MOST GRUESOME MURDER
SCENE THE CITY...
- THE BODIES OF TWO TEENS
ON THE RINK FLOOR
AND FOUR MORE TEENAGERS
WHO HAD BEEN REPORTED
MISSING LAST YEAR
WERE FOUND DISMEMBERED
AND STUFFED INTO METAL DRUMS.
- A SHOCKING TURN OF EVENTS
IN THE ROLLERDOME MURDERS CASE.
- TODAY WAS THE DAY
CHARLIE ROTTER WAS TO BE
OFFICIALLY CHARGED
IN THE ROLLERDOME MURDERS.
- ALLEGED SERIAL KILLER
CHARLIE ROTTER HAS DIED
IN AN EARLY MORNING
CAR ACCIDENT
WHEN THE POLICE CRUISER LOST
CONTROL, ERUPTING INTO FLAMES.
- CHARLIE ROTTER, WHO CONFESSED
TO KILLING SIX LOCAL TEENS,
WAS AMONG SEVERAL PRISONERS
KILLED.
THE BODIES WERE BURNED
BEYOND RECOGNITION.
- SKYE ROTTER,
THE ONLY CHILD OF CHARLIE,
SAW HER FATHER COMMIT
HIS LATEST MURDEROUS ACT.
- NEW EVIDENCE IN
THE ROLLERDOME MURDERS CASE
REVEALS A HISTORY
OF MENTAL ILLNESS
IN THE ROTTER FAMILY.
- THE WHEREABOUTS OF
SKYE'S MOTHER ARE UNKNOWN.
- BUT PERHAPS THE MOST TRAGIC
VICTIM IS YOUNG SKYE ROTTER,
NOW IN THE CUSTODY
OF HER AUNT SARAH.
- THE ONLY PERSON
LEFT ALIVE
WHO WITNESSED
THE SHOCKING CRIME
IS YOUNG SKYE ROTTER.
- SKYE, YOU'RE GONNA BE
LATE FOR SCHOOL.
- I'M UP, AUNT SARAH.
- HURRY UP.
[Alarm beeps]
[alarm stops]
- YOU NEED TO JUST
GET YOURSELF A REBOUND,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
JUST SOME SKANK
TO LET MADISON KNOW
YOU'RE OVER HER.
- I AM OVER HER.
- YEAH, BUT YOU NAILING SOME
RANDO WOULD BE WAY BOMB.
I MEAN, LOOK, DUDE,
YOU'RE BRIGG, YOU'RE COOL,
YOU'RE GOOD-LOOKING,
YOU'RE FUNNY.
YOU'VE GOT IT ALL, MAN.
HEY! HEY, WEIRDO!
- LEAVE HER ALONE, MAN.
- NO, NO, NO.
YOU'D GIVE YOUR LEFT NUT
TO DO IT
WITH THIS GUY,
WOULDN'T YOU?
- SOUNDS LIKE YOU'D GIVE
YOUR LEFT NUT
TO DO IT WITH HIM.
- WHAT'D YOU--
WHAT'D YOU SAY,
FREAK SHOW?
- NOTHING. I JUST THING
BRIGG CAN DO BETTER
THAN A QUARTERBACK
LIKE YOU.
- OH, HA HA HA. FUNNY.
IDIOT.
I'M NOT A QUARTERBACK.
I'M A RECEIVER.
- I BET YOU ARE.
- WHAT?
- [Laughs]
- THAT'S NOT WHAT--
LOOK, I'M NOT GAY
FOR BRIGG.
- [Laughs]
I'M SORRY.
- OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
SCREW YOU, AND I'LL SEE YOU
AT PRACTICE.
- THAT WAS SWEET.
- YEAH, WELL,
KEVIN MAKES IT EASY.
- [Clears throat]
- WELL, SEE YOU LATER.
- OKAY.
HEY, SKYE.
YOU'RE IN MR. NEELY'S
BIO CLASS, RIGHT?
UM, DID YOU FINISH THE LAB?
WHAT?
- UM, NOTHING.
I'M JUST NOT
USED TO POPULAR PEOPLE
TALKING TO ME.
- WELL, RELAX.
I'M JUST LIKE ANYONE ELSE,
EXCEPT WAY COOLER.
[Both laugh]
YEAH.
- YOU KNOW, YOU ONLY
TURN 16 ONCE, CLAUDIA,
SO MY PARTY HAS TO BE
PERFECTION. TOTES.
- MADISON, I NEED
TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
I MEAN, YOU'RE NOT
GONNA BELIEVE--
- I'M SORRY, DID I GIVE YOU
THE IMPRESSION
I WAS DONE TALKING?
DAD WANTED ME TO HAVE IT
SOMEWHERE ELSE,
BUT EVER SINCE THE DIVORCE,
HE'S SO
WRAPPED AROUND MY FINGER.
- I WISH MY PARENTS
WERE DIVORCED.
- ANYWAY, HOW EXCITED ARE WE
ABOUT THE ROLLERDOME?
- LIKE, SO MUCH.
- IT'S THE PERFECT PLACE,
RIGHT?
- IT'S GENIUS,
PURE GENIUS.
MADISON, ONLY YOU
COULD BRING THE ROLLERDOME
BACK FROM THE DEAD.
- I KNOW.
DAD'S TAKING US
DRESS SHOPPING ON HIM.
I WANT YOU TWO
TO LOOK GOOD FOR ONCE.
ALL RIGHT, OLIVIA.
WHAT ARE YOU PEEING
YOUR PANTS ABOUT?
- I JUST SAW YOUR EX
FLIRTING IN THE HALL
WITH SKYE ROTTER.
- TELL ME YOU DID NOT
JUST SAY THAT.
- IT'S TRUE.
THEY WERE TOTALLY
DIGGING ON EACH OTHER.
- I CAN BELIEVE BRIGG'S
INTO THAT FREAK.
I MEAN, SKYE ROTTER
IS PSYCHO.
- HE'S NOT INTO HER.
WE JUST BROKE UP.
BESIDES, WHEN HE SEES ME
AT MY PARTY,
HE'LL BE BEGGING
TO GET BACK WITH ME.
- DEFINITELY.
- I DON'T KNOW, MADISON.
THERE WAS A VIBE
GOING ON THERE.
I THINK SHE'S TRYING
TO MOVE IN ON HIM.
- WELL THEN, WE'LL JUST
HAVE TO REMIND SKYE
THAT THERE ARE SOME BOYS
WHO ARE OUT OF HER LEAGUE.
[Pop music]
¶ ¶
- ¶ ANY WAY
YOU LOOK AT IT ¶
- OKAY,
LET'S MAKE A PACT.
IF I HAVEN'T LOST
MY VIRGINITY
BY THE END
OF THIS SEMESTER,
YOU'LL TAKE IT
FROM ME.
- LIKE, BY FORCE?
- TRUST ME, THAT WON'T
BE NECESSARY.
- I'M NOT GONNA SLEEP
WITH YOU, DEREK.
- OH, COME ON, LOOK.
WE'RE BEST FRIENDS, OKAY?
BEST FRIENDS LIKE SLEEPING
WITH EACH OTHER.
PLEASE?
I'D DO IT FOR YOU.
- HAVE FAITH.
YOU'LL FIND
SOME POOR, PATHETIC GIRL
WHO WILL GIVE IT UP.
- YEAH, YOU KEEP
SAYING THAT.
I JUST DON'T SEE IT
HAPPENING.
- SO I THINK BRIGG WAS FLIRTING
WITH ME THIS MORNING.
- [Laughs]
I THINK YOU'RE OFF
YOUR MEDS.
- NO, SERIOUSLY, WE HAD,
LIKE, A MOMENT.
- YOU AND THE BRIGG-MAN,
HUH?
YEAH, I MEAN,
THAT--THAT'S--THAT'S COOL.
THAT'S AWESOME.
AND IT COULD HAPPEN.
I'M NOT SAYING IT COULDN'T.
I MEAN, YOU'RE CUTE.
AND YOU--YOU'RE REALLY
STARTING TO FILL OUT
THAT A-CUP.
- SCREW OFF.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT WAS PROBABLY NOTHING.
- [Inhales deeply]
THIS IS NICE.
- YOU SERIOUSLY
WEIRD ME OUT.
- [Laughs]
[intermittent drips]
- HELLO?
- IS THAT BLOOD?
- NO. PAINT.
- OH.
SO THAT'S WHAT MADISON
AND HER BITCH SQUAD
WERE DOING BY YOUR LOCKER.
WHAT'D YOU DO
TO PISS HER OFF?
- I TALKED TO BRIGG
THIS MORNING.
- OUCH.
I HEARD MADISON WAS TRYING
TO HOOK UP WITH HIM
AT HER SWEET 16
THIS WEEKEND.
GUESS SHE THINKS
YOU GOT A SHOT.
YOU SHOULD TOTALLY
HOOK UP WITH BRIGG.
THAT WOULD BE AWESOME.
- LILY, AREN'T YOU
ONE OF HER FRIENDS?
- WHEN I NEED TO BE.
IT DOESN'T MEAN I LIKE HER.
- SO YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO HER PARTY?
- OF COURSE I'M GONNA GO
TO HER PARTY.
IT'S LIKE THE PARTY
OF THE YEAR.
CAN'T MISS THAT.
SORRY FOR...
YOU KNOW.
[Bell rings]
[laughter and chatter]
- OH, SKYE, YOU WEREN'T
GOING TO LEAVE
WITHOUT SAYING GOOD-BYE,
WERE YOU?
[Laughs]
- NICE LOOK.
IT'S VERY--
WHAT'S THE WORD?
PATHETIC.
- ARE YOU DONE?
- WELL, THAT DEPENDS.
ARE YOU DONE
SCAMMING ON MY BOYFRIEND?
- ALL WE DID WAS TALK.
- THE ONLY REASON BRIGG WOULD
TALK TO A PSYCHO LIKE YOU
IS IF HE FELT SORRY
FOR YOU.
- I'M NOT THE ONE
WHO GOT DUMPED.
- YOU'RE NOTHING.
NOBODY.
YOU COULD DIE,
AND THE YEARBOOK
WOULDN'T WASTE
AN INCH OF SPACE ON YOU.
SO WHY DON'T YOU GO BACK TO
YOUR PATHETIC, LITTLE LIFE.
THIS END OF THE POOL
IS JUST TOO DEEP.
FREAK.
LOVE THE SUIT,
BY THE WAY.
IT REALLY SHOWS OFF THAT
12-YEAR-OLD BOD OF YOURS.
[Car horn honks]
- DADDY, WE ARE SO READY
TO GET OUR SHOP ON.
[Laughter]
- UH, ACTUALLY, HONEY,
THERE'S BEEN
A LITTLE CHANGE OF PLANS.
WE'RE NOT GONNA GO SHOPPING.
- WHAT?
- I FLEW IN A STYLIST FROM L.A.
AND HE'S BACK AT THE HOUSE.
[Gasps and laughter]
- DADDY,
YOU ARE THE BEST.
[Somber music]
¶ ¶
- YOU NEED A RIDE?
- UH, NO, THANKS.
I'M GOOD.
- IT'S A LONG WALK
IN FLIP-FLOPS.
- YOU KNOW, I SHOULDN'T EVEN
BE TALKING TO YOU.
YOUR CRAZY GIRLFRIEND
IS THE REASON
I'M ROCKING THIS ONE-PIECE.
- EX-GIRLFRIEND.
COME ON, I DEFINITELY
OWE YOU A RIDE HOME.
GET IN THE CAR.
COME ON.
- OH!
WHOA.
MY BAD.
- [Giggles]
- LOOK, I'M REALLY SORRY
MADISON'S BEEN MESSING WITH YOU.
- YEAH, I GUESS SHE THINKS
THERE'S, LIKE,
SOMETHING GOING ON
BETWEEN US.
WEIRD, RIGHT?
- SO, WHAT--WHAT ARE YOU
DOING SATURDAY NIGHT?
- THE USUAL.
I MEAN, ME AND DEREK WILL
PROBABLY JUST GO TO THE MALL
AND MAKE FUN OF ALL THE OTHER
KIDS THAT HAVE NO LIVES.
- COOL.
- UM, BUT I MEAN,
YOU KNOW,
THAT'S NOT SET IN STONE
OR ANYTHING.
I MEAN, IF SOMETHING ELSE
CAME UP...
- ACTUALLY,
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU MIGHT
WANT TO HANG OUT WITH ME
ON SATURDAY.
- WHAT ABOUT MADISON?
- WHAT ABOUT HER?
WE'RE BROKEN UP.
- SHE WANTS TO KILL ME.
- [Laughs]
DON'T WORRY.
I GOT YOUR BACK.
- I'M TRYING TO DECIDE.
SHOULD I JUST GIVE BRIGG
HIS INVITE
OR SHOULD I MAKE HIM
SWEAT A LITTLE?
- WELL, AFTER
THE WHOLE SKYE THING,
I'D MAKE HIM SWEAT.
- WHAT IF BRIGG DOESN'T
WANT AN INVITATION?
- OLIVIA,
WILL YOU STOP BEING RETARDED
FOR, LIKE, ONE SECOND?
OF COURSE HE WANTS
AN INVITATION.
BRIGG AND I ARE DESTINY.
- HE DID BREAK UP
WITH HER.
- WHATEVER. DRAMA. WE BREAK UP,
WE GET BACK TOGETHER.
WE'RE PASSIONATE.
IT'S SERENDIPS. DEAL WITH IT.
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT, MADISON.
SKYE'S PROBABLY JUST
A HOOK-UP OR SOMETHING.
- [Gasps]
- THEY ARE NOT HOOKING UP.
THESE DRESSES ALL SUCK.
- NOW MADISON,
THAT LOOKS BEAUTIFUL.
- THAT IS RIDICULOUS.
- HONEY,
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
- THE PROBLEM IS
THIS LAME STYLIST
AND HIS TRASHY-ASS DRESSES.
- WHAT ABOUT, UH, THIS ONE?
THIS ONE LOOKS NICE.
- NICE.
YOU HEAR THAT?
MY DAD THINKS
THIS ONE'S "NICE."
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
WE DIDN'T FLY YOU
3,000 MILES
TO SHOW ME SOME
MALL STORE MILF-WEAR.
NOW FIND ME SOMETHING
PERFECT.
- MADDIE, HE'LL FIX IT,
I PROMISE.
[Pop music]
¶ ¶
[hip-hop music]
- ¶ I STAY HUNGRY FOR THE MONEY
SO I GRIND ALWAYS ¶
¶ DON'T GET IT TWISTED
IF I SHINE ALL DAY ¶
¶ I AIN'T AFRAID TO GO
AND PUT YOU IN YOUR PLACE ¶
¶ I STAY HUNGRY FOR THE MONEY
SO I GRIND ALWAYS ¶
¶ DON'T GET IT TWISTED
IF I SHINE ALL DAY ¶
¶ BEIN' ON TOP IS ON MY MIND
ALWAYS ¶
¶ AND YOU CAN HEAR
IN EVERY RHYME I SAY ¶
¶ I GIVE IT
TO YOU STRAIGHT ¶
¶ THAT IS HOW I FEEL ¶
¶ PUT YOU IN YOUR PLACE,
NO MISTAKE, I WILL ¶
¶ ALL THESE FALSE
MISCONCEPTIONS ¶
¶ 'BOUT ME I KILL ¶
¶ THESE CRITICS ARE MO' BITCH
MADE IN THEIR HIGH HEELS ¶
¶ I'M FROM THE HOME
OF THE BRAVE ¶
¶ WE BLOW HABALA ¶
¶ THEY SAY WE COUNTRY,
WE AIN'T SLAVES ¶
¶ BOY, WE GOT A LOT ¶
¶ GANGSTAS BEEN
TO ATLANTA ¶
¶ LEARNED TO ROB A LOT
AND BOB A LOT ¶
¶ AND I AIN'T TALKIN'
BARBERSHOP ¶
¶ WE'RE NOT SENDING SHOT ¶
¶ I STAY HUNGRY FOR THE MONEY
SO I GRIND ALWAYS ¶
¶ DON'T GET IT TWISTED
IF I SHINE ALL DAY ¶
¶ I AIN'T AFRAID TO GO
AND PUT YOU IN YOUR PLACE ¶
[somber music]
¶ ¶
- HE'S GOING TO THAT PARTY.
- OF COURSE HE'S GOING
TO THAT PARTY.
EVERYONE IS
GOING TO THAT PARTY.
- WHY DID I THINK
FOR ONE SECOND
THAT ME AND BRIGG
WOULD ACTUALLY HAPPEN?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE MADISON'S
HAVING HER PARTY
AT THE ROLLERDOME.
I MEAN, THAT HAS...
THAT HAS GOT TO BE
WEIRD FOR YOU.
- YEAH.
WELCOME TO MY LIFE.
YOU KNOW, JUST ONCE,
I WOULD LOVE TO BE
A NORMAL HUMAN BEING.
- WELL, THEN YOU SHOULD CRASH
MADISON'S PARTY WITH ME.
- YEAH.
THAT'S A TERRIBLE IDEA.
- NO, NO, NO, SKYE, LOOK.
MAYBE IT'S A GREAT IDEA, OKAY?
- [Woman on computer moans]
- YOU ALWAYS--UM...
- WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
- [Woman on computer moans]
- HOW DO YOU CLEAR
YOUR BROWSER HISTORY?
- OKAY, GIVE ME THAT.
- OKAY, JUST--LOOK.
YOU'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO BE
A REGULAR PERSON, RIGHT?
RIGHT?
WELL, ALL THE REGULAR PEOPLE
AT THAT SCHOOL
ARE DYING TO GO
TO THAT PARTY.
- I CAN'T GO THERE.
- SKYE, WHAT HAPPENED
WAS, LIKE,
A MILLION YEARS AGO,
OKAY?
MAYBE IT'S TIME TO,
YOU KNOW,
JUST LET IT GO.
- DEREK,
I DREAM ABOUT MY DAD
ALMOST EVERY NIGHT.
I MEAN,
THE THINGS HE DID.
AND KIDS AT SCHOOL
LOOK AT ME
LIKE I AM THE SPAWN
OF SATAN.
MY MOM LEFT BECAUSE
SHE COULDN'T HANDLE IT,
AND MY AUNT
CAN BARELY LOOK AT ME.
SOMETIMES...
- WHAT?
- I WONDER IF HE COULD
STILL BE OUT THERE.
THEY NEVER FOUND
HIS BODY, DEREK.
- SKYE, HE'S GONE,
OKAY?
HE'S NOT COMING BACK.
[Doorbell rings]
- STAY OUT OF
MY UNDERWEAR DRAWER.
- THERE WAS ONE TIME.
IT WAS JUST...
ONCE.
- [Sighs]
[sighs]
WISH I WASN'T WEARING
SWEATS RIGHT NOW.
- HEY.
SOMETHING ON YOUR MIND?
- YEAH.
YEAH. LISTEN, ABOUT--
ABOUT SATURDAY NIGHT.
I'M NOT GONNA
BE ABLE TO GO--
- BRIGG, IT'S COOL.
I MEAN, I GET IT.
IT'S THE PARTY OF THE YEAR.
- NO, NO, NO, NO, NO,
IT'S NOT THAT.
IT'S JUST--
IT'S COMPLICATED.
ME AND MADISON HAVE HISTORY
AND IT'S A BIG NIGHT FOR HER.
- DON'T--DON'T EVEN--
DON'T EVEN WORRY ABOUT IT.
- LET ME MAKE IT UP
TO YOU.
- OKAY.
UM...
YOU AND I BOTH KNOW
THIS ISN'T GONNA WORK.
I MEAN, YOU'RE YOU,
AND I'M, WELL,
YOU KNOW.
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
- IT'S EXACTLY LIKE THAT.
I MEAN, I JUST NEED
TO ACCEPT
THE FACT THAT I'M ALWAYS
GOING TO BE--
- I LIKE YOU, SKYE,
AND I WANT TO SPEND MORE TIME
WITH YOU.
I JUST HAVE TO GO
TO THIS PARTY,
AND--AND AFTER THAT,
YOU AND ME ARE GONNA GO OUT.
NICE SWEATS, BY THE WAY.
- SHUT UP.
[Door opens, closes]
- WAS THAT BRIGG?
- YOU STILL WANT
TO CRASH THAT PARTY?
¶ GOT THIS CRAZY FEELIN'
AND I THINK IT'S ABOUT YOU ¶
¶ OH, YOU GOT A MAN BUT NOW
HE'S SOMEWHERE WITHOUT YOU ¶
¶ I DON'T WANT TO BE THE ONE
THAT FOLLOWS YOU HOME ¶
¶ HANDS INSIDE MY POCKETS
I'M ALONE ¶
¶ AND YOU'RE TURNING ME ON ¶
¶ YOU'RE TURNING ME DOWN ¶
¶ YOU'RE TURNING ME INSIDE OUT
AND UPSIDE DOWN ¶
¶ YOU TURN ME ON,
YOU'RE TURNING ME DOWN ¶
¶ YOU'RE TURNING ME
INSIDE OUT ¶
¶ AND UPSIDE DOWN
AND AROUND ¶
¶ ¶
¶ AND AROUND ¶
¶ ME ON,
YOU'RE TURNING ME DOWN ¶
¶ YOU'RE TURNING ME INSIDE OUT
AND UPSIDE DOWN ¶
¶ YOU TURN ME ON ¶
¶ YOU'RE TURNING ME DOWN ¶
¶ YOU'RE TURNING ME
INSIDE OUT ¶
¶ AND UPSIDE DOWN ¶
¶ ¶
¶ OOH ¶
¶ YOU'RE TURNING ME ON ¶
¶ YOU'RE TURNING ME DOWN ¶
¶ YOU'RE TURNING ME
INSIDE OUT ¶
¶ AND UPSIDE DOWN ¶
¶ YOU TURN ME ON ¶
¶ YOU'RE TURNING ME DOWN ¶
¶ YOU'RE TURNING ME
INSIDE OUT ¶
¶ AND UPSIDE DOWN ¶
¶ NAH NAH,
NAH NAH NAH NAH ¶
[rhythmic music]
¶ WHOO ¶
¶ EASY ¶
¶ ALL DAY BE EASY ¶
¶ WHOO ¶
¶ MAY I HAVE YOUR ATTENTION ¶
[cork pops]
[laughter]
- I'D LIKE TO PROPOSE
A TOAST...
TO ME...
THROWING THE PARTY
OF THE CENTURY
AND GETTING THE CAR
OF MY DREAMS.
[Laughter]
- DO YOU THINK YOUR DAD
GOT YOU THE BEAMER?
- EITHER THAT OR A LEXUS.
BUT IF HE GOT ME THE LEXUS,
I WILL VOM ALL OVER IT.
OKAY.
- [Laughs]
[all laugh]
- SHUT UP.
¶ ¶
[music and chatter]
[cheers and applause]
[cheering grows louder]
- WHEN I WAS
EIGHT YEARS OLD,
MY BEST FRIEND RICK
HAD A BIRTHDAY PARTY
AND BUZZ LIGHTYEAR
SHOWED UP.
I THOUGHT THAT
WAS AWESOME.
I WAS WRONG.
THIS IS AWESOME.
SKYE.
YOU KNOW YOU DON'T HAVE TO
GO IN THERE, RIGHT?
- YES, I DO.
[Music playing
inside Rollerdome]
¶ ¶
[spray spray]
- WOW.
YOU LOOK...
GREAT.
- YOU THINK?
- YEAH.
SO, HOW DO WE, UH,
HOW DO WE SNEAK INTO
THIS FIESTA?
- UH, I TEXTED LILY
AND ASKED HER
TO LEAVE THE BACK DOOR
OPEN FOR US.
THAT GIRL KIND OF HATES
MADISON,
SO SHE WAS
ALL TOO HAPPY.
- SWEET.
IT'S OPEN.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
- ALL RIGHT, GOOD.
FINISH LACING THOSE UP
AND THEN JUST WAIT
FOR THE DJ TO CUE YOU.
- IT HAS TO BE F-A-B.
FABULOUS.
- OH, KITTEN,
THAT'S WHY YOU HIRED ME.
OKAY, TELL THE DJ
WE'RE ABOUT TWO MINUTES.
- WHAT?
- ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE 16?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU LOOK WAY OLDER
TO ME.
- THANKS.
- YEAH.
- ARE YOU DRUNK?
- THIS ISN'T DRUNK.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M A KID.
- SO? I JUST WANTED TO MAKE IT
A CELEBRATION TIME.
- STOP! EW! YOU THINK
I WOULD KISS YOU?
YOU'RE, LIKE, 30, DUDE.
[Cheering]
- HEY, Y'ALL, PARTY PEOPLE,
PUT YOUR HANDS TOGETHER
FOR THE BIRTHDAY GIRL.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
MISS MADISON PENROSE.
[Cheers and applause]
- THE BRAT'S COMING
YOUR WAY.
[Musical fanfare]
- WHO WANTS TO PARTY?
[Cheers and applause]
- HMM.
THE JOKE'S ON YOU.
I'M 35.
[Club music]
¶ ¶
- WHY COULDN'T I
HAVE BEEN BORN RICH?
ARE YOU FREAKING OUT
IN HERE OR WHAT?
- ACTUALLY, NO.
I THINK TONIGHT'S
GONNA BE OKAY.
I'M GONNA GO FIND BRIGG.
- COOL. I'M GONNA FIND ANY GIRL
THAT'LL TALK TO ME.
- GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
- THANKS.
- WHAT THE HELL
IS HE DOING HERE?
[Blade scraping]
- HEH.
THAT'S CUTE.
YOU GOT ME.
[Static]
- WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, MAN?
[Groans]
- ¶ OOH, OH, YOUR DRIVE
IS AFFECTING ME ¶
¶ ¶
¶ OH, AS YOU'RE TAKING
THE WHEEL ¶
¶ ¶
¶ MOVE LIKE YOU'RE MORE
THAN JUST WANTING ME ¶
¶ ¶
¶ SOON I WILL DIG IN
MY HEELS ¶
¶ JUST LISTEN TO THESE WORDS
THAT I SAY ¶
¶ THIS IS NOT
A GAME I PLAY ¶
¶ I'M NOT JUST
ANY OTHER GUY ¶
¶ YES, YOU USED TO LOSE
YOUR WAY ¶
¶ JUST KEEP ME
IN YOUR EYES, BABY ¶
¶ DON'T GET CARELESS
WITH MY HEART ¶
- WHAT'S THIS?
I DIDN'T EXPECT
TO SEE YOU TONIGHT.
YOU LOOK... WOW.
[Both laugh]
- WELL, YOU SAID YOU WANTED
TO SPEND MORE TIME WITH ME.
- [Laughs]
I DID, DIDN'T I?
SORRY.
THIS IS JUST...
YOU CAUGHT ME
A LITTLE OFF-GUARD.
- [Laughs]
THAT WAS MY PLAN.
- SO WHAT'S NEXT
IN YOUR PLAN?
- ACTUALLY, I DIDN'T REALLY
THINK PAST THIS PART.
UM, YOU COULD ASK ME
TO SKATE.
[Pop music]
¶ ¶
- HEY, LILY.
WHAT, SAY,
A HOTTIE LIKE YOU
DOING SITTING HERE
ALL BY YOURSELF?
- I GOT TIRED
OF SWEATY-PALMED TOOLS
SKATING UP ON ME.
- OH.
YEAH, I HATE THAT.
CAN I, UH, HAVE A SIP
OF YOUR WATER?
[Coughs]
- [laughs]
- WHAT IS THAT,
MOONSHINE?
- IT'S VODKA,
YOU LITTLE GIRL.
- [Groans]
- WHY DON'T YOU GO GET YOURSELF
SOME OF THAT FRUITY PUNCH
AND WE CAN HAVE OURSELVES
A DRINK.
- I MEAN, UH, YEAH.
UH, I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
LILY TOTALLY WANTS ME.
[Boys laughing]
NO, NO!
[Thud]
- CAN I SEE
YOUR INVITATION, PLEASE?
- OH, JEEZ,
I'M SORRY, I MUST HAVE LEFT IT
IN YOUR MOTHER'S PANTS.
[Laughs]
- YOU DON'T BELONG HERE.
LOOK, THIS IS HOW
THIS IS GONNA WORK.
I'M GONNA KICK YOUR ASS,
AND THEN
THEY'RE GONNA THROW YOU OUT.
COOL?
- NOT REALLY.
[Thud]
AAH!
- WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
- IT'S CHARLIE ROTTER'S MASK.
BOO!
- [Grunts]
[coughs]
- IT'S FINE. HEH!
YOU WANT TO STAY
AT THE PARTY?
- NO, NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
- THEN STAY.
WHOO!
- DUDE, I WAS GONNA
HOOK UP WITH LILY.
- [Laughs]
- AW, DUDE, COME ON.
CAN'T WE DO THIS
ON MONDAY?
[Groans]
THIS SUCKS!
- ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL.
WE'RE ABOUT TO
SLOW IT DOWN
FOR ALL YOU COUPLES
OUT THERE.
[Slow music]
¶ ¶
- HEY, JUST--JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I'VE NEVER DONE THIS BEFORE,
SO I'M PROBABLY
GONNA SUCK.
- OH, COME ON,
YOU'LL BE GREAT.
THERE YOU GO.
[Gasps]
- [laughs]
- ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU SUCK AT THIS.
OKAY, THERE YOU GO.
NOT SO BAD, RIGHT?
- NOT BAD AT ALL.
- SO, UM, UH...
- SORRY.
- I NEED TO ASK YOU
SOMETHING,
AND I'M NOT REALLY SURE
I WANT TO KNOW THE ANSWER,
BUT, UH, HOW DO YOU GO
FROM MADISON PENROSE
TO SKYE ROTTER?
SHE'S, LIKE,
EVERYTHING I'M NOT.
- THAT'S WHAT I LIKE
ABOUT YOU.
THE BETTER QUESTION IS,
HOW DID I GO THIS LONG
WITHOUT NOTICING YOU?
- THAT IS A GOOD QUESTION.
[Laughs]
YOU'RE A LOT DIFFERENT
THAN I THOUGHT YOU'D BE.
- HOW'S THAT?
- UH, YOU'RE LESS JOCK-ISH.
[Both laugh]
- THEN I PROBABLY
SHOULDN'T TELL YOU
THAT I'M SCREWING MY WAY
THROUGH SCHOOL ALPHABETICALLY.
I'M MIDWAY THROUGH
THE Rs RIGHT NOW,
SO CONGRATS,
YOU'RE UP.
- [Laughs]
I THINK I LIKE
THE OTHER BRIGG BETTER.
- YEAH.
- LOOK AT YOU.
YOU'RE SKATING LIKE A PRO.
- [Squeals]
- [laughs]
SMOOTH, SMOOTH, SMOOTH.
I KNOW.
- AW.
HEY, KEVIN,
WE CAN PARTY, HUH?
- NOT NOW, LILY,
I'M ON OFFICIAL BUSINESS.
MADISON,
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
- WHAT YOU NEED TO DO, KEVIN,
IS LEAVE ME THE HELL ALONE
WHILE I GET MY GROOVE ON.
- LOOK, I JUST CAUGHT
THAT DUMB-ASS DEREK
CRASHING YOUR PARTY.
- WELL, HOW THE HELL
DID HE GET IN HERE?
- MADISON, YOU ARE SO
NOT GOING TO BELIEVE THIS.
- WHAT THE W-T-F IS SHE DOING
AT MY SWEET 16?
THIS IS MY NIGHT,
AND SHE'S TRYING TO RUIN IT.
- MADISON, MAYBE YOU
SHOULD JUST LET IT GO.
- OLIVIA, SERIOUSLY,
CAN YOU STOP BEING SO
FREAKING LAME ALL THE TIME?
YOU'RE KILLING ME.
- IT'S OKAY, UM,
WE'LL TAKE CARE OF SKYE.
- YES, YOU WILL.
- HELP!
SOMEBODY HELP!
[Rattles]
- DAMN.
LILY.
- I DIDN'T SCARE YOU,
DID I?
- PFFT! NO.
JUST--HOW'D YOU KNOW
I WAS DOWN HERE?
- JUST FOLLOWED THE SOUND
OF A CHICK SCREAMING FOR HELP.
- UH, SO YOU HEARD THAT.
AWESOME.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN THERE?
- OH, YOU KNOW,
KEVIN AND HIS DOUCHE SQUAD
THOUGHT I'D ENJOY THE PARTY
A LITTLE MORE FROM DOWN HERE.
- KEV'S JUST TRYING
TO SCORE POINTS
SO HE CAN HOOK UP
WITH MADISON.
- THANK YOU.
WELL, I HAVE TO GO TELL SKYE
ABOUT MADISON.
- LISTEN, HERE'S THE DEAL.
I'M SERIOUSLY DRUNK
RIGHT NOW
AND FINDING YOU
STRANGELY IRRESISTIBLE.
SO IF YOU WANT TO
MAKE OUT WITH ME,
THIS IS, LIKE,
YOUR ONLY SHOT.
LIKE EVER.
- SKYE'S A BIG GIRL.
SHE CAN HANDLE
HER OWN PROBLEMS, RIGHT?
- I'M GONNA GO GET US
A DRINK. COOL?
- YEAH.
- WHAT?
- UH, NOTHING.
I JUST KEEP THINKING
YOU'RE GONNA WALK AWAY
AND NEVER COME BACK.
- I'LL BE BACK.
I PROMISE.
[Club music]
¶ ¶
- IS IT REALLY YOU?
- WHO'S YOUR DADDY?
[Laughing]
WHAT, NO CLEVER QUIP?
COME ON, NO COMEBACK?
AW, YOU'RE GONNA CRY?
REALLY?
YOU'RE GONNA CRY?
DADDY'S GONE?
MAKES YOU SAD?
[Laughs]
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
BRIGGS IS USING YOU!
JUST WONDERING
WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO GET SOME OF THAT
CRAZY LOVE.
[Sighs]
WHAT A TEASE.
[Gasps]
[gagging]
[screaming]
- I.D.K, OLIVIA,
ALL I KNOW
IS MADISON
WANTS SKYE OUT.
- LOOK, I DON'T LIKE SKYE
ANY MORE THAN YOU GUYS DO,
BUT DON'T YOU THINK WE'VE
MESSED WITH HER ENOUGH?
- OLIVIA, THIS IS
MADISON'S SWEET 16.
IT ONLY HAPPENS, LIKE,
ONCE IN A LIFETIME.
IT HAS TO BE
THE BEST BIRTHDAY EVER.
- I KNOW.
- GOOD.
[Gasps]
I HAVE AN IDEA.
[Squeals]
HERE'S THE PLAN.
I'M GONNA GO IN THE...
[whispers]
BATHROOM, AND THEN,
WHEN SKYE COMES IN,
I'M GONNA BLOW
THIS EXTINGUISHER ON HER.
- OKAY, BUT HOW ARE WE GONNA
GET SKYE TO GO TO THE BATHROOM?
- OLIVIA, I THOUGHT
OF THE FIRE EXTINGUISHER.
GOD, DO I HAVE TO
THINK OF EVERYTHING?
- ALL RIGHT.
[Club music]
¶ ¶
- BARKEEP,
A SHOT OF JAGER.
GOOD IDEA.
I'M DRIVING.
DUDE.
- HEY.
SO I JUST MADE OUT
WITH LILY.
I SEVERELY
MADE OUT WITH HER, MAN.
SHE TOUCHED ME.
- CONGRATULATIONS.
I HOPE SHE REMEMBERS.
- I'M GONNA REMEMBER,
SO...
- DUDE, YOU HAVEN'T
SEEN SKYE, HAVE YOU?
- CRAP.
UH, NO.
I TOTALLY FORGOT.
AND YOUR BRO KEV
KNOWS WE CRASHED,
SO I'M ASSUMING
HE STOLE MADISON BY NOW.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT'LL BE FINE.
- TRUST ME, IT WON'T.
- OOPS.
SORRY.
[Gasps]
STOP IT!
SKYE, I SAID I WAS SORRY!
- SORRY.
- IT'S...
IT'S OKAY.
WHY DON'T YOU GO
CLEAN YOURSELF UP.
THE RESTROOM'S--
- YEAH, I KNOW WHERE IT IS.
- DAMN IT.
- MADDIE,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- COME ON, BRIGG, DON'T YOU WANT
TO KISS THE BIRTHDAY GIRL?
- MADISON--MADISON, I--
- SHH, BRIGG, DON'T TALK.
- WE--WE BROKE UP,
REMEMBER?
- SO LET'S GET
BACK TOGETHER.
- MADISON, BACK OFF.
- OH, PLEASE, YOU ACTUALLY
LIKE THAT LOSER? WHY?
DO YOU HAVE SOME SORT OF SERIAL
KILLER FETISH OR SOMETHING?
- WE'RE DONE, MADISON.
WHEN ARE YOU GONNA REALIZE
THAT I DON'T WANT YOU?
- EVERYBODY WANTS ME.
- NOT ME.
NOT ANYMORE.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
- YOU KNOW, I ONLY INVITED YOU
'CAUSE I FELT SORRY FOR YOU.
YOU CAN'T RUIN MY BIRTHDAY.
NO ONE CAN RUIN THIS NIGHT.
- [Exhales]
THERE YOU ARE, FREAK.
ONE, TWO, THREE!
[Laughs]
SKYE?
WHERE ARE YOU?
[Coughs]
SKYE?
AAH!
¶ I ESCAPED
THROUGH A KEYHOLE ¶
¶ BEFORE THEY ERASED ME ¶
¶ I MARRIED THE BEETLE ¶
¶ AND LEARNED TO BE GRACEFUL ¶
- WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
- SWEETIE, YOU SAID
YOU WANTED A SUSHI CAKE.
- THAT'S A CRAPPY,
DISGUSTING CAKE
SHAPED LIKE SUSHI.
I WANTED FIVE TIERS
OF PREMIUM,
FLOWN-IN-FROM-FRICKIN'-TOKYO
HAND ROLLS.
YOU KNOW, A SUSHI CAKE.
- FINE.
WHERE THE HELL
IS THAT PARTY PLANNER?
YOU, I WANT YOU TO FIND ME
A SUSHI PLACE THAT DELIVERS,
AND I WANT YOU
TO HURRY YOUR ASS OFF.
- [Groans]
- MADDIE, DADDY'S
GONNA MAKE IT... RIGHT.
DAMN IT.
- HEY,
DEREK'S LOOKING FOR YOU.
- WHERE IS HE?
- AROUND SOMEWHERE.
BUT YOU SHOULD FIND HIM
AND TAKE OFF,
BECAUSE MADISON
KNOWS YOU'RE HERE.
- SCREW MADISON.
- THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
HEY, I SAW A BEEMER
PARKED OUTSIDE
WITH A BIG, PINK BOW
ON IT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE GO GIVE IT
A LITTLE MAKEOVER?
- NO, I'M--I'M DONE
TRYING TO PLAY THIS GAME.
I MEAN, I'M DONE
WITH ALL OF YOU.
I JUST WANT TO FIND DEREK
AND--AND LEAVE.
- WHATEVER.
I'M GONNA GO HAVE SOME FUN.
- COME ON, PICK UP.
- YO!
- DEREK, WHERE THE HELL
HAVE YOU BEEN?
- OH, SORRY, MAN, MY RECEPTION
IS CRAP IN THIS PLACE.
- [Sighs]
I WANT TO GO HOME.
- YEAH, YEAH. UH, I MEAN,
ARE YOU OKAY?
DID MADISON DO SOMETHING?
- I DON'T WANT TO
TALK ABOUT IT.
I-I JUST WANT TO LEAVE.
- SURE, UH, YEAH,
NO PROBLEM.
LOOK, LET ME FIND LILY
AND SAY GOOD-BYE.
I'M GONNA MEET YOU
AT THE FRONT ENTRANCE.
- NO, NO,
FORGET ABOUT LILY.
LET'S JUST GO NOW.
- MM-HMM, OKAY. UH, TEN MINUTES.
LOOK, SKYE, SERIOUSLY,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BELIEVE
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME TONIGHT,
ALL RIGHT?
I WAS IN THE BASEMENT,
AND LILY COMES--
[beep]
- DAMN IT!
[Sighs]
[sniffles]
- OH.
OH, WELL, HELLO.
THAT IS ONE KILLER
AUTOMOBILE.
IT FEELS LIKE
SOMETHING'S MISSING.
[Scraping]
[rock music]
¶ ¶
[blows]
[laughing]
[engine starts]
WHAT THE HELL?
[Engine revs]
HA HA, REALLY FUNNY.
YOU GOT ME.
WHATEVER. LAME!
HA HA, REAL FUNNY.
I'M GOING INSIDE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[Screaming]
NO! NO!
NO!
AAH! HELP ME!
COME HELP ME, PLEASE!
SOMEBODY HELP ME!
PLEASE! NO!
NO! NO, NO!
OH! OH!
GOD!
HELP!
NO!
OH, MY GOD!
[Screams]
[grunts]
OH!
[Screaming]
NO! NO!
[Groans]
NO!
[Grunts]
NO! NO!
[Groans]
[screams]
[slice, blood splattering]
[electrical buzzing]
- HEY, I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR YOU ALL NIGHT.
APPARENTLY THE FIRST PLACE
YOU CHECKED
WAS IN MADISON'S MOUTH.
- THAT--THAT WASN'T
WHAT IT LOOKED LIKE.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER.
- YES, IT DOES.
IT DOES TO ME.
- YOU KNOW,
I WAS FINE
BEING THE OUTCAST.
AND THEN YOU SHOW UP
AND I THINK, MAYBE,
JUST MAYBE I CAN BE NORMAL.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT I REALIZED
TONIGHT?
THIS ISN'T NORMAL.
THIS IS THE FREAK SHOW,
AND YOU'RE PART OF IT.
- SKYE, I--
SKYE, DON'T.
- BRIGG, LET GO
OF MY ARM.
[Club music]
- WHAT THE HELL, CHLOE?
- ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
EVERYBODY HAVING
A GOOD TIME?
[Cheers and applause]
- GOOD. YOU GUYS KNOW THIS IS
NO ORDINARY NIGHT, RIGHT?
THIS IS MADISON PENROSE'S
SWEET 16!
ALL RIGHT!
THAT'S WHAT I'M
TALKING ABOUT.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
PUT YOUR HANDS TOGETHER
AND GIVE UP
THE MADDEST OF PROPS
TO OUR GUEST OF HONOR,
MISS MADISON PENROSE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
[Cheers and applause]
- HEY, THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
EVERYBODY.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
I, UH, WANT TO START OUT
BY SAYING I APPRECIATE
YOUR BEING HERE
TO HELP CELEBRATE, UM,
THIS VERY HISTORICAL MOMENT
FOR MY BEAUTIFUL BABY GIRL.
- NO.
[Crowd ahing]
- CHLOE?
OH, THE SLUT'S PROBABLY
SOMEWHERE, HOOKING UP.
[Sighs]
NICE.
[sighs]
- YOU KNOW,
I EVEN REMEMBER, YOU KNOW,
THE GIRL SCOUT
FATHER-DAUGHTER DANCES
ON VALENTINE'S DAY,
AND, UM...
- OH, THE DANCES.
- YEAH, THE DANCES.
AND, OF COURSE,
YOU KNOW, WHEN--
WHEN STEPMOM CAME IN
AND HELPED TURN US
ALL AROUND.
I MEAN, THAT WAS
A HAPPY DAY FOR ME,
AND, UM, AND, YOU KNOW,
FOR ALL OF US, I THINK.
AND, UM, IT SEEMS REALLY
LIKE ONLY YESTERDAY...
- EW!
EW.
- I HAVE TO TELL YOU
THAT I'VE TAUGHT MADISON
MANY, MANY THINGS.
I'M ESPECIALLY PROUD THAT I
TAUGHT HER HOW TO BE SUCCESSFUL,
HOW TO, UH, TO GO AFTER
WHAT SHE REALLY WANTED
AND NOT LET ANYBODY
STAND IN HER WAY,
AND, UH...
AND WHEN I LOOK
AT MY DAUGHTER,
I SEE MYSELF.
[Crowd ahing]
AND, UH,
THAT'S THE GREATEST GIFT
THAT A FATHER COULD ASK FOR.
- JUST GET TO THE PART
WHERE YOU GIVE ME A CAR, DAD.
- OKAY, OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
UM, SORRY.
UM, WELL, WHY DON'T WE
JUST GO AHEAD THEN
AND BRING OUT THE CAKE?
BRING OUT THE CAKE,
PLEASE.
[Cheers and applause]
- CHLOE?
IS SOMEBODY IN THERE?
- THERE IT IS,
RIGHT THERE.
[Cheers and applause]
- OH, GOD!
[Screaming]
[sound muted]
- [gasps]
MY SUSHI CAKE!
[All screaming]
[all screaming]
- BRIGG, BRIGG,
BRIGG, BRIGG!
WHAT WAS THAT IN THERE?
WAS THAT REAL?
- MY GOD, DUDE! IT DOESN'T GET
MORE REAL THAN THAT.
WHERE THE HELL IS SKYE?
- I THINK
SHE'S STILL INSIDE!
[All screaming]
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
THIS PARTY ISN'T OVER!
DADDY!
- MADISON!
- DADDY!
YOU HAVE TO FIX THIS!
- MADDIE! MADDIE!
[All screaming]
- YOU BITCH.
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT!
YOU PSYCHO SKANK!
YOU RUINED MY PARTY!
- IT WASN'T ME.
IT WASN'T ME!
[Door slams]
- WHO THE HELL IS THAT?
- IT'S MY FATHER.
WE HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE.
MADISON, RUN!
THIS WAY.
COME ON, COME ON!
- [Whimpering]
- MADISON, WE'RE GONNA
GET OUT OF HERE!
- [Gagging]
[squealing]
NO!
[Whimpering]
[panting]
- THERE IS A WINDOW IN HERE,
I THINK.
- YOU THINK?
NO.
- BRIGG!
YOU CAME BACK!
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- [Whimpers]
RUN, RUN!
- [Squeals]
WHY ARE WE UP HERE?
- I'LL HOLD HIM OFF!
YOU GUYS GET OUT OF HERE!
- OKAY.
- NO, NO, NO!
BRIGG, DON'T, DON'T.
- COME ON! COME ON!
COME ON!
[Club music playing]
COME ON,
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE!
[Both scream]
- BRIGG!
- HE'S DEAD!
COME ON!
- IT WON'T OPEN!
- DEREK!
LEAVE HIM ALONE!
HE'S MY FRIEND.
- SKYE!
SKYE!
- DADDY.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHERE ARE WE?
- THE BASEMENT.
- HE'S GOING TO KILL US.
WE HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE HE GETS BACK.
- HE'S STANDING
RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
- YOU SICK BASTARD!
LET ME GO!
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
- BECAUSE HE THINKS
YOU DESERVE IT.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
TELL HIM IT'S NOT TRUE.
- I TRIED TO TELL HIM,
MADISON.
I TRIED TO TELL HIM
YOU'RE A GOOD PERSON,
THAT HE'S GOT YOU ALL WRONG.
- IT'S TRUE.
I AM A GOOD PERSON.
- BUT YOU'RE NOT.
YOU'RE A MONSTER.
- I'M A MONSTER?
WHAT ABOUT YOUR CRAZY-ASS,
MASK-WEARING DAD?
HE KILLED MY FRIENDS.
HE KILLED THE BOY YOU LIKE.
- THE BOY YOU TORTURED ME
FOR LIKING.
- THAT WAS A JOKE.
- YOU'RE A BULLY, MADISON.
- SO I'M A BULLY.
I'M A HUGE BITCH.
I DON'T DESERVE TO DIE
FOR THAT.
[Crying]
[blade scraping]
PLEASE STOP.
PLEASE, PLEASE STOP.
UHH! HUH!
- AAH!
- KILL HER.
- WHAT?
- SHE ALWAYS GETS
WHAT SHE WANTS.
NOW GIVE HER
WHAT SHE DESERVES.
DO IT, SKYE.
- PLEASE. PLEASE.
I'M SO SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY
FOR EVERYTHING I DID.
PLEASE, DON'T KILL ME.
I'M SORRY.
- I'M SORRY, TOO.
BUT I HAVE TO DO THIS.
- [Groans]
- JEEZ, I THOUGHT YOU WERE
ACTUALLY GOING TO KILL ME!
- [Groans]
- WILL YOU HURRY UP, YOU IDIOT?
- I'M TRYING!
- THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT!
IF YOU HADN'T CRASHED MY PARTY,
NONE OF THIS
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED!
- [Groans]
- UNTIE ME RIGHT NOW, LOSER,
OR I SWEAR TO GOD I'LL
MAKE YOUR LIFE A LIVING HELL!
- [Grunts]
- OUT OF MY WAY!
HELP ME, YOU FREAK!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU CAN'T DO THIS!
- HAVE A SUPER BIRTHDAY,
MADISON.
- I ALWAYS KNEW
YOU WERE A PSYCHO!
YOU LOSER!
YOU'RE NOTHING!
YOU'RE NOBODY!
YOU SUCK!
¶ HEY, MISS MURDER, CAN I ¶
¶ MAKE BEAUTY STAY
IF I TAKE MY LIFE ¶
[Madison screams]
- [calmly]
HE'S IN THE BASEMENT.
[Indistinct radio chatter]
- [groans]
¶ ¶
¶ WITH JUST A LOOK ¶
¶ THEY SHOOK ¶
¶ AND HEAVEN'S BOUND
BEFORE HIM ¶
¶ SIMPLY A LOOK ¶
¶ CAN BREAK ¶
¶ YOUR HEART ¶
¶ THE STARS
THAT PIERCE THE SKY ¶
¶ HE LEFT THEM ALL BEHIND ¶
¶ WE'RE LEFT TO WONDER WHY ¶
¶ HE LEFT US ALL ¶
¶ BEHIND ¶
¶ HEY, MISS MURDER, CAN I ¶
¶ MAKE BEAUTY STAY IF I ¶
¶ TAKE MY LIFE ¶
¶ OH OH OH ¶
¶ ¶
¶ OHH ¶
[engine revs]
¶ HEY, MISS MURDER, CAN I ¶
[engine revving]
¶ MAKE BEAUTY STAY IF I ¶
¶ TAKE MY LIFE ¶
¶ OH OH OH ¶
[electrical buzzing]
[heart monitor beeping]
- YOU'RE AWAKE.
- SKYE?
WHERE AM I?
- THE HOSPITAL.
YOU'VE BEEN OUT FOR DAYS.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE DEAD.
- IS IT OVER?
- I DON'T KNOW.
IS IT?
- I'M GLAD YOU CAME BACK.
- I HAD TO.
FOR YOU.
- [Screaming]
- SKYE! SKYE, DON'T.
- NOW CALM DOWN.
CALM DOWN.
IT'S OKAY.
- [Breathing heavily]
WHERE'S SKYE?
- DON'T WORRY.
NOBODY'S SEEN THAT GIRL
FOR DAYS.
TRY TO GET SOME REST,
OKAY?
I'LL COME BACK AND CHECK ON YOU
IN A MOMENT.
Captioning by CaptionMax; resynced by Zyuranger
[Thrice's In Exile]
¶ ¶