Subtitles by explosiveskull
All right...
You're the Sprite, right?
Okay.
Um... okay.
Ladies and gentlemen, cabin
crew, please remain seated.
Looks like we got a ways before
we break through this thing.
We're gonna have some
rough air coming up.
We're gonna leave the seatbelt
signs on for the time being.
So just sit back, relax.
And we hope to see sunnier
skies here in a bit.
Hope to punch through
the storm shortly.
And again, please remain seated
and keep those
seatbelts fastened.
Everyone, thank you so much
for your patience.
We'll restart beverage service
once we reach clearer skies.
Did you check the ATIS?
I want to get a
read on the weather report.
See when we might break
through this thing.
In sports,
the international...
Why doesn't your
dad smile in photos?
He never has.
Yeah, but... but why?
Oh, I don't know.
Just not his thing.
Even in my baby photos,
he would just like hold me
and just be like...
Probably something I did.
As a baby?
Hey, Mom looks happy.
Did they hate me?
They hated me.
They did not hate you.
That's just how they are.
- You're just saying that.
- No, no.
See, I love you.
And because I love you,
they love you, too.
And even if they hate your guts,
they're still 2,600 miles away.
- Well, Raisinet loved me.
- Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry.
It was fun.
Yeah?
Yeah, and this shit going
on in my brain doesn't matter.
Thank you for asking me to come.
It was perfect.
Yeah?
And thank you for smiling.
Yeah, my pleasure.
Anything?
No change.
Looks like it's unavoidable.
Projections are all
over the place.
Precipitation patterns
are screaming MCC.
But that can't be right.
Great.
It's like this thing
is following us.
It's 25A.
And it's your turn.
Uh...
Yes, sir?
What can I do for you?
Can you please tell the pilot
to not crash the plane? Thanks.
I assure you that
he's already considered that.
Are you on the same
flight as me?
I...
Can I get you something?
My medicine?
It's in my bag.
Sure.
Is it in your carry-on?
Do you know which bin you...
No, no.
My suitcase!
Oh, sir, if you checked
your luggage at the airport,
we can't get to it.
It's in cargo.
No, no, no, no.
Don't you have access to that?
I mean, what
if it's an emergency?
Sir, I'm sorry.
I can get you a headset
or pillow, blanket.
I can get you some water.
How can I
relax knowing that
we could crash any minute now?
Hey...
Oh!
What a little heartbreaker!
- How old is she?
- Almost four.
Oh, what a great age.
I wish I could see the look
on her face when she sees you.
I'd be happy to see
any look on her face.
I've been overseas deployed
for 24 months now.
The only thing I could think
about was her and her mom.
Are you a soldier?
Yes, ma'am.
Army Ranger.
So how much more time
do you have left?
Well, I was delayed in Paris.
The only flight out was to LAX.
So we got five hours
to New York.
And then an hour car ride.
And I get to see my family.
You're adorable.
- She's adorable.
- Oh, I'll say.
They're getting restless.
Yeah. Well, hopefully,
we break through this
before they get
"restless" restless.
Well, we're about
to start service.
So does anyone need
anything now, though?
Oh, yeah. Can you pass me one
of the blankets, please?
Yes. Here you go.
You're too nice for this crew.
Thank you, Liam.
Wow.
Hey.
Don't worry.
I'm supposed to have it.
Sorry.
I wasn't worried.
I'm lying.
I was worried.
Name's Thaddeus.
U.S. Air Marshal.
Anna.
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
Flight Deck?
Can I get you
guys anything?
No, I think we're good.
Thanks, Alice.
Everything good back there?
Mostly.
We had one passenger ask that
you guys not crash the plane.
Hadn't thought of that.
All right.
Well, let me know if you guys
need something. Just ring.
We will. Thanks.
Everything all
right back there?
Yeah, yeah.
Seems good.
Alice was just checking in.
It would have been nice if
JFK had given us
a heads up on this storm
before takeoff.
Oh, I don't think
they knew about it.
I never seen a storm this
big creep up out of nowhere.
We should have been able
to eyeball this thing
the moment we were
off the ground.
Yeah, these domestic
red-eyes are a nightmare, too.
I've done my fair share.
But after a while, I start,
you know, needing some daylight.
Any tips?
All the coffee
in the world, my friend.
All the coffee in the world.
Any plans for New York?
Absolutely.
Got a hot date.
The most beautiful woman
you've ever seen.
- Oh, yeah?
- Oh, yeah.
What's her name?
Don't know yet.
Blanket make things better?
Maybe.
I don't get people
who are afraid of flying.
Like if you can't do it,
why try?
I don't think it's the flying.
I think it's being stuck in
a compressed metal tube
that resembles a penis
while thinking
about falling and exploding.
That's not an image
I want to think of.
What?
A giant penis?
Or the falling and exploding?
Both.
Were you ever
afraid of planes?
I'm afraid of a lot of things.
But flying isn't one of them.
Being up here, it's a
beautiful thing we do.
And look at us.
Up here in the darkness
where no one can see us.
Still majestic birds
after all this time.
How long has it been?
Like three years, girl.
Please? I'm busy.
You're shameless.
- I'll get the next one.
- Oh my God.
It's just...
Ah!
- What happened?
- No, no, there's something...
- I saw...
- What?
- On the wing!
- Sir, please take your seat...
There's something out there!
- Sir, calm down.
- Easy, man.
You need to take a breath!
I saw something!
Calm down, please.
Sir, the storm has
everyone shaken up.
Sir, please, please,
please take your seat, okay?
- Calm down.
- Come on. I can assure you
that there's nothing like
that out there, okay?
Take your seat.
You need to calm down.
Okay, okay.
I just need... excuse me.
Oh, sir, I'm sorry.
You can't use the bathroom.
The captain hasn't turned
off the seatbelt sign.
Sir, don't close the door!
You okay?
Everything's fine, everyone.
Everything's fine.
Excuse me?
What's happening?
It's just nerves.
It happens.
The storm has
everyone shaken up.
Literally, I take
this flight all the time.
This is the worst I've seen it.
Do you live in Los Angeles?
No, my parents do.
We were just there on vacation.
We're heading back
to New York... Brooklyn.
Actually, it was a
late honeymoon, really.
Oh, well, congratulations.
Thanks.
Let me ask you something.
So what happens
when a passenger's
more out of control,
like more than that?
Um...
Generally, these situations
resolve themselves.
But we have protocols in place
for extreme situations.
Yeah, man.
That's scary.
As I said, these situations
usually resolve themselves.
Nothing to fear.
Oh, it's just the storm!
It's just the storm!
You're seeing things!
It's just the rain!
The turbulence.
Sir! Sir!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
- Sir!
- Let me out!
Let me off this plane!
I can't be on this plane!
Sir, please calm down!
Get me off this plane!
She tried to grab me.
Who tried to grab you?
A woman!
A woman in the mirror!
- A woman in the mirror!
- Excuse me!
- Get down! Get down!
- Liam, call the captain!
Need any help?
No! I'm an Air Marshal.
Everything's fine!
Back in your seat!
Everyone back in
your seat, please!
- What happened?
- I don't know.
I think he's having
a panic attack.
I'm not having a panic attack!
I saw something!
Stop!
No, no, I saw something
in the mirror!
Okay, I'm going to have
to restrain this passenger
'til we get to JFK.
Do you have anything
to calm him down?
Yes, but we've never given...
Whatever it is, grab it now!
Grab it now, grab it now!
Hey, are you sure you
guys don't need any help?
Everything's fine, okay?
I'm a U.S. Air Marshal.
Back in your seat!
Everyone back in your seats!
Oh my God, he's a terrorist!
No! I'm just dealing with
somebody who's a little detached
from reality right now.
Miss!
I really need you to hurry!
I can hear you people!
I'm not a terrorist!
How am I a terrorist?
I'm not making this up!
You have to believe...
Here we go.
Swallow! Swallow!
Swallow, that's what we
right there, okay?
Swallow it.
That's what we want.
Right there, okay?
We're okay.
Now we're good.
Now we're calm.
Are you tying him up?
Got to keep him under control.
We still have a lot of
time left on this plane.
I don't want him waking up
and freaking out, okay?
Okay.
- We can get him up right now.
- Okay.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Okay, everybody
in first class,
I need you to get up.
And move to the back of
the plane right now, please!
- Everyone out. Come on.
- So sorry.
Sir, this way.
Ma'am.
Ladies, you too.
Thank you so much.
Okay, go ahead, sweetheart.
I am so sorry...
The passenger that
was giving us the issue
has been restrained.
He's been medicated.
Thank you so much
for your patience with us.
I think that the flight
should return to normal now.
Again, I'm so sorry.
You okay?
That's what we want right there.
Everything's okay!
All right.
You can't interfere
in stuff like this, Bran.
What?
I just wanted to help.
Yeah, I know,
but this isn't something
you should be involved in.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I guess I'm still in my head
about my parents.
I don't know what
their problem is.
You said it was okay.
I believe you.
I always believe you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Maybe next time,
it'll be better.
Yeah. I hope so.
This storm is huge.
It's blanketing everything.
Five minutes ago, it looked like
we'd be out of it in 20, but...
At least the altimeter
and fuel gauge are working.
Lightning screwing with us?
Yeah, looks like it.
But it shouldn't be
doing all this at once.
Flight Deck.
Captain, it's Liam.
The storm caused a
passenger to freak out.
The marshal stepped in
and assisted
but we had to sedate
and restrain him.
Restrain him?
Is everything under
control back there?
I think so.
Okay, good.
Just make sure
everybody's comfortable.
The storm is the only thing
I wanna worry about right now.
Got it.
Okay. Here you are, ma'am.
Sir, what can I get you?
- Just a water, please.
- Okay.
Miss?
I was wondering if you had
anything else I could snack on.
I had the peanuts and
this gentleman gave me his.
But my stomach is
still rumbling.
Oh, we're gonna start
the in-flight meals
as soon as the storm dies down.
Oh, okay, but is there
anything you can do?
If I get you one
of the prepackaged salads,
- would that help?
- Great.
Okay. All right.
Shh.
Here you go.
Thank you, sir,
for sharing your peanuts.
Of course.
You think he saw a ghost?
No.
I mean, I think he probably
thought he saw one, but come on.
Yeah.
Probably just crazy.
You know, I think I saw
a ghost when I was little.
Really?
I mean, maybe.
You know, you see things
you don't understand
like walking down
an old hallway
and you see someone out of
the corner of your eye.
But you look
and they're gone.
Or you're driving and
there's someone behind you.
You look for them and
then they're just gone.
Is that ghosts
or just other people?
Okay, like this one time,
I remember being in
my bed at night.
Lying on my side,
looking out my window
at this line of trees
that's behind my house
and I was blinking a lot 'cause
I'm trying to go to sleep.
And there's this guy
that walks out of the woods.
A guy?
He looked like Frankenstein.
But that's probably not right.
He started walking towards
the house through the backyard
straight towards my window
until I could see
the whites of his eyes
and then he just stood
there and looked at me.
No shit.
What did you do?
I freaked out.
I ran to my parents' room.
Woke them up, told them
I saw a guy in my window.
And then my dad, he came
in and looked around,
but there was nobody there.
They even went into
the backyard.
They said I was dreaming.
Were you dreaming, though?
You think?
I don't remember falling
asleep or waking up.
I mean, I don't...
I don't think
you saw a ghost, babe.
I think you saw creeps.
I don't know.
Have you ever seen one?
No.
But I have seen an angel.
Okay, you know that's
not gonna get you
out of my happy wedding
conversation, right?
All right, worth a
try, worth a try.
I know.
- Cool it.
- All right.
You know, if you give
someone a salad during a storm,
we'll be picking
crouton crumblies
off the floor for hours.
I know, but she was very cute.
This has been a flight, huh?
I know.
I hope that's the worst
that will happen.
Well, we've got
Charles Bronson
over there keeping watch.
We should be fine.
You okay?
Okay, all right...
Need some help over here!
Oh, my God!
Ma'am, are you all right?
- You bring a towel!
- Yeah.
Napkins! Anything!
Okay.
Can you breathe?
All right.
She's coming back.
The hits just keep coming.
Here you go.
Let's get you back in the seat.
There you go.
Get up.
Easy, easy.
I think it's in my hair.
Check the other salads! Go!
Jesus!
Flight Deck.
Hey, sorry to bother
you again...
Pan US57. Be advised,
you're rapidly approaching
a low-pressure system.
It will be difficult to
continue tracing you at...
This is PAN US57, over.
We're losing you.
PAN US57, over.
Pan... 57... Repeat.
Advised... rapidly low
pressure...
system, will be difficult
...to track you.
Liam, what's going on?
Our in-flight meals are,
well, they're rotten, I think.
Rotten?
They're like Satanic rotten.
Full of maggots,
actual maggots.
That is disgusting.
The in-flight meals
are rotten.
Great.
Have Liam call LAX.
Tell them about the food.
Captain says to call LAX.
Let them know about the food.
There's not much
we can do from up here.
So just try and
keep the passengers
as comfortable as you can,
and worst case, we'll take
care of them we land.
What did he say?
You keep
everyone comfortable.
The phone's not working.
We're running out of ways
to keep them comfortable.
Seriously, bring
on the frogs!
What?
What else was there?
Locusts? Darkness?
Yeah.
Bring on the...
Ryan, go for shoulder straps!
No power to the engines?
That's gotta be
a technical bug!
No way we got struck!
No thrust!
Altimeter's out!
All right, we have to keep
the nose up in this glide!
You got eyes on
the horizon, Ryan?
I'm trying.
I can't tell if it's up
or down right now.
All right,
keep your eyes out there.
Wait for a lightning strike!
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
JFK center, this is
Pan US 57!
We've got dual engine failure!
I repeat, all engines out!
Going for an engine failure
systems check!
- Ryan! Anything?
- No...
Come on!
We're in aerodynamic stall!
We are dead stick!
We've got to get
the APU fired up
or we are up a shit's creek!
Auxiliary's not working.
Shit!
30 degrees up!
Copy that!
Pull back with me!
We gotta get this nose level!
Let's go!
Come on, come on!
We're still dropping!
We need to get
the engines working!
We get 'em spinning,
the generators will run!
What about the RAT?
Well, we're too far out.
Not gonna work.
Fire, damn it! Connect!
Come on, fire, damn it!
Connect!
Connect, damn it!
It's now or never, Jack!
We're at the point
of no return!
Hold on.
Hold on!
Please work, please work.
Please work, please!
Here we go!
Come on, pull!
Thank God.
Flight Lead,
please contact the cockpit.
Thank you.
Good work.
I've never seen a plane
die like that before.
I have, but not like that.
Looks like you're getting
to see a lot of things
you never seen before tonight.
Jesus Christ, I think
I almost had a heart attack.
Okay.
Can you start the walkthrough?
Yeah.
You okay back there?
Sir, you okay?
How we doing over here?
Yeah, I think so.
That was a lot.
How about everyone else?
Any injuries?
I don't know.
I haven't started
the walk-through yet.
Copy that.
Looks like we're about
4:10 till we hit New York.
Just try to keep everyone
calm and comfortable.
And let's see if
we can make this
a better trip
from here on out.
Last thing we need is
a plane full of angry people.
Okay. Thank you so much.
Yes?
Oh, sweetie, that looks bad.
Oh, my God.
Why don't we touch you up
in the restroom?
I'm not qualified for this.
Thanks.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
My apologies.
They're doing
everything they can.
Ladies and gentlemen,
apologies for the turbulence.
As you may have gathered,
our aircraft experienced
a brief loss of power
which caused the drop
in altitude.
But everything's
back in order.
Good news is, planes are made
to handle situations like this.
We hit a rough patch of sky.
But it's our
number one priority
to get you to New York,
or wherever your
final destination
may be with us this evening,
safe and sound.
Hoping to have you on
the ground in
just about four hours.
So just sit back
and try to relax.
We'll be sending the flight
crew through the cabin
to make sure everyone's okay.
Once again, we apologize
for the discomfort.
On behalf of the airline
and the crew,
we hope you enjoy the
remainder of the flight.
Hey, why... why am I...
It's just a zip tie, okay?
- Zip tie? But...
- Shh.
You had an episode.
I had to restrain you.
- All I'm saying...
- It's for your own good.
But... No, no.
You don't understand...
I'm gonna tell
you one more time!
Shh!
Listen to me.
You have the right
to remain silent.
And if I were you, that's
exactly what I would do.
All right.
- Relax.
- Okay.
JFK Center, PAN-US 57.
LAX Center, PAN-US 57?
We've lost contact with JFK.
Do you copy?
Shit, I can't get anyone.
They were updating us on
the pressure systems.
This all happened after
we lost power.
Keep trying.
They'll come back.
What about the systems check?
I've ran through the book.
The plane can fly.
But after the outage,
we got a few problems.
According to the diagnostics,
the cabin pressure's good.
Fuel's good.
Landing gear...
Landing gear is out.
Coms are down.
And autopilot's gone?
- Yeah.
- Okay, well...
This plane may not be brand new,
but it's one of the
greatest ever built.
Keep our hands on the wheel,
we should be just fine.
What about FMS?
What happens if, for some
reason, we lose navigation?
You've never flown one of
these things before, have you?
Through a storm
with engine failure?
Not really.
Keep calm, kid, all right?
I've been through
worse than this.
Keep your head on.
What's ATIS saying about
the weather report?
Well, still surrounded.
Even if we wanted
to divert our path,
according to the data,
there's no way around it
and we're stuck in the middle.
I can't see
anything out there.
Look, equipment,
no equipment,
radio or no radio,
storms only last so long.
We'll be through this shortly.
Your head.
Keep it on.
I'll do my best.
What?
Oh my God!
What's going on?
Hello? Hello?
Ma'am?
Excuse me, ma'am?
Ma'am, can you hear me?
Ma'am?
Can you let me know
that you're okay, please?
Help! I can't get out!
The door won't open!
Somebody, please help me!
Ma'am?
I'm sorry ma'am, the lock
override is stuck.
I can't open the door
from this side.
I can't get out!
Help me!
Ma'am?
Can you... Can you let me know
that you're okay, please?
I can't get out!
Hello?
Ma'am, please.
Ma'am? Please.
Okay, someone's coming
to help, okay?
Please just stay calm.
If you can hear me, stay calm.
What's up?
I think that there's
a woman trapped inside.
She's stuck?
Yeah. The locking mechanism,
isn't working properly.
All right, here.
Let me try.
Okay.
Ma'am?
This is the U.S. Air Marshal.
I need you to open
this door right now.
Your right, the lock override
switch seems to be jammed.
We need something
to pry open the door with.
Oh, okay, we have, um...
Oh, great. Um...
There's a killer
on your plane.
All right.
Ma'am, on the count
of three,
I want you to push the door
open from the inside, okay?
What?
I don't understand
what you're saying!
There's a killer.
One, two, three!
Oh my God.
Okay. Come on, sweetie.
Come on.
Okay, okay.
Shh, okay.
Okay.
This way.
Yeah, can you take
a seat for me?
Good girl, good girl.
What happened?
The mirror, the mirror!
What about the mirror?
I saw her.
She was pregnant.
I couldn't breathe!
That doesn't make any sense.
We're gonna get you
to your seat,
we're gonna get you
comfortable okay?
Can you stand up for me?
Come on, okay?
It's okay.
Shh, shh, shh.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay, all right?
It's okay.
Thank you.
Go ahead, take a seat.
What is going on?
Seriously.
We're never flying this
flight again is what's going on.
No, I'm serious, Bran!
Okay, that guy freaks out,
there's maggots in the food!
- Hey.
- No, no.
People are throwing up,
the lights are going out
in the plane.
People are getting hurt,
And that poor woman,
I don't know what's going on!
I know.
I don't know either.
We're in a... hey, we're in
a hell of a storm, okay?
And storms pass, all right?
- Are you okay?
- I thought we were gonna die.
You're not gonna die.
The Air Marshal said that
the crazy one was a terrorist.
Okay, ma'am,
he didn't say that.
I think he actually said
the opposite.
Hey, what are we supposed
to do when there's
a crazy person on the plane?
I mean, what if he hurts
somebody?
Okay, well, maybe
we shouldn't call him crazy?
And what's this
talk about ghosts?
Okay, nothing, right?
It's just...
We're all just a little
frazzled right now.
It's a malfunction,
a malfunction of the plane.
That's it.
Look, all I know is
you better
keep that man away from
me.
'Cause I just want
to get on the ground.
You know, maybe we got
struck by lightning, you know?
I mean, that explains
the power going in and out.
Lightning hits planes
in the air all the time.
What?
Are you a mechanic?
No, I'm a teacher
and I watch the news.
Okay, you know what?
Cool it, all right?
We're in a storm, okay?
We're on a plane.
The plane is a machine.
If you so much as use
your cell phone,
the signals get
jumbled, all right?
So if we're this high up
covered by clouds surrounded
by lightning, of course,
some shit's gonna go wrong.
So, please stop
making accusations
if you guys don't even
know it's true.
You'll only make everyone panic.
Exactly.
Everyone just take
a deep breath.
Sit back and try to relax.
Are you sure
everything's normal?
No, I'm not sure,
but it's not supernatural.
We're on a plane and
planes have problems.
Something's not right, Bran.
I know, look.
How about we take our
mind off this?
Like music maybe?
You still haven't listened
to the mix tape
that my brother put on
your phone in L.A., right?
I don't know.
It feels weird.
Okay, okay,
babe, babe, babe.
We're in a storm,
but storms pass, okay?
Now if I open my carry-on
and snakes fall out...
I'll be the first to
let you know, okay?
- Okay.
Hey!
Listen to me!
You're really stupid
if you think
I'm letting you
out of my sight.
Relax!
Revenge!
He wouldn't stop!
Did you say something to me?
What?
I... um...
I thought I heard something.
Where are you?
Please help!
So dark down here...
Okay, did you not hear that?
Hear what?
There's someone trying to call
me or speak to me or something.
What?
What am I trying to hear?
I don't hear anything.
- Brandon?
- What?
Nothing.
Murder!
Shit! Did you mess with
my volume or something?
No.
Oh, my God!
Did you sit on it
or something? Jesus!
No!
Are my ears bleeding?
Danika, what's going on?
You're scaring me.
My...
Hey.
Captain?
What the...
Alice, there's
procedure for a reason.
You can't just barge
in here like that.
Look, three hours and some
change, we'll be on the ground.
That's what
I'm worried about.
That's what we're all
worried about.
We're losing this flight.
I need you to take control now!
I'm sorry?
So far, we've had a
lightning storm, rotten food.
People having panic attacks.
And then losing power?
I don't know what this is
but it isn't normal.
She's got a point.
Look, Alice.
I need you to calm down, okay?
It's a rough flight.
But you've been doing this
long enough, you should know.
All right, I don't know
what's going on back there.
I have no idea
what the problem is.
But I can't be back there
to fix it personally.
I'm doing everything I can
to keep us in the air!
Yes, sir. I...
Oh, I know you're trying
and you're doing a great job.
It's just we're doing
all we can up here.
Sorry, Alice.
Yes, sir.
I understand.
Look, I'm not trying
to be a hard-ass here.
It's just that, if we can
all make it through
this flight without losing
our minds, drinks are on me.
You seeing this?
See what?
What is that?
Up there in the clouds?
Are those birds?
Uh, that's impossible.
Birds don't fly
at this altitude.
Well, then what
in the world...
Are those people?
What are you talking about?
Captain, I...
I don't see anything.
You're not seeing this?
Right here!
I swear to Christ!
People?
Uh, you want me to
take over for a minute?
Maybe, you know, I think a
break might do you some good.
Maybe some coffee or something?
A break?
No, I don't need a break.
Shit!
A bottle of water,
please, Alice?
Jack, there's no shame
in being exhausted.
It's a red-eye direct
coast to coast.
And look at what
we're flying in.
I know. I'm just...
Scared?
Yeah, me too.
Yeah, maybe a little.
I don't know.
Something's not right.
Something just
doesn't feel right.
Your hands have been shaking.
Are they?
Didn't even notice.
I guess I just got
a lot on my mind.
Thanks.
What'd you see?
I don't know.
Make sure this
stays open, okay?
Dani?
Brandon?
What?
I don't feel well.
What's going on?
Would you think it was
weird if I thought
there was something else
on this flight?
Is it like your
Frankenstein thing?
No.
I'm not following.
Dani?
Honey, hey!
Dani!
Are you okay?
Do you have aspirin?
Uh, yeah.
I think there's some
in my carry-on.
The killer...
There's a killer on this plane.
I... I...
I don't know
what's happening!
There's a killer
on this plane!
There's a killer...
Dani?
Dani!
Hey!
Hey, babe, hey.
You're okay,
you're okay.
Look at me, look at me.
You're fine.
You're okay.
Come on.
Okay, come on.
You're okay. Come on.
Come on, honey.
It's okay, it's all right.
What happened?
Get it away from me!
Get what away from you?
There's nothing there.
Baby, look,
there's nothing there.
Dani, look, look.
Look, look. There's nothing
there, babe.
Hey! How about you two quit
freaking everybody out!
We're not trying
to freak anybody out!
Guys, keep your
voices down, all right?
This is not making it better.
In fact, it's making it worse.
- This is some bullshit!
- Sir...
I'm just trying
to calm her down!
Better?
What did you see?
A woman, I think.
She was dead in the bin.
Stuffed in there!
I opened it and
she grabbed me.
And I know there's
nothing there
but it looked and
it felt so real!
I believe you.
- You do?
- Yeah.
Something's going on here.
We just need to find out what.
Hey, is she all right?
Uh, yeah, I think so.
I'm fine. I promise.
I just don't know
what's going on.
All right, I'm done.
Look, excuse me.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom,
all right?
You really don't wanna
go to the bathroom!
Oh, great.
Mr. Crazy Man's awake.
Please don't say it, okay?
There are no
terrorists on this plane.
Look, Mr. Marshal.
Come here.
Why don't we just tie her
ass to the chair and...
Sir!
I won't let you
tie her down!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
No one's gonna get tied down
to anything, okay?
You keep her calm,
you got nothing to worry about.
Right.
I just don't understand, okay?
I don't understand
what's going on.
what's going on with my wife.
Look, nobody knows
what's going on.
But the one thing that
I do know is
that I trust the man
with the badge.
And the gun?
Look, there's a lot of crazy
unseen shit going on here.
I don't know what it is.
But I do know that this woman
here has to be detained!
Hey, hey, hey!
Enough.
Easy! Enough!
Listen to me.
We are just trying to get
back to our families
just like everybody
in this place.
Get to your seat.
Just get to your seat.
Hey, enough! Enough!
I said in your seat now!
Sit down! Hey!
In your seat now!
Now listen up!
I need everyone to keep
their head on their shoulders!
Let's stay calm, okay?
Now I don't
think it's terrorism.
So let's stop using that word.
That word just gets
everyone worked up.
- Yeah, but what if...
- Don't!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What? Are we in North Korea now?
We can't express ourselves?
Really?
Are you serious?
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm not usually this
much of an asshole.
I just wanna get
on the ground!
Hey! Hey!
Look, it's scary when
the plane malfunctions.
It is.
But we are people who
do this for a living.
So let us do our job
and we will be fine.
See? That's exactly what
I was saying, malfunction.
So what are
we talking about here?
Gas leak?
Loss of cabin pressure?
I didn't say that.
How much longer until
we get to New York?
Are we gonna be okay?
It's just gonna be
a couple more hours, okay?
We're almost there.
Miss?
Could you please check
in with the captain?
Make sure all the mechanical
issues are in order, please?
What do you think
is going on here?
We are losing
electricity often.
It's a good place to start.
I'm no mechanic.
But I'm sure the captain's
doing everything
he's supposed to be doing
on his end.
Most important thing is
we're still in the air.
We got that going for us.
Fantastic, fantastic.
Finally, somebody that knows
what the hell they're doing.
Hey, sir, you keep
talking like that,
the two of us are gonna have
a real serious problem.
So I need you to sit here
and keep your mouth shut.
You got that?
Yeah.
I'm so sorry about all this.
Hey, hey...
Hey, don't be
sorry, okay?
You didn't do anything wrong.
I don't know what's happening.
Did you take the aspirin?
Of course, but I wouldn't...
Don't worry, sweetheart.
You all do realize
that if there is
a major malfunction while we're
in the air during a storm,
that's worse
than ghosts, right?
Because that can
actually kill us.
Okay, the plane
is not haunted.
That's an insane theory.
Look, why don't
we just land the plane
and check for problems
on the ground?
Look, has the captain
mentioned anything
about when and where
we're gonna land?
From what I can tell,
the storm
is making it hard
to get anywhere.
I mean, at this point,
trying to land in this,
we're safer up here.
Excuse me?
What about the storm?
Do you have any idea
when it'll be behind us?
No. I mean, at this point, the
storm's blanketing everything.
It seems to be
tracking with us.
- Excuse me!
- What do you want?
It's not electrical.
We need to do an
emergency landing now!
It's real!
What's real?
Look, we can't land until
the storm clears up, Alice!
- You know that!
- We need to land it now, Jack!
Alice, what's going on?
It's ghosts!
The plane is haunted!
Again with this?
Ryan?
Look, we're all tired.
No, no, no, no.
You need to listen to me!
You don't know
what we just saw.
This lady down in the aisle!
You're the only ones
that didn't see it!
Will you maybe sit down
for just a little bit?
I'm getting worried about you.
We're gonna be on the ground
in like 95 minutes or...
No, listen! No!
The longer that
we're up here,
the longer the lives
of everybody up here
- is in jeopardy!
- Yeah?
Where do you want me
to land, Alice, huh?
Our coms are out.
The storm's been on
us since takeoff.
We're on our own
with nowhere to go!
The plane is haunted.
Would you listen to yourself?
We're not gonna land the plane
because you're superstitious!
I mean, why would ghosts
want to haunt this plane?
For revenge.
Excuse me?
What did you say?
Revenge!
Ryan, leave your belts on.
Ryan?
Ryan...
Revenge!
Ryan!
Stop!
Ryan, stop!
What are you doing?
In your seats!
Ryan, what are you doing?
Stop!
Hey, hey, hey!
Get off of him!
You okay?
You're not flying autopilot?
No.
We lost it when
the plane lost power.
What the hell happened?
I'm so sorry, Ryan.
All right.
I don't know what
the hell we just saw.
But something's
definitely wrong.
We agree on that, right?
I mean, you said
there's something
physically wrong
with the plane, right?
No, not anything that's gonna
cause hallucinations or visions.
I don't know what would cause
us to see the things we saw.
Okay, well, let's start
from the beginning.
So the storm started
soon after takeoff.
Precheck was fine.
Luggage was fine.
Mr. Peck in 25A...
Yeah, poor guy.
And Mr. Peck claimed that
he saw something unusual
on the wing of the plane
and then he went to
the bathroom to cool off
and then he got spooked again.
Well, I know what I saw
in the bathroom was real.
The woman in the bathroom,
she was in the mirror
and she was
reaching out for me.
And then I fell
through the floor.
I couldn't
get the door unlocked.
Me either.
I tried, but I couldn't.
It felt like it was being
held from the inside.
We checked it, though.
I mean, there's nothing
physically unusual about it.
Okay, then the plane
lost power and we fell.
And then the food
was spoiled somehow.
I heard a woman scream
through my earbuds.
Scream?
Scream what?
At first it was whispers.
Then it got louder.
It sounded like
she said, "Murder".
Well, then that's
when my phone stopped working.
Mine too.
I thought I was
the only one.
And there was something
really weird on my screen.
What was it?
A sonogram.
A what?
You know, like when
you take pictures of babies
from a pregnant lady.
That woman in the aisle.
And then Ryan going crazy
and attacking Jack.
Then the corpse
in the overhead bin.
And now someone's
written "murder"
on the outside of your window.
Okay, so what are
we looking for?
And where do we even start?
I mean, it has to be coming
from around here somewhere.
Well, it all started in
the front of the plane.
But I already checked
the bathroom, though.
And we've been up there
most of the flight.
That wouldn't explain the
phones or the overhead bins.
Or what happened
in the cockpit.
We're so screwed.
No, we're not screwed,
guys, okay?
Listen, we just need
to find the source
to what the hell
is going on right now.
Ryan?
Where am I?
I can't move my hands.
It's on purpose, kid.
- What happened?
- You attacked Jack.
What?
You got crazy eyes
and went straight
for the throat.
Why would I do that?
All right, listen up.
I know it's been a crazy night
for all of us.
But there has to be
a perfectly reasonable
explanation for all of this!
There are only
so many places to look.
If not the cabin, the front
or the back, what else is there?
Okay, well, we decided
that it started on the wing.
And now we have that
word written on his window...
Yeah, but we can't check
outside on the wing right now.
We're in the middle
of a flight.
What about the manifest?
Is there anything onboard
that's out of the ordinary?
Nothing that I know of.
No special packages
from museums?
No dead soldiers
being transferred
at home from Afghanistan?
Brandon?
What are you saying, man?
I mean, objects could
be conduits for spirits.
Okay. Maybe there's
something on the plane
that's traveling with it.
Okay, so if there's nothing
on the manifest, what do we do?
What were you saying?
When?
When you said you fell through
the floor, where did you go?
Um, I don't know.
The cargo hold, I think.
Why?
Because I saw that too.
When I fell back
against the seat
and then I was
in the cargo hold.
Babe...
There was someone there.
And I don't...
And I don't know, but...
I felt like
they needed my help.
What... What are you saying?
There's something...
something happened.
Something bad.
We have to go down there.
Babe...
If we are having visions
of the same thing
in the same location,
something is telling us
to go down there.
The luggage.
Speak up.
I don't know what's going on.
But talking about it isn't
going to solve anything.
Like she said,
we need to go down there
and see for ourselves.
If I find out you
had something to do with this,
you are in a
big world of hurt.
Do you understand that?
How? How?
You tied me
and put me in a chair.
Cut him loose.
Yeah, cut him loose.
Any of us would have
freaked out in that bathroom.
Miss, would you happen
to have any scissors, please?
Yes. Thank you.
Don't make me regret this.
You won't.
Ah, God.
Okay.
Here's what's gonna
happen next.
You're all gonna go
back to your seats
and I'm gonna go down
to the cargo area
and check it out for myself.
I'm sorry. Sorry, guys.
No one can go down to cargo.
Do you want this to come
to an end or not?
Because I gotta cover
all my bases here.
- I'm going with you.
- Dani...
No, you are not going with me.
No! It was speaking to me!
I saw it!
I'm not gonna sit
up here and wait
for someone else
to figure it out!
I'm going!
No, you're not going!
Look, I'm going too.
I didn't travel this far
to get back to my wife
and my kid to
not get home now.
Now if getting down
there finding out
what's going on is going
to help us all get home,
then I'm gonna help you.
I have your six, man.
I appreciate that.
But I'm doing
my job right now
and I'm going down alone!
Dani, you stay here.
I'm gonna go with the marshal.
Nobody's coming with...
Please stop!
Just follow me.
You guys are gonna
have to be quick.
I can't see anything
down there.
That light won't
be strong enough.
Hang tight.
That one will.
There we go.
What is that?
Sounds like a baby.
Oh!
Guys, what is happening?
Sorry! I thought I saw
something, but it's gone.
This is a nightmare.
Oh!
- You okay?
This is bad.
Oh...
It's leading to that bag.
Austin, do you want
to grab that?
Yeah, sure.
Guys?
What are they?
- Her!
- Who?
The overhead bin!
In the overhead bin!
That's blood.
Souvenirs.
Typical serial killer.
Holy shit!
What, what?
It would be her.
Are they all here?
Where's the woman that ran
towards us and disappeared?
Holy Mary Mother of God,
that's her.
There.
This bag belongs
to someone on the plane?
A killer?
Whose bag is this?
- That's easy to figure out.
- Find out.
No way.
Captain, I'm gonna have
to speak with you
about what's been
going on tonight.
No disrespect, Marshal.
But can we do this another time?
I don't know
if you've noticed,
but I'm flying this
plane by myself
and we haven't really been
having a great night.
You sure you wanna
do this right here?
Do what?
Talk about the women
you've murdered.
Murdered?
You serious?
Cut the bullshit!
Whoa!
You can't talk to me like that!
Look, Marshal, whatever
you think's going on,
we can't have this many
people in the cockpit.
I'm sure you know protocol.
I'm afraid I'm not
gonna be able
to follow protocol
right now, Captain.
Neither are they.
What is this?
We're almost on the ground.
Whatever it is can wait
till we're on the ground.
No, it can't wait.
We're talking about
this right now!
Where did you get these?
What did you do to her?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
What is this?
Good God!
What's wrong with you people?
I don't know who this woman is.
Don't lie to me!
What did you do to her?
What did you do to her baby?
It's funny how the women
in these photographs
were the same women
causing all the problems
on this plane tonight.
Also very funny how all the
pictures ended up in your bag.
Jack....
Captain.
I don't... look, these
aren't my... oh, come on!
Tell the truth!
Captain?
- Cut me loose!
- What?
Don't do it!
We need somebody to fly
the plane, please!
Cut me loose!
Trust me!
Without a pilot,
we're gonna die!
Hurry!
Revenge!
Please!
Hurry!
Revenge!
Move!
Murderer!
Revenge!
You know who I am?
Get your hands off me!
Christ!
Dani? Baby?
Hey...
Come on...
Come on.
What happened?
I didn't...
I didn't do it, I swear.
Save it.
What did you do?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Let's get her
to her chair.
- Can you...
- Yeah, I got her.
I got you.
Come on, babe.
Hey, hey.
Tell me what you did!
I didn't do anything!
You tell me what
you did right now
or I will end you
where you sit.
Look, nothing
I did matters, okay?
Austin!
Okay?
None of it matters.
You're gonna get
everyone killed!
Wake up, honey,
come on, babe?
Come on.
No, not everyone.
Just you.
Oh, my God.
No!
Stop. Please stop.
No, no, no, no!
It's not my fault!
I didn't mean it the first time!
It was an accident!
She liked it rough, you know.
I did too,
so I thought it was okay!
We were role-playing!
And I guess I just got
a little too into it!
I was scared the first time!
I felt guilty,
but deep down inside.
I liked it.
I loved it.
I loved watching
the expiration light
blink and then fade.
It became an urge.
A need.
Then it became me.
I realized I could
just fly away
and no one would know.
And I didn't know how to stop!
I just...
Oh God, I'm so sorry, please!
I'm so sorry! I just...
I don't know how to stop it!
Forgive me.
Please forgive me.
I'll do anything.
No!
Brandon!
Come here!
No!
This is all your fault!
Bitch!
Don't...
No!
No, no!
Everybody, please hang on!
JFK Center, PAN-US 57!
Do you copy?
Damn it!
Hang on!
Brace!
Brace, brace, brace!
- Brandon!
- I got you!
I got you!
Shit.
We're coming in hot!
Hold on!
Come on, baby,
come on, come on!
Come on, come on.
Got this...
Everyone brace for impact!
Are you okay?
You okay?
We're good back here.
Oh my God.
It's okay, it's okay.
Hey, hey, it's okay.
I got you.
Ryan?
Ryan, okay.
Subtitles by explosiveskull