- Are you ready?
- Are you?
Well...
Seat belts.
I forgot one thing.
Then go.
Hey.
No, we go just for the weekend.
Tell him that I'm flying there
after two weeks.
Alright. I will think about it.
Is that your brother?
Hey, Doug.
He says hello.
I have to go.
You are dear. Bye.
Is everything okay?
Calls to stop. Now I belong to
you for the whole weekend.
How can your mother?
He...
Case does not change.
Actually I do not know.
Makes good to get away from.
- I'm excited.
- So do I.
our nature
Is this pihatienne?
Is this it?
Is. How come?
Beyond belief,
because you have hidden this from me.
I have not concealed anything.
What a mess.
You said this mökiksi.
It's just a house.
Detectives got it cheap.
Before here was not expensive.
Did you bring the goods go
in the fridge?
You mean soy yogurt?
Yes, sir.
It is not, however, spoil easily.
I go to the toilet quickly.
Deuce! I forgot prevention.
I packed them in your bag.
DOES your father seats himself?
No. My mother care valtaosasta-
- But then the father took the house.
She probably gets to work in your yard
of the local schoolchildren.
- Where are we going?
- Come on.
Are those nice tits?
Yeah.
- Time weird.
- Children are doing weird stuff.
What would you say,
if our children were running here?
What children?
I forgot to tell you,
menkkani that are overdue.
- Do it again.
- I do not.
- Try again.
- Your turn.
Feels good is not it?
I can not continue.
OK...
What is that?
What?
Listen.
the bad guys come
to do us mischief.
Disgusting things ...
What?
What the hell?
Who is it?
- Who is it?
- My father.
Exported stuff upstairs.
- He is.
- Who?
I do not know. My father is.
Would you help clean up? Get dressed.
Do not freak out.
- Get dressed.
- Puen, upon.
Here.
Do not freak out.
- Yes All right.
- What was that?
Where?
Where are my underpants?
Hey.
Seth.
I did not realize that you were here.
So...
This was a last minute thing.
We hopped in the car and Martha ...
... On the way.
- Hello, I'm Gil.
- Andie.
Nice to finally meet you.
So, at last.
Hey.
This is my friend Vicky.
Vicky, this is my son Seth.
- Hey.
- And Angie.
- Andie.
- Excuse me. Andie.
- Nice to meet you.
- Likewise.
I just said Vickylle,
that your sister would soittanut-
- So confused the car.
Martha gave us a car.
We do not have guessed you'd
come here.
In your email you said, that you
would have a whole month on business trips.
My plan changed.
Well, we pack kamamme
and we will leave you alone.
Are you going to you?
We came here just for a day.
You sure?
So, we were just leaving.
Do not be late takiamme.
Do you have someone in Brooklyn gig?
Something like that.
Alright.
The restroom is a terrible mess.
Did you see?
Wet towels on the floor.
And did you see the yard?
He does not clean up their tracks.
He throws stuff in a dumpster in
the direction of and leave them to it.
- He did not even know my name.
- He has a bad nimipää.
Do not you find it strange,
that me loving poikaystäväni-
- Has not told me his father?
It has nothing to do with you.
This is so typical of him.
Why can not he be
more like her sister?
Martha would not do such a thing.
Should I ask them to stay?
What?
I do not want her to receive
the starting passports for me.
As for the "departure passports'?
He wanted to back to the city.
Do you really think that they drove
here until one day?
Gold...
I know that you had planned everything.
It is true golden ...
... But your father is here.
I have not even met him.
It would be strange to bust out.
It would be weirder to stay
and his guest with a woman.
How do you know that?
Annoyed him,
when we said leave?
No. He wants that we leave.
Hopefully, I did not interrupt.
You do not at all.
I was just wondering ...
... That you can stay for dinner,
If you want.
You would leave
before the backlog, which is a good idea.
But if you really want to,
Vicky will soon begin to cook.
He is not a ...
Well, the kitchen is not
his strong point.
But...
Sounds great.
We have not eaten.
Sounds good.
He delights.
Food is about an hour away.
Mr. Sherwood?
Just tell Gil.
I'm still not so old.
Gil, I do not want to be ilonpilaaja-
- But I'm a vegan.
- Vegan.
- Yes.
- Are you a vegan?
- I'm not a vegetarian.
He is a liar.
He eats fish.
All right, I'll tell Vickylle.
- Thank you.
Looks really good.
Thank you. No, this is nothing.
There are movies,
if you want to look at something later.
TV does not work. I paid for it in 2000
dollars, and does not even start.
I invite someone to take a look at it.
Seth might be able to fix it.
Are you adept with the machines?
I do not, but I'm used to
to do in the studio of any kind.
I can not delete the images from your computer.
I do not know what to do.
Maybe you can help?
Hey.
No, now is well suited.
Yup. Why did he do so?
I already said,
it will be resolved in arbitration.
It is really embarrassing,
while about it publicly.
Yes, it should get the hang of.
- Was it opera ?
- It is, Pagliacci.
It is his lempimusikaalinsa.
He went always watching it.
You have not told all.
Forget the statements of witnesses.
I wonder what can it?
So you're a machine wizard.
Not me...
I help my friend to build studion-
- That is, the plug must be poked
into the wrong sockets.
Right, right, bye.
Can you believe that Ben was threatened
to bring the case before a judge?
This is tasty.
- Thank you, that you put the food.
- Really good.
It is nothing.
You should use a lot of butter,
if they want people to like the food.
Is this butter?
Seth, it's okay.
What now?
You are a vegan.
- It is okay.
- Where the problem is?
- I put the butter.
- So what?
It is an animal product, Gil.
It is not an animal.
He talked about vegetarianism.
- What the hell difference does it make?
- It does not matter.
- What can you eat?
- Can I have a salad?
Clear.
Seth, you said eat a fish.
I applied mine vegan.
- Why did you choose to vegan?
- In other words, I do not eat this.
Alright.
Seth, providing the most viiniä-
- But it is the bacteria,
receiving the wine käymään-
- And you probably do not want to kill them.
- Gil.
- How would I know?
Thank you.
- Of course.
- I did not know.
So.
- Thank you dear.
- You're welcome.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
It is okay.
- You're welcome.
- Thank you.
If you fix the TV'S,
maybe we can watch a movie.
I can look at it
and find out where the problem is.
I glanced at it already. It does not work.
I invite someone to fix it.
This is from the 1600's.
Does anyone play Scrabble?
Not anyone?
I'm a pretty clever.
Alan to be tired.
I think I'll go to bed.
I apologize for his stunts.
What tricks?
He behaved like a teenager in vain.
Sometimes people fall
stuck in a rut.
Who supposedly behaves like that?
You are right.
Why do you put their food butter?
- Is that a joke?
- Is not.
We would have avoided the whole mess.
How had I known,
they do not eat butter?
- I told you.
- You talked about vegetarianism.
What difference does it make?
You'd asked minulta-
- Before you asked them to stay.
It's just one night.
I had a lovely evening.
- But not this evening.
- But not this evening
So.
I do not know.
She is a bit crazy.
You could say "interesting".
Alright. No, I understand.
Got to go.
You are dear.
Do not you talked about this
afternoon?
He played with when you were
in the bathroom.
We should leave in the morning.
Alright.
Let's do what ever you want.
- Why did you say about it?
- How?
- Passive-aggressively.
- I meant that if you want to go.
Have you eaten enough?
Are you hungry?
Is not.
- I'll put something, if you want to.
- I'm not hungry.
Alright.
Vicky is my sister lived.
He is not so young.
If the father wants to conceal things,
Let them keep their secrets.
I do not want to know.
Why did you do that?
Excuse me.
- Why is it bothering you?
- There is a bully, but ...
Well...
It seems childish.
I did not do it in relation to your father.
The same it, even though you would do.
- In a way, teitkin.
- Alright.
Alright.
Hey.
- Good morning.
What the hell is this?
I thought it was coffee.
It was a thermostat,
when I got up in the morning.
What the heck Yerba Mate is?
It is Yerba Mate.
- I put on a new pot of.
- Do not.
The pan is full of it.
Putsaan it.
I'm not going to clean up their footsteps
throughout the weekend.
- I did not know that you know how to paddle.
- They have kayaks.
It would be nice to try them later.
I'm not very clever.
That's why you have those four.
They are not for me but for my father.
He forced us to.
He is kajakkimestari.
He or she can even eskimo rolls.
Along with the kayak with your name.
- Good morning.
Where are you going?
Vicky and me
must return to the city.
So...
Hey, we were going to ...
We were going to leave,
so you should ...
It is okay.
All is not worth to leave.
Stay and enjoy the weekend.
It is reportedly pretty.
I do not want to talk about it.
- It is easier if we leave.
- Are not you going to even try?
I tried already. I have tried 15 ...
Hey. Do you really
to leave so soon?
So.
We got tickets to tonight's
Don Giovanni presentation.
It is reportedly awesome.
I just found ... I mean canoes kayaks.
He said that you kajakkimestari.
Is that what he said?
He loves it
and talks about it constantly.
I hear you're the only one who knows how to
alaskankääryleen to do?
- It's sushi.
- Eskimo rolls.
I do not know. It has been a while.
Maybe you could get help.
I've never tried it,
and you are the champion ...
It would be nice to see a master at work.
So.
- You could keep the lesson.
- Yes.
I'm not a teacher.
And I did not bring a bathing suit.
The basics only.
We can change plans.
I think that...
We could call,
but tickets can hardly be replaced.
You should paddle steady tahtiin-
- So that the boat is not
accidental keikahda.
Like this?
Just like that.
How do I stop this?
Oh God.
It is not a vehicle.
It is not water brakes.
Excuse me.
Seth was a pretty good kid.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
He knew very creative
over rocks and rapids.
Can you teach a translation?
- You would under water.
- So what?
You kastuisit.
I never learned them properly.
I will do the translation.
Is it dangerous, Gil?
Probably. Hold your breath.
Gil! Please help him.
- Pretty good old pierulta.
- It was awesome.
Hey, race.
- I can not believe you were gonna say.
- Hey, race.
- What does it mean?
- Nothing.
- You have to make one.
- I could not even if I wanted to.
- You know how you do.
- I do not.
Kajakkini only be satisfied out of the water.
- Now make one.
- I can not.
- Do it!
- Come on.
- Hey!
Excuse me.
- That's enough. You will end up in the water.
- You go first!
- Come here.
- No no!
Oh God.
Seth, do it in translation.
Where are you?
Make a translation!
Seth!
Oh God.
Seth.
Even ...
That was not nice.
You think this is funny?
- Is.
- Fine true?
- Hey, come on. In peace now.
- What do you in peace?
- I'm serious.
- Fine true?
Gil.
Seth, get her!
No. Do not, Seth. Please.
Your turn. Sorry.
- Do not do it.
- I am sorry.
Do not do it.
The water is dirty. Please, do not.
My hair! You can not know...
Oh God...
No worries.
- This is not funny.
- Come on.
- Here is shallow.
- Click here to get out.
This is good.
Forgive me.
This will reach the bottom.
Try yllätkö.
- Yllän.
- Good. Now.
- All right.
- It was not fun.
Huhuu!
Deuce.
Should we apply for boats?
You seemed to be having fun.
I do not mean to be rude.
This is just not a good time.
Excuse me.
Can we go to the boat, Mom?
Asked about the point.
- Is that muusikkopoikasi?
- Is.
I thought that Vicky phoned.
We got the message, when we were already here.
We thought to give the children to stretch your legs.
I am sorry.
Today is not a good day.
- I thought that Vicky declared unto you.
- No worries.
I do not want to interrupt perhehetkeänne.
I do understand.
At any other time.
- Alright.
- Sorry extra effort.
Mother, I want the boat.
Soon you boat
the option for a weekend.
- Who wants ice cream?
- I will.
- Ice cream?
- I will!
I.
Do not blame me,
that they ignored my inquiry.
It does not have to be the message.
You had to talk to them.
The memories come to mind.
I'm going for a walk.
Hello.
Hey.
You will not eat anything unhealthy,
but smoke.
Well...
Al, it is not the cigarette.
Not really.
What?
Sorry, I did not like ...
- I can stub out it.
- I'm not a cop.
You sure?
Do you want?
Do you offer me marijuana?
I think I'll offer.
After all, lawyers do drug testing?
Probably should do.
- If you want...
- No thanks.
I have not smoked weed in 35 years.
I'm sorry to hear that. What a pity.
Well why not.
Did you get tickets for tonight's canceled?
Yes.
We called and we agreed on a new era.
I felt like a savage,
so I took Don Giovanni clear.
It ended last week.
- Hey.
What hommailet?
I fixed the rotten spool.
I thought to go up to take a look.
We built that?
One hundred years ago,
together with my father and my sister.
Do you want to go see?
Ylöskö over there?
Here is raging in at least 30 storm.
It took them, and take us also.
Little comfort.
Go first.
I will make sure not to fall.
I grew up in the city.
Play in the streets.
- Alright.
- This is not...
lhan how you want.
Wait. Is it a supermaket?
It was when I was 12 years old.
It's so beautiful.
It should be finer.
I wanted to try to copy
part of Prospect Park.
One landscape architect,
who works ...
Prospect Park?
Clinton used her
Chappaquan site at.
He pay for the property,
and not listen to a word.
Did not work in your yard short form
of the local schoolchildren?
I just thought ...
I do not remember olleeni
In such a cloud.
What kind?
All kinds of things are going on.
So much is happening.
I remembered it to be relaxed.
You seem relaxed.
But everything is so intense.
It is as if I could see the trees leaf
moving one by one. See now.
I wonder how many magazine
in that tree is?
I do not know.
Forty thousand.
One hundred thousand magazines.
- Is it the final answer?
- As long as I guessed.
You're a very punctual.
Right scientist.
I can not believe-
- That you own all of this.
So.
All of this. It is...
- Have you been here before?
- I do not.
Never.
This is a big deal for him.
That he brought me here.
For him, this is the place,
where she got to be with you.
Hardly.
When we were here, he usually
hid in my tree house.
I got the only lake in the dirt
purified iholtani.
I do not think it will harm,
we did not have pants?
- What?
- When we were walking through the bushes.
I do not understand what you fear.
Ticks, Lyme disease, bedbugs.
Should you lie,
if I ask the people that came here?
I...
Does the house have already been sold,
or is he still hierooko shops?
I thought your father would have told.
He gets what he wants to do at their house.
- I start to feel hungry.
- It happens.
Did you get enough
nuts and berries for breakfast?
Did you eat chestnuts?
- You know, from that good ...
- Bambuversoja?
Tonight, you get to enjoy
vegaaniaterian delicious.
Not now, after all riehaannuta.
It must be made,
because you are so prejudiced.
Do we eat twigs?
- We do not. You may even ...
- Speech of Peru.
You may take vegan,
when the master chef has done its job.
Mestarikokkiko?
I saw you on TV. You were excellent.
I do not Seth.
Seth?
Does he not put you food?
Sethkö putting me food?
No. How come?
He is like
personal huippukokkini.
Hard to believe.
His mother does not know how to cook eggs.
No, Teresa knows how to put good food.
You know Teresa?
I know.
In other words...
We have met a couple of times.
- Incinerated bring out?
- Place it on fire.
Why stop?
Where he learned to cook?
In restaurants, where he was working.
Right.
I knew that he was a waiter,
but the chef?
That I do not know,
but he worked in the kitchens.
Fine restaurants,
such as Mercer.
- Then there was the Eleven Madison.
- Eleven Madison?
We went there often.
I took Vicky Eleven Madison.
- It's a great place.
- He spent there?
No, he hated it. He...
Fortunately, he is no longer
need to do them a job.
He never ...
Is not he ever mention me?
He is afraid,
what do you think about me.
How long have you been together?
Maybe two years.
Where do you live?
- You're asking we live together?
- Do you live in?
Do not you want to ask your father?
He says true things openly.
Can you stop?
- Why? It bothering you?
- Downright uncomfortable.
Apparently, it is your intention.
I am now out enough to upset.
I'm sorry I almost
you cut off earlier.
It is okay.
Thank you.
How do you remove the planks felt?
Sometimes you sound like a shrink.
How does it feel, when I sound like?
Are you really a shrink?
Oh God.
Manhattan: lawyer and a psychiatrist.
Brooklyn: Lord Musician. and Andie
I guess there is a non-commercial organization.
He told you.
- Not been told.
- Do not you really know?
- I do not.
- No way in hell.
Are all predictable?
I spent the whole time here yön-
- In the middle of February.
It was really cold.
- Why did you do that?
- I do not know.
Dad yelled at me or something.
Bedtime My time After-
- I slipped in here and waited.
What happened?
Nothing.
I got a terrible rhinitis.
I was absent from school for two weeks.
The father did not even mention the issue.
She barely even knew,
that you were here.
Hey.
Where are you going?
This is good.
I do not want to waste it.
No thanks.
You do not know what you're missing.
- But she ...
- He refused.
He was 7-vuotias-
- And refused to go into the pond
without a cowboy hat.
Otherwise, he was completely naked.
Cute. Oh, man.
They are coming. Take it easy.
- Hey.
Hello, cowboy.
What's so funny?
We just ...
Gil, do you smoke weed you?
Well look at something.
- Take you too. Will he?
- Of course.
Not for me, thank you.
Excuse me.
Come here.
Is it siirappihana?
Is. On its inside.
- Hey.
- Wait.
Do not mess it up everywhere.
Did I should not smoke weed
in my own house?
Geez.
He is otherwise comfortable.
Really nice.
- Who?
- Andie.
So it is.
That cheese is really good.
Hard sheep's milk cheese from Holland.
It is so expensive,
the lobster is cheaper.
Excuse me. I take the rest back.
No, no, please not.
Then we set out to juustonsyöjäksi, huh?
Clear.
Damn.
Every time.
You do this every time.
Every single time.
I have not touched it in 15 years.
Whatever.
Teen about every single time.
Damn.
- Leave it alone.
- It's ready.
What kind of real estate market
here is?
What?
How to store it here?
I do not use the house ever again.
Its maintenance cost a fortune.
Mere taxes are property.
I was going to tell you.
You there!
What are you doing here in bed?
It does not seem to do anything.
Something strange is going on.
There were just four beds.
- Come on ...
- Them not get bored ever.
It is in good condition. See what you want.
Where did you find it?
It was lying in the corners.
I invited him to burn with me.
He caught me.
Feel free to do what you want.
We had really nice.
Everything was fine,
until you came and ...
Excuse me,
that I interrupted you and your father's joy grip.
Shove it.
I do not understand,
why are you so dramatic.
You got it nice scratch.
Listen...
I do not know how lucky you are,
that you got to be here.
Your father brought you here to a minimum.
Most people
do not get to experience that.
As a small saw such places
only elokuvissa-
- When on rare occasions
torsas money.
I know I know.
A poor childhood made you ärhäkän.
No, I was taught to be
paapomatta people-
- Which behaved
like spoiled brats.
Excuse me. I just do not
seen you like this before.
all families
are not as close as you.
I am a weekend here
you and your family.
What are you doing?
Do you care about me any?
My mother and I have all the ...
more sense than you.
Did anything happen?
He does not improve.
It just is so.
I know.
Excuse me.
My brother takes care of everything,
and I just ...
I was thinking to go back.
Of course, you go.
Is work hard to get a vacation?
Do they not gonna admit it?
No, I was thinking to move back.
So you change out.
I do not know. Perhaps.
Look at me.
I'm not going to leave you.
I mean only,
that I might leave.
You can get involved.
We could buy a big house halvalla-
- Or stay in my brother's house.
His dreams would come true.
He should be you,
if you got to know you better.
I just started
with Pete's new album.
I know.
I can not smoke weed in my own house.
You and Vicky therefore sell the place.
What do you do on weekends?
I do not know.
But Vicky is sure to come up with,
how the money gets wasted.
We rent the place.
Private beach would be nice.
If you can afford it.
You'd be welcome to the village.
Is this permanent?
Is there anything permanent?
Vicky!
Vick!
So?
Where is the shampoo?
In front of you on the left.
I do not see it.
Nothing. I found it.
I like Andiesta.
He's a good catch, right?
Yup.
How are you?
Are you still completely in the cloud?
What?
What did you say?
Seth had earlier upset.
You know Seth.
He is like that.
You think you do not have
nothing to do with it.
Why am I suddenly questioned?
- It is not related to us.
- It is specific to us.
Have you heard of respect?
- Just like that song?
- There is now serious.
You even told the sale of the house.
- I was going to do it gradually.
- Look, Gil.
I'm too old for this.
Are we a family or not?
I do not understand where this is going.
We stayed here because you wanted to stay.
I did not realize,
you'd be so defaulting.
- The 'missing?
- Yes.
I see. He is a little boy,
and I'm defaulting father.
I do understand.
It's no wonder,
that you're on his side.
- Which side?
- "Which side?"
No more questions.
You are right.
I'm going to sit here
and allows you to transfer the responsibility to ...
... All the other buck.
- Stop the analysis.
He is not 12 years old.
We're both adults.
You're the father.
Behave accordingly.
I signed up to the doctor.
What?
When?
Why did you do it without telling me?
I'm telling you now.
You decided the matter on their own.
Somebody had to.
Does this speak now?
All this in the middle?
There is no time.
Time's up.
To tell the truth I do not know,
I can take care of one another.
We take care of all together.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
As you take care of me in the kayak?
Or so as to take care of Seth,
when he was a small tree house?
- Seth and tree house ...
- He almost got pneumonia.
Did he tell the story
a tree house, and rhinitis?
It is a classic story,
and you believed it.
I want to do it with you.
I know you want the same thing.
What worries you?
- I do not want that it happens that way.
- How?
Like you and Sethille.
In this respect, can not be
later change their minds.
My mind does not change.
- Are you sure?
- I am.
As a child, he sat kivellä-
- Practicing for hours.
If he thought he was someone kuuntelevan-
- As soon as he stopped and waited,
until I left.
I do not want disturbed family.
Me neither.
- Are examined for ticks yourself?
- Berths?
- I do not inspected.
- You do not like that.
- Maybe I should check you in.
- Yes.
I know what you're going to start.
In.
The next train leaves
30 minutes to get to.
Good. Thanks for the information.
Are you okay?
I am.
There is nothing to this.
Everything happens at the same time.
It seems that I step on everyone's toes.
I'm supposed to leave today.
I said Gilille fully samaa-
- About a quarter of an hour ago.
Geniuses think the same.
Hey.
- Vicky?
- Yes.
- Have you seen laturiani?
- That's it, you left it.
There you are.
Have you seen laturiani?
- Did you transfer it?
- I do not.
- Then that's it, where you left it.
- It's not there.
- I moved it.
- Alright.
I found this. It is not Vicky,
so it is probably you.
Thank you. I'm looking for it.
- Search your charger.
- I did not touch it.
What's this?
This way when you hid it.
You know what it is.
Tell me.
Did you go back to
necklace circulation 7th Avenue?
It's plain silver.
It is looked at.
You brought me here because of it.
- It does not matter anymore.
- Of course it is.
- I can restore it.
- No, you can not.
- Why not?
- As engraved on it ...
... A funny, poetic message.
How do you know?
That's what you do with it.
I want ... Can I see it?
Only if you want to buy it.
I do not know.
Then do not.
I do not even know what this means.
If you want to ride,
we should go.
I think I'll stay after all.
Good.
Did you think I really
leave you to single-
- So that you could mill around in self-pity
and blame me?
Before long, it happens.
That I can not say anything.
But this will not happen today.
I do not understand why we do this.
They are guaranteed to like it.
- Damn it.
- What?
- I got a wound. The knife is really sharp.
- Are you okay?
Yes. Can you survive on your own for a moment?
I'll handle this.
- How serious is it? Show.
- I'll just clean it mass.
- Gil, are you there?
- I am.
What now?
Sorry to interrupt.
- I cut my finger off.
- What?
- I ...
- Are you okay?
- Clean it up?
- I make it a point.
The kitchen is a critical step on,
I do not feel no good.
Could you please come and help her?
- What?
- Yes.
Vegan Foods What do I know?
Do not worry. He will tell you what to do.
Andie said that you need help.
Where is he?
He received a wound
and sent me to fill in for.
Alright.
Can you look at that grill is on?
- You got it, sir.
- Thank you.
Andie?
Damn.
Huusitko something?
I do not.
- Everything is ready.
- Thank you.
What do these have to do?
They must be cut longitudinally,
no slices.
Good.
What is on the menu?
A couple of different stories.
This is an Indian lentil dalia,
plus...
That is what is on the menu?
That's the lentils and tomatoes.
There are also other vegetables,
and you will help tekemään-
- Ratatouille spiritual vegetarian food.
Is that what I put?
You just grilling the vegetables,
to be added to myöhemmin-
- But they have a better grilling first.
Did you learn all this in restaurants?
I learned.
- Did you like it?
- I hated it. It was horrible.
I can imagine.
Fortunately, you do not need
do it anymore.
I will do.
I'll sometimes shifts,
while doing rigorous.
Seth, this is very impressive.
- Gil agrees.
It is organic quinoa,
fried tofu, corn, coriander.
No animals or additives.
- It is one of Seth's nimikkoaterioista.
- I know.
I helped in cooking.
We increased the dose of your
extra butter.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Excuse me. I clean it.
I have a question.
What is the "race" mean?
Hoitte it in the past.
We were Housatonic River, is not it?
It is a fourth-class river.
- It was no more than second class.
- It was what was, it was big.
Seth made the turn,
and then I, and then the tail
- And then I will again.
At some point, Seth said:
"It's like translation contest."
Now, as they say
After each turn.
- "Race."
- It infuriated my sister.
- He was jealous of the boys.
- Here we go again.
It is interesting.
I read one artikkelin-
- In which evolutionary biologists
was the theory siitä-
- Why men tend to
prefer sports.
He says
Biology articles Maxim.
- But it is interesting.
- What's it say?
The article says that men and women
brains have evolved in different fashion--
- And that it stems from the
hunting-collector-time.
Men are much more
the status of realizing demanding toimista-
- Such as throwing a spear,
and now throwing the ball.
They had to assess the state of
and hit the target at the right moment.
Women, in turn, are able to
find tomato jääkaapista-
- Because we are collectors.
- Fully makes sense.
- Maybe our brains really ...
... Are different,
because all men are of the opinion.
No. Really, Seth?
Seth argues that women
do not know how to enter protected from the wind.
- What?
- I did not say anything.
- Gold ...
- Put it in song.
I saw you today.
Call your song new to them.
It's really good.
I have not even discussed it yet.
Now is a good opportunity.
If it suits you, maybe we can get
a private concert after food.
I do not know. I just have a guitar ...
I read the review The Voice.
- Oh, really?
- Your father showed it to me.
It was well written.
He was like,
testimony swanky little boy.
When I come tomorrow back-
- I'll take you there,
and we can choose for you a new one.
What you want.
Is that okay?
Time to go to bed.
I give the phone to your mother.
Good night, kid.
Hey honey.
No, no, no computer games.
You are dear. Go to sleep now.
Gil told me to open this.
Gil.
Why should I call him?
What are you doing?
I can put wood in order upon the fire.
Wait now.
Damn, I'm sorry.
- No worries.
- Are you okay?
Wait a minute. Where is your wound?
Maybe it's improved.
- I should not have brought you here.
- Bye.
How can I trust you?
You relied on before.
Seth, is there a concert?
Can you hold this? I go to the restroom.
Is everything okay?
Is.
Do you want some wine?
- No thanks.
- It has already been cleared.
There is really cold at night.
Fire is for it.
Can you increase the heat?
Come here.
This is hotter.
Is it better?
- Is it possible that the air is colder?
- Are you always this persnickety?
I do not.
I get upset so airy spaces.
City tricking people to believe,
that we are not alone.
We are not alone.
What do you want?
How come?
Will you let him fuck you,
so that he will help your child elätyksessä?
Hell.
- Do you drink?
- I hold it only.
Your breath smells of wine.
I can drink
if I want a glass of wine.
Hold this.
Old woman did not like the fact that I eat this.
It will be a spare tire.
So you eat in secret?
spoon by
you promise not to tell him.
- I will not tell.
- What is the password?
- Really?
- The password.
- Are you going to do?
- Password?
- Swordfish.
- Good man.
Do you remember that kulmapuodin,
the ice cream place?
I remember.
You will not find any kind of ice cream
throughout the rest of your life.
- I forgot insecticide.
- Here.
Try it. It is the Andes.
Oh God.
organic
garlic and black pepper?
Tehoaako it also vampire of?
I'll take the risk.
Guess that will help?
When standing next to the woman.
- What?
- I do not know why.
Their blood is different.
Women are like sticky flypaper.
- Have you noticed?
- Andie always complain itikanpuremista.
- I'll get bites just alone.
- Do you see?
Point it is a heterosexual
with respect to the only good thing.
I like the way a lot of Andiesta.
So do I.
Do you Vickystä?
I like.
But?
Nothing.
We are considering getting married.
Lhan true?
It is otherwise -97 Barolo.
How old is his son?
Eight.
Who is the father?
Not me.
Someone doctor. You do not know him.
- Do you like him?
- Lapsestako?
He is a nice boy.
Well...
...congratulations.
Where is he this weekend?
Jake has his father's house.
Lhan crazy. I mean, not ...
It's not crazy, but ...
I never would have guessed.
I was younger than you when I got him.
Would it be awful?
Is it weird if I ask,
what happened to the marriage?
No.
What happened,
what did not happen ...
Would you like a professional
or personal opinion?
Professional.
Alright.
Where to start?
Michael and I ...
We were so in love.
We thought we were strong
and we decided to have a baby.
Starting a family is amazing.
But to create space.
Space must be created literally.
Suddenly, in the same bed
sleeps a new little person.
- Like with a new lover.
- It sounds like Seth's dream.
It can be wonderful.
But with so many things will change.
It can not be predicted
before income children.
For example...
To each other is no longer possible
love just as much.
It is as if love be divided into sections.
We did not prepare for it.
I think that...
... We could not accept,
that part of our relationship died.
This was followed by grudges, and ...
Well, you realize yes.
- It is therefore a professional opinion.
- That's right.
What about a personal opinion?
He was the son of a bitch.
For real. One morning-
- He turned to the bed and said:
"I'm not ready for this."
- What?
- Yes.
We already have a son.
What should be prepared?
Excuse me. I did not mean...
You do not leave me.
Did you choose an older male
- Because he has already experienced
midlife crisis?
I think I'll be in his mid-life crisis.
Too late to regret.
I have not thought about it that way.
Exactly this...
Do you sell the house in order to
Vickystä care and child?
It's not that simple.
Do you go on holiday,
you pay for tennis lessons ...
You never redeem uploaded on checks.
I do not need your money.
Paid for their university.
Are you trying to make up for it now?
- Credit for what?
- The fate of the first family.
Why would you say about me?
What should I say?
You sound just like your mother.
I am sick to death
continuous criticism.
I just want to enjoy the rest of my life.
Why can not you be happy for me?
The family did not have any space.
with Vicky I am different.
I can relax and enjoy olostani.
He listens to me.
Between us has not had time to accumulate
mistakes and guilt.
Why this need to talk?
We had so nice.
We have never talked so much.
It's probably the reason.
You understand, then,
when you have children.
I understand what?
Everything can not speak.
If ever I could get lapsia-
- I would have done this winter
ice hockey rink.
It would have been a good idea.
You said that the place would always be here.
I know. It was a long time ago.
Things are changing.
I have to take other people into account.
Is there a different matter to say nothing,
because there is nothing to say ...
... And not to say anything ...
... Because there is too much to say?
Oh God.
- What now?
- What happened?
- He saw something.
- What did you see?
I do not know.
I only saw a little bit, but it was big.
- Where were you?
- He applied for a glass of water inside.
Talossako?
Did you see something for sure?
What's wrong with you?
We are in danger.
You said it was in the house.
What if it came out
or if there are more?
It's probably a raccoon.
Are you going to leave me here?
Come on.
- I hear something.
- They kusettavat us.
- And we do not bullshit!
- It's just a raccoon.
It's not a raccoon.
- Is not...
- Holy shit.
Great!
Oh God...
- It messes up the place.
- Gil, our house is a bear.
- What do we do now?
- We can not do anything.
- What?
- I do not know.
Do not discharge into the lamp.
Oh God.
It's probably afraid of us
more than we do it.
- It is not possible to.
- Where did it go?
Did it come out?
Gil, do not you have a gun?
I am a member of the Nature Conservation Agency.
- Can you call someone?
- My phone is inside.
- What do we do then?
- Be at peace!
Be pretty in peace.
Let's take a look at the other side.
No worries. Stay calm.
Come on.
Come now.
Are we trying to attach it to your attention?
- Calm down.
- Completely absurd.
What are you going to do?
It splashed on a wooden floor.
Is it oil?
It is organic,
cold pressed ...
- unprocessed
extra-virgin olive oil.
What the hell does that mean?
- The fact that it is environmentally friendly.
- The devil.
The floors must not go to pot.
- Come on, Gil.
- What?
- Concentrate.
To protect me and the baby.
It...
... Is still in its infancy.
I did not want to tell in this way.
- Are there any other children, of whom I do not know?
- Of course not.
We have not told anyone.
You can play thirties
as much as your soul to put up with.
To obtain
a new house, a wife and a son.
I can not get a new father.
Wish I could.
Guess how many times I
tried to call you?
How many Meilian I have left
sending, because you would be?
It did not happen only to you.
Do I have supposedly been easy?
What crap.
You've never tried to fix things.
What would be enough?
Nothing.
Nothing is ever enough for you.
We both did our choices.
You did not choose me,
and I am you.
Maybe it was a mistake, maybe not.
Shit,
I go out to scare the bear.
It is responsible,
when you're about to get a baby.
Do not berate the sense of responsibility.
- Because of you bear is in the house.
- How come?
Junk Box is not for it,
that you can throw debris on the ground.
- The same as if you called it.
- Debris were all over the place when we arrived.
- I cleaned them.
- And if it was the tooth fairy ...
... Who left the towels on the floor?
- What difference does it make?
The house has in any case been sold.
Why did not it would mess up?
Why do you care? You do not even go here.
You wait for me to die, so that perisit it.
I come here often.
In most cases, I make sure ...
... I did not crash into you.
- Come on be childish.
Do not interfere in the matter.
We do not need your help.
- That was a flow of 320 bucks.
- Gil.
- What?
- Do something.
If you're so damn baby
Worry, why do you drink wine?
- It is due to spill syrup.
- He spilled it.
- Whose side are you on?
- There's no sides.
- Stay out of it.
- Do not talk to him about.
- This is not his family.
- Now is.
- Be quiet!
- Enough already!
What are you doing here?
I look around.
It has survived pretty well.
Why did you come here this weekend?
I...
I wanted to talk Andielle
getting married.
Then I came to ...
... And ruined huvinne.
This time I can not blame you.
I see.
Yes, you probably ...
... You come up with something.
There is no reason to hurry.
You have time.
I wish someone would have told
it to me at your age.
It just goes on and on.
Be careful where you step.
Gil, thank you for this.
It was nice to meet you.
- Similarly you.
- Thank you.
Seth, it was nice to finally meet you.
- Yes.
- And spend time together.
So was.
Well.
Here.
Take the gas money.
I do not need money.
I'll give you gas money.
I do not need that.
I know, but I will give it to you.
Thank you.