[JET ENGINE]
TANGO FLIGHT, THIS IS
RINGLEADER. CHECK IN.
DRAGONFLY TO RINGLEADER,
CHECK. -COUGAR, CHECK.
BULLDOG, CHECK.
I'M READY TO PLAY.
THE CAPTAIN HAS TURNED ON
THE "NO SMOKING" SIGN.
PLEASE RETURN YOUR TRAY TABLES
TO THEIR FULL UPRIGHT POSITION.
WE ARE APPROACHING
CHECKPOINT ZULU.
BANDIT INBOUND, 600 KNOTS.
DRAGONFLY, TAKE 'EM OUT.
-ROGER, SIR. I'M ON MY WAY.
BANDIT CLOSING. SET TO
ENGAGE. -ROGER. SEARCHING.
HE'S ON MY
TAIL... 6 O'CLOCK.
POWER UP. POWER UP.
HE'S ENGAGING ME.
BREAKING LEFT--
HE'S STILL ON ME.
COME ON. COME ON!
DRAGONFLY,
HE'S GOT YOU TARGETED.
GET OUT OF THERE!
SON OF A BITCH,
HE'S ALL OVER ME!
[BEEPING]
HE'S GOT LOCK. HE'S
GOT LOCK! [BEEPING]
DAMN IT!
CONTROL, THIS IS BLACK
ANGEL. REQUEST CONFIRMED KILL.
Controller: AFFIRMATIVE, BLACK
ANGEL, YOUR KILL CONFIRMED.
ROGER.
MOVING TO ANGELS 10.
OK, DRAGONFLY, THAT'S IT.
PARTY'S OVER.
HOW'D I SCORE, SIR?
NOT PARTICULARLY WELL.
WE'LL GET YOU SOME MORE TIME
ON THE SIMULATORS.
CONTACT G.C.I. RETURN TO BASE.
BLACK ANGEL,
THIS IS RINGLEADER.
WHAT AM I GOING
TO DO WITH YOU, HUH?
YOU KEEP SHOOTING DOWN MY
BOYS. -THAT'S MY JOB, SIR.
YEAH, WELL, YOU'RE
TOO GOOD AT IT, EDDIE.
GIVE THEM SOME ROOM TO BREATHE.
DON'T POP THEM RIGHT AWAY.
THEY NEED THE TRAINING.
BLACK ANGEL COPIES.
OK, BULLDOG, YOUR TURN.
GET IN THERE AND MIX IT UP.
YOU GOT IT, COLONEL.
BLACK ANGEL, YOU FINALLY MET
YOUR MATCH TODAY, PAL.
YOU'RE DEAD MEAT.
YOU'RE LUCKY THIS AIN'T REAL
'CAUSE I GOT IT TODAY.
12 O'CLOCK?
WHAT IS THIS,
A GAME OF CHICKEN
OR SOMETHING?
EDDIE, BULLDOG,
WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
JESUS!
GODDAMN IT! GODDAMN IT!
YOU LUNATIC!
YOU'RE DEAD.
GENTLEMEN...
BASIC HEAD-TO-HEAD.
THIS MORNING UP THERE,
YOU GOT A TASTE
OF THE REAL THING.
NOW, I KNOW
IT'S SCARY AS HELL.
BUT BE GRATEFUL YOU GOT
A CHANCE TO EXPERIENCE IT.
BECAUSE AS BRILLIANTLY
AS I CAN TRAIN YOU,
I CANNOT TOTALLY PREPARE YOU
FOR THE UNEXPECTED,
EXCEPT TO WARN YOU
THE UNEXPECTED
WILL KILL YOU.
AH, CAPTAIN GORDON.
SIR, YOU WANTED
TO SEE ME?
LET'S BREAK FOR LUNCH.
WE'LL TAKE ANOTHER CRACK
AT THE SIMS AT 1400.
NEXT CHANCE IN THE AIR--
MODIFIED ZOOM MANEUVERS,
MONDAY AFTERNOON.
WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH YOU?
SIR?
COMING AT A ROOKIE
HEAD-ON--
YOU HAD THE POOR BASTARD
PISSIN' IN HIS PANTS.
SIR, I UTILIZED
ENEMY TACTICS
IN AN EFFORT
TO DESTROY MY OPPONENT.
THOSE ARE THE ORDERS
YOU GAVE ME, SIR.
BUT IT'S AN EXERCISE,
CAPTAIN.
I DO WHAT YOU
TRAINED ME TO DO.
I FIGHT TO WIN.
EDDIE, THIS IS
FIGHTER WEAPONS SCHOOL.
IT IS NOT
REAL AIR COMBAT.
YOU GOT TO PULL BACK.
THE KID WANTS TO FILE
A FORMAL COMPLAINT,
SAYS YOU
ALMOST KILLED HIM.
NOW, I KNOW
YOU'RE AN EXCELLENT PILOT.
JUST HOW CLOSE WERE YOU?
THERE WAS NO DANGER.
OK. I'LL TALK TO HIM.
BUT YOU BETTER BE
MORE CAREFUL.
WE'RE ALL ON
THE SAME SIDE HERE.
THEN, SIR, WHO'S THE ENEMY?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
NOTHING. SIR, I'LL BE
OFF THE BASE FOR A FEW DAYS.
GOT PLANS
FOR THE WEEKEND?
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
AH, HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
CAPTAIN.
UH, THANK YOU, SIR.
OH...
WELL, THAT'S
ONE HANDSOME SWEATER.
I HOPE IT FITS.
IT'S VERY NICE.
THANK YOU.
HERE YOU ARE, SON.
COOL.
IT'S TRUE WE HAVEN'T BEEN
HUNTING IN QUITE A WHILE,
YOU BEING SO BUSY.
MAYBE THIS SEASON.
THANKS, DAD.
IT'S REALLY GOOD.
THANKS.
Man on TV: I DON'T WANT
THAT DISEASE IN MY BLOOD.
I DON'T WANT IT IN MY MIND,
POLLUTING MY MIND,
MAKING ME DO THINGS
THAT ARE WRONG.
I NEED TO BE SET FREE.
I NEED TO BE DELIVERED.
I SAY TO THE LORD,
"LORD, BRING PEACE
INTO MY BODY.
BRING PEACE INTO EVERY CELL
OF MY BODY."
BUT SIN--SIN IS COMING.
THE PROPHETS TELL US.
[GUNSHOTS]
Father:
THERE YOU GO, ACE.
SO WHAT HAVE YOU
BEEN UP TO ALL DAY?
UH, NOTHING.
JUST DRIVING AROUND.
GET IN SOME SHOOTING?
YEAH.
HOW'S THE SCOPE?
IT'S GREAT.
UH, WE'LL BE HAVING
A BARBECUE LATER--
SAUSAGE, RIBS,
STUFF LIKE THAT.
TRUST YOU'LL DO THE HONORS.
NOBODY MAKES
A BETTER FIRE THAN YOU.
SURE.
[SCREEN DOOR OPENS]
YOU READY FOR THE MEAT?
ALMOST.
DID YOU INVITE ANYONE
FOR DINNER?
NOPE.
THERE'S JUST SO MUCH MEAT,
I THOUGHT...
MAYBE YOU MIGHT BE
SEEING SOMEBODY.
NO, I'M NOT.
THAT'S TOO BAD.
IT'S TRUE, YOUR CAREER
IS THE MOST IMPORTANT THING.
I GUESS YOU FIGURE THAT
AFTER ALL YOUR HARD WORK,
YOU DON'T WANT
TO GET TIED DOWN
AND TAKE ANY CHANCES.
WE'RE VERY PROUD OF YOU,
ESPECIALLY YOUR FATHER.
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH
HE WANTED TO BE A PILOT.
IT IT HADN'T BEEN
FOR HIS EYES--
I KNOW.
YOU DID ALL THE WORK
HERE, ACE.
AREN'T YOU GOING
TO EAT ANYTHING?
NO. I'M NOT
REALLY HUNGRY.
Mother:
YOU HAVEN'T EATEN
ANYTHING ALL DAY.
OF COURSE
YOU'RE HUNGRY.
Contestant:
12, JOHN--THOSE ARE
GOING TO BE MY NUMBERS.
Host: 7 AND 12
ARE A PERFECT PAIR.
ALL RIGHT!
SO GOING ON YOUR HOUSE
IS THIS BEAUTIFUL,
BEAUTIFUL FRONT DOOR
WITH THE STAINED GLASS.
NOW, DARLENE, IT'S YOUR TURN.
YOU'RE WELL ON THE WAY
TO BUILDING THAT DREAM
AUTOMOBILE OF YOURS.
PICK YOUR 2 NUMBERS.
Darlene:
UM, 11...AND 3.
11 AND 3--ARE THEY
A PERFECT PAIR?
YES! ALL RIGHT.
NOW YOU PUT 4 TIRES ON THAT
BEAUTIFUL CAR OF YOURS.
YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY.
REMEMBER, THE TRIP TO PARIS IS
WHAT YOU'RE ALL GOING FOR HERE.
JIM, IT'S UP TO YOU NOW.
Jim: OK.
YOU'RE BUILDING THAT BOAT,
THAT PLEASURE YACHT OF YOURS.
I WANT THAT BOAT.
PICK YOUR 2 NUMBERS.
JEEZ, LET'S GO
WITH NUMBER 2...
WHERE YOU GOING, DEAR?
...UH, NUMBER 6.
2 AND 6.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
Host: NO, I'M SORRY.
OH, YOU GOT A CLUNKER
THAT TIME.
2 AND 6 DIDN'T MAKE IT.
BUT YOU'RE STILL
WELL ON THE WAY.
ALL RIGHT, DAVID,
BACK TO YOU FOR 2 MORE NUMBERS.
David: OK, I KNOW THAT 8's
GOT TO BE ONE OF THEM.
I'LL GO WITH 13.
I'LL TRY 13.
8 AND 13. YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHOO-HOO! ALL RIGHT.
[GUNSHOT]
NOW, DARLENE, YOU'RE NEXT.
PICK YOUR NUMBERS.
PICK CAREFULLY.
Darlene:
UM...HOW ABOUT 7 AND 14.
7 AND 14. EVERYBODY'S CHOOSING
SCARY LUCKY NUMBERS HERE.
7, 13. 7 AND 14--
THOSE ARE YOUR CHOICES.
UH-HUH. YES.
IS THAT A PERFECT MATCH?
YES, IT IS!
ABSOLUTELY!
THAT PUTS A 6-CYLINDER ENGINE
RIGHT IN YOUR AUTOMOBILE.
ALL RIGHT. DAVID,
YOU'RE UP NEXT--2 NUMBERS.
[APPLAUSE]
David: WELL,
I'M GONNA GO WITH 2--
[CAR HORN HONKS]
Man: COME ON,
MOVE IT, DUMMY!
HELLO, CAPTAIN.
RESTFUL WEEKEND?
YES, SIR.
GOOD. BECAUSE I LIT A FIRE
UNDER MY BOYS.
THEY'RE GONNA BE
ALL OVER YOUR ASS TODAY.
YOU SURE YOU'RE UP
FOR THIS AFTERNOON'S FLIGHT?
YEAH, OF COURSE, SIR.
BECAUSE I CAN SUB JACKSON
IF YOU PREFER--
NO! UH, SIR, I'M
LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
GOOD.
IT'S JUST YOU'VE BEEN
A LITTLE, UM,
PREOCCUPIED LATELY.
IS EVERYTHING OK?
WELL, FRANKLY, SIR...
YOU KNOW, I DON'T LIKE
TO TALK ABOUT MYSELF...
AND MY PROBLEMS.
BUT YOU'VE KNOWN ME
A LONG TIME, RIGHT?
3...3 1/2 YEARS NOW.
SINCE YOU WERE MY STUDENT.
IT'S JUST THAT SOMETIMES
I WONDER ABOUT MYSELF.
I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING,
RIGHT?
I MEAN...
YOU THINK I'M DOING
THE RIGHT THING.
OF COURSE.
EDDIE,
YOU'RE ONE OF THE BEST.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S
ANY PILOT WHO WORKS HARDER.
MAYBE A LITTLE TOO HARD.
THE OTHERS
DON'T CARE FOR ME.
THEY NEVER HAVE.
YOU'RE NOT HERE TO BE LOVED.
YOU'RE HERE TO BE THE BEST.
THIS ISN'T
A POPULARITY CONTEST.
YOU'VE ALWAYS KEPT
AN EYE ON ME,
HAVEN'T YOU?
YEAH.
YOU'RE THE ONE TO WATCH.
I'M THE ONE?
HMM?
THANK YOU, SIR.
SEE YOU UP THERE.
GIVE 'EM HELL.
[CLEARS THROAT]
YES, SIR.
THINKING ABOUT
GROUNDING HIM?
NO. I THINK
HE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
IT'S YOUR CALL,
MATT.
LET ME SEE
HOW HE PERFORMS TODAY.
COME IN.
HI. CAPTAIN GORDON,
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
FINE, FINE.
UH, DID YOU HAVE
A GOOD WEEKEND?
WILD TIMES. READ A BOOK,
CLEANED THE KITCHEN.
HOW WAS YOURS?
FINE.
IT WAS FINE.
WE NEED A COUPLE
OF CHANGES MADE
TO THE FLIGHT MANIFEST
FOR THIS AFTERNOON.
COLONEL RYAN WANTS YOU
TO PLUG THEM INTO THE COMPUTER
AND SEND THE CHANGES
OVER TO MAINTENANCE.
"HOT MISSILES
AND EXPLOSIVE SHELLS"?
YEAH. WE'RE GONNA FLY
SOME TARGET RUNS
OVER THE GUNNERY RANGE.
WHY ARE WE ONLY
LOADING YOUR PLANE?
I GUESS SOMEBODY THINKS
I NEED THE PRACTICE.
AN ECM POD?
WHY DO YOU NEED
A RADAR JAMMER?
FOR REALISM.
WAIT A SECOND.
RYAN CAN'T WANT
IRON BOMBS.
HE MUST'VE MADE
A MISTAKE.
I'M GONNA CHECK
WITH HIM ON THIS.
DON'T.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR] BOBBY!
NOW CALL UP A B.D.U.
B.D.U.?
THAT'S A DUMMY BOMB.
YEAH, DO IT.
OK, NOW BRING UP
THE SERIAL NUMBERS
IN THE STORAGE
WEAPONS AREA.
NOW CHANGE
THE SERIAL NUMBER ON MY B.D.U.
TO AF-463908-SW.
CAPTAIN,
THAT'S A SPECIAL WEAPON.
OH, JEEZ.
I CAN'T DO THIS.
I MEAN, IT WON'T FLY.
I'M NOT AUTHORIZED.
I'M AUTHORIZING YOU.
I CAN'T LOAD
A TACTICAL NUKE
ON A TRAINING FLIGHT.
IT HAS TO GO
THROUGH S.A.C.
THAT'S NOT YOUR PROBLEM.
I CAN'T.
I WON'T.
YOU SHOOT, AND EVERYONE
WILL BE IN HERE.
ALL RIGHT.
OK.
[STRUGGLING]
[CRACK]
MELISSA?
HELLO?
LET'S GO. CHECK OUT
THAT HARNESS.
YOU GOT IT.
1521 COMIN' THROUGH.
MOVE IT, GUYS.
WE GOT A PROBLEM.
THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE
A MODE 2 DUMMY BOMB.
WELL, IT'S NOT.
WE'RE TALKIN'
SERIOUS PROBLEMS HERE, SIR.
THIS IS A MODE 1,
SW SERIES.
WE DON'T NORMALLY
MOUNT THESE ON MIRAGES.
THEY DON'T HAVE
THE PROPER RELEASE SYSTEM.
OK.
UM,
COULDN'T WE JUST FORGET
THE EXTRA PINS,
AND, UH,
MOUNT IT ON
A CONVENTIONAL BRACKET?
I GUESS I COULD.
IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU'RE GONNA DROP IT,
OR ANYTHING.
I MEAN, IT'S A DUMMY.
WHAT'S THE POINT?
YEAH.
YOU GOT ME, SERGEANT.
I, UH--
I'M JUST
FOLLOWIN' ORDERS
LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE.
I DON'T GET THIS.
THERE'S GOTTA BE A MISTAKE.
WHY DON'T WE PUT ON
A MODE 2?
NO,
UH,
NO, YOU BETTER STICK
TO THE MANIFEST.
UH,
INTELLIGENCE
HAD A HAND IN IT.
MILITARY INTELLIGENCE...
IT'S LIKE JUMBO SHRIMP,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
HEH.
HELL, THEY DON'T PAY ME
TO THINK.
COME ON! TAKE IT
TO THE HOOP!
NICE SHOT.
LET'S SEE THAT KIND
OF CONCENTRATION
IN THE AIR TODAY.
WE'RE GONNA KICK BUTT
TODAY, SIR.
I APPRECIATE YOUR
FIGHTING SPIRIT, LIEUTENANT,
ESPECIALLY CONSIDERING
YOUR DOGFIGHT SCORES
HAVE BEEN SO PATHETIC.
MAYBE THAT'S NOT
OUR FAULT, SIR.
OOH, IT'S
THE BLACK ANGEL.
YEAH, WELL,
CAPTAIN GORDON'S GOOD.
BUT SO ARE THE REST OF YOU,
OR YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE MADE IT THIS FAR.
THE DIFFERENCE IS,
WHEN HE'S UP THERE,
HE BELIEVES IT'S REAL.
THAT'S 'CAUSE HE'S A NUT.
YOU'RE OUTTA LINE.
GORDON DOES
WHAT YOU'VE ALL GOTTA DO,
TAKE THIS SERIOUSLY.
IT IS NOT A GAME.
YOU ARE EITHER
A FIGHTER PILOT,
OR YOU ARE A TARGET.
THE CHOICE IS YOURS.
NOW, I'M NOT HERE
JUST TO TEACH YOU
TO SCORE KILLS.
I AM TRYING TO TEACH YOU
HOW NOT TO DIE,
AND BELIEVE ME, GENTLEMEN,
UP THERE,
DYING IS EASY.
NOW HIT THE SHOWERS
AND SUIT UP.
[SIRENS
AND POLICE RADIOS]
YOU SAID
THERE'S AN OLDER SON.
MM-HMM.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHERE HE MIGHT BE?
BLACK ANGEL,
PREPARE TO LEAVE.
LAST CHANCE,
NUMBER ONE,
YOU'RE CLEARED
FOR TAKEOFF.
Gordon: UH, BLACK ANGEL
AFFIRMATIVE FOR TAKEOFF.
UH, ROGER, GROUND.
SWITCHING TO TOWER
AT THIS TIME.
BLACK ANGEL,
THIS IS RINGLEADER.
DO YOU READ, OVER?
THIS IS BLACK ANGEL.
I READ YOU, COLONEL,
LOUD AND CLEAR.
WE ARE ENTERING THE AREA
AT THIS TIME.
PREPARE FOR ENGAGEMENT.
ROGER.
BANDIT APPROACHING
AT ANGELS 2-2 AND CLIMBING.
BEARING 1-7-0.
RINGLEADER,
THIS IS DRAGONFLY.
I GOT A GOOD PAINT ON HIM.
READY TO BREAK
ON YOUR SIGNAL.
HOLD ON, DRAGONFLY.
COLONEL, THIS IS BULLDOG.
REQUEST PERMISSION
TO ENGAGE BANDIT.
DRAGONFLY'S UP FIRST.
LET ME TAKE HIM, SIR.
ALL RIGHT, BULLDOG.
PERMISSION GRANTED.
BUT REMEMBER, THIS ISN'T
A GRUDGE MATCH.
KEEP YOUR COOL.
YES, SIR.
JESUS, THAT'S HORRIBLE.
OF COURSE,
WE'LL INFORM HIM
RIGHT AWAY.
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
RIGHT. WE'LL SEND HIM
RIGHT OVER.
THANKS FOR CALLING,
DETECTIVE.
CAPTAIN GORDON'S FAMILY.
THEY'VE ALL BEEN MURDERED.
OH, MY GOD.
SHOULD I RECALL HIM?
NO.
NO, LET HIM FLY.
I'LL BREAK THE NEWS TO HIM
AFTER HE'S LANDED.
ALL RIGHT, GORDON,
YOU SON OF A BITCH,
YOU WANT HEAD-ON?
WE'LL PLAY IT YOUR WAY.
[BEEPING]
COME ON.
YES.
[BEEPING]
HA HA! ALL RIGHT!
I GOT YOU, BASTARD!
HE'S BEEN HIT! OH, MY GOD!
BULLDOG'S REALLY BEEN HIT!
BLACK ANGEL
IS OUT OF IT, COLONEL!
HE IS SHOOTING FOR REAL!
REPEAT,
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU TALKIN' ABOUT?
MAYDAY! MAYDAY! MAYDAY!
MAYDAY!
JESUS CHRIST!
WHAT DO WE DO?
DRAGONFLY, COUGAR,
RETURN TO BASE NOW.
BLACK ANGEL, COME IN.
COME IN, EDDIE.
DAMN IT, TALK TO ME!
DON'T JAM ME, EDDIE!
CONTROL, THIS IS RINGLEADER.
WE HAVE A PLANE DOWN.
ONE OF OUR PLANES IS DOWN.
WE HAVE A POSSIBLE
LOOSE CANNON SITUATION.
DO YOU READ?
A RENEGADE PILOT...
COLONEL,
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
WHERE THE HELL IS HE?
I GOT HIM!
COMIN' IN ON MY 6!
GET HIM OFF ME!
STEADY, DRAGONFLY,
LISTEN TO ME.
STEADY, DRAGONFLY, STEADY!
HE'S GOT TONE!
BREAK RIGHT! BREAK RIGHT!
I CAN'T SHAKE HIM.
AAH! HE'S FIRING!
GOD, NO!
RINGLEADER,
THIS IS COMMAND.
COME IN.
WHAT'S GOING ON
UP THERE?
I NEED TO SPEAK TO YOU
ON SECURE VOICE.
SWITCH TO WINCHESTER
BACKUP, OVER.
SWITCHING NOW.
WINCHESTER?
CONTROL, DO YOU READ?
AFFIRMATIVE, RINGLEADER.
SIR, WE HAVE A DEFINITE
LOOSE CANNON SITUATION.
BLACK ANGEL IS ARMED,
JAMMING RADAR,
2 PLANES DOWN.
WE'RE SITTING DUCKS
UP HERE.
NO WEAPONS AT ALL.
MATT, FOR GOD'S SAKES,
RETURN TO BASE
IMMEDIATELY.
THAT'S NOT ADVISABLE.
I THINK HE'S GOT BOMBS.
IS RED FLAG HOT?
I'M GONNA LEAD HIM
INTO THE S.A.M. RANGE.
THE RANGE IS HOT,
BUT THIS IS A NEGATIVE.
REPEAT, NEGATIVE.
ANY PLANES ON ALERT?
NO, SIR.
HOW LONG TO GENERATE
AN ARMED FLIGHT?
15 MINUTES, MINIMUM.
DO IT.
YES, SIR.
ALSO ALERT THE RED FLAG
S.A.M. INSTALLATIONS.
SIR, THE S.A.M.s COULD
TAKE OUT COLONEL RYAN
AS WELL.
I KNOW.
COLONEL, HE'S ON MY TAIL!
EDDIE, LISTEN TO ME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON
IN YOUR HEAD,
BUT I WANT YOU
TO RETURN TO BASE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
I WANT YOU TO BRING
YOUR PLANE DOWN NOW.
COLONEL, HE'S ON ME!
I CAN'T SHAKE HIM!
JESUS!
EDDIE, LISTEN TO ME.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE DOING.
BRING YOUR PLANE DOWN.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT.
FOR GOD'S SAKE, EDDIE,
WE'RE NOT THE ENEMY!
WE'RE ALL THE ENEMY.
JESUS, COLONEL,
HE'S GOT TONE!
BAIL, COUGAR, BAIL!
JESUS, GOD!
LORD,
HE GOT ANOTHER ONE.
HE'S IN RANGE
OF THE S.A.M.s NOW, SIR.
SO IS RYAN.
GORDON, 3 MEN ARE DEAD.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
WHY?!
I HAVE TO, SIR.
THIS IS WHAT IT'S ALL FOR.
THIS...
IS WHY WE'RE HERE.
I'M ON HIS TAIL.
I'M GONNA RUN HIM
INTO THE S.A.M.s
HA HA HA HA.
VERY GOOD, COLONEL.
YOU GOT ME.
I'M DEAD.
OK, I'M OVER
THE RANGE.
FIRE THE S.A.M.s.
"THE FOURTH ANGEL POURED OUT
HIS VIAL UPON THE SUN;
AND POWER WAS GIVEN UNTO HIM
TO SCORCH MEN WITH FIRE."
WHAT?
THE ANGEL, SIR.
I'M HIM.
I'M THE ONE.
SON OF A BITCH.
HE'S GOT HIM
IN S.A.M. RANGE
AGAIN, SIR.
ALL RIGHT.
TELL 'EM TO FIRE.
MATT,
HERE THEY COME.
RED FLAG NUMBER 3
AND NUMBER 5,
YOU HAVE CONSENT
TO FIRE.
BILL, HE'S TAKING OUT
THE S.A.M.s.
CHRIST, HE'S BEHIND ME!
I'M HIT! I'M HIT!
BILL,
HE'S COMIN' AT YOU!
HE'S FULLY LOADED!
I'M GOIN' DOWN!
I GOTTA BAIL OUT!
GOOD LUCK, MATT.
RECORD A FIX ON HIS
LAST POSITION.
CALL UP A
SEARCH-AND-RESCUE TEAM.
RYAN'S BAILING.
GORDON, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
YOU CRAZY SON OF A BITCH!
YOU HEAR ME?!
YOU'RE GONNA DIE!
SOMEHOW,
I SWEAR I'M GONNA KILL YOU!
CONDITION RED.
WE'RE EXPECTING
ATTACK AT ANY MOMENT.
WHAT ABOUT THOSE PLANES?
THEY'LL BE UP
IN 2 MINUTES, SIR.
NOT SOON ENOUGH.
[SIRENS]
CHRIST.
HE'S DROPPING HIS LOAD.
SCRAMBLE, BLUE ONE.
YOU'RE CLEARED FOR IMMEDIATE
TAKEOFF.
NEGATIVE, SIR.
HE JUST TOOK OUT
THE RUNWAY.
[PANTING]
COME ON,
WHERE ARE YOU,
YOU SON OF A BITCH?
HE'S STILL JAMMING US, SIR.
I CAN'T GET A DECENT FIX.
HE MAY BE GETTING AWAY.
DAMN IT!
CAPTAIN GORDON,
THIS IS BEDFORD CONTROL.
YOU ARE ORDERED TO LAND
YOUR PLANE IMMEDIATELY.
CAPTAIN GORDON, DO YOU COPY?
OHH.
Woman: HI.
Man, yawning: HI.
OH, HOW LONG
HAVE I BEEN ASLEEP?
OH, ABOUT AN HOUR.
WHEW.
[SIGHS]
OH, MY GOD,
RICHARD, LOOK.
[BABY CRIES]
WHERE'D IT GO?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT LOOKED LIKE
IT WAS TRYING TO LAND.
LET'S CHECK IT OUT.
VALERIE,
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
YEAH, I GUESS
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS WEIRD, THOUGH,
ISN'T IT?
MAYBE WE SHOULD
CALL THE COPS.
[BABY COOS]
UH, BREAKER 1-9,
BREAKER 1-9,
DOES ANYBODY
OUT THERE HEAR ME?
BREAKER 1-9,
PLEASE COME IN.
Woman on C.B.: THIS IS
GARRISON COUNTY
SHERIFF'S OFFICE.
UH, YES, UH
THIS IS VALERIE DWYER.
WE SAW SOMETHING
ON THE ROADWAY--OHH!
DON'T DO ANYTHING.
[BABY COOING]
[CRYING]
FREEZE! DROP IT!
HANDS IN THE AIR!
DROP THE GEAR,
PUT YOUR HANDS
IN THE AIR NOW!
DO IT!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
DOING, SOLIDER?
I'M LIEUTENANT COLONEL
MATTHEW RYAN.
SORRY, SIR.
THINGS ARE PRETTY
RAGGED AROUND HERE.
WE THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
BE THE OTHER ONE.
JEEZ, SIR, I THINK
WE OUGHT TO GET YOU
TO A HOSPITAL.
NO. TAKE ME
TO THE BASE.
SIR, I REALLY
THINK WE OUGHT TO--
THAT'S AN ORDER.
[ENGINE REVS]
[BABY CRIES]
YOU HAVE ANY TOOLS
IN THE VAN?
GET 'EM.
[CRYING]
HE'S HUNGRY.
I--I HAVE TO FEED HIM.
GO AHEAD.
HEY, IT'S OK.
SHH! DON'T WORRY. SHH.
I'D LIKE TO TAKE HIM
IN THE VAN.
NO.
OK. SHH.
SHH.
[HUMS]
PUT 'EM DOWN.
GOOD. THE KEYS.
GO, GO, GO, GO!
SIT DOWN.
OH, PLEASE, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO DO THAT.
WE'RE NOT GONNA
DO ANYTHING.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
JUST TELL US
WHAT YOU WANT.
I HAVE WORK TO DO.
BASED ON HIS
SCHEDULED FUEL LOAD,
HE COULD BE
ANYWHERE FROM
THE MEXICAN BORDER
TO OREGON, OR AS FAR
EAST AS COLORADO.
WHAT ABOUT SALT LAKE
CENTER'S RADAR OR L.A.'s?
NO, HE WAS
FLYING TOO LOW
AND HE WAS JAMMING
OUR G.C.I. SITES.
THEY NEVER GOT
A FIX ON HIM.
HOW ABOUT FIRST STRAT
WING AT BEAL?
THEY RELEASED
2 U-2s AND A TR-1,
SO WE'LL HAVE
PHOTO AND INFRARED
IMAGERY.
THE PROBLEM IS,
THEY'RE ASKING
TOO MANY QUESTIONS.
TAC WANTS TO KEEP
THIS IN THE FAMILY.
OH, CHRIST.
SCREW THE POLITICS, BILL.
THIS IS SERIOUS.
I KNOW.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHY
TAC WANTS TO KEEP
A LID ON THIS
INFORMATION.
THE LAST THING
WE NEED RIGHT NOW
IS A MEDIA LEAK.
NOW LANGLEY RELEASED
AWACS TO US,
SO IF THAT BASTARD
TAKES OFF AGAIN,
WE'LL CATCH HIM ON
THE AIRBORNE RADAR.
AS FAR AS LANDING,
WE KNOW HE COULD'VE
USED ANY LONG
STRETCH OF HIGHWAY,
A SALT FLAT,
OR DRY LAKE BED.
AT DAWN, WE'RE
GONNA CONCENTRATE
OUR SEARCH
IN THE DESERTS.
WE'RE GONNA MOVE
DOWN TO
THE AGRICULTURE
AREAS AND SO ON.
A 40-FOOT COMBAT JET
IS NOT THAT EASY
TO HIDE.
GORDON'S SMART. HE'S NOT
GONNA LEAVE HIS ASS EXPOSED.
WHAT KIND
OF AN ANIMAL
SLAUGHTERS HIS OWN
FAMILY LIKE THAT?
I DON'T KNOW, BILL.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO TELL YOU.
THE BASTARD
HAD ME FOOLED.
MATT.
THIS IS HARVEY GLATMAN
WITH JANAC.
HE JUST CAME IN
FROM LIVERMORE.
NOW FOR THE BAD NEWS.
WE THINK YOUR MAN'S
STOLEN A NUKE.
OHH.
CAME UP
ON THE COMPUTER.
HE MUST'VE SWAPPED
SERIAL NUMBERS
WITH ONE
OF YOUR TRAINING UNITS.
CLEVER. FORTUNATELY,
IT'S A COMPARATIVELY
SMALL ONE...
50 KILOTONS OR SO.
THERE REALLY ISN'T
ANYTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
HOW'S THAT?
IT CAN'T GO OFF.
LOOK.
THERE'S A CONVENTIONAL
EXPLOSIVE UP FRONT,
RADIOACTIVE FISSIONABLE
MATERIAL TOWARD THE OUTSIDE
AND THE PLUTONIUM CORE.
NOW ON A DEVICE
OF THIS TYPE,
THERE ARE 8 FAIL-SAFE
ARMING MECHANISMS.
THEY'RE DESIGNED
TO PREVENT UNAUTHORIZED
DETONATION.
THE ONLY WAY
TO TRIGGER THE WEAPON
IS TO ENTER
THE PROPER ARMING CODES,
AND I CAN ASSURE YOU,
YOUR MAN DOES NOT
HAVE ACCESS TO
THE ARMING CODES.
WHAT IF HE
DISMANTLES THE BOMB?
COULDN'T
HE RECONFIGURE
THE DETONATOR
AND DEFEAT
THE FAIL-SAFES?
MAYBE.
BUT THEN THE EXPLOSION
WOULD BE REDUCED
TO A FISSION BLAST,
AN A-BOMB.
LIKE HIROSHIMA.
UH, ABOUT THAT SIZE.
BUT HE'D ALSO
DESTROY THE FUSE.
THE CONVENTIONAL BLAST
CAN'T BE TRIGGERED
ONCE THE FAIL-SAFES
HAVE BEEN TAMPERED WITH.
IT'S A MOOT POINT.
OPENING THE BOMB
IS SUICIDE.
IF HE BREACHES
THE CONTAINMENT VESSEL,
HE'LL BE EXPOSED
TO MASSIVE DOSES
OF PLUTONIUM GAS.
RADIATION SICKNESS.
HOW LONG WOULD IT TAKE
TO KILL HIM?
DEPENDS UPON DURATION
AND PROXIMITY.
HE'D SUFFER
INTERNAL HEMORRHAGING,
MASSIVE TISSUE DAMAGE.
MY GUESS,
36 TO 48 HOURS.
WELL, THAT'S
PLENTY OF TIME.
BESIDES,
GORDON ISN'T
AFRAID OF DYING.
WELL, HE'S JUST
A PILOT, RIGHT?
HOW LIKELY IS HE
TO HAVE THIS KIND OF
TECHNICAL EXPERTISE?
VERY GODDAMN LIKELY.
YOU'RE
UNDERESTIMATING HIM.
DON'T YOU
UNDERSTAND?
THE SON OF A BITCH
IS ON A MISSION.
WHAT? BLACKMAIL?
NO, IT'S NOTHING
SANE LIKE THAT.
THIS ISN'T RATIONAL.
HE'S NOT GONNA
GIVE US A LIST
OF DEMANDS.
IN THE AIR...
I HEARD HIM PRAYING.
STUFF
FROM THE BIBLE.
I THINK HE'S DECIDED
HE'S SOME KIND OF
AVENGING ANGEL.
GOD HELP US.
[GAS ESCAPES]
UNH.
NO. NO.
IT'S OK.
NO, IT'S NOT.
UH, PLEASE...SIR.
THE WIRES,
THEY'RE CUTTING HIM.
CUT HIM LOOSE.
YOU CAN GO TO THE VAN
IF YOU WANT.
YOU CAN SLEEP THERE.
LEAVE THE BABY.
OH, NO. PLEASE.
I--I CAN'T.
SUIT YOURSELF.
[GAS ESCAPES]
[ELECTRONIC HUMMING]
BEDFORD CONTROL,
THIS IS ASPEN-1
NO SIGN OF TARGET ANGEL.
REQUEST UPDATE, OVER.
NEGATIVE, ASPEN-1.
NO SIGHTINGS.
WE'RE COMPILING DATA
FROM LOCAL POLICE
THROUGHOUT
THE TARGET ZONE.
MOVING TO GREAT HOTEL 6.
ASPEN-1 OUT.
[WHIMPERS]
GET UP.
WE'VE GOTTA FIND
A TOWN.
NOT HIM. JUST YOU
AND THE BABY.
UH, YESTERDAY,
RICHARD AND I
PASSED A TOWN
ABOUT 20 MILES
FROM HERE.
GARRISON, I THINK.
WE WERE ON OUR WAY
TO LAS VEGAS.
[BABY COOING]
THAT WON'T BE THERE
MUCH LONGER.
WHAT?
PULL OVER.
[VOMITING]
WHAT'S WRONG?
NOTHIN'.
YOU, UH...
KNOW HOW
TO HOLD A BABY.
YEAH, I HAD
A LITTLE BROTHER.
YEAH?
THIS IS A MISTAKE.
WHAT?
MAKING A BABY.
MAKING MORE OF US.
IT'S WRONG.
HE'S SO CLEAN.
YES.
HE IS.
IT WON'T LAST.
HE'LL BE POISONED.
WELL...
WE, UH, TALKED
A LOT ABOUT THAT.
BRINGING A BABY
INTO A WORLD
THAT'S FALLING APART
LIKE THIS.
YEAH, BUT YOU
DID IT ANYWAY.
GO ON, KEEP DRIVING.
[WHISPERING]
Wait at the counter.
Don't talk
to anyone.
[CASH REGISTER BEEPING]
UM, DO YOU TAKE
TRAVELER'S CHECKS?
YEP.
AND PUT YOUR
DRIVER'S LICENSE NUMBER
ON THE BACK.
[COUGHING]
YOU'RE SICK.
YOU NEED
SOME MEDICINE.
WE PASSED A PHARMACY
BACK THERE.
I'M FINE. I NEED
TO GET BACK TO WORK.
WHAT IS IT
THAT'S WRONG
WITH YOUR PLANE?
NOTHING.
MY PLANE IS FINE.
WELL, THEN WHAT ARE
YOU WORKING ON?
FOR CHRIST'S SAKE,
SHUT UP!
PLEASE--
[BABY CRYING]
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I NEED SOMETHING.
TURN AROUND.
[CASH REGISTER BEEPING]
UM, TRAVELER'S
CHECKS OK?
Pharmacist: UH-HUH.
THERE YOU GO.
30, 40, AND 50.
LET'S GO.
THANK YOU.
WHAT DID
HE DO TO YOU?
[BABY WHIMPERS]
NOTHING.
IT'S OK.
WHO THE HELL
ARE YOU?!
RICHARD, DON'T.
HOW LONG IS THIS
GONNA GO ON?
TILL IT'S OVER.
TILL IT ALL STOPS.
TILL I MAKE IT STOP.
OH, FOR GOD'S SAKE,
WHY DON'T YOU
JUST LET US GO?
WE WON'T
TELL ANYBODY
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
I'M BRINGING 'EM
THE LIGHT.
THE LIGHT OF HEAVEN.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
BRINGING
WHO THE LIGHT?
THE DISEASED.
THE UNCLEAN.
THE CORRUPT.
THE LIARS.
ALL THE DIRTY
SONS OF BITCHES.
[BOMB BEEPS]
JESUS, I KNOW WHAT THAT IS.
MASSACHUSETTS
LICENSE PLATE.
[GUNSHOT]
[GUNSHOTS]
[BABY CRYING]
GO, GO!
[GUNFIRE]
[GUNSHOT]
AAH!
RICHARD!
[GUNSHOT]
OH, GOD.
Valerie: UHH!
[BABY CRYING]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
NOTHING
FROM THE AWACS.
THAT MEANS HE'S
STILL ON THE GROUND.
THESE ARE NEW.
THE ONE IN COLORADO
IS A FALSE ALARM.
IT WAS A FOILED ROBBERY.
THE GUY JUST HAPPENED
TO LOOK LIKE GORDON.
SACRAMENTO, THAT'S
A CRASHED HANG-GLIDER.
HOW ABOUT THIS ONE?
THAT'S AN ABORTED
C.B. COMMUNICATION
OF SOME KIND.
SOMETHING
ABOUT A LANDING.
PROBABLY A UFO NUT.
WAIT A SECOND.
THIS SAME AREA REPORTED
A HOSTAGE SITUATION.
ANY RESOLUTION?
LOCAL COPS INVESTIGATED,
BUT THEY HAVEN'T
REPORTED IN YET.
THAT'S THE BEST SHOT
WE'VE GOT SO FAR.
IT'S ONLY A COUPLE
OF HUNDRED MILES.
I WANT TO CHECK IT OUT.
MATT...
YOU'VE GOTTA TAKE
A COUPLE STEPS BACK
FROM THIS ONE.
LOOK, I KNOW
YOU FEEL RESPONSIBLE,
BUT YOU CAN'T
HANDLE IT ALL YOURSELF.
GORDON HAS
KILLED PEOPLE...
THAT I CARED ABOUT.
JESUS CHRIST, MATT.
HE BOMBED THE HELL
OUT OF MY GODDAMN AIR BASE.
DON'T YOU THINK
I WANT THE BASTARD'S ASS
AS MUCH AS YOU DO?
EMOTIONS ONLY MAKE
YOU SLOPPY, MATT.
NOW, THIS IS
A MILITARY OPERATION,
NOT A PERSONAL VENDETTA.
WILL THAT BE ALL?
YES.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
UHH.
OH.
[BABY CRIES]
IT'S OK.
[WIRES BUZZ]
[BOMB BEEPS]
[BEEPING]
[BABY CRYING]
[AIR HOSE HISSES]
[BUZZING]
[BABY CRYING]
UHH!
OH, GOD.
UHH! UHH!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Truck driver:
HEY, LADY!
YOU ALL RIGHT?
WE SHOULD MAKE GARRISON
IN ABOUT 10 MINUTES.
DID SHE SAY WHO DID IT?
MM-HMM.
RIGHT. WELL, UM--
THE SHERIFF'S
NOT AVAILABLE
AT THE MOMENT,
BUT WE'LL SEND
SOMEONE AROUND.
THANKS FOR CALLING.
SO?
THAT WAS THE HOSPITAL
IN MILFORD.
THEY GOT
A GUNSHOT VICTIM.
A WOMAN WITH A BABY.
ANYTHING ELSE?
APPARENTLY,
SHE'S BEEN BABBLING
ABOUT A BOMB
OR SOMETHING.
Nurse on P.A.:
DR. COLLINS TO O.R. STAT.
Valerie: JAMES.
WHERE'S JAMES?
YOUR BABY'S FINE.
WE'LL TAKE CARE
OF HIM UNTIL YOU'RE
OUT OF SURGERY.
NO. SOMEBODY'S GOT
TO STOP HIM.
HE HAS A BOMB.
I--I SAW IT.
IT'S OK.
I'M NOT CRAZY.
Doctor: CHECK THE I.V.
WAIT!
IS THAT VALERIE DWYER?
Nurse:
NO VISITORS NOW!
THE BOMB.
TELL ME ABOUT THE BOMB.
Nurse: WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
TALK TO ME!
SHE HAS TO SPEAK TO ME!
HE'S THE LIGHT.
HE--HE'S GONNA
DESTROY THEM.
THE PILOT,
EDDIE GORDON.
HER PULSE IS
DROPPING, DOCTOR.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE HE IS?
WE WERE ON OUR WAY
TO VEGAS.
EXCUSE ME!
IT'S NOT THERE ANYMORE.
HE'S DESTROYED THEM.
OK, JUST RELAX.
Ryan: CLOSE EVERY AIRPORT
WITHIN 200 MILES
OF LAS VEGAS.
GROUND ANYTHING
THAT FLIES.
THE ONLY THING
IN THE AIR SHOULD BE
THE 34th AND 421st
TAC SQUADRONS.
YOU CAN'T BE SURE
HE'S COMING TO VEGAS.
Ryan: ARE YOU WILLING
TO GAMBLE HE ISN'T?
MAKE THE CALL, BILL.
AND TELL THE 34th
I'LL BE DROPPING IN
TO HILL TO PICK UP
A PLANE.
I'M GONNA FLY LEAD.
Douglas: HE'S NOT
YOUR RESPONSIBILITY ANYMORE.
Ryan: NO, SIR,
HE IS MY RESPONSIBILITY.
AND I WANT HIM.
[PANEL BEEPS]
[TURBINE STARTS]
[BEEPS]
BEDFORD CONTROL,
THIS IS RINGLEADER.
I'M AIRBORNE.
COME IN, OVER.
ROGER, RINGLEADER.
THIS IS CONTROL.
LISTEN, YOU MAY NOT HAVE
TOO MUCH TO WORRY ABOUT.
OUR ADVISORS INSIST
THAT IF THE PACKAGE
HAS BEEN TAMPERED WITH,
IT WILL NOT DETONATE.
HE CAN DROP THE BOMB,
BUT WITHOUT A FUSE,
IT WILL NOT GO OFF.
WHAT IF HE'S NOT
GOING TO DROP IT?
WHAT IF HE'S THE FUSE?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
LET'S SAY
HE RIDES IT DOWN,
GOES KAMIKAZE,
BLOWS UP HIS PLANE.
A COUPLE OF HUNDRED POUNDS
OF JET FUEL
MAKES A HELL OF A LOT
OF FIREWORKS.
IS THAT POSSIBLE?
CAN HE USE THE PLANE
TO DETONATE THE BOMB?
I DON'T--
HE WOULD HAD TO HAVE DONE
EXTENSIVE REWORKING
OF THE BOMB CIRCUITRY.
IS IT POSSIBLE?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE.
RINGLEADER,
LISTEN TO ME.
YOU'VE GOT
TO KEEP HIM AWAY
FROM POPULATED
AREAS.
REPEAT, AWAY FROM
POPULATED AREAS.
GETTING SHOT DOWN
MAY BE EXACTLY
WHAT HE WANTS.
I COPY YOU, CONTROL.
PROCEEDING
TO RENDEZVOUS POINT.
TANGO UNIFORM.
Ryan: BLUE ZERO 4-FLIGHT,
THIS IS RINGLEADER.
WE ARE IN PURSUIT
OF AN F-21 MIRAGE,
AND HE IS HOSTILE.
HE WILL BE JAMMING
AND FLYING LOW
ON HIS APPROACH,
SO KEEP YOUR HEADS
OUT AND CLEAR.
ALL COMMERCIAL AIR TRAFFIC
IN THE AREA HAS
BEEN SUSPENDED.
WE ARE TO PURSUE
AND REPEL FROM THE CITY,
BUT NO SHOOTING.
I REPEAT--
DO NOT FIRE ON HIM.
RINGLEADER,
THIS IS FALCON ONE.
WE'VE BEEN GETTING A LOT
OF DOUBLE-TALK BACK AT BASE.
COULD YOU BE STRAIGHT
WITH US, SIR?
[SIGHS] ALL RIGHT.
WE ARE IN PURSUIT
OF A RENEGADE PILOT.
OUR BANDIT IS HOT.
SUSPECTED TARGET
IS LAS VEGAS.
WE'RE DEALING WITH
A REAL SITUATION HERE.
AFFIRMATIVE,
FALCON ONE.
[GEIGER COUNTERS CLICK]
CONTROL
TO RINGLEADER,
COME IN.
READ YOU, CONTROL.
HE WAS DEFINITELY
IN GARRISON, UTAH.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
PLUS AWACS
JUST PICKED UP
A NEW RADAR PAINT.
BANDIT
APPROACHING VEGAS
FROM THE NORTHEAST.
YOU PICKED IT,
RINGLEADER.
HE'S ALL YOURS.
RINGLEADER COPIES. OUT.
OK, GENTLEMEN,
THIS IS IT.
LET'S GO TACTICAL AND COVER
THE BRIEF PATROL POINTS.
REMEMBER, THIS IS
THE REAL THING.
GIVE IT ALL YOU'VE GOT.
[CAR HORN HONKS]
[RADAR BEEPS]
[BEEPS]
VISUAL CONTACT.
THIS IS FALCON ONE.
I HAVE VISUAL CONTACT
WITH AN UNKNOWN COWBOY
APPROACHING BELOW ME
FROM THE SOUTHEAST.
I AM DESCENDING
TO ANGELS 2,000
TO VERIFY.
RINGLEADER COPIES.
USE EXTREME CAUTION.
I'M ON MY WAY.
THIS IS FALCON ONE
TO UNIDENTIFIED AIRCRAFT
AT 2,000 FEET.
IDENTIFY YOURSELF.
THIS IS
RESTRICTED AIRSPACE.
IDENTIFY.
Falcon one:
MY ORDERS ARE
TO ESCORT YOU
OUT OF THE VICINITY.
PLEASE FLY
BEARING 2-3-5 DEGREES.
RINGLEADER,
HE'S ON MY 6!
GET OUT OF THERE!
HE'S ALL OVER ME!
BREAK HIGH!
LEAD HIM HARD LEFT!
HE'S GOT LOCK ON ME!
RINGLEADER!
FALCON ONE,
COME AROUND--
NO! NO!
Ryan: COMMAND,
THIS IS RINGLEADER.
FALCON ONE IS DOWN.
GORDON HAS BROKEN
OUR PERIMETER
EN ROUTE TO CITY.
NO ONE ELSE IN RANGE.
I AM IN PURSUIT.
CAN YOU STOP HIM, MATT?
Ryan: I DON'T KNOW.
RINGLEADER OUT.
BLACK ANGEL!
THIS IS RINGLEADER.
DO YOU COPY?
RING LEADER
TO BLACK ANGEL.
DAMN IT.
I KNOW YOU CAN
HEAR ME, EDDIE.
THIS IS COLONEL RYAN,
COME IN.
COME ON,
YOU CRAZY BASTARD.
WHAT'S HIS HEADING?
3-0-0.
Ryan: EDDIE,
THIS IS A MISTAKE.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONE.
Gordon:
THIS IS BLACK ANGEL.
FAILED TO COPY
LAST TRANSMISSION.
[RADIO BEEPS]
Gordon: PLEASE, REPEAT.
-I SAID YOU'RE NOT THE ONE.
YOU'RE NOT SPECIAL, EDDIE.
YOU HAVE NO MISSION.
YOU HAVE
TO LAND YOUR PLANE.
I'M THE ONE.
I HAVE THE POWER.
I HAVE TO USE IT.
THIS POWER HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
YOU. IT DOESN'T BELONG TO YOU.
IT DOESN'T BELONG TO ANY
OF US. IT BELONGS TO GOD.
I'M DOING HIS WORK.
-KILLING YOUR MOTHER?
YOUR FATHER? YOUR FAMILY? IS
THAT DOING GOD'S WORK, EDDIE?
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
EVERYTHING DOWN THERE
HAS TO BE DESTROYED.
WIPED CLEAN.
IT'S GOD'S MISSION. -NO,
EDDIE, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
GOD. IT'S YOU. YOU HAVE TO STOP.
Controller:
20 MILES TO CITY CENTER.
RINGLEADER, THIS IS
GENERAL LINDSAY
AT SAC HQ.
I AM AUTHORIZING YOU
TO DOWN THE TARGET.
YOU HAVE GO-AHEAD
TO FIRE.
YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
IF I HIT HIM NOW,
THE BLAST ALONE
COULD KILL
20,000-30,000 PEOPLE.
General Lindsay:
WE'RE PREPARED TO ACCEPT
CIVILIAN CASUALTIES.
IF WE WAIT ANY LONGER,
WE'LL LOSE THE WHOLE CITY.
WE'VE GOT NO CHOICE.
Controller:
BANDIT, 15 MILES.
EDDIE, I CAN
FIRE RIGHT NOW
AND END YOUR MISSION.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
I CAN KILL YOU RIGHT NOW.
WHY DON'T YOU?
I WANT TO GIVE YOU
A CHANCE TO PROVE YOURSELF.
MAYBE YOU REALLY ARE
THE ONE, EDDIE.
DOING GOD'S WORK.
SHOW ME, EDDIE.
SHOW ME YOU'VE
REALLY GOT THE POWER.
TAKE ME OUT.
General Lindsay:
DAMN IT, RINGLEADER!
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?!
Controller:
10 MILES.
I'M GIVING YOU THE CHANCE
TO PROVE YOURSELF, EDDIE.
YOU TAKE ME OUT,
WE'LL KNOW
YOU'RE REALLY THE ONE.
YOU FAIL,
WE'LL KNOW YOU'RE LYING.
YOU DO NOTHING,
AND I'LL SHOOT YOU
DOWN RIGHT HERE!
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
Controller:
4 MILES AND CLOSING.
I'M COMING AROUND
TO TAKE MY SHOT, EDDIE.
YOU WANT TO STOP ME,
THEN YOU COME AFTER ME.
Controller: 3 MILES.
Ryan: IT'S UP
TO YOU, EDDIE.
YOU PROVE IT
OR YOU DIE.
Controller: ONE MILE!
[RADAR BEEPS]
IT'S WORKING.
GORDON'S FOLLOWING HIM.
COME ON!
TAKE YOUR SHOT!
COMMAND, AM I OVER
THE BOMBING RANGE YET?
AFFIRMATIVE,
RINGLEADER.
KEEP THE OTHER PILOTS
OUT OF THE AREA.
RINGLEADER,
IS THERE ANY WAY
YOU CAN FORCE HIM
TO LAND?
NO.
I HAVE TO TAKE HIM OUT.
MATT...
THERE'S NO WAY
YOU CAN SURVIVE
IF THAT DAMN THING
GOES OFF.
RINGLEADER COPIES.
GODSPEED, MATT.
IT'S OVER, EDDIE.
NO.
GO TO HELL.
NO!
TV news anchor:
...YESTERDAY'S DETONATION
OF A TACTICAL NUCLEAR WEAPON
OVER THE NEVADA DESERT.
DESPITE REPEATED ASSURANCES
FROM THE PENTAGON
THAT THIS ATOMIC ACCIDENT
POSES NO DANGER TO LAS VEGAS
OR THE SURROUNDING
COMMUNITIES,
CONGRESSIONAL LEADERS ARE
DEMANDING AN INVESTIGATION
OF THE EFFECTS
OF THE RADIOACTIVE FALLOUT.
IN ADDITION TO THE 36
CONFIRMED FATALITIES,
THE PENTAGON
FOR THE FIRST TIME TODAY
ACKNOWLEDGED
2 MILITARY CASUALTIES,
A PAIR OF AIR FORCE PILOTS
FLYING OVER THE AREA
ON A ROUTINE MISSION.
THEY HAVE BEEN IDENTIFIED AS
COLONEL MATTHEW RYAN OF SEATTLE
AND CAPTAIN EDWARD GORDON
OF LAS VEGAS.
RYAN, A DISTINGUISHED
VETERAN PILOT,
WAS SENIOR FLIGHT INSTRUCTOR
AT THE U.S. AIR FORCE ACADEMY.
GORDON, A JUNIOR OFFICER
WITH THE ACADEMY,
WAS BELIEVED TO HAVE BEEN
ON A TRAINING EXERCISE
WHEN THIS ACCIDENT OCCURRED.
FUNERAL SERVICES FOR BOTH
WILL BE HELD
AT THE AIR FORCE CEMETERY
LATER ON THIS WEEK.
IN RELATED DEVELOPMENTS...
www.prijevodi-online.org