[man's voice]
Monday April 18, 2049, 7am.
Morning glorious!
May I be the first to tell you
how fully stellenarious
you look.
As usual.
Don't forget,
science test today.
Plus, if and when
the predicted Class Five
solar flare arrives,
you will for sure
want to check it out.
I know, I know.
This all seemed decidedly
more amusing last night.
Have you had a chance
to check this latest data?
The molecular changes
in Max's marrow...
We're closing in
on it, honey.
I really feel like all of our
hard work is about to pay off.
Why wasn't she in the
mess module for breakfast
this morning?
I don't know.
Are you sure she's
even awake yet?
Zenon?
Zenon, it's 7:45.
Cetus-Lupeedus,
how'd it get to be so late?
Get moving, please.
Your Dad and I have to
get to the lab. Come on.
Remember, you loathe
waking up this way.
Time Minor, Tasks Major.
Oh, shut up.
There's one thing to be
thankful for. At least you
don't live down there.
I'm going to be
in so much trouble.
Excuse me, coming through.
The kitchen,
Zenon, is closed.
No, wait! I didn't...
Wait, wait... No! Ow! Ow!
[computer voice] Decompression
drill at 1100 hours.
Overslept again, huh?
Thanks, Gemma.
You're a life saver.
Excuse me. Coming through.
Come on. Hurry.
No... Wait, wait, wait!
No, no, no, no!
Not good. This is not good.
Also the fusion trays
in the cafeteria
are misfiring.
Tell Andy in
engineering to use...
Oh! Morning glorious,
Commander Plank.
Walk, Zenon. Walk.
[voice on PA] Electrical
malfunction in
elevator number three.
Please use alternate routes.
[electrical zapping]
[voices overlapping]
[zapping]
[woman] This sound
is hurting my ears.
Yes!
[man] Hold it! Watch out!
[man 2] Zenon!
[girl] Late again, girl.
[boy] You're gonna
get busted.
[chattering continues]
Good morning, class.
Good morning, Mr. Perez.
As we were saying yesterday,
perhaps the most remarkable
thing about President Clinton
is that, unlike
her father, Bill,
who also held the office at
the close of the last century,
President Chelsea Clinton
has taken a forceful
and unwavering stand
in favor of the harvesting
of underwater vegetation
as a major source
of energy and food.
Ms. Clinton believes
our oceans are
the new frontier.
She has repeatedly
stated a firm...
[man's voice] ...one of the
hottest groups in rock,
Microbe,
and lead singer, Proto Zoa,
will become the first group
to perform live in space.
They are going to appear
on the WyndComm Space Station
next month.
[squeals]
Zenon Kar?
Is there something you wish
to share with the class? Hmm?
Uh... no, Mr. Perez.
I guess I got all
flared-up because...
I never knew history
could be so thrilling.
Ah! I'm glad
you're thrilled.
Yeah.
As I was saying,
Chelsea Clinton
has taken a...
When I tell you the
real reason I squeaked,
you're gonna go nova.
No, no, wait.
Super nova, guaranteed.
Oh, just tell me.
Microbe is coming here!
For the very first
rock concert in space.
[screaming]
What happened? What'd I miss?
Zenon says Microbe's coming
right to this very station.
Not a Giant Screen
performance, not a hologram.
They're appearing in their
heart-fluttering flesh.
I heard it on the CRR News!
[all screaming]
Zenon, please,
control yourself.
Control myself? Yes, sir,
Commander. Lieutenant Schiff.
Control myself.
Control myself?
When my all-time Crush Major
is coming to our humble halls?
[squealing quietly]
Let's spread the word!
[girls] Microbe's coming!
Microbe's coming!
Microbe? They're about
as thermo as some band
from back in 2025.
According to who, Aquila?
They happen to be
the greatest ever.
Their songs have melodies.
I mean, those guys are
so anti-matter
you can actually
understand their lyrics.
What'd you expect?
[both] Men!
Wait, wait. I still haven't
told you the best part.
They're having a contest.
The winner gets to dance
on stage with Proto Zoa!
Can you believe it?
I'm going to get
to dance with Proto Zoa!
Who said it's
gonna be you?
What is she,
new in the galaxy?
Ladies and gentlemen.
May I have your attention
for a moment.
Please? Thank you.
Now, as all of you
undoubtedly already know,
given that gossip travels
at the speed of light
here in space...
[laughter]
...Parker Wyndham, owner
and chief operating officer
of our parent company,
WyndComm,
will be paying our
space station
a visit on Friday.
[murmuring]
Shh, shh, shh...
Now, I don't think
I'm giving away any secrets
when I say this has not
been our finest year.
March we had
cooling system leaks,
May brought power blackouts.
And that
small, unfortunate
computer room fire.
Yes, that small fire.
Well, our space station
is 27 years old, people.
The fact is, it needs major
improvements and repairs.
And since many of you
are so close
to successfully
completing your most
prodigious experiments,
it would be a shame to have
Wyndham shut us down
at such a juncture.
Well, he'll never do that
because we won't
let him, right?
[cheering]
Yes, I know. I know we feel
that way, but our job is
to convince Wyndham.
We need to get him excited
about our research,
to show him things.
Like the fine work
on bone marrow density
being done by
Mark and Astrid Kar,
that could literally
save millions of lives.
Wyndham needs to understand
why so many of us
have devoted so much of our
lives to this place.
He needs to see that we are
a dedicated, hard-working,
cost-conscious asset
that he simply
cannot afford to abandon!
[cheering]
Now, I'm counting
on each and every one of you.
I know you will
make me proud.
[applause]
[computer voice]
Sterilizer activated.
[buzzing]
Sorry to barge, you guys,
but I'm in
Hysteria Mode Major.
What's gonna
happen to us if the
Wyndham beast rockets up
and hangs a condemned sign
on our space-stay?
Slow down, Zee.
Retro-fire.
But I've been here since
I was five, and I don't want
to live anyplace else.
No one is going
anywhere.
But Commander Plank said...
All we have to do is convince
Wyndham how valuable
our work is, so we will.
We couldn't do our experiments
anywhere but a space station.
Because you need a lab with
a weightless chamber. I know.
Hi, Cleo.
[Astrid] She actually listens
to us once in a while.
Wow.
So, Wyndham would have to be a
Scrooge Major to shut us down?
Oh, exactly.
I mean, once he is here,
we will blast him
into orbital bliss Major,
with all the great things
our scientists are doing.
If you're so concerned
about his visit, help out.
How?
Start by trying to keep
your gang in line while
Wyndham's aboard.
No air duct cruising,
no recycle bin diving,
and please, please,
try to stay out of
restricted zones.
OK.
Thank you.
You'd fully blow an O-ring
if we had to return to Earth,
huh, Mom?
Mom?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Absolutely.
Hey honey, um,
why don't you let us get back
to work, OK, sweetheart?
See you at dinner?
Love you.
Bye.
[rock music plays]
I think that if Microbe's
coming all the way from Earth,
somebody's getting
rich off of it.
So young and yet so cynical.
Everything down there
is motivated by money.
is motivated by self-defense.
You've gotta watch for germs,
speeding trucks, earthquakes,
madmen, muggers...
You were in kindergarten
when we came up here.
My mom's told me stories.
She was in that horrible
earthquake back in '35.
And once she got robbed
at gunpoint.
Why do you think her mom
was so anxious to
bring her up here?
Can I borrow this?
Yes.
Down on Earth, people with
runny noses are packed
together like microchips.
Yeah,
I've never even sneezed.
Plus, Earth's gravity
adds about 30 pounds to you.
Can you imagine playing?
The weather? One minute
you have rain, then snow.
Then a fully
anti-matter tornado.
How would you ever know
what to wear? This too?
Yes.
Face it, our lives are like
a day at the Jovian moon
compared to theirs.
Yeah, yeah.
But I still think...
Don't, OK?
That's when he ends up
in trouble.
We'll have to ice
while Wyndham's here.
It's only three or four days.
How hard can it possibly be?
For you? Impossible.
Lunarious bracelet, Neb.
Thanks. I found the disks in
a Satellite Lab recycling bin.
They have the best throwaways.
I decorated two whole t-shirts
with their discards.
I'll show you.
As fascinating as this is,
are we gonna do something
tonight or what?
Oh, it would be stellar
if we could catch
the Class Five Solar Flare
that's due.
That won't peak 'til 4:00
this morning.
What better way to enjoy it
with Adult Interference Minor?
I can't believe you guys
are chickening out on me.
If my dad found out
I swiped the code book
to get us down here,
he'll go into global meltdown.
Why?
Tell him we simply needed
to gain a deeper understanding
of our native environment.
Couldn't you be happy
watching the thing in here?
I mean,
we have a perfect view.
Why be in the audience, Neb,
when you have a chance
to be center stage?
Come on.
[hissing]
All right,
let's rock and roll! Whoo!
Now remember,
if you hear anybody coming,
tug on my tether.
Are you sure about this?
Trust me, Lynx,
it's the only way to fly!
Good to go!
I hope she knows
what she's doing.
[Nebula] Yeah. Me, too.
Whoa.
[squealing]
[gasping]
[groaning]
I don't understand
why I'm getting all the blame?
The other kids
were down there, too.
Excuse me, but were the
other kids out of the craft?
Lynx told her mother
the entire thing
was your idea.
Really nice!
Why would she go
and say that?
Oh, I don't know.
Probably because
everything always is.
Must make you proud to know
you're raising a leader, huh?
Stow the jokes, Zenon.
This is serious.
You guys are constantly
begging me to take
a greater interest in science.
Then tonight when
I finally do, everyone gets
all gaseous on me.
An unauthorized
middle-of-the-night space walk
is hardly what we had in mind.
Sweetheart, what if
your tether broke?
What if we got bombarded
by a sudden meteor shower?
I can handle myself. I'm 13.
Then you better
start acting like it.
You have to admit,
it was pretty stellar.
It was probably the best one
we will ever have
an opportunity to see.
Those colors were undulating.
It was almost
like a religious ex...
You were still very
wrong to go out in it.
That is exactly the kind
of thing that cannot happen
when Wyndham's here.
Are we clear?
Yes, ma'am.
It's tough, but if we
don't buckle down while
Wyndham's here,
he could have
our mission scrubbed.
Scrubbed, Zenon.
As in over for all of us.
Do you want to be a part
of causing that?
You know that
I would only say
this as a last resort,
but mess up again and
your father and I will be
forced to ground you.
[electronic beeping]
That is the third time this
month you have pushed her
into the Stress Helmet.
I know.
Behave before she ends up
in the Chill Chamber.
I know, you're right.
[both] But those colors
were stellar!
Want to see my entry
for the Microbe contest?
It's not finished or anything,
but what do you think?
[gasping]
I didn't know
you could do
a whole sculpture.
Man, I just did a dumb essay
about what dancing with Proto
Zoa would mean to me.
You're a lunarious
writer, Neb.
I'm sure it was
Impressive Major.
Mm-hmm.
You don't have any
stellar chain I could use
for his guitar, do you?
No. But tomorrow's
compactor day.
Right, right.
I'm sure the Discard Bin's
filled with all kinds of junk.
Let's go.
Can't. Math homework.
Oh, yeah.
Have you met
the Wyndham beast yet?
Not yet. But I heard
he got in a few hours ago.
And because life isn't hard
enough, Plank-the-Blank
plucked my parents
into being his tour guides.
Pressure Major or what?
[computer voice]
Artificial gravity
malfunction in level four.
malfunction...
And right down here you see
the biology lab and
the anti-gravity.
Mom, Dad!
I've been looking all over
for you guys.
Uh-huh.
Mr. Wyndham.
Hi, I'm Zenon.
I didn't mean to interrupt
your tour, but I've heard
so much about you.
I couldn't wait
to make your acquaintance.
It's a pleasure
to meet you.
This is my
assistant, Mr. Lutz.
Hi.
Oh, is that Proto Zoa I see?
Oh, yeah.
You know, I happen to be
quite a microscope fan myself.
I'm considering coming back up
for the concert next month.
You'll be attending?
Oh, wouldn't miss it for all
the stardust in the galaxy.
[all laughing]
Tell me, Zenon,
and tell me honestly,
how do you like living
up here in space?
Well, the life your
very generous support
has created for me
and my rads
is the most lunarious
and interesting way any kid
could hope to grow up.
The experiments,
the research we get to watch,
the amazing teamwork,
the unique view
of the universe...
Thank you, Mr. Wyndham.
Thank you.
Well, let me just say,
if you ever consider
a career in PR, my dear,
WyndComm Enterprises could
definitely use your services.
And how. Well...
Well, uh, math homework.
Sorry.
Uh, right down here
we have the cryogenics lab.
She's very verbal.
[Mark] Zenon's never short
on energy.
As soon as I told Mr. Wyndham
I loved TurboMaster movies,
he started quoting
all the dialogue,
doing all the voices.
It was hilarious.
You know, when he looked over
my mom's Reflex System data,
he actually understood it.
Not even my dad can do that.
[Zenon] Something about
that guy shivers me out.
What are you talking about?
I mean, he's a great guy.
Calling Planet Leo.
The only thing that should
be that smooth and oily
is a propulsion module
solar coil.
This is from the girl
that said I was cynical.
I wish I could
explain it more.
I just get the very creepy
feeling that something
doesn't quite fit.
Sorry, but every time
you get one of these feelings,
it always ends up
in Disaster Major.
[Wyndham laughing]
[gasping]
[grunting]
[screaming, grunting]
[gasping] Good evening.
Hi.
Do you always hang out
in trash bins in
the middle of the night?
I've, uh, uh...
...killer insomnia, ya know?
Going down there
really helps to Zen me out.
Fascinating.
You're up kinda
late yourself.
Mr. Wyndham likes the latest
interglobal stock quotations
when he wakes up.
And I was hoping
that I could use these
computers to get a jump on it.
Oh. It wouldn't help
to go in here.
This is just
the Main Memory Bank.
Besides, it's a
restricted area.
Class Four.
"Any unauthorized presence
will be a Danger Major
to the entire base."
Thank you very much
for enlightening me.
Well, goodnight now.
Aren't you going upstairs?
Soon enough.
Pleasant dreams.
Hmm...
What?
It's so dark
and inky around here,
I'd hate to have to go
all the way up to
the habitation module alone.
Please?
My goodness,
you are exhausting.
Perfect, huh?
Now that I've exhausted you,
you might as well go up
and go to sleep.
Thanks.
[Perez]
For thousands of years
regular polyhedrons have been
a source of great fascination
for mathematicians
and scientists alike.
The philosophers of ancient
Greece looked at these
principles
as the universe's
guiding forces.
It was the conjecture of the
great philosopher, Pythagoras,
that our universe
was ruled by numbers,
that all forces of nature
obeyed their
very specific laws.
[crashing]
Polyhedrons have been
a source...
I know why you're so wiped.
You stayed up to
tail Wyndham's toady?
Lutz-the-Klutz? Yeah.
He's itching to get into
that Memory Bank.
You told your mother
your suspicions?
She just said I was
into Drama Mode Major.
I'm gonna find out
what Wyndham and Lutz
are really up to.
And then all of you
will be thanking me.
See ya.
Bye.
Bye, Mom.
Honey, honey...
Your dad and I both
really want to say thanks.
For what?
For being terrific
when Wyndham's around.
You are making
a sincere effort to
stay out of trouble,
and we want you to know
that we appreciate it.
Sweat Minor, Mom.
Oh, gotta lift off.
It's a Microbe moment!
? Zoom, zoom, zoom
Make the heart go boom, boom ?
Make the heart go
boom, boom ?
I love that song.
[music playing]
? Our love is automatic ?
? Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
Over here! Hurry!
It's starting!
What are you guys doing here?
I thought you fully
loathed Microbe.
We do. We just wanna see
you two go nuclear
when the winner turns out
to be some sub-dwarf
third grader.
[all] Six, five, four,
three, two, one!
[squealing]
Good evening,
out of sight rock and rollers!
Are you primed and pumped
for our arrival?
[squealing]
Could he be
more Gorgeous Major?
I'm gonna faint, I swear.
Our judges scrutinized,
criticized and categorized
your entries, space fans.
Now it is time
to declare a winner.
[squealing]
The winning entry is...
Should I maybe milk this
a little bit longer?
No!
The winning entry in the
Dance With Me contest is...
...13-year old Zenon Kar.
I won? I really won?
Big surprise.
[screaming]
Congratulations, Zenon.
I can't wait to get up there
to meet you!
You're so lucky.
The only thing inky about
me winning, Neb,
is it means you didn't.
Hey, my best friend won,
so who cares?
Yeah. But I still wish
it could have been
the both of us.
Thanks. Me, too.
Hey! Good. There you are.
Look... You can't keep it
or anything.
Just write down what you need,
and give it back quick.
Thanks, Leo. I owe you.
Yeah.
But if you get popped,
don't tell them where
you got the code.
What code?
Hold this a sec.
Wait. You're not doing this
to spy on Lutz again, are you?
Why not?
Because if you get busted,
you know it's just
gonna ruin everything.
I ever tell you,
you worry too much?
With you for my B.F.,
you better be glad I'm not
dead from the stress.
Oh, I am.
Thanks.
Bye.
Zee!
[banging]
[whimpering]
OK.
One... three...
...five... zero...
Start.
[alarm buzzing]
No, no, no!
One... three...
four... five...
[alarm continues blaring]
I'm so glad you're here.
There was this guy, and...
Commander Plank!
We need to talk.
Yes, we do.
Why won't you guys
listen to me?
I didn't break into
the Memory Bank.
Lutz did. I was only
down there to spy on him.
Because...?
Because I knew he was up
to something inky and
nobody would listen to me!
Would you mind telling me
what led you to this
outrageous conclusion?
For one thing, Wyndham's eyes.
Have you ever looked at 'em?
I mean, when he's lying,
they do this flickering thing.
And since everybody else
is so convinced
he's up here to help us,
I was fully following my gut
to prove he's not.
I spoke to Mr. Lutz
and Mr. Wyndham.
Neither has been out
of his quarters since dinner.
That's not true!
They're lying! I saw Lutz.
Why would I be making this up?
An attempt to save
your own skin.
[Mark] Commander!
The security team says
you didn't tamper with
the data banks.
And for that we can
all be grateful.
I don't think you realize
how serious this is, Zenon.
Being in a Class Four zone,
you could've put everybody
on this station at risk.
But I didn't do anything!
Clearly, not for
lack of trying.
Silence Major!
This is the last straw, Zenon.
Now I'm leaving the punishment
to your discretion,
but do know this.
Unless you impose a sentence
as severe as the crime,
I'll be forced
to take action myself.
But you're not...
Zee!
But listen to me! Please!
Let's go.
No!
I honestly think if
you put these on,
it'll help all of us.
Or not.
You have put us in a very
difficult position, Zenon.
You can't imagine how much
I don't want to do what
I have to do now.
But you haven't left us
any choice.
What?
I'm sorry, Zee.
Your mother... and I...
...have contacted
your Aunt Judy.
Aunt Judy?
She hates space,
she hates to travel.
You wanna bring her up here
to be my "keeper"?
You don't get it, Zee.
We're grounding you.
I understand that.
No, Zee. I mean,
we're really grounding you.
What?
No. No, you can't...
Mom? Mom!
[Astrid] I'm sorry, honey.
Dad?
So, the rumor's true?
Zenon's really outta here?
Isn't it the most
gaseous thing ever?
They're shipping her
off this afternoon.
Wait, wait, wait.
[computer voice] All off-duty
personnel to mess module.
Oh!
This is stellar.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Parker Wyndham.
[applause]
When I came up here,
I half expected to
be confronted
with exhaustion
and frustration.
What I found instead
was incredible,
unwavering dedication.
Yes, there's room for
improvement here. Oh, yes.
But, overall, I could not
be prouder of the
great pioneering spirit
that I've encountered up here
on the WyndComm Space Station.
Because of it,
I am hereby pledging
an additional $500 million...
...to go to the perpetuation
and repairs of this,
your beloved base.
Call it a vote of confidence
in the many benefits
I know we will all reap
from the remarkable research
and experimentation being
conducted up here.
Thank you very much.
[cheering]
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
If anyone's reaping benefits,
it has to be you.
[voice on PA] Shuttle
departure in three
minutes from Bay Four.
Shuttle departure in three
He's not shutting us down.
He gave us more money.
Maybe you were
wrong about him.
Et tu, Nebula?
Quoting Billy Shakespeare.
You must be inked out.
Well, I made you something.
It's no big deal or anything.
It's for good luck.
Here.
It's lunarious, Neb.
Thanks.
How's that look?
Sincerely stellar.
I'm scared, Nebula.
After all the inky stuff
my mom's told me about Earth,
how am I ever
gonna survive?
Well, avoid tornadoes,
don't drink the water
and Data Zap me every day.
I've gotta go.
My ex-parents are coming.
See ya.
Thanks for all your help
and good work.
Yeah. Sure. Thank you.
Stand by
for shuttle departure.
I have to travel all the way
down there with them?
Mr. Wyndham is doing
us a great favor taking
you along on his ship.
Oh yeah, big favor to me.
About ready, ma'am?
If we miss our weather
window, our flight
will be scrubbed today.
Break my heart.
Look, Zee,
we know this is hard.
But why don't you try
to see it like an opportunity,
an adventure?
Yes, you have traveled
the universe,
but you have never really
lived outside of these walls.
Don't worry, honey.
We will bring you back
as fast as we can.
We love you.
[buzzing]
[woman] Is everyone
strapped in back there?
We're ready for lift-off.
[man] Ten...
nine... eight...
seven... six... five...
four... three...
two... one...
We're showing separation.
Roger that.
Confirming separation.
Tango-delta-bravo,
this is WyndComm Center.
We show on-board power
switchover, internal sync
at zero plus minus.
Good and good.
Start emission clock on my
mark. Three... two... one.
Emission clock is running.
We have status created across
the board.
Flight ops says
you are good to go.
[man] Tango-delta-bravo,
we show sub time at
zero-eight-23-zero.
Telemetry, direct reach
to three-two-zero.
Three-two-zero. Got that?
[groaning]
[Wyndham]
We'll be there momentarily.
[sneezes]
[woman] Is she OK?
[man] Is she all right?
[woman] Are you OK?
Thank you, gravity.
[Wyndham]
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
[groaning]
[grunting]
Zenon, your aunt will pick you
up at the main gate.
That's right over there.
Good luck.
Ya know, you may fool
a lot of people, Mr. Wyndham,
but just know,
you don't fool me.
[gasping]
What's wrong with you?
Uh, nothing.
Nothing at all. I've got
everything under control.
Fine. Let's go. We're gonna
be late for the meeting.
[distant sirens blaring]
[horn honking]
Doll face, is that you?
You look like the Zenon
I knew as a baby.
Only taller,
and more miserable.
[sniffing]
Yeah, afraid so.
Hi! Oh...
I can't believe
you made it. Flying
through space like that.
I would rather face
62 weeks of dental surgery.
Terra firma. That's my motto.
[stamps foot]
The firma the betta.
Get it?
So, how's your mom?
Still skinny as a rail,
I'll bet. Yeah?
Here. Let me get your bag.
[groans]
Are you starved?
I don't know. I guess.
Yeah? I'd take you home
and make you something myself,
but I figure
you've been traumatized
enough for one day.
[giggles]
OK... let's go.
Yeah, yeah, OK.
I'm gonna be calling.
Excuse me. Oh!
[sneezes]
Wait!
[pop music playing]
Oh, there's a table.
[boy] Take a look
at what's coming.
You don't see that every day.
Who would want to?
Oh, boy.
Why they sent you to me,
I'll never understand.
I know zip about kids.
I didn't even get 'em
when I was one of 'em.
You do eat this
sort of stuff, don't you?
Pizza, burgers, fries?
I've never had any of it.
Our food is
hydroponically grown,
no dirt, no preservatives,
no artificial coloring.
Wow! Put that much purity
into my system,
I'd be dead in 24 hours.
Isn't that outfit viral?
This place doesn't
look like anything
what I've seen on the news.
It's like some
time warped village supreme.
Well, that's part
of its appeal.
All those overhead monorails
and high-rise megaliths
in New York and L.A., it's
enough to make your head spin.
Here, we just let progress
take its sweet time.
Well, listen, hon.
While you decide,
I'm gonna go wash my hands.
Ultra graphic and historic.
Hey... pay attention!
So, like I was saying...
Absolve me from interrupting,
but my pack and I have a bet.
They think that with those
clothes and that do,
or shall I say, "don't",
you must be from some Viral
Extreme place like Eastern
Jersey.
I guessed you were simply
getting a six-month head start
on Halloween.
You win.
It's the Halloween thing.
Now lend me that mask
you're wearing
and I'll have the most hideous
Major costume ever.
Ooh! That was good.
Not bad.
Can we scrub
this mission, please?
I suddenly lost my appetite.
Pretty gorgeous, huh?
They're interesting,
but what's their purpose?
I mean,
our hydroponic chambers
are for producing oxygen,
but you've got plenty of that.
Oh, down here, not everything
has to have a purpose, hon.
Some things are
just good for your soul.
[knocking]
Hi.
I know that this is the part
where I'm supposed
to offer great words of
wisdom and comfort,
but that's why
I'm such a bad grownup.
I'm incredibly
inept at this stuff.
Sweat Minor, Aunt Judy.
I'm really glad you're here.
A little family connection,
it's nice. It's been such
a long time.
If you don't mind me asking,
how come you've never gotten
married or had any kids?
Well, unlike you, sweetie,
I've always been petrified
of putting myself out there,
or taking a risk.
Yeah. Look where
it's gotten me.
Oh, no! No, no.
You're my hero.
You're brave.
Well now, on that soul-bearing
little note...
Good night.
Zenon, just...
...know that I'm around
if you need me.
[electronic beeping]
A blocking chip has been
installed in this unit.
Calls can only be made to...
[Astrid] Mark
and Astrid Kar.
What?
A blocking chip...
I heard you, I heard you.
Thanks a metric ton, folks.
Banish me, cut me off...
One Sin Minor and my life
is a living Black Hole!
[chattering]
[beeping]
Hey.
Good morning.
Settle now, please.
If I may have
your attention...
We have a new student
joining us today.
Her name is Radon Kar.
Actually, it's Zenon.
Like that's
a whole lot better?
[laughter]
People, people. Zenon is no
ordinary visiting student.
She comes to us having spent
eight years on the WyndComm
Space Station.
Hope she's had her shots.
[laughter]
Now, that's enough, Margie.
I'm sure there's a great deal
that Zenon can teach us while
she's here,
if you'll all be wise enough
to give her that chance.
[whistle blowing]
Come on, let's go, Tracy!
Come on, let's go...
Come on, pull, pull.
Beat your time. Do it!
Pull, pull!
Come on. Pull.
That's it, keep it up...
OK, uh, new girl,
you can swim, can't you?
Sweat Minor, Commander.
I once swam from Perseus
to Pleiades in
a Class Five solar flare.
[scoffs]
OK... Go!
Hey!
Come on. You're OK.
You're OK. It's all right.
I thought you said
you could swim?
Yeah... in space.
Welcome to Earth.
I would've been OK, ya know.
You just never
gave me the chance.
Hold it over the flame more,
it needs to be hotter.
A little more.
[screaming]
I did exactly
what you said to do.
I heated it
to 250 degrees Celsius.
Down here we're still
using Fahrenheit.
[Margie] So, you made it
twice as hot?
One seventy-five, please.
One-seventy-five what?
Oh, money.
You must mean money.
Where she comes from,
they don't have cash.
Yeah, we just barter with moon
rocks and alien skulls.
I'll pay you back.
You know, the truth is,
I think it's pretty macro
you grew up in space.
Yeah? Well, I think
it's "macro" you grew
up here on Earth.
No, no, no. Go easy.
"Macro" is a good thing.
"Micro" is bad.
"Viral" is nasty.
"Graphic" is beautiful.
Excuse me.
But I studied my schedule
and nowhere on it does it say
anything
about taking
a foreign language.
"Forget about Wyndham,"
Nebula says.
"Who cares if he's
up to something inky?"
Do I listen?
Do I ever? Oh, no.
You heard about
that concert in space?
Yeah.
One girl gets to dance
with Proto Zoa?
Did anybody tell you that,
that lucky girl was supposed
to be me?
No lie?
You won that contest?
Uh-huh. But will
I be there for my
Glory Moment Major? Negative.
I'll be here getting
blown up and drowned
in a torture chamber
people call school because I
couldn't mind my own business.
Would it make any difference
if there was some lesson you
could learn?
Something about the dangers
of jumping to conclusions?
No. Because I still fully
believe I was right!
If you could have just seen
that look Lutz gave me before
I left them.
OK then, would it make
any sense to go and discuss
this with Parker Wyndham?
Cetus-Lupeedus, no!
Whatever's going on
up in that space-stay,
he and Lutz
are in it together.
I can feel it.
[Judy] Wait.
Why is my door open?
Nothing like this
has happened to me before.
I understand.
Anyways, thank you
for everything, Officer.
Uh-huh.
I hope you find him.
And lock the door
on your way out.
You bet.
Well, this place
is really turning out to be
everything your mother
warned you about, isn't it?
Not a lot of crime in space,
I'll bet.
Nowhere for the bad guys
to run to.
You know, the oddest thing is,
none of my stuff seems to be
missing.
What about you?
It's all here.
I don't buy
this random break-in stuff.
It was and Lutz and Wyndham.
What would they
be looking for?
[screams]
So, guess you're surviving?
Barely.
Look, this is Difficult Major
for me,
but I have this situation
I'm dealing with,
and I could fully
use a little help.
Last time I tried to help you,
I nearly got whiplash from the
verbal assault.
Well, obviously, your life is
so lunarious you can't relate.
But I was having
a very bad day.
I'm sorry.
Look, I'd like to help, but
I can't. I'm on my way out.
I work at a stable.
You know, with horses.
It's kind of cool.
Do you want to check it out?
No, thanks.
Suit yourself.
Real horses?
Does it always smell
like this around here?
Yeah. It's great,
isn't it?
That's not exactly the word
I would have picked.
Cetus-Lupeedus!
Pretty alpha, huh?
Pretty... humongous.
You're not scared of them,
are you?
Me? No. Of course not.
He's going to stay
in his little box, isn't he?
Sure. Until I let him out.
Out? Why would you want
to let him out?
I thought
you weren't scared?
I'm not. I just think he looks
very content where he is.
This is Pogo. I'm going
to bring him out and brush him
now, all right?
[whinnying]
See how mellow he is?
I think he likes you.
Wanna give it a try?
Not like that.
Come on.
Like this.
It's not so scary,
is it?
You want to ride him?
Oh no. I can't do this.
Mistake Major.
Just swing your leg over.
You'll be all right.
I'm up. I did it!
Cetus-Lupeedus,
it's so high.
Ready?
Go, Pogo.
[laughing]
I've never seen an ocean.
It was so beautiful
out there.
Yeah. So, your
Aunt Judy said it was
OK for you to go to dinner?
Roger that.
Now, riding a bike
is something you do
know how to do, right?
Greg, practically our whole
space-stay gym is made up
of bikes.
[crashing]
Did I mention that
those were stationary bikes?
[pop music plays]
Stellar!
A food that gives a whole new
meaning to the term "O-rings".
Oh, hot, hot!
But good. So good.
OK, what else can we order?
Whoa.
Slow down. I said I'd buy you
dinner, not 10 dinners.
I know but
I can't stop. It all
tastes so fully illegal.
Considering how many horses
I'm gonna have to groom
to pay for tonight,
I'm glad to know
you're loving it.
I am.
See, in space we can only eat
what we can cultivate.
Cows and little piggies
definitely don't make the cut.
None of that bothers you?
It's home, Greg.
I've lived there
since I was a little kid.
Cetus-Lupeedus!
What?
Lutz... where did he go?
Who?
Lutz, I said. I saw him.
He was staring at me.
The guy that works for
the WyndComm guy? You sure?
Mondo-sure. Come on, Greg.
Time for Evasion Mode Major.
Check!
Oh! Could my legs
be any whiter?
They like glow-in-the-dark.
They're fine.
Is it OK to...?
Yeah. Sure. Go ahead.
[gasps]
It's freezing.
Well, what did you expect?
I don't know.
Everything here is so...
different from what
I thought it would be.
To me, your whole planet's
just one big Mystery Extreme.
[electronic beeping]
Speaking of mysteries,
from what I can see,
the whole WyndComm operation's
not nearly as Midas as it used
to be.
What did you uncover?
Financial forms,
confidential memos.
You hacked into
their internal data bank?
Without breaking a sweat.
Stellar!
So, why would Wyndham promise
the space-stay more money
if he didn't have it?
That's the alpha question,
isn't it?
All right, tell me again
the weird look Lutz gave you.
We went through this already.
OK. I put my luggage down
and I told Wyndham that he
didn't fool me for a minute.
Then I picked up my luggage
and I turned away.
Were you wearing that?
Aunt Judy bought me this.
Not the shirt, the earring.
Yeah.
Well, maybe that's it!
If Lutz was
acting generic until
you tucked back your hair,
maybe he was reacting
to the disk.
Cetus-Lupeedus!
Lutz had a disk!
In the Main Memory Bank.
I don't know
if he put something
on it or took something off,
but he definitely
had a disk.
Will you quit wiggling?
I can't help it.
One more block and my butt's
gonna be ready for
the discard bin.
[thunderclap]
What's that? What's happening?
Zenon, it's OK.
It's just rain.
Rain?
Rain.
I remember this.
When I was real little,
getting caught
in a summer storm.
Wow, you don't
get out much, do you?
Uh-uh.
I had an alpha time tonight.
Yeah. Me, too.
I'd, uh, better get inside.
Yeah. First thing tomorrow
morning, we gotta get over
to Andrew's
to see if we can figure out
what's on this earring.
See you there.
Come here.
You know what?
You've only
been here five days
and already
you're having better luck
with guys than I ever have.
[boy] I've never seen a disk
like this one.
[groaning]
Come on. Come on.
Gregory, are you gonna
do this all day?
Probably.
But it's so boring!
Don't you want
to go for a ride with me
in my dad's hover limo?
No, thanks.
You always used to like
riding with me,
before she dropped out of the
sky like a ton of space junk.
[boy] Reality pill, Margie.
It was never you he liked,
it was the car.
[Margie] Shut up, Matt.
[Andrew] Why can't I
get into this thing?
[Greg] You'll get it.
Keep trying.
You know, a very close friend
of my father's works for IMC,
and I was thinking,
isn't it only fair to let them
know that their contest winner
won't be around
for her big dance?
I'm gonna be back
there in time.
The concert
is next weekend, Zenon.
Do you really think
your parents are gonna forgive
and forget that fast?
I don't see
why this is your business.
It's not.
My business is keeping you
away from Gregory.
He's helping me
with a Problem Major.
That better be all.
Or I'll sprint to that
view-phone and tell those
Microbe folks
that they need
to pick a replacement.
Because the girl they thought
was a winner is nothing
but a stranded-on-Earth
Loser Extreme!
[snoring]
[electronic beeping]
[beeping]
What the heck?
Ew!
Oh, no. Hey!
[electrical zapping]
[gasping]
Oh, come on. Come on.
Oh, man!
It's a highly sophisticated,
untraceable nano-virus
that'll slowly continue
to replicate inside a system
until the entire
hard drive crashes
down and self-destructs.
Cetus-Lupeedus,
are you sure?
Considering the hunk of melted
junk that now sits where my
computer used to be,
I'm very sure.
Fortunately,
after several hours
of highly-skilled maneuvers,
I have managed to
refashion this program
into an "undo" file
that should remove the bugs
from whatever system
they've been introduced to.
Can you guarantee that?
Nothing can ever be guaranteed
until it's...
...well, put to the test.
Here. But to put it there,
we would have to get it there.
That's a problem?
She's talking about the Main
Computer on the space station.
OK, if everything
you're saying is true, Andrew,
how come it hasn't
come crashing down?
The system your space
station has must
be incredibly powerful.
So, you mean,
Wyndham's bugs might not work?
Oh, no,
they'll work big time.
They just might
take a little longer to do it.
Let's go.
Go? Go where?
School's about to start.
Not for me. My parents
are in Jeopardy Major!
You go.
I can't believe you think
I'm making this up!
I, more than anyone,
understand how
traumatic Earth can be.
But you haven't given yourself
time to adjust.
I still cannot regulate the
oxygen flow to the rat cages.
I can't seem
to find the glitch.
The entire experiment
is hinging on this.
I know. I know.
Mom!
This could be
a part of what
I'm trying to explain to you!
Zenon, tell your Aunt Judy to
stop letting you watch
so many movie chips.
Unless I get up there
to deliver the undo file
Andrew created,
the whole space-stay will be
blasted into some Universe
Minor!
Would you mind telling me
why Wyndham would want to
destroy his own space station?
For, for money? I don't know.
I only know he is!
You're still trying to make it
back for the Microbe concert,
right?
This isn't about Microbe,
Dad!
It isn't about having learned
a lesson down there!
[Mark] We know you're in
a new environment and it's
disorienting.
But why don't you make
the best of it?
Will you guys listen to me?
You're running out of time!
Besides the oxygen thing,
what other
systems are breaking down?
Nothing, Zenon.
It's business as usual.
By the way,
who is your friend?
[man] Commander Plank
needs you to meet him
in Lieutenant Orieux's office.
Zenon, honey, we gotta go.
Love you.
No, Mom, wait.
Yeah. Goodbye, sweetheart.
You stay out
of trouble, OK?
But...
[electronic beeping]
[Astrid] How could
she possibly know
that the system failures
are becoming more frequent?
There haven't been news leaks?
Not that I've heard.
But when Zenon's
on a mission,
we should never underestimate
what she's capable of.
[electrical buzzing]
[screaming]
Here we go again.
Why can't they figure out
what is wrong?
I'm sorry your parents
didn't believe you.
Yeah. Me, too.
You know, for a girl
who just got to this planet,
you're awfully hard
to get hold of.
You think that's an accident?
Chill, metro boy wonder.
I come in peace.
What do you want?
All I want is your earring.
It wouldn't look good
on you.
Do you know
what that disk contains?
It's just a bunch
of boring corporate records
that wouldn't mean anything
to you, but are valuable
to Mr. Wyndham.
Meaning...
...that you'll be in
Trouble Major
if you don't retrieve it?
As a matter of fact, yes.
What'll you give me for it?
What do you want, cash?
Nothing quite so tacky,
Mr. Lutz.
I'll be happy
with a ride home.
I thought you were home.
To the space station.
For crying out loud!
How am I supposed
to arrange that?
Ask your boss.
He's got a bunch
of shuttles.
I give you a lift
and you give me the disk?
Instantly.
All right. All right,
I promise I'll arrange it.
Wait!
Write it. Sign it.
Disk, please.
Hey, don't give
that to him 'til
you're boarding the flight.
Greg, show a little faith,
will ya?
Besides, we have to learn
to trust each other.
Right, Mr. Lutz?
Actually, wrong.
See, now, I've got the disk
and you have got... squat.
OK, so I get this unblocked,
you can call Nebula.
But what good will it do
if you gave the disk to Lutz?
You weren't listening,
Andrew.
I said I gave him
"a" disk.
But with my Skill Minor
but Ingenuity Major,
we can have as many rainbow
disks as we need.
All right!
[Wyndham] ...therefore, our
attendance at the Interglobal
Conference
on BioTechnic
Oceanic Harvesting
hinges upon your
acceptance and
support of the following...
Sir... could I, uh,
speak to you for a moment?
Very well.
It's not my fault, but...
[Wyndham shouting]
You lost the what?
Yes. It's working!
It's going through.
Andrew,
you're a miracle worker.
No applause.
Just, uh, send money.
Nebulator! Oh, it's me!
I've missed you so much!
Is everything OK up there?
You guys aren't having
global meltdowns yet, are you?
Cetus-Lupeedus! How did you
know? The attitude thrusters
are messed up.
The base has been
going through
these wild plunges.
It's been awful.
Oh, Neb!
Look at you.
You're alive.
Has it been gaseous?
Tell me all about it.
I'll tell you megabytes
when I see you.
But listen, everybody up there
is in danger mortis
and my parents are living
on Planet Denial.
I can't get into all the inky
details, but I was right
about Wyndham.
He put this
gunkball nano
virus in your computers.
We tried uploading
the undo disk from here,
but we can't.
The only way
I can possibly help
is to get up there
with the disk.
And to do that,
I need you.
What can I do?
Go to the shipping bay,
check the schedules
and let me know
when the next cargo ship
is set to go up.
That means
I have to break in.
So?
I'm not you, you know.
Sorry, Neb. For today
you're going to have to be.
You have a Videogram.
I hate to do this to you,
Aunt Jude, because you've been
Stellar Major,
but things have gotten
desperate.
It looks like I'm the only one
who can save my friends
and family.
Cryptic. But since Lutz
will most definitely
be back looking for me,
the less you know,
the better.
He's Viral-in-the-Extreme
and you do not want to tangle
with him, OK?
Now, I'll give you updates
the nano second
I possibly can.
Thanks for everything,
and I hope to see you soon.
Maybe you'll get brave
and come visit us in space.
Gotta go. Love you.
Bye.
Go? Go where?
[Leo] I still don't see
why you had to
wake me up for this.
This is an Emergency Major.
Your dad has the code pad,
and if I'm getting caught
down here,
I am not
getting busted alone.
OK!
Here it is.
Seven... one...
...five... four.
It's the cargo
shuttle schedule
we're looking for?
Yeah.
Look, here it is.
Whoa, talk about
your Karma Major.
Oh! Cetus-Lupeedus!
There's a ship set
to be launched tonight!
[machinery grinding]
What happened?
Something gaseous,
that's for sure.
Sounds like the entire station
shut down this time.
[groaning]
[electronic blast noises]
[chuckling] All right!
You know,
when you're up there,
the sky never seems
quite this massive.
[Zenon] Isn't it weird
to think they're all up there?
I mean, my parents and
my friends, they're all
in Danger Mortis, Greg,
and they don't even know it.
They're gonna be all right.
I know it.
Then why hasn't Nebula
called back?
Three hours
we've been stuck in here, Leo.
Shouldn't the back-up
generators be kicking in?
Why don't these doors
have manual overrides?
How should I know?
Am I Plank-the-Blank?
[machinery whirring]
Listen.
Supernova!
[Greg] I don't know
if you want to hear this,
but if you leave now,
I'm really gonna miss you.
Really?
Yeah.
You're not like girls
around here.
You're... I don't know...
Alpha Extreme.
Cetus-Lupeedus, Greg.
If you want to kiss me,
just do it.
Ow!
I'm... I'm sorry.
Dare to try again?
[electronic beeping]
Zee, you have to leave now!
A cargo ship's being launched
from WyndComm in less than an
hour!
Come on, Greg.
[Andrew] Quiet.
Shh, don't wake my parents.
[Zenon] How do we drive?
It's got an auto pilot.
It practically drives itself.
Man, this car's heavy.
Push.
Hello!
I could have sworn I told you
to stay away from Gregory.
Margie, I'm dealing with
a Crisis Major, and Greg
is a big boy.
Who's here to tell you to stop
being a halftone, all right?
I'm not your boyfriend.
Not since she arrived.
Not ever. I never was.
I never will be.
Swallow the reality pill,
read my flapping lips.
OK, Zenon or no Zenon,
I will never be
your boyfriend!
Is this negotiable? Maybe
I caught you at a bad time.
I could come back tomorrow.
Hey! In case you people
are blanking here,
Zenon's got a short amount
of time to talk her way
onto that shuttle.
You're leaving us?
Sorry to break your heart,
but the space-stay needs me.
In that case, pop the trunk.
I have to come along
and say good-bye.
So, you do know how
to pilot this thing?
As long as you've got
the ignition code
and enter departure
and destination points...
Supposedly my dad keeps
this puppy programmed
to do all the rest.
[nervous laugh]
Supposedly?
[Andrew]
There! There it is!
[Zenon] Wait!
Come back, please!
Look over here!
[beeping horn]
Wait! Come back!
Please don't go without me.
No! Come back!
And there it goes.
What now?
I think we ought
to go to the cops.
Yeah, right.
My own parents
didn't believe me.
Why should they?
It's over.
Wyndham's nano-virus will chew
through all the systems,
everybody up there
will be finished.
It's really awful.
But wouldn't it be viral
if the explosion happens
while Microbe's there?
What did you say?
I wasn't trying to be cruel.
Margie, Margie, Margie!
Are you feeling all right?
Margie, you are a Mega-Genius.
I know. Why?
Well... Microbe.
They've got to be heading up
to the space-stay
for their concert.
Right?
Right.
[man on TV] Rock and roll fans
around the world...
It's not that
I've lost track of her,
Astrid.
It is just that...
...I have no idea
where she is, exactly. Oh!
...with an update, here's
Jillian live from WyndComm
headquarters.
Dozens of people,
and diehard rock fans,
have gathered in anticipation
of today's launch of the
shuttle
that will be
transporting Microbe...
[gasps]
...making them
the first rock band...
Hello, pal. I'm sure we're not
on your list or anything,
but this is Zenon Kar.
You know, the Microbe contest
winner.
And it's alpha-vital that
she speak to Proto Zoa ASAP.
Did you say Zenon Kar?
That's me all right.
Guess you've heard of me, huh?
Step out of the vehicle.
I've got instructions
to detain you.
You mean, like
take her prisoner?
Mr. Wyndham is anxious
to get hold of you.
I'll bet he is.
Sorry. Love to hang around,
but gotta rocket.
Hey! Hey!
I came up with the concept
for the first rock concert
in space
as a way of saying thank you
to the crew of my
WyndComm Space Station.
Look! There it is!
Being a visionary...
[Andrew] Microbe's gotta
be back stage.
...it's a burden
I'm willing to carry.
I'm going in.
[applause]
And being visionary
is what WyndComm Enterprises
has always been about.
That's how the WyndComm Space
Station came into being.
Ladies and gentlemen,
at this time
I'd like to introduce
to you two of the people
that are responsible for the
concepts, design and execution
of the world's first
commercial space station.
Our conceptual engineer
and project manager,
without whose exceptional
talent...
Cheers.
Do you believe
we're going into outer space?
Mr. Zoa?
It's me, Zenon Kar,
your contest winner.
I'm here instead of up there,
but you have to take me
back up there with you.
I don't have a lot of time
to explain,
but it's Urgent Major.
You have to believe me.
You're my one and only hope.
It is you, isn't it?
Got you now, kid. Game over.
Sorry about this.
We'll get her out of here.
No! No, tell them!
You have to tell them!
It's urgent in
the Viral Extreme.
[guard] Let's go.
Gentlemen, you obviously
don't know who this is.
We have orders
to deliver her to Mr. Wyndham.
And disappoint
all my adoring
disc-buying fans
who are waiting
to see me dance with her
up there in space?
I don't think so, boys.
Lacy, would you do me a favor,
darling?
Please escort Ms. Kar
to the space shuttle.
I'm going?
You're taking me with you?
Yes.
Cetus-Lupeedus! As much
as I loved you before,
now I love you even more!
Of course you do.
Thank you,
thank you, thank you!
Mr. Zoa, this is
strictly against regulations.
But, Mr. Zoa, this...
[crowd applauding]
Boys, are you going to be
Wyndham's monkeys
for the rest of your lives,
or might you consider
a career in rock and roll?
Rock and roll!
All right, then. Here you go.
Without further ado, let me
introduce the group who,
to my way of thinking,
has always been
out of this world.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Microbe!
[crowd screaming]
[Zoa] Calm down, calm down.
You know I love ya.
It's good to see ya.
So, uh, today's journey
is one small step for Microbe,
and one giant leap
for rock and roll!
[cheering]
Sir, excuse me. Hello.
I'm looking for my niece,
Zenon Kar.
You and everyone else
around here.
She's here?
Who do you think
wrecked my gate?
Sorry about that,
but I gotta go.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
[cheering]
This really was inspired,
sending such a popular group
up to the space station
hours before
it's going to self-destruct.
What a perfect smoke screen
to keep fingers
from ever being
pointed at you.
Yes. If only you hadn't
allowed that little brat
to steal our disk.
Where is she?
What have you done with her?
Who is this woman?
I am Zenon Kar's aunt.
And I demand to know
where she is.
I can assure you
she isn't here.
Well, that's not
what the guy at the gate said.
The guy at the gate
was mistaken.
I am Parker Wyndham,
and nothing goes on here
that I don't know about.
She's here.
She's determined to get back
to the space station
with Proto Zoa.
Find him and you'll
certainly find her.
Oh, no.
[cheering]
You don't suppose she...
Wait!
Everyone strapped in?
Make sure those seat belts
are securely fastened.
Stand clear for shuttle
lift-off.
That shuttle's
not going anyplace.
Zenon,
I'm responsible for you!
We're ready for lift-off.
Ooh! Whoa!
[alarm buzzes]
Ahh!
[grunting]
[giggling]
[buzzing]
No!
We're headed for outer space,
right? I mean, I'm going
to outer space?
Yeah, right.
Listen, Aunt Judy?
Yes.
There's some stuff
that I should fill you in on.
[voice on intercom,
indistinct]
The cooling and
the heating systems are down.
The living module is freezing,
the tech module is sweltering.
Well, at least
it's bearable in here.
For the moment.
The entire habitat wing
lost power about an hour ago.
Right about the time the
attitude thrusters started
acting up.
[alarm sounding]
Why is this happening?
As if there isn't
enough going on, sir,
the shuttle carrying Microbe
will be arriving within the
hour.
The whole world has to be
turning its eyes on us now?
Sorry, sir.
We're doing the best we can
to keep things going.
Well, wave them off. At least
they can save themselves.
Without refueling
they'll never get home.
If we get to total system
failure, none of us will.
Good thing that you can sing
better than
you can play poker.
Cheeky little scamp,
isn't she?
Mm-hmm.
Um, there is one thing
I should mention.
There's this little situation
happening on the space-stay
I need to take care of
when we get home.
You'll fully love
being up there
and I've got everything
under control.
We can only hope.
Breathe, Aunt Judy.
Breathe slowly.
OK, I'm breathing.
I hate flying.
Again?
[Wyndham] A toothpick
is never going to work.
You have a laser knife?
[Lutz] What am I,
a Boy Scout?
[Wyndham] You are an utterly
useless, over-paid, spineless,
incompetent,
jabbering fool!
[computer voice] Confirm hard
dock on shuttle in Bay 3.
Welcome to WyndComm Space
Station. I'm Lt. Schiff.
Proto Zoa,
pleased to meet you.
[man on intercom] Zero-G
technician to the bridge,
on the double.
[screaming]
[alarm sounding]
We're currently experiencing
a few technical glitches.
Nothing to be alarmed about.
Right this way.
Zero-G technician
to the bridge on the double.
We're floating up here.
Hi.
Come on, Aunt Judy.
Trust me. Turn off all
non-essential systems!
Give me more...
[grunting]
Sir!
What are you...
How did you get back?
Commander, Wyndham and Lutz
are trying to bring down
the space-stay!
I'm the only one
who can stop them.
As hard as it may be
to believe,
she's telling you the truth.
Who are you?
Judy Kling.
I'm Zenon's aunt.
Edward Plank.
[screaming]
[pounding]
Pilot, turn this
shuttle around immediately,
and get us out of here.
We can't. We have to refuel
and cool the booster cells.
No, we don't!
We have to leave right now!
I'm sorry, sir, but there...
No excuses! Just do it!
Even if your credibility
wasn't shaky,
nothing you're telling me
makes sense.
Because she's the one
who tampered
with your systems.
And she's trying
to cover it up
by blaming me!
He's a liar!
A mondo liar!
I'm not going to engage
in a name-calling contest
with a teenager.
Because you know
you'll lose!
The computer's gone flatline.
We've got less
than 15 minutes.
That's what
I'm trying to tell you.
It's all because of him!
If you allow this child
to speak to me in this manner,
I will have
this entire station
shut down!
Oh, button your lip!
Look! I have no time
for bickering!
Take Zenon and her aunt
to my office.
No! Wait! Please.
If you and Mr. Lutz will relax
in my V.I.P. lounge,
we'll sort this out
after I get the space station
under control.
Commander, I need
emergency re-fueling.
I have to leave immediately.
I bet you do!
That's enough! Go!
[Zenon screaming]
Gentlemen, please.
Find the disk!
I'm trying
to find the disk.
[computer voice]
Keep all hatches closed.
700 channels and I can't get
one report on what's going on
in space.
You can't talk
to Zenon directly?
I can't believe it.
What's going on up there?
You guys OK?
Emergency Major.
Where's Andrew?
What's the static?
You unblocked my communicator
for calls between
Earth and the space-stay.
But now I can't
get it to make local calls.
Where are you?
In more trouble than I've got
time to explain. Call Nebula.
Tell her Aunt Judy and I are
being held captive in Plank's
office,
and she has to come
and get us out.
You just got there
and you're in detention?
Call Nebula!
Code Red! Emergency conditions
on all levels.
Code red. Emergency conditions
Just my luck. The one room
in the whole space-stay
where the ceiling tiles
don't come loose.
That's why we went
to "Plan B".
That's my girl!
Code red. Emergency
conditions...
Neb, try to find my parents
and fill them in.
I've got to try and undo
what Wyndham and Lutz did.
All right. Bye.
Bye.
What about those scary guys?
Aren't you afraid
they're gonna try
to get out of here?
Sweat Minor, Aunt Judy.
I've already taken care of it.
Continue evacuation
of section 11 on level four.
Activating ignition sequence.
Go! Go!
[engine running]
[engine stopping]
Oh, this was
a great plan, sir.
A great plan.
Only one small hitch,
I might point out.
We weren't supposed
to be on board when
it self-destructed.
Incorrect access code.
The virus originated here.
We can't figure out
what to do to stop it.
Total system failure
in 30 seconds.
Thirty seconds?
This was supposed
to be the safe place to live.
Any last thoughts, sir?
Clear the way.
I've got the undo disk.
[overlapping voices]
Commander, trust me.
We'll talk later, OK?
I've got a space-stay to save.
Total system failure
in 20 seconds.
Not if I can help it.
Incorrect access code.
I know this. I can do this.
What's the story, Zenon?
It all turned out to be
exactly like I told you, sir.
Wyndham had Lutz place this
virus in our computer,
so he'd collect
the insurance money.
Incorrect access code.
Total system failure
in 10 seconds.
Nine... eight... seven...
Incorrect access code.
...six... five...
four... three...
...two... one.
[whirring]
Total System rehabilitated.
[cheering]
Oh, sweetheart!
Is it over? Is it safe?
Lieutenant Schiff,
arrest those men!
You are so brilliant.
I am so proud of you.
[cheering]
Thank you.
Thank you!
Thank you. Thanks.
We love you Proto Zoa!
Thank you,
ladies and gentlemen.
Settle down, settle down,
we've still got
a long way to go.
Now, uh,
this next part of the show
was supposed to be
when we bring up
our contest winner.
But she's kind of requested
a slight alteration
in our plans.
I mean, once you
save an entire space station,
what can you possibly do
for an encore, right?
[cheering]
So, she's asked me
to do two things for her.
Number one, she'd like me
to dedicate this next song
to a very lucky guy
named Greg.
[applause]
[electronic rock music]
? Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
? Star-gazing mega fast you
hit me like a cosmic blast ?
? You've given me
a technicolor world ?
? Putting me in overdrive ?
? Speed of light
I'm so alive ?
? Could you be
my super nova girl ?
? Interplanetary,
mega stellar, hydrostatic ?
? There's a gravity
between us ?
? Our love is automatic ?
? Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
? Make my heart go boom, boom
My super nova girl ?
? Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
? Make my heart go boom, boom
My super nova girl ?
? Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
? Make my heart go boom boom
My super nova girl ?
? Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
? Make my heart go boom, boom
My super nova girl ?
[cheering]
? Visions of your pretty face
send me into hyperspace ?
? Caught up
in a planetary world ?
? Breathing in you
give me air ?
? I'm living off
your solar flare ?
? Could you be
my super nova girl? ?
? Interplanetary,
mega stellar, hydrostatic ?
? There's a gravity
between us ?
? Our love is automatic ?
? Zoom, zoom, zoom
Make my heart go boom boom ?
? My super nova girl
Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
? Make my heart go
boom, boom ?
? My super nova girl
Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
? Make my heart go boom, boom
My super nova girl ?
? Zoom, zoom, zoom
Make my heart go boom, boom ?
? My super nova girl ?
All right,
bring it down, boys.
And number two, Zenon asked me
to pass her winning dance
on to somebody she says
was always there for her,
without question, up for every
adventure she ever proposes.
Everything
a B.F. should be.
Nebula?
? Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
According to Zenon,
you're the true winner.
So, why don't you
come on up here! Come on.
Go!
No, no. You won. You go.
I got to ride all the way back
on the shuttle with him.
Go, Neb!
I'm all yours.
Somebody better get up here
before I get a complex!
Go!
? Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
Come on, darling!
Come and get your tambourine,
and beat it, Nebula!
? Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
Did I ever tell you how truly
amazing I think you are?
Only about 22 kajillion times
since I've been home.
? Interplanetary,
mega stellar, hydrostatic ?
? There's a gravity
between us ?
? Our love is automatic
Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
? Make my heart go boom, boom
My super nova girl ?
? Zoom, zoom, zoom
Make my heart go boom, boom ?
? My super nova girl
Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
It's good to be home.
? Make my heart go boom,
boom ?
Cetus-Lupeedus,
it's good to have you home.
It's great
to have you home.
? My super nova girl ?
[French accent] Come here,
my little brussel sprout.
? Interplanetary,
mega stellar, hydrostatic ?
? There's a gravity
between us ?
? Our love is automatic ?
? Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
? Make my heart go boom, boom
My super nova girl ?
? Zoom, zoom, zoom
Make my heart go boom, boom ?
? My super nova girl
Zoom, zoom, zoom ?
? Make my heart go boom, boom
My super nova girl ?
? Zoom, zoom, zoom
Make my heart go boom, boom ?
? My super nova girl ?
[cheering]
[crowd cheering]
Zenon! Zenon! Zenon!