Woman: Bless me, father, for i
have sinned. It has been a day
since my last confession.
I saw Agnes Dunn as I was
entering the dry cleaners,
and took the lord's name in
vain.
I disrespected sister Joan
by daydreaming in our lady's
altar society meeting.
I believed it was the lesser
of two evils.
Often, when I pay attention to
what she's saying,
I begin to have doubts.
For this, and so much more,
I am terrified I am going to
hell.
The body of Christ.
The blood of Christ.
( Loudly ) The blood of Christ.
The body of Christ.
The blood of Christ.
- The body of Christ. - The
blood of Christ.
The body of Christ.
Mrs. cleary, is something
wrong?
I lost a contact.
I had that Lasik procedure two
years ago.
It changed my life.
I'm glad to find you alone.
As you know, this is the time
of year
we nominate women for the
catholic woman of the year
award.
Well, I want you.
Thank you, monsignor.
Oh, don't be thankin' me yet.
Sister Joan nominated Agnes
Dunn.
Agnes Dunn?
The rest of the committee is
divided.
So sister Joan suggested an
outside party
make the decision.
I offered bishop Donnelly.
Oh. Head of catholic families
together.
Exactly. That's where you're
strong.
You have the perfect family.
We'll need frank and the kids
to provide letters of
recommendation
when they meet with bishop
Donnelly.
Meet with him?
Oh, yes, yes, at the in-home
visit.
That holds the most weight in
the decision.
- Oh. - Oh, Mrs. cleary.
I've been blessed to take tea
at your home.
You could eat off the floors.
Thank you, monsignor.
Oh, I probably shouldn't
divulge this,
because it hasn't been
announced yet,
but we're to have a special
guest at the ceremony.
The archbishop of Dublin.
- Oh! - Yes.
The archbishop himself will
offer our most holy sacrament
to the winner.
The prayer of absolution.
All sins forgiven.
( Phone rings )
Hey, ma.
( Whispering ) Monsignor
Murphy has nominated me
for catholic woman of the year.
That's great, ma. No one does
more for the church than you.
Why are you whispering?
Oh, um...
( Normal voice ) I'm still in
church.
It's a sin to boast.
It's Thursday.
Why are you still at church?
Look, ma, I have to... I'm
gonna be late for work.
( Whispering ) No caffeine.
So we'll use the good China
tonight to celebrate.
Celebrate?
The nomination.
Shannon, I really wish you
would stop with the emails
when I'm talking to you. This
is important.
Ma, I'm really happy for you,
but I have to leave for work.
All right. Dinner will be at
7:00.
My youth ministry class got
pushed back an hour.
Fine.
And Mr. o'Riley can't have any
red meat.
His cholesterol is too high
for the living now.
These are vegetable tamales,
Mrs. cleary.
Here. I made you one.
Lord Jesus, be our guest,
that this food to us be
blessed. Amen.
Amen.
Mmm!
I told you.
How do I make these?
Well, I have ay chaparita.
- Is something the matter? -
My daughter marcella.
Oh, my!
Are we serving the homebound
cobbed corn?
Um... tamales wrapped in corn
husks.
And they are delicious.
Oh. Well, wrap them up,
because sister Joan suggested
that I take over Megan
O'Donnell's route
since her mother's in hospice.
Mmm. Is she at meridian?
I have a prayer meeting there
this week, I could look in on
her.
I have no idea.
Did you hear the good news?
What good news?
Makes me think about the third
grade
when we were both considered
to lead the may procession,
and then again, in high school.
Both considered to play Mary
in the Christmas pageant.
Agnes and I have been
nominated for
catholic woman of the year.
Ah! Congratulations!
And now, here we are again.
I have to be going.
I just wanted to say good luck,
and I hope you win this time.
* it's a perfect day
( humming along to radio )
* it's a perfect day for you
and me... *
( humming continues )
* it's a perfect day
these tamales better not be
too salty.
Congratulations on your
nomination.
Mrs. punch, how on earth do
you know about that?
O'Riley calls us all after you
leave.
He's more reliable than the
evening news.
You know you're a shoo-in.
How do you figure that?
Agnes Dunn's cousin married a
protestant.
( Both laughing )
Every time something good is
about to happen to me,
Agnes Dunn pops up.
Who lives a more divine life
than you?
You do so much for the church,
it makes St. Nicholas blush.
Oh, Mary!
Every day mass, ministry to
shut-ins, meals on wheels.
There isn't a person from two
to 92
you don't preach god's
blessings.
Thank you.
Even mama would've been proud.
She never had a kind word for
me.
I didn't say she would tell
you she was proud.
Mmm. She'd probably say,
( Irish accent ) "Most people
get this award sooner or later,
Eileen,
but most of them get it a lot
sooner."
Well, wouldn't you be proud if
Shannon got an award like that?
Oh, that's different.
Shannon and I get along great.
- Gonna eat that? - Go ahead.
So Nick asked me if we're both
wearing tuxedos.
Oh, no. He is so uninvited.
- Was he serious? - Mm-hmm.
Oh, my god.
When do I get to see you in
your dress?
I told you, I'm traditional.
You're gonna have to wait.
So unfair. My mom gets to see
you, and I don't. Not fair.
Sorry.
Speaking of mothers...
I know I...
I keep thinking that there'll
be a moment
that feels right, but...
I know.
I have to tell her.
I mean, it's bordering on
ridiculous at this point.
How about you come with me to
dinner tonight?
Tonight?
Yes.
Hmm.
What?
I'm just trying to picture it.
Me at the cleary family dinner
for the first time in six years.
I could come for dessert.
- That sounds perfect. - Okay.
I have to go.
I'm super behind on those
spring street grants.
Right.
I love you.
It's gonna be fine. I'll see
you later.
- Bye. - Bye.
Frank!
I've got news.
I've been nominated for
catholic woman of the year.
Yeah? That's great.
What's wrong?
Patty called.
He left her again.
He'll be back.
Lord Jesus, please.
Help our son frank junior
to stop being an idiot and go
back to his wife and children.
Amen.
Where is he?
You need to stay out of it.
- He's ruining his life. -
It's his life.
You need to let him make his
own decisions.
Oh, is that what you were busy
doing
when he got Patty pregnant in
high school?
We shouldn't have pushed him
into marrying somebody
he didn't love.
He's got another woman?
It won't last.
He's not like you, frank.
Who is she?
Theresa hennessey.
The manicurist?
What is it?
There's some bag lady staring
at us.
- Uh... - What?
- Just one second. - Where you
going?
I'll just be right back.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
Ma, what the hell are you
doin' here?
What am I doing here? What are
you doing here?
I am not discussing this with
you.
She's older than you are.
You can't even have a mid-life
crisis right.
Who's gonna teach the boys how
to drive?
Ma, I am leaving Patty, I'm
not moving to Siberia.
You didn't tell monsignor
Murphy, did you?
Why the hell would I tell him?
Because if you want marriage
counseling,
monsignor Murphy isn't very
good at it.
I think you should go to
another priest, maybe another
parish.
Ma, my marriage is over.
It's been over a long time.
You took a vow.
Once you say something, you
can't take it back.
Once you do something, you
can't undo it.
I'll see you at dinner tonight.
Uh, it's at 7:00.
The youth group got pushed
back an hour.
Ma, do you want me to give him
a call or... ?
( Door opens )
You're late.
Sorry. Theresa's sister got
engaged, so...
There was a thing at
O'Malley's.
You were at a bar?
Yes. She got engaged today,
so...
There was a thing.
Okay. Let's eat.
Bless us, o lord,
for these, thy gifts,
we are about to receive from
thy bounty,
through Christ our lord. Amen.
All: Amen.
All right, well, let's dig in.
What are you waiting for?
What is it?
It looks great, ma.
Thank you, Shannon.
Yeah, I thought I'd try a new
recipe.
Vegetarian tamales.
No meat?
Ma, this is excellent.
( Mocking ) Ma, this is
excellent.
- ( Thudding sound ) - Ow!
- Will you stop kicking me? -
Will you stop being a jerk?
Knock it off. You stop kicking
him,
- you stop being a jerk. - How
am I a jerk?
Well, what do you call leaving
your wife and kids,
and going to a bar with a
girlfriend?
Oh, boy, here it comes.
Without Patty and the kids,
we had to take a leaf out of
the table.
Your father almost strained
his back.
So okay, so now I'm
responsible for dad's back.
Be nice if you took
responsibility for something.
Eileen.
I don't understand what he's
doing.
I'm just trying to be happy,
mom.
Well, who cares if you're
happy?
You need to do the right thing.
Ma, why don't you tell us
about the award?
Oh, well.
It's a great honor.
- You deserve it. - Thank you,
Shannon.
See, not only is it just being
nominated,
but there is also a luncheon,
and, um...
And the prayer of absolution.
Ma, I don't think you were the
only one who thought
that corn dog was a fish stick.
( Laughter )
I have other sins.
Oh, I'll need all of you to
write a personal statement,
a letter of recommendation,
for the monsignor.
I don't know much about your
church work.
I think it's more sort of
personal reference.
Sure. We can do that for you.
And also, they...
They want to meet you, too.
Why do they want to meet us?
Well, just to see if, you know,
everything's okay.
What does that mean?
Well, if everything is normal.
Ma, what are you talking about?
Well, that you are not married
and over 30.
Is that a new sin I'm not
aware of?
No, I just think it would be
nice
if you told the committee
you were dating a good
catholic man.
Dad.
So you want her to lie.
Or you could start dating a
good catholic man.
I want her to try.
Ma, it's never going to happen.
Oh, if Fiona Doyle's obese
daughter can get a man,
well, so can you.
Are you all right?
I'm fine. ( Clears throat )
Maybe we should change the
subject.
No.
I don't need a man.
I have Angela.
Well, honey, friends are nice,
but at your age,
you should start thinking
about a family.
We are family.
Angela and I are together,
and I'm five months' pregnant.
- That's not funny. - (
Doorbell rings )
It's true, ma.
I don't know what you're
talking about.
You know. You must know.
I live with a woman.
- I never date men. - ( Door
opens )
- Hi. - Hi.
Thanks.
Uh, I don't want to know about
this.
What part, ma?
What part don't you want to
know anything about?
Me? Your grandchild?
You're talking crazy.
Eileen.
Great. All right then. I'm
going to go.
I'll pray for you.
Pray for yourself.
Come on.
You know, I got married to
frank in a thrift store gown
borrowed from cousin rose.
I always dreamed better for
Shannon.
She's a lawyer.
I'd say your dreams came true.
It was monsignor Murphy who
made sure she got that
scholarship.
Every good thing my family has,
the church has made possible,
and now...
Did Shannon tell you about
those meetings,
you know, for families of gay
people?
You sound like frank.
Meetings can be helpful.
Like the al-anon meeting
where that woman went on about
hiding money from her drunken
husband
- in her douche bag? - That
was just one meeting.
What kind of person does
something like that?
Eileen...
What sort of woman hides money
in a douche bag,
- Eileen... - And then talks
about it in public?
It's not about the douche bag.
I don't need meetings.
There's nothing wrong with me.
I just need my family to
behave the way they're supposed
to.
( Phone rings )
Hello.
My daughter is Shannon cleary.
Eileen. Shannon's in with the
doctor,
and frank is waiting around
the corner in the waiting room.
Who are you?
Oh, I'm Christina, Angela's
mom.
- I'm Eileen's sister, Mary. -
Come on.
Frank is right this way.
They're here.
What happened?
Shannon called me on the way
to the hospital.
- She called you. - Eileen.
There was some blood.
The doctor told Angela to meet
her here.
What did the doctor say?
She hasn't come out yet.
You must be Mrs. cleary.
I'm Lou reyes, Angela's father.
Nice to meet you.
Maybe you should wait in the
car.
- Yeah. - Okay.
You've gotta be kidding me. An
insufficient cervix.
( Laughter )
And the doctor said it could
also be referred to as an
incompetent cervix.
Oh, great!
I'm already insufficient and
incompetent,
and the baby isn't even here
yet.
- ( Laughter ) - It isn't
funny.
( Laughter stops )
Sorry, folks. Visiting hours
are over.
Oh, shoot.
- Thanks, mom. - Thanks for
coming.
Take care.
- Bye, dad. - Get some sleep,
okay?
I will. I'll try.
- I'll bring the car around. -
All right.
- See you later, frank. - See
ya.
So I talked to the doctor.
You have to take this
seriously.
I do.
She doesn't want you going to
the office.
She wants you off your feet
most of the day.
You're gonna have to get
someone to help.
Eileen: I can help.
We'll manage.
I can clean and shop, cook...
When Angela's at work.
Ma...
You need me.
Shan, it would be a big help.
You've never even been to my
apartment.
You hate highways.
( Horn honking )
Mrs. cleary.
- Come in. - Thank you.
Sorry, I'm running late for a
meeting,
or I'd give you the tour.
Oh, no, I'm fine.
You go ahead.
Shannon should be off the
phone soon.
Right.
We appreciate you being here.
No, I gave Steve...
Uh, I'm sorry.
I gave Steve all the
instructions.
And they're happy with the
contract as it is?
Sorry, Robert. I didn't hear
you.
Well, can't they push it up?
No, ma, leave those on the
rack.
No, if you hang pots, they
just collect dust.
Ma, I like
but then, when you wanna use
'em, you have to wash 'em.
Rob, let me call you back.
Hand me the bread. I'll start
breakfast.
Oh, no, I had coffee.
Decaf.
Half a cup of decaf.
Okay.
Eggs.
Why are you wearing a suit?
Well, I'm working.
From home, but I'm working.
Were you going to make
Shepherd's pie?
I thought I would.
Yeah, after I make you
breakfast,
I'm gonna fix something for
lunch and dinner.
Her friend Maria put a skull
and crossbones on her arm.
What does she think she is, a
pirate?
Oh, Mrs. cleary, there you are.
- Good day, carmelita. - Good
day, monsignor.
Can I talk with you about the
home visit next week?
Oh, yes, of course.
The archbishop is a go.
We have confirmation from the
pontifical council.
- How exciting. - Yes, it is.
It's put us all into a
pressure cooker.
The archdiocese wants to make
sure our choice is beyond
reproach.
That's why it's so important
the home visit goes well,
to ensure you're our choice.
Everyone should be there,
frank, frank Jr., Shannon.
The grandchildren.
Well, Shannon isn't feeling
very well.
I don't know if she can make
it.
Oh, that could be tricky.
Well, if she can't make it, be
sure and explain why.
Talk about her church duties,
what her fianceé does.
She's not officially engaged.
What is it with young men
these days?
What are they waiting for, the
second coming?
- Hey, ma. - Yes.
Dr. chen wanted me to ask you
about your hysterectomy.
Why?
Well, she thinks it might be
relevant to my condition.
It's not.
Well, you sure, because you
were pretty young?
She just wants to know if my
condition is hereditary.
I didn't have that short
cervix thing.
So what did you have?
Shannon, some things are
personal,
and best left to prayer.
What is this?
That was a gift.
Is there anything that you
want to ask me?
Hi. We're home.
Oh, my, what did you get?
It's from my sister in Miami,
for the baby.
It's a little early for that,
isn't it?
In my family, we celebrate
Christmas in July.
Oh, my god. My feet are
killing me.
This one schlepped me all over
town
looking for decorations for
the wedding.
Oh. Somebody's getting married?
Angela and I are getting
married
next Sunday.
Lou and I, we insist that they
have a cer...
A party, really,
but being that the baby's
coming and all that...
We would love for you and
frank to be there.
I didn't mention it because i
didn't think
that you would come.
Of course you'll come.
Possibly. If it's after church.
Open it.
- Do you know what it is? -
Uh-uh.
I have no idea.
( All exclaiming )
Oh, my...
That's beautiful. Are those
diapers?
It's so cheesy. It's cute,
it's cute. We'll use it.
The call to marriage is woven
deeply into the human spirit.
What makes a nun an expert on
marriage?
If you would like to hear
bishop Reynolds' lecture on
marriage
and the complementarity of the
sexes,
here is all the information.
I highly recommend it.
It's about time
I see our time is up.
Oh, please remember, it is
girl scout cookie season.
Our parking lot will host
several tables this weekend.
Make sure you use the rear
parking lot
when you come to mass this
Sunday.
Mrs. cleary, does monsignor
Murphy have
your letters of recommendation?
Not yet, but I'm sure he will
soon.
See that he does.
Yes, sister.
I have to go deliver meals to
the homebound.
Oh, I'm done with all that.
Megan O'Donnell's mother's
finally died,
so she's got the time now.
And giving her back her route
really is the only Christian
thing to do.
Did you hear that my youngest,
Peter's, been promoted to
lieutenant?
- Congratulations. - Thanks.
And Michael was promoted to
captain.
Of course, frank Jr.'s a
captain, isn't he?
- No, he's a lieutenant. - Oh?
Speaking of frank Jr.,
what is Patty's secret for
keeping him so well-groomed?
What do you mean?
Well, my cousin owns the real
estate office
just right across the street
from Theresa hennessey's salon.
She said that she saw frank
Jr. there nearly every day this
week.
And I can't even get Carl to
trim his nose hairs, so what is
her secret?
I wouldn't know.
Have a good day.
Oh, sorry.
All right, so have you, um...
Picked a color yet?
Okay. That's a nice color.
What did you do, ma?
We just talked.
Oh, you just talked.
She not only broke up with me,
she decided to close the salon
on Sundays.
Theresa's not a catholic, is
she?
Is that what this is about,
- that she's not catholic? - (
Turns vacuum off )
It's about, she's not your
wife.
All right, just stay out of my
life, ma.
You are ruining your life.
You never even liked Patty.
This is about you.
I don't want you walking
around with regrets.
- They eat at your soul. - How
do you not see
that my whole life has been
one long regret?
One stupid night.
You have to live with the
choices you've made.
I had one thing...
And she meant something to me.
I was just gonna do the same...
Wear it the same way I wear it
every day.
- Oh, honey. - What?
- I could do it for you. - I
wanna look like myself.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you get my message?
You nearly had a miscarriage.
You have no business playing
baseball.
I'm just watching Angela's
soccer game, ma.
You should be in bed.
The doctor said it's okay as
long as I sit.
Did you make me a fruitcake?
You have to go home now.
Well, I'm pretty sure if we
play the game there,
someone will knock the pans
off the wall.
This is not a joke.
Ma, ma, calm down. I feel fine.
Well, you shouldn't have
walked here.
Oh, Eileen, she didn't. I
drove her.
I was going stir crazy.
We thought if she got out in
the sun, it would be good for
her.
Well, I guess it's all right
then.
Ma, why don't you release the
fruitcake
and sit down?
No, I can't stay. There's so
much to do
with the bishop's visit.
- Oh! - Sorry.
Ang, it's almost game time.
Okay. Put it over here.
Oh, honey, don't put it there.
Ants. Over there.
Here, put it on the chair.
Have a good game.
She's worried about you.
* your mother loves you
what are you doing here?
Lookin' for you.
Shannon said you went home,
but I knew better.
She should not be here.
Ah, you're a doctor now?
She could be hit in the
stomach by a baseball.
Yeah, that's unlikely in a
soccer game.
Well, no balls should be
around her.
Oh, you... you're sick.
Let's, uh...
Let's go for a walk.
I'm watching Shannon.
Okay, let's watch Shannon.
We have to talk about this
wedding.
Why?
I don't understand any of this.
Maybe you don't have to.
You think we should go, don't
you?
I do.
It's probably at some woman's
commune.
Worse. It's at Christina's
house.
Oh, god.
The cleary clan!
Hey! I love what you're
wearing.
- Hi! - Hi.
This is so beautiful.
Eileen.
You look fantastic.
Oh...
Frank, how about a hand, huh?
You wanna eat? There's plenty
of food in there. Welcome.
Welcome, welcome.
Father Joe, this is frank and
Eileen cleary.
Shannon's parents.
Lovely to meet you, Mr. and
Mrs. cleary. It's a privilege
to be here.
Thank you, father.
Father Joe will be performing
the ceremony.
Woman: Christina!
You'll notice that my full
name isn't in the program.
It's kind of a risk for me to
be here.
It's also an honor to
participate in
Angela and Shannon's holy
union.
Mrs. cleary, I wanted to
actually give you my card,
in case you ever feel like
talking.
Would either of you like
something to drink?
Frank's a drunk.
Don't look at me.
He asked to be left alone, I'm
leaving him alone.
( Processional music begins )
Please be seated.
This is an occasion of great
joy.
We gather to witness the
exchanging of vows
between Angela and Shannon.
As I pray that god invokes his
blessings on the couple,
I invite each of you to
quietly, and in your own way,
also pray that god blesses
Angela and Shannon
and their intentions.
In the presence of god,
and loving friends, do you,
Angela,
take Shannon to be your spouse
and your partner in life?
I do.
In the presence of god and
loved ones and loving friends,
do you, Shannon, take Angela
to be your spouse and your
partner in life?
I do.
May I see your rings?
I declare these rings to be a
symbol of your sacred vows.
Shannon...
I give you this ring as a
symbol
of my commitment to you.
May it remind you always that
you are surrounded
( voice echoing ) By my
eternal love...
And devotion.
( Shannon's voice echoing )
Angela...
I give you this ring as a
symbol of my commitment.
May it remind you always
that you are surrounded by my
enduring love
and devotion.
Father Joe: You may now
exchange a kiss
as a sign of the sacred
sacrament.
Are you okay?
No cuts.
Come on. Let's go get you
dried off.
Here you go.
- Thank you. - Oh, not a
problem.
It's all good.
How do you accept this?
Shannon is a lovely girl.
It was really hard for me
when Angie first told me.
But that's normal.
You should talk to father Joe.
Oh, he was a big help for me.
He's a catholic priest.
Father Joe believes
that we all do the best we can.
What does that mean?
Come join the party,
get cleaned up,
'cause I can't wait to see you
in my track suit.
You look nice in that outfit.
( Huffs )
You know, they've taken quite
a few cruises,
and say they're a great
vacation.
- Who? - Christina and Lou.
Ah! Bless, o lord, and
sanctify the flesh of this bird.
In Jesus Christ our lord. Amen.
Amen. You know, on a big ship.
Christina said the food is
wonderful.
They go to great places,
and there's dancing every
night.
What are you talking about?
A vacation.
- A vacation? - Yeah.
You know, like we used to.
Vegas, Reno, Italy.
We never went to Italy.
I know that.
But you always wanted to go,
remember?
Hmm? You wanted to see the
David,
visit Rome.
All those beautiful churches.
That was a long time ago.
Yeah, but we could go, Eileen.
I'm saying we could go.
It would be good for us.
It would've been good for us
20 years ago.
I know.
You wanna go on a vacation.
Our family...
Is falling apart...
And you wanna take a cruise.
You liked it before,
Eileen, when I was drunk,
running around?
Our children shared nothing
with us.
Shannon is havin' a baby.
This should be the best time
in our lives.
All right, frank.
All right.
Don't forget the circulars at
the end of the driveway.
Can't that wait until you get
to the office?
This isn't work stuff.
This is us stuff.
What is it?
Well, she's gonna need a safe
place to play,
but I wanna keep the open feel.
Oh, carpets.
Play mats.
Aww.
I think it looks perfect.
Yeah.
Yesterday was a nice day.
Yeah, for everyone except my
mother.
Why are you so hard on her?
You didn't grow up with her.
My mother threw me a party
when I got my first period.
She invited all the relatives,
even the men.
Mortified.
I'd be happy with mortified.
At least I'd know that she was
invested in our lives.
She's trying.
( Door opens )
Mrs. cleary, let me help you
with that.
Oh, no, I've got it. It's fine.
Okay, I should get going.
Well, Angela, I wanted to show
you
these freezer bags.
You take a portion, and zip it
closed,
and then, just put it in the
freezer.
Okay.
Yeah, like these.
Wow. That's amazing.
Well, that way, if I can't
come by for some reason,
you and Shannon will have
plenty to eat.
Well, thank you. That's great.
It's convenient.
It meant a lot to the both of
us
to have you at the wedding.
Bye, baby.
Bye.
It's nice you're trying with
Angela.
Are you feeling okay?
I'm good. Ma, I'm good.
Today is the bishop's home
visit,
so I won't be back this
afternoon.
Do you want me to come?
No. No, it's too far for you
to travel.
Frank and Patty and your aunt
Mary will be there.
The perfect family.
Good luck, ma.
Thank you, Shannon.
Just stay calm.
* you've been far away from me
*
* another land across the sea
* and all this time, my heart
has been breakin' *
* just waitin' round and
achin' for *
* a letter or a telegram
* tellin' me how sweet I am
* you swear your heart will
never roam *
* so till you come back home
* I'll wear your colors, my
dear *
* till you're standin' right
here *
* next to the one who adores
you *
* whose heart is beating for
* like a lighthouse guides a
shipwrecked sailor... *
would you take this junk and
hide it?
They'll be here in two hours.
There's nothing wrong with
being in a.A.
I don't want the committee to
know you're an alcoholic.
Eileen, I drank for 25 years.
There is no one in this town
unaware that I'm an alcoholic.
Are you crazy?
* realize this love is strong
*
* as it has been all along
* for miles and miles can't
come between *
* the kind of love we've seen
*
( exhales loudly )
Oh, don't touch. Don't touch
that.
Where the hell is he?
Patty will get him here.
- ( Doorbell rings ) - Oh!
Hi, mom. I'm home.
- Frank! - ( Frank Jr.
groaning )
Jesus, Mary and Joseph!
What are you doin' drunk in
the middle of the afternoon?
Who cares what time he drinks?
The bishop is gonna be here.
What, they're not here yet?
Bishop!
Frank, what are we gonna do?
- Uh... bring him to the den.
- I am here
oh, bishop! ( Laughs )
- Put a sock in his mouth. -
Okay.
Is my lezzie preggy sister
here?
On your feet.
One of the guys at the
firehouse told me
those babies are called
Turkey-baster babies.
- What? - ( All talking at
once )
- ( Doorbell rings ) - Oh, my
god!
- They're here. - ( All
exclaiming )
- Turkey-baster babies. -
Yeah, it's funny.
- ( Laughing ) Turkey
baster... - Yeah, yeah.
- Whoa, whoa. - Gay-bies!
Hey, when did you get here?
Oh, god!
Frank Jr. followed in his
father's footsteps.
Both hero firemen.
Thank you, monsignor.
Frank got a medal of valor for
saving an entire family
in an apartment fire.
Mm, by the favor of the
heavens.
We should do good deeds for
the glory of god, not to get
medals.
He didn't save those people to
get medals, sister. It was his
job.
Uh, would you like to see some
family pictures?
Oh, yes.
This is frank Jr.'s wedding
picture.
( Thudding sound, frank Jr.
groaning )
What was that?
The, uh... the plumbing.
Isn't it lovely, your eminence?
Yes. Is this your daughter?
No. That's our son and his
wife.
Where's your daughter's
wedding picture?
There's no husband.
No, but she's dating a very
nice young man,
and we expect to hear that
they'll be married soon.
Would you excuse me a moment?
Well, what's the young man's
name?
Your eminence?
The young man's name.
What young man would that be?
The young man your daughter is
about to marry.
They're not officially engaged.
Regardless, he has a name,
doesn't he?
- Angelo. - Antonio.
Angelo Antonio. He's one of
those people
who has a first name for a
last name.
Like my friend.
She had the maiden name Riley,
and she had a brother, John.
Well, her daughter married a
man with the surname John.
So she named her daughter
Riley.
So she had a brother, John
Riley,
and a granddaughter, Riley
John.
( Weak chuckling )
Oh! I think that went well.
Bishop Donnelly is a good man.
He seemed to focus on the
positive.
What was positive?
My work for the church.
Our beautiful home.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Do you remember when Shannon
was a baby,
how people used to stop us in
the street?
She had those blonde curls,
big, blue eyes.
Why are you talking about this?
It's always the same word.
She's... she's perfect.
Not cute, not adorable.
She's perfect.
Frank?
I can't live like this anymore.
Like what?
Well...
We could start with the lying.
Oh. What am I supposed to say?
My daughter is a lesbian,
and is having a Turkey-baster
baby?
I'm not just talking about
today, Eileen.
Oh, I don't think you want to
talk about the past, frank.
I'm sober now.
Things could be very different
for us,
but no. See, you're stuck.
Stuck in the way it was.
Oh, let me tell you about the
way it was, frank.
I put up with your crap for 20
years.
I held this family together on
my own,
and I never once considered
leaving you.
Maybe you should have.
* there was a house halfway
around the world *
* and I was invited in for a
small taste of gin *
yes, could I...
Please speak with, uh, father
Joe MacDonald?
* cage too small
uh, yes.
* I asked the caretaker 'cause
he was the maker *
* looked at me and laughed
* took another sip from his
glass *
* he said, open up your ears
and heart *
* you put a big bird in a
small cage *
* and it'll sing you a song
* that we all love to sing
along *
Mrs. cleary?
* to the sound of the bird
that mourns *
* put a big bird in a small
cage *
* and it'll sing you a song
* you put a big bird in a
small cage *
* and it will sing you a song
*
before we discuss our luncheon,
Agnes Dunn would like to
update us on the petition drive
to stop gay adoption.
Who's adopting gay people?
No one is, Greta.
It's the gays that are trying
to indoctrinate our children.
Nun: Mm, yes.
The law currently states that
gays can adopt children.
But we are working with the
catholic league
of religious and civil rights
to gather signatures to put
a "protect our children"
initiative
on November's ballot.
Is this really where we should
be focusing our energy?
Well, we know where you stand,
miss "i have a gay big brother."
Yes, I have a gay brother
and I am going to start the
petition,
and once we all have signed it,
we will then circulate it
among the congregation.
Well, then, let us move on
to our catholic woman of the
year luncheon.
As you all know, both Agnes
Dunn and Eileen cleary
have been nominated.
However, there's only one
honored,
and to receive sacramental
absolution
from the sacred heart of Jesus.
To quote Matthew 22:14,
"many are called,
but few are chosen."
Wonderful. Wonderful.
- Oh, what are you doing? -
Ma, it's okay.
You can't handle anything
toxic.
It's a green product. It's
non-toxic.
Why didn't you tell me daddy
left home?
We had a little fight. He'll
be home soon.
But he's never left you before.
Shannon, everything is all
right.
- Ma. - Nothing is wrong.
You're working too hard.
We've gotta pay for the baby,
ma.
This baby is yours. No one can
take it away from you.
What are you talking about?
Just that I'm glad you're
having the baby.
It's yours. No one can dispute
that.
No, this baby is mine and
Angela's. We planned it
together.
Well, I know that, but some
people don't understand.
Some people.
Who doesn't understand, ma?
Some people at the church have
started a petition
against gay adoption.
Okay.
Most people think that a baby
needs a mother and a father.
Just because you've chosen an
alternative lifestyle
doesn't mean people accept it.
I don't care what those people
think.
I signed it.
You signed the petition?
How could you do that?
What if I don't agree with
your lifestyle?
You just assume I'll accept it.
- What about accepting me? - I
don't petition against you.
That was Agnes Dunn's idea,
not mine.
But you signed it. You signed
it.
What is it about my life that
you find so reprehensible?
- You're living in sin. - Says
who?
The pope.
Well, what do you think?
I don't have to think. I'm a
catholic.
I don't know why I'm still
surprised by you.
I raised you in the church.
Why don't you understand?
I do.
Damn it.
That's why you have to leave.
I don't want my baby around
you.
* look out the window
* it's all horizons and halos
*
* holding a moment
* healing the scars so they
don't show *
* someone say something to
crush all the noise *
* that surrounds us
* if I catch a bullet
*then maybe we can make it
through this *
- oh... - Ah, Mrs. cleary.
Thank you so much for meeting
me here.
- I'll see you next week. -
Oh, thank you.
Sorry for not introducing you.
Anonymity is the spiritual
foundation
of all our traditions.
Oh, I understand.
Can I get you anything?
No.
Why don't you hold these
meetings in your own church?
Oh, I don't lead these
meetings. I attend them.
There was a sense of urgency
in your message.
I asked my sponsor if I could
use the room to meet with you.
Glad you called.
I just meant because you
didn't show up the last time.
I'm sorry, father.
Uh, let's have a seat.
So, how can I help you?
I've made a lot of mistakes.
We all struggle from time to
time.
What if it's all the time?
I think you're being a little
hard on yourself.
No. I'm not.
Why don't you tell me why
you're here today?
I've been nominated for
catholic woman of the year.
The archbishop of Dublin is
flying over
to sanctify the winner with a
prayer of absolution.
That's a great honor.
I want it so badly.
I sacrificed my family for it.
You think the church wouldn't
approve of them.
Do you?
Mrs. cleary, I think that,
uh...
God sits at the head of your
family,
and the only real obligation
you have is just to be one unit,
united in love.
I've been going to church my
whole life,
and I've never heard anybody
like you.
( Door opens )
- Frank. - Dad asked me to
wait for you.
Shannon was rushed to the
hospital.
( Monitor beeping )
Shannon.
* I've been finding puzzle
pces of us *
* kept in the dust
* I've been hiding letters and
photograph frames *
* to forget your name
* we were never meant to be
this damn broken *
* words were never meant to be
this half-spoken *
Eileen, you left the front
door wide open.
* ...The space between the
universe *
I brought in your mail.
* and all we see has gone away
*
* gone away
I'm so sorry, Eileen.
We're gonna take a walk.
Shannon's in the bedroom.
Okay.
Shannon.
I'm so sorry.
They let me hold her.
It was so quiet, except for
Angela crying.
Even a moment can be a gift.
Is that a god's will thing?
We don't know his reasons.
Really, ma. You don't think
he's punishing me for having
this child with another woman?
Shannon, you are going to be a
wonderful mother.
It just wasn't in god's plan
right now.
That's your answer for
everything.
Sometimes, these things just
happen.
To me. It happened to me.
Nothing I'm going through
could you possibly understand.
I do.
No, you never had to imagine
what you could've had.
You never had to imagine what
her first smile,
her first steps, her first
word would've been.
I have.
I had an abortion.
I don't understand.
I thought your father was
leaving us.
So all these years of spewing
all this crap,
of putting all this morality
on dad, on frank, on me.
It's not that simple.
How could you have an abortion?
I never worked.
I married your father in high
school.
I didn't even know how to
drive.
Your father came home,
and told me he was in love.
I had two small children.
What was I supposed to do?
I didn't want another child.
I couldn't have another baby
alone.
I wasn't alone. I just didn't
know that.
You just lacked faith.
So that's what I need to do,
right, mom?
Turn to god, and it will be
all right.
I don't know.
I don't know anymore.
Turn to me.
You're quiet today.
Am I?
You excited about the award?
Mrs. punch, I haven't won it
yet.
Well, you believe you deserve
it, don't you?
Mrs. punch.
I think you deserve it.
Why?
Because you show up,
every day like clockwork.
You're one to be counted on,
Mrs. cleary.
That's not an unremarkable
thing.
Ah, Mrs. cleary.
Always our most faithful.
I don't wish to disturb your
prayer,
but I wanted to know when I'd
be getting your family's
letters.
I'm sure they'll be arriving
soon.
The bishop was disappointed
the children were not able to
make the in-home visit.
The letters will be most
helpful.
Yes, monsignor.
And you should know that he
was most impressed
with your record of service.
And I assured him that your
family
is a model of honest, faithful
catholic values.
I'll leave you to your prayer.
Dear monsignor Murphy and
members of the committee:
I have been giving a lot of
thought
to what it means to win the
award,
to be recognized by the church,
and, of course, to be absolved
of my sins.
I realize now that, in order
to be truly forgiven,
we must first come to terms
with our choices,
no matter how difficult that
might be.
My efforts to repair things
begins now.
Before you make your decision,
there's some things I'd like
you to know
about my family.
Thanks for bringing me my
watch.
Mmm.
How's frank Jr. doing?
Working a lot of overtime.
Frank, what happened to us?
You married an alcoholic.
I had an abortion.
- It was when you were seeing
- I know.
You know?
You were hemorrhaging.
It was pretty bad.
The only way they could stop
the bleeding
was with a hysterectomy.
The doctors didn't wanna do it
without your husband's consent.
It took Mary six hours to find
me.
You almost bled to death.
That night was the first time
i tried to get sober.
Oh, frank.
It took me 15 years to forgive
myself.
Can you forgive me?
I never blamed you.
Uh-uh.
No.
I got a meeting to go to.
Can I go with you sometime?
( Sighs ) It's not really...
Sure.
Well, this is highly unusual.
I have glowing recommendations
from frank and the children.
Yes, but you also have a
letter written by Mrs. cleary
herself.
I think the immodesty of the
family confessions in her
letter is
refreshing.
* somehow
* I'm leading someone else's
life *
* I cut her star down
* with my knife
* and right now
* I still see the way the moon
*
* plays this tune
* though our lights died
* my hands shake
* my knees quake
* it's every day
* the same way
* 'cause then came you
Mrs. cleary.
What are you doing here?
Well, I just thought I'd get
an early start,
you know, on account of the
luncheon.
Don't you remember?
You arranged with Mrs.
O'Donnell to deliver your meals
today,
on account of the luncheon.
Oh, I'm...
I'm glad you're here.
Come here.
I'm rooting for you, Mrs.
cleary.
I am preparing a special meal
for the occasion.
Pollo con crema, my mother's
recipe.
I prepared it this weekend for
my family,
just so I wouldn't be so rusty.
Oh, you have a beautiful
family.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to meeting
your family today.
Aah!
( People talking quietly )
You hardly said a word to him.
- Who? - The archbishop.
Agnes Dunn's been circling
them all morning like a shark.
Can we all take our seats,
please?
They're not coming.
What are you talking about?
Try to enjoy yourself.
Welcome to a very special
commemoration
of what it means to be a
catholic woman.
We are exalted by the presence
of the archbishop of Dublin.
( Applause )
This year, we are particularly
blessed
to be honoring someone who
continually commits herself
to all manner of pastoral good
works in our community.
But community service alone
would not be enough.
We are lucky to have in our
parish
a woman who embodies both
faith and family.
She has been part of our
community for many years,
and in some ways, is our
community.
Her dedication and devotion
mirrors...
What are we doing here?
You're being honored.
Who cares?
Eileen?
*