*
(helicopter blades chopping)
(dogs barking)
Where the hell
is everyone?
Great, we spend two years
planning a party
and no one shows up.
There's no
question he's here.
Keep your eyes open.
*
What the...
Head shots,
head shots only.
Come on !
Get off of me !
The thing bit me.
Target spotted.
Move move !
*
I think I see
the target.
Clear.
(whimpering)
(screaming)
Clear.
(gun shooting)
Let's bag 'em
and tag 'em
and get
the hell out of here.
(man)
For god and for country,
Geronimo, Geronimo, Geronimo.
You're not
lookin' so good.
(coughing)
Bravo,
are you all right ?
Bravo, what's going
on, are you okay ?
(man)
What's
going on back there ?
Stand down, stand down,
soldier !
Ahh !
Hold your fire,
hold your fire.
In 20, going down,
in 20, going down.
(screaming)
(man)
Hold on !
Thanks for bringing me
out here.
Hey, let's go swimming.
I am not swimming.
Oh come on,
don't be such a baby.
Baby, come on !
*
(gasping)
Ana ?
(roaring)
(phone rings)
(heavily breathing)
*
What's up, doc ?
What ?
What you mean, what's up ?
Nice doc, five minute
mile in full gear.
I was being chased.
How many ?
To be honest, Captain, I didn't
get an accurate head count,
'cause I was
running for my life.
DC, get some eyes on.
Odds aren't terrible.
What does
that mean exactly ?
Means you'll have plenty
of chance to use that.
Be more specific,
Lieutenant.
I'd say four to one,
roughly a hundred meters,
closing fast.
That's what
I'm talking about.
Are you serious ?
What ?
It's hot out.
It could be snowing
and you'd be hot.
That is a terrible
pick up line, but, yes,
I will go out with you.
Eat me, Chippendale.
Me and everything
else out here.
(laughing)
Juliette 6-4,
Juliette 6-4.
This is Juliette 2-5 over.
Why aren't there any
Walnuts in Afghanistan ?
Ah, hell.
Why ?
'Cause there's targets
on every corner.
(man)
Go ahead 2-5.
6-4, this is 2-5.
We have twenty Class D
hostiles moving to our position.
Request authority
to engage, over.
Affirmative.
Predator ETA two minutes.
Roger, ISR, two mikes out.
Look alive, gents.
Look alive ?
Oh, the irony.
On me.
Hoot !
Enjoy your
unlimited virgins, mis amigos !
What ?
I don't mean you, tomboy.
I hate you Carol !
You're a pain in my ass !
Just had to have
the dog, didn't ya ?
We good here ?
What do you call a guy
with no legs...
... and no arms ?
What ?
Matt.
*
You have fallen
in with the wrong crowd.
Your mom warned you about
friends like this, right ?
Save some for me !
Fighting zombie
insurgents, fine by me.
(Doc)
A little help ?
Killing infected
civilians, it makes me sick.
Can't kill something
that's already dead.
Even if I get infected,
consider me a goner.
And kill the
zombie that took my place.
*
Take it easy,
DC, save some for me.
Do you like that ?
Yeah.
Hey, you can't
shoot the tip.
That was totally mine.
*
Ah, this sucks.
(exploding)
Where's Kate ?
(man)
1-9-3-7.
Slew in target
cords now.
On target 1-5-3-1-zulu.
We're all right.
We don't know the status
of the captain,
God rest his soul.
Permanently, I hope.
Certainly takes the fun
out of things, doesn't it ?
Captain's wearing the comm's
gear and radio.
So we're fubar in
that regard.
(Joker)
* Swing low sweet chariot
Now is not the time.
We have seventy-two
hours until show time.
I say we proceed
as planned.
Any bites, scratches,
blood intake, et cetera---
(growling)
Uh... uh-uh-uh...
(gun shooting)
I guess you only
live once, right ?
Or twice.
You know we can't
let that happen.
Tell Thayden I love him.
Rottweiler.
Okay, then.
Well, carpe diem...
... sempre phi and all
that other crap.
I'm sorry, Herc.
Yeah.
How much time we got ?
He hit an artery.
Five minutes, tops.
Let's get this
show on the road.
Who's gonna do this ?
Jeppo ?
Sorry, amigo.
You see Chip I'm thinking of a
number between
one and a hundred---
Sorry, man.
I'm only killing the
undead right now, buddy.
Joke ?
Rock, paper, scissors ?
All right...
but if I win, you gotta
figure it out yourself.
Fair enough.
One, two, three.
Rock beats scissors.
Two out of three.
Why does everybody
think that's part of the game ?
Come on, two out of three.
One, two---
I'll do it.
I figured you'd do
the same for me.
Thanks.
I'm not gonna watch.
Finish the mission.
Whatever's going
down the brass feels it's big.
Find the militia camp,
Stop the broadcast
and send as many of these things
as you can back
to hell.
Make it count.
*
(gun shooting)
Here
you are, Asif.
Shochran.
Aswan.
It's Asif.
I didn't say Asif ?
How do you say it ?
Ah-- sif.
Good enough, right ?
I'm sorry.
(growling)
Did you hear that ?
No.
(speaking foreign language)
You know
what, you're right.
Sorry, you'd think after a
couple weeks here
I wouldn't be so jumpy.
So these are the mountains of
the Registan Desert.
(speaking foreign language)
Yeah.
Still no sign of Derek.
Not to worry,
we'll find your brother.
Thank you, Asif.
When the embassy
wouldn't help me,
I didn't know what I
was gonna do.
(speaking foreign language)
I'm happy you're --
(growling)
You heard it that
time, right ?
Stop, stop.
Nothing to be afraid of.
Ahh !
Help me my
friend's been hurt !
Ahh !
Help !
(Doc)
Hold your fire !
I'm from Colorado !
Drop your weapon !
I said drop your weapon.
I'm American.
Do not make me count because I
will not get past one.
You all right ?
Yeah.
It hit the vest
you're good.
Perimeter static for
fifty meters,
anything beyond
that is anyone's guess.
Everyone keep
your ears on.
I think I killed my guide.
Once he was bitten,
he was already dead.
If anything
you did him a favor.
Loser.
Yes.
(Chip)
He's gonna be fine.
Doesn't mean it
hurts any less.
Believe it or not,
he was wearing his vest.
It's a Christmas miracle.
That's gonna leave
a mark.
You should be dead.
Who are you... What are you
doing out here ?
You take a wrong turn
at the trail heading to India ?
My name is Dusty Miller.
Ahh !
(gun firing)
Pleased to
meet you in one piece.
DC, take corner !
My bad.
I'm not sure if you're
fully aware
of what we're
dealing with here,
but if you so much as
get a scratch
from one of these
things, you're dead.
Might not be a bad idea
if I check you out.
What ?
Scratches and bites.
Your safety and ours.
Your chivalry is
overwhelming, Chip.
If anyone's gonna be
checking her out,
it's gonna be tomboy.
Now remind me,
who are you ?
And what are you doing out
here in the middle of BFA ?
I'm trying to find my
brother, Derek Miller.
And he is... ?
Or was.
He is trying to end
the war on terror.
Well cheese and rice.
A gosh darn
freedom fighter !
Let me guess.
Business went up in
flames back home,
blamed it on the
war,
decided to solve the
world's problems
all on his own.
Probably bought a couple
of cheap weapons,
maybe a sword.
And tried to grow a beard.
You know, to fit in ?
Definitely a beard.
Probably still thinks
bin Laden's alive.
All right, listen up.
If it's all right if our
house guest here
solidify the perimeter
and hole up for the night.
This place is
as good as any.
*
Zombies.
Must not have
eaten for awhile.
What do we have here ?
(growling)
*
We may wanna start thinking
in terms of agua .
My map says there's
water maybe a mile out.
Let me see.
Yeah.
This is as good as ours.
Yeah, yours probably cost
about half a million dollars.
Close.
DC, Chip, you guys
wanna hop ahead ?
Make sure we're not
walking into an ambush.
Roger that.
Copy.
See you, boys.
So, um, what's
going on here ?
Can you be a bit
more specific ?
Okay, uhh...
how about the walking
dead to begin with ?
Some run.
That's classified.
I think your secret is
safe with me
considering none
of us are probably
going to make it out
of here alive.
She's got a point.
Speak for yourself, Joppo.
I plan on living in a
living sort of way.
Um, isn't el chapo a
new Mexican drug lord ?
Isn't dusty
an adjective
for something
covered in dust ?
I wasn't trying to
be rude.
That's better than
yelling cabeza .
Slow... slow !
Getting a little soft.
That's not what
your mom said.
My mom's dead, man.
Ugh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
She lives in
Toledo, sucker !
Can you at least tell
me where we're going ?
Classified.
From the outside looking
in, it seems like
everything is
so classified.
None of you have any
idea what you're doing.
What does your brother
know about bin Laden ?
Well, for starters, he doesn't
think he was thrown to sea.
He's wrong.
Well, he still
thinks he's alive
and after
what I saw last night,
he can't be too
far off.
What aren't you
guys telling me ?
After the 9/11 attacks,
Bush pledged to win
the war on terror
by providing
increased weapon transfers
to all countries willing to
join America in the fight.
Enter Godsmack.
Godsmack was a biological
agent used to push
the militants out
from the high ground.
It was designed to contaminate
the natural water resources,
thereby forcing
the militants out of hiding.
Everything was going
as planned--
Until small man syndrome kicked
in from one of the piss ant
countries we sold
the stuff to.
Every country
has its Napoleon.
Who's ours ?
Well, there's Bill
Bonaparte, George Bonaparte.
Both George Bonapartes.
(speaking Spanish)
Those are the kinds of
guys that sign our checks.
And there's
Barack Bonaparte.
That one actually has
a nice ring to it.
It also increases
resale value.
Someone was bulking the
formula by adding other
biological agents to make
a sort of biochemical cocktail.
The combination had, let's
say, unexpected results.
It went from being a
relatively harmless nausea,
that temporarily contaminated
the water
to an active carcinogen
that create acute
biological mutations.
Acute biological mutations
as in, the living dead ?
Give that woman a prize.
As far as we know
the pathogens are regionalized.
Most of the outside
world has no clue.
Yeah, for now.
If it's anything
like Facebook,
it'll be in
Panama by next week.
I love Facebook.
(raspberry)
Now it's an
aggressive contagion.
And as far as we know, it
can only be transferred
by direct exchange
of bodily fluids.
Could you be a little more
specific on fluids, doc ?
Blood.
Unless you wanna do
your own research.
I'll pass.
The Department of Defense
has been monitoring
the militia camp for months.
Something big is going
down in less than 48 hours.
Detail was sketchy,
but intel suggests
there's gonna be
some heavy hitters.
(Dusty)
Do you think bin Laden's
still alive ?
It's not in our
pay grade to even ask.
Minimum, plus time and
a half on weekends.
And I'm super happy
about that.
But he could be, right ?
We've all considered it.
But how are they dealing
with the undead ?
I mean, they don't
seem too manageable.
They might be using them.
For what ?
For every few militants we
wipe out,
they get a few of ours.
Remember, there were
several hundred thousand
NATO boys and girls
occupying this hell hole
not too long ago.
But after somebody farted
under the covers,
the slumber party was over.
Everyone went
home in a hurry.
Confucius say, man who
fart in church
must sit in his own pew.
No one wanted to risk the
spread of the contagion
on their own country.
So all that's left is a few
lucky units of Special Forces
from a few
NATO countries.
We're American flavor,
with a squeeze of limey.
So... where's all
your support ?
We lost contact
with the OD a day ago.
Yeah, this is getting
better and better.
Well at least you're not
dragging around a civilian chick
with a mullet looking for
her retarded brother.
We have a rendezvous
point established
with overhead in two days.
My guess is we'll find
the militant's
stronghold before then.
I knew that my
brother was crazy,
but none of this makes
any sense.
When has terrorism
ever made sense ?
We and a few others are
the only things standing
between the people of
Afghanistan
and a zombie apocalypse.
Whether it makes sense to
you or not,
it's a hell of a mission.
One that we all
signed up for.
(man)
Doc, are you guys coming ?
We found a spring 30
minutes ago.
Copy...
We're on our way.
(Tomboy)
Joker, check this !
Hey, buttface !
(growling)
(gunshot)
(Joker)
Oh !
You mean no face.
*
(distant movement)
Shouldn't you be
in school or something ?
(groaning)
Some water ?
Come on, take some.
Should call these MRH's.
Meals ready to hurl.
Got some of the baddest
weapons on the planet
and the food still sucks.
Hey, doc.
Hey, tomboy.
Okay, shifts.
DC, you're first.
And Chip, then Chapo.
How come DC
always gets to go first ?
Joker and Tomboy will
take us 'til sun up.
Circle the perimeter
and rest on the high ground.
Everyone else, get your REM's
with one eye open.
I was only kidding
about the body search.
Yeah.
You married ?
Nope.
Girlfriend ?
A couple.
But we don't usually do body
searches on the first date.
I like to always buy
them dinner first.
How long you
been out here ?
Uh, couple weeks,
including the week it
took to get here.
And you never came across
'em till last night ?
I guess I was lucky.
Your brother either owes
you a lot of money
or you must
really love him.
Both.
You know in the end,
I think you end up doing
anything for family.
I got an uncle I
never really liked.
Probably wouldn't walk his
butt across the street.
You older or younger ?
I'm younger
by a couple years.
Don't take this the wrong way
'cause I'm not a psychologist,
but, your brother fits
the profile
of a guy who's a couple
tacos short of a combo plate.
Well, you're doing
the same thing,
so what does
that make you ?
Touché.
You know my brother was
a fire fighter in New York.
He was there 9/11 and his
whole crew died
in the collapse of the
towers while he was home sick.
Wow.
Yeah.
You know he never really
got over it
and he always thought of
himself as dead already
living on cheated time
and when they caught bin Laden
I thought you know,
it's finally over
and then it just got worse.
His conspiracy theories,
his obsessions,
and I think he just, he wants
to kill him himself, you know ?
That way, he knows
that he's dead.
I just want him home.
Derek.
Deh-deek.
No, my name is Derek.
Fine, take it.
What are you doing here ?
(speaking foreign language)
I have no idea
what you just said,
but I like you.
Ooo, ooo just not
the green one.
That tastes the best.
You think bin Laden's
still alive ?
I was reading some pretty
crazy stuff on this website
a couple weeks ago.
It made the hair on
my neck stand up.
Just something's
not right.
And I won't rest 'til
I know he's dead, I mean,
really dead this time.
What I've seen, there's a
fine line between
dead and not so dead.
Lieutenant ?
Where is everyone ?
Chip ?
Ahh !
Hey, easy.
Take it easy.
We're on civilian patrol
and sounds like the fight
is getting closer.
We have to pack
and go quietly.
Okay, okay.
Stay close and follow me.
Isn't
that your family ?
They look
non-infected to me.
Go get them.
Ah-hee !
(speaking foreign language)
We locked and loaded ?
I think so.
Can you please check ?
Thank you.
By the way, you could
sleep through a tornado.
I guess I felt secure.
You were.
They've flanked us
from both sides.
How many ?
Fifty plus.
Fifty ?
I say we cast off before
they reach
Joker and Tomboy
in the rear.
Where's Chapo and DC ?
Chapo's holding the front,
DC's in the tree line
with big mama.
Carol !
That was gonna be
for your therapist !
And for your
plastic surgeon !
That was your trainer !
And whoever else
you're sleeping with.
I want my--
Well, it seems like
he's got things handled.
Let's move.
You stay here, duck
down by the rocks.
Try to shoot only what
you're sure is dead this time.
I'm not staying here.
You don't listen,
do you ?
(growling)
Oh, crap
it's a convention.
(gun clicking)
We have to get
to the tree line.
Let's move.
Haven't seen a group
this big
since they
opened a Walmart in my town.
All right.
Listen up.
We got about three minutes
to regroup before we're lunch.
How are we doing on ammo ?
Big mama's just
warming up.
Okay here.
Good n' plenty.
I love those.
Dropped my 45
in the clearing.
Yeah I dropped
my rifle too.
You guys cover me.
I'll get both.
That's suicide, doc.
I'm already dead.
I'll get the guns.
Wait.
That's for getting bit.
I was supposed
to have your babies.
You know he's
infected, right ?
Only by blood.
You better hope so.
*
(growling)
Oh man, he's
still holding the grenade.
Shoot it !
30 meters.
20 meters !
Guys !
Shoot it !
*
You gonna be
all right ?
Yeah, I'm fine.
That something we're gonna
have to worry about ?
Well left my Flintstone
Band-Aids back at base,
so this may
leave a pretty bad scar.
But if you're worried
about zombie offspring,
don't be.
You can still
have my babies.
This is what you
call friendly fire.
Well after reviewing all
the intel,
which consists of two maps,
one of which does not belong
to the US army, I think
we're close.
How close, I don't know.
Based upon our rations, I think
we should divide up
into two faster
moving quieter units
and before we start campaigning
or complaining,
let's discuss our options.
(Dusty)
I think first---
I think DC's right.
Splitting up increases
the chances of at least
one team making it to
the mission camp
and completing the mission.
Anyone got a better idea ?
Steak and potatoes
at my mama's house ?
Porcelain toilet,
running water.
We'll equally divide the
food rations
and the nine mil ammo.
Joker you take the saw and
I'll keep Big Mama,
unless you wanna trade.
I got enough monkeys on my
back, but thanks, though.
You guys take
the military map.
Get out your compasses 'cause we
have zero calm overhead.
We are on our own.
I'm estimating about
a day and a half,
maybe faster
if you're humpin'.
Do not, I repeat, do not
go so fast
that you can't
fight when necessary.
Ranger training 101.
Water resources are
highlighted on the map,
we'll rendezvous at
the objected point in 36 hours.
If you do not arrive at or
before 36 hours,
rangers, we will
expect the worst.
(Chapo)
We'll be there.
One way or the other.
Hopefully not the other.
All right, then.
We'll head due south in
the opposite direction,
but we'll be flanking you
for about the last ten miles.
Now if you're gonna get
in trouble, do it there.
Good ?
Let's move out.
* One little, two little,
three little zombies *
* Shoot 'em in the head and
wipe the brains off me *
*
(growling)
No, no, no, no !
(gunshots)
*
Did you ever think that
dead people
would be
the worst kind of enemy ?
Dead enemies were always
the best kind of enemies.
So where's all
the zombie crap ?
What ?
Zombies obviously extract
some kind of nutrients
from eating, so,
where's all the poop ?
Are you serious
right now ?
Unless there's
zombies that I haven't seen
keeling over from
exploded bowels,
they're evacuating somewhere.
I'll tell you what.
Next time we see one,
we'll flag him down
and check and see if he's
wearing a diaper.
(laughs)
Great, guys.
Maybe they're bulimic.
After a delightful meal,
it daintily excuses itself
only to return happily
for more brains.
I'd rather be bulimic
than poop my pants.
(growling)
Go ahead.
You ever seen
"Intervention ?"
Yeah, it's the
worst show on TV.
There was this one
episode where this lady
was yakkin' in zip loc bags
after every meal,
hiding them in a closet.
No !
Yep.
After a hearty meal,
she'd go in the bathroom,
say hello to her dirty
little secret,
bag it up in a
zip loc, put it in her closet.
And one day her husband
was putting his shoes on,
slides his foot into
yesterday's lunch
and cat's out of the bag.
That's assuming
she had cat for lunch.
So what happened ?
Of course they did an
intervention on her
with that crazy host lady.
You know, the one that
could probably use
an intervention herself.
They got her
all squared away.
We had to do an intervention
on my mom once.
Oh yeah, what for ?
You remember those little
stuffed animal toys,
the Beanie Babies ?
Yeah, I remember those.
She had hundreds of them.
After she filled up all
the bookshelves in the house,
she started buying special
cabinets to put them in.
At first, my dad
thought it was a good idea,
you know, give her
a little hobby.
What he didn't know was
that there was hundreds more
underneath all the beds
in the house.
So how'd it
come to a head ?
My little sister, she
wanted to take one to school
for "Show And Tell."
She just reached up one
of the bookshelves,
she didn't know what she was
bringing down, you know.
Turns out it was Paddy
the Platypus,
one of the original nine.
Oh, not Paddy.
So my sister comes home
from school,
takes it
out of the backpack,
it's got a little
stain on it
'cause all the kids were
passing it around at lunch.
She goes ballistic.
Geez.
So my dad's like, "Enough's
enough," y'know ?
"It's either us,
or the Beanie Babies."
To be honest, it took her
a little while to decide.
(laughs)
(Joker)
Nice, Tomboy.
Nice.
Feel better ?
Yeah, a little.
Check the pants ?
Who's Carol, anyway ?
I mean, I don't mean to pry...
it's just I heard you
yelling her name
in what seemed to be
like a hate filled rage
over and over.
I loved Carol
my whole life.
Operative verb tense--
loved.
Well, maybe you still do,
that's why it hurts.
Somewhere in the recesses
of the heart she ripped out ?
Doubtful.
All Carol does is motivate
me to kill things
that should already be dead.
But you loved her.
Well, how could I not ?
She gave me her juice box when
I was in Kindergarten.
She doesn't
seem that bad.
She was like a foot taller
than me.
I mean, she used to make me so
nervous my hands would sweat.
Maybe she just
felt bad for me
because I never had
enough money for school lunch.
You grow up poor ?
No, I had
a Pokémon problem.
Mom gave me money for
school lunch
and I used to spend it
on Pokémon cards instead.
Carol bought me school lunch
every single day
all the way up
through eighth grade.
Well, she doesn't sound
that bad to me.
Well, prescription drugs
do funny things.
I mean, she was so beautiful--
she just never saw it.
I don't know if it was
the screwed up relationship
she had with her dad-- Man,
that guy was a tool--
Or maybe some people are
just born that way I don't know.
But no matter how many
times I told her
how beautiful she
was, it never sank in.
I guess it didn't help
I was gone all the time.
She knew that going in.
Well according to her therapist,
I have all the blame.
Yeah, well next time
some rag head decides
to park a 747 in the lobby of
a ninety story skyscraper,
a therapist will be
the first on my call list.
It wasn't his fault.
I mean, the over abundance of
crap he was prescribing
for her didn't help, but
her damn plastic surgeon.
Sleeping with him ?
Knocking boots.
Horizontal hopscotch.
Bumpin' uglies.
Thank you, Chip.
Point is, there wasn't a
whole lot of sleeping going on.
Turns out the road between
patient to bed buddies
isn't very long.
How long did
they know each other ?
Huh-- Let's see.
After the nose job she
absolutely didn't need.
Then Botox for the crow's feet
that I thought were sexy,
maybe two months.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
And then all the Prozac and
whatever the hell else
she was taking, combined
with the fact that I was gone,
combined with the fact that
doctor was whispering
in her ear the whole time.
I guess we both
just changed.
And that's
when DC was born.
You mean reborn ?
No, he means born.
My name is Ryan Parker.
DC has nothing to
do with my initials.
What's DC ?
Well my best friend called me
that after I spent a year
in divorce court.
It got so ugly.
Not because of me, dude--
I gave her everything.
I know--
I was there.
It was the dog
we argued over.
She hated that thing until
she knew I wanted him.
That sucks.
Yeah, anyway.
Joint custody.
Weekends and Christmas.
(grunts)
(DC)
I doubt he'll
be getting back up.
That's nice.
One less we have
to kill again.
Well what do you think
he was doing out here alone ?
Maybe that was his friend
dining on him.
Doubt it.
The one I shot's militia.
What's left of
this one, civilian.
Not that--
What the...
His throat's been cut.
Nobody move.
This guy's wired.
You think he was
wired before ?
Looks like an IED.
I doubt it was Hannibal
the Cannibal here though.
What's the point ?
Whatever it is,
we fell for it.
Slowly step away.
Retrace your steps.
Yeah, real slow.
Incoming !
Move, move, move !
This is actually
kind of nice.
Humans shooting humans...
More like the war
I'm used to.
Son of a card !
Hey, DC, you ok ?
I think I picked
up some schrap.
(grunting)
All right.
Let's take five and
get our bearing.
I'm going to take one.
A number one.
Do you take a number one or do
you leave a number one ?
Sounds like a
personal decision.
I'll leave it.
Looks like we're coming up
on some hostile territory.
No, really ?
I thought this would be a
great place for a summer home.
There's no indication of
this road on the map
but its clear they used it
for transport at one point.
Yeah, maybe there's an IHOP
at the top of the hill.
You know,
what's your deal, Huh ?
Whoa !
Joker ?
Yeah I know.
It's platter charge.
Never deployed.
How many of those
have we walked by ?
Man.
It's a Tupperware party
from Hell.
All right, well... uh.
Let's very carefully retrace
our steps and head back
the way we came.
Man !
Looks like the party's
still in full swing.
Where are
these guys coming from ?
That one's gonna hit
a bomb.
Hit it !
Yes !
(guns shooting)
Chapo, we got to move !
Hold your position unless
you want to go kaboom !
(grunting)
Guys, what are we
gonna do ?
Chapo !
I'm open for
suggestions, Joker !
We gotta move !
All right, it's better than
staying for dinner.
Either way,
it's gonna end bad.
Just watch your step !
(Screaming and shooting)
That was awesome !
Whoa !
Watch where you're
pointing that thing.
Who the hell are you ?
Derek Miller.
And you shouldn't
be on this road.
Chances are there's
road-side bombs on it.
You don't say.
You could have gotten
yourself and us killed.
You wouldn't be complaining if I
didn't show up when I did.
The man's got a point.
We know who you are.
Your sister's with
the rest of our unit.
My sister ?
She's here ?
Looking for you.
I didn't think she'd come !
Apparently stupidity
runs in the family.
We had to save her.
Albeit, the same way
you just saved us.
I guess that makes us even.
Yeah.
Except you have no
business being here.
I'm helping to
fund this thing.
Why shouldn't I be here ?
Because you're gonna get
yourself killed, Mr. Miller.
Yeah ?
You guys want
to ride somewhere ?
Uh, not on this road.
Come on !
*
(shouting Arabic)
What do we got ?
Glass !
Cheap mothers !
Guns are way more effective.
File a complaint.
What are you doing ?
You want to bleed out ?
You couldn't think
of anything else ?
Nothing came to mind.
Let's see what we got ?
(grunts)
Yeah, that's in deep.
You may want to
leave this in.
You out of your mind ?
If it hit an artery and I
pull it out, you're screwed.
I'll take my chances.
All right.
You better
bear down then.
What does that mean ?
Like you're having
a baby or something.
I don't know
what that means !
You know what ?
Just clench your butt cheeks
cause this is gonna hurt
like a son of a--
(screaming)
It's definitely
an artery.
If you bleed to death,
I'm going to be really pissed.
Any better ?
No.
Guys, we have
a serious problem.
Here, chew on these.
Don't get comfortable--
It doesn't' sound like
we're staying long.
Anything else ?
Yeah-- Don't die.
What do we got ?
That's our exit.
Come on !
(shooting)
Hey !
What's the last
thing I said ?
I'm not dead yet.
You're going to hate me, but
we got to move now !
I can't.
Hey, hey, hey !
Look at me--
Look at me !
Do it for Carol,
all right ?
We're all going to die
if you don't leave me behind.
You are so negative !
Come on !
Dusty, grab my pack and gun !
Stop being such
a baby.
You know I'm right.
We leave no man behind,
weren't you listening in
boot camp ?
Dusty, if anything gets
within ten feet
put a bullet in it.
(grunting)
So what do you know ?
I know this whole thing would
be a little easier
without the flesh eating ghouls.
I mean what do you know
about where you are,
what your destination is,
what you plan to do
once you get there, Superman ?
Pretty sure I'm still in
the Registan Desert
at least that's
what the map says
that I downloaded from
Google Earth.
Six dollar
compass may be cheap,
but it's still
pointing north.
So my destination
is militia camp
where I think
they're hiding bin Laden.
And yes, he's still alive.
So my plan is to kill him
when I get there,
before we have
to wait another ten years.
Although I'm thinking about
bringing him in alive,
I think the bounty on
him would still be pretty good.
Would go a long way
in paying for this
expensive vacation of mine.
I don't know how
you guys got here,
but my, uh, coach ticket
was two thousand bucks.
I haven't even heard
of another bounty.
I mean, most of the free
world has no clue
what's going on.
Oh.
Well, that sucks.
What makes you think
he's still alive ?
You're telling
me that he's not ?
Truth is,
we don't know.
I know.
How do you know that,
living in Colorado ?
Let me know if you want
to talk about
the two hundred fifty
billion dollar in bail out.
That didn't do anyone
any good.
I got some
thoughts on that one, too.
Oh, I'm sure you do.
How about we talk about
this militia camp ?
Like why you even think
it's there to begin with ?
And why you think bin Laden
might be there ?
I took this off of a guy that
obviously can't read anymore.
Yeah-- No question that
this is Intel
on the militia camp.
But who's there is
anyone's guess.
Even we're guessing.
You guys do that a lot.
But you're trying, which
is all anyone can ask.
Look, the road that
we're on was not on my map.
Okay-- It's not on
any maps.
But it is on this one.
So someone went to great
lengths to cover it up.
And my guess is
that anyone that stumbles
on this road would get a
butt full of hello.
Great name
for a band.
So we must be
close to a town.
No.
No, there's no town
on here.
So where are all the
civilian zombies come from ?
Well, it's my personal opinion
that they're making them.
Well we know
they're making them, genius.
No, I think they're bringing
uninfected people
into the camp and
they're holding on to them
until they need them
to eat people.
I think the altitude
has gotten to you, amigo.
Most of them are prisoners,
but I think some
come willingly,
you know, in the name of Allah.
Suicide chompers.
Estás loco .
You're crazy.
Well I mean, if you
think about it,
it's really no different
than a woman walking
into a crowded market
with ten kilos of C4 packed
in her baby's stroller.
Makes sense to me.
Well, not really, but why not
send in a suicide bomber
that has a bomb
that doesn't just go off once,
but over and over and over ?
So what makes you think
bin Laden might be there ?
What makes you think
he isn't ?
(grunting)
Sorry.
Dusty, can you
grab that ?
Little help here, buddy.
We still gotta make it
up that hill.
(DC)
Then what ?
I don't know, I'm not
a cruise director.
Can't feel my leg.
That's cause you have
a bottle of Coke in it.
I'm not gonna make it.
Remember that weekend we came
home from munitions training
and Carol had all your
stuff across the front yard ?
Damn yard sale.
It was all your
stuff, too.
She had it priced good.
She sold my alligator boots.
I bought three pairs of jeans.
Parker.
Get up, Parker.
Get up, soldier.
I can't.
We're almost there.
Come on, come on !
(Dusty)
They're coming !
What else is new ?
Shoot 'em.
We're going to have to find
some water if we're going
to get this thing
running again.
Pee in it.
Ain't gonna happen.
I went an hour ago.
Well, I'm empty--
We leave it.
Leave it ?
It's a perfectly good truck.
Put a for sale sign
on it.
Somebody
will come along.
No, we wait around
a bit.
We'll find water.
What do you want us
to do, a rain dance ?
Hey, pack it up.
I don't want to be
here when it gets dark.
We got to at least
take this gun.
Oh sure, as long as
you want to carry it.
Never mind.
What ?
One here, one there,
they weren't using them.
Don't shoot yourself in
the foot, Captain America.
Don't shoot
anyone in the foot.
(Chip)
Come on,
almost there.
(Dusty)
They're coming up fast !
I got one !
You with me, buddy ?
Huh-- Parker ?
(grunting)
Yeah, I know.
Just tightening
my shirt.
I got to go
in here and clear this,
but then I'm coming back
to fix your leg
I promise.
Okay ?
You have my gun ?
All right, let's go.
Stay with me, buddy.
(Dusty)
This can't be
a good idea.
(Chip)
It's not.
We're clear.
What do you think
they're on line for ?
Who knows ?
They're crazy.
Eight trillion dollars worth
of untapped natural resources
here and no one can seem
to get past the oil.
I think I'd rather take
my chances out in the open.
(growling)
I think
you're right.
Let's get out of here.
(screaming)
Just run !
Chip !
Get out of here !
(Chip)
DC, we're coming !
Get out the way !
Here !
I got you, I got you.
It hurt.
They don't call it
Big Mama for nothing.
All right.
Let's get your leg fixed.
I just want to lay
down for a second.
Just let me lay here.
We can do that.
I really
want my dog back.
Okay.
We can do that.
Bark.
Stay with me, man.
Stay with me.
I always loved her.
I know.
Oh God.
DC.
*
(Chapo)
Zombies
and insurgents.
Flank out.
Keep your eyes peeled.
Lock and load.
Shoot anything that's
alive or zombie-fied.
What did the zombie eat after
he got his teeth pulled ?
I don't know-- what ?
The dentist.
(laughing)
Shut your mouth.
You might as well send up a
flare while you're at it.
Sorry.
But you just
gave me the best idea.
I don't know if these
things can smell this
but this is the best we
can do for now.
And then what ?
When we get square,
we come back for him.
What are you going
to do with these ?
These rightfully belong
to his ex-wife,
but that ain't gonna happen.
Uh, how'd he
carry this thing ?
There's movement down there.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait-- Derek ?
Derek !
I can't' believe
you're here !
Derek !
You're so stupid !
Come on.
Why doesn't it surprise me
you're not wearing a shirt ?
I'm going to have
to borrow one.
Give 'em a little taste
of their own medicine.
Anything that decides it
needs a breath of fresh air,
it will most certainly be
its last.
Again.
(Chapo)
Will you go grab that guy ?
The idea of a civilian
covered in guns out here
peeing by himself makes
me a little nervous.
Where would you
like me to grab him ?
That's up to you, amigo.
He's done okay
this far.
Well I guess you
can choose to be offended
by that comment.
Or you can see it
as a gesture of caring
that I don't want another
American to die out here.
Especially not
under my watch.
Thank you, then.
Hey.
Would you
put those away ?
That one, too.
Sorry.
Hey, check this out.
No question.
Seems like a
lot of extra effort.
Pays off.
I'm wearing DC's dog tags
to prove it.
So they slit the throats,
wire them up,
hoping to
draw in the opposition.
When the booby trap
doesn't work,
they send in
the second string to eat them.
Sounds right.
We must be getting close
to our objective.
We'll make the
final push at dawn.
Derek, what
are you doing here ?
What am I doing here ?
I'm doing what
needs to be done.
You need to come home.
No.
Yeah, I thought about, for
weeks, what I was going to say
to you when I found you and
I realized none of that
really matters
because you're stubborn
and no matter what
anyone says to you
it's never going to
change your mind.
Remember when we were kids,
and the weatherman spoke about
the wind chill factor ?
And you always thought
he was talking about the
wind chill factory ?
And you said it's always
colder in the wind chill factory
because it's in Alaska ?
It is always colder in
the wind chill factory.
No matter what anyone says to
you, you're never going
to change your mind.
If you don't want to
for yourself,
will you do it for me ?
If you care about me,
will you come home ?
Because I care
about you, I can't.
*
Are you okay ?
Are you ?
(laughing)
Dusty !
Run !
(Dusty)
If you saw Derek,
why didn't you stop him ?
(Joker)
I'm not his babysitter.
He's a grown man.
If he wants to get
eaten, he can get eaten.
I don't care if he doesn't
value his own life,
but he's going
to get us all killed.
No offense, Dusty, but
being this close
he's probably already dead.
And if not, there'll probably
be a ticker tape parade
waiting for us
when we get there.
Let's go.
I don't think he's dead.
Thanks.
It's the back door.
(speaking foreign language)
(gun clicks)
(groans)
(grunting)
Thank you "Call of Duty."
(screaming)
*
(Dusty)
Wish my brother wasn't
so stubborn.
(Chapo)
You're confusing
stubborn with stupid.
(Tomboy)
Geez, Chapo do you
ever stop ?
(Joker)
Cut him some slack.
He was never asked to
a dance in high school.
Still eats him up inside.
So what's eating
you, Tomboy ?
(Tomboy)
I'd kill for an hour
on the beach right now.
Yeah ?
Do you like to rollerblade ?
Never been.
(Chapo)
I love rollerblading.
I used to go every
weekend back home.
You know what the hardest
thing about rollerblading is ?
Probably, uh,
learning how to stop.
It's telling your parents
you're gay.
*
(grunting)
Stay or go ?
(Chapo)
We're running short
on time.
We got to get there
before the air strike.
Move out !
(shooting)
(screaming)
(Chapo)
What do we got ?
Looks like someone
let the dogs out.
Derek's been here.
(screaming)
Stay tight.
Shoot anything
on two feet.
Joker, take Big Mama.
Thought you'd never ask.
I'm gonna flank the perimeter,
see if I can find an opening.
Chip, not a good idea.
The sooner we secure the cave
the sooner we know exactly
what we're dealing with.
I'll find a radio
and call HQ.
It's a death sentence.
I knew that when
I enlisted.
I'm coming too.
Like hell you are.
My brother
might be there.
Along with everything else.
I'm coming.
It's her life.
All right,
don't be long.
If our birds actually show up
we don't want to be
anywhere near this place.
I only need a few.
Stay close.
Let's give him some cover.
Wake up Big Mama.
She's awake.
I gotta
remember this room.
(Chip)
Watch your head.
*
Get them !
(screaming)
(radio playing static)
We're in business.
(whispering)
Dusty-- What are
you doing ?
That hat almost got
you killed, bro.
Come on, we've got
to get out of here.
I've called an air strike--
We have to leave now.
This is the end of the
cave as far as I can tell.
This is the last room.
(grunting)
I knew it.
We got to move.
We got to go now !
(Derek)
Oh I hate
being in the back !
Go, go !
I'm right behind you !
Tomboy, down !
Joker !
Where's he hit ?
I don't know--
Looking for the entry.
Well get the vest off !
Just what
I need, right ?
Another pie hole.
Yeah, well
shut both of them.
Put pressure on it.
Put your hand here.
Stay with me, Joker.
I mean it.
I don't
have anything.
So, there's
a murderer, right ?
He's sitting in an
electric chair.
He's about to be executed.
"Any last requests ?"
asks the chaplain.
"Sure," says the murderer.
Will you hold my hand ?
(crying)
That was the worst
joke I've ever heard.
They're all bad.
I'm going to miss you.
I'm going to miss me, too.
Damn you !
Where's Derek ?
He was right
behind us.
We have to go
back and get him.
Dusty, there's no time.
The strike's coming now.
Just in time to blow
out the candles.
Die !
Who crapped their pants ?
(heavy breathing)
This is what
I've been waiting for.
Go back to hell
you son of a--
*
Bring in the rain-- we gotta
get out of here.
(Dusty)
Derek !
We've got to move.
(man)
Target neutralized.
Pick up our boys
and bring them home.
Guys, we got a straggler.
(Chapo)
Shoot it,
I'm too tired.
You have got
to be kidding me.
Derek ?
Derek !
Oh !
It's over.
I got him.
You're so stupid !
Was it worth it ?
Yeah.
Nothing left
of the bastard.
I got to say,
I'm kind of jealous.
Amen, brother.
The man who did the deed.
(Tomboy)
I don't know about you guys,
but I'm due for a leave.
(Chip)
Yeah, I could
use some time off.
What are you doing the next
couple of months ?
I'm available.
(Dusty)
I'd go
to Alaska if you go.
Alaska it is.
You might have to wear a shirt,
it's kind of cold out there.
Hey, well he isn't
coming with us, is he ?
I don't know.
Derek, do you want to go ?
Please no.
(Derek)
I wouldn't mind seeing the
wind chill factory up there.
*