I believe you are sincere
and good at heart
If you do not attain happiness always
remember that you are on the right road
try not to leave it. Above
all, avoid falsehood
every kind of falsehood,
especially falseness to yourself
teach us something useful
Watch over your own deceitfulness and
look into it every hour, every minute
avoid being scornful, both
to others and to yourself
What seems bad to you
within yourself will grow
pure by the very fact
of you observing it
-this is ridicilous
-we're paying for this
you're a disgrace
Avoid fear, though
fear is only the
consequence of every
sort of falsehood
Never be frightened at your own
faint-heartedness in attaining love
Don't be frightened overmuch
even at your evil actions
I am sorry I can say nothing more
consoling to you, for love in
action is a harsh and dreadful thing
compared with love in dreams.
Love in dreams is greedy
for immediate action,
rapidly performed and
so everyone can see
Men will even give their lives if only
the ordeal does not last too long but
is soon over with all looking on
and applauding as if on a stage
But active love,
active love is labour
and fortitude
Dostoyevsky
so what was that all about?
that's what we're here to discuss
but you never discuss anything,
you just ask questions
we've been stuck on the same
paragraph for a month and a half
it's an important paragraph
read it
i believe you are sincere
and good at heart
if you do not
attain happiness
always remember
you are on the righ road
try not to leave it
a bove all, avoid
falsehood, every kind of
falsehood, especially
falseness to yourself
watch over your own
deceitfulness and
look into it every
hour, every minute
by the very fact of
your observing it
-what do you make of that?
-it's good advice man
-is it?
-you tell me
i don't know
but you're the teacher
i teach literature,
i dont give advice
you're wasting our time
i'm asking you questions
we're supposed to
ask the questions
you're supposed to
give us the answers
perhaps its not as
important to know
the answers as it is to ask
the questions better
there you see he told us something
no he didnt he just asked
us another question
Never be frightened at your own
faint-heartedness in attaining love
Stop that!
what is father Zossima
trying to tell this woman?
I'm warning you man
is it possible to appreciate this advice
if we aren't faithful?
tell me something! tell me something
thats gonna help me pass the final exam
what do we mean when we use the word faith?
two coffees please
you can't beat up students beacause
they don't like Dostoyevsky
perhaps
-can you give a ride to town today?
-sure
are you okay?
Air's too cold, sun's too bright.
this coffee although i haven't had
any yet is undoubtedly too strong.
i wanna lie down and evaporate
you're having a crisis of faith
-No i'm not
-Yes you are
Henry i'm an atheist
maybe you only think
you're an atheist
-i'm in pain
-all pain is desire
Is that criticism or advice?
i think its Buddhism
-Henry?
-yes?
-i'm in love
-no really?
yes i think so
how can you tell?
lack of concentration
erratic mood swings
faulty reasoning
obsessive behavior
its not like you to go running off
after young women
i'm not running off after anyone
i'm falling towards her
-as if you cant help yourself?
-yea something like that
i see, i've read about this type of thing
and then there's this
love in action is a harsh and dreadful thing
compared with love in dreams
is this an active
love or a dream?
it's a dream about
to become reality
name the proofs of this reality
a thoughtful gesture,
delicate smile
white slender neck
an earnest inquisitive and alluring voice
greacful figure, intelligent sensuous eyes
-describe the nature of the dream
-intimacy
name the constituent elements of intimacy
kissing, caressing, holding
slapping, shouting, talking
waiting, sleeping, crying
listening, hoping, incouraging
forgiving, laughing, volanting
in a word: verbs
and therefore active
oh i feel much better now
waitress are settling much prettier
than i first came in
ambient shadows less irritating
daylight is not threatening me anymore
it's just there
filling the street for
no apparent reason
a mistake perhaps but in
any event i'm not afraid
-glad to hear it
-check please
how do you proceed?
to live just move forward
towards those you love
-intriguing theory
-no an impeccable truth
but knowledge wont
help where you're going
what will?
-faith
-you mean love
no faith
whats the distinction between
faith and love?
love without faith is merely a infatuation
infatutaion
such a beautiful word
my friend you're doomed
perhaps, so why do you
need to go into town?
-i've been thrown out of school
-No
well what are you going to do?
i dont know maybe i'll get a job
-well if there's anything you need just ask
-thanks
-so i'll see in the parking lot at 4
-okay
well here goes
desperate, his
frustration spills
no bursts forth
thats better
his frustration bursts
forth into audacity
he says as fast as he can
whatever he feels
he says as fast as he
can whatever he feels
he feels hurt and speaks pain
i like that very
direct, passionate
he feels
he concludes
he likes you
-who?
-your literature professor
oh yes i know
you shouldnt get mixed
up with him people will
think you sleep with him
to get a better grade
people are disapointing
let me intruduce you to Mark
i dont want to get involved
with anyone right now
why not?
because i'm busy
i have a lot to study and i'm
enjoying it, working hard
but Mark is so good
looking and he likes you
-he fascinates me a little
-Mark?
No my teacher
Really?
there's something sort of tragic
about him don't you think?
he's name is Jude like in Jude The Obscure
-he looks half mad
-he's in love
Men are pathetic
i think he's kind of charming
in a way
i write about him
what do you write about?
different things,
speculate, study him
i'm going to write a short story with
him at the center or some one like him
Him that's what i call it
Him
-i'm doing laundry tonight
-me too
do you want to split a
bottle of detergent?
okay
thanks for the ride
where you gonna stay?
oh i have some friends
who will put me up
-i'll see you later
-see you around
marry me? come on
excuse me sir but will you
take my hand in marriage?
-come on get outta here
-marry me please
to love and to cherish
would you get out of the street?
what are you looking at?
square.. bug off
excuse me sir but will you
allow me to be your wife?
-please!
-here
don't want your money
to love and to cherish
hey you marry me
come on
somebody need any help?
somebody need any assistance?
can i help some one?
somebody need any help?
my manager says you either
gotta buy a book or leave
listen to this
ignorance is the necessary
condition of  human happiness
we're almost entirely
ignorant of ourselves
absolutely of others in
ignorance we find our bliss
in illusions our happiness
i write down all those
questions you ask in class
you do?
i take them home and re-read the
chapters you've assigned, it helps
- what does?
- asking the questions
how?
submitting all i read in the book
to that ongoing list of questions
somehow it shows
it shows how consistent
his concerns were
Dostoevsky
it does huh?
before i began asking
those questions over
and over again of the text
i was having a hard time
i couldn't see what he was getting at
i kept hoping he get back to the story
and then what happened?
the questions focused my concentration
i'm getting more out of my reading now
does anybody work here?
i can't say i intended to teach you
anything but i'm glad it helps
but they're your
questions you asked them first
i asked them for
different reasons
what reasons?
the book seems alive
you seem alive
that book there seems alive too
things you're reading are
having an effect on you
me? i read
i understand, i appreciate
but still i'm left unchanged
i can't put into actions
what it is i understand
shouldn't knowledge
provide solace?
i don't know
perhaps i don't
understand anything
do you have anywhere to go?
you've been in here for hours
when do you get off work?
8 o'clock
can i drive you back to campus?
no thanks i take the bus
will you have a drink with
me before you take the bus?
okay but only if you leave now my
manager will yell at me if you don't
okay the bar on the corner?
do you wanna buy the book?
nah books don't help
to love and to cherish
what's that?
it's coffee and a muffin
what's this suppose to mean?
it's not suppose to mean anything
you can't get something for
nothing you know mister
no not usually i suppose
just because a guy buys
a girl a cup of coffee
doesn't mean she has to
jump into the sack with him
look i'm putting it over here
why buy the cow when you
can get the milk for free?
what?
that's the truth
about things mister
look it's right here see?
coffee and a muffin okay?
to love and to cherish
marry me
excuse me?
let me be you wife
i'm sorry
to love and to cherish
hey professor you waiting for somebody?
yeah a girl
pretty girl?
yes. a pretty girl
and young too i imagine
what's it to you?
you admire her inteligence
as a matter of fact yes i do
and you're impressed with
her charming combination
of unassuming conscientiousness
and girlish naivete
so what if i am?
trouble with us americans is we always
want a tragedy with a happy ending
hey i need a beer
- Hi
you want a drink?
a beer please i
have to make a call
a beer
Joe it's me Sophie
i won't be home for an hour
so sorry something came up
i'll do my laundry
tomorrow night
i'm at a bar with some friends
girlfriends
bye
do you like your job?
it's okay i get a discount
on my books it helps
do you like yours?
not really i'm bad at it
are you bad at it because
you don't like it or
do you not like it
because you're bad at it?
do you think i'm a bad teacher?
i have learn things in your class
you're a better student
than i am a teacher
that's because you give me
more attention than the others
that's true
does that bother you?
no
to tell you the truth
when i feel i'm teaching well
when i'm making myself clear
when i'm actually incouraging a
student to think specifically
and articulate
more appropriately
when i feel this
i'm usually thinking of you
does that embarrass you?
a little
when i'm reading that really
excites me for instance
i want desperately to
share it with some one
it's you i wanna share it with
why me?
it's complicated
no it's not
it's not?
it's because you
think i'm pretty
perhaps
i'm sorry it doesn't change
the fact that i care for you
you hardly know me
that's true i hardly know anyone but i
know how i feel even if i don't know why
would you like me to tell
you something about myself?
if you want to
i appreciate being taken seriously
but i'm always concerned
that i'm not
sufficiently serious
i know men look at me and think
i'm alright but i think it's
contemptuous to utilize that
fact in order to achieve something
but if had to i'm afraid i might
and that bothers me
i'm very curious and i'm
afraid of seeming gullible
so i'm argumentative more
than i think i should be
what did you lie to your roommate
you were out with some one else?
if people knew we were out
together they would say
i was sleeping with you in
order to get a better grade
- but we're not
- not what
sleeping together
not yet anyway
one..two..three..four
five..six..seven..eight
- i don't like this song
- i love the video
can you turn it down i have to study?
- that guy called again
- what guy?
- you the one
- the one you like?
with the long hair
- did he ask you out?
- yes
- but i said i was busy
- do you think he'll call back?
definelty
i wish i had legs like hers
i wish my breasts were smaller
do you like this dress?
i like that one better
i'm going to write a novel
- now?
- no someday
can i help someone?
somebody need any help?
somebody need
any assitance?
can i help someone?
somebody need any help?
- you weren't in class today
- i've missed you
i've missed you too
it was terrible i
didn't know what to do
i overslept
my class is a 2 o'clock
in the afternoon
let's not argue
i'm not arguing i'm concerned
are you eating alright?
look i'm a grownup person
- can i see you tonight?
- perhaps
what's that suppose to mean?
it's what you always say
- is it?
- yes perhaps
when do i say that?
well for instance whenever you don't
want to admit that you're wrong
you always look away
and say perhaps
- no i don't
- yes you do
i always admit when i'm wrong
that's not true
yes it is i cherish my flaws
ah you see that's another
thing you always do
what is?
whenever you're losing an argument
you always depict yourself
as hopelessly incompetent
as if humbly admiting
your shortcomings
somehow places you above
the argumentative hand
there for negating the other
person's point of view entirely
you're pretty thorough
honestly observent
- i'm pretty flattered
- i'll make a note of that
you haven't answer my question
what question is that?
- can i see you tonight?
- perhaps
i've gotta go call me
- Henry
- oh hi Jude
what are you doing here?
i work here now
- no kidding
- yea
great job, all these books
boss doesn't like
me too much but
i always had a problem
with authority
what are you doing here?
oh i came to see Sophie
ahh Sophie
Sophia that's greek you
know it's means to know
i'll keep that in mind
but she's got a boyfriend
- no she doesn't
- sure she does
lots of 'em, they're in here everyday
she flirts with them constantly
no she would've told me if she
were involved with some one
- why?
- why what?
why would she have told you?
because she would have wanted me
to know we are close you know
- how close?
- close
- do you sleep together?
- no not yet
so you're just friends
we're a little bit
more than friends
Jude you're deluding yourself
you don't know anything about it
a man'll throw all his heart won wisdom
toss away years of aquired knowledge
all for what? a pretty face
well what is all your
deligent cynicism and
years of intellectual
inquiry gotten you huh?
a job in a bookstore
- piece of mind
- what?
or atleast something
approximating piece of mind
you don't live in the real
world henry you live in books
and ideas you're a victim
of theoretical abstraction
hey i struggle with my
demons as much as you
but are they
really demons?
all distractions are demons
you know my biggest fear is this
that all my hard work
all my good intentions
all my studying have
been nothing more than
bulding of a wall
between me and life
- extacly
- what?
you must withdraw from life
don't be stupid i wanna embrace life
to know about life sometimes
you have step away from it
oh yeah? listen to this
''yet, every now and then, there would pass
a young girl, slender, fair and desirable
arousing in young men a not ignoble
desire to possess her, and stirring
in old men regrets for ecstasy
not seized and now forever past''
he is quiet
yet opinionated
powerful but shy
i need new clothes
thoughtful and impetuous
- i hate this video
- i like this song
the lead singer is hot
he looks mean and insensitive
do you think i should
make my hair blonde?
not untill summer
i wanna lose weight
is Marguerite Duras a lesbian?
god i hope Mike calls me back
he is solemn despite himself
reckless and hell bent
freightened of his own carelessness
that's a pradox
- hello?
- get outta here
it's my mother
how are you?
Jude?
i'm a wreck
excuse me?
i'm excited too excited to sleep
- where are you?
- on a street
in town?
i've been walking for hours
i had to walk, think i'm
gonna walk all night
why don't you come out
and walk with me?
what's come over you?
i can't get you out of my head
i'll drive up to campus and pick
you up we stay out all night
- i can't
- why not?
i've got classes tomorrow
i've gotta study
so what! i wrote a poem for you
a poem?
- yea
- really?
yea i was at a bar
i was possessed, inspired beyond
belief i grabbed a napkin
scrolled it out in one
huge burst of creativity
beautiful poem really beautiful
and then i spilled my bear on it and
now i don't remember how it went
meet me at the cafe in an hour
- Henry
- Jude
ive decided i'm joing
the priesthood
you always say that when
you've had too much to drink
yeah this time i mean it
what about your job
at the bookstore?
i got fired
jesus Henry monastery is
probably just the place for you
think so?
you are socially retarded
i march to the beat
of a different drum
you got any money?
i don't need money
i got conviction
well here this will help
sustain your conviction
you know Jude that's your problem
you don't believe in anything
that's a problem?
ofcourse it is
it seems to me the people who
believe in things are the problem
how do you mean?
people who bomb embassies usually
insist that they believe in things
rival terrorist organizations machine gun
women and children in the supermarkets
because they believe in things
elected officials shut down
hospitals and then vote for
increases in the defence budget
usually because believe in things
no i rather not
believe in things
but what's the alternative?
man can't live without faith
he can live without faith he can't
live without understanding
faith comes after
understanding
and how do you suppose
one gains understanding?
through exprience
ah you wanna achieve spiritual
end through materialist means
that's your problem
Henry leave me
alone you're drunk
you won't listen to reason
no i won't listen to
reason not tonight
- but you must
- don't try and stop me Henry
you'll never survive this
how do you know?
besides i don't
know if i want to
are you okay?
i don't know maybe i'll
never be the same again
but who cares?
kiss me
why did you tell your roommate
it was your mother on the phone?
- i told you why
- but it's different now
how is it different?
it's understood that you're not
here in order to get a better grade
isn't?
well yes it is
between us
no one else matters
i'm embarrassed
of me?
i don't want to seem like somebody i'm not
to who?
to myself
you should go
i don't want to
you don't know why you're here
people often do things
they don't understand
it doesn't make
them less genuine
maybe
do you want me to go?
no
are you sure?
yes
i'm going to undress
okay
do you think i'm very beautiful?
yes
if you never see me
again after tonight
will you be sad?
don't worry about it
yes but you know
will you be tortured by the
memory of having been with me?
of having caressed me
will you wonder if
i'm with other men?
will you be jealous?
will you become obssessed?
will you carry your disappointment
around with you forever?
will you be maudlin
and anti-social?
will you get into fights?
will you expect other women
to be somehow more like me?
my mouth my eyes
the way i wear my hair
will you? will you be
like that you think?
perhaps
it's the nature of
things you know
regret
i'll risk it
hey will you marry me?
please
why do you wanna marry me?
why not?
i can think a lot of reasons
if i weren't so drunk
why are you so drunk?
i don't know,
nights are too long
the nights are too long because you
have no one to share them with
that's a very compassion
way of putting it
- marry me
- but i don't know you
what does that matter? does
anyone really know anyone else?
ah that's a good point
i'd go a step further and ask does
anybody really know themselves?
exactly
what's your name?
Katy
- glad to meet you Katy, Henry
- how are you Henry?
wasted
so what do you say
will you marry me?
well i doubt we can get married right
here in the middle of the night
- we could if we were in Reno
- yea
god i wish we lived in Reno
let's sleep on it
no way mister why buy the cow when
you can get the milk for free?
- what?
- you know what i mean
we don't have to
sleep on it together
why? don't you think i'm beautiful?
Katy you're a goddess
listen pal don't waste my time
there are plenty of men out there
who died trying to marry me
i don't doubt it
listen why don't we just get
engaged for the time being?
- engaged huh?
- yea
that way i can find us a place
to live get set up right and proper
why don't you
have a place to live now?
no not exactly
what about a ring?
a ring?
a ring if we're gonna get engaged
you gotta give me a ring
oh ring here, it's my college ring
oh god
- it's beautiful
- it's a little big on you
oh no it's just perfect
henry thank you
aw it's worth just to see
you smile like that Katy
so do you have a job?
a job? ahh no not at the moment
i'm working on my PhD
you're a doctor?
of theology. almost
what are you gonna do when
you get out of school?
ooh i don't know i've been in school all
my life i don't know how to do anything
well i hope you don't
expect me to go
and support you for the
rest of your life?
already with the nagging
what a torturous path
i've made for myself
shackling myself to you
oh Katy now don't get so upset
all newlyweds have these
little battles we'll survive
- you think so?
- absolutely
you're a good man Henry
Ah Kate come on let's go
home and get some sleep
- okay i know a place
- good
his weaknesses
are enduring
his strengths
threathen to eclipse
my own self confidence
he eats out
a lot
- hey aren't you?
- no
- yes you are
- no i'm not
- but last night
- what about last night?
you were with him
no i wasn't
i'm sorry perhaps i'm mistaking
perhaps
i just saw your girlfriend
Sophia
she claims not to know you
- no
- yes
NO
afraid so
i don't understand
there's nothing to
understand we're animals
"Eros is a bad and fickle little godhead"
does this thing still work?
i hate when she does that
today's the first day of spring
that's no consultation
boy i must've been hammered
last night i woke up in a strange apartment
somehow i managed to
lose my college ring
eat your toast and get out
- no love is free
- what?
freud said that
don't start with me Henry
heard a fascinating statement
in a movie last night
you don't seem to be aware
of the pain i'm expriencing
- excuse me?
- forget it
- it's biblical
- what is?
the statement, "love
does not discriminate"
i don't follow
and the people asked him saying:
"what shall we do then"
- that's Luke
- chapter 3 verse 10
- so?
- "so the apostle replies
love and cherish unquestioningly
whoever happens to be before you
Love does not discriminate"
I'm no apostle, Henry
Take it easy, it was just
something I heard in a movie
Listen pal, you can't
waltz in here, use my toaster
and start spouting universal
truths without qualification!
what's that?
what?
you smell that?
oh yeah
she's left her fragrance here
that's it. Get out!
- what about my toast?
- Get out!
- Scram
- what?
why did you do that?
i'm upset i guess
idiot
why do you deny me?
i don't wanna get involved
with anyone right now
i'm busy
studying working hard
and i like it
why do you need what's
between us to be seen?
i don't
i need it to be acknowledged
this is embarrassing
what are you writing?
it's part of a story
can i hear it?
no
read it
he is desperate and his
frustration mounts to overflowing
before giving way to his
final and audacious mistake
finaly he caves in
gives up
and takes what is offered because he
knows he can because he knows he wants
he lacks faith and
therefore patience
the giving of himself has left him
empty and old before his time
that's very interesting
but i think it should be a woman
what do you think?
go on read it as a woman
she is desperate and her
frustration mounts to overflowing
before giving way to her
final and audacious mistake
finaly she caves in, gives up
and takes what is offered
because she knows she can
because she knows she wants
she lacks faith and
therefore patience
the giving of herself has left her
empty and old before her time
just don't
damn
excuse me miss
what do you want?
i want you to be my wife
what?
i mean it. marry me. please
why should i marry you?
well why not me?
listen mister i'm
already engaged
see? this is an engagement ring
that's not an engagement ring
that's a college ring and it
belongs to my friend Henry
Back off pal
i don't know anyone named Henry
this is an engagement ring
a significant emblem
a potent piece of jewelry
and it's mine
but i thought you
wanted to get married
i just wanted somebody to ask
Fyodor Mikhailovich Dostoyevsky
born in moscow 1821
his father was a
drunken brute of an army Surgeon
who treated his sowers horribly
so he... they murdered him by pouring vodka
down his throat till he gagged
Fyodor had some success
with his first novel but
then he was arrested for
subversion against Tsar
after 8 months in
solitary confinement
he was led before a firing squad
he stood there in a death shroud
facing an open and hastily dug
grave awaiting his execution
then some one decided he
didn't need to be shot
so for the next 4 or 5 years he did hard
labour in some cold siberian prison
it was there in siberia that he
began to suffer from epilepsy
finally 10 years after being
dragged away in chains
he returned to Saint Petersburg
he converted to a conservative and
profoundly religious philosophy
nevertheless he was
utterly destitute
an alcoholic and a
compulsive gambler
he married Anna Dostoyevskaya
and wrote atleast 4 of the
greatest novels in history
i have nothing else to say
i can't teach you anything
class dismissed
Knowing is not enough
pal you alright?
yeah i'll be okay
just let me rest my head here in
the gutter for 5 or 10 minutes
i'll be alright
i'm sorry to bother you
what is it?
can you tell me how to get
down to the river from here?
does anyone need any assistance?
anyone need any assistance?
can i help someone?
somebody need any help?
someone need any assistance?
can i help someone?
somebody need any help?
someone need any assistance?
can i help someone?
someone need any help?
does anyone need any assistance?
can i help someone?
Subtitle by:
AleeReza