Where's the damn negotiator?
-They said 10 minutes.
-10 minutes?
They're all gonna be
dead in 10 minutes.
Sir, I think we got company.
What the hell
is he doing here?
I don't know. Son of a bitch
thinks he's a hero now.
Well, he's gonna
get us all ki...
Look out, Jack!
Hold your fire!
Get down!
No, Jack! No!
No!
Jack!
Don't leave me, Jack!
Don't leave me! Jack!
No!
Cut! Cut! No!
That's a cut!
Cut! Cut! Cut!
Are those the lines?
Is that the script?
Give...
Colton!
Hey, man, are you okay?
I think I hurt my back.
You were so good, man.
I know why I quit acting now.
Yeah. Everything looked
just fine to me.
You looked fine to me.
Let me rub that back for you.
-Good job, Marty.
-Come on.
Come on. Come on. Let
me rub that for you.
What happened to the scene?
What happened to the comedy?
Well, I changed
a few things, kid.
You changed some things?
You can't do that. Were
you gonna tell anyone?
Well, you know, I...
Wasn't working for me.
It might be
a little too funny.
Yeah, it was too funny.
Yeah.
Too funny? It's
supposed to be funny.
It's a comedy.
It's called "Clown Cops."
Yeah, well, my friend...
You came out of
a pizza cop car.
My friend just got shot, Joshie.
It's a flesh wound.
He lives.
Yeah. I mean,
you seen the scene.
Have you read the scene?
Have you read the script?
Yeah, I have,
but my character hasn't.
You know, in my opinion,
it should be
more serious, I think.
You think? No, you're
not paid to think.
You're paid to act,
I'm paid to direct,
and it's
not going well.
I'm gonna have
to tell the studio.
I don't want to have
No.
Joshie, no, no, no.
You know what it is?
I'm... I'm crashing.
That's the problem.
I'm crashing.
-Are you okay?
-Low blood sugar!
Chair!
Chair! Chair! Chair!
I'm telling you, I'm no good...
Where's Kyle?
Maybe I need a salad
or something. Kyle!
-Kyle!
-Yes, Mr. West.
Kyle! Lips! Lips!
Quickly! Quickly!
Well, okay.
Kyle, where's that salad,
the kale salad from Lou's?
There was a problem,
Mr. West.
A problem?
Your credit card
maybe was declined.
-Who knows? I don't...
-What?
This is very lovely.
Just go get some food.
Get your blood sugar into
just a nice comfy place...
-I need something.
-Thank you.
-And then you come back here...
And then read the freaking
scene as scripted!
I promise. I pro...
This is nice.
This is
a nice sport coat.
Barney's?
Where's this from?
It's from my grandfather.
It's beautiful,
really beautiful,
-lovely.
-I'm sorry I snapped.
It's okay.
It happens.
-Just read the scene.
-It's moviemaking. Okay.
All right, people,
we're resetting!
Back to one!
I'll be better!
I'll be better.
I swear I'll be better.
What happened?
What happened with the credit
card? How'd it get declined?
Well, there were several
suspicious charges...
What?
In Fort Lauderdale.
Fort Lauderdale? Who's
in Fort Lauderdale? I...
Gee. Look, just call
the credit card company.
Approve the charges.
Get my kale salad,
and do s...
You're so muscular.
-Yeah.
-Looks nice.
You're working out.
-Sort of.
-Good. Okay.
Yeah.
I'm not.
Fort Lauderdale?
Who said I was
in Fort Lauderdale?
Your best friends,
Amex and Visa.
Hey, will you pass me
that mango colada?
Hey!
That's not code name
for a science book?
Mango colada?
No, it's a beverage.
Well, that's alcohol,
and it's Friday.
I'm 21, and I'm parched.
Besides, we didn't
have class today,
so we have
a three-day weekend.
Some of us
went to the beach,
so stop freakin' out.
I'm not freakin' out,
okay? Look,
I'm supposed to be looking after
you while your mother's gone.
How am I supposed to do
that when I can't find you?
I'm not 10. I don't have
to tell you everything.
Well, you know what?
You do, as long
as I'm paying for it.
I'm fine,
and I don't need
my stepdad babysitting me.
You're not checking up
on Mom every day
while she's halfway across the world
on some yoga retreat, are you?
Hey, you know what, Raya?
You're not your mother, okay?
And she had a very
tough year last year.
You know that.
My mom's gonna be fine.
And, no, you're right.
I wasn't there.
I was stuck in a library for 72
hours studying for finals week,
being responsible, which is why
you can trust me now, Colt.
I do trust you, Raya,
and I know you could
take care of yourself.
I know
you're responsible.
And, Raya...
you can call me Dad.
My God.
Raya?
What just happened?
Nothing good.
They're here.
Lavalantula!
Run!
Watch out!
God! Raya!
Casey!
-Casey!
-Raya!
Help me!
No!
Casey!
We have to go!
Hey, this is Raya.
Leave me a message.
Bye.
Raya, call me back.
It's your dad.
This is Lisa Johnson,
and I am here in the downtown
district of Fort Lauderdale
after massive sinkholes
all over the city
have birthed another wave
of lavalantulas.
And almost a year ago
to the day
where they first
wreaked havoc on Los Angeles.
The big question on
everyone's mind right now
is when will the military
take action?
Or does Florida
need Colton West?
This is Lisa Johnson signing off
from downtown Fort Lauderdale.
I'm not
doing this again.
Hey, did you feel that?
No.
Hey, man, this is
not California.
Things do not shake
like this in Florida.
Not outside of South
Beach, anyway.
Are you all right?
Army helicopters, shaking!
I'm having a bad déjà vu.
No, you're not.
Were you on the phone
with somebody?
Yeah, my daughter, Raya.
-Where's she at?
-Fort Lauderdale.
Man, I heard that's where the
epicenter of all this mess is.
Come on, Colton.
What would Red Rocket do, man?
Where are those guns
you were working on?
You okay?
This is a modified XM25 Counter
Defilade Target Engagement System,
specially designed to shoot
armor-piercing 50-millimeter rounds
and my favorite,
liquid-nitrogen bombés.
The Army likes
to call this...
the Punisher.
And Swiss Army knife
in the clip.
But with
our modifications,
I call her
a cold day in Hell.
Have you tested it?
Nope, but she's
pretty as hell.
Mr. West, they're calling
everyone back to set.
Go ahead.
We're not going
back to set, Kyle.
Excuse me? When you
signed up for this,
you knew what it
was gonna entail,
didn't you?
Yes, Mr. West.
And you said it was okay
with you, didn't you?
Yes, Mr. West.
So I gotta know, punk,
are you in,
or are you out?
If it means I can stop
getting your salads
and start shooting spiders, Mr.
West, then I am all in.
Wait.
Who's shooting spiders?
No, the only thing we're
doing is shooting a scene,
a very large,
expensive scene
that's going tens of thousands of
dollars over budget every minute.
Calm down, Joshie.
Here's the deal.
I'm gonna go
take a whiz,
and then you and I,
Mr. Director,
we're gonna make
movie magic.
Okay. Sounds good.
I have a good
feeling about this.
Let's do it!
Get my bag.
Okay.
I can't.
I can't. I can't.
No, no, no. Not again.
Not again.
Well...
you have to.
Just one more time.
You all better be be safe.
Safe is our middle name.
Okay, everyone,
we're back in two minutes.
Get the helicopter
back up in the air.
We can't do that.
Why the hell not?
Colton just,
hijacked it.
No!
Colton!
You know I'm gonna get
fired for this, Mr. West.
You know you're gonna
get a Purple Heart
for this, Lester.
Anything?
No. The circuits
are probably overloaded.
Keep dialing, Kyle.
Hey, Colt, Colt, Colt!
We got trouble down there!
Take a look!
You're crazy.
This is as far
as I go, Mr. West.
My God.
My God, this is not happening!
Damn it.
-Casey...
-I know. I know.
We have to keep it together.
No! We have to get
out of here, all of us.
The others.
We have to go.
They're at the bar!
Okay, you know, I don't feel
so good after that flight.
Just what are we gonna do?
We gotta help
every man, woman,
and child in that order.
Gotta get everybody
outta here,
and we haven't even
tested these yet.
-Shoot it!
-Gun's not working!
-It should work!
-No, it isn't.
If it was working,
I would have done it!
Shoot it!
Yeah. Yeah!
You okay, Mr. West?
Hell to the yeah, baby!
Yeah!
Gun works.
Go easy on the explosives, man.
Just use the 50 millimeter
rounds.
There's only 100 per round.
Don't tell me what to do.
-Kyle.
-Yeah?
You got a stepfather,
don't you?
Depends on who you ask,
but yeah.
Do you call him Dad?
Yeah. Sometimes.
If I was
your stepfather,
would you call me Dad?
Yeah.
-You would?
-Yeah.
-Really?
Now go get us
a vehicle!
Okay, Dad.
Ho!
We're going in!
-We have to hurry.
-I know.
-My God.
-The music's still on.
Where's Jen and Claudia?
I don't know.
Maybe they left before us.
Without telling us?
I'm really worried.
Me, too. We have to get
everyone out of here.
-Hey, guys!
Hey!
Guys!
Listen to us!
Stop the music!
Lavalantulas are coming!
What?
Lavalantulas!
Never heard of 'em!
-They're coming!
-Cool,
but I don't have
that record yet!
I can't play what I don't have!
-No! No!
-Listen to me!
You have to clear
everyone out of here!
What?
The city's on fire!
Hear that?!
Yes.
This city is on fire!
-No! No!
-No!
No! That's not what I meant!
Cut the music!
God.
Come on! Raya!
Everybody has to leave!
Daniella!
Please!
Get it off!
Come on!
Help me!
We gotta split up.
Not a good idea.
I said split up.
Just do it!
Yeah, I said it before.
You lookin' for something, pig?
Pig?
No. A pig? A cop?
No, no, no.
I'm not a cop.
Help! Help me!
Help me, please!
Okay, pig cop,
you can die, too.
Makes no matter
to me, pendejo.
"Pendejo"?
No, no, no, no,
you gotta listen to me.
There's spiders
all over the city
w-with flames coming
out of their mouth.
Flames coming out of
their mouths! I mean,
look, if we don't
all get out of here,
we're gonna be corpses,
believe me.
Or not.
Come with me!
Hey! Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey,
Who dat?
Who dat? Who dat?
Say hello to my little friend!
¿cómo se llamo?
I'm Dave.
Nice to meet you.
Mi hermana tiene cataro.
What?
I'm American!
I didn't know.
Run, Dave!
I owe you my life!
Let's go!
Dave!
Wait up, man.
Have some of this!
Have some of this, some of
this, and some of that!
Have some of this and
some of this and some of that!
They dead?
I don't know.
Damn!
Get it off!
-Can't get it off!
-Come on! Come on!
Let's go!
Man, it's a tad breezy out here.
Yeah, we gotta Kyle Reese
this situation ASAP.
-Where the hell is he?
-I don't know.
It's so hot out here, I could
fry an egg on my face.
-Nice ride, Kyle.
-Get out.
He's driving, Switek.
Let's go.
-Come on.
-Your stuff's in the back!
Thank you, Detective Gina.
Yeah. You're in the back.
Let me have it.
Let's go.
Wait.
Where are we going?
I can't run anymore!
We have to get out of here!
Daniella?
I'm fine.
I just got burned
back at the club.
Wait.
What?
It's nothing.
It's just
slightly burned.
We have to get you
some medication.
Screw the medication!
What are we gonna do?
I have an idea.
Where are you going?
How we doing back there, Kyle?
Well, there's nothing yet,
but I did find her
on that "Find My Phone" app,
and she's still
in Fort Lauderdale.
Hey, hey, hey! Castillo finds
out, we're both busted again.
All right.
First, we save Raya.
Then we save Florida.
Yeah? You save Raya.
You save Florida.
You save California.
Who's gonna save us?
We did it in LA.
We'll do it here.
We get this wrong,
we're gonna get a burn notice.
What is this place?
Hello!
What is this?
This is sick,
exactly what we need.
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't touch that, man! What you
doing? That's nothing to play with!
Okay, that's loaded with super-cold,
compressed liquid nitrogen.
I use it for house parties. Nah, I use
it to freeze the crap out of spiders,
so please just put it down before
you hurt somebody. Put it down.
My gosh!
Hey!
-I just said put it down!
-Hey!
This is a workplace, TJ!
Safety first!
I know. I just told 'em...
You good, bro?
I told 'em to put it down.
Yo, I look like I got
eight legs and spit lava?
Sorry. I'm sorry.
What the hell
they doing here anyway?
I don't know. They just
let themselves in.
-We really need a car.
-Yeah?
Well, that's
a $10,000 deposit
and a three-month
waiting list.
-Deposit?
-Yes.
Lavalantulas are
tearing up the entire city.
Yo, she right, TJ.
Probably be a four-month
waiting list.
What?
Did you just hear her?
We all have
to get out of here!
We all heard her.
Half my family's
from Los Angeles.
They were all killed by the
lavalantulas, rest their souls.
That's why I made this gun.
True. Now bye, Felicias.
Yeah, well, my stepfather was
the guy who killed them all, okay?
Wait a minute.
Colton West?
That's your father?
Stepfather, and yes.
-Really?
-Really.
Yo, that man's a legend.
He's the reason I made this gun.
Ain't that right, Brick?
Yo, "Swamp Justice,"
crazy movie.
Crazy movie. Crazy...
Hey, yo,
what's wrong with her?
She was burned by the spiders.
She really needs help,
so are you guys
gonna help us or what?
Please.
Yo, duck. Brick!
Stop!
Is there a problem, officer?
You can't get through this way.
You have to turn back.
Hey, yo,
what's up, M.P.s?
We need to get
to Fort Lauderdale.
That's not possible.
Listen, officer...
Get back inside the car, sir.
We have a serious
lavalantula outbreak.
I know.
That's why we're here.
No one can get through. All the
roads have been closed off.
Look, I don't know if
you fellas watch the news,
but we took care of these
guys in Los Angeles.
My name is Colton West,
authorized movie star.
I know who you are,
Mr. West.
I don't care if you're the
President of the United States.
No one's getting through.
What the heck are those?
Guns!
For killing spiders!
All right,
everyone freeze.
Hands up in the air.
Nobody move.
Officers! Look!
Get down!
Give me the gun!
Hurry up!
God!
Go!
Gun! Give me the gun!
Come on, man!
Get us out of here!
Man!
-Look out!
-Okay, let's go.
Yo, fool, be careful!
My God!
My God! Hurry!
That's what
I'm talking about, boy!
Let's go.
If we keep driving
in the Glades like this,
we are going
to get stuck.
Damn!
I hate being right.
Phone call!
It's Wyatt.
Probably asking for money.
Wyatt? Wyatt?
Dad. Dad, are you
hearing the news?
Yeah. Thank God, son.
You're okay. Thank God.
It's happening again in Florida.
I am freaking out right now.
No, no, no. Wait. What do you
mean, son? What do you mean,
you're freaking out? Why
are you freaking out?
"Why?" What do you mean,
why? You're in Florida.
Raya is in Florida.
What...
Wait. Where are you?
I'm... I'm on a movie set.
I'm not in the jungle.
I'm not stuck in the Everglades,
and... and I'm not
chasing lavalantulas.
Who said anything
about the Everglades?
I didn't say...
Nothing. I'm just...
Nothing, son.
Just...
I'm okay.
Raya's okay.
We're all fine. We're
gonna get out of here.
Give my love to your mom.
I love you very much, Wyatt.
Okay, Dad.
I love you, too.
And I'll see you soon.
Okay.
Bye.
So you can get
a video chat from Wyatt,
but can't get ahold of Raya.
Technology. Go figure.
Technology and the
fricking Everglades, man.
I'm... I've had enough
of this place, man.
Where's my can of Raid?
I'm hot, and I'm thirsty,
and I'm tired.
Kyle, you just
left the car.
Okay.
Dead end,
multiple directions.
Plan D?
Why Florida?
You ever wonder why Florida?
No! I mean, all the
crazy crap that happens
in this country
happens in this state!
A man ate another man
on the side of the freeway.
I mean, a couple had to remove their
time machine from their driveway.
A time machine
from their driveway!
Just last month,
a man was arrested
for having sex
with an alligator.
No offense, Florida!
But I'm surprised it
didn't happen here first!
A man and an alligator? Really?
Yeah, yeah.
Looked it up on the Internet,
one of those sites.
Don't go there.
Marty, if that's you, I'm
gonna shoot you in the foot.
What do you expect, man?
We're outside of
a floating house.
What kind of a house is this?
I don't know.
I'm sure they got a boat,
and that's what we need.
They don't even
have a yard. God.
All right.
Split up. Hey, man, I
don't want to split up.
Every time we split up,
what happens?
Like in the damn movies, man.
I don't want to split up.
Marty, help me out.
Just go around.
Come on, man.
Let's go around.
The dude said split up, man.
Go around.
Go ahead.
Still alive.
Quiet.
You see?
Over there on my wood crapper.
Over there.
I see you.
Boy, you smell purty.
Where are we going?
Anywhere these spiders ain't.
-Where's that?
-Pittsburgh.
We ain't never been
to Pittsburgh before.
What are you even
talking about?
Slow down, TJ!
What is that?
The road!
Great! Now what?
Stay here.
Brick, how we gonna
get around that?
I don't know.
Yeah, this hole...
Look out!
Look up!
Let's do this!
Damn.
No.
I'm out.
My God.
Me, too, bro. Damn.
Sh...
-Back up!
-Go!
-Hey, get us outta here!
Hey!
I got a plan.
You colder than a
penguin's toenail.
Yeah.
-My God.
-Look at that.
That is amazing.
Yo, but we out
of liquid nitrogen.
How the hell we supposed
to get more of that now?
The school
at the medical lab.
-What school?
-Miami North University
just a few miles
down the road.
We go there.
Yo, what's the mascot?
I... I don't know.
I'm a medical student.
But they keep a stockpile
of it for experiments.
I do not like this idea.
I like it.
TJ!
Yo, I do not
like this idea!
What the heck was that?
My.
It's a little girl.
No, no, no!
They're okay! They're okay!
He's okay.
We're being hunted.
What that was
was the first wave.
What do you mean,
"first wave"?
Well, first there were them,
snakehead frankenfish.
Then everybody got crazy
about them Burmese pythons.
Aha.
And now we got,
-lavalantulas.
-Yeah.
Don't they know how delicate
our ecosystem is out here?
All right. How do we
get to Fort Lauderdale?
Well, I'd say your best bet...
is I-95.
Jeez!
National Guard
closed it.
Well, can you get
us across anyway?
Can we just take
that boat right there?
That boat's got
a flat tire.
Strange things
have been happening.
I ain't been
out there in weeks.
Why is that?
Well, about two weeks ago,
the manatees started
beaching themselves.
Didn't think
much of it.
Then all of a sudden,
these outcroppings
started to rise from the Glades.
Look, I appreciate your
passion for this stuff,
but we got a
life-and-death situation.
Mister, you're talking to
Florida's number one gator man.
Name's Jim Dundee.
But, hey, strawberry, you
can call me Alligator.
Alligator Dundee?
What?
Well, it's like,
Alligator Dundee,
it's kind of like...
Kind of like what?
Well, it's quite similar to...
Like a superhero doing his
thing. Yeah, you know.
It's nothing!
Look, can you get us across?
You wanna get across?
Then you talk to me.
But I thought that's
what we were doing.
-Do what?
-Talking to you.
I'm talking to you
to talk to me.
-Yeah, I know.
-I said you talk to me.
No, I understand that.
Then who you talking to?
I'm... Nothing.
I apologize.
Do you have a boat
that works?
-Do I have a boat that works?
-Yeah.
Sure. Follow me.
It's deserted.
There must have
been an evacuation.
If there was an evacuation,
then either spiders are
coming, or they're here.
We need to get in and out
as quickly as possible.
Help her.
We need to talk.
Okay.
Your friend,
was she burned or bit?
I don't know. Why.
Your father, Colton, he didn't
tell you what happened in LA?
I mean, I know what
everyone else knows,
but my family doesn't
like to talk about it.
No, I heard some crazy stuff that
happened when people got bit.
Like what?
I don't know.
I'm not from LA,
so I don't know. I'm
not even... Like what?
I heard
that if you got bit,
you become a host
to baby spiders,
like, thousands of 'em.
Like, they just,
you know, burst
out of your body.
You know what I'm saying?
That's what I heard,
all right?
She got burned,
okay?
So is that
little strawberry
a real close friend
of yours?
Yeah, yeah,
just a distant relative.
I'm right here.
I can hear you.
There you go! Look
at that right there.
There's an outcropping.
Boy, I ain't ever seen anything
like that
in my whole life.
Have you ever seen
anything like that?
Didn't I just say that?
Yeah.
Hey, Colton, what do
you think that is?
Hell of a coincidence.
All right!
Lavalantulas!
Over there! Over there!
Come on! Get some of this!
Come on! Come on!
On the crapper!
I want some of this!
Hey!
Get down!
Off to the boat!
To the boat!
Let's go!
Have ever seen them
do this before?!
It's a new breed!
Get in the boat!
Just get in the boat! Yah!
-Gator.
-Dundee?
Yeah!
Get that knife
behind you!
Hey!
Kill that thing, man!
You okay?
I'm okay.
I got you.
I'm fine.
-No, I feel secure.
-You do.
-No, I feel safe.
-There's one!
Come on, man!
Get us out of here, man!
Go! Go! Go!
I mean, we were stuck
inside a ring of lava!
But we sure taught
those guys something.
We gave them two cents,
okay?
We took the fight
to those suckers!
Wait. Is this where
my highly paid star is?
Taking the fight
to these things?
I ain't saying anything.
Here come the cavalry!
Come on, guys.
Where's Colton West?
Good. Are you guys
here to evacuate us?
I am Colonel Nathan R. Jester
with the Army
Corps of Engineers,
and I'm looking
for a Colton West.
I was told he was here.
Can you tell me where I
might find Colton West?
Well, I could think
of a few places.
Well, name one.
The unemployment office.
How 'bout another?
The studio blacklist.
Yeah.
-All right.
-Where are you going?
Let's set up a mobile
command station right here!
No. No.
Move out!
No one's going in there!
That is a hot set!
That's a hot set!
That's movie talk for
you can't move anything.
It's movie talk.
Studio blacklist?
You think this is funny?
Colonel Jester,
I don't think
there's anything funny
about this at all.
Colonel Jester...
is a little bit funny.
It's a little bit funny,
yeah.
You know, I do not
like your attitude.
You know, no one does.
That's what makes me
a good director.
So are you here
to evacuate us or what?
Well, we'll talk
about that.
But right now,
for the fourth time,
I'm gonna ask you, can you tell
me where I can find Colton?
This is a matter
of national security.
General...
Colonel.
Colonel...
he could be on a fan boat
in the middle of the
Everglades for all I know.
What's happening?
How's Gator?
Not good, man.
Jim's dead, Colton.
I think I can save him!
-Come on!
-I stopped the bleeding,
or he ran out of blood,
one of the two.
He's gone, yo.
Do you even know
where you're going?
Kyle, we're in a swamp.
Of course I don't know
where we're going.
Wait.
Got it.
Thank...
Go that way!
No, no, no, no, no.
That way!
A'ight, where they at?
Where they at?
Where we at?
What's up, man?
Hey, yo, Brick.
Don't lose these.
Okay.
Are you okay, girl?
I think my burn is
making me feel sick.
Okay. You're gonna
be fine, okay?
Man.
Hey, guys,
it's a cold room.
Come on.
In here.
Okay.
Damn, it's cold in here.
It has to be to
keep things fresh.
We got 'em.
Come on.
Is everybody okay?
Jim's
still dead, man.
I meant you girls!
I'm fine.
Where the hell are we, Kyle?
Give me a second.
By my calculations,
we're about 40 miles west
of Fort Lauderdale.
That's not good enough!
We gotta get to Raya!
Well, she's...
Hey, wait.
She's at her school.
Wait a minute! Why would
she go to her school?
Because she wants
to be a geologist.
All right, we gotta
get to that school.
What about...
What about Alligator,
who died of natural causes?
That's what he
would have wanted.
He's a swamp man.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
News flash.
We are in the middle
of nowhere!
Hear that?
People?
I smell popcorn.
And I'm gonna eat it.
She's been with us for 20 years!
That's right.
Green!
We call her Mean Green.
She ain't the biggest,
but she's the meanest captive
alligator in the Everglades!
It's an alligator show.
That's not part of the show.
Keep going! Go!
Move! Move! Move!
Keep going!
Come on!
Keep moving, everyone!
Move!
Keep moving!
Move it! Move it!
Move! Move it!
Yo, let's load the guns up, bro.
Where the guns at?
Don't you have 'em?
Man, do I look like I got 'em?
No.
Dude, I told you
to get 'em from the truck.
That ain't
what you said.
Man, yeah, I did, man.
You told me to help
what's-his-face here!
-No, I didn't, man!
-Okay, enough!
I'll grab the guns.
All right, I'll help you if
that's what you trying to do.
Back away from the lavalantula.
It's not doing anything.
What is happening?
Why isn't it attacking me?
It's like it doesn't see you.
It's the cold.
That has to be it.
We're so cold that it
doesn't see us a-as living.
You mean, because I'm freezing,
it sees me as a chair?
Nah, it probably
sees me as a chair.
It probably sees you
as like a couch or something.
Whatever. So as long as we
are cold, we're safe?
Well, we're gonna die
if we stay in here,
and we're gonna die
if we go out there.
Man, wish we had guns
right now.
But maybe if we keep our body
temperature cold enough,
we can go get the guns.
With the liquid nitrogen tanks.
Like they use in cryotherapy.
-Cryo-what? What...
-Therapy. It's the use
of really low temperatures
in medical treatments.
That's it.
I don't like this idea.
I do not like this idea.
You saved my life!
Thank you!
My pleasure.
You know who I am,
don't you?
You recognize me
from movies and television?
What about, Red Rocket?
"Hey, I'm the Red Rocket!"
Or... Or, "There's Hell to Pay!"
What about the condom
commercial in the nineties?
"This isn't mine.
It's too big!"
No? What about,
"Hey, nice pants."
Nice pants?
"Nice tattoo."
He doesn't know who
you are, Colton! Sorry!
Okay. I'm just trying
to talk to the man.
That chopper,
do you know who owns it?
Zed.
Zed. Where's Zed?
Zed's dead, man.
Zed's dead.
Well, do you know
how to fly it?
Not a lick!
Okay! Do you mind if we take it?
-If it works!
-If it works?
Wait a minute.
What's going through
your mind, Colton West?
A little flick
I did in the nineties
called "Air Bandits."
Big hit.
That was 20 years ago.
It was three hours training.
They cut the scene.
That's not a plan A.
What's your plan B?
I'll catch you later.
-You know that one?
-Yeah, yeah!
Catch you later!
Catch you later.
He remembers!
Catch you...
Colton, you can't fly
that chopper!
You got 847-to-3 odds.
Never tell me the odds!
And it was
four hours training!
And 25 years ago...
Yo, I'm so cold,
I could hug
a lavalantula right now.
Okay, that should
be enough.
Yeah, we should
be cold enough.
We just gotta head
to the truck
and grab the guns, okay?
Okay.
But we gotta move slow.
Give me the keys.
I put 'em on the table.
What the... Why?
I didn't want
to lose 'em.
Okay, let's go, but slowly.
Moving faster will raise our
body temps too quickly.
And mine rises much faster
than the rest of y'all's.
Okay, TJ and I will
go out there.
Brick, stay with Daniella.
It's safer in here. And then
once we reload the guns,
we'll come back
for you.
Nuh.
Let's go.
Come on.
Hey, yo, two words!
Don't die.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
Stay over there.
You gonna be good.
Expensive.
All right.
Okay.
Button, button.
Who's got the button?
-Too low.
-No. No.
Yes. Yes.
Aha.
Just like I remember.
Well, fellas, I think I'm gonna be
pretty good at this flying thing.
Hey! Hey!
You want my opinion on that?
Okay?
Just a little bump
in the road, ladies.
Kyle, I'm gonna need you to keep
an eye on Raya's coordinates.
You're gonna be my GPS.
I'm gonna need you
to keep us in the air!
You're my pilot!
Piece of cake.
Okay.
Where they go?
Okay. Almost there.
Okay.
Get the door.
I am
Go! Go!
Run!
Go, go, go!
Man, I hope they made it.
Brick, can you
please look at my burn?
I feel really weird,
like I'm gonna...
Like I'm gonna hurl
or something.
Yo, I'm a mechanic.
I work on cars,
not spider burns.
Brick, please?
All right.
-What?
-Nothing.
Nothing. It looks good.
I don't know what it
was like before,
but you gonna be all right.
It doesn't hurt
as bad as before.
I think the cold is helping it.
Hoo.
Snap!
My...
No!
Get out of here.
Open the door! No.
Come on.
No!
Come on!
Hey!
-Move!
-What happened?
-Raya, no.
Where's Daniella?
Raya. Raya.
She ain't gonna make it!
-What? No!
-Take her! Go!
Raya, no!
Raya, come on!
-We can't leave her!
-No! Come on!
We're right above her!
I'm gonna take her down.
She's moving faster!
That could only mean...
-She's in trouble.
-Man.
Are you sure you
can land this thing?
Never underestimate me,
Marty.
You know that.
Brick, my gun's jammed.
Brick, save your ammo, man!
Brick!
There's way
too many of 'em.
They're too lava,
too lantula!
Get outta here.
Brick! No, man! No!
-We have to go, TJ!
-No.
Let's do this!
Man, I don't want to die today.
We're not gonna die. We just
have to keep it together.
Brick's gone, okay?
Brick's gone.
Listen to me.
I lost
my best friend, too.
But we're gonna
get out of here, okay?
I promise.
-Wait.
-Okay.
Okay.
Go, go, go!
Go, go! Go, go, go!
Keep going! Keep going!
Don't wait for me!
Keep going.
Where's the gun?
It's still in the
kitchen right now.
My God.
Damn it.
God.
-Come on!
-I'm coming.
Leave us alone.
No, no, no.
-What are we gonna do?
-They're everywhere.
Hey!
Colton!
Yes! Yeah!
Hey.
Wait. Wait.
Raya! You got a boyfriend.
-Raya.
-Colton!
Ho ho.
Thank goodness.
You're okay.
Daniella's dead.
Everyone's dead.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, honey.
I promise you,
everything's
gonna be okay.
I didn't think
you'd come.
Well, if you would answer
your phone once in a while.
What do you mean,
I wouldn't come?
How could I not
come back for you?
You're my daughter.
It's gonna be okay.
That ain't true.
Ain't nothing gonna be okay.
Who's he?
That's TJ.
Saved my life.
Yo, I'm a great fan,
man, a big fan.
Thanks for coming for us, man.
I got a gun!
I made a gun,
and you inspired it.
It's in there. I'm gonna
go get it for you.
Okay, you can thank us later.
Right now we are not
out of the woods yet.
We've got to find her
and kill her.
-Find who?
-These are just babies.
The mama's
hiding somewhere.
When this happened
in Los Angeles,
the good Dr. Von Struble gave
us a thermal image of the city.
We were able to find her.
I can do that.
Thermal, spectral,
infrared.
Last semester, I did my
thesis on global drought
and raising
global temperatures.
We had access to all the
satellite information.
Show us, honey.
Just follow me.
You got a cool-ass daughter, Mr.
West.
Don't even think about it.
I...
I don't want it
crossing your mind.
How you know...
You got me?
Can...
Okay.
All right.
So we gotta get that chopper
operational. Can you do it?
Come on, man. What happens
every time we split up?
Weird stuff happens.
Come on, Marty.
How 'bout we split up
temporarily?
I get the chopper,
and I'll meet you out front.
-Great idea.
-All right? Cool.
Go!
Sir. We think we've
located Colton West.
Well, get him on the line.
What did you do to my set?
You wrecked my set!
Wait.
Did I hear you correctly?
Did you find that S.O.B.?
Did you find them?
Are they okay?
Will you get these morons
out of my office?
Yes, sir.
Wait! This is crazy!
You can't take me off
my own movie set, General!
It is Colonel, and this is
now a military operation.
I can do whatever
the hell I want to do.
Now, Private, please get
these people out of my face!
Don't you touch me!
I'm gonna go
under my own accord.
Humph!
Don't let me
die on "Clown Cops"!
This can't be my last movie.
We're so overbudget.
Something like this?
Exactly like that.
Now zoom in on Miami.
Brilliant.
And you thought I was
only partying, Colt.
When did I say that?
I never said that. I never
said you were only partying.
So that's it? You think
that's the mamalantula?
That is one massive heat
signature under Miami.
Whatever it is, it is huge.
What, the mamalantula?
No, no, no, no.
That's much, much bigger.
That's no mamalantula.
That's a freaking
gargantulantula.
Mamalantulantula.
What?
The... The mama tarantula?
No. Gargantulantula.
Gorgantulantula?
What? Is it...
Gor... The gorgantula? No.
Yes... No, it's a gargantulantula.
-It's a gor...
-Mormalantula?
-With an "O"?
-No, with a G-A-R, gar.
-Gargan... Gargantu...
-Gargar...
-Gargantula.
-Gargan...
What's the last part?
-Say it slow. Just say...
-Gargan...
It's very, very bad.
It's very bad.
That's the government.
How do you know that?
'Cause it's ringing
really weird.
Hello.
Colton West?
Speaking.
Yeah, this is,
Colonel Nathan R. Jester.
You are familiar with the
situation down in Florida?
Yeah, slightly.
Yeah, well,
you are the only one
that has successfully
dealt with these things...
I'm sorry.
And, I need your help,
and I need your team.
Great.
Then come pick us up.
No can do. You're
located in a hot zone.
Yeah, in a hot zone.
Believe me, I been
through this before.
-I know you have.
Well, I got an idea.
If you listen to me, I...
No, you listen to me,
General.
It's Colonel.
Colonel, you listen to me.
You position your satellites
for a thermal image
of Miami stat.
You found her.
I found something,
'cause this one
makes the one in LA
look like a flea.
So we find her,
we root her out,
and we blow her up.
I'm no expert,
but the heat signature
on this one
is like something
I've never seen before.
It worked once.
It'll work again.
We strike hard,
we strike first,
and we show no mercy.
No, these aren't
like the ones in L.A.
They're bigger.
They're hotter.
They're nastier.
So what are you suggesting,
that we just,
simply do nothing and move on?
Suggesting you
don't piss it off.
I don't want you
and your... your friends
to do anything real stupid
like the last time.
I don't have friends.
I got family.
Well, I got bombs,
so you and your family
can just stay tight.
We'll check out your map.
We'll get a confirmation to you.
Don't hang up on me.
They want us to sit tight.
Sit tight? How can anyone
sit tight right now?
They're gonna get us all killed.
Colton, this is the U.S.
military we're talking about.
Kyle, you know I have
a problem with authority.
Nobody, nobody knows
these spiders
like I know these spiders.
Colonel, thermal images are up.
He's right.
Whatever that is,
it's huge.
That is the behemoth
of all spiders.
Get CENTCOM on the line.
We're gonna smoke her out.
Then we're gonna
light her ass up.
We're gonna light her ass up.
What happened to the chopper?
-We can't get to the chopper!
-Why not?
Remember when I told you
that every time
we split up, weird
stuff happens?
-Yeah.
Well, I was
on my way to the...
-Right.
-And all of a sudden...
And...
-And then what?
-Marshmallows.
So what do we do?
Does anybody have a car?
I do.
-Brilliant!
-Go.
I don't understand
why we can't just sit back
and let the military
handle this.
'Cause they don't know.
And they don't know.
You keep saying that.
What don't they know?
They haven't ridden on the back of
one of these things like I have,
And he has.
And they haven't
looked in the eyes
of one of these
things like I have.
And he has.
TJ...
I think you made a wrong turn.
Yo, yo, chill out.
This is my hood, a'ight?
We're dead.
What's happening?!
TJ, shut the hell
up, and get down!
They're shooting at us!
They're not shooting at us.
Let's go.
Get 'em!
Let's go!
-There's so many of 'em!
-No! No! No!
-Are you Colton West?
-Damn skippy.
"Red Rocket."
Crazy movie, man.
Yeah. They should have
continued the franchise.
Look out, man!
Come on!
What are you doing
with my punk-ass brother?
Who you calling punk-ass, man?
We over here saving Florida.
'Bout to get medieval on y'all.
Dad, get back
in the house, man!
You two stand back.
I'm gonna show you boys
how it's done.
-What is that, sir?
-Fire retardant.
Well, whatever the hell it is,
it chased them the hell away.
-You have any more of it?
-I'm out.
I'm out of ammo.
Everybody back in the house.
-All right. Come on.
-When they return...
-Go in, Pops. Go in.
-They're gonna be pissed.
This is Delta One.
Target is in sight.
-We have missile lock.
-Copy that.
Operation Alpha Foxtrot
is a full go.
Roger that.
Let her have it, boys.
We have direct hit, sir.
Well, that should
wake her ass up?
Greetings.
It's... It's a nice night,
all things considering.
Yeah. It's all right.
I loved "Straight
Out of Compton."
What?
Yeah, I know he's busy,
busy destroying this entire city.
He doesn't know
what he's dealing with.
Now put him
on the damn phone.
What do you want?
The little spiders,
they don't matter.
It's the big one,
the gargantulantula.
You kill it, and
you kill 'em all.
-Who's he talking to?
-Well, if it's that easy,
why don't you just
get some bug spray?
I've done this before.
These lavalantulas, they're
not like the last ones,
and this big one,
it's got so much heat,
no weapon can come close to it.
-I'm about to prove you wrong.
-Really?
Who's hungry?
Really, Mom, who could
eat at a time like this?
A man's got to eat. Now shut your
mouth, and put some food in it
before I slap you upside
the head, damn boy!
What's wrong with you?
You don't question your
mama in front of guests.
I was just saying
I wasn't hungry.
Well, make your butt hungry.
Lord, is this what it takes
for a mama to get her kids
back in the house at the same time,
a damn lavalantula invasion?
Hell, if I'd have known that,
I'd have called up them
lavalantulas years ago.
Woman, what's wrong with you?
You can't call no lavalantula.
Don't tell me what
I can and can't do.
I got Colton West up in my
house, a real movie star.
That's very kind of you, ma'am,
and completely accurate.
Don't interrupt me,
movie star.
You need to eat, too.
Look skinnier than
you did 20 years ago
in that "Crimson Flyer" movie.
It's actually called
"Red Rocket,"
and it was a huge hit.
That's the potatoes.
Elizabeth, you know
them potatoes give me gas.
You gonna eat some potatoes,
or I'm gonna make you wear 'em.
Sir, can you tell me again
what was that material that you were
shooting out of your leaf blower?
-Fire retardant?
-Really?
Yeah, it's
ammonium phosphate.
That's right.
Girl got a brain.
TJ, why can't you find
a girl like that?
What are you
talking about, Pops?
I do. She... She right here,
ain't she?
Hal, where do you
get that stuff?
Pops used to work
for a fire department.
-Really?
-Yeah.
30 years.
You know, I played
a psychologically
complicated fireman
with a drinking problem
in the hit film, "Scorcher."
I didn't really care
for that movie very much.
Really?
They should have consulted
a real fireman.
And the fire, that computer-generated
crap, man, that just looked silly.
Well, it's Hollywood, Hal.
You know, I just read 'em.
I don't write 'em.
But, anyway,
do you have any more
of that stuff down
at the station?
Hell if I know, man.
I ain't been to the station
since they cut
my damn pension.
But I can tell you where they
got a load of it, though.
Where?
At the airfield,
at the Forest Service.
That's where we drop it out
of planes for forest fires.
Know anybody who could
fly one of those planes?
You're looking at him.
First job I had when
I got out the Air Force.
Really?
Colton, is there
something on your mind?
I'm thinking.
Now, one of those planes, we'd
never get close enough to drop it.
That big one, the heat
coming off of it,
would explode
the plane immediately.
Yeah, or if we even
try to get close,
she'll shoot that cilica
garbage or whatever that is,
and we would fry.
At the school, when we
were being attacked,
the spiders didn't see us.
She's right.
We got so cold in there.
We lowered our body temperature
enough that we were
invisible to them.
Really?
So have you got any guys
who could help us load
one of those planes?
Not a problem.
And have you got any guys
who can get us to that airfield?
Not a problem.
And how do you feel
about helping me
beat that thing and
saving this city?
Not a problem.
Good.
Then let's extinguish the bitch.
Heavenly Father.
-What?
-Breaking news.
Live pictures coming in
now from downtown Miami
-at Imagination Stadium.
-Damn.
We can now see
what the military
has been targeting
with those airstrikes.
My goodness.
It's a giant lavalantula.
The entire stadium
has been reduced to rubble.
Let's move out.
Well, that sure as hell
ain't no itsy-bitsy spider.
She's really big, sir.
Blow her up.
Target is live.
Proceed and destroy.
Roger that. All right, fellas,
you heard the man.
Let's go light her up.
Tommy's hit!
We're too close!
Pull up! Pull up!
It's not working, sir!
Nothing is getting through!
Gimme, gimme. I'm gonna
maintenance these.
Thanks a lot.
Yes, yes.
Colton!
Arni!
What the hell are you
do... Zip it, Colton!
You were a pain in the ass when your
career was going in the toilet,
and you're a bigger
pain in the ass now!
That's what you risked
your life for to tell me?
I know what you're up to.
Are you out of your mind?!
No, I've never been clearer.
I think I found
a higher calling.
Higher calling, my ass.
You want to waltz into cities
and save millions,
you go through me.
I'm your agent!
-You think Hollywood pays well?
-Yeah.
Well, wait'll we hit up
Uncle Sam for your services.
Really?
Now you want to save a city...
They go through me.
And we're gonna make millions.
-Millions? Millions.
-Millions! Millions!
I gotta go save the world.
All right.
I'm gonna make some calls.
That's my agent.
-You came to me.
-Go get 'em!
-Amazing! Came to me!
All right, what's the
number for San Francisco?
She can drop 90,000 gallons
of fire retardant on a target
before you can call
for more peanuts.
That good enough for you?
That'll be just fine.
This is gonna be
a dangerous flight, Hal.
Man, I've flown
through stuff
turn your butt whiter
than you already are.
Ain't no spider
gonna take me down.
This is not your average spider.
That's great,
but in my world,
if it's got eight legs,
it's a damn spider.
Now we gonna keep
wasting time talking,
or we gonna go ahead
and take her out?
We're gonna take her out.
Sir, the missiles
can't get through.
Well, target the ground
near her feet.
Maybe she'll sweep the leg.
We can't, sir. It's her heat
signature. Nothing's getting close.
The missiles are detonating
before they can impact.
Colton was right.
She's too hot.
Well, it's time
for an alternative.
Alternative, sir?
Get the President
on the horn.
We just may have to nuke my
little darlin' straight back to hell.
Sir, if we do that,
you'll destroy the entire state.
Let's hope that's all.
Good people of Florida,
your state has come under attack
from one of the worst menaces
known to modern history,
a creature so heinous,
it can only come
from the pits of Hell,
and if we don't stop it,
millions of people will die,
and your great city
will be reduced to ashes.
But not on my watch!
Do you know what people say
about the great state of Florida?
It's too humid.
Yeah, yeah, they
actually do say that.
What does this Angeleno know
about the great state of Florida?
Florida is a state of winners!
Can you tell me what NFL team
is the only team to be
undefeated in history?
-The Dolphins!
That's right.
The Dolphins from '72.
And where did the king,
LeBron James,
go to get his championship ring?
Cleveland!
-Miami!
That's right, Miami.
And which state has the
most beautiful beaches,
the hottest women,
the most golf courses?
And the only state to have
no state income tax?
Alaska!
Nevada.
-South Dakota's one.
-Yeah.
It's true, but, Arni,
I'm trying to do
a hero thing here.
You asked a question!
I know, but give me a break!
When aliens come to visit,
which state do they choose?
Florida.
She's just kidding.
There are no aliens in Florida.
Okay.
I don't know
anything about aliens,
but I do know when
the United States of America
sends a rocket into space,
they don't send it
from Oregon
or South Dakota or Nevada.
They send it from...
-Florida!
I won this fight in Los Angeles,
and fate has brought me
here to Florida,
and together, there's
no way we're gonna lose.
-Amen.
-Amen. Yeah.
Tonight we win!
We win! We win!
-Yeah.
-That's right.
-Yeah!
Can somebody help me down?
I got you, buddy!
I got you.
-Thank you, Arni.
-Swing your leg down.
I have to swing
my legs down.
Okay, then I go...
All right.
1, 2, 3. Go!
Yo, Arni! My God!
Colt, if the missiles can't get
close enough without detonating,
how are you gonna get close
enough in the plane?
I got this, sweetie.
You just stay here
in the hangar.
I'll be back.
You better be back.
Promise.
Love you.
Get some coolant right here.
Let's go ahead and mark it off.
Hey, we're all clear over here.
...3, Philadelphia.
300,000 for Allentown.
-Hey, turn that up.
-Okay.
Continuing our live coverage now
of this catastrophic event.
Miami has been evacuated,
and the military continues
to pound this enormous beast
in what is now being called
"Arachnid Freedom."
Hal, how do we get close enough
to that thing without being seen?
If we take her high enough,
the plane will freeze.
Mr. West, stand by
for Colonel Jester.
Colton!
How's it going, Colonel?
I think you damn well know
how it's going, Mr. West.
Don't you worry. We got a
plan that'll save us all.
-Well, we got our own plan.
-No, no, no.
You cannot nuke Miami, sir.
That's insane.
Well, who said
anything about that?
I've made that movie,
and it always
ends with nukes.
You just can't do it. You
gotta trust me on this one.
Sir, we picked up a C-130 entering
the restricted no-fly zone.
Colton, is that you
riding through a
restricted air zone?
You're gonna
get yourself killed.
I'm trying to tell you
we've got a plan,
but you gotta
listen to me.
I've got 90,000 gallons
of fire retardant
that says I know
what I'm doing.
I love all your films, Colton,
but we're out of time
for any Hollywood
half-baked rewrites.
Look, I took one
of these things out
without the military
and without you,
and I'll be damned
if I can't take another,
but I'm gonna need your he...
Holy...
The repeated military attacks
on this enormous creature
are failing to have
their intended effect,
but we understand new reports
are filtering in,
and you are
hearing this correctly,
that Colton West is
piloting a civilian aircraft
into the hot zone.
Pull up!
Incoming!
Brace yourself.
Tail!
Marty, you guys
all right back there?
We're hit! I repeat,
we're hit, captain!
How bad's the damage?
We're in a plane full of smoke!
How bad do you think it is?
It's bad!
It's very, very bad!
Come on, Colton. No more
screwing around here.
Just hold on.
I do not have time to hold on,
and neither do you.
We gotta get higher.
Right now, I'm just
hoping it stays together.
If she sees us,
it won't matter.
Colton...
Colonel, just trust me.
Get your fighters in position,
-and wait for my mark.
-Colton!
I don't think I could
take her any higher!
Come on! Come on!
No! No, no! Man,
we're in a stall!
Come on!
He's so bad at this!
Hey, what are you
doing up there?!
Not good!
This is not good!
-Come on!
-Colton,
your plane is
in a dead stall.
I'm sorry, but it's time
for my plan now.
No! No nukes,
Colonel!
Don't count us out yet!
Marty,
get the payload ready.
Houston, we got
a damn problem.
What?
He's right!
The drop mechanism
is malfunctioning.
The bay doors won't open.
That's not good.
Not good?
Our odds of getting out
of this alive are...
Never tell me the odds!
You get this plane
out of a stall,
and, Hal, get the
bay doors open.
They're headed
right for her, sir.
That son of a bitch
is going kamikaze on us.
I've got the controls back!
I'm coming home, Elizabeth!
Hal, open the bay doors!
I can't. The mechanism
is still fried, man.
You gotta cut the
hydraulic cables.
What do you mean? You
can't drop the payload?
We have no power at all!
The only way this is
gonna work is manual.
We gotta do it manual,
or we all die, savvy?
But wait.
We gotta be closer.
If we drop this now,
it's just gonna
disperse into nothing
over Florida.
Then I'm going down with it.
Kyle, cut the cable!
Okay.
Hal, patch me
into the hanger.
All right, man.
Raya!
That red light in the sky,
that's for you, honey.
You tell your mom and
Wyatt that I love 'em.
Dad!
I love you!
Ahoy.
Hey, Colton, are you
sure about this?
Just like old times, Marty!
Damn!
Let's go!
Go get 'em, baby!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Let's go!
Colonel,
we're getting intel
that Colton West is doing a
HALO drop into the hot zone.
He what?
Yippee-ki-yay,
gargantulantula!
Indiana Jones got
nothing over this guy.
Spiders. I hate spiders.
She's down.
What the hell's
going on up there?
Colonel, hit her
with all you got.
Who's this?
Now!
Fire.
Direct hit, sir.
Yeah!
Target is destroyed.
I repeat,
target is destroyed!
Yeah!
Son of a bitch.
He did it again.
Right on!
All right!
...talking about,
fellas. Good job.
What about West, sir?
He couldn't possibly
have made it.
Real good job.
Hey.
Look.
Good job, man.
Remember me?
Come here.
Where's my buddy?
God!
Yeah.
Ho ho!
Let me see here.
Colonel.
Colton West.
Told you. We had a plan.
Glad you made it.
Yeah, well, thankfully I did,
but the gargantulantula,
she wasn't as lucky.
She's terminated, all right.
It's a job well done, boy.
Sorry I ever doubted you.
You know what?
I'm gonna take my whole battalion
to see your next movie twice.
Well, thank you, General.
It's Colonel.
Whatever.
My little girl.
I love you, Dad.
I love you, too.
Wait a minute.
You called me Dad.
That's the sweetest thing
you could say to me.
Deal with it.
Gladly.
And you cannot tell
your mom about any of this.
Dad,
it's all over the news.
I guess
she's used to it.
Come here.
Just remember, guys,
it doesn't matter if you win
by an inch or a lavalandslide.
Winning is winning!
Yes!