That kid right there?
That's me, Ariana Berlin.
Gymnastics is my life.
I've been doing it since I
was three years old and I've
never looked back.
That's my best friend Isla.
She and I used to choreograph
our future Olympic
routines in our hallways.
What? Normal
kids don't do that?
My coaches always said
that sometimes you have to fall
before you can fly.
I fell a lot.
I trained a lot.
And right now I'm in the
middle of the most important
level ten meet of my life.
Going too fast?
Let me step back.
♪ You gotta get up Whoa
You gotta get up ♪
Ladies and gentlemen, thank
you to UCLA for hosting this
year's level ten regional meet.
The opening heat will begin in
fifteen minutes.
♪ You gotta get up Whoa
You gotta get up ♪
Good job.
We've got this.
No kidding. We're toast.
Just breathe.
It's just, if I don't place...
If you don't place you can
just ask to borrow one of his
Olympic medals. What
does he have, like three?
Four, actually.
See, you'll be getting off
easy. Now if I don't qualify, my
parents will
pep-talk me to death.
Oh I'm sure it's tough living
with all their love and support.
Forget about your
Dad. Today is about you.
Nervous?
Nervous I might kick you into the
foam pit if you ask me that again.
Here, I got you
something for good luck.
Aw. Did you splurge at the
prize machine in the lobby?
Yeah, a whole dollar.
I love it.
You've got this.
Okay, okay! Let's do this.
Hey, ladies! Quit joking around.
The stakes are even higher
than what we thought today.
Why?
If you ever want to go to
UCLA, the woman who holds the
keys to your future is standing
right over there.
That's Valorie Kondos-Field,
head coach of the
six-time Champion UCLA
Gymnastics Team.
Up next on the uneven
bars, Isla Steponchev from Elite
Gymnastics.
That was amazing.
Thanks.
And Isla scores a 9.85.
You were fantastic.
It was okay. Wasn't perfect.
You'd only be satisfied with
twenty out of ten.
Up next Ariana Berlin.
Which is what I'm about to get.
♪ I feel so good
♪ I feel, I feel
____, I feel so good ♪
♪ I feel
♪ I feel so good
♪ I ain't trusting tonight
nothing on my mind on my mind ♪
♪ Why you wasting your time ♪
♪ Let's get on a high
stay with me there ♪
Up next Ariana Berlin from
Elite Gymnastics in San Diego.
♪ I feel, I feel, I feel
Hold, extend, twist, focus
on the catch.
Flip, toes up, dismount, stick.
Who's that on the bars?
Ariana Berlin from San Diego.
Yes!
Ariana scores a
9.95 on the bars.
Sweetheart! You put on
quite the show
for the college coaches.
You think they noticed me?
Noticed you? Are you kidding
me? Our phone's gonna be ringing
off the hook tomorrow.
Oh we'll know in a few days.
They said they'd have the final
results by Friday.
Hey Ariana. Wow, you
nailed it out there.
Thanks, you did great, too.
You're totally going
to qualify for sure.
The way you stuck that
landing on bars. Wow.
I was jealous.
Don't be. This is just a
Level 10 meet. There's still a
long way to go.
Could you imagine what
it would be like to make the
Olympics?
It would be so unbelievable,
but I doubt it's something I'll
ever get to experience.
Me neither. I
wish I could go.
Come on, you gotta be more
positive. You never know what
life is going to
throw at you, right?
Yeah.
Okay, remember this trip?
That girl who peed her pants on
the bus ride home?
What? We were six and I
had way too much water.
Okay. I'm so glad your Dad
let you come over.
How was he about your score?
He said it was acceptable.
But, of course if I don't
qualify for the Olympic
team he'll downgrade it to
"deplorable" or something.
Well don't worry, you'll qualify because
you are the best in the country.
It would be a dream come true.
Yeah, for me it's the
Olympics and then UCLA.
I haven't even started
thinking about college.
Well UCLA has an amazing
gymnastics team.
Well you came over to
study so let's get to it.
Nooo
So how late were
you and Isla up?
Late. We were trying to
cram for organic chemistry.
A champion gymnast and a
straight 'A' student.
I'm still waiting for this
teenage rebellion
that everyone keeps
telling me is on the horizon.
Overachieving is my personal
form of teenage rebellion.
I think I deserve a reward.
Well I have a better idea.
Why don't you come shopping with
me this afternoon?
Aw, do I have to?
I know, it's so awful. I'm
serious, you've been so busy
training, I just think you need a
regular mother-daughter afternoon.
I see right through you, mother!
You're trying to distract me.
And it's working, isn't it?
So you're lost in
thought, what's going on?
Nothing.
Uh-huh. Can you
be more specific?
Pierce said one of the
coaches from the
UCLA team was at qualifiers.
Yeah, well honey, you throw
a rock in that stadium you're
pretty much gonna
hit a college coach.
Well don't throw any at UCLA
'cause I want to get in there.
I know you do.
One thing at a time.
Let's just focus on the
shopping today.
What if I don't qualify
for the Olympics?
Would you be upset?
Are you kidding me? Your
father and I are so proud of
you. Olympics or -
Mom, watch out!
Hey! Hey! Are you okay?
Are you okay?
I don't think she's breathing. Go
call an ambulance. Call an ambulance.
Try and stay awake for me, okay?
Can you tell me your name, honey?
Tell me what happened.
Do you know what date it is?
No, she's gone again.
Ar, honey. It's okay, I'm
here. I love you so much.
Where?
You're in the hospital.
You had an accident.
But-
Don't try to talk, okay?
I'm gonna go get the doctor.
Where's mom?
She's just down the
hall in another room.
I, I need to see her.
No, you need to, you need to
lie down, okay?
You've been in a coma, honey. I'm
gonna tell the doctor you're awake.
Both lungs punctured, broken
collar bone, two broken ribs,
slight fracture of the right
wrist, injured pancreas, one
femur snapped, the other
fractured. Well the good news is
she only suffered minor head
trauma, no major concussion.
Neck and spine are in fairly
good shape considering the
accident. I would say under the
circumstances, your daughter is
a very lucky girl.
I don't feel very lucky.
The fact that you feel
anything at all is enormous.
We could have lost you,
young lady.
Sweetheart, I'm so
happy to see you awake.
When can I get up?
We're looking at nine to ten
weeks for the bone to heal, then
physical therapy for a few
months. Luckily you're an
athlete so I think the body
is going to respond quickly.
So I lose four, maybe five
months, and then I can get back
to training, right?
Truth is, gymnastics is
pretty much off the table.
Honey, I'm so sorry.
You don't know what you're
talking about! I want another
doctor! This is ridiculous.
Calm down, honey.
I, I can't sit in bed
all day. I have to train.
I'll see you outside.
I need to go to the
Olympics. It's okay.
Want a gum? Nope, I'm
good mom. Thanks for asking.
No problem, anytime.
Oh...
What?
Nothing.
You know, Isla had a great
floor routine and a perfect
vault, but she did take that step
after the dismount from her bars.
And, that's the difference
between Gold and Silver.
Yup.
Somebody's in a mood.
I'm not in a "mood".
You know, you've had your
pictures on the paper, too.
Yes, I know, Mom.
I especially liked the one of me
unconscious in the hospital.
You know, you were a lot
more pleasant
when you were unconscious.
Touché.
Ariana? Hey, I'll take you
in. My name's Michelle and I'll
be-okay. Uh, are you coming?
No, no, no. She's all
yours. Where's Brittany?
She's not here today. I'll be
putting you through the paces.
Aren't you a little young
to be a physical therapist?
I'm a physical therapy
resident, which means I'm in
training to become a P.T.
I was in training
once. Lot of good it did me.
Well let's see if we
can get you back on track.
♪ Too easy to slip into
darkness sometimes ♪
I'll be back in a second.
♪ I find it hard to get the
light into this room ♪
♪ Let's break the door open Break
it wide open Break it wide open ♪
You know, you could still
compete. I mean maybe not soon,
but if you want something you
have to fight hard for it.
And what if something I
really want is
no longer attainable?
Look, sometimes when the
front door gets slammed in your
face, you have to go
through the back door.
What if there is no back door?
Then go through a window.
There's always a way in. Ready?
I just need you to just trust
me, okay? One, two, three, up.
Okay, put your weight onto me.
Okay, take a step. Slowly..
♪ We will come alive ♪
Are you okay? And then you're
going to lean forward onto the
mat with your arms
and then push up.
♪ The music never dies ♪
Oh my gosh, wow.
How'd that feel, good?
Yeah.
Yeah, good.
Asthma.
♪ We bring in the light
the music never dies ♪
♪ We've been high and low pulls us
under light's beyond the door ♪
♪ Never let it go Won't let these
locked doors Shut me out anymore ♪
♪ I will break them down
Let the daylight show ♪
Alright, so last time we did fifteen
steps, but I think we can beat that.
Without holding onto the railing.
It says here
that you should be able to walk
now on your own without help.
It says that?
Yup. It says your body's well
on the road to healing. But your
mind's still broken.
It does not say that. They
wouldn't put that in a chart.
Yes they would.
It's even in pen.
Let me see that.
Sorry, professional eyes only.
Well that rules you out,
resident! Give it to me.
No! And you just
did twenty steps.
Nicely done.
My leg is killing me.
Yeah, but for a
minute there you forgot.
Does it really say all
that stuff in my chart?
What's a six letter word
for stubborn? A-R-I-A-N-A.
Thank you for helping me
through all this. I owe you one.
Come. You did really good
and you should be very proud of
yourself. Maybe
thirty steps tomorrow?
♪ Still have the letter that
you wrote
♪ I wanna know what it says
but I don't So it stays, ♪
♪ Cuz I won't throw
it away just yet ♪
I just don't think I'm
up for a visit today, mom.
You'll be fine. You're old
teammates have been asking about
you. You can't stay
away forever, you know.
Says who?
I better go move the car.
I don't want to get towed.
But wait, mom, I can't-
I'll be right back.
Hey coach.
Hey I'll see you guys in there.
Hey, welcome back, kid.
Great to be here. Are my
uneven bars ready and polished?
Well you know they've been
covered in dust
since you've been gone.
It's great to see you.
The gang will be so
excited to see you again.
Hey guys, listen
up. Ariana's here.
Hey, stop. Hey, hey, stop,
stop, stop. Where are you going?
You just got here.
I saw enough.
Huh?
Isla and Nate?
Come on, Ariana. It's
not what it looks like. He's
probably just congratulating
her for getting into UCLA.
She what?
Hey, what's uh, what's going on?
I'll give you guys
a minute. I'm sorry.
This isn't going to work.
What's going on?
I just want my life back.
Hey, you better get
ready, you're going out.
With who?
Michelle.
And you didn't think to tell me?
Of course not. That would
have given you more time to say
'No'.
Mom!
Come on, don't
want to disappoint her.
Welcome to Palace.
Hey Cashmere.
'Sup brother?
I get the feeling we're not
a physical therapy convention.
Where are we?
Girl, for all your whining
and complaining about your
boyfriend and your medals, have
you ever thought to ask me one
question about myself?
Michelle, my babe!
Hey!
Where you been?
Well besides making money to
pay for this place?
Picking up Ariana here.
Ah, you're the gymnast. Sorry
about your accident.
How you doing girl?
I've been better.
Wow.
Watch where you're wavin'
those on the dance floor, you'll
take someone's eye out.
Actually, there's one or two
guys I wouldn't mind
you wavin' those at.
What?!
She's kidding. Emma has
a strange sense of humour.
I won't be getting out on the
dance floor. What kind of party
is this, anyway? Is this a rave?
Darling, the '90's ended a
long time ago.
This is a session.
A session?
Adam! Step! We got
a lady on crutches!
Oh, you're Michelle's gymnast
friend from the hospital?
I'm not from the hospital.
Adam.
Ariana.
That's not right.
He's gonna be sore tomorrow.
Michelle. We up.
Who's up? What?
Come.
♪ We get down
we get to the ♪
♪ Get down
♪ Go go she go she go
Bring it burrito boy!
♪ Go go she go
she go get down ♪
♪ Down check down
Down check down ♪
♪ Go go she go she go
You just did a side-semi
after eating a burrito!
What? That? You should
see me after
a double-cheese quesadilla.
♪ Down check down
♪ Go go she go she go
♪ Get down
So, you post all
those videos online?
Yup. It's a good way to
promote.
We usually get a
few thousand hits.
Wow.
That's nothing. My goal is
to get a million hits one day.
So you're a champion dancer
who runs a studio, and does
physical therapy? And I
thought I was an overachiever.
I'm all about that hustle,
baby. So... can you help us?
Me? What could I
possibly help you with?
Well, there's this big
talent management company called
Crystal Image. They represent
the best of the best. They hold
auditions once a year, and
anyone who gets in with them, is
in with the money. Travel around
the world, be on TV, tour with
rock stars. You get the picture.
Auditions are coming up soon.
I still don't get what I can do.
Well, they're looking for a
dance crew with edge - some sort
of unique special skill, and
I was thinking since you have
Olympic level experience -
Michelle, first-off, I'm
not Olympic level. Second, I've
never danced hip-hop a day in my
life. And third, even if both of
those were the case, look at me.
You look to me like you're
ready to get moving
again. Think about it.
Mom, Dad, I'm
home. Sorry I'm late.
Alright, this little rift
between you guys is hurting
everyone, and it's hurting your
recovery. So you're not leaving
this room until
everything is settled, okay?
Look, I'm sorry about
what you saw earlier today.
I had no right coming
back there unannounced.
I know what it looked like.
But I want you to
know that it's nothing.
Yeah, you're
right. It is nothing.
Listen Ariana. You can get
back on your feet.
You can get into UCLA.
I have a metal rod in my leg.
I'd be lucky to hop
up on a beam again.
Well I can help you. Pierce
can help you.
Please just come
back to the gym tomorrow.
I'm busy with something else.
Yeah? What?
I'll do it.
Do what?
Help out your crew. Teach you
guys some flips
and handsprings and stuff.
Really? Wow. Sorry,
Ariana this is Caity.
Hi. Ariana.
Caity.
Caity was a
professional downhill skier.
I got in a fight. With a
tree. Been a regular patron of
room 404 ever since.
How long is your
recovery schedule?
Only another, what, 60 maybe
70 years. If I'm lucky.
Does that sound about right?
Caity has come a long
way. A very long way.
I'm sorry.
No, don't be. You should see
the tree. No, I'm not a patient
anymore - I just come to spend time with
others here who are in similar situations.
Caity heads a support group
for families with spinal cord
injury patients.
If there is
anything I can do to help-
You just stay focused on yourself.
You've got your own hill to climb.
Thanks.
I'll see you next
week, okay? Take care. Bye.
So? You had fun last night?
Yes. Thank you for taking me.
I dunno, it's taking a while. They're
late probably, right? I don't know.
Hey. I got us some help.
Welcome back.
Hold up. Hold up. What do
we need peg-leg's help for?
"Peg-leg?" She ain't no dang
pirate! What's wrong with you?
I just don't need no gymnast
telling me how to dance.
There's a small chance
the speaker may be broken.
That's Twist
running up my overhead.
And you remember Adam
from the other night?
And of course, Emma.
The "Empress" at
your acquaintance.
And this fountain of
positivity here is Cashmere.
Eighty percent attitude
and twenty percent high heels.
So, what are you going to
teach us that
we don't already know?
She's going to teach us moves
that we can use in our routine
so that we can get a
contract with C.I.
With some leverage training
and a little less burrito I
could help you get seven
or eight feet of air.
Seven or eight feet of air?
Mhm.
Okay.
So, you're gonna
teach us leverage?
Sounds good to me. I'm always
down to learn something new.
I'll bet you are.
So you going to take those off?
There's two things you need
to know, honey. One. I take off
my heels when I'm good and
ready. Two... can someone help
me take off my heels?
Girl, you are a mess.
♪ You run me like a machine We go
faster You know exactly what I mean ♪
♪ It's all in our heads
Get out of this bed get up ♪
♪ I'm a house fire I'm a hot
iron I'm burnin up burnin up ♪
♪ Out of crushed carbon Build a hope
diamond, Then we run run run run run run ♪
♪ This is my hot house pool party
Like a cool high school party ♪
♪ While the cats away the
mice will play ♪
♪ It's all in our heads
♪ Easy money in my hand Body
under my command I can let go ♪
♪ This is my disco
♪ Easy money in my hand Drawing
lines in the sand I don't tiptoe ♪
♪ This is my disco
♪ You run me like a machine We go
faster You know exactly what ♪
♪ I mean It's all in our heads
Get out of this bed get up ♪
♪ Out of crushed carbon Build
a hope diamond Then we run ♪
♪ This is my disco
Alright, I have a patient
to get to. Adam, would you mind
closing up?
Sure.
Sweet.
Okay, let's go.
Shoot. I don't think I'll
have time to drive you home.
I can drive her.
Okay.
Yeah, no problem.
Yeah. Alright, later guys.
Yeah let's just get this
place cleaned up really quick
and then -
Dude, actually, I
gotta pick up my sister.
But you don't have a car?
Or a sister.
Okay, gotta go. Bye guys.
Have fun cleaning.
Every time we have to clean up.
Need help?
No, don't worry about it.
Just chill out. This won't take
long. So, uhm, what kind of
gymnast are you? Do you jump
around on mats or
swing around on bars?
Wow. You know the technical
terms. I've done it all -
balance beam, uneven bars,
vaults. Now I'm just a girl who
used to be a gymnast.
Once a gymnast,
always a gymnast.
So, where'd you learn to dance?
I learned to
dance on the streets.
Oh, the
streets. Wow. Hard-core.
Mostly my backyard
or in the schoolyard.
So how'd you guys
all get together?
Well we all went to the
same elementary school. But this
whole C.I thing, this is recent.
Michelle's just been laser
focused, she wants
to go big time.
You guys totally could.
You're honestly amazing.
So, do you have a
boyfriend? Smooth.
I mean, I was just wondering
'cause I think Twist thinks
you're really cute.
Oh. He's kinda cute.
Okay I think it's time to
take you home because you're
mentally exhausted or
somethin'. Let's go.
What? What are you doing?
So tell me more
about these auditions.
Ever seen "Dance
for the Moment?"
Both the movie and
the Broadway show.
Well those are Crystal Image
dancers. Look, if you want to
make it as a dancer, you have to
go pro. And making this audition
is the best way to do that.
And what about the clinic?
I love it here. But, dance is
my passion and I'd say passion's
worth a shot, no?
Well you guys need to
gain confidence for acrobatic
stability and that's after many
hours on the floor and that's
before we even start
with the trampolines.
Trampolines? I'm sorry, what
kind of hours are we talking
here?
Well, for expert-hood they
say ten thousand, but since we
don't have that kind of
time... all of them?
Are you crazy?
You just realized that?
Michelle Franklin room
316, Michelle Franklin 316
Look, I gotta run. But,
we'll talk about this later.
Practice starts tonight.
Remember, ten sits and
stands three times a day.
Hey! Look who's ready
to conquer the world.
I'm feeling pretty good.
Michelle's a great motivator.
That she is.
Well, it's my last day here today
and I just wanted to say that -
This is one place where
goodbyes are a good thing. It's
great when people can leave,
especially on their own two
feet.
There should be gold medals
awarded to inspirational people
like you.
What's a medal anyway?
You're gonna be okay.
Go make room 404 proud.
Nice Vicki. Work your snap down.
Keep your weight behind you.
Pierce, I need a favour.
Okay?
Can my dance troupe practice
in here during your off hours?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Since when
do you have a dance troupe?
It's a hip hop group. I'm
just teaching them some flips
and stuff.
Okay.
What?
Nothing. It's just..
Spit it out.
If you're doing hip hop, why
aren't you doing gymnastics?
And where am I going
to do gymnastics, Pierce?
Same place as Isla. UCLA.
You know, I can get you a demo in front
of Coach Val in a couple of weeks.
You really oughta
think about it.
So what about
letting us practice in here?
Well done, Vicki!
Let's see that again.
Wow.
Okay, so last time we did
this everyone had to hold back.
Now we can all let loose and
not worry about anyone breaking
their necks. Okay, so what
do you guys want to do?
I know what I want to do.
Uh, Cashmere, take off those
high heels before you get on
that mat.
♪ You're wonderin' if I'll be back
again You knock me down but ♪
♪ Baby don't count me out I love it,
I love it, I'll never be above it ♪
♪ But you can still watch
me soar I love it, I love it, ♪
♪ I'll never be above it
♪ But you can still watch me soar
How many layers did I shed ♪
♪ When I was lying in that other
bed If fate's a ninja I'm a ♪
♪ Victim of it's karate
Let's do this! Five, six,
seven, eight. One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, and eight.
You know you wanna dance.
Hello.
So, can you give us an
edge? I have an idea.
Knees up. Push
your torso forward.
♪ I'm putting on the gloves
'cause today is another fight ♪
Ok, just let go.
♪ Swinging through the jungle
and hanging on to every vine ♪
♪ The animals keep
on nipping at my heels ♪
Woah! Woah!
Good!
♪ You can pull me down but
I'm made of steel ♪
Put your arms over
your head, and your fingers
♪ I ain't no fool
Mama didn't raise no fool ♪
One and up. Nice.
♪ I make the rules You can knock
me over but I'm getting up again ♪
♪ I ain't no fool Mama didn't
raise no fool I make the rules ♪
♪ You can knock me over
but I'm getting up again ♪
♪ It don't seem right if we
don't give it a shot ♪
♪ We might seem small but we got a lot
going on Until we try, we won't ♪
♪ Know what we got
We see that mountain, ♪
♪ We're holding out
until the top ♪
♪ Like a child taking
everything we want and more ♪
♪ Before we could run we were
moving on dance floors ♪
♪ We make a million miles seem like
twenty four No longer tied up we're ♪
♪ Kicking down the doors
♪ We're kicking down the doors
kicking down the doors ♪
♪ We're kicking down the doors woah
We're kicking down the doors ♪
♪ Kicking down the doors
Come on. Come on.
♪ We're kicking
down the doors woah ♪
♪ It don't seem right if we
don't give it a shot ♪
♪ We see that mountain, We're
holding out until the top ♪
♪ We're holding out
until the top ♪
You're looking
amazing, kid. How's the pain?
Manageable.
Normal human manageable,
or Ariana manageable?
Well, let's say it's manageable.
Look, I know I mentioned this
to you a few weeks ago,
but UCLA is having
some walk-on demos soon.
I don't know.
You should go. Just to try. I
know, you have your dance thing,
but come on do you really
want to leave your entire past
behind? This is
the date and time.
Five, six, seven, eight. One,
two, three, four, five, and six,
seven, eight.
Aight, everyone take
five. This isn't working.
Ok, the problem is we're too
coordinated. We need to loosen
up. Instead of getting together
at this point, let's break off
in a freestyle section. Play to
each of your strengths. Twist,
you've come further than anyone
else with the height, you're
going to do a chest lift off of
Adam since he has the strength.
And then Cashmere, aerials
moving forward, Michelle you're
going to run through it all.
Yeah, but we still need
something bigger to close it.
An aerial section?
No, that would be good enough
for the Palace, but not for C.I.
We need something bigger.
What's the holy grail
of gymnastics, Ariana?
The full out. Two flips with
a full twist. Thought impossible
until the invention of spring
floors. Even elite gymnasts have
a hard time with it. I tried
landing one in practice a few
weeks before my accident. Never
had the chance to try it in
competition.
You could totally do one now. I
mean you are stronger than ever.
Please. Do you know
how tough it would be
with a rod in my femur?
Yeah! Full out, full out,
full out, full out, full out,
full out, full out,
full out, full out-
Yeah, come on. Do a full out!
Yo, if you're gonna gawk, you
gotta pay admission!
Hey, what are you guys doing
here? Isn't it a little late?
Pierce told us that
you skipped out on UCLA.
I'm good.
I didn't think you were
serious about the hip hop thing.
I figured it was a
cover story or something.
Well, here it is.
Who's the Swedish bikini model?
Isla's one of the top
gymnasts in the world. She just
won a Silver medal.
Ariana, this is ridiculous.
Are you really gonna throw away
a chance at college gymnastics
to hangout in alleys making up
dances with low-lifes?
We're five of the top ten
ranked artists in the city.
Sorry, I guess I wouldn't
know about artists. See, I'm
what they call an athlete.
Well, that's good.
Considering that you're
definitely not a stylist.
Stop taking advantage of
Ariana's fragile state, and let
her come back to
where she belongs.
She belongs wherever she
wants. She's here. So why don't
you just do a
little flip outta here.
Oh, you mean like this?
Hold my burrito.
♪ My tape booming out ya speakers
loud we take it back to ♪
♪ The lac with a big old sound I
said my high top shell-toes, ♪
♪ Finished with Velcro big brick
cell phone, keepin' my belt low ♪
♪ I came up where the B-Boys was
at same place where all them ♪
♪ D-Boys was at rollin onto
feeling like the Z-Boys of rap ♪
♪ Round the way girls
sayin' these boys can rap ♪
♪ Now here's a little story
that must be told about the old ♪
♪ School way before the school was
old we made em clap-clap, lose ♪
♪ Control DJ put the
record on cruise control ♪
♪ We got the cardboard taped to the
concrete we rocking with the ♪
♪ All-star crew how it got to be
got us on a big stage paying us ♪
♪ Handsomely shouting out
♪ "all I wanna do is make you
dance with me" ♪
♪ Don't Stop - Put ya hands up
Don't stop - People Stand up ♪
Don't stop -People Stand up Get ♪
♪ Off the wall and get on the
floor scream out loud if you ♪
♪ Want some more rock ya body just
lose control everybody let me ♪
♪ Hear you say Ho-oooooooh
♪ what you wanna do my DJ bumping
out his speakers loud we ♪
♪ At the house party rocking with
that big old sound we do the ♪
♪ Roger Rabbit and the Cabbage
Patch we do the Running Man then ♪
♪ Moon walk from that
♪ take your - Take your front
back spin it all around and ♪
♪ Bring your front back spinning
on the ground and when you done ♪
♪ That DJ playin something make
you come back - DJ Run that ♪
♪ It's a full moon so you
know the beasts come out ♪
You guys are good.
Well, if you watch who you
call a lowlife, I might say the
same to you.
That was actually
pretty impressive.
Why thank you, your highness.
But you're a gymnast, Ariana.
You should be at UCLA with me.
It was very nice to meet
ya'll. You're very talented.
Ariana Berlin, right? I saw
you compete two years ago. You
did well. It's a shame
about the accident.
Yeah.
What can I do to help you?
I'd like to know, what do I
have to do to become a walk on
at UCLA?
You want to walk onto my team?
Yeah.
You realize I get paid to
produce the most elite athletes
in the country.
I've always been a winner
and I'm ready to win again.
Well I'm sure you are. But
that's not enough. Please don't
waste my time.
Sorry to have bothered you.
Ariana, if you're going to
come back to gymnastics, you
need to come back like
you really mean it.
Ma'am, I'm willing to do
anything and everything to be a
part of this team.
Look, I've seen your work
ethic. I know it's good. But can
you give me one
hundred percent commitment?
Absolutely. A hundred
percent. A hundred and ten
percent.
I'll need to see you do a demo.
Sure, yeah.
Right now?
Oh, sorry, did you
mean another time?
No, if you're
ready, then let's do it.
♪ This is game day right here Get
your game face on It's time ♪
♪ To shine
♪ So here we go Deep breath and don't
look down Time to make a move ♪
♪ So here we go
Here we go ♪
The level of difficulty
isn't high enough.
♪ So here we go Deep breath and don't
look down Time to make a move ♪
♪ So here we go
Here we go ♪
Ariana, I told you not to
waste my time. And you didn't.
Welcome to UCLA. You're sweaty.
Thank you, thank you ma'am.
Thank you so much.
Ariana, don't call me ma'am,
sounds old. The other girls call
me Miss Val.
Ok ma'am-I mean Miss Val.
She's good. She's not great.
It'll be good to have a
dancer on the team. The other
girls can learn from her. But
she'll never compete.
Gymnastics all day, hip hop
at night. You sure you're not
pushing yourself too hard?
Heck, when I was her age I
used to play football, baseball
and basketball.
Not all in one day.
I'll be fine Mom.
Just take it easy young lady.
We don't want to have to put you
back together again.
I'll try to pace myself.
Ohhh.
Sure you will.
Yeah.
Ariana, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Do you want help?
No.
Why are you so mad at me?
I never said I was mad at you.
Not in so many words. Mainly 'cause
you don't say anything to me anymore.
Why do you keep
shutting me out? Are you okay?
Stop asking me that!
Look, I didn't cause your
accident. What was I supposed to
do, stop living my life?
I don't want to talk about it.
Look, I wish you were at
the games too. But it is not my
fault.
She's hit a plateau. It's one
amateur mistake after another.
Can you talk to her?
Help her find her focus.
Why me?
Because she'll listen to you.
I think it coming from me it's
more pressure.
Well Miss Val, Isla and
I don't really talk much.
I thought you two were friends?
We kinda fell out.
Well fall back in, Ariana.
This is a gymnastics team and
your teammate needs your help.
Isla! Wait! Where are you going?
Just to the bus stop. My dad
left without me so...
Why?
He said he can't even
look at me right now.
Do you want to talk about it?
Val set you up for this, didn't
she? I bet you didn't want to.
Isla, it was always my dream
to go to the Olympics and win a
medal and then go to UCLA
and have lots of fun. But that
didn't happen, instead you got
it all. And I guess it's just
hard for me to watch
from the sidelines.
Really?
Yeah, really.
I thought you were mad at me.
Well I guess I was a bit mad
about the whole Nate
thing, but I'm over it.
I'm so sorry about that. I
should have told you the truth
but it's over and
it didn't work out.
It's okay. And I'll
still always know that you peed
yourself on that bus.
Well, just so you know, the
Olympics weren't all that great.
Don't believe the hype.
Are you serious?
No! They were amazing and you
needed to be there. It was so
awful that you weren't. I
missed you the whole time.
I bet you did? Especially
when you blew that dismount.
Well at least I was there
and not slacking off in some
hospital room.
Well at least I
got free pudding!
Well, you're getting your
revenge now. I peaked and it's
been downhill ever since.
You can break out of it.
Oh I would love to just
forget about gymnastics for a
little while.
What?
Hey. I haven't seen or heard
from you in weeks. I was about
to bust down your door.
I was sick.
There's no time to be sick.
Auditions are twelve days away.
Check what we've got it on.
They don't know you're back
on the gymnastics team, do they?
I just haven't
figured out how to tell them.
Or have you not
figured out what you want?
I miss hating you
for knowing me so well.
Hi.
Chill cheese fries?
No, no. I can't.
Sure you can.
No seriously. My
coach will kill me.
I, I don't see any
coaches around here.
Okay but, just,
just a little bit.
Okay just a-
Just a small-
Just a small-That's pretty
big but yeah go for it. It's
good, just, just
try it. Just try it.
Okay. Oh that's good.
See, this is what I do. I
bring joy to the people. Want
another one?
Just one more.
Okay.
Just one.
I'm going to take one too.
Really good.
Oh okay. Alright.
So you feel like
putting on a show?
I don't know.
We just got here.
Guys, let's dance. Come on.
♪ I can't believe we've
not met yet Now talk to me ♪
♪ I'm tired of seeking blindly
I'm tired of hiding in plain ♪
♪ Sight
Come set me free ♪
♪ One, two three this party
goes all night One last chance ♪
♪ Before we say goodbye I need to know
your name Boy, It's such a shame ♪
♪ Take my hands, throw'em up in the
sky I hope your heart beats faster ♪
♪ When it's close to mine
Before we run out of time ♪
♪ We'll dance all night ♪
Go Isla!
Rest time is as important as
training time. You have got to
give this up.
I know you're upset, but
that's what got me back into
gymnastics.
It got you moving again, it
got you motivated. But look at
you, you're tired and
you're burning out.
I don't know if you noticed,
but Isla spent one night around
that stuff and
she's back on track.
Ariana you've got to start
thinking about what's important
to you. And start making the
right choices. You've gotta feel
it in here. This is where it
matters the most. So what's it
gonna be? What family are you
gonna choose? Are you gonna
choose the one that will put
you on the road to becoming a
champion? Or are you gonna
choose the one that could lead
you to being a back up
dancer in some rap video?
It's not fair.
You focus on one or you
fail at both. It's that simple.
Hey.
What's up?
Nothing. Just starting to
realize my limitations I guess.
I don't think you know the
meaning of limitations. They
literally could not stop you
unless they hit you with a car.
Thanks.
I think you're
really cool, Ariana.
You're pretty cool yourself.
Let's go warm up. So I heard
you really brought it at
the dance jam the other day.
Well I'm paying for it today.
Is there anything I can do to
take your mind off of it?
You just keep massaging,
Mr. That's what I'm good at.
I can't do this. There's
something I need to tell you.
Hey it's the dancing queen.
Did you see the video we posted
last night?
Yeah, I did. And
so did my coach.
Coach? What coach?
I need to tell you guys
something. I can't dance with
you anymore. My coach wants me
to focus entirely on gymnastics.
What?
Why didn't you say something?
I didn't know how to. Look,
it's not an easy decision, but
I've been doing gymnastics my
entire life.
They're like my family.
And what are we?
Cashmere, you know it's not
like that. I can't do both.
Really? After everything
we've been through? This is it.
I'm really sorry.
Let's go.
Where are you guys going?
We can still practice. Adam?
See you later, Ariana.
It's alright Soph.
Are you kidding me? Where is
your head? Why are you waiting
for the audience to give
you your performance and your
energy. Why are waiting for
that? It's like you only come
alive when your audience notices
you. Your performance starts
from the moment you step on
this floor. Not when you get the
applause. Now someone better
show me a collegiate level
performance or we're going to
start an hour early everyday
this week. Ariana, you're up.
Sometime today please.
Full out. Backhand, snap
down, round off reach into the
back handspring, and then
tuck. Reach back into the back
handspring stay tight. Pull
legs. Squeeze legs tight to
turn. Spot the landing.
What was that?
A double back with a full
twist. A Full Out. But I kinda
missed the landing. Sorry.
I know what a Full Out is.
I meant your music, your whole
routine. What was that?
Background
dancing for a rap video?
♪ Go go she go she go we get down
we get to the Go go she go she go ♪
♪ Go go she go she go Get
down we Go go she go she go ♪
♪ Go go she go she go Go go she go
she go Go go she go she go we ♪
♪ Get down we get to the
I still think we have
a chance. I honestly do.
Hey.
Well look who it is. The
gymnast. Nadia don't-a-need-ya.
And how long have you
been waiting to use that one?
She thought it up after
the last time we saw you.
Guys, I kinda need a favour.
Can you teach my gymnastics team
a few hip hop moves?
And why can't you?
I can only show them so
much. You guys are the experts.
You walked out on us.
Why should we help you?
Agreed.
Bring it in.
Come on, bring it in.
She didn't walk out on us.
Alright? She's a gymnast and
gymnasts have to train. Don't
you think we owe her a little
pay back for all the things
she's helped us with? Twist,
man, if Ariana wasn't there you
would have for sure broken your
neck on that gain. And Cashmere,
who do you think taught you that
incredible back handspring pass?
Adam's right. Surprising
because he's never right. But
this time I agree. Okay, fine.
We'll teach your sorority
sisters a little soul.
That's great. Because
They just got here. Yeah.
♪ You run me like a machine We go
faster You know exactly what ♪
♪ I mean It's all in our heads
Get out of this bed get up ♪
♪ Easy money in my hand Body
under my command I can let go ♪
♪ This is my disco Easy money in
my hand Drawing lines in the ♪
♪ Sand I don't tiptoe
This is my disco ♪
♪ This is my Disco
♪ You run me like a machine We go
faster You know exactly what ♪
♪ I mean It's all in our heads
Get out of this bed get up ♪
♪ Out of crushed carbon Build a
hope diamond Then we run run run ♪
♪ This be like a hammer in my
chest My heart is pumping ♪
♪ Through my vest I know
exactly what it means ♪
Hey.
Hey. Hey!
Hey you wanna show me how to
do those fancy spins of yours?
Come on.
I hope you don't think I
kind of ditched you guys.
You more than kind of ditched
us. But, I don't blame you for
getting back to what you're
meant to do. I don't know how
we're going to make it at this
audition, but if we do, it's
because of you.
That is not true. You guys
are an amazing team. Here. It's
the medal from my first
meet. I want you to have it.
So are you going to
be at the audition?
I can't. Coach Val wants
me at practice that day.
No problem. Come on.
♪ Easy money in my hand Body
under my command I can let go ♪
♪ This is my disco Easy money in
my hand Drawing lines in the ♪
♪ Sand I don't tiptoe This is
my disco This is my disco ♪
♪ You run me like a machine We go
faster You know exactly what I mean ♪
♪ It's all in our heads Get
out of this bed get up ♪
We're learning life
skills. That's what's important.
But I do respect the discipline
needed for training. If you're
going to do a sit-up, you do
that one sit-up the very best
that you can. You don't take
anything for granted. You don't
assume that you have tomorrow.
Everything we do in life is a
choice. Everything. And those
choices dictate the kind of life
that you're gonna lead. And as
soon as you can understand that,
then you start to take ownership
of your life, you start to be
able to design your life to turn
out whatever way you want it to.
And I have a secret for you,
this isn't about gymnastics.
It's about life.
Hello?
Hey. I just wanted to
wish you luck one last time.
Listen, we just got tossed a
huge curve ball. It's Ariana.
Wait, what's going on?
The usual.
Is your inhaler working?
I just need a minute.
Hey, yeah, no, she's seen
this before, she'll be fine. I
just don't think
she'll be able to dance.
Well who's going to
do the handspring pass?
I guess we're just gonna have
to lose it. Okay, gotta go.
Bruins, let's go!
Miss Val?
Yes, Ariana.
Remember when you told me
to feel it? Now I know what you
mean. I'm feeling it.
Well that's great,
Ariana. Now you go get ready.
What I'm saying is, I'm
really, really feeling it.
Are you okay?
Next up, team G-Raid.
♪ Oh I've been down down lately
but I'm coming' up ♪
♪ Ohh I'm coming' up
♪ I'm off the ground now
baby and I'm coming' up ♪
♪ Ohh I'm coming up
♪ You know I'm comin'
up-up-up-up-up-up-up-up-up-up ♪
♪ Just live for the moment Let
me know that you want it ♪
♪ We got this locked and
loaded I'm coming up ♪
♪ You know I'm comin'
up-up-up-up-up-up-up-up-up-up ♪
♪ Just live for the moment Let me
know that you want it I'm comin' up ♪
♪ Up, I'm comin' up-up-up Base
____ bass I'm comin' up Bass ♪
♪ ____ Bass I'm comin' up-up-up-up
Come along children ♪
♪ Base I'm comin' up
Aight y'all, let me watch
you guys run it from the top.
What for? We're done.
How are we going
to go on without you?
We'll be out of
balance. It won't look right.
Then we'll improvise?
We'll make it work. Just go
full out and hope for the best.
Okay?
♪ I'm off the ground now
baby and I'm coming' up ♪
♪ Ohh I'm coming up You know I'm
comin' up-up-up-up-up-up-up-up-up-up ♪
Next up! Team Soul Flow.
It's now or never.
Just make this work, okay?
Let's do this.
♪ Got that booty Alright
Hey number tutti fruity ♪
♪ Get on the floor if you got that
booty You know you wanna dance. ♪
♪ One, two three, hit it. Hey number
tutti fruity Get on the floor if you ♪
♪ Got that booty.
Alright ♪
♪ Hey number tutti fruity Get on
the floor if you got that booty. ♪
Thank you.
We'll let you know.
Thank you for
that. You saved us.
You owe me one.
Oh okay, is that how it is now?
Mhm.
If gonna keep keeping
score like this we might find
ourselves into some trouble.
Nice timing.
UCLA need a 9.85 to finish
with the National Championship
title. It appears that Coach
Kondos Field is gonna be putting
Ariana Berlin up last
on the floor routine.
Only a few years ago Ariana
made a huge comeback into the
world of gymnastics after
suffering a debilitating car
accident.
I was watching practice
earlier today and it seemed like
Ariana was having a lot of
difficulty with her final
tumbling pass. The Full Out.
This is a somewhat
controversial move for Coach
Kondos Field. We'll
see how she does.
Thought you said she
was never going to compete?
Did I say that?
♪ We will come alive
The music never dies ♪
♪ We've been high and low Pulls us
under Light's beyond the door ♪
♪ Never let it go Won't let these
locked doors Shut me out anymore ♪
♪ I will break them down
Let the daylight show we... ♪
We all have our ups and
downs, but it's how you deal
with them that defines who you
are. You must do the thing that
you think you cannot do.
What do you think? She
gonna stick the landing?
Focus. Two flips with a full
twist. Push off with the right
leg, momentum
through the round off.
Gymnastics is
pretty much off the table.
She'll never compete.
I have a metal rod in
my leg. Mom, watch out!
You're not ready. You can't
do this. Get up. You're broken.
You'll never compete.
Look, sometimes when the
front door gets slammed in your
face you have to go
through the back door.
You don't take anything for
granted. You don't assume that
you have tomorrow.
You're gonna be okay.
There's always a way in.
Go make room 404 proud. Get up.
You've got this. You've got this.
You've got this.
Let the daylight show
Mind if I borrow this?
Nope.
I realize this is kind of
unorthodox, but nothing about
the past few years of my life
has been orthodox, so here it
goes. Several years ago, I was
told by my doctors that I was
likely to never do gymnastics
again. But I didn't believe
them. I had a bunch of
people who stood behind me and
encouraged me every step of the
way. I want to give a special
shoutout to my friend, Caity,
because I know you're watching
this right now. Caity, even
though you're a little behind me
in your recovery, you'll be
running circles around me
forever. With every person
you make walk again, the world
becomes a better place. There's
no medal for that, but what's a
medal anyway, right? And
Michelle, there's definitely no
medal I could give you to truly
show my thanks. But I just might
be able to get you your million
hits. That's gotta be worth
something, right?
♪ I'm putting on the gloves
'cause today is another fight ♪
♪ Swinging through the jungle
and hanging on to every vine ♪
♪ The animals keep on nipping at my
heels You can pull me down but ♪
♪ I'm made of steel
♪ I ain't no fool Mama didn't
raise no fool I make the rules ♪
♪ You can knock me over
but I'm getting up again ♪
♪ I ain't no fool Mama didn't
raise no fool I make the rules ♪
♪ You can knock me over
but I'm getting up again ♪
♪ Flying through the air like a
daredevil acrobat I can do it on ♪
♪ My own without no safety net Let
my engine purr like a wildcat ♪
♪ I'm facing you now you
see whatcha can't get ♪
♪ I ain't no fool Mama didn't
raise no fool I make the rules ♪
♪ You can knock me over
but I'm getting up again ♪
Is that from Crystal Image?
Guys, it's not good
news... it's great news.
What?
Let me see this.
We won?
We won Crystal Image!
♪ I ain't no fool Mama didn't
raise no fool I make the rules ♪
♪ You can knock me over but I'm
getting up again I ain't no fool ♪
♪ Mama didn't raise no fool I make
the rules You can knock me over ♪
♪ But I'm getting up again I ain't
no fool Mama didn't raise no fool ♪
♪ I make the rules
Mama didn't raise no fool ♪
♪ I make the rules You can knock
me over but I'm getting up again ♪
Just kidding.
Hey Ari! Wow. You
nailed it out there.
Could you imagine what
it would be like to make the
Olympics?
It would be so unbelievable
but I doubt it's something I'll
ever get to experience.
Me neither. I
wish I could go.
I think Miss Val is the most
brilliant woman on the planet.
Really? Do you know her?
I don't, but I would love
to get to know her some day.
She's good. She's not great.
Who's that on the bars?
Ariana Berlin.
From San Diego.
She's gonna be a star.