(music box playing)
- [Little Girl] Uncle
Henry, tell me a story.
- [Henry] No, it's late.
Go to bed.
Santa will be here soon.
- [Little Girl] No, I want a story.
Please.
- [Henry] All right, all right.
You want a happy story or
you want a scary story'?
- [Little Girl] I want
a happy scary story.
- [Henry] A happy scary story?
- [Little Girl] Yeah.
' [Henry] Fine.
Once upon a time there
lived a man by the name,
by the name of Jack Frost.
- [Little Girl] Jack Frost?
- [Henry] That's right.
Like in the song, Jack
Frost nipping at your nose.
(laughter)
Only this guy did it for real.
- [Little Girl] Uh.
- [Henry] You know how regular
folk get up in the morning,
eat something and then hurry off to do
whatever for the day.
- [Little Girl] Um, hm.
- [Henry] Well Jack would get up,
eat something, then hurry
off and kill someone.
'Cause that's what he
did; he killed people.
He'd stick knives in their
faces and cut out their tummies.
And stamp on their heads till their
brains got all runny.
- [Little Girl] Uncle Henry I
don't think this is such a--
- [Henry] You wanted a
story, you got a story.
- [Little Girl] Uh, okay.
But why did he hurt people?
- [Henry] How should I know'?
Maybe his mum and dad
never gave him enough hugs.
Maybe they gave him too many hugs.
Or maybe he just liked the color red
and things that went
squish when he stuck
sharp points in them.
- [Little Girl] Oh.
- [Henry] It doesn't matter.
The only thing that's important
is that no one could catch him.
Some say that Jack was a ghost,
that he was already dead and could
walk through walls or
vanish into thin air.
- [Little Girl] Oh.
- [Henry] Truth is he
never stayed in one place
long enough to be caught.
See Jack was smart.
He'd drift into a town, blend in,
puree a few of the locals then just
drift off to some place else that
needed a little social pruning.
Any towns that
had too many little girls
that looked just like you.
- [Little em] But they
did catch him didn't
they Uncle Henry?
- [Henry] Well, for five years through
11 states and 38 deaths.
Jack was nimble,
Jack was quick, Jack gouged
eyes with candlesticks.
Smashed in skulls with
sticks and stones.
Used iron bars to crush their bones.
So he could
hide his kills in tiny places
and he wouldn't have
to see their faces.
- [Little Girl] Uncle Henry.
- [Henry] That is until the pies.
- [Little Girl] Pies?
- [Henry] Yeah, little bits
of people started turning
up in Mrs. Puddles pecan
pies all over the Midwest.
Fingertips, eyelids, ear lobes.
Mm-hm, some say
that Jack had got sloppy
or that deep down he
really wanted to be caught.
Others said that it made
the pies taste better.
- [Little em] Eww.
- [Henry] Bottom line; Jack
had made his first mistake.
Authorities knew where he worked.
Within a week they traced his car.
Then it was just a
matter of time before
he was caught, tried,
and sentenced to die.
- [Little Girl] Oh.
- [Henry] In fact, right this
very moment Jack is being
taken to his place of execution.
His story should end at midnight
but the fun's just about to begin.
So why don't you go to bed
and have sweet, sweet dreams.
(christmas music)
- Tell you something; that
murdering bastard Jack Frost
in here is one lucky son of a bitch.
- Lucky'?
He's being executed in 30 minutes.
- Yeah well, at least he
doesn't have to drive back
through this crap.
- Deep fried Jack sewed at midnight.
(laughter)
(ominous music)
- Say pal'?
How about a smoke?
(lighter striking)
- Say Frost, why don't
you shut the hell up?
(exhaling smoke)
- Filtered.
(christmas music)
- Hey, Jack we just crossed
the Snowmonton county line.
Ain't this where you screwed up'?
- Screwed up'?
- Yeah, for years the FBI was chasing
this overgrown piece of shit.
Crossed like half a dozen states.
Then this backwater sheriff plays hero
for five minutes and
takes all the glory.
(laughter)
Ain't how it happened Jack?
Almost got away with it didn't you?
Haw'?
Everything okay back there Harv?
- Oh we're doing fine, real fine.
(neck snapping)
(light piano music)
(ominous music)
(coffee sloshing into cap)
- What--
- The...
- Fuck--
(brakes squealing)
(screaming)
- Oh yeah.
(screaming and vehicles crashing)
(wind blowing)
(fire roaring)
(thumping)
(creaking)
(heavy breathing and footsteps)
(handcuffs clinking)
(laughter)
- Looks like deep fried
Jack is off the menu
for tonight, huh'?
- Jesus Christ.
(creaking)
- Now, we can do this the easy way
Of we can--
(door bursting open)
This is gonna hurt.
(chemicals exploding from truck)
(screaming)
(ominous music)
(gun shots)
(car engine)
(car radio playing)
- Honey, you're miles away.
- I'm all right.
- It's after midnight.
No more stays of execution.
It's over.
No more nightmares about Jack Frost.
(police radio)
(door opening and shutting)
(footsteps)
- Hi there.
Engine problems'?
- Bladder problem.
- I'm gonna need to see
your license please.
Stay away from the vehicle please.
- Make up your god damn mind.
You want to see my license
or do you want
me to stay here?
It's your move Sheriff.
- I want you to stay
away from the vehicle
and lie down on the ground.
(ominous music)
- This one you are gonna regret.
That's right Sheriff you take a good
long look at this face.
'Cause the next time
you see it it's gonna
tear your world apart.
I'll find a way.
I'll tear your town apart.
I'll kill your family.
I'll kill you.
You're dead.
You hear me'?
Dead.
- Honey, honey, honey'?
Slow down.
- What's going on'?
Whoa.
Touch my finger, touch my knee.
Thank the Lord it was not me.
Wow, there's an ambulance.
Can we stop please'?
- Oh I don't think so.
Now you just settle down we'll be home
in about 20 minutes.
- There's two squad cars,
an ambulance.
- And a partridge in a pear tree.
- That's very nice Ryan.
- Sweetie put your seat belt on.
- What happened here officer?
I'm with the local--
- Keep it moving sir
this is a federal matter.
- Okay.
(police radio)
- Then it just ran off.
But he couldn't run.
It was, it was like
he was trying but he
didn't have legs.
Like he was part of the snow.
- What the--
- I'll take it from here.
You the man who
witnessed the incident?
Let's you and me take a
little midnight stroll.
(police radio)
(footsteps)
(christmas music and news broadcast)
(door creaking)
- The driveway is clear.
- It's all over the news.
- Yeah, I was listening
to it on the car radio.
(news broadcast)
- Dad, who's Jack Frost?
- Jack Frost was a very bad man honey
but now he's gone.
Poof.
- Like magic?
- Yeah that's right, just like magic.
- And is he coming back'?
- No.
So you don't have to worry about him.
- And you made him go
away, didn't you dad?
- Well I kind of helped I guess.
- My dad's a hero.
- No son, I just happened to be
in the right place at the wrong time.
I'm not a hero.
- You are to me.
- Me too.
- Oh come on now.
You're gonna get all mushy
and I got a job to go to.
- But I made you special.
(laughter)
- Oh yum Ryan, that looks great.
Uh look, I think I'm
gonna save this for lunch.
Okay?
I'll put it in a baggie--
- Coward.
- And I'll have it for lunch.
Okay?
- Take some more.
- Thanks.
Fill it up.
- Sam'?
- What?
It's okay, it's going to be okay.
Come on, fill it up.
- Dad, can I build a snowman
for the competition today?
- Oh sure, how else you
gonna win first prize.
But I want you all wrapped up.
Okay?
And the tree trimming
is at 5:00 sharp.
- How could we forget'?
- Yeah.
No, no, no, no.
(giggling)
- You're toast Mr. Snowman.
(christmas music and laughter)
(christmas music)
(car breaks squealing)
- Hey, hey no looking 'till Saturday.
You know the rules.
- Come on Dad.
- No, not until Saturday.
You're gonna jinx us.
- [Female] Look at this over here.
(car door shutting)
- [Female] Hey Sam!
Oh oh Alex come here for a second.
- [Alex] What do you want?
- Morning Jake.
I see you couldn't get to that porch
railing while we were away.
- No I didn't get to it.
I'll do it.
- Sure, by New Year's?
- Yeah I said I'll do it.
- Great.
_ Hey hey hey.
- Hi Jill.
- Hi Mr. Tyler.
- I'm making angel wings.
- Oh that's beautiful Sally.
- Sally you want to help me with this?
- You know when I was a little girl
I always wanted to be the angel
on top of the Christmas tree.
- Good.
You want to help me tie this now'?
- Sure honey.
- How's it going there Billy?
- It's going.
- I see your dad's got his snowman
all covered up; big secret.
- I guess.
- Well he may win for the 5th year
in a row, right'?
That's a pretty big deal.
- Whatever.
- Well, nice talking to you Billy.
- Working hard Tommy'?
- Hey there Mr. T how you doing'?
Everybody, the law is back in town.
So Mr. T, what do you think?
It's a snow babe.
I'm gonna call her Cindy Snowflake.
(laughter)
- I think it's very cool Tommy.
- All right.
Hey wait a second.
What's the difference between snowmen
and snow-women'?
- Tommy.
- Now really, what's the difference?
- I'll see ya Tommy.
- It's snowballs.
Gel it Mr. T'?
Snowballs.
(honking)
- Hey Bob.
(car engine)
Morning Paul.
I saw your Tommy.
- Keeping out of trouble I hope.
- As ever.
- I heard about, uh, Jack Frost.
End of an era.
- End of a nightmare.
- I'll find a way!
- Sam you okay'?
- Oh yeah yeah.
No I'm great.
I'm great Paul.
- So you, uh, dig out your
driveway this morning?
Huh'?
(laughter)
- Up at 6:00 AM.
- Okay all right,
you come in the store,
I'll give you 20% off because I think
you're about the best
law enforcement officer
we ever had around these parts.
All right'?
- Maybe next season Paul.
- Okay.
Hold on, you know what the difference
is between a snowman and a snow--
- I heard this one Paul.
- Oh, okay.
(footsteps)
Uh Tommy!
- Good morning Tommy.
- Oh hi Jill.
- Whatcha making Tommy?
- Oh this?
Um, nothing.
Just uh, I mean it's
not supposed to be you.
- So uh you want to meet up later?
- Later?
Um, actually you know kind of busy.
Busy stuff, doing a lot of things.
I don't know if I can make it over.
- We can go snowballing.
- Tommy we got salt, ice, you know.
Deliveries.
Come on.
(car engine)
(car door opening and closing)
(footsteps)
- But daddy I made those
oats special for you.
(footsteps)
(door opening and whistling)
- Morning Marla.
(blow dryer)
Where is everybody?
Well good morning to you too Sam.
And how are you on this fine morning'?
How was your weekend skiing?
Well Marla you know I
don't like to ski myself
but Ryan and Anne told me
they had a really gnarly time.
What's the matter, somebody die'?
(rocking chair creaking)
- Shit Sam, we ain't had a killing
in the county all our lives.
- I knew Old Man Harper ever since I
learned how to steal
apples from his orchard.
- We all did Chris, we all did.
So what do you got'?
- Nothing.
- What do you mean nothing'?
You got to have something.
- Look about Sam.
We got no vehicle tracks.
- No footprints in the snow.
- I got no sign
of a struggle or attempt
to break into the house.
- No blood.
- Nothing.
Nothing.
- All right, I don't want
this thing spreading anymore
than it needs to.
The whole town will go crazy.
Why don't you get Doc Peters?
Take your foot off the chair.
Get Doc Peters on the phone,
tell him to come up here.
- Yeah.
- Why don't you go
down to Donna's motel,
the gas station, liquor store;
ask them if anybody
passed through last night.
Tell them a feed store
was robbed or something.
- Feed store, right.
Sam, what are you gonna be doing'?
- I got to make sure of something.
(footsteps)
(car door opening)
Marla put me through
to the FBI will ya'?
- Will you get me some apples?
(laughter)
- Show me two hours no
injuries, natural obstacles.
- [Female] I have a sheriff
from Snowmonton County
on the phone for you
asking about Jack Frost.
- Put him through.
This is Agent Manners;
who am I speaking to?
- Uh, Sam Tyler, Snowmonton
County Sheriff's Department.
I'd like to ask you a
couple of questions about
the Jack Frost accident.
- Well I'm afraid
that most information
concerning the incident
is confidential
but I'll help you if I can.
- Well we had a killing
down here last night
and I need to know that
Jack Frost is really dead.
- Oh yeah Sheriff, Jack
Frost did indeed die
in the accident;
that I can assure you.
Anything else I can help you with?
- No, thank you very much.
- Not a problem.
Good luck with your investigation.
- Thank you.
(signing)
It's over.
- It started.
- It wasn't meant to happen like this.
- So you keep saying.
- We hadn't even tested
the acid on an amoeba.
Let alone a human cell.
This is a disaster.
- Disaster?
You got to learn to look on
the bright side of things.
- The bright side?
- Sure.
At least you know it works.
It's just a shame that your guinea pig
had to be a homicidal
maniac like Jack Frost.
Who I now have to put
back in the test tube.
- Well, there are no lesions
in the muscles of the neck.
No tears.
Now, there is a fractured
cervical vertebrae one and two.
So I'm guessing that his
head was snapped back
with alarming force but just the once.
Also notice that there's
no bruising in the face.
So I would say something soft was held
in place to disperse the pressure.
Like, a mitten or a large glove.
- That's all we need around here;
the catcher mitt killer.
- Yeah.
You think he's gonna strike again?
- I don't know doc but I'll
be bolting my door tonight.
- I'll be tracking my
dresser in front of mine Sam.
(car pulling into the driveway)
(car door opening)
(bags rustling)
(car door closing)
(footsteps)
(ominous music and dog barking)
(creepy christmas music)
(door opening)
- Look, I made special.
- Honey I just cleaned up
after your special oats.
- But these are extra special.
- They're very, not as
special as that snowman
that you made outside.
- I didn't make a snowman.
- Oh, well someone built it.
But it's not finished.
Needs a face so I
thought that maybe you
could go outside
and finish that up for--
(running)
I'll just spray down the kitchen.
(panicked chatter)
- Sam what's going on'?
- What the hell are you
going to do about this?
- All right, hold it hold it hold it.
- I tried to calm them down, I tried.
- There's no need to panic.
- What the hell are
you talking about Sam?
Old Man Harper's dead.
- That's right, Old Man
Harper has been killed
and we don't have a lead.
But you guys running
around here like a
a bunch of vigilantes
isn't going to make
my job any easier.
- Right.
- Now I suggest you men
go home to your families.
- Jesus, you think this
psycho drifters gonna
snub out some other
poor son of a bitch.
Don't ya?
- Did I say that?
Did I say that?
Look, Old Man Harper
lived way out here
five miles outside of town.
- What does that mean'?
We all live on the outskirts of town.
- Right, and so do we
and we're not scared.
Now whoever did this
is already a 100 miles
away from here.
- Yeah Sam, well that may
be but I'll tell ya what;
I'm going to keep
my store open all hours,
anybody wants to buy extra ammo, huh.
20% discount for an emergency.
Come on, come on.
(group chatter)
- It's gonna be a
gal dang turkey shoot.
- Of hell Sam it's
quicker than a jury.
(tires screeching)
- So you reckon you're about ready
to step out to lunch with me then?
- Do I look ready?
- Sure do to me.
(spraying aerosol spray)
- Ah, luckily for you Joe the power
to cloud men's minds
is a responsibility
I take very seriously.
(makeup mirror snapping shut)
(trashcan banging against leg)
(ominous music)
(rustling)
(birds cawing)
(ominous music)
- Hey move it.
I said move it.
Or are you deaf as well as butt ugly'?
You're standing in the
middle of a black ice
sled run snot for brains.
- But this is my dad's front lawn.
- Look, are you gonna move
or am I gonna
have to kick your
stomach out the top of
your head again'?
(signing)
- I hope he breaks his face.
- What'd you say'?
- Nothing.
- Look, nobody says
nothing behind my back.
The killer snowman, is it yours?
- Yes.
No!
- Oh yes.
I think the black ice sled
run is officially open.
And all the kings horses
and all the kings men
couldn't give a rats ass
about Tyler's little snowman.
Huh.
(screaming)
- I didn't do it.
- Holy moly Ryan killed Billy!
- It wasn't me.
(ominous music)
- Billy just had a birthday.
(light christmas music
and soft crowd chatter)
(crying)
- Shh, it's okay.
- Will you please stop
telling me to calm down'?
Shut up!
I'm not nuts!
There's one god damn
psycho in this town
and it's your kid Sheriff.
- Jay, Jay-
- That kid is touched by the devil.
- Honey don't.
- Let's take this somewhere
else, come on.
- This is okay with me right here.
- Look, I am truly sorry
about what happened
but I have to believe my son.
- Your son says a snowman
pushed my son Billy.
Do you believe that'?
- There couldn't have been a fight.
Billy is two feet taller than Ryan.
- [Female] Not anymore he ain't.
- You haven't heard the last of this.
- L, I believe that.
I believe that Jay.
- And you watch
the way you talk to me.
I'm not above punching
an officer of the law
if it calls for it.
- Why don't you go home and calm down?
We'll talk about this tomorrow.
- 'Cause I can't
talk about it tomorrow.
'Cause I got to look for a
place to bury my son tomorrow.
Jill, Sally, we're
going home, come on.
- He's usually not so short tempered.
- I know, I know.
- I'm sorry.
(horn honking)
(footsteps)
- All right, why don't we all
just go on home, all right?
Let's keep Billy in our prayers.
(footsteps)
- I didn't do it.
The snowman pushed him.
- That's all he keeps saying.
He must be terrified.
- I know Ryan.
I know.
(ominous music)
(gas stove lighting)
(humming)
(knife hitting cutting board)
(ominous music)
(chopping celery)
(stirring soup)
- You take a good
long look at this face
'cause the next time
you see it it's gonna
tear your world apart.
I'll find a way.
I'll kill you and your whole--
- I thought you destroyed those.
(signing)
- I wish it was that easy.
- Sam, he's gone
and he can't come back.
The only place he
exists now is in here.
I'm gonna destroy these.
(rustling papers)
(crash outside)
(ominous music)
(cocking handgun)
(lampshade clanging)
(ominous music)
(door opening)
- Oh, Jesus Sam.
- Well, gosh sakes
I could have shot you.
(laughter)
- Well Sam hell, everybody knows
you couldn't hit
the broadside of a barn
with a scatter gun.
(laughter)
Annie hi, evening.
- Hi Paul.
- Uh, where you want the salt?
Garage is all locked up.
- The salt?
Why don't you just put it right there.
- All right, didn't
mean to scare you Sam.
- That's all right were
just a little jumpy tonight.
All right'?
- Oh, okay all right.
- I'll see you in the morning.
- All right.
- Thanks for the salt.
- 20% off on the salt too.
- I'll see you in the morning.
- [Paul] And I'll give you
20% off of that garbage can.
- Paul, thank you.
- [Paul] Your snow shovel's
not looking very good either.
(door closing)
Okay.
(christmas music)
- Don't ya think we ought
to put the tree lights on'?
(christmas music)
- Your son isn't cold five hours
you want festivities.
- I was only--
- Yeah, well don't.
(christmas music)
(footsteps)
- Hey!
And where in God's name
do you think you're
prowling off to like
some lady of the night?
Our grief isn't good enough for you?
You may not have cared
for your little brother--
- Jesus dad, I loved Billy.
- Do not be forsaking the Lord's name
in my house little girl!
- The Lord forsook
this house long ago.
I'm going to see Tommy.
(christmas music)
(footsteps)
(door opening)
- She's only talking back to you
because she's upset.
(christmas music)
- Sally, when I want
philosophy I'll turn on Oprah.
Finish my scarf.
I'm going to get more wood.
(christmas music)
(door opening)
- I'll make us a pot of tea.
(chain clanking)
(footsteps)
(ominous music)
(match striking)
- [Jack] Say pal, how about a smoke'?
(laughter)
(ominous music)
- Who's that?
What's that?
Sam?
Hey Sam.
Sam is that you?
(ominous music)
You come to make peace?
(laughter)
(ominous music)
- [Jack] Yeah, get it.
Put your back into it.
Come on, come on, you can do it.
That's my boy.
Get it, get it, oh very good.
(laughter)
(ominous music)
- All right, all right come on.
Come on you god damn psycho freak.
I'm ready for you.
(ominous music)
Come out here where I can see you
you Christ loathing dog.
(ominous music)
(footsteps)
I'm warning you.
(ominous music)
(gasping)
- [Jack] Gosh, I only
axed you for a smoke.
(laughter)
(ominous music)
- Oh Jake, if
I've asked you once I've--
(ominous music)
Oh.
(footsteps)
(humming)
(ominous music)
Oh Jake, that's so sweet of you.
That's funny.
(ominous music)
(footsteps)
(ornaments rattling on tree)
(ominous music)
Oh.
(fast paced christmas music)
(ornaments breaking
and muffled screaming)
(fast paced christmas music)
(star buzzing)
(knocking)
- Oh, sorry folks.
Shed was all blocked.
I didn't know where
you wanted the salt.
- [Jack] Ho, ho, ho, and what's your
name little boy'?
(laughter)
- Oh my god.
(ominous music)
- [Jack] Always remember
to dress up warm.
(laughter)
(heavy breathing)
- I just came over here to tell them
all how sorry I was about Billy.
Jesus Sam.
- All right, Joe.
We're gonna do this thing calmly.
I want you to get the photographer--
- For Christ's sake, who
the hell would do this?
Well someone's got to go tell Jill
her entire family's dead.
Jesus, she's only 18.
- Keep it down Joe.
The whole town's gonna go crazy.
I need for you to keep it together.
We got a job to do.
We're gonna do it right.
First I want you
to find Jill and I want
you to get Doc Peters
and bring him up here.
Take a look at Sally.
- You don't reckon we
should leave her up
for the 12 days of Christmas then?
(gagging)
(horn honking)
(footsteps)
(wind howling)
(door opening and shutting)
- Marla I want you to call around
see if you can
get a hold of Jill Metzner.
Oh, call the FBI in Denver too.
Some asshole named Manners.
Who are you'?
(footsteps)
- I'm the asshole.
I'll get back to you later.
Well, this is an auspicious
start we've gotten off to.
You must be Sheriff Tyler.
- Yeah, Tyler.
- I'm agent Manners.
- FBI?
- Sure, why not.
And this is Stone.
- [Sam] Agent Stone.
- Sheriff.
- Why are you here?
- We've got a line
on your Abraham Harper.
- Old Man Harper,
yeah, what about him?
- His death matches the MO of someone
we've been tracking for some time now.
- Yeah, well we've
got two more deaths.
I was just about to try
to get you on the phone.
- Good.
Have the MV's been moved'?
- Motor vehicles?
- Have the murder
victims been moved yet'?
- No, uh, Jake and Sally
Metzner have not been moved yet.
- Fine, first take
me to the crime scene.
Excuse me, Jake and Sally's place.
If everything checks
out as I think it will
I'll have a task force
in here by midnight.
- This mean the case is
being taken out of my hands?
- It was never in them Sheriff.
(police radio)
(footsteps)
(door opening)
- You were right the first time Sam.
(door closing)
Asshole.
(fast paced music)
- I don't know why you're
so interested in this
dam footprint.
Whoever did this obviously
came through the backdoor.
- It was locked.
- They locked it behind them.
- You're obviously not a
man of science Sheriff.
The latest advanced in forensics
means that a
footprint can be as accurate
as a fingerprint.
(footsteps)
- I'm reading something.
- What?
- Oh sweet Jesus look at this.
This thing is able to latently alter
it's elemental molecular structure.
- English Stone, English.
- It can freeze and unfreeze at will.
It melted, came through the doggy door
and refroze on the inside.
- You mean Jack came
through the doggy door
and refroze on the inside.
What the hell have you
let loose in this town?
(ice cracking)
- Now there should be lacerations
to indicate where the handle of the ax
we twisted from side to
side to help it down.
But no, all the cuts
are near vertical.
It forced the handle straight down.
That's immensely powerful.
(Sigh)
- Did you say it Doc'?
- I beg your pardon.
- You said it instead of he or she.
- Well, that's just a
figure of speech Sam.
Whoever did this is an animal.
Metaphorically.
And, I found this backdoor key
inside Jake's pocket.
- How many backdoor
keys do you own Doc?
- Just the one.
- Me too.
- So, how did those footprints walk
into a locked backdoor'?
- Am I missing something?
- Oh no, nothing at all Agent Manners.
I'm just having some
small town gossip here
about some tractor pulls
and a barn raising.
- Right.
Well our equipment does in fact
support your theory Sheriff.
The killer locked the door
himself after entering.
- He--
- Sheriff I'm
gonna need you to arrange
a curfew for the rest of the night.
It'll be safer for everyone involved.
- Are you gonna tell
me what this is about?
- I'm afraid it's on a
need to know basis Sheriff.
I'll have a task force
in here by midnight.
You just keep your townsfolk
out of my line of fire
and we'll get along real fine.
- Sure.
- Now don't pout Sheriff.
You should be grateful.
You've got a madman on
the loose in your town
and I'm gonna take him out for you.
(car engine)
- Sam.
- What's this?
- Federally approved curfew
regulations and procedures.
Yeah.
- Evening Sam.
I'm afraid I haven't got round
to turning the furnace on.
It's a trifle chilly inside.
- Let's get it fired up Father.
Is everybody here?
- Pretty much yeah.
- Yeah.
You seen Jill'?
- Uh, no a few of the
kids are still missing.
- Well let's round 'em up all right'?
Come on Father I want to
keep a close flock tonight.
(footsteps)
(applause)
Okay, now Father Branagh
tells me the heating
will be turned on any minute now.
(applause)
Folks, folks, we have a situation.
- Way to go Sam!
- All right now, let's just
setting down all right?
(footsteps)
(clanking)
(valve squeaking)
- That ought to cheer everyone up.
(footsteps)
- Under the advisement of
the local federal officers
I am going to put the town
under a 24 hour curfew.
Listen, I'm not gonna arrest you.
If you're just walking down the street
I'm not gonna waste my time but this
is for your own safety so
I urge you to follow it.
(yelling from outside)
Now Father Branagh has told me that
he'll keep the church open.
You can sleep down here
community style if you want.
That might be a good thing.
I want you to stay
off the phones except
in case of an emergency.
All right'?
What the heck is going on out there?
- It's uh--
- Paul Davrow.
- Fucker's a snowman.
(scuffling)
- Paul, what are you talking about?
- No you don't understand.
- Paul.
- No, she had wires coming out of her.
She had little lights--
- Paul.
- It was a seven foot tall--
- Oh god.
(shocked gasp by crowd)
Okay.
- Well bravo Sheriff.
- You didn't have to do that.
- I hope this isn't a
taste of what I can expect
from this town under your direction.
- It's nothing, all right'?
We'll take care of him.
- Well you better.
The man's a danger to the public
and a possible
hindrance to my operation.
- Your what?
- You better get your
act under control Sheriff
or I'll have you replaced.
I would appreciate
it if all you people
would get off the streets.
Go darn a quilt or something.
(footsteps)
- What the hell's eating him?
- I bet ya it ain't his girlfriend.
You should have punched him out sir.
(Sigh)
- Joe, come here.
Get ahold of Paul.
Take him somewhere will ya?
Let him cool off for a
while down at the jail.
- Come on Mr. Davrow.
Okay.
- Big nose.
- Okay.
- Sharp teeth.
- Chris.
- Yeah.
- I want you to go up to Paul's place.
Maybe you can
find out what set him off.
- Uh, maybe I should help out Joe.
You know, with
Paul 'cause he's a big guy
and he might be a little nasty later.
- Chris.
- Right, I'm on it.
Nah, sure Sam I'll go check it out.
I'll see what freaked everybody out.
No problem.
It's a madman on the loose.
Hey Deputy Chris
Pullman captures madman.
Get the madman be a
hero, fa la la la la la.
Whoa.
(breaks squealing)
(car door opening)
(ominous music)
(car door closing)
(footsteps)
(creepy christmas music)
Okay.
I've heard of stuff
happening, thermal updrafts.
(banging around in trunk)
(ominous music)
(sirens blaring)
- Hey kids.
- Hi.
- Ryan, where's your mom?
- She went home to get
some more blankets.
- Did somebody go with her?
- I don't know.
Is she all right?
- Hey Joe!
(sirens blaring)
(knocking on window)
- Sam'?
Sam?
Is that you?
Deputy?
(water flowing from cabinet)
(ominous music)
(steam hissing)
(screaming)
- I got it.
I got it.
(steam hissing)
(valve squeaking)
(ominous music)
(Sign)
Ice burst.
Lucky Sam sent me, huh?
- Don't you ever creep
up on me like that again.
- You ought to get these
pipes fixed Mrs. Tyler.
- (Chuckle) We ought to fix you Joe.
(water dripping from paper towel)
- I think we're gonna
need a mop on this one.
- And the roadblocks at
4th and Lacy completely
seal off main avenue.
- You're forgetting the church.
- No Sheriff, the
blockade is complete.
- No, Father Branagh removed the fence
here from the cemetery last week so this
is all open field now.
- All right, thank you
very much Sheriff.
Anything else you
care to share with me?
- No, not at the moment.
But if I think of something
you'll be the first to know.
- After you get that done though
you want to get the fittings wrapped.
You can do that yourself.
Take some Teflon tape, no you can,
you wrap the male fittings only.
You don't wrap the female fittings.
You've got to make sure you wrap them
as you're looking down clockwise.
(car door opening)
You wrap them counterclockwise,
here you go Mrs. Tyler.
Then all the tape shreds off.
Also I noticed that your linoleum's
starting to peel up there from all
the water being on down there--
(car door closing)
(footsteps)
(car door opening)
Get some caulk and get that
back down there real easy.
Silicon caulk is
probably better than--
(car door closing)
(car engine starting)
(ominous music)
- I don't think they saw us.
- Jill, I don't know about this.
I don't think it's such a good idea.
- Come on, you want me
to have fun don't you'?
Or do you want me to sit
around and get morbid'?
- Jill, this is Sheriff Tyler's house.
- Exactly.
Are you gonna come or not?
(footsteps)
- Jill.
(crashing)
(door opening)
No, no, no, no.
Don't turn on the lights.
- I'll get all scared of the dark.
(Sigh)
And then I'll need a really
big boy to look after me.
(nervous laughter)
. Big boy?
You're getting there.
(christmas music)
(unzipping jacket)
(christmas music
and zippers unzipping)
(christmas music)
- If you want me
I want a roaring log fire
and a bottle of wine.
(heavy Sigh)
Come and get me when you're ready.
- Yes.
If I wasn't anymore ready I'd explode.
(radio playing and blow dryer)
(cork popping)
Shit.
(heavy Sigh)
(radio playing and blow dryer)
(pouring wine into glass)
(spitting wine into sink)
Need some ice.
(glass bottle hitting counter)
(fridge door opening)
(footsteps)
(digging in drawer)
(wind blowing)
(chipping away at ice)
(ice clinking in glass)
(ominous music)
(snowball hitting window)
(blow dryer)
(radio playing)
Sheriff Tyler'?
Sheriff, it's Tommy Davrow.
Look, uh, I'm not a burglar.
(ominous music)
Sheriff?
(pulling drawer open)
(ominous music)
(digging in drawer)
(wind blowing)
(ominous music)
(door slamming shut)
Who's out there?
(ominous music)
I said, who's out there?
(door creaking open)
Who's out there?
(ominous music)
I said, who's out there?
(heavy metal music)
- Well it ain't fucking Frosty.
- You stay back man, all right?
I'm gonna use this thing, all right?
Listen, just stay back.
Just--
(screaming)
- Ah.
- What the hell are you?
- World's most pissed off snow cone.
No, no!
(heavy metal music)
(groaning)
Well what do you know,
armed and dangerous.
Bottom of the ninth, four dead,
here's the windup and the pitch.
(screaming)
Woo hoo, it's a long drive.
(laughter)
(rock music and blow dryer)
(rock music)
- Thank you Tommy.
(ominous music and
water sloshing in tub)
Tommy no.
Don't put cold water in.
Oh it's freezing.
(screaming)
(fast paced christmas
music and screaming)
(head banging into wall and screaming)
(fast paced christmas music)
- Looks like Christmas came
a little early this year.
(laughter)
Well, hope it was good for you honey.
Oh I must remember to send flowers.
(laughter)
(Paper tearing)
(footsteps)
- Hey, bad Manners, this is for you.
Coffee?
- Yeah, please.
Just to the brim.
You heard from Chris yet?
He was up at Paul Davrow's place.
- Not that I know of.
- Why don't you see if you can get him
on the radio, okay?
I'm worried about him.
- Okay.
- There's a storm
moving in over Denver.
They can't get the
choppers off the ground.
They'll be taking everyone in by road.
(laughter)
- No way, never happen.
- Might be a little late
but they'll be here.
- Oh no, tell him Marla.
- No way.
We're dead center
of the Snowmonton Bowl.
It's 20 miles uphill in any direction.
If it's anything like
last week you won't
even be able to get a snowplow across
the highway in an hour from now.
- You telling me that there's
no way to get my men in here?
- Duh.
- [Stone] You can't let him escape.
- Well don't you fret Agent Stone.
Nothing comes in, nothing gets out.
Ain't that right Manners'?
- Yeah right.
Tell me Sheriff, what sort
of armory do you have here?
- Armory?
- What kind of weapons
are available to us'?
- We're just a small
town sheriff's office.
- I told you conventional weapons will
be useless against him.
We need the company.
- Watch your mouth.
- What are you two talking about?
- Nothing Sheriff.
- I told you the company
should have been called
in to handle this whole thing.
Not some bureau mercenary.
- You want to let me in on this?
- Sorry Sheriff, it's
on a need to know basis
and you don't.
- Oh yeah, well I think
I might need to know.
- Oh boys, Chris is back.
I just heard his car pull up.
- We're not finished.
(footsteps)
(car engine idling)
His car's here.
Where's Chris?
Chris?
Wherever he is he's soaking wet.
- Hey Sam, isn't this
Jake Metznefls old scarf?
- Marla, Marla don't touch that.
- What's the problem Sam?
(laughter)
It's just a scarf.
(screaming)
- Mother of god.
- Nah, bitch couldn't make it.
(gun shots)
- I thought you said
conventional weapons
couldn't touch that thing.
- Now look what you've gone and done!
Mm-mm.
- Inside.
- Made in America.
- Get out of the way,
what are ya nuts?
Get out of the way Stone.
(door slamming shut)
- What was that?
- What's this place made out of'?
- Got quarter inch steel in the walls
and the ceilings, half
inch plate in the windows.
- That should hold us enough.
- Enough for what?
Tell me.
- Sam, Sam all the
outside lines are down.
- We need something
to fig ht back with.
- What are we fighting?
Look, I just saw something
that doesn't belong in this world
and it's out there killing my friends.
Now tell me what it is.
- Jack Frost.
- No, Jack Frost died.
- Jack Frost changed.
- He changed'?
Who are you people?
And don't give me this FBI bull crap.
- Shut up, shut up, listen.
What is that?
(water flowing)
- Sounds like water.
(water rushing under door)
- [Sam] Oh my god.
What is it'?
Oh Lord, the footprint at
Jake and Sally's place.
- [Jack Voiceover] I'll find a way!
- He came back.
- All right, stand clear.
(gun shots)
Dammit it's not working.
- He's only vulnerable
in his elemental state.
- English Stone.
- He can only be
hurt when he's frozen.
- Well then he can stick himself right
back together again right?
(ominous music)
' [GTWP] 0h my god!
- Come on, come on.
- [Stone] Don't hurt him.
(blow dryer)
- Oh, hey.
(door opening)
- Come on, come on, come on.
Sam!
- Sheriff come on move it.
- Don't hurt him!
- Shut up!
(blow dryer)
- Ah it's hot.
" [Jack] Oops.
Uh oh.
(laughter)
- Sam, come on hurry up.
- Heat, we got to heat this place up.
- You got to blow this place.
You got any cleaning supplies,
aerosol's, something?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
(cans clanking together)
We got a lot of them.
What are you doing'?
- I can't authorize
this kind of action.
- Nobody asked you to authorize it.
- Stop this now.
Agent Manners your
orders are to observe,
restrain, and entrap.
Not question directives.
- You see what's out there?
- What's out there is my proof.
- Yeah, well fuck that.
(can clattering)
- Get him out of here now.
- Come on.
(cans spraying)
(struggle)
- [Marla] Come on, come on hurry up.
Hurry UP-
- Move it.
(struggle)
(coughing)
- Damn, it's locked.
Stand back.
- [Sam] No, don't do that
you'll blow the place.
- Where's the fucking key?
- Oh heck.
Don't leave without me.
(banging on lock)
(coughing)
(water pouring through door crack)
(water rushing under door)
- Come on, come on.
Come on, come on.
- Sam!
Sam where are you'?
(water rushing through crack)
(keys dropping on floor)
- Oh shoot.
(water rushing through crack)
- Come on.
Pick 'em up, pick 'em up.
(ominous music)
- No.
- Sam we can't breathe here.
(screaming)
- Don't leave me!
Help me, help me.
Help me please.
(keys rattling)
- I got the key Paul.
- That one, that one, try that one.
- I don't think that's--
- Try it.
- Easy Paul that's not it.
- That one.
- Paul, you're chocking me.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, come on.
Let's go, let's go,
let's get out of here.
Killer snowmen.
(screaming)
- Hurry, hurry, hurry he's coming.
(coughing)
- [Sam] I got it.
- Hurry up, hurry UP-
- All right, come on.
- Come on, women and cowards first.
- Come on go.
- Give me his legs, give me his legs.
- I'm sorry Jack.
- Shut up.
- Paul, Paul, need a forklift?
Come on.
(scared screaming)
' [Marla] Push!
(screaming)
(ominous music)
(coughing)
- [Paul] Come on.
Come on, come on.
- [Marla] Run.
(coughing)
- Come on, shoot it.
- Those are not your orders.
- I hope somebody remembered
to put out the cat.
(gun shot)
- Oh shit!
(explosion)
(christmas music)
- We got him, we got him.
- It's over now.
- I don't know Paul.
(christmas music)
- I told you I'd take it
out for you and I did.
- He's come back before.
(christmas music)
- Oh maybe Manley's right.
What could have survived that?
- Look ma, I'm a Picasso.
(laughter)
(ominous music)
- You got to be shitting me.
- Come on!
- Run!
- I'll be back when I
pull myself together.
(door closing)
- Hey, anyone got an aspirin?
(laughter)
Oh my head.
- Your place or mine?
- Yours.
- Come on.
- [Male] What the hell was that Sam'?
- It was a god damn snowman.
- [Sam] Look, we're all gonna have to
fight this thing together.
- [Male] Tell us what's out there'?
- Look, I need everybody here to work
with me on this, all right.
I need you to stay calm.
I need you to trust these people.
- Why in the hell should
we trust these guys?
- Because we
mightjust be your only hope.
- That's right.
- [Paul] Sam, Sam wait, wait.
(footsteps)
- They're gonna send in
some kind of snowmobile
two hours at most.
(phone slamming down)
- [Sam] Too late, now cut the crap.
I want to know who the hell you are.
- Let's just say
we're in damage control.
- You I don't care about.
I want to know where you fit in.
Listen to me!
We're in this together.
That thing has got to be destroyed.
What exactly are we up against?
- Not even the Secretary
of Defense knows
what I'm going.
(gun shot)
- Thank you.
- No problem.
- Do something.
- Like what?
Teach him how to shoot better?
- Welcome to the team doc.
Now talk to me.
- Jack Frost was an accident.
It was meant to be next
level genetic research.
To ensure the survival of our race
through a global holocaust.
I created an acid that would bond
a human chromosome helix
with an inert material
so that we could be
resurrected in the future.
But something happened
in the accident.
The snow didn't just
store Jack Frost's DNA.
- It's taken on his personality.
- Exactly.
You know what that means?
- It means he's killing my friends.
- No Sheriff.
It means that the soul exists.
And it's not just
some esoteric spiritual
entity or even a
vague electrical force.
The soul is a chemical.
- You're insane.
This isn't what we could be talking
about right now.
- Frost's manifestation is my proof.
It's invaluable, we cannot destroy it.
- Don't you get it?
Jack Frost came
back here to get at me.
And he's gonna kill anybody who gets
in his path.
If we don't destroy him he's gonna
kill every last one of us.
- I have no idea how to stop it.
We have to contain it.
- How?
We have to put him
in an absolutely water
tight container otherwise
he's gonna leak out.
We can't risk that.
- But to destroy it--
- What do you want us to do Stone?
Wait till spring and see if he melts?
- Wait, what about the
furnace down in the basement?
Surely that's hot
enough to destroy him.
- Well we tried blowing him up.
It just pissed him off.
- I suppose it's possible
that the sustained
heat could agitate the molecules
sufficiently to destroy the helix.
- Fine, fine, but how the hell
do we lure him down there?
- We don't lure him.
We force him.
(old western music)
- What if he doesn't show?
- Jack was never one to miss a party.
(old western music and footsteps)
You know I remember a night like this
back in '79.
There were three of us holed up--
- Shh, shh, shh.
- What?
- You feel that?
- [Manners] Feel what?
I don't feel anyihing.
- [Sam] You don't feel that?
- A stampede of buffalo
coming over the hill?
- What the hell is that?
(old western music)
- I think Jack's about
to make an entrance.
(screaming)
(snowball crashing through doors)
- Hey Jack!
- What?
- You left a 7110 split.
- Why you, oh shit.
Can't we talk this over'?
It's hot, it's hot,
oh great another one.
My hair is dry fellas.
(valve opening)
(fire roaring)
(screaming)
My face is melting.
MY EYES, my nose.
Oh that was--
(screaming)
(furnace door closing)
No, no, no.
(screaming)
- We iced him.
(cheering)
- Oh baby.
- Is it finished?
- Oh yeah, it's all gone honey.
Poof like magic.
- I told you the snowman did it.
- I need for you to get to a phone.
We're gonna need some medical help.
- I love you too.
- What about me'?
- No, you're gonna
stick with dad, okay.
Fastest blow dryer in the west.
(laughter)
(christmas music and steam hissing)
- You know, at least you've still
got your records, right.
(christmas music)
You know it's at a time like this
when I think all we
can do is turn our eyes
to the heaven's and say, oh shit.
(ominous music)
- Blow me.
(moaning)
Frost bite.
Next time we'll use mistletoe.
(screaming)
I need floss.
- P-Please we know it's you Jack.
- Bah humbug.
- Wait, wait.
I can help you.
Maybe turn you back.
- But I'm having so much fun just
the way I am.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Then tell me what it's like to have
breached death, a dream
of every man on earth.
You're immoral.
How does that feel?
- Oh it feels cold!
(screaming)
- Put it on your head.
It's cold out here.
(footsteps)
Listen I want you to wait
in here forjust a minute.
I've got to talk to this guy.
Here.
(car door closing)
(footsteps)
(door creaking open)
(door closing)
(footsteps)
(Creepy music)
- Fuck it.
(gagging)
' [Sam] Ryan!
- Dad.
- Ryan open the door.
Quick, quick.
- I'm scared dad.
- Don't eat yellow snow.
- Where's the key'?
(ominous music)
- Where's he going'?
(water pouring out of vent)
- It's coming in.
- Don't touch it, don't
let the water touch you.
Come here.
Get over here.
Now don't let it touch you.
Don't touch the water.
Here.
(grunting)
- [Ryan] Dad.
- Come on, come on.
(car engine sputtering)
Come on, come on.
- I think your engine's flooded.
(laughter)
Locked.
(glass breaking)
Oh what a (inaudible).
- Go, hurry Ryan.
That a boy.
- It's just you and me baby.
(laughter)
(screaming)
- It's burning.
He's burning.
The oatmeal is making him burn.
Buddy what did you put in those oats?
. Sci"!-
- No it's a good thing that you did.
- I didn't want you to get cold.
- Honey what did you put in the oats?
- Anti-Freeze.
(laughter)
I'm sorry.
(crashing)
- You are so fucking dead.
- Just what I was thinking Jack.
(horn blaring)
- I can see your house from up here.
(crashing)
(laughter)
- Anti-freeze, anti-freeze,
you got any anti-freeze'?
- Oh yeah, yeah, I just got a load--
- Oh, somebody get me
the number of that truck.
- I want you to get the anti-freeze.
- Okay.
Put it in the truck.
- Right.
I want you to be back here
in five minutes.
Five minutes Paul.
Exactly five minutes.
- Okay.
- All right'?
What about Ryan'?
- Ryan, go with Paul.
- Get in the truck babe.
- [Sam] Five minutes Paul.
- All right.
- Looks like it's
just you and me Jack.
- And then there was one.
- Hey Jack!
- [Jack] What?
- What's the difference
between snowmen and snow-women?
- I don't know.
- No balls.
- I'll finish this.
(heavy metal music)
(door opening and closing)
(truck breaks squealing)
(heavy metal music)
- Ryan stay there.
(christmas rock music)
(footsteps)
(water dripping through door crack)
(doors opening)
(heavy metal music)
(footsteps)
" [Male] Go away!
" [Mam] We're busy!
(goat bleats)
- [Female] (gasp) It's my husband.
- Ryan, Ryan don't move.
It'll all be over soon.
- [Ryan] Okay.
(tarp rustling)
(heavy metal music)
- [Male] Under the bed, the closet.
Just hide.
(ominous music)
(anti-freeze pouring into truck bed)
(empty bottles hitting ground)
(ominous music)
- Those stairs were a killer.
(heavy metal music)
(door slamming shut)
(heavy metal music and snow blowing)
- Is it cold in here or is it just me?
(laughter)
Shall we dance?
Oh, I feel a hug coming on.
(laughter)
Oh yeah, you have
been the best so far.
Listen, I've got a
point I'd like to make.
(laughter)
Quit wriggling will ya'?
Oh, just a minute, let me see.
Oh I think it is, I
think I got some flesh.
(laughter)
Oh yeah.
Oh, looks like I got right
to the heart of the matter.
It's a gusher.
(laughter)
- You're not gonna get my family.
- Oh, going, going, gone.
I'm really looking forward
to your wife dead man.
(9359)
(horn honking)
(tires spinning on snow)
- It's the cavalry asshole.
(screaming)
(glass breaking)
(Splashing)
(fighting)
- Come on honey!
Come on honey!
Come on baby!
(screaming)
(fighting)
(heavy breathing)
Poof
All gone.
- Yes.
- Oh bravo, praise be to God.
Praise be to God.
- Dad, you forgot this arm.
- No Ryan!
_ Help.
- Drop him.
(screaming)
(ominous music)
- [Father] May no one break
the seal of holy earth
by which we now inter this evil
on consecrated ground.
J1 Round yon virgin mother and-- J1
(police sirens)
- Looks like the calvary
has finally arrived.
- So what do we tell the FBI Sam?
- Tell them it's too late.
J1 Sleep in heavenly peace
J1 Sleep in heavenly peace J1
(rock music)
(christmas music)