Heck, I'm awake.
I'm awake.
What are you doing?
[Inaudible]
Come here.
Good morning.
They are good mornings
waking up with you.
Kampo, let's play a game.
What kind of game?
I'll ask a question.
And you answer.
Oh, what do you want to know?
Tell me about your friends.
Oh, well, I don't have
that many friends other
Than the guys on the swim team.
But I don't hang out
with them all the time.
Next question.
OK.
How about your family?
You do have a family, don't you?
Kampo?
Tell me about your family.
I have a brother named Jett.
Well, that's a start.
Tell me about Jett.
Well, he's older than
I am, bigger than I am.
And he works and lives
in Washington, DC.
Washington?
Oh, I love Washington.
Cherry blossoms in the
spring there are beautiful.
I wouldn't know.
I've been there.
What about your... your parents?
Where do they live?
My parents are dead, Jessie.
I'm sorry.
I don't like to talk about it.
Sometimes it helps
to talk about it.
Yeah, I know.
Remember, I'm the psych major.
It's just I never had
anyone I felt close
Enough to to talk to about it.
What about Jett?
There's just certain
things we can't talk about.
Well, how long has it
been since you've seen him?
Six months.
I mean, it's not like he
doesn't care about me.
Jett's been paying
for my college.
He's been taking care of me
ever since our parents died.
How old were you
when it happened?
12 years old.
Oh, so young.
[Scream]
WOMAN: (SHOUTING) Oh my god.
You asshole.
I can't believe you.
Aw, man.
Call an ambulance.
No, I don't know what to do.
What am I supposed to do?
You hit him.
And I'll be at the
library until about 6:00.
And we're still on
for dinner, aren't we?
Yes.
Now, let's go.
I have to make a quick
stop before I drop you
Off at your class, all right?
Agents.
Back away from the body, please.
Hey, look, it
wasn't my fault, man.
He just ran out, OK?
WOMAN: Oh my goodness.
Hector's dead.
Yeah.
We found the postcard.
But there's no luck
locating the key.
Yes, I understand.
Good evening.
Topping this evening's
news at 6 o'clock
Is the death of Hector Ramirez,
brother of reputed drug lord,
Manuel Ramirez.
It happened this morning
shortly after 10 o'clock
At the First Federal Bank.
That must be what we saw
this morning at the bank.
Manuel Ramirez, the
bearded drug czar
Heads a powerful cartel.
He is on the run from the
DEA, and believed to be hiding
Somewhere in South America.
Federal authorities are hopeful
that recent developments
May flush Ramirez out.
I take it you're not the maid.
Don't those do not disturb
signs mean anything anymore?
Hey, whatever it is
you're looking for,
I'm fairly certain
it's not on me.
You're really in on position
to play games with me.
Well, why don't you untie me?
We can try a new position.
If anyone's going to get
poked, it's going to be you.
Now, just what should
I blow off first?
Ah, I know what.
It that how I taught
you to tie a square knot?
Oh, goddammit, Jett.
You always do this.
It's not fair.
You cheat.
I don't cheat.
I'm just a better
player than you.
That's all.
Oh yeah?
Well, then play
with yourself then.
Jett, no.
No, Jett.
No.
Yes.
[Moaning]
Oh, god.
Oh.
What's wrong?
What are you?
An amphibian?
I mean, I gotta come up
for air once in a while.
Well, Jett used to say I
was a fish in my past life,
Because I can hold my breath
underwater almost four minutes.
Four minutes?
Come on, nobody can hold
their breath for four minutes.
What about those guys
that dive for pearls.
It just takes practice.
All right, I can see
you don't believe me.
[Laughs]
How about a little bet then?
A bet?
For what?
What else?
Food, my second favorite
pleasure in life.
When I win, you will cook dinner
for me for an entire month.
In the unlikely event
that... excuse me,
The highly unlikely
event that you win,
I will cook dinner
for you for a month.
Cook?
Mhm.
Wait a minute.
When I win pizza...
[Coughs]
Pizza does not count as dinner.
OK.
Let's do it.
On you mark, get set, go.
Make all the
necessary arrangements.
I'll go personally this time.
Boos, please.
You have to wait six months.
Silencio.
I cannot wait
another six months.
And I will tolerate
no other mistakes.
Vamanos.
56, 57, 58.
Call me [inaudible].
Yes!
How do you do that?
Oh, it's like learning
how to ride a bike.
Once you learn,
you never forget.
Mm.
You're going to have time
to practice your knots.
I have to go under for a while.
Do some hotel hopping.
Good.
I could use some new towels.
Talk about the check
is in the mail.
It's hard to
believe this thing's
Worth a bazillion bucks.
Oh, just the stamps are.
They're not worth
quite a bazillion.
But you're not that far off.
But, uh, this thing is a
key to Ramirez' future.
The word around the office
that Ramirez wants it back.
The boss thinks
he's going to come
And try and get it himself.
Duh, now.
Our brilliant bosses are
the ones who delivered
This thing this morning to me.
No.
No, really... personally.
You're kidding.
Nope.
They want me to try
and use this for bait
To try and trap him with it.
Well, that's going to put a
crimp in our plans, isn't it?
Oh, does it?
Well, yeah.
Ramirez was going to give
the postcard back anyway
Once... once you got him
safely out of the country.
If the agency knows
you have it, you're
Going to have to give it back.
It's state's evidence.
OK.
I'll give it back.
Like hell you will.
This is our ticket out
of the civil services.
Sweetheart, how long you've
been in the espionage business?
I mean, you're overlooking
one of our most
Time honored traditions.
And what's that?
The double-cross.
See, I will use this
postcard as bait.
As the loyal
agent that you are.
And I will accept this
postcard as payment
For helping that
drug pushing amigo
To cruise on past customs, with
his delightful nontraceable
Funds.
As the disloyal scoundrel
you turned out to be.
Only see, Ramirez won't
quite make it to the airport.
- He won't?
- Nope.
He has a tragic accident.
Aw.
I'll send flowers, and a card.
And all of his nontraceable
funds, they disappear.
Without a trace.
And our agency, well, they
get back to their precious four
Curtiss Jenny stamps.
And we walk with
$64, give or take.
Take.
Always take.
Speak.
All the arrangement
have been made.
We leave for Los
Angeles within the hour.
Leave me.
[Inaudible] How can I say?
Classic.
First off, [inaudible]
Just your being here
tells me that you're
Mixed up in this some what.
Come on, Sal, you still
bitter about that Iran deal?
Look, look here.
I getting my fingers broken for
doing favors for your people.
It's not the way I
usually do business.
[Inaudible]
Yes.
But pain lingers on.
So tell me, what is cut?
And what assurances
do I have that
I will not end up with
Colombian necktie.
Hey, every job has certain
risk and a price to pay.
I am only interested in cut.
What is it?
And what do I have
to give you for it?
How about you
give me some names.
And I'll give you one.
It's simple.
What name is that.
Like Curtiss Jenny.
Oh.
Easy, easy, easy.
For you, 25% to do
with as please, Sal.
But it's going to cost
you plenty of names.
And as far as reinsurance,
Ramirez is going to lose
It at all in one fell swoop.
Default on his debts to
his associates, and zap.
He owes that much, yeah?
Fighting a drug war
these days is expensive.
When Ramirez's buddy
Noriega got pinched,
He panicked, made mistakes.
He got messy.
So we checkmated him.
He not only lost face
with his drug buddies,
But he pissed a whole
bunch of them off.
So now he's hiding out
down in South America.
And he sends his brother
up here to some bidding.
He gets killed.
You getting the picture?
Oh, yes.
I get picture.
So I will bring
you list tonight.
Then I can assume
we have a deal.
No, until I get paid,
you can assume nothing.
OK.
Then tonight at 7:00...
No, no, no.
What do you mean, no?
I will set place for meeting.
All right.
Where?
Well, it seems to me I
remember you like movies
About [inaudible] fancy beach.
Get on with it.
You know where is old
theater on Birchwood?
Yeah.
I know where that is.
There is double feature.
I will bring the popcorn.
If a man truly loves a woman,
he will never leave her.
But you must have a tree.
For you man must lead the hunt...
You know what all this
salt's going to do
To your blood pressure, Sal?
WOMAN 1 (IN MOVIE): Or
you should go hungry.
WOMAN 2 (IN MOVIE): You
two speak with idle words.
If I had a man like Duran,
he could leave for years,
[Spits]
And I would wait for him.
WOMAN 1 (IN MOVIE): But you
do not have him, do you?
Only Lystra has
that good fortune.
[Grunting]
Hey come on, Harold.
Cut the crap, huh?
Someone else had to know
about my meeting with Kerovac.
Yeah, he was a good contact.
HAROLD (ON PHONE): Look,
I'm sorry about Kerovac.
But as far as we're concerned,
there's nothing to worry about.
Nothing?
That could have
been me, asshole.
HAROLD (ON PHONE): Right.
But it wasn't.
So relax.
Trust me.
I have some good news for you.
It's going to cheer you up.
Yeah?
What kind of news?
HAROLD (ON PHONE): The Ram
man, he's making his move.
What, Ramirez?
HAROLD (ON PHONE): Yeah.
We got the word that
he's on his way to LA.
From who?
HAROLD (ON PHONE): A
very reliable source.
Do you still have the postcard?
Yeah.
It's right here with me.
HAROLD (ON PHONE):
That's my boy.
I'll be in touch with you.
And Jett...
Yeah.
HAROLD (ON PHONE): Try and relax
[Grunting]
That'll do it.
No more piano
concerts for a while.
You'll survive.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Jesus frigging Christ.
You OK, Jett?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Can you move it?
I said I'm fine.
Just a flesh wound then, huh?
You know, I should
kick your ass.
Sweetheart, you, uh,
think you can find some bed
Pans that need emptying.
I think it's a
good time to look.
I think it's a good time
for you to get that groin
Pull looked at, you know?
All right, Harold.
Level with me.
We've been in LA for
less than 24 hours.
And somebody already
tried to take my head off.
Well, it's the freeways, Jett.
They bring out the
worst in people.
All right, Jett.
Couple of minor details
we've been holding back on.
Oh, that's great.
That's great.
Holding back information breaks
our basic trust, partner.
So why don't you try
talking to me, huh?
All right, before you go
getting off on the high horse
Here, let me give you
my reasons why, OK?
Yeah.
Well, I'm listening.
Now, we had to wait for
Ramirez to make his move.
And he made his move.
That still doesn't
answer my question.
He wants to set the
meeting up with you.
Why me?
Because this is
your deal, Jett.
Remember, you set this up.
All right.
Who else knows
about this meeting?
- Just you and me, pal.
- Just you and me?
- That's what I said.
- Good.
You just keep it
that way, all right?
Fine.
Now, I think I should be
there as backup, just in case.
In case of what?
What, are you
expected more trouble?
No, I just thought, well,
with the hand, what happened
At the hotel, you might need...
No, I'll be fine.
You just set up the meeting.
OK?
Sure.
It'll probably be soon,
and someplace local.
Shit.
Where you gonna be?
Someplace safe... neutral.
I'll contact you.
Whatever you say, partner.
Fuck.
Rest the hand, Jett.
What are you doing here?
This is not a social affair.
I have important
business to attend to.
What kind of business?
Matters that don't concern you.
Are you sure?
What's the matter, baby?
You don't mix business
with pleasure anymore?
MAN (ON PHONE):
Kampo, are you there?
Call me when you get in.
About last night, I'm sorry.
Beep.
Hi, it's me.
Call me.
Beep.
Where were you when
your parents died?
Forget I even asked that.
It's none of my business.
At home.
I was in trouble for getting
bad grades on my report card.
So my parents took away
the thing that meant
The most to me at the time.
Swimming?
Not only that, they
also grounded me
From using our backyard pool.
I was so upset.
That night, my parents
went to a dinner party,
Leaving Jett in charge.
What a break?
I thought.
One more swim.
So after they left,
I got ready to go in.
And just as I was about
to dive into the pool,
Jett comes out of the house and
says, get away from the pool...
Just like a big brother.
So what'd you do?
What little brothers do best.
I pissed him off.
That wasn't a good idea.
Why?
What happened?
He chased after me.
We went around and around
the edge of the pool.
He almost got me.
And suddenly, he slipped
and fell into the water.
What happened next?
Nothing.
See, Jett had hit his head
on the edge of the pool.
And he was lying
there at the bottom.
Did you know he was in trouble?
Yeah, he wasn't moving.
I had to dive in
and bring him up.
He started splitting up water.
That's a good sign.
So he was OK.
You saved him.
Yeah, he was OK.
I still called emergency.
And they notified my parents and
sent an ambulance to the house.
So you called emergency.
Thank God.
Thank God for what?
My parents ran that red
light, and were killed rushing
Home to see how Jett was.
They died instantly, never
knowing that Jett was OK,
And that I was the
cause of everything.
[Phone ringing]
Hello.
Hello?
Jessie, is that you?
[Phone ringing]
Hello!
Who is it?
[Knocking]
It's me, Jessica.
Can I come in?
Sure.
I've been trying
to call you all day.
I left messages.
I just got home.
What is it?
Term paper time?
Yeah, I got three of
them this semester.
Need any help?
Can you type?
70 words a minute.
Whoa, that's 60
more than I can type.
You're hired.
Listen, about last night.
Please, Jessie, just forget it.
No, I never would have...
Can we drop the subject
right now, please?
Look, Jessie, I'm
not pissed at you.
I wasn't last night either.
It's just that what I told
you is something I never told
Anyone before, not even Jett.
I'm glad you could talk to me.
Look, for what it's worth,
I really did feel a lot
Better last night after I left.
I'm glad.
I've never been that
good with letting
People get inside my head.
That's why I had to go.
I just needed to be
alone for a little while.
I understand.
Thanks, Jessie.
Come here.
Listen, you worthless
piece of shift.
I'm risking everything
by just being here.
I haven't the time
or the patience
To deal with your
stupid little problems.
No, hombre.
I can afford to wait no longer.
Just do it.
Set the meeting for tonight
and leave the rest to me.
[Speaking spanish]
Did you locate him?
Yes.
Good.
Very good.
[Laughter]
Excellent.
(WHISPERING) Kampo, wake up.
In the morning.
Go back to sleep.
- Wake up.
- What is it, Jessie?
Shh.
There's somebody in your room.
Turn on the light.
I probably won't be able
to find anything anyways.
Go to sleep.
Someone's in my room.
Who is it?
I have a gun.
[Inaudible]
Yeah, you and I know that.
But the burglar doesn't.
You don't have a gun.
In fact, you never even fired
one before, you little pussy.
Jett?
Ah, Jett, you asshole.
Now is that any way
to greet your brother?
Oh, hey, man.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you had company.
You guys sure have a
weird way of saying hello.
How long you been in LA?
Two days.
I tried to contact you earlier.
Was that you on the phone?
No, I didn't call.
I stopped by at school.
You didn't call my machine?
No.
I didn't call your
machine or you.
Why?
Well, it's... it's
probably nothing.
I've just been getting some
weird phone calls, that's all.
Oh, really?
How so?
Well, like, somebody
calls my machine.
And then they hang up
as soon as I pick it up.
When did this start?
Just this afternoon.
[Clears throat]
Oh, I'm sorry.
Jess... uh, Jett, this
is Jessica Roberts.
Jessie, this is
my brother, Jett.
JESSICA: Hi.
How you doing?
Nice meeting you.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, listen, how about
a toast, you guys?
You, uh, do have glasses
in this pit of yours.
Yeah.
Can't guarantee they're clean.
Hey, man.
What's that on your tie?
Can't expect miracles, huh?
Kampo tells me you live in DC.
Yeah.
What else did he
tell you about me?
That you're a
successful businessman.
Ha.
- Here you go.
- Ooh, hey.
These are nice.
Just for you, babe.
Ladies first here, huh?
Beauty before age.
To life.
[Burp] Good year.
You're a pig, man.
I see you still practice
those good manners, huh?
He taught me everything I know.
So what kind of
business are you in?
Personal finance and
business speculations.
Why?
Just curious.
Will you join us
for dinner tonight?
Hey, look, I was going to
treat the two of you, you know,
For scaring the crap
out of you earlier.
No, I insist.
See, she really hates to cook.
But we made a bet, and she lost.
And now she has to
cook for a whole month.
I won't even ask
what the bet was over.
So you'll come?
7 o'clock sharp?
Do I have a choice?
No.
Sounds like she means business.
She does.
OK, then.
I guess I better be on time.
Yeah, OK.
Good.
Now give me full details when
I see you this afternoon.
Yeah, it's at Westside
Fencing Center.
OK.
Hey, put that thing out, man.
Ah, dammit, dammit, dammit.
You clown.
What happened to your hand?
I've been meaning to ask
you since last night.
Got slammed in a car door.
That's smart.
When did Jessie leave?
About an hour ago.
What time is it now?
It's almost 8 o'clock.
Shit.
I'm late for class.
Hey, Kampo.
Yeah?
I like Jessica, man.
She's full of fire.
How long you two been going out?
Two weeks.
Ooh, two weeks, huh?
That's a new record for you.
Yeah.
She's quite a woman.
I won't argue with that.
She hates businessmen.
Hey, Jett.
Yeah?
I told her about Mom and Dad.
Hey, Kampo, here's
something to hold you over
For the next couple
of months, man.
Thanks Jett.
You butthead.
Glad you're here.
Looking good, Kampo.
Hey, now get to cl...
Now get to class,
Man, before they drop you.
[Phone ringing]
Hey, butthead.
Could you get that phone?
Hello
Who was it?
Jessie?
Nah, it was the wrong number.
Hey, don't forget
about tonight.
Right.
7 o'clock sharp, huh?
I left the directions
to Jessica's house
By that notepad
their on the phone.
All right?
See you later.
All right, man.
Take care.
With the other three
fingers providing
The control of the tip.
If you grip too tightly, then
you lose that point mobility.
And if you don't grip
tightly enough, then... well,
You get disarmed.
Hope you're not
thinking about turning
In your service revolver
for one of those things.
Hand's looking better.
Too bad I can't say the
same thing about you.
Jett, you light up my life.
You know that?
So what's up?
The Ram man, he
wants the meeting
Tonight, Jones construction
site by the water tower.
Yeah, I know where that's at.
Figured you did.
Could have told me this morning
over the phone, you know?
I'm missing a hell
of a ballgame.
No, the line was bugged.
Ramirez?
Probably.
That oily bastard.
How'd he get a line on you?
You were supposed to
be someplace neutral.
Don't know.
I'll find out tonight.
I still think I should
come along as backup.
No.
I'll be fine.
Ramirez won't fuck with me.
Remember, I got the
ace in the hole.
Yeah, well,
speaking of the ace,
I hope you got it
up your sleeve.
It's safe.
He may ask to see it.
Don't worry about it.
You'll still get your cut.
It's just that I
told Ramirez you'd
Show him the postcard
tonight as good faith.
You know, why
would Ramirez care
So much about this postcard?
I mean, it's no
big thing to him.
Well, it seems Juan
Valdez is a little edgy
Since his brother ate all
that chrome at the bank.
Unless you and him know
something that I don't.
Well now, Jett, that would
break our basic trust,
Wouldn't it?
Besides, like you
said, why would I
Risk my share of the cut?
Because you're a
greedy man, Harold.
And you got no balls.
Touche, Jethro.
Touche.
Why do you stand
so far away from me?
Ven aqui, mi amigo.
Come closer, my friend.
Are we on schedule?
There was a few minor setbacks.
May I assume that
you have taken
Care of these minor setbacks?
Yeah.
While all the artillery?
Protection.
One never knows who
his friends and enemies
Are in this crazy business.
Are you my friend?
Friends don't bite the
hands that feed them.
Lay off my brother.
I know nothing of your brother.
So he tapped his
own phone, huh?
And Kerovac, he
slit his own throat?
Not to mention the fucked
up attempt on my life.
If I had wanted you dead,
you would not be here
Now insulting my friendships.
And as for Kerovac, he's
a fool, and unworthy
Of my consideration.
And my brother's phone?
Yes.
For that I am responsible.
Why?
McBain told me he
thought you might
Be staying with your brother.
Oh, fucking McBain.
And it is my life
that is in risk
By coming back to the States.
Do you understand?
Did you bring the postcard?
I'd like to see it.
No.
But it's safe.
You've got to remember, I hold
all the cards in this game.
And this whole thing
goes down on my word,
And my word... [grunt]
He's not coming.
I could have told
you he'd be late.
We might as well
just get started.
If you're so hungry, eat.
Where are you going?
Home.
Kampo, I didn't
mean to upset you.
Yeah.
Well, somehow you
still managed to.
I mean, that's the
problem with you, Jessie.
You just don't think
sometimes before you speak.
When Jett tells me he's going
to be somewhere, he's there.
I just need to be alone
for a little while.
OK?
Yo, Weezy, get a
look at this guy.
Oh, man.
This guy's really messed up.
Looks like Fuzzy's boys
are painting the town.
Nah, Fuzzy does much
better work than this.
This guy's not even dead.
I mean, Fuzzy's
ruthless, but [inaudible]
[Garage door opening]
Why are my ears burning?
Fuzzy?
Ah, now, correct
me if I'm wrong.
But didn't we discuss the
relocation of your operation.
What did we say?
Taiwan?
Having trouble packing?
I'm not having trouble
packing anything.
I'm packing this.
Nice gun.
[Gunshot]
And it's loaded.
[Gunshots]
I thought you told me he would
be bringing me the postcard.
McBain, I believe he
might have talked.
WOMAN (ON PHONE): I don't
care what you believe.
I'll take care of it.
May be able to kill two
birds with one stone.
I hope so for your sake.
WOMAN (ON PHONE): Buenas noches.
No!
Jett!
[Sobbing]
No!
Go ahead, take a sip.
It'll make you feel better.
The body's been taken care of.
Thank you.
That'll be all.
Officer Kersey, could
you come with me, please?
Put that down.
Just following
standard procedures.
Why don't you just
leave me alone.
My brother dies outside.
And you and your
people are up here
Taking pictures, and snooping
around like I was guilty.
We know you had nothing to
do with your brother's murder.
We just have to make
sure our investigation's
Thorough so we can find out who
killed your brother and why.
You can understand
that, can't you.
I don't want to understand
anything right now.
Please, just a few
more questions.
Was your brother's
visit planned?
No.
None of his visits
where ever planned.
He traveled a lot for business.
Whenever he came to LA,
he'd stop in to see me.
Mhm.
And what can you
tell us about this?
I wrote that on the pad over
by the phone... directions
To my girlfriend's house.
Jett was supposed to
come over for dinner.
Make a note of that.
That'll be enough
questions, Lieutenant Weller.
You and your people
are relieved.
You do the uniform justice.
Oh, Weller, did you find
anything on the body?
Haven't heard the
Dodgers score, have you?
Sure.
It's four to four in the ninth.
Hell of the game.
Hell of a game.
Thanks for the cooperation.
I'm sorry about all this.
It's a damn freaking
lousy time to bother you.
Don't then.
I don't have a choice.
I worked with your brother.
He was my friend.
My brother was not a cop.
I know.
I'm not a cop.
I'm a federal agent,
just like Jett.
My brother was a businessman.
Kampo, I suggest you listened
to what I have to say.
Your life may be in danger.
Who are you?
Name's McBain, Harold McBain.
Jett was my partner.
Look, I'm sorry.
It's just that...
That's all right.
Been a lousy day for me too.
What am I supposed to do?
Right now, you can listen.
Your brother worked
for a special agency
Tucked away between the Treasury
Department and Foreign Affairs.
What does that have to do
with my brother's death.
Kampo, this just wasn't
another tuition visit.
Jett was in LA on assignment.
We'd like to use you, Kampo,
to get to Jett's killer.
Why would they want me?
I'm just a college student.
Well, Jett was staying
with you, right?
Now, whoever
killed him may think
That he told you something.
He didn't say a word to me.
Christ's sakes, I
didn't even know he
Was a federal agent until now.
All right, Kampo.
I know.
But just try and think, did
Jett say anything unusual?
No.
Did he... give you
anything to hold for him?
No, nothing.
Anything, Kampo.
He didn't give me anything.
All right, Kampo.
It's been a long day.
I'll leave you alone.
Everything that I've told you
is pretty highly classified.
So don't repeat a
word to anyone, OK?
What about tonight?
My men will be
watching your apartment.
You'll be fine.
Why don't you get out of those
wet clothes, have a drunk,
And try and get some sleep.
I'll pick you up in the morning.
Here's a 24 hour number
you can reach me at.
Don't be afraid to use it.
Your tax dollars
are paying for it.
The number spells out any time.
And Kampo, try and relax.
You'll be fine.
Trust me.
Who's there?
Who are you?
Hey, what do you want?
Nice work.
Just in case your boss
decides I'm expendable.
To the warehouse, boys.
Andele.
[Whistling]
Relax, Kampo.
How do you know my name?
Tell me, what do you know?
About what?
What are you talking about?
Ah, truly you disappoint me.
I expected so much more
from Jett's little brother.
Really, I don't know
what you're talking about.
I'm just a college student.
Enjoy it.
It is the last time in
your life that people
Will expect nothing from you.
Unfortunately, I have not
the time or the patience.
Did you kill my brother?
Yes.
Dirty fucking scum!
You see how easy it is, Kampo?
You ask me a question, I
answer it... simplemente.
Now, once again, tell
me, what do you know?
Son of a bitch.
Oh, your brother,
he surprised me.
It took a great deal
of stamina and courage
For him to make it back to you.
He must have wanted to tell
you something before he died.
I'll kill you.
Oh, the puppy growls.
You know, it is so interesting.
Right now, mi amigo,
you would do anything
You could to get me.
Es verdad?
Shortly, you will do anything
you can to get away from me.
Wait.
Wait!
What is this?
[Gasping]
Amazing how the body reacts to
a sudden change in temperature.
Quite draining, hm?
Kampo, spare yourself
this barbaric [inaudible].
It is so distasteful.
Now, tell me.
What do you know?
Nothing.
You see, college, during
each time you do not answer
My question, I
will instruct them
To hold your head
under the water
For a longer period
of time until... well,
Until you pass out or drown.
Come on, scholar.
Being able to coax
answers from your mind
Is a student's greatest asset?
Hm?
Getting weaker?
Having a hard time seeing?
You're hearing is going.
Is that not correct?
Yes.
Ah, see, that is the
first correct answer
You have given me.
Now tell me.
What do you know?
Postcard.
Ah, excellent.
Excellent.
What about the postcard.
I don't know anything
about the postcard.
[Gasping]
Donde esta la tarjeta postal?
[Inaudible] Spanish.
La timbre postal.
I don't speak...
La tienes bien cuidada?
- Speak Spanish.
- The postcard.
Where is it?
Is it safe?
[Inaudible] Yes.
I believe you.
Get him out of my sight.
Oh, those goddamn Mets.
Took you long enough.
What did he say?
He knows nothing.
Really?
You call this nothing?
Shit.
He's gone.
I told you not to
leave him alone.
I only left him alone
for a couple of minutes.
That's all.
Long enough to let him escape.
Well, check the property.
In his condition, he
could not have gone far.
Now!
Well, well, well.
Ramirez family sure
is getting sloppy.
Guess our climate
doesn't agree with you.
Sloppy?
You asshole.
I'd be out of the States
by now if you were taking
Care of business properly.
Yeah, well just remember who
needs who for this little deal
To work.
What I need you do is to
take care of this kid once
And for all.
After I get in the car,
I want you to follow us.
Where are you going
to direct him to?
Do as you're told
and follow us.
And how are we
going to know where?
[Inaudible] and listen.
I want you to fire in
the car a few months
Miles away from the airport.
I'll handle the rest.
Jessie?
Relax, Kampo, she's fine.
She's very fine.
You were part of it all along.
Why?
I collect stamps.
Well, almost 10 AM.
Where does the time go, huh?
What happens at 10 AM?
I'll be a very wealthy man.
And the two of you will be dead.
Now I have to pick up
Senor Ramirez at the bank,
And escort him to his airplane.
Unfortunately, he'll be just as
accident-prone as his brother.
Oh, speaking of brothers, Kampo,
tell Jett is was a sweet deal,
A very sweet deal.
[Gunshot]
Oh god.
Are you all right?
Come on, we have to go.
I have to get dressed first.
Change in the car.
Where are we going?
- To the bank.
- Bank?
Why?
I'll explain to you in the car.
[Engine sputtering]
Dammit!
What is it?
Bastard cut all the wires.
Oh, god.
What are we gonna do?
I have an idea.
I'll be right back.
Any problems with the kid?
Problems have only just begun.
Get in.
Get in!
JESSICA: Keep your hands
where I can see them.
Sure.
Whatever you say.
KAMPO: Pass your
briefcase back to Jessica.
You're making a big
mistake [inaudible],
Just like your brother did.
KAMPO: Bastard.
I should fucking
kill you right now.
[Laughing]
You haven't got the
balls... the huevos, eh?
Tu sabes, profesor.
Where are you taking me?
Somewhere I can drop you off
to the proper authorities.
Bad idea.
[Gunshots]
Get out of the car.
Get out!
Slowly.
Put your hands up.
Put them up.
Kampo, my men are just outside.
You're sealed in.
Give it up.
There's no reason
for you to follow
In your brother's footsteps.
Shut up.
Put your hands up.
Jessie, get out of the car and
handcuff this piece of shit.
Kampo... Kampo, why put
the girl at risk as well?
Your plan will never work.
I said shut up.
Jessie!
[Scream]
[Gunshots]
RAMIREZ: After him.
He went behind
the wooden crates.
Come on, college student.
There's no way out for you.
All I want is my briefcase.
[Gunshots]
Carlos?
Cacho?
Answer me.
Do you have my briefcase?
Shit.
You're a dead man, Kampo.
Ramirez [inaudible].
Surprises.
[Gunshot]
[Bang]
This neighborhood
has gone to hell.
Kampo!
You can't hide from me.
[Gunshot]
Dios.
Mi Dios.
[Inaudible]
Fuck you.
Don't move.
[Gunshot]
[Sirens]
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
It's over.
Not yet.
MAN: Damn.
What the hell was that?