[Piano music and fire crackling]
Welcome, everyone.
I am so glad you're here.
I love Christmas.
I admit it, I love everything
about Christmas time.
I love the cookies,
I love the fire,
I love the presents,
I love the stockings,
I love the tree,
I love the fudge,
I love the lights.
It's a great time for growing
out the winter beard.
I love everything about it.
I love the music, I love
the carols and the hymns,
I love all the kids.
And I love the spirit in the air
at Christmas time,
Wherever you go.
There's something that makes
people want to be more kind.
At Christmas, they want to be
more compassionate,
More helpful, more generous.
Donations go up
all around the world.
Something that makes people
bring others in
From out of the cold
and help them,
Clothe them, feed them.
And best of all, I think there's
something about Christmas
That all of us sense deep inside
that says,
"Something big happened,
and because of it,
Everything is going to be okay."
And I love hot chocolate!
[Fire crackling]
But have you noticed,
there's some people
Who would love to put a big
wet blanket on all of this.
They don't want us to love
Christmas so much
And celebrate it the way we do.
There's this one group over
here that says,
"Hey, if you want to sing
your songs and do your stuff"
At Christmas time,
that's fine, but tone it down.
Don't sing so loud."
Right?
"Just, you take
your private stuff"
And you just keep it
in your house.
Don't let it spill out
into the public
And bother the rest of us.
"Just keep it tucked in
and private."
And then there's
this other group over here
Who's actually on
the inside who's telling us,
"Everything you're doing,"
All this stuff, the images,
the characters,
The traditions, it's all wrong.
It has nothing to do
with Christmas.
As a matter of fact, you should
just take all of that,
Wrap it up and throw it
out the door
"Because it's all bad."
[Piano music]
You know, what are they
gonna do next,
Tell us hot chocolate's
bad for us?
That the Druids invented it?
So what are we supposed to do?
I mean, it can get
pretty confusing.
And all this bickering
is definitely not
Doing anything good
for our kids.
Maybe we need a word
from the outside.
A voice, someone
who can remind us
Of the true meaning
of Christmas.
Because maybe somewhere
along the way,
We lost sight of the real story.
Maybe we've got it wrong.
Or, maybe we're listening
to the wrong people.
Or, maybe, just maybe,
Someone like Santa Claus is
actually on the team?
Sir?
Go away.
He's here, Sir.
[Instrumental music]
Where?
Here, at the Tavern.
Grab my coat.
[Instrumental music]
Stories are tricky things,
Especially the ones that
we've heard lots of times.
There was a time when
we didn't mind hearing
The same stories over
and over again.
In fact, when we were children,
We insisted on hearing them
on an endless loop.
In fact, we'd even beg and plead
with our parents
Until they either gave up
or gave in.
Then we got older,
and we thought maybe
It's time for some new stories.
We wanted to be surprised.
We wanted more twists and turns,
and we'd roll our eyes
If something ever got
too predictable.
But then we had kids of our own,
And we found ourselves
telling them
The same stories our parents
told us.
Only we thought that
maybe the stories
Were a bit too scary.
We got nervous that
the wolf or the witch
Might actually give them
nightmares.
So, we eased off on the bad guys
or even left them out entirely.
Our heroes got tamed
And cut down to more
manageable size.
They needed to be less intense,
more jolly.
But the stories we hear
And the stories we tell
shape us.
They teach us how to live
by showing us how to live.
You and I are in a story
right now
And how we enter this story
matters.
* "Silent Night"
[Upbeat music]
[Background conversations]
* "Hark the Herald Angels Sing"
Hey, everybody.
That's me enjoying the party.
And that's my sister.
She's throwing the party.
No one loves a Christmas party
more than her.
As always, amazing.
Hey, you really stepped it up
this year.
You got Santa Claus.
Where'd you find him?
What do you have to pay
a guy like that?
It's Uncle Bill.
[Kids giggling]
Maybe it was the beard.
I didn't see him.
Hey, does Uncle Bill work?
Does he have a job?
No, that's why we hired him.
No.
Hey, uh, where's Christian?
Oh, he's in the other room.
Yeah? How's he doing?
Is he okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah, he's fine.
- You sure?
Yeah.
I don't know.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, do I need to break
some legs?
Is he not treating you right?
No.
I'll take him out in the back
right now.
No, no. He's fine, really!
He's just... he's just not
into Christmas this year.
That's all.
[Instrumental music]
All right, who wants
hot chocolate?
I'm hot chocolate guy!
Come on in, guys!
Remember how I said earlier
that you and I are
In the middle of a story?
The difference between our story
and the stories we heard as kids
Is that we get to help
write ours,
And we can choose to be
the hero or the villain.
We can be the wise man
or the fool.
We can be Tiny Tim
or Uncle Scrooge.
Even Uncle Scrooge has a story,
and he has his reasons.
Problems don't take a break just
because it's Christmas time.
Maybe someone's missed
his Christmas bonus this year
Or maybe he lost his job
or even a loved one.
Or maybe, just maybe,
He just doesn't like Christmas
under any circumstances.
And that's Christian,
my brother-in-law.
My sister wasn't exaggerating.
He is not into Christmas
this year.
You just don't know
someone's story
Until you see what's going on
inside his head.
[Intense music]
Where some see youthful joy,
Others see phony smiles
and spoiled, bratty kids.
Where some see laughter
and holiday cheer,
Others see pretense
and obligations.
Where some see
festive decorations,
Others see perverted symbols
with hidden meanings.
Where some see innocent toys,
Others see pointless
distractions.
Where some see generosity
and the joy of giving,
Others see needless spending
and bad stewardship.
Commercialism, greed,
holiday junk, materialism,
Paganism, elf worship.
The list goes on and on.
Some people are determined
to see the worst
In even the best of things,
A big slap in the face to
the true meaning of Christmas.
[Distorted laughter]
[Intense music]
My man, Christian!
How you doing?
What's up, Deandre?
How you been?
You know me, blessed
and highly favored.
And?
Saved and sanctified,
filled with the Holy Ghost
And that with a burning fire!
And?
Made evident by speaking
in tongues, of course.
[Laughing]
You guys and your verses.
You really need to work
on your exegesis.
Extra Jesus?
Man, I've had my extra Jesus
Ever since I was baptized
for the second time. Ha!
You gonna give me some?
Yeah.
That's not what I meant...
- You get that memo?
- About what?
No more crazy shirt Fridays.
From who?
The man, corporate.
They think they gonna
tell us what to do.
We gonna go to HR.
I'm gonna take it
straight to HR.
You got to read your emails.
If we don't have
crazy shirt Fridays,
It's the end for us, man.
That's all we got!
What else do we get?
Floor two?
I don't want floor two.
You know what happens
down in floor two? I don't.
Don't want to find out
'cause I'm on floor four,
And I like it that way.
We gonna keep it that way.
We gonna march if we have to.
Straight power.
Me and you.
My people have been
through enough.
First they come in, start
telling us what we gonna do,
And then they start taking over,
Telling us we can't have
Fridays,
Then you can't have
Thursdays,
Then you can't have Tuesdays,
and what's left?
Wednesday. Hump day!
That's already a day.
That's not our day.
We need a day for us,
crazy shirt Fridays.
Do you know how many
crazy shirts I've got
That my wife gave me
for Christmas?
What am I gonna do with those?
[* "Deck the Halls"
(playing over dialogue]
- Are you listening to me?
- What?
I'm gonna get some
hot chocolate.
I'll send you the email again,
all right?
I'm out.
* "Deck the Halls"
And when we see someone
struggling around Christmas,
We should reach out.
Hey, Christian!
Nope. Not here.
Just Bill on the couch.
[Instrumental music]
And if that person goes missing
from the Christmas party,
Especially if it's
at his own home,
A good place to look would be
somewhere quiet,
Free from Christmas.
[Instrumental music]
Ah, the car in the driveway.
See, if this were a story,
That's exactly where you
would expect to find him,
And you would know that this
character needs an intervention.
[Instrumental music]
- Hey.
I was wondering where you were.
Just, you know... taking a break.
You okay?
Yeah.
It just gets... noisy, yeah.
[Humming "Carol of the Bells"]
I was driving home today,
and, uh...
Right on Main,
everything's lit up.
I'm driving by a store,
and I, I see...
I see a little girl and her mom.
The little girl's got this look
on her face like... [whining]
And her Mom's looking at her
like, "Oh, it's okay, okay,"
And you know, the mom's
got bags with her.
You can tell they've been,
they've been shopping,
And the little girl is
just so upset.
Obviously, whatever she wants,
she's not getting.
Everybody just wants stuff.
And then, then I, come here
And I look at here,
and I look at the...
I look at the food,
I look at like, a ham.
I didn't even know we could
get a ham that big.
I see the presents.
I see, I see... I see the tree.
I see... I see Santa.
It's like, what are
we gonna do?
We're gonna open those presents.
Nieces and nephews are gonna
get all excited,
They're gonna tear through...
And it's like three weeks
from now,
No one's gonna be
playing with it.
And that money spent...
How many kids could we have fed?
How many wells could
we have dug?
Yeah.
That's Christmas.
Don't... don't...
I love your sister,
I love her to death.
And she loves,
she loves doing this.
She loves putting all
the lights up and...
But I look... I look
at what Christmas is.
I think to myself, "This cannot
be what God wants."
[Instrumental music]
And deep... and deep
in the corner,
Stuck in the corner will be
a little snow globe,
A little nativity scene,
a little baby Jesus.
We stick it somewhere
in the corner,
Don't really see it,
and it's a trinket
While a big old Christmas tree
just...
"I'm the big tree!"
I'm the big center...
I'm the big centerpiece
"Of all of Christmas."
And Santa's over there,
and over here...
"Yeah, let's just put Jesus
in the corner."
Let's put him right there,
And put a little glass thing
around him.
Shake it upside down.
It's winter.
Snow falls all over,
all over baby Jesus.
And then finally, he was
not born in December.
This is not what Christmas
is all about.
I hear you.
- I get it.
- My man.
But this is all wrong.
This is all wrong.
No.
You're all wrong.
About what?
About everything you just said.
I said a lot.
Yeah, and it's all wrong.
[Instrumental music]
I think you mean well,
But you got the whole thing
wrong.
You, you drank the Kool-Aid.
You, you took the bait,
hook, line and sinker.
You swallowed the whole thing.
Guess what?
Everything you see
inside there,
It's all about Christmas.
It's all about Jesus, and you're
spoiling the whole thing.
Not just for your wife,
But for everybody
inside your house.
You're listening to
the wrong people.
Are we seeing the same party?
Are we seeing the same
everything
That's going on in there?
Yeah.
Okay, so, okay, so...
explain to me
How when I walk into
that Christmas party,
Which is going on all over
the world...
Uh-huh.
Explain to me how
that Christmas party
Honors and glorifies Jesus.
'Cause I'm not seeing it.
Where do I start?
Let's start with
your snow globe.
The Nativity.
Now, I want you
to visualize this.
Close your eyes
and, and visualize this.
Okay, alright, I'll play.
I see it.
A baby is born.
If you had to pick
one valuable thing
In all of the decorations around
your house at Christmas time,
It would probably be
your Nativity set.
But Christian, I don't
even think you see
What's so amazing
about that scene
Because to think that
it's only valuable
Because the baby Jesus is there
Misses a huge part
of what's going on.
The birth of the baby
is valuable
Because of the story
he enters into.
* "O Come, O Come, Emmanuel"
I want you to see a cave,
not a stable
Or some little prairie farm
barn thing.
First of all, a manger is
a feeding trough,
And it's probably going to be
carved out of a rock.
It's going to be in a cave,
And upon that rock you would
feed your animals.
* "O Come, O Come, Emmanuel"
Now, move beyond the cute
and traditional
Where everything is
safe and soft,
Where everyone has white skin
and clean clothes.
See a cave, see a place
for food.
Now, let's get this story right.
This was a child that
was born into a world
Where the world power
wanted to kill him
Just for being born.
K of soldiers surrounding the
You need to think
of Herod's soldiers
Moving through the streets,
Finding babies
and murdering them.
And mothers weeping
for their children.
[Weapons clanging]
Let's set the stage.
We're very careful about
having Mary there,
Kneeling by her newborn miracle.
Joseph is there, surely amazed
at what had just happened.
Baby Jesus is there,
And the Bible draws
our attention
To something that we usually
think of as just a prop.
Let's take everything away
for a moment.
Let's take away Joseph,
Leaving just a young girl
and her newborn infant.
Now, let's take away Mary,
leaving the baby.
Let's even take away the baby
himself for just a moment.
Now, don't panic.
It's not because he isn't
The most important person
in the story.
He is.
But because by getting
a look at this prop,
We'll get a better idea of why
he was born in the first place.
Swaddling cloth.
What is this swaddling cloth?
Is it just a blanket for a baby?
We usually only think
of the baby Jesus
Being wrapped in cloths,
But the Bible brings these
cloths back into the story
One more time...
At his tomb when they rolled
that stone away.
The cloth in the tomb was empty
Because it could not hold
the body wrapped inside.
Jesus escaped death as a baby
by the hand of God,
And he conquered death
as an adult
By that very same hand,
And because that cloth
could not hold him,
Death still cannot win.
Did you ever wonder
why the wise men
Brought frankincense and myrrh
at Jesus' birth?
Those are burial spices.
Why would they bring
burial spices to a baby shower?
The birth scene is a picture
of a coming burial scene.
The soldiers don't get to kill
the baby, though.
He came to die, but it was
according to his Father's plan,
In his timing and on his terms.
The death of Jesus was not
the tragic end to the story.
It was the plan all along,
To offer up his body as bread
for the hungry
And to shed his blood to cover
the sins of the guilty.
Now, put Jesus back
into that cloth
And let that image paint
the picture for you.
A baby who came to die,
But not until
the appointed time.
Yes, that's the reason for
the season right there.
[Instrumental music]
I got to admit I never saw
the whole swaddling cloth thing.
I, I didn't either.
But that's my point.
Like, I can open the Bible,
I can look right there,
and I can go, "Oh, there it is!"
Like, I didn't,
I didn't even see that!"
Like, that stuff blows my mind!
Like, that's, that's
all I'm saying.
And Herod's soldiers
And kind of looking at
that whole thing like that's...
I feel like we need to have
like little Herod soldiers
Like all around, you know,
the chimney...
Right.
For me to be able to see like,
this is what's going on.
Right, right.
[Background conversations]
* "We Wish You
a Merry Christmas" *
My man, Deandre.
What's happening?
You get that memo?
Oh, you know I got that memo.
(chuckles)
It's not a laughing matter,
though man.
You know what's really
going on here.
Yes.
No, no, no, I don't.
Three words: war on Christmas.
Oh yeah.
I think it would be
in our best interest
Before we go any further.
We got to be really careful.
You never know who's listening
or watching.
Cups up.
All right, man, check this out.
We got to go on the offensive.
It's like the rapper, Sugar Free
said, "If you stay ready",
You ain't got to get ready."
They're already taking away
our freedom of speech.
I can't say Merry Christmas
at work no more.
I have to say Happy Holidays,
but I am not in a daze.
I am wide awake.
It's deeper than that, though.
You heard about Area 51?
What about Area 52?
That's where they keeping
all the mangers and trees
And Nativity scenes
they keep taking down.
Speaking of down, you know why
the Pope really stepped down?
Da Vinci code, right? Wrong.
There's a whole Picasso code.
I'm actually still working
on that one.
Come on, man, they got fluoride
in our water.
[Instrumental music]
I'm saying, that's gotta cause
at least Asperger's.
Speaking of burgers,
You probably ain't even
had one in years.
That ain't no ground beef,
homie.
That's pink slime.
I seen it on YouTube.
Look it up.
You know what you got to do?
Get like me and wifey,
Strictly ostrich and emu meat,
homie.
Delicious and exotic.
Come on, you got the chemtrails
and HAARP
Trying to control the weather
With the womp, womp,
womp sounds.
GMO's and pesticides.
You know there's a huge
honey bee shortage, right?
Exactly.
Colony collapse disorder.
Ah, that rhymes
with new world order.
Coincidence? I thinks not.
I saw "Loose Change,"
I know what's up
With the whole Koch brothers,
Halliburton,
Dick Cheney, Enron, Fannie Mac,
Freddie Mae tie-in.
But I mean, that's obvious.
Look, man, I saw it on Fox News,
so you know it's true.
War on Christmas,
it's everywhere.
Hey! Who needs more coffee?
Uh, no, we're good.
Delicious, though.
[Instrumental music]
All right, man,
I think we're cool.
Cups down.
[Instrumental music]
So you know what
we got to do, right?
What?
The only thing we can do.
[Instrumental music]
Christmas trees.
(chuckles)
News flash!
Christmas tree,
not in the Bible!
Matthew, Mark, Luke, John,
Deuteronomy.
Did I miss it?
I miss Leviticus sometimes,
But I'm pretty sure
it's not in there.
That's the big thing I got
sitting in my house right now,
Is a big Christmas tree.
That's a pagan...
That's a pagan idol symbol
worshipping thingy.
You know that, right?
That's what they would
worship the god with.
You know, the gods.
- What gods?
- The gods.
Which gods?
[Thunder rumbles]
Thorsus, Thorsirus, Thor...
it's always a Norwegian...
It's, that's what they would do.
It was winter, it was
the Winter Solstice.
News flash, it's December.
Jesus was not born in December,
And we're celebrating
his birthday in December.
Hello?
When was he born?
Probably, he was probably,
probably...
I don't know, but he wasn't
born in December.
Everyone knows that.
So, we're celebrating that...
And the trees are like,
it's about like,
The evergreen trees
represents eternal life...
- Yes.
- And fertility, fertility gods.
Wikipedia. Yeah.
And people would worship
these symbols then,
And they believed that if they
worshipped these symbols
And they laid down their
offerings and their gifts,
That they would inherit
eternal life.
You know this.
And this is...
this is all idolatry.
Yes, it's idolatry in my house.
How do your kids react
every morning on Christmas?
What do they do? Tell me.
What do they do?
I make my kids wait at
the top of the staircase.
I don't let them come
down the stairs
Until my wife and I get
everything ready, the tree,
And the anticipation builds,
and they run down the stairs
When I tell them they can,
and they run out to the tree,
And they just are blown away
By all the presents sitting
at the base of the tree.
That's exactly what
the Druids did.
- Right.
- Druids.
You look this up.
This is all history.
So, where, I ask again,
Where are Christmas trees
in the Bible?
I'm glad you asked.
I'll close my eyes again.
Here I go, I'm waiting.
Okay. What's the chapter?
What's the verse?
Do you have a weird, obscure
verse in Numbers?
Where... where am I going?
Where do I start in the Bible?
Christmas trees, I'm waiting.
Where do I go?
I'm glad my sister married you.
This is awesome.
[Humming theme to "Jeopardy"]
Bro, bro, look at me.
* Do, do, do, do, do
Where we going in the Bible?
Genesis.
* "Ding, Dong,
Merrily on High" *
The whole biblical story
starts in a tree lot.
The Garden of Eden was
full of trees.
Adam and Eve were given
the fruit of these trees to eat,
But the story calls
our attention
To two of these trees
in particular.
First, the tree of the knowledge
of good and evil
And then later the tree of life.
One tree was off limits
because by eating it,
Man would surely die.
But Adam ate from the first tree
and was thrown out of the garden
So that he couldn't eat
from the second.
Mankind would have to wait
Until the path to that tree
was reopened,
But I'm getting ahead of myself.
We'll come back to that later.
Let's talk about that
evergreen tree in your house
Decorated with stylized fruit
and lights
That's making you so nervous.
You're anxious because
you can't find it in the Bible.
Well, let me help you.
When God created the world,
he filled it with trees.
He hung fruit on the trees.
When it was time for him
to build his house
And make it beautiful,
God brought trees inside.
The walls of his temple were
frescoed with images of trees.
The lamp stand in his tabernacle
was an almond tree.
And guess what he placed
on the branches of the tree
In his house?
Lights.
Beautiful green trees
decorated with fruit
Shimmering with lights
inside a house.
That's God's idea,
not the Druids.
And the early church had
plenty of good reasons
To celebrate the birth of Jesus
on December 25,
And it had nothing to do
with the winter solstice.
By the way, last I checked,
It was God who made
the winter solstice
When he set the planets
on their path around the sun.
And it's actually quite fitting
That we celebrate the birth of
Jesus in the bleak, mid-winter
When the world appears
to be sleeping and dying,
The darkest and coldest time
of year.
Right then at that time, we're
proclaiming the turn of history
From darkness to light,
from coldness to warmth,
And from death to life.
So, enough with what pagans
want us to see.
Let's look at what God
wants us to see.
Let's go back to our story.
As I was saying,
Adam stole the fruit
from God's tree and ate it.
Now, when you steal something,
you're required to put it back.
But how could he?
Adam had already eaten it.
It had gone down inside,
and become part of him.
The only way that Adam could
put the fruit back on the tree
Would be, as crazy
as it sounds,
He would have to put himself
up on that tree.
Now, think.
What did Jesus do?
He was the last Adam.
Jesus was able to do
what Adam could not do.
He put himself up on a tree,
making us right with God.
Jesus was God's blessed fruit
hung on his blessed tree.
[Instrumental music]
Remember that swaddling cloth?
It comes back into the story
again at Jesus' burial.
Nicodemus brings all
the funeral preparations,
Frankincense, myrrh,
aloe and cloth.
And why is he
bringing the cloth?
To wrap the body of
our crucified Savior,
Jesus, put to death on a tree.
The Bible begins with trees.
Adam stole the fruit from
God's tree and ate it.
The fruit that the first Adam
stole was put back on the tree
By the last Adam when he,
himself, hung on a wooden cross.
[Instrumental music]
So, when you walk
into a Christmas tree lot,
I want you to see
hundreds of crosses
That will never be used because
of Jesus' finished work.
He paid the price that
we could never have paid.
He took the curse
that was rightly ours.
He reconciled us to God.
He is the light of the world
that has pierced the darkness.
[Instrumental music]
So, when you see
empty Christmas trees,
See an empty cross.
And when you see
the empty cross,
See the empty cloth lying
in an empty tomb.
And when you see an empty
tomb, do what the disciples did,
Turn and run to tell the story
that Jesus is alive.
[Rain falling]
That's pretty cool.
It's awesome.
Just I wasn't...
and I almost feel bad.
I wasn't looking closely
enough at...
I just didn't, I didn't,
I didn't see that.
I didn't...
Hey, I didn't see it either.
That's why I'm sharing it
with you.
Santa Claus... in the Bible.
Unless I missed somewhere
in the Bible
Where God sends his
only begotten...
Elf? (Laughs)
Elf, Santa dude, like...
Reindeer pulling a sleigh?
Just tell me right now
you're not going to pull like...
Sliding down a chimney.
Zephaniah 4 or like
3rd Corinthians 15,
Like, "Oh, there's Santa Claus."
I didn't even see it
right there!"
Just tell me right now.
Okay, we're good, right?
That's not going
to happen, okay.
So, hold on, hold on.
So, I'm, I'm safe in saying
That there is no Santa Claus
in the Bible?
[Instrumental music]
No, there is no Santa Claus
in the Bible, but...
Okay. Hold, eh...
No, no, no, hold on.
Hold on, hold on.
Just think about it,
think about it for one minute.
That's the guy, Santa,
that's obliterated Jesus.
Jesus is gone!
The reason for the season
is Santa Claus!
What the kids are saying
all across the world is not,
"I'm so excited to celebrate
the birth of Jesus!"
No, they're saying,
"I'm so excited"
To get my picture taken
with Santa Claus!
"You're going to bring me
presents!"
S-A-N-T-A.
Rearrange the letters.
Satan.
Santa, Satan.
Same letters.
- Right?
- Right.
Coincidence?
[Instrumental music]
Yeah.
Okay, and who's completely
gotten rid of Jesus?
Satan. Santa.
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
Where's ho, ho, ho, ho, ho
in the Bible?
Ho, ho, ho. Bible.
* You better watch out,
you better not pout. *
* You better not cry,
I'm telling you why. *
* Santa Claus is coming
to town. *
What's the next line?
* He knows when you are
sleeping. *
* He knows when you are awake.
Right, omniscient.
* ...so be good
for goodness sake. *
Omniscience, omnipresence.
He rewards the good,
and he punishes the bad.
Last I checked, that was God.
By the way, this is works based.
Last I checked, saved by grace.
This is, this is a complete
hijacking.
This is a hijacking...
High-handed hijacking,
handedness jacking.
It's like a carjacking
but like of our religion.
And guess what,
Santa got in the car,
Kicked Jesus out and was like,
"Rolling, rolling, rolling,"
and took it.
Gone.
Christmas is gone.
It's all about Santa.
Where in the Bible?
Flip, flip, flip, flip, flip.
Red letter, red letter,
red letter.
Where is it?
So, okay. Hold on.
I can't, I can't wait
for this one.
Here we go, here we go.
I'm ready. Eyes are closed.
I'm looking at, I see him.
Hold on, I see his face.
[Static noises]
Oh, I see his face.
What do you see?
You see a little elf
and he's in a sleigh
And he's in a little red cap
with a little red,
Little red outfit.
- Yeah.
- He's got a sack over his back.
And he's being pulled
by a team of reindeer.
Right. Not in the Bible.
And he's gonna land on a roof,
And he's gonna slide
down a chimney,
And he's going to fill stockings
And put presents around
the base of a tree.
- Right.
- Right?
- Okay.
[Static noises]
[Inhales]
Let me tell you about
the real Santa Claus.
Oh, I'm ready.
[Instrumental music]
The real Santa Claus was
a real bad, bad dude.
And when I say bad,
I mean bad in the good way.
So Christian, you want Christmas
to be all about Jesus?
You think you're fighting
the good fight
By scowling at decorations
and scoffing at presents
And mocking Christmas trees?
Let me show you how a real
defender of the faith does it.
Now, if I tried to show you
how this really happened,
You'd see a lot of guys in robes
wearing tall hats,
Carrying scepters and swinging
incense everywhere.
It'd be a mess.
[Knuckles cracking]
I want you to imagine this
a little more...
Lord of the Rings-y.
Sir?
Go away.
He's here, Sir.
[Fire crackling]
Where?
Here, at the Tavern.
[Instrumental music]
Grab my coat.
His real name was Nicholas.
He was a devout Christian.
He was the Bishop of Myra,
a city in modern day Turkey.
He was left with a large sum
of money when his parents died,
And he became famous
for his kindness
Toward the poor and his generous
giving of gifts to children.
[Instrumental music]
He was there at the Council
of Nicaea in A.D. 325,
One of the most important events
of church history
Use one of the most
rtant doctrines of the faith
Was being challenged.
There were leaders in the church
that had begun
To deny the deity of Christ,
The doctrine that confessed
Jesus as the Son of God,
God in the flesh.
Nicholas did not take
kindly to those
Who wanted to reduce Jesus
to a mere man.
The Council of Nicaea ended up
producing what is known today
As the Nicene Creed,
A profession of faith used by
churches all around the world.
The Creed affirmed
the deity of Christ
And the three persons
of the trinity,
But that affirmation
didn't happen
Without Nicholas and a fight.
[Instrumental music]
He was a real man who
fought for a real truth
Against a real enemy
of the faith.
[Instrumental music]
Leading the charge in this
heresy was a Bishop named Arius.
He was known as a charismatic
and compelling speaker.
He was traveling from region
to region spreading his heresy
Like a plague, saying that Jesus
was less than God.
[Instrumental music]
Nicholas had heard enough
of Arius' babbling.
He would be the shepherd
that protects his sheep
From the wolves.
[Instrumental music]
[Heavy thud]
In the beginning was the Word...
And the Word was with God
and the Word... was God.
[Thunder crashes]
The official record says
that at a critical moment
During the Council, Nicholas
put the heretic Arius to shame,
Not only by word but also by
deed, smiting him on the cheek.
[Intense music]
Now, of course, not everyone
at the Council was happy
With his less than jolly
actions.
In fact, they were
so displeased,
They removed his title
as Bishop,
But he was so loved
by the people
That they gave it back to him.
In fact, he was even sainted.
That's why we call him
St. Nicholas.
Those were difficult
and desperate times.
Truth was on the line,
And it was not the time for
this pastor to go soft on truth
Or stay quiet for the sake
of being politically correct.
Nicholas was a hero
who became legendary.
And that legend became
larger than life
And reached mythic proportions.
In France, he was called
Pere Noel.
In Sweden, he was Tomte.
In Norway, he was Julenissen.
In the Netherlands,
he was Sinterklaas.
Everyone wanted a piece of him.
Oh, look who it is.
Better?
You get that out of your system?
Come on. We've got work to do.
[Cheerful music]
Come on.
Let's go bless
some kids tonight.
We've got gifts to give.
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
[Thunder crashes]
So, Christian, the guy
you think is distracting
Everyone's attention from
the birth of the Christ child
Is actually the defender of
the faith you want to be.
[Instrumental music]
Santa...
Is the man!
[Instrumental music]
Yeah, he is.
Bro, let me just say this.
I know you love my sister.
I know you love Christ.
I know you love Christmas,
And you want it to be all about
what it's all about.
But all this is good!
All this is what it's all about.
You just need to see it
with new eyes.
[Rain falling]
I've missed it.
I've absolutely... missed it.
Oh, dude, I am...
I'm that guy in the story.
I'm the jerk.
Oh, dude, this is bad.
This is bad.
I'm that guy.
Oh, dude, I'm staying
in this car all night.
This is horrible.
Do me a favor, go back in,
Say like, "Christian got
a rash," or something.
Like, I broke out in something.
(laughing)
Like I had like some eggnog.
Something that I had no idea
that I was allergic to.
I was like, I couldn't like...
(fakes gagging)
- Someone spiked the egg nog?
- Acid flaccid something.
Like, yes, yes.
And I, and I...
and I had to go.
I had to go get the eggnog shot.
Whatever they give for that,
nog shot.
No.
There's a better way
to end this story.
You know what you need to do?
You need to be the guy...
Who walks back into your house,
walks up to your wife and says,
"I was wrong. I blew it."
You know what you need to do.
What if you did that?
No, you're right,
I should do it.
Or you. It's your sister.
- No, it's me.
- It's your wife.
It's me. It's me.
The best ending to this story
is you being the guy...
That everyone roots for.
You be the guy who saves
Christmas.
You being the
guy who's all in.
I'm going to be that guy.
Go, bro. (Slaps hands)
I'm going to be that guy!
I'm going... I'm going...
I'm going to be the... grrrr.
I'm going to be that guy.
(laughing)
What's up baby,
I'm going to be that guy.
What you got going on, girl?
I'm going to be that...
I'm going to be that guy.
[Instrumental music]
Whoa.
Looks like somebody's
having a moment.
Umm.
[Inhales]
So take it all in,
all the glory of Christmas.
[Instrumental music]
Now, see Christmas through
new eyes.
[Instrumental music]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Back up, everybody!
[Slow motion yelling]
[Floor squeaking]
[Crash, screaming]
Whew! Work, Holy Spirit, ha!
- Can I get a amen?
- Amen!
The scales are falling off.
Glory! Ah, glory! Hmm.
[Instrumental music]
Sometimes you have to be
brought low
To be humbled as a little child
To get the right perspective
on Christmas.
Look at the presents
around your tree.
When you see them
from this perspective,
See how they look
like a city skyline.
[Instrumental music]
Imagine the new Jerusalem,
A heavenly city whose builder
and architect is God,
And the wall of the city
was adorned
With all kinds
of precious stones.
And what's at the center
of that city?
A tree.
[Instrumental music]
The tree of life, made available
By the conquering blood of Jesus
to all who believe.
This tree, full of
healing leaves.
This tree, full of fruit.
This tree, full of lights
that shine in the darkness,
Lights that shine over the city.
[Instrumental music]
So, see the lights,
the stars over Bethlehem
Announcing the birth
of the Prince of Peace.
Lesser lights that remind us
That Jesus is the light
of the world
And that we are to let our light
shine before men.
[Instrumental music]
And there's another thing.
Ook at those presents again,
stacked and wrapped
And made beautiful, waiting
to be torn open.
This isn't bad stewardship.
This is doing what God does.
He has always been giving
gifts to his children
At the base of trees.
Abraham was given the gift of
a son at the Oaks of Mamre.
The Cedars of Lebanon were
given as materials
For Solomon's temple.
R salvation was given to us
t the base of a tree.
[Instrumental music]
So, does this tree belong
in your house?
Should it be loaded with fruit
and lights and presents?
Hmm. Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Part the red sea!
[screams]
[Instrumental music]
And now that you know
who the real Santa is,
I got a question for you.
Would you like to take
a picture with him?
[Upbeat music]
[Instrumental music]
Our Christmas traditions are
so rich and so full
If only we had the eyes
to see them.
[Instrumental music]
It's time to step
out of the car,
Out of the quiet and safe place
where we've been hiding.
It's time to tell everyone
That every inch of this creation
belongs to Jesus.
[Instrumental music]
So, you're out of the car.
Are your eyes open?
What do you see?
A soldier?
[Instrumental music]
We need to make traditions
of our own.
We need to infuse old symbols
with new meaning.
We need to rearrange our lives
and our homes
So that every single thing
points to Jesus.
[Instrumental music]
We need to tell our children
new stories.
We need to be bold.
Remember those soldiers
at the Nativity?
These were Herod's strongest
warriors doing his bidding.
Every toy soldier can be
a reminder
Of the whole story of how a baby
was spared in his infancy
To become the warrior
that ensured
That death finally was killed.
[Instrumental music]
So, bring the soldiers close.
Let them be near the nativity,
and remind your children
That every character
in God's story has a place.
[Instrumental music]
And if you've been that guy,
if you spent the holidays
Terrorizing your family
and your friends,
Scowling at Santa,
frustrating your wife,
It's time to make it right.
[Instrumental music]
Christmas, after all,
Is ultimately about making
all things right.
[Instrumental music]
You okay?
Honey, I've been a bit of a jerk
this Christmas season.
Yeah, you have.
[Instrumental music]
You deserve so much better,
And this Christmas, I want
to give you something
I've been wanting to give you
for a long time.
What do you got in mind,
big papa?
Now, what happens in most
stories at this point?
I mean, if you were writing
this story right now,
What would you want
to have happen?
The cliche kiss, right?
But, if we learned one thing
in all this, let's not forget
That sometimes our heroes
do the unexpected.
I went ahead and just organized
a hip hop dance crew
That encompasses all the joy
in gospel,
Bursting in excitement
that I alone as one man
Just cannot express.
No, really, I did.
Hit it, Deandre!
Oh, man, I got just the track
for you!
How about some
Family Force Five?
"Angels We Have Heard on High".
Come on, people, let's do this!
Yeah! I want to see
a choir in here.
A God squad.
You know how we do.
Ooh, Marshall Foster's
in the house
Kicking it old school.
He on to me. [Laughs]
You know how we do it.
Altos, sopranos and tenors.
Let's do this, baby! Unh!
* Angels we have
heard on high *
* Sweetly singing
o'er the plains *
* And the mountains in reply
echoing their joyous strains *
* Glo-ria,
* In excelsis Deo!
[Cheering]
* Shepherds,
why this jubilee? *
* Why your joyous strains
prolong? *
* What the gladsome
tidings be? *
* Which inspire your
heav'nly song? *
* Glo-ria,
* In excelsis Deo!
[Hip-hop music]
* Come to Bethlehem and see
* Him whose birth
the angels sing *
* Come, adore
on bended knee, *
* Christ the Lord,
the newborn King *
* Glo-ria,
* In excelsis Deo!
[Hip-hop music]
* Uh oh, here come the angels.
[Beat-boxing]
* Put your wings in the air.
* Flap 'em like you
just don't care. *
Oh, flying in, flying in!
* Here come the angels.
[Cheering]
* Talking about the angels.
* Uh oh, here come the angels
[Cheering]
Come on!
* Put your wings in the air.
* Flap 'em like you
just don't care. *
[Hip-hop music]
* Talking about some angels.
* Here come the angels.
* Put your wings in the air.
* Flap 'em like you
just don't care. *
* Talking about some angels.
* Here come the angels.
[Hip-hop music]
* Talking about some angels.
* Uh oh, here come the angels.
* Put your wings in the air.
* Flap 'em like you
just don't care. *
* Talking about some angels.
* Here come the angels.
* Put your wings in the air.
* Flap 'em like you
just don't care. *
* Talking about some angels.
* Here come the angels.
* Glo-ria,
* In excelsis Deo!
[Hip-hop music]
* Talking about some angels *
[Applause]
All right, everybody!
Let's feast!
[Cheering]
Well, that's why I show up
for these parties.
[Instrumental music]
So, this is Christmas.
Pull out your best dishes,
your finest linens,
Your nicest silverware,
the biggest ham.
Every side dish you can
possibly imagine,
And the richest butter.
It's time to feast.
[Instrumental music]
Invite your neighbors,
you co-workers,
Your friends and your family
and make the most of Christmas.
Fill your table with laughter
and stories and songs.
Don't miss a single opportunity
To pass along the joy
of the season.
And don't buy into the complaint
about materialism
During Christmas.
Sure, don't max out
your credit cards
Or use presents to buy friends,
but remember,
This is a celebration
of the eternal God
Taking on a material body.
So, it's right that our holiday
is marked with material things.
Things we can see
with our eyes
And touch with our hands
and look upon.
Ribbons, decorations,
hot chocolate, lights,
Presents, giant hams, stuffing,
fudge, Christmas cards,
And more hot chocolate
piled high with whip cream.
[Instrumental music]
How could we possibly capture
all that Christmas is?
We could eat until we split
at the seams.
We could smile
until our cheeks hurt
And laugh until
our bellies ache.
We could sing until our voices
grew hoarse,
And we would not have even
scratched the surface
Of this glorious day.
Throw your doors open
and invite the world
Into the story of this king
and his kingdom.
This is our story, our city,
our tree, our lights,
Our presents, our songs,
our Saint Nick,
Our hope, our future,
our Savior.
My brother-in-law is seeing it
for the first time,
And once your eyes have been
opened, you can't go back.
[Instrumental music]
All the best to you
and your family this Christmas.
I have to say, things
have improved around here.
[Instrumental music]
* "Christmas Time Again"
* Christmas time is here
* Come and celebrate
the best time of the year *
* The jingle bells are ringing
* And the carolers are singing
their Christmas songs *
* Christmas time has come
* Can you hear the little
drummer boy playing his drum*
* And everywhere you go,
* somebody's wishing you
a Merry Christmas *
Main man, Christian.
How you doin', man?
How you doin', Deandre?
How you been?
Bring it back, here we go.
Alright.
Here we go, and action.
My main man, Christian!
How you doin'?
What's up, Deandre?
How you been?
You know me, blessed
and highly favored.
- And?
- Ha-ha ha...
Bring it back, here we go.
- Blessed and highly favored.
- Blessed and highly favored...
[Both speaking quickly]
Here we go, it's digital,
roll all day, here we go.
It's the end for us, man.
That's all we got!
What else do we get?
Floor two?
I don't want floor two.
Do you know what happens
down at floor two?
I don't, don't wanna find out
'Cause I'm on floor four
and I like it that way.
We gonna keep it that way.
We gonna march if we have to.
Straight power, me and you.
They're not gonna do this
to us, man.
We done been here before.
My people have been through
enough.
I think you Jewish,
So your people have been
through enough too.
We all done been through it,
and that's enough.
- How many people you got?
- All of us, we all people.
Came from Adam, right?
Six, seven, I don't know.
We got a whole bunch.
But who's countin'?
They ain't countin'.
All they see is people.
Me, you, all of us...
- Fingers, do your fingers.
- Five, six, seven.
I don't even know what
I'm saying right now.
I'm just gonna talk and move
my hands and keep going crazy
Till you get everything you
need from this camera.
I'm not gonna... tell them to
come get me 'cause we here.
We got it all up, mmm.
Can't silence me.
- We shall overcome one day!
- Do a little spin.
And they ain't gonna tell me
what to do...
- Do a little spin.
- We gonna do it, we gonna do it.
We gonna take it to,
we gonna march,
We gonna do the running man,
We gonna do everything we got
to do 'cause they don't get us.
No, man, it ain't gonna happen
that way.
Get back in position
and question me,
- You listening?
You heard what I said?
* Thank God for his gift
of love *
* This Christmas
- We say ho!
- Ho!
- Ho! Ho!
[Clapping]
Now, stop!
- Oh, we bad.
- Hammer time.
Oh, we bad.
[Laughter]
Am I good here, Andy?
Kirk, what do you do for
dry mouth in between scenes?
What do you do?
Um, just water.
Water, or do you do like
a fruit thing, like celery?
- What do you do?
- What happened to the ranch?
* Little drummer boy
playing his drums *
- Isn't it terrible?
- Oh, my goodness.
I don't know how you guys
do this.
[Background conversation]
Here we go, quiet please.
Here we go.
(Exhales) Sound, speed.
Hey Kirk, can you puff up
my sweater dirt... dust?
- Pull camera.
- Speeding.
Just hit it, hit, hit, hit.
Hit, hit, hit, hit...
And step out.
[Instrumental music]
- I like fat geese.
- We're rolling, here we go.
Okay, speed and I'll go ahead
and give it a clap.
(Laughing)
Fat geese, giant hams.
I love fat geese
and giant fams.
[Laughs, snorts]
Here we go.
- I'm ready.
- Hey!
* Fa, la, la, la, la, la,
la, la, hey! *
* There's a joy in children
seeing Santa at the mall. *
* There's a joy
the bright lights *
* of this season bring us all.
* How can these compare
* to the good news
the angels tell? *
* Heaven has sent us a Savior.
* What a night,
there is no greater! *
* Jo-o-o-oy, Jo-o-o-oy
* Light a star on
the Christmas tree. *
* Love has come
for you and me. *
* Jo-o-o-oy, Jo-o-o-oy
* I hear the carols
on the radio. *
* So turn it up and let
the whole world know. *
* Because I've got a love
that's so, *
* There is no greater joy.
* I hear it in the bells,
* they're ringing up
and down the street. *
* I see it shining in the smiles
of everyone I meet. *
* It feels to me like hope is
stirring with the winter wind. *
* Heaven has sent us a savior.
* What a night,
there is no greater! *
* Jo-o-o-oy, Jo-o-o-oy
* Hang a star on
the Christmas tree. *
* Love has come
for you and me. *
* Jo-o-o-oy, Jo-o-o-oy
* I hear the carols
on the radio. *
* So turn it up and let
the whole world know. *
* Because I've got a love
that's so, *
* There is no greater joy.
* Joy to the world.
* All Heaven and nature sing.
* Yeah, yeah
[Instrumental music]
* Joy to the world!
* Oooooh...
* Jo-o-o-oy, Jo-o-o-oy
* Hang a star on
the Christmas tree. *
* Love has come
for you and me. *
* Jo-o-o-oy, Jo-o-o-oy
* I hear the carols
on the radio. *
* So turn it up and let
the whole world know. *
* Because I've got a love
that's so, *
* There is no greater joy. *
So, you know what
we gotta do, right?
[Coughing]
I do.
You gotta drink some stuff
down the wrong pipe
And then you go, hah!
[Coughs]
- Throat lozenges.
- Then you go, hah!
[Coughing]
[Laughter]
* La, la, la, la
So you know what
we gotta do, right?
What?
There's only one thing
we can do.
We gotta call Kirk Cameron,
Get him involved,
make a movie about it,
Then we got ourselves
a movement.
You know I love movements.
Start beat-boxing on that.
[Beat-boxing]
It be the movement, improvement
They say the new world order
Flipping in the air
just like a quarter.
How's your daughter,
how's your father,
How's your sister?
Excuse me, mister,
how do you do?
You want some coffee?
My name is Raphi,
maybe Shames Worthy.
Maybe you've heard of me,
maybe it's rapping like this.
Swiss Miss, soft as cocoa.
You know, no, no,
yes, yes, Wes, Wes,
All day, every day,
every which way.
Look at what the plants say.
I listen to nature,
mother nature, father nature.
Your father hates you.
Oh, I'm sorry, Dad,
what did I do?
You know what you did,
call all your crew,
Call your friends,
dress up in some baby blue.
Come back, write an essay.
Tunnel Rats,
that's what they say.
Sleigh, sleigh, pray every day.
Essential.
Monumental.
Environmental.
Heart... control.
They wanna take your soul.
They wanna beat Solid Gold.
I'm on a roll.
They wanna say things
and think about 'em.
I doubt 'em, bing!
'Cause you know what it is.
Music, Cameron, music,
movie biz.
- Kirk, Kirk...
- Cameron.
- Kirk,
- Kirk Cameron.
- It be the, be the...
- Camfam,
- Kirk,
Kirk, Kirk Cameron.
Kirk, Kirk, it ain't James.
- Kirk,
Kirk, Kirk Cameron.
Movement.
We don't stop, baby.
All day, every day.