Low rumbling
orchestra tuning up
sad piano music
Tchaikovsky's
Piano concerto No.1
animalistic grunts
Give me your money...
We know what's
good for you...
Animals are trying
to influence my mind...
Does this look
infected to you?
Animals are trying
to influence my mind...
Mmm, do I like fish sticks!
I could eat them
all day long.
Lemme tell ya,
I just gotta say...
It's time to get moving...
Yes, it might hurt
a little bit...
Little people scrub and clean
my teeth when I sleep at night...
20% more fruit filling!...
I think that she's cheating...
You people make me sick...
I am well prepared and alert...
What? What? What?...
Today I saw five lizards...
A family of air purification
and regulation panels...
All you need is love...
What? What?...
Anybody got a light?...
There's nothing I can do...
Nooo. Nooo. Nooo.
I have important things to say
why won't you listen to me!...
- What?...
- Nooo!...
Your safety is our business...
God is watching you
and he's shaking his head...
Two for the price of one...
Read my bad poetry...
But I want iiiiit!...
The saddest part,
she had no idea...
Those stars are billions
of years old...
The saddest part,
she had no idea...
Those stars are billions
of years old...
More productive!...
Antibacterial...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
Sit still and do what you're told!...
Where's my hat?...
If I smile, everything will be okay!...
Stop following me!...
My career is on the fast track...
When you're good you watch TV...
If you set your mind to it,
you can do anything!...
That's not what I said!...
I'm gonna sue you!...
Do I look like I care?...
cacophony of overlapping voices...
I want my mommy...
I am not your dogfood pony...
That's just what they
want you to believe...
Well that's just too bad...
It won't last, it never does...
Let go of my leg!...
Feed me walnuts!...
Get off my property!...
the music swells
Do I look like I'm made of money?...
You could tie the child down,
with a secure rope or chain...
Stop touching me...
Stop touching me!
Screaming
You are either with us
or against us!...
cacophony of overlapping voices...
Those buildings are falling over!...
Look out!... Look out!...
No! No! No!...
One day we're going to have
all the answers...
intense music begins
Tchaikovsky's Waltz of the Flowers
Tchaikovsky's Piano concerto No.1
begins again
barking
strange animal calls
territorial barking
low repeated grunting
angry squawks and preening
passionate chirping
the music swells
ocean waves and faraway howls
unknown language...
..."meaning of life?"
"Meaning of life."
Ha!
Unknown language...
ocean waves continue
silence
light piano music begins