Hi. Can I have a 7 and 7?
You look like an athlete.
I'm sorry?
You look athletic.
You know, like an athlete.
We're here
for a basketball game.
I knew that.
You don't see
too many girls in here.
Yeah. No, it's just
a close bar for me.
It's just... Close place
to get a drink, whatever.
Shh, shh.
Go get dressed, hon.
There's no school today.
You don't got school today?
- It's Columbus Day.
Well, go get dressed
and wash your face.
Listen. I... I, uh...
I had a nice time.
Hey, do you, um...
Do you think I could
get a hundred dollars?
You wanna borrow
a hundred dollars?
Well...
You work at that place,
don't you?
No.
- Yeah. You do.
No. It's just...
I could really use it.
Look, I don't got
that kind of money.
Well, why not?
Aren't you, like,
a ballplayer and all that?
Look, I'm sor...
I had a nice time.
You wanna get
something to eat?
Is he coming?
Look at this. You're gonna
need some new shoes, huh?
Mm-hmm.
I'll take the dog out for you.
I'm gonna be late.
Almost forgot
about you, huh?
All right, let's...
Uh-oh.
Come on.
Fuck.
Sunny!
We'll go eat.
You know what you want?
Go ahead. Read it
and tell her what you want.
All right, we'll just have two
of the 2.99 breakfast specials.
That's scrambled?
Scrambled.
And coffee comes
with that, right? - Yeah.
Do you have your
players card? - Oh, yeah.
Got ya.
This is nice, huh?
Well, I'm gonna
call a car.
And they can take you to
Jenny's, if that's what you want.
Okay.
That'd be nice.
You get the day off.
Can I go get a pie?
They sell pie
at breakfast?
Well, I mean,
it's definitely a flood.
I know it's a flood,
but it's, you know,
not a natural one,
and that's...
Okay.
Okay. Yeah.
Well, you're probably fine,
but I'm here if you change your mind.
Mm-hmm.
There's no direct extension, but
anybody here can help you start a policy.
Yeah.
It's a call center.
Mm-hmm.
Hi. Sorry.
- Hold on a minute, will ya?
Max, um,
I was hoping that if... if, um,
Ted comes walking through here,
could you maybe
just tell him I'm around?
If I'm around, sure.
Actually, looks
like Ted needs you.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
They're gonna use the lot.
We can triple the investment.
Okay.
You wanted to see me?
We're getting a new
software package, okay?
Which means all of us are
gonna have to use the computers.
I'm just bringing everyone in in person
to see if there are any issues with that.
Yeah, that sounds great.
- All right.
So you got a big investment coming up?
- Yeah, what, on the phone?
You know the dirt lot
across the street?
They're gonna run
a gas line through it.
I know the guy
who's got the lease.
He doesn't know
anything about that.
We take over the lease,
we could triple it.
I always mean to invest.
You know,
you always hear about that.
"Invest for the future."
So...
You want in?
I mean, we could maybe
give you a share for... 2.000.
And I could triple it?
- That's what we're talking about.
But you gotta come in soon, by
the end of the week. We close on Friday.
Okay. I will.
Good. Give me your cell.
We'll work on the details later.
You know what? It's new, so I
can never remember the number.
Look it up on the phone.
- I don't have it with me.
It's at home. I don't like
to take personal calls at work.
Hey, give it to me later.
This will be good.
Yeah.
- Yeah. Shh.
Thought you
were going home.
Oh. Yeah.
I'm just waiting on a car.
How far are ya?
I can take ya.
Well, what about Ted?
I mean, don't you gotta work?
I'll take you, I'll come back.
Come on.
What's this?
Oh, uh,
that's just work.
You take pictures?
Portraits. Part-time,
at the mall.
That's really nice.
All right.
Maybe I can come in for a
minute and use the bathroom?
Um, yeah, you know,
Sunny is kind of shy.
Oh.
- Is that okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Sunny?
That's her name?
Uh, yeah.
Sunny.
Let me see.
I don't know.
I think these are narrow.
Here.
All right. What do you say?
We go with these, huh?
Hmm?
Come on. They got the little...
pink stripy guys on 'em.
What about Keds?
What's the difference,
Sunny, right?
If they had 'em here,
I'd get 'em.
I want what I had.
Well, we're here now,
and these are fine.
I still gotta get stuff for your party,
and I gotta get back to work.
Hi.
Go get your stuff.
I can charge these, right?
So which is it?
You're gonna
wear 'em or not?
All right, fine.
Fuck it.
One cheeseburger meal?
Yeah.
And a shake.
Just with a normal drink, like
a coke, and also a number three.
6.37.
What, are you...
What, are you... You're not hungry?
You don't wanna eat?
Are you gonna eat
the Happy Meal or what?
I'm gonna go get a shake.
You know what? No.
We're going.
Come here.
Take your food...
so you can eat it at home.
Here.
Can't look for shoes for you
all day and then have you throw a fit.
Hi. Can I have a car
at the Galleria Mall, please?
Yeah, how much
is that gonna be?
It's gonna be
a minute, so...
might as well eat.
Let's take the bus.
I'm not taking the bus.
- I can eat on the bus.
We're not taking
the fuckin' bus, Sunny,
so eat that or I'm
gonna take it away!
Come on.
It's too late to go back
to work now too.
All right,
I'll be back in a bit.
I can give you five dollars.
Yeah. Leave it
on the table there.
How's your girl?
Oh, she's good.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
She's growin'.
Sonny, right?
Uh-huh.
Like Sonny and Cher?
No, it's not a man's name.
It's... It's...
S-U-N-N...
It's like the sun,
you know?
Sunny.
You still dancing?
I never danced there.
Mom, these are too hard.
What?
Oh, God. Don't eat it.
It's okay.
It's not okay. It's not okay.
You gotta eat.
We can order pizza.
- Honey, we can't.
You want some soup?
Just microwave it,
and it'll become soft.
Let's see.
It's good.
It's hot. Be careful.
This isn't fair.
Look, I just
wanted to see, uh,
maybe what was going on
with the money, you know.
'Cause, um,
I got this investment
coming up.
No, it's with work.
You can come here.
Please. I never said that.
No, that is not true.
Yeah, well, you know what?
I'm not the one...
Why don't you stop
worrying about me?
Why don't you
stop worrying about me?
Yeah? Well, when?
Come on.
Yes!
I can't take you every day though.
You know that, right?
I know.
- Good.
Yeah, I liked
being a waitress.
It was great 'cause you got to eat.
You know?
Be no good for me.
I eat enough dog shit
as it is.
You like it?
- What, the job?
I love it.
It's the best.
But you know what?
Every month, this guy
gives me five bucks a pop...
for some names,
their socials, e-mails.
What's he do with them?
Mm-mm-mm.
It's 400 bucks though.
Jesus.
I could see if he needs
some more.
Huh? No.
Well, I can get you a deal
for your little girl.
If you want
some portraits of her.
It iher birthday tomorrow.
I gotta get back. Come by tonight.
I'm on till 9:00.
I'll try. Like... Like,
how much would that be?
Just come by.
So, how are we today, good?
Yeah.
That is quite a little blouse
you got there.
Oh, don't forget
about our little talk.
Hey, you mind if I ask...
Wha... You work
for a separate company, right?
What do they pay?
5.85.
Is that part-time only?
After 11:00 or mornings.
So, like, who would I talk to
if I wanted to, you know...
I used to...
Hey.
Mrs. Harwood?
Oh. Jerome.
Angela is fine.
- Sorry.
Harwood's her dad's name.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Next time if you, um...
You can't leave her here this long.
Yeah, no, sometimes,
she goes home with friends.
But, uh, you know, today I had the car,
so I-I... I told her to wait.
Do you have a minute?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
Uh, have you ever tested Sunny
for reading difficulties?
No.
No. I know.
I will. You know?
If you think that I should.
You know, we're not...
we're not always right.
And she's young,
and dyslexia is tricky.
But we just
recommend testing.
Okay.
That's something
the school does, right?
I often recommend
private consultation.
It's...
Well, it's better.
It's faster.
And, uh, you must know someone
who could help.
Why would I know someone?
Being a nurse.
All right, listen.
You know what?
I'll, uh... If you have a test or whatever,
I'll let her take it,
but I don't know anybody.
'Cause I'm not
a fuckin' nurse.
Sun, come on.
Well, I gotta get back to the mall and pick
up some shit for my big new nursing job.
I'll probably get some pretty nice pills
if I was a nurse.
I was thinking we'd go get
your picture taken.
You wanna do that?
That way we'll always see what you looked
like right before you turned eight.
Thank you.
Sorry about the mess.
So... this is Sunny, huh?
Hey there, cutie.
Just let me move this.
Okay.
You wanna have
a seat up here?
Up.
All right.
Ah, oh.
Ohh!
There we go.
Okay.
Like it?
Yeah.
Looks great.
You wanna get in there?
- Oh, no, it's okay.
It's not like I'm gonna
charge you, Angela.
Ah.
All right.
Do one, me and you?
Think of something
that makes you both happy.
You want one of just you?
- Oh, God, no. No.
Sunny, there's some,
uh, toys out there.
Do you wanna play outside
while we finish up?
You know, it's nice,
what you got... you two.
Yeah.
My sister tried
to adopt a girl.
Turned out it wasn't even
the agency's to give.
Louise paid $20.000 for her.
Jesus.
They still never
seen the kid.
It was all in China, so it was a
real mess. Finally just gave up.
I'm sorry.
So you like it here better?
You like taking pictures?
- Oh.
It is a dream come true.
Hey, Sunny's got
a birthday party tomorrow.
You... You should come by.
Of course, I still gotta
get stuff for it.
I could bring some coleslaw
or something.
Yeah.
Hey, Sun, you ready to go?
Come on.
Hey, you know,
my sister is visiting.
Uh, she's gonna come by
if you wanna meet her.
Oh, yeah, we should go.
It's late for her.
Uh, could I keep one
of the wallets?
I mean, I won't take one of
your copies. I'll make a copy.
No, I...
I don't need them all.
You ready to go?
Wanna say good-bye to Max?
Good-bye, Max.
Okay.
Thank you.
Listen. I gotta run a quick errand.
You wait here for me for a sec?
Can I have some gum?
- Honey, I don't have any gum.
Can I go buy some gum?
All right.
Here. But just gum, all right?
We meet back on this bench.
I don't wanna have to go looking
for you. So two minutes, okay?
Okay.
Can I help you?
- Uh, yeah.
What's, like, the cheapest I could
get in on a cell phone?
The pay-as-you-go phone
would be the least expensive.
This one.
Great.
Um, do I get my own number with this?
- Of course.
The phone plus the first
30 minutes is 59.99.
Thank you.
Hey.
Come on.
All right, go get in.
I gotta make a call.
You got a cell phone?
Can I get one?
You can see it in a minute.
Just go... go get in.
I know. Listen.
If you get me two grand,
I won't come after
any of it anymore, okay?
I told you already.
I'm gonna invest it.
Well, I don't got an account,
so you gotta wire it.
No, I'll pick it up.
Well, you can call her then.
All right?
But don't call this number though.
Call... Call us at home.
Are we headed
to the car wash?
Yeah.
It's got games on it!
- Yeah, just...
Don't...
I just got the thing.
You can play with it later,
all right?
It wouldn't have games on it if
you weren't supposed to play 'em.
Just don't break it, all right?
Mm-hmm.
All right, who has the ticket?
- Me!
All right, what's the number?
Four, seven, two...
Two... one, six...
one, six... 0.
0.
Enter.
Roll the window up.
Roll the window down.
Oh, here we go!
Here we go!
Spaghetti!
Look!
Here we go.
Here come your pinecones.
Whee!
Pinecones!
Here they come. Mixing bowl!
We're in the mixing bowl!
Rinse. Whoa!
All right, we're gonna get...
- Mom! Mom!
What? What?
Oh, we're leaking!
We're leaking!
Do it! Do it! Do it!
- I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna do it.
Oh, no, no, no!
Don't shut it off!
Don't shut it off.
It's wet.
No.
Crap.
Come on.
Damn it.
It's fine. It's fine.
It's not gonna start.
I'll just come back
and get it.
At least it's clean, right?
- I guess.
Sunny, go on up ahead.
I gotta make another call.
Uh, yeah. No, I have done
a little, um...
House Helpers.
Tonight?
Um, I mean, doesn't somebody gotta,
like, show me around or something first?
Uh... Yeah, no...
No, I can meet her.
No, I actually know
that building. Um...
Yeah, no, I know it.
It's where...
I know it.
Okay. Thanks.
Who was that?
Nobody.
Let's take the bus.
Sunny.
- It'll be quick.
You wanna take the bus
the rest of the way?
One way.
Hey, Cheryl.
Does your kid still
do any babysitting?
I'll go check.
You need a sitter?
Oh, I was looking
for your sister.
She moved out.
Oh, okay. I didn't know that.
I'll watch your kid. I've watched
my cousins. So, you know...
I think I gotta find a girl.
- Really, I can do it.
Just if Sunny wanted
to get at you, and she said...
You know, I don't know.
Just... You're a boy.
I don't think it's
gonna work out. I'm sorry.
Get under the covers?
Good.
All right.
Good night, sweetheart.
Hi. I need a cab at the corner
of Trop and Eastern.
Listen, can you stop by the
check-cashing place up on Trop...
and just give me a minute?
It's 24 hours.
I'll be right out.
Hi. I'm-I'm picking up
a wire. Jerome.
You would like that
in money order?
No, cash. Thanks.
Wait. That's supposed
to be 2.000. right?
The service fee was $153.
He didn't pay that
when he sent it?
Do you do, uh...
You do payday loans?
Do you have an account?
- No.
Credit card?
- Yeah.
Just give me your card number
and you can apply.
For how much?
Um...
I could get 200?
It's 25 per hundred.
Okay.
- Wait one moment.
Thank you for waiting.
I appreciate it.
Oh, God.
My girl.
I had a bad dream.
It's okay, sweetie.
Just go back to bed, okay?
Just think of some
nice things, okay?
Tomorrow's your birthday.
Can I sleep with you?
Oh, Sunny, please, I got
to go to work tomorrow.
Is someone with you?
Just go think of some nice things,
sweetheart.
Balloons.
Hey, thank you
for coming out so early.
It's my kid's birthday, so I'm
trying to get the car back for it.
Is this a Triple "A" call?
Yeah, yeah. It's my ex-husband's
card though.
What's wrong?
Well, they ran it through the wash,
and they turned it off.
And the thing don't start up
when it gets wet, so...
Can you pop the hood?
- Yeah.
All right.
Thank you. Here, can I...
can I give you something?
No, no.
It's all right.
Thank you.
Do you want the card?
- No. Don't worry about it.
Hey, happy birthday, baby!
You got the car back!
- Yeah.
You wanna stay home today,
help me get ready for your party?
Really?
- Yeah. Why not?
It's once a year.
Jesus.
I'll take it off with you.
Okay.
- Okay.
Just remind me to call in sick.
Go get your coat.
Hurry up!
- I'm hurrying.
Baby, don't get...
Don't get crayons
in little packs like that.
I was gonna give them out.
- I know, but I can just get a big box.
Put it back.
What's this?
- Coconut cups.
Sweetie, we've got cups.
- Not coconut cups.
I know.
It's junkie.
You can put it back.
They have a balloon machine where
you can make your own balloons.
Yeah?
Oh, yeah.
It's cool.
Yeah, but I don't think
we need that.
Why don't you get some regular
balloons and, um, party hats?
Did you get party hats yet?
- No.
You gotta get your party hats, and then...
and then, uh, we gotta go.
Okay, that'll be 42.30, please.
It's gonna be a great party.
- Mm-hmm.
You're gonna see.
Whew!
Sunny, he wants
to talk to you.
It's for your birthday.
Hello.
I stayed home today.
We're having a party.
Eight.
Mm-hmm.
Okay. Bye.
I love you too.
Here they all are.
Hi.
- Hey!
Hi, you two. Come on in. Come on in.
Thank you for coming.
Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
Hi.
Hi. Ooh! Presents.
Yeah, put 'em there.
That's good.
Uh...
Come on.
Let's go outside.
Hello.
- Hi.
I'm Louise.
- Michael.
Michael. Nice to meet you.
My husband Adam.
How you doing?
- Hi.
Hey there.
- Hey.
Pics.
Great.
I wanted to introduce you
to someone.
Who?
- My sister and her husband.
They're in town from Toronto,
and I wanted to bring 'em over.
This is, uh, Louise.
Oh.
Hi.
- And her husband, Adam.
Yeah, I love the decorations.
Do you guys need a drink?
No, I'm good.
Okay. You sure you don't...
- No, I'm good.
Yeah. Excuse me. Thanks.
Blow out the candle.
Yeah!
Did you make a wish?
That's for you.
You want cake? Wait. She gets the
first piece. Sorry. I screwed up.
Hey, you need
some help with that?
I'll show you something.
You put it like this and pop
your fist over on top of it.
Ooh.
There you go.
That's not good
for our counter, okay?
Oh. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Say "thank you", sweetheart.
Thank you.
I'm gonna get a beer.
You want one?
Uh, yeah. Sure.
You okay?
- Yeah.
Oh, uh, Max, this is my neighbor,
Michael, from upstairs.
Hi.
How old are you, Michael?
- Sixteen.
I said
he could drink.
You, uh, drive around in one
of those big black S.U.V.s?
I don't got a car.
Time.
There's the silent "E."
"There... were...
four lit-tle rab-bits...
That's right.
in... their"...
- Their.
Sunny, you having fun?
Who gave you that?
- Louise.
It was nothing.
Yeah, it's a nice book.
She really...
She's eight now, right?
I think she could
use a tutor.
Hey, Sunny, you wanna come in?
There's one more present for you.
Sunny is really wonderful.
I'm happy to watch her for
an afternoon if you need it.
Sure.
Maybe even tomorrow
if you'd like.
I mean, we're only here
for another day or two.
And, uh...
You know, I could...
I could do more
reading exercises with her.
Yeah, she usually goes to this after-school
thing until I get off work.
Well, I could pick her up,
or we could do it here.
I mean, we're staying
at a hotel...
You don't have
to pick her up.
I can't pay you.
Oh. No.
God, I wouldn't...
You wanna do that? Sun?
You wanna meet Louise
to do some reading?
Sure.
You have a nice birthday, Sunny?
Uh-huh.
A lot of work for me,
you know.
Make sure these gifts
get put away, yeah?
Hey, Sunny,
come here a second.
Come here a second.
What's this say?
"Go...
- Yeah?
into...
Don't... Don't go into...
Mr. Membredin"...
That's okay.
That's good.
Here. Just make sure
it goes inside, okay?
Hey.
Come here.
I take you for granted.
Hey.
Sunny, wake up.
Wake up.
Hey. Sunny.
Where's my white bag?
Huh?
- My white purse, honey!
Where is it? This is
really fucking important!
Were you kids
playing around with it?
Sunny, get up and help me find it!
Get up!
Okay.
Get up. Are you up?
Are you helping?
Are you looking?
Will you please look?
Yeah, I think some...
I've been robbed.
Yeah. $2.000
and the bag that it was in.
Cash.
Okay.
That's right.
Yes. 1367 Sombrero.
Okay. Well, when?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Are you sure you didn't see it?
- No.
Seen anybody with it?
I didn't fucking
call into work!
Sunny, damn it! You were
supposed to remind me!
Here. Watch some TV
until they get here.
Okay.
Try and think
if you've seen it.
Shit!
All right.
All right, all right, all right.
I was gonna
invest it tomorrow.
It was going
to the office tomorrow.
It was gonna be one day.
Did you see anyone with it?
- No, I would've told you.
Do you have insurance?
No.
That your daughter?
Yeah. Sunny.
Sun.
Did you see anyone
with your mother's purse?
Tell him if you saw it!
I had a lot of money in there, Sunny.
I didn't see it.
- Well, somebody must've fucking taken it, huh?
I'm gonna lose it on you if you fucking don't tell me!
- Please. Ma'am.
Uh, I don't have the time for this
right now. I gotta go to work.
You work at night?
- It's a new thing.
It's not all night.
Is someone else in the house?
What do you mean?
Is there someone else here to
watch her while you're away?
Yeah, somebody's comin'.
When?
I had a sitter, and I just
put her to bed, all right?
She's fine. She's...
It's a couple nights a week,
all right? We got a big dog.
See, I can't leave here knowing you'll
be gone. It's endangerment.
Look, we can take her.
We can take her.
There's a children's room
down there.
I'm not supposed to, but...
You can come pick her up
when you're finished.
She's not gonna get any...
She's not gonna get any sleep.
Sunny. Hey.
Sunny, come on.
Wake up, sweetie. You gotta go with
these guys for a few minutes.
Okay?
- Why?
Cause', um...
Come on. Sit up.
'Cause I gotta go out, and you
can't be here on your own.
Let me see... see your foot.
Okay?
I've, uh... I know.
- The tongue's wrong.
Okay. I'll fix it.
Here, take your blanket.
Let's put your coat on.
Okay.
Go with this officer.
Thank you.
You're here kind of early.
Hi.
Uh, you're here early.
I know. I was, um, just trying
something out.
I was looking for something
part-time. Um...
We missed you yesterday. You're staying home
from work, but you're coming in for this?
I know. I meant to call.
It was my kid...
You should get home.
I know. I'm... I'm
about to go home soon.
See you soon.
- Yeah.
Hey, Sun.
Where did you go?
I was just trying
something out.
It was really bright
in there.
Well, we're both
gonna sleep soon.
I know your father's
not around, and...
I know you'll never
get that back.
But I'm just me, and, uh...
Good morning.
How's the new
program coming?
It's really a lot easier for me
to just use the big book.
Yeah.
Well, we all gotta be on board
on this one, okay? Right?
Yeah.
Did you, uh... Did you manage
to get enough sleep?
Yeah. Yeah, thanks.
Um, listen.
You know, today's the day
that... uh...
Right.
Listen. I, um...
I had it wired to me,
so I could get you cash.
It doesn't have to
be cash, Angela. No.
Well, my kid had a party,
and there were a lot of new people
at the house, and, uh...
I... Somebody...
I don't know.
We can't find it.
And, uh, somebody must've stole it.
- You don't have it?
Well, I'm still trying
somethin' else.
Why didn't you
tell me this sooner?
I had it.
You know, let's meet
in my office in an hour.
Don't... Don't you have
other people?
Come to my office
in an hour.
Everything all right?
- Did you see my white bag at Sunny's birthday party?
No.
- It had all my back child support in it.
It's gone.
- You should call the police.
I called the fuckin' police.
They can't do anything.
What about that kid upstairs?
- What about him?
I'm sorry, Angela.
God.
Listen, um, Louise really
enjoyed meeting you.
Uh... Thanks for letting her teach
some today. She misses it.
She fell
for your little girl.
Maybe they could, uh...
Maybe Sunny could
visit 'em sometime.
Looks like Ted
wants to see you.
Fine.
Thanks.
I thought you said an hour.
You know what? In the end,
it is just completely inappropriate...
that you're cleaning up this place while
you are an employee of the company.
I was just trying somethin' out.
I don't...
I probably...
I don't have to do that.
It's like
a couple nights a week.
Don't you think you should get
something that pays better?
A little more steady, so you're not
spread so thin? Especially with your kid.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
I mean, we all have to be
with this program right now.
This is a custom database, and it just isn't
gonna work if we're not all doing our part.
Yeah.
So, with you cleaning up while
you're working, it's just all too...
You know.
Yeah.
So look, just, you know,
finish up your calls today.
You can leave early
if you want to.
And, um, take this.
Like a severance.
Hello?
Max?
I gave you this number?
No. No, I'm not coming in.
That's it.
It's 'cause that's the end
of my time there.
Uh, 'cause, uh...
Yeah, I don't know why.
Yeah?
Like what?
No. No, I don't wanna meet
Louise for dinner, no.
They... They have a good time?
Did... Did Louise have a nice time
today with Sunny?
'Cause I haven't
been home yet.
You can drive, right?
- Mmm.
You didn't see my white bag
at Sunny's party, did you?
No.
All right, listen. Wanna
make a hundred bucks?
All I want you to do
is take my car out of town.
Just stick it someplace.
- Where?
Lake Mead, maybe.
Just hide it.
Do you wanna
do it or not?
Your car that tan LeSabre?
- Yeah.
You gotta pay me now
though.
All right.
Here.
You can't tell anybody about this,
and you gotta keep it clean...
because I'm gonna report it and I'm
gonna get some insurance out of this.
Whoa, whoa. I'm not gonna steal
your car, Angela.
I don't want you to steal it. I want you
to take it and stick it somewhere.
What if you report it
and I'm still driving it?
Well, I don't know, you know? I'll wait
for you, you know? You could call me.
Nah, nah.
Fuck it.
It's too late now anyway.
What the fuck
is this now?
We didn't feed Casey.
- You didn't feed him, you mean.
You didn't feed Casey!
So what'd you guys do?
Couldn't clean all this up?
It just happened.
We can't keep this dog
like this.
Are you gonna help out
or what?
Oh, God.
What happened?
Uh... Shut it, Case.
Jesus.
The dog just got
to the couch.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's terrible.
Hello again, Sunny.
- Hi, Louise.
Can I... What?
- Hi.
Um... Oh, um, Sunny and I
had a wonderful afternoon.
And I just wanted
to make sure that...
Um...
C-Can we talk outside?
I... I would love to
see you two again,
and I... I wanted
to make sure...
that you were
planning to visit.
I mean, I'm inviting you
to visit.
It-It would be like
a long vacation.
Um, I have an extra room,
and I know a wonderful
children's therapist.
I, myself,
was a schoolteacher,
and...
Sunny needs something more
than she's getting.
Uh, okay. I mean, Max knows
where you guys are,
so, uh, I'll talk to him
about it later.
Well, if you tell me when,
I could send tickets.
Okay.
I'll talk to Max.
And I gotta see what kind
of vacation time I got.
It's hard for me
to get away from work.
Well, maybe just Sunny then.
And you could come visit later.
I could enroll her in this great intensive
children's program for reading.
She's getting better.
And it's really far
for her, you know?
Yeah, but...
- Okay. I can't talk right now.
There's been a robbery
or somethin' here.
And I mean...
Thank you for watching
her today. Thank you.
I appreciate it. I really enjoyed
meeting you and your husband.
You seem like nice people.
All right?
Thank you.
Sunny.
Turn that off.
Honey?
Go get Casey's leash
and get your shoes on.
Yo!
200.
Go put Casey
in the car.
I still need the car.
- When you get back.
Look, the best thing you can do
is just forget I ever asked.
You're a good kid.
Where are we going?
Just give me a minute, okay?
Come on.
Go take him out, sweetie.
Go ahead. Just go and take
him out and tell him to sit,
and then come back inside.
Honey, look. We're gonna let
Casey go to a new home.
Where?
I don't know where,
but somebody will take him.
Okay?
We can't.
I know you don't understand right now,
but you will.
All right, listen.
I know it's hard
right now.
But...
It's just hard
right now.
That's all.
So are you gonna
help me or what?
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come here.
Listen, Casey, sit.
Come on. Come here.
Come here, buddy.
Come here. Sit. Sit.
Sit, buddy. Come on.
You're a good dog.
Sunny?
- Casey!
Sunny, shut the door!
- Casey, come here!
Sunny! Close the door.
- Casey!
Sunny, shut the goddamn door!
He's gonna be okay.
I need some help too!
We're gonna meet Max for some Chinese
food. Won't that be good? Huh?
He's gonna treat us, so you can get
whatever you want.
Do you wanna go eat?
Come on.
Hmm?
All right. You can stay in the car
alone if that's what you want.
Hmm.
Hey, you two.
- Hey.
I hope it's okay. I ordered you
something. I didn't know.
I wasn't sure.
- Yeah, yeah. No, that's fine.
That's good. Here.
What is this? Chicken?
Come here, honey.
Make yourself a plate.
Fuckin' believe this?
What the hell happened?
Were you sleeping with him?
No. No.
It was the money.
I had...
It's not important.
You want me to talk to him?
- And say what?
I lost my other job.
You know, Louise and Adam
are going back tomorrow.
I mean, she refused to leave
before I talked to you.
Yeah, yeah.
I've seen her.
We talked already.
No, they, uh... they wanna
give you some money.
Some real money.
Can we, um...
Can we talk for a second,
you and me?
Hey. Hey, Sunny.
You wanna go check out
the desserts for a minute?
Okay?
Please?
It's their adoption money,
Angela.
There's $20.000.
and it's yours.
They wanna help Sunny.
What?
No, I mean...
I don't believe it. I mean, uh...
That would really help.
Um... What, do they just have
a lot of money or something?
They wanna help her
as a family.
They wanna help her with who they know,
where they are.
Where are they?
I mean, you'd still be able
to see her and everything.
But they'd wanna
take care of her,
and you're just...
you're just you.
Now, without a job and...
What?
- She wanted me to really talk to you about this.
See if we could
work something out.
It'd have to be clear-cut.
They can't go through
another mess.
That's crazy.
Hey, Sunny?
Sunny, come on back, honey.
It's okay.
Think about it.
You know what?
I'm not gonna think about it.
It's not even legal.
What's legal?
You're gonna pay
for all this, right?
I don't think
you can smoke in here.
I could give a shit.
Call me.
- Jesus.
I'll call you.
- Sweetheart, come on. We gotta go.
I didn't even eat anything!
Louise is a nice person.
All right?
I'm just trying
to help you both.
Hey, can we get a, uh... a to-go
thingy over here, please?
Come on.
Would you be careful,
please!
Didn't we get
you shoes already?
You're gonna kill
yourself in these.
Do you know a place?
- They're all closed.
They're not all closed!
All right, here.
Here's a nice place.
We're gonna get you
some things here.
Hey, honey, you want
a little tiger toy?
You need undies?
Hmm?
All right. What about the sneakers?
- They don't have any.
What are you talking about?
They got big bins back here. - Not kids.
Excuse me. Do you have any sneakers?
Kids' sneakers?
S. Aqu.
Yeah, no, I saw. But I only saw
slippers and like big men's shoes.
I need kids' sneakers,
for a little girl.
No se.
No, you don't know
or no, you don't have any?
Lo siento.
Her goddamn shoes
are falling off her feet.
You want her
to go barefoot?
Can you try a little bit harder
maybe with some fucking English!
I'm sorry.
What do you wanna do?
I wanna go find Casey.
Honey, I don't even know
where to look.
I... think
it was somewhere here.
Casey!
Come here, boy!
He'll be better off, okay?
Sunny.
Come on.
Casey!
- Get in the car right now.
Or I'm gonna leave
without you. Come on.
Here, honey.
Will you go in and get like a travel
toothbrush or something?
For me, or for you?
Uh, why don't you
get us both one, okay?
I got some toothpaste too.
Good.
You know,
Louise likes you a lot.
Just even after
meeting you a few times.
She knows about how your dad's
not really around...
and how...
you need school help.
She's nice.
She is nice.
How would you feel about letting
them help you out for a little while?
Up where they live.
For me.
Okay.
Sunny. You stay in the car
a sec, okay?
Can I play
on the phone?
Uh, I need the phone
for a minute,
but you can play
with it after.
Hey.
Um,
why don't we talk more
about, uh,
helping her?
Yeah, I mean,
she said she would,
but she doesn't know
what it means.
It's not Canadian
money, is it?
No, I don't care if they come.
I just don't want to see them.
I don't know.
I'm not going home.
That's for sure.
Look, I'll go to a motel
and I'll call you.
Back in a second, okay?
Hey, baby,
we got a room.
You wanna...
You wanna go on up?
I'll meet you up there
in a second? Okay?
Here. It's Room 220.
Give me the phone back, okay?
Yeah, I'm at the Ponderosa.
It's past Decatur.
It's Room 220.
You gotta give me
some time though.
I don't know. Um...
You know what?
Just... Just come.
What's this, a movie?
Did you press something we're
gonna have to pay extra for?
No. Geez!
Why don't you
go wash your face?
Why?
Just go wash up a little
while we're here, you know?
He's out.
It's pretty late, Anna.
He'll be here in a minute.
- Will he?
Yes, he will.
Where's Louise and them?
- You said you didn't want to see her.
I know, but where are they?
- They're in the car.
You want me to come in?
No.
They give you the money?
Yeah.
You gettin' something
out of all this?
Listen, I'm not doing it here.
- Wait a minute. You said...
You said to meet here.
- I know, but I can't do it here.
I'm...
All right. I'm gonna go get Sunny,
and you guys...
you guys just pull up.
Pull up to the side up a ways.
And you follow me, yeah?
How do I know
you won't just take off?
I won't.
Whatever you want.
Come on, baby.
They're here. Let's go.
Sunny, come on.
Get your coat.
Let's go.
Hey.
Here.
So,
listen, they, uh...
Louise is gonna take you up
to Canada for a while.
And...
that's where you'll be taught
better and everything.
I've never been, so, uh...
What about my clothes?
They're gonna have
new things for you.
Toys.
Books and...
A little vacation.
You know?
Come on.
Come outta the car, okay?
Let's go see Max.
Hey there, cutie.
She'll be okay.
Help me out a little, huh?
I'm gonna see you soon.
I'll come up and see how
you're getting on up there.
You can call me whenever
you want. Okay?
Here.
I'll give you the phone,
like you wanted.
You want that?
Go on with Max.
Go ahead with Max.
Don't be difficult, Sunny.
Louise is with him.
You guys drivin' up?
I don't know.
Doesn't she need papers
or somethin'?
They got all that.
All right.
Huh?
Go on ahead, okay?
I'll see you soon!
Hey.
Think of me.
Shit.
It's, uh... It's fine.
I'll, uh... I'll get it goin'.
It just needs a minute.
I can call someone.
I'll get it started.
Just go.
Okay.
Come on.
The car got wet.
It got wet.
It won't start.
Oh, God, come here.
Come here.
I can take a look
at the car.
It just needs a minute.
Just go.
I have to tell Louise...
- Just go!