www.subscene.com
Some believe that Eve
was the first woman... -
born of The Garden of Eden-
Others believe
there was another... -
created flawed, imperfect... -
from a substance most vile-
Her name is Lilith-
She believed she was
Adam's equal-
Would not lie beneath him-
For this, she was cast out-
Cursed for eternity... -
she became something else... -
Her killings were relentless-
The Faith was formed... -
to end Lilith's wrath-
Each of you is part
of that same Order.
Together, we will
fight Lilith... -
and all her kind-
- Prefect?
- Yes, Chapel?
Why does God allow
such evil to exist?
You ask an eternal
question.
One that will follow you
throughout your life.
But one thing is certain...
the mysteries of this world...
will be solved in the next.
While we live here...
we must put our faith
in the Creator's plan.
So, Prefect... -
the Creator planned
what happened to my parents?
One day
you will not question... -
why your parents
were taken from this world.
You must find meaning in
what has happened to you.
You must grow, evolve...
and overcome.
Every life has a purpose
and a plan-
The Faith has fought Lilith
and her brethren for centuries-
But one day... -
one day, we will stop her-
No! Wait!
Put the restraints on her!
Now!
You have succeeded.
Not until I've watched
her draw her last breath.
She will not die today.
I forbid it!
Prefect, I thought our duty
was to end her wrath.
- And we have!
- The Faith exists to eliminate her!
She has to pay
for the lives she's taken.
- We're not killers, Shaw.
- This is wrong!
My decision is final.
The matter is closed!
The Raeborne Team received... -
the "Starker Prize" for pioneering
research that extends human life-
Former member, Anders Raeborne
was expelled in a major scandal... -
for testing dangerous substances
on humans-
Son of team leader
Cyrus Raeborne... -
Anders has not been heard from
in over a year-
His whereabouts are unknown-
Lies.
Silence!
It's pure.
No one believed that I could
accomplish this, except you.
This time, there are no
side-effects.
It's flawless.
I tested it myself.
Do it!
We've conquered
the valley of death.
Immortality.
Put it to the test.
Again.
Still alive.
True immortality
wears a different face, Anders.
You're more than human.
You're a Demonicos.
Your destiny awaits.
I'll be watching.
Now, go.
Go, go!
I've located agent Geresh.
He had this.
Prefect, an Agent has been murdered.
Our security breached.
Someone is tampering
with Darklight.
The prophecy has begun.
Maltheus 6: "And the Demonicos...
shall carry a Red Plague...
sweeping the earth...
smiting mankind."
Then we only have a few days
before it's too late.
Her time has come.
Elle-
"Each mark carries the curse... -
that the bearer shall suffer
for all of eternity-"
- I smell trouble.
- What?
I'm just bringing you flowers.
There's no trouble in that,
is there?
With you, Elle,
I never can tell.
Are you all right?
Abe, what do you know
about biblical curses?
Not a darn thing-
Why? -
There's something called "The marks
of Daggoth". I read about it.
Elle, why do you do this
to yourself?
It's been three years since
I took you off the streets...
- a vagrant.
- And I'm grateful for it.
Elle, listen to me.
You need to focus on...
building a new life,
here and now.
Now you got a new job.
What about that?
You call working
at a flower shop a job?
I call it a start.
I have to find out who I am.
Elle, you may not want
to know everything.
You've got a clean slate...
something most people
just dream about.
Use it!
It's not so easy.
Yeah... I'm trying
to figure it out.
Let us now,
pray for this child... -
who is to receive the sacrament
of new birth-
Deliver him, oh Lord... -
Open his heart
to Your grace... -
- This is Shaw.
- Shaw, I need your help-
The Faith is in trouble-
We need to meet-
- Marcus, slow down. What's wrong?
- Someone has committed sabotage.
- You're the only one I can trust.
- Right, Marcus. Where are you?
Loading Dock 44. The Toschko Plant.
Do you know where that is?
Yes, I know where that is.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
- Is there some place we can talk?
- I don't think it's a good idea.
Jenn, please,
just give me a chance.
It's Conner's fourteenth
birthday.
I know. Will, why did you come
today?
Our marriage is over.
You still haven't moved on.
Conner is gone.
I didn't come for the lecture.
I just came to give you this.
It's for your newborn.
Congratulations!
Will?
I really have to go.
Marcus!
- Marcus!
- Shaw.
Who did this to you?
Marcus?
I'm open! I'm open!
Are you all right?
I swear I couldn't stop!
Don't worry about it.
I'm fine.
Dr. Hardwick is one of the four
Raeborne Team members...
who have revolutionized our
understanding of human mortality.
We're pleased to have you
on this broadcast.
Thank you.
Tell me, where does
your Team's discovery take us?
Can we extend
the human life span...
to 150 years?
Oh Jerry...
we're a long way
from an advance like that.
We've simply provided
a road map to...
See? This is what happens
when you cut the budget, Ray!
I'm terribly sorry!
Are you ok?
Yeah.
It's just a rash.
It's nothing.
All medical units
be advised... -
there are unconfirmed reports
of a highly contagious virus-
Patients with rash like symptoms
should be immediately taken... -
to the nearest King's Point
Care Center-
Marcus is dead.
- Murdered.
- I promise there'll be retribution.
But there's something
more pressing.
A Demonicos is loose.
And it's carrying
the Red Plague.
So, we'll handle it like
we handled other one.
The Talis won't work.
It's immune.
Go to King's Point, William.
Contact Lilith. Train her.
- You're not serious!
- She's the only weapon we have.
What you're asking
is something I can't do.
Can't or won't?
Is this really wise, Prefect?
See to it.
Why is she still alive?
Who are we to question why?
If only you had killed her
when you had the chance.
- Come in.
- Thank you.
I need to speak with her right away.
Is she here?
She's gone.
She fled again.
I don't know where she went.
You might try Abel Gardens.
She goes there often.
Makes sense, because it was us
who placed her there.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Be careful.
She's confused.
Going through changes.
I'm not sure
what she's capable of.
You need practice.
I'm not interest in company
or conversation...
- in case you didn't notice it.
- Just a moment of your time.
Do you know why you have
those marks on your arm?
You don't remember anything before
you woke up here three years ago.
It's public record. If you're
trying to scare me, don't bother.
It's public record
because we staged it that way.
Have you ever heard
the name "Lilith"?
An old legend
from the Garden of Eden.
She was Adam's first wife.
An immortal.
She was cursed and became
a demon out for revenge.
- What's that got to do with me?
- The legend is true.
Lilith curse is known...
by the five Marks of Daggoth...
on her wrist.
Everything you know
about yourself is false.
You took the name "Elle"
because it was the only letter...
that you could remember
from your real name.
You have no memory...
because you have
this substance...
inside you.
It's blocking out
the past.
Why would I believe you?
I don't even know who you are.
My name is William Shaw.
I work for an organization.
It's called The Faith.
And I need your help.
I know all of this sounds crazy...
but there's something out there
called the Demonicos...
and in a few days,
all that you care about...
will become meaningless.
And you're the only one
that can stop it.
I think you've got
the wrong girl, William.
I'm not going to go out there
and fight some evil.
I can't even hold down
a minimum wage job.
I've got real problems.
You can't run away from this.
It will catch up with you.
I know that mind of yours
is still functional, Anders.
So I'm certain you'll grasp the
importance of what I'll tell you.
The one person out there
who can kill you, Lilith...
is now hunting you.
I suggest you strike first.
Abe?
Run!
Things got a nasty bite.
- Am I dying?
- Not yet.
This will neutralize the Talis
in your bloodstream.
Accelerate your ability
to heal.
Now, just rest. Save your strength.
We've got some catching up to do.
Here.
What did you shoot into me?
I removed the Talis that's been
clogging your body.
This is what it looks like
in solid form.
It's bark from a tree.
Dates back to the Garden of Eden.
Here.
Abe was one of us-
He believe in your potential-
- What do you want me to do?
- Prove him right.
You have extraordinary gifts.
You can either use them
to help...
or watch everyone around you dead.
It's your choice.
Show me what I'd have to do.
In order to use it, you have to
understand the source of your power.
It's called "Darklight".
An energy as old as the universe.
It's what you're made of.
It's what makes you unique.
It's the reason why
your wounds always heal.
And it makes you damn
near invincible.
You're going to go through physical
changes. Not all of them pleasant.
You'd better prepare yourself.
You're not hurt.
Now focus.
Your instincts will take over.
Ok.
So, other than Talis,
nothing can hurt me.
Exactly.
Next lesson.
Sometimes there's
nowhere to run.
You have to read the situation
and improvise.
I warned you.
- You like it down there?
- Not bad.
But don't get overconfident.
Now, let's go.
We have our first appointment.
We're here to see
Dr. Katherine Hardwick's body.
The director is out sick,
like the rest of the staff.
- Can you come back tomorrow?
- No, that won't do.
We have to see her right now.
Ok. Follow me.
Here she is.
We should get the first
test results back tonight.
No, no!
Don't touch it!
Where are the others?
- We need to go-
- If it's this contagious...
everybody who has touched
these bodies, could be infected.
- They could be spreading it by now.
- You catch on quick.
How bad is this thing?
Heard of the Black Plague?
The Middle Ages?
Think of something
a hundred times worse-
- What is it?
- I have to stop-
What's wrong with your hand?
Will, are you ok?
It happens sometimes.
I can't control it.
How long have you had it?
Since my son died.
- I'm sorry. I didn't know.
- I don't want to talk about it.
I have news.
Shaw has begun his work
with Lilith.
But the Red Plague...
is spreading.
Please, sit.
This is difficult for me...
but it's time
you know the truth.
There has always been a link
between you and Lilith.
The day your parents died
was a Faith mission...
gone terribly wrong.
We didn't know that a boy
had survived the fight...
and managed to find us.
It was our pursuit of Lilith, that
caused the death of your parents.
By not telling you the truth
until now...
I was trying to protect you.
I did know...
even though you never told me.
But you did teach me
about the human spirit...
and how it can overcome
the greatest of the tragedies.
I have learned not to question
why things happen.
Through faith...
and prayer...
I have found strength.
More strength
than you can imagine-
Today I am proud to announce...
the formation of
Raeborne Life Industries.
A private entity
established to turn...
the Raeborne Team's research...
into new antiaging drugs.
The revolution in
extending human life...
is just beginning.
I'm certain the late
Dr. Hardwick...
would want us to continue
this pioneering work.
Now I'd like to present
this short video.
The Fountain of Youth:
Does it exist?
The Raeborne Team
has made discoveries... -
that one day, will lead us
to the well-spring of eternal life-
Attention, all units- Wild animal
loose at the Jasmin Hotel-
Numerous casualties
are reported-
- All units respond-
- Game time!
Move, move, move!
Let's go! Let's go!
Where is everybody?
Let's go!
Stay with me.
I don't understand.
Why come here?
What's so special about
Raeborne Life Industries?
Quiet. It's here.
Now remember, your Darklight
is the only thing that can kill it.
- Get in close to be effective.
- What if it gets me first?
Focus. Just trust
in the training.
Now, you head up top.
I'll stay here...
and draw it out.
Get up!
Wait!
- Or he dies.
- What do you want?
Why do you fight me?
This Shaw, he wants to kill you.
He used Talis against you.
He hates you with all his will.
You and I are of the same blood.
I'm not like you.
So many innocents were killed...
by your hand.
- You didn't tell me.
- Elle...
No, my name is not Elle.
It's Lilith, remember?
You put that thing in my neck.
You tried to kill me, didn't you?
That's right.
Because you murdered my son.
- I don't remember your son.
- That makes one of us.
Let's just do this.
End it now.
I don't want to kill you.
I just want answers.
Ok?
Let's go.
There will be no turning back-
These samples could be enough
to create a vaccine for us.
I take it you received the book.
- That was from you?
- Yes.
Are you now ready
to reclaim the past?
Yeah.
Follow me.
Am I responsible
for all of this?
Yes.
The world was created
from love and hope.
Qualities which are
Divinely Ordained.
Each of us has them,
except you-
You rejected paradise-
You were cast out-
You could never die-
Darklight
raged inside of you-
Your pain was all consuming-
This organization was formed
to stop the evil you spread-
Talis brought you down-
You were on the edge of death-
The prefect made sure
that you were kept alive-
We placed you
in Abel Gardens... -
knowing you would be
labeled as a transient-
When you awoke
you remembered nothing-
Abe was instructed... -
to monitor your attempt
at a normal life-
As Elle, you may have convinced
the others...
of your compassion
and your humanity.
But I still know that you are
an abomination.
And you'll continue to kill.
I suggest you do
the right thing.
It's made from Talis.
My gift to you.
Anders?
My lord, I need to get you
to a hospital.
No. No hospital.
That's why I came to you.
The reason Lilith lives... -
is because of the prophecy among
the most sacred of our texts...
detailing her future role
as our protector-
What happened to Conner
couldn't have been Ordained.
I don't accept that. I won't.
And yet the prophecy exists.
You must resolve this conflict
in your own mind.
Each of us has the task
of not succumbing to the abyss.
- Don't.
- I killed your son in cold blood.
I'm cursed. I don't know
when I'm going to stop killing.
- I might not, unless...
- Unless you choose not to.
There were five marks on your arm.
Now there are four.
Curses can be lifted, Lilith.
Even yours.
But I killed your son.
How can you let me live?
Because doing this
won't bring Conner back.
What if I won't be able
to control my urges? What then?
That will be
my responsibility.
Give me the knife.
Come on.
Let's go.
We could not
create a vaccine...
from the specimens
that agent Shaw retrieved.
We were able to construct
this model...
from the Demonicos' DNA.
As you can see,
the brain is highly developed-
This node generates the virus.
We believe that a vaccine
can be created...
but it requires fluid
from this portion of the brain.
- But you need the entire head-
- Exactly.
There are two ways
in which the virus spread.
The first is from
the Demonicos' bite.
The virus is injected through
the tongue into the bloodstream.
Without a cure, it dissolves flesh
in a matter of hours...
resulting in death.
The second is through contact
with an infected individual.
Like acid, it burns through
clothing and flesh.
But, if you can isolate
the infected area...
you can stop its spread.
Contamination is rising.
The death total is 93.
Within hours,
numerous cities will be at risk.
The Red Plague is beginning.
It's out there, Leo.
And it's coming for you.
Each one of the Raeborne Team.
Father should have never
kicked me out.
But the three of you...
conspired against me...
putting him up to it.
The Starker Award
belongs to me.
You parade around with your...
trappings of success,
but you're frauds.
You never revolutionized science.
I did.
I discovered immortality.
You want proof?
What have you done to yourself?
I've made fools of you all.
This area is
under martial law-
You're quarantined until you prove
your identity and your health-
Get out of the car. Now.
Please remain calm-
You will be arrested,
if you leave the premises-
Any citizen,
showing signs of infection... -
will be taken
to a stage two facility-
You can't keep us here.
Everyone must remain calm-
You won't survive without
another injection of Darklight.
You did this. The virus was never
part of our agreement.
You were the one who tampered
with Lilith strain.
The virus is a side-effect
of your own ambition.
- I wanted immortality, not...
- Well...
every wish has its price.
Forgot that you're human?
I'll deliver Lilith to you.
Take what you need...
but kill her.
They are not going to make it,
are they?
No. And I don't think they
expect us to either.
So try and keep the body count down
and get us out of here.
I'll be gentle.
- Stop right there! Hold it!
- On the ground now!
Don't move!
Wait! Hold your fire!
- You're with The Faith?
- Yes, sir.
Look, The Faith saved my life
a few years ago. What do you need?
If you can get us out of here, I got
a way to put an end to all of this.
Alright. This way.
Stand down!
- But, sir... -
- I said stand down!
Godspeed.
A friend gave this to me
before he died.
There's an encrypted file
on it-
You crack the code. I think we'll
know where you came from.
- This is Shaw.
- What's the status?
I need someone
who can break code.
I think it will take us
to the Demonicos.
Shaw, this is not going to be
necessary. We found its lair.
It's an abandoned facility
about the King's Point reservoir.
Agents are on the way.
They're coming.
This is the place?
It looks like the Cavalry
never came.
Do you recognize these names?
From the morgue.
And the conference center.
- These were not random kills.
- But why would the Demonicos...
want them?
They were scientists.
Raeborne journal-
Experiments on the test subject
caused deadly mutations-
I've fixed the problems-
Tomorrow, I'll prove
the world wrong-
Revenge.
I caused all of this.
Check this out.
Talis-tipped.
For my protection.
Chopin was a fascinating
individual.
He wore his beard
on the right side of his face.
The side people saw
during his performances.
People only see what we want them
to see, Lilith.
Nothing more.
Enjoy the music.
Well, I have to hand it to you,
William.
I never thought you would turn
Lilith around. It's very impressive.
The two of you have been
quite a thorn in my side.
It's too bad
she's not going to make it.
Why are you doing this?
There are no answers in life,
William. You should know that.
As much as I've searched,
I've found nothing-
Evil not only exists in this world.
It prevails.
The Faith has accomplished
nothing...
except to ease the pain
and delay the inevitable.
Remember what the Prefect
used to tell us?
"The mysteries of this life
will be revealed in the next."
Well...
I am forcing the Creator's hand.
Judgment Day.
You're sick. And you'll die
like everyone else.
Yes...
but not before looking into
the Prefect's eyes...
as he watches the world
come to an end.
For that, I will gladly
sacrifice my soul.
What about Raeborne?
Is he one of your converts?
Anders? No?
He's just a petty man, seeking
revenge against his father... -
and the Raeborne Team-
He played right into my hands-
I knew he would start
the Red Plague-
How did you keep tabs on him?
I have a tracking device.
Anders is so desperate
for answers... -
he'll believe
anything you preach-
I thought you were
a man of faith.
My father was a man of faith...
and it earned him
an early grave.
I have learned that there is
no purpose in life.
No grand scheme.
All is wasteland.
Wake up.
You remember anything?
Only your ugly face.
You are so resilient.
And so was Marcus.
But we know
what happened to him.
You have a cure.
I don't leave things to chance.
Hold on. I'll figure something out.
Optimistic. It's in my bloodstream.
You know that.
- Where are you going?
- Get another dose of the cure.
- You got to get Raeborne.
- I can do both.
- There isn't time.
- What are you talking about?
Follow Raeborne.
Get to the people that are infected.
Their time is running out.
- Now, go.
- What about you?
I knew the risks.
Now go. Go!
Hello-
Jenn, it's Will. There's something
I need to tell you.
Put one on each table-
- It's about Conner.
- Will? Are you still there?
Yeah, I'm still here.
It's crazy now- We just
opened the new restaurant-
- Jenn, I haven't much time.
- I can barely hear you-
I said...
I haven't...
much time.
Will, you're breaking up... -
Where could he be?
Where is Conner?
Yeah.
It's my turn.
Ok, ok. Don't cheat.
- Don't leave the perimeter.
- Ok.
One, two, three...
four, five, six...
forty!
Conner!
You're too late...
just like when you were
too late with your son.
The viral outbreak crisis
continues in King's Point-
The governor has declared
a state of emergency... -
and called in the National Guard-
The centers for disease control... -
have reported cases of infection
across the east coast-
The origin of the mysterious
plague, which scientist say... -
is far deadlier than Ebola virus,
is still unknown-
Some are calling it:
A disaster of biblical proportions-
One thing is certain: Unless
a vaccine is quickly developed... -
the entire nation will be
threatened by this epidemic-
Jackson Therber, standing by
King's Point General... -
- with this reports-
- It's chaos here-
People are demanding answers-
Dr. Raeborne, the sooner we get
you out of the city, the better.
Now?
The only way to protect you
from this thing...
is to get you on the base.
I don't think you understand... -
the urgency.
Let's go!
Go, go, go-
Doctor, wait here.
Under no circumstances are you
to leave this truck. Be right back.
Anders, son...
all this people...
Why do this?
I can still help you.
Hey up here!
Hurry!
I...
Both cure and vaccine
have been given to the authorities.
The Red Plague
has been eradicated-
You were the one
who believed in her.
But you were the one
who didn't lose your faith-
And for that, I thank you-
Continue on the path.
I've had to make new memories.
You should do the same.
I don't know where to start.
Start here.
You're needed.
There are threats
only you can handle.
I need to do something first-
Since the dawn of creation,
I've been searching for a purpose-
Now, I have one-
I'm here to protect-
The Faith is my calling-
My name is Lilith-
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com