American?
No doubt.
Now since when did the Americans
start working for the Russians?
The images on this draw
won't serve you in the least.
Go!
Artillery placements,
troop movements,
these images won't aid
the cause of American men.
They are just currency.
Currency traded at
the cost of my people.
First, your foot.
Then, your knee.
Blow torch
to cauterize the wound.
One.
Two.
- Three!
- Okay, I'll give you the code!
Give me the code.
You need my thumbprint...
before entering the code.
I swear.
Hurry!
Come on, come on!
Code error.
Now, we'll all die.
20 seconds to auto-destruct.
Everyone out now! Now!
Auto-destruct aborted.
Fire!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Did I park it close enough?
Did you get the drives?
I got them.
Outstanding.
Let's go home.
I've got a lone boogey
coming in from above.
Confirm the boogey
He's coming in hard and fast.
Let's see what he wants.
What the hell?
This thing's all over me.
Get this thing off of me!
I'm all over him.
Fire it!
Green deck
Let's make sure it's neutralized.
Stay sharp.
Staying sharp-
What the fuck?
I'm losing control.
Get out of there!
I've lost control.
Repeat, I've lost control.
Rosnibich, come in!
I'm under attack.
Hello.
You got a cigarette?
Want a date?
Already got one.
Too bad.
Well, hello there.
You're my doctor?
Yeah.
I got your medication right here.
Take one preferably without food.
Repeat as necessary
until pain subsides.
Bavaro wants us right away.
Congratulations on the op
in Chechnya.
Oh, thank you, sir.
Now, tell me something useful.
Chemical weapon plants.
Hum, good.
Well, we'll get these coordinates
off to the military.
Congratulations, gentlemen.
That was an excellent recovery.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
Oh, gentlemen, by the way
Don't get too comfortable!
We have another situation.
An unidentified inbound came down
over eastern Russia 7 hours ago.
But we just left.
Then maybe
you should have just stayed.
An unspecified
displacement signature.
One of their experimental jets?
Well, if it is, its propulsion
system isn't fossil fuel based.
And so what you're saying
is it isn't earth-based.
What I'm saying is
it's unspecified...
for the time being.
Thank you, gentlemen,
you can go.
But I'm keeping you both
on active.
But...that means
no leaving the base.
I know.
Forget Vegas.
Hey! Wait a second!
No cheating.
What are you doing here?
I'm looking for someone.
You have come with me.
Ziggi!
Demitri!
Corporal,
where are you taking that weapon?
Lambert,
Bavaro wants you up front.
Lambert.
We have new intel
on the Russian situation.
In my office in 15?
That's very good.
The displacement signature is the
same as the ones in Yellowknife.
And El Descanso
and the other sites.
So what you're saying is
they're back.
What I'm saying is they match.
Then one of these things wiped
out your entire team last time?
Yeah, we had to drop
a tactical nuke.
That must have been
a public relations nightmare.
Well, gentlemen, this time
we don't have that option.
That is a Russian military base
40 kilometers east of Grozny.
Excuse me.
Demitri Pavakori.
According to his record,
an excellent soldier.
He used a Kanashnikov
EM-7 rocket launcher
to take the camp out.
And no personality disorders
no mental illnesses.
Well, maybe Demitri
was not really Demitri.
I'm sure he's missing now.
There has been no trace of him
since the base attack.
If it's a pattern
of assimilations.
We took these transcripts
a few days ago
from a couple of
Russian MiG-29 fighters
intercepting
an unknown hostile target
on a direct course for Grozny.
Get out of there!
I'm losing control.
Rosnibich, come in!
I'm under attack.
There's more.
The same displacement signatures
Incredible turn ratio.
So this thing is looking
more and more like
the same thing you dealt with
four years ago in El Descanso.
- It fits the pattern.
- Well, that's just great!
I want you to take an I Force
team and go back to Russia.
When do I pick my team?
You don't.
Well, if it's my mission
then it's my team.
Negative.
I Forces have been government
funded for two years now.
You're no longer
a private contractor.
We pick the teams.
Maybe we should continue
this conversation outside.
If you wanna say something, just
say it in front of everybody.
Webber's gone.
You are no longer a gun for hire.
You are employed
by an organization
that reports directly to the NSC,
the CIA, the FBI and ultimately
the president himself.
You are required to
execute your orders
in exactly the manner
in which they are given to you.
Now I've got a lot of
other people out there.
Do you want this mission or not?
When do we leave?
I want you prepped and ready
to leave by 1800.
Wait a minute! Why so fast?
Can't the Russians control
things for a while?
No.
Come on, Jack!
The Russians wouldn't accept
out assistance
unless it was something worse.
Why was the base really attacked?
We don't know.
But it's not the base
that's of prime importance.
It's what's next to it.
Here.
Chernobyl era plant
upgraded in '92.
That is one hyper-fusion reactor.
Which makes a lovely byproduct.
Uranium 237.
237?
The worst of the worst
of the uranium byproduct class.
A Chernobyl-level release
from that baby
would make Three Mile Island
look like a leaky faucet.
Yeah, this just
keeps getting better.
We have to get
that thing out of there
with no collateral damage.
I see.
This is your new team.
McCallister you already know.
Adriana Sikes.
Expert in demolition.
She's military trained.
She's done many operations
with the DEA
both in and out
of the United States.
She's clearly
not a lady to piss off.
Bjorn Hatch.
Former German special forces.
He's a weapons
and combat specialist.
Not the most polished operative,
but an invaluable asset
on any mission.
That is your team.
Mr. Bavaro, I'm been working on
replicated samples
of this antibiotic material
taken from Yellowknife.
And when using a focused
microwave beamer...
Microwave?
Remember?
I designed the core filament,
sent it over
to the Weapons Division?
Right.
Well, I was hoping it would
be possible to test them on...
There's no time for that.
Faulker, I want
the I Force transport fueled
and on the runway ASAP.
Shut down the reactor!
Shut them off!
Seal the core!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry, hurry!
Hurry! Hurry!
The team is ready, sir.
Good.
You have ten minutes to get them
down to the air strip.
You're shipping out right now.
I thought it was 1800.
The nuclear plant at Grozny
has been taken.
There's no contact.
No word of hostages or survivors.
Hell, we don't even know
if the reactor still online.
What about the radiation levels?
No word.
Listen, that nuclear plant
has six times
as much uranium fuel
as the one in Chernobyl.
If it starts leaking,
the whole world gets a taste.
I know.
Lambert, I need you to
take along another team member.
Who?
Her.
Who is she?
Science Division.
- No.
- Yes.
No.
I want you to take a
science officer along with you.
Now you call me when you land.
The weather satellite shows
a major storm system heading in,
so it's gonna be a rough ride
over there.
Anymore surprises, Jack?
Not from you.
'Cuz you're gonna
obey my orders over there,
exactly as I give them to you.
No exceptions.
You understand?
Hi!
Dawn De Silvia.
Look, I know I'm not trained
in combat or missions,
but I'll try to do my part.
Just strap in.
Little motion sickness?
Look, I don't mean to be rude,
but what the hell
are you here for?
I brought along some...
some reading material
for you to take a look at.
Nuclear site emergency
procedures and containment.
- What the hell is this?
- We just found out.
Did you know about this?
They figure the specimen
might go for the plant,
just not so fast.
But the Russian government
wants to keep it quiet.
They have assigned us a Russian
commander to work with us.
What's the specimen
doing with the power plant?
It's our job to find out.
My gig's ops. I'm not trained
for radiation work.
Me either.
Okay, I'll make you a deal.
When we get there, if
the labels outside are too hot.
We'll abort. Deal?
I go if you don't.
Deal.
What about you, princess?
Are you cool with this?
Hey, be careful!
Please.
Put that down!
It's hell of a welcome wagon.
Aren't these chuckle heads
supposed to be working with us?
Yeah.
Welcome to Russia, Mr. Lambert
- Commander.
- You've heard about us.
Mr. McCallister.
Commander, is there any radiation
leaks outside the plant?
Levels are normal,
but it's better to be safe, yes?
Any words on the workers?
Nothing.
All communication has been cut.
No.
I have specimen samples
in those cases. No!
They'll be fine.
Yeah, we'll see.
No, no, no.
No, no.
No, not!
The seal's good.
Let me handle this.
It doesn't look so dangerous.
You should see what happens
if they get loose.
The containers have microwave
transmitters inside.
It keeps the samples
from growing.
Follow me to the plant.
Our report said that
you were at the plant
when your base was attacked.
Yes. Why?
- Just lucky for you.
- Yes.
We can get to the main reactor
through access
in the cooling tower.
I'll take my men to the
first sub-level
and later radio for your team.
Hey, general, you're kidding.
This is not why we came here.
You're invited guests
of the Russian government.
You are brought here because you may
have some experience
in dealing with this.
Sounds like BS to me.
We didn't come here to baby-sit.
Are you prepared for
what might be inside?
My soldiers are prepared to
handle anything they find inside.
Now, Mr. Lambert,
if you don't mind.
Bavaro.
Yeah, we're outside the plant.
Well, I'll go ahead and assume
that there's no radiation leak.
Yeah, the plant is in one piece
Radiation levels are normal.
But Gorshkov won't let us go in.
He's sending his men
in first, Jack.
- What?
- Yup, he wants us to wait outside.
Did he say why?
I'm in Russia, Jack.
Under the command of
a Russian general.
Did you advise him
of the situation?
Yes, I did.
- Well, you hold your post.
- And do what?
At the moment,
we have the specimen
contained inside the plant.
If it gets outside again,
we have a much bigger problem.
Lambert, do you understand?
Let Gorshkov go in first.
- Well? Do we dance?
- We wait.
Why did Bavaro send us here
just to sit on the bench?
What's going on?
Remember, we're in Russia?
It sure isn't the French Riviera.
So you got a deck of cards?
Who are you eyeballing, Boris?
Sexy G.I.
Remember this?
Yeah.
Electromagnetic disruptor.
Used once in El Descanso.
Which exploded the specimen,
but didn't keep it
from performing, right?
You're right.
That's why the Science Division
developed this.
Microwave rifle.
It is much better
than your EMG disruptor.
I hope so.
Oh, Hatch's favorite toy.
Chain gun.
Packed with 300 pieces
of razor chain.
Used for rock cutting.
Razor chain.
Continuing search
Radio is on channel four.
Once the specimen
assimilates an organism,
it then stores that information
in cellular memory.
You wanna give us
the English version?
It means that the specimen
can look like
anyone it has assimilated before,
not just the last person.
The tissue is silicone-based.
It's very tough
Very resistant to temperature
and impact.
It can also camouflage itself
to hide in its surroundings,
like a chameleon.
The bottom line.
How do we kill it?
Well, use the microwave gun
the best we can.
Come up with another way to
destroy the binding structure.
Where is it coming from?
It seems to be
from the reactor room.
What was that?
I don't know, sir.
Come on.
Commander,
should we call for the Americans?
Not yet.
Gorshkov, do you read me?
Gorshkov!
You are to stay out here.
Until the commander
gives us the orders
for your team to enter.
Your men are dying in there.
We'll wait for orders.
I told you your men
are dying in there.
I said we'll wait for orders.
Well, what are you gonna do?
Shoot me?
No, I won't shoot you.
Leave your weapons on the ground!
I think you just bought yourself
an old-fashioned
sort of Russian ass-whopping.
- Guys!
- Remember me, baby?
Lambert! Guys! Oh, my God!
Your commander and his men
are getting killed in there.
We're going to go in
and help them out.
All right?
Let's go!
My equipment. I'm a scientist.
You're a soldier now.
Ready, Hatch?
Big time.
We're in.
Commander, we need backup.
Listen to me, we have to
clean up our mess in here first.
You understand?
For three years,
I have kept this operation
hidden from the energy counsel,
police and RSS.
I have billion dollars
in black market weapons.
I want them all moved out.
Commander, how?
The entire facility is
under attack by that creature.
Then called in Lambert's team.
Let them deal with it.
Then they've killed it.
We'll report that
the reactor is leaking.
That will
keep everyone out of here
for at least a week.
That's when we move
the war heads.
- Commander, are you sure?
- Listen to me.
We have to get back to the top
and get Lambert's team inside.
If we're lucky, they'll kill it.
And we'll be back in business.
Yes, commander.
Move.
The reactor's intact.
I got no signal.
We're in the core.
It's the lead walls.
All right,
I'll try the access area.
Everybody stays here.
You sure?
I'll be right back.
What do you mean
you can't locate the commander?
Well, we heard gunfire,
we entered the plant.
We haven't found him yet.
What's the status
outside the plant?
Well, Gorshkov's men
still got it locked down.
Is there any further evidence
of the specimen?
No, no visual yet, but...
it's definitely been in here.
Casualties?
Well, the specimen
took the entire facility
and most of Gorshkov's team.
Okay,
so now it's containment procedure
and exterminate the specimen.
- We still have to find it.
- You will.
Listen, one more thing
I think Gorshkov
is hiding something from us.
Based on?
The fact that
he wants to keep us out.
Well, maybe he's just
being a good soldier
and keeping the civilian teams
out of harm's way.
- I don't think so.
- Investigate if you must.
But remember, your priority is
containment and extermination.
Roger that.
Somebody help us!
Please help us!
You don't work here.
I think he still lives.
Get up very slowly, please.
Now turn and face me.
Okay, so what are we
gonna do about this?
Give him a few minutes.
He's probably fine.
What's wrong?
Afraid to fight a woman?
The fun is just starting.
Who are you?
You have more spirit
in your fight.
I'm just visiting.
Where are your friends?
I came a long way for this.
For what?
To destroy your world
with the poisons you create.
And one other thing. Revenge.
But you won't live to find out.
Is there more of you here?
One of me is enough
to destroy your kind.
I've got some shocking news
for you, lady.
Sean, are you all right?
He's headed back here.
Something's chasing him.
What? I said he's probably fine.
How are we gonna know
it's really him?
- Who?
- Lambert.
Cut it out!
Get behind.
Get ready.
Now!
Go on in, Sikes. Check it out.
Lady's first, McCallister.
I'll go.
Wait!
Got more bodies here.
They were Gorshkov's guys.
We've been sweeping
the entire facilitie.
One contact for nothing.
So we go topside
and wait for that thing to move.
The Russians are dead.
Gorshkov's probably dead too.
This is a real swell mission.
You know, we're walking around
some Russian nuke plant,
probably designed by the same guy
who brought us Chernobyl.
- We're breathing in poison.
- Give it a rest!
How do I know princess here is
reading the geiger counter right
and we're not getting fried?
- Check it yourself.
- Hey!
Looks to me like another
El Descanso is about to go down.
You were the sole
survivor there, Lambert.
How did you get so lucky?
- Come on, Sikes. Relax!
- I didn't pick you.
Quiet!
Don't shoot!
If you don't want
to get your head blown off...
The creature,
it killed my soldiers.
We have to go.
All right,
we'll get you out of here.
Come on, let's go!
All right, this way?
This way. To the elevator shaft.
Lambert, come on,
let's get out of here!
I thought it was the other way.
Gorshkov!
Commander Gorshkov!
You just shot
a Russian commander.
We're never gonna get out
of this country alive!
- Calm down!
- What?
Give it to me.
The gun's down.
Come on, let's go!
How did you know that really
wasn't Gorshkov back there?
I'm paid to know.
We're running out of ammo.
Aim for the weapon!
Sikes, give me your gun.
No, Hatch!
Hatch!
Sean.
You had to be a hero, huh?
Yeah.
Cover me!
You're all right?
Yeah.
Come on!
He's gone.
I know.
Who's next?
It's getting away.
You'd better come up with
something to kill it fast,
because we're out of chain guns.
Lambert!
- These are old S-7s.
- S what?
S-7 nuclear warheads.
One megaton each.
I mean, they were retired
from the old Soviet military
maybe 20 years ago.
And most were destroyed
or at least
the nuclear material removed,
but these warheads are armed.
What would they be doing
inside a nuclear power plant?
My research on the plant
shows an abnormal use
of uranium-235
for the last three years so...
Which is why Gorshkov
was so concerned
about us getting in here.
And finding out about
his little secret.
Maybe he was using the uranium
from the power plant
to build nukes.
What for?
A lot of money.
You know,
it still doesn't explain
what this creature's doing here.
I mean, what about the one
from El Descanso.
Yeah, what about it?
Well, did you ever find out
why it was there?
I mean, before you destroyed it.
They nuked the town, remember?
Wait a second.
These warheads are wired to
some kind of detonator.
Are you telling me
that this lunatic Gorshkov
was not only building nukes
but was gonna detonate them too?
Not Gorshkov.
What, you think
this thing did this?
You know what?
We're not gonna wait to find out.
I'm gonna cut the wires.
No!
The S-7 has
a mercury switch beneath.
You cut it, you detonate it.
We can only defuse it
from the detonator.
All right, Sikes.
You're staying here
with McCallister.
And you're coming with me.
Repeat, move in.
Let's go!
I guess we know where
the detonator is now.
The water
shields the uranium rods.
With this type of reactor,
the water's lethal.
That's just great!
The warheads will level
an area six miles wide.
And along with this reactor,
the fall out will be 1000 times
greater than Chernobyl.
It's a worldwide problem.
I mean, possibly 100 million dead
in the next 12 months.
No, I wouldn't do that.
Someone's gonna
have to go down there.
Yeah.
McCallister, do you read me?
Yeah, where are you guys?
We're at the core.
Listen,
I can't get a signal from here.
So I want you to use your phone
and relay a call for me.
All right, what is it?
Listen carefully!
Excuse me, people!
I've just been informed
that our situation in Grozny
could well end
with the detonation
of multiple nuclear devices.
From the description, it seems
like ten S-7 class ICBM warheads
have been configured
for simultaneous detonation
inside the plant.
Now, I need blast radius
and fall out patterns now.
What do they know
about the detonator?
Nothing, except that it's
at the bottom
of the reactor's cooling tank.
Can they see a timing device?
Nope, we don't know
how much time is left.
We can insert
an engineering team.
They could drain the cooling tank
and shut down the reactor.
We don't have that option.
There's no time
for a second team insertion.
Whatever help or information
that we get
has to be made use of
by the team that's already there.
The clock is literally ticking,
ladies and gentlemen.
Every second counts.
McCallister,
I'm not gonna just sit here
with ten megatons wired to blow.
It's painless.
You won't feel a thing.
That's very funny.
You've only got maybe
one or two shots left.
It's almost dead.
Well, I'm gonna
go to the reactor.
I'm not gonna wait here
for Armageddon.
Well, you think you're gonna be
any safer down there?
The blast radius on one of these
babies are at least five miles.
I know that, McCallister,
but maybe I can do something.
So you're gonna
leave me, alone.
You're a big boy
Just, you know, sit there
and make phone calls to Lambert.
Where is McCallister?
He's back at the warheads.
You left him alone?
You know, just sitting in that
place was giving me the creeps
without those wired nukes.
You guys don't look any better.
And you think this place
is any safer?
Don't even think about it
I am fine.
Think about what?
Lambert, do you read me?
Yeah, go ahead.
I found a live one here.
One of Gorshkov's soldiers?
No, a plant worker.
The guy's alive, but...
Lambert.
McCallister, you're breaking up.
Say it again.
I want you to go back in there
and get McCallister.
You go.
I'm not going to
leave you alone with her.
If you bring back McCallister,
I'll be sure at least one of you
is who you say you are.
McCallister?
McCallister.
Okay, what have we got?
The S-7.
It's primitive.
Early Russian design.
It's gonna be a problem.
This thing was built to
fail safe detonation.
Descriptions of the wiring
make it nearly impossible
for them to disarm
at the warhead.
I mean, it would take them hours
of checking the lines
and cutting the power on each one
for them to even have a chance.
We need to get to the detonator.
The real problem is we don't know
how much time is left.
Sir.
We have to think the way
it thinks.
Now, suppose
you were the specimen,
how much time would you put
on the detonator?
- Maybe two hours.
- Too generous.
An hour, if we're lucky.
Now, all we need is to know
when it was set.
And if we can get someone
to that detonator on time.
Going into the cooling tank
would be suicide.
I know.
Damn it, McCallister!
Geez, Sikes
Feeling froggy, are we?
You should be careful
where you point that thing.
I heard you on the radio
Did you find somebody?
Yeah.
Where did he go?
You tell me.
He was right here.
I... I left him to find you.
He was right here. I swear it.
Well, where did that plant worker
run off to, then?
I don't know, but he was here.
McCallister!
- Go!
- How's that plant worker doing?
He's gone.
What?
I left him
to go hook up with Sikes,
came back and he was gone.
I want you both back here now.
You ready?
Whenever you are.
After you.
I don't think so.
You take the front.
What?
What happened to him?
Look, the guy was right in front
of me when I called it in.
I left him alone for 30 seconds,
came back, he was gone.
No, McCallister.
What really happened
to that worker?
Better yet, was there a worker?
Oh, I see, so I'm the alien now.
- Let's find out.
- Screw yourself.
You're not going with this,
are you, Sean?
Let me ask you a question.
- Proof who you are.
- Don't flip this on me!
Well, should we put into a vote
to see who's telling the truth?
Thank you.
Now this witch hunt is over
can we continue the mission?
Wait!
What now, Sikes?
I just don't believe your story.
He wasted that worker.
I don't know where
the real McCallister is,
but this isn't him.
Don't move!
Keep pointing
that thing at me, Sikes.
It'll be the last thing you do.
I am right here.
You're barking up the wrong tree.
- Sean!
- Both of you, back off.
Back off!
Sikes.
Put it down!
Everybody watch out!
It's gonna come out of his body!
Wait!
You knew it was me, right?
Sean!
You knew, didn't you?
It's not him.
Mr. President.
I recommend
putting Air Force One
into secure air space
immediately.
And call the G8 countries
and inform them of the situation.
Yes, sir.
God help us all!
Hey, Sikes. What are you doing?
I thought
I'd go for a little swim.
Someone's gotta
get the detonator.
You don't have to do this.
Someone has to.
Sikes. Don't do it!
Come on, Lambert.
You knew one of us
was gonna have to do this.
It's our job.
No.
Sean.
Get back!
You know what I hate most
about the human body?
It breaks too easy.
Oh, your weapon does not
seem to be functioning.
It's out of power.
The last shot was wasted
on your friend.
I liked that one.
Fearless.
- Like someone I knew.
- Who?
He came here before me.
Arrived at the place El Descanso.
Four years ago?
You were there, weren't you?
You destroyed him.
You took him from me!
He was my mate!
Your husband wiped out
an entire town and my team.
And on this planet...
that tends to upset people.
- You took my mate?
- Yeah.
Now I take yours.
What?
No, he's not. I mean,
we're barely even friends.
Go! Go!
Where's the commander?
We have to keep it away
from the cooling tank.
We are running out of ammo!
- Seven minutes.
- Can you disarm it?
I think so.
The problem is I don't know if
I can hold my breathe that long.
It's down really deep.
Good luck!
Thanks.
Yes, sir, I understand.
Switch to NORAD.
Who are they?
That's a joint Russian-American
task force.
They're carrying
deep impact missiles.
If we don't have an answer
in five minutes,
they're gonna launch.
I need Lambert on the wire now.
Yes, sir.
All American and Russian pilots!
I'm speaking to you
personally today.
Not only
as the American president,
but also
as an arm forces veteran.
As your commanders have told you,
the situation in eastern Russia
has turned critical
and unfortunately,
we have few options.
Today, we are forced to accept
the lesser of two evils.
If the ten warheads inside
the Grozny nuclear plant
are detonated,
it will cause a massive
radiation cloud
that will kill
millions upon millions worldwide.
No person, no nation,
will be safe.
By firing deep impact missiles
at the base of the nuclear plant,
we have a chance
to localize this problem.
We believe that the warheads
can be destroyed
prior to detonation.
And that most of the nuclear fuel
in the plant will be vaporized
before it can be released
into the atmosphere.
It's not a perfect plan,
nor is it without consequence.
But the price of freedom
is paid by the people
who defend it
in its hour of need.
There are American and Russian
personnel inside the plant
and they
have accepted their fate.
Now I respectfully ask you
to accept yours
and preserve what life
can be spared.
Godspeed!
The fate of the world
rides with you.
- The timer?
- Less than two minutes.
I still have three links
to disconnect.
Hey, Sikes!
What?
It's okay.
I just don't wanna screw it up.
Reporting zero barrier
Lock and load.
Less than one minute.
You can do it.
It's been fun.
Firing!
Recharged.
Three seconds left.
Pretty soon I'll be able to
apologize to McCallister myself.
This is Sean.
The nukes are neutralized.
Lambert!
A joint Russian-U-S- task force
launched a
deep impact missile attack
- two minutes ago.
- What?
You have to clear
the facility immediately.
How? We're at least half an hour
from the top of the plant!
People, we have four minutes
to transmit override codes
to all those missiles.
There's over 50.
Well, that means we have
an awful lot of work to do.
And not much time to do it.
Come on!
- Oh my God! It's locked.
- We're trapped.
Wait!
Some of these containers
had sulfuric acid.
And the alien is silicone-based.
So?
So caustic compounds,
they destroy
the binding structure
in silicone.
We have to open the tanks.
Can't trust your eyes now!
Like you trusted your friend
with the gun?
You're nothing
without your weapon.
How many left?
Five.
Initiate auto-destruct
on whatever is still hot.
The last four are GPS locked.
This is gonna take a minute.
Lambert, get up.
It's on the move.
Sort of burns...
doesn't it?
Sorry,
I can't join you for a swim.
But maybe you should do it.
Or go take a dip in the reactors
pool like your friend Sikes.
I'm still here.
High and dry.
You're such a clever man,
aren't ya?
I should end our little game,
but I'm having too much fun.
Is that all you got?
You are a barrel of laughs.
Speaking of barrels.
You need to do better than that.
Looks like you took a hit.
Batter up.
Got them.
Transmit now.
Done.
Specimen destroyed.
I repeat, specimen destroyed.
Yes!
Okay, man.
Well, it doesn't get
much closer than that.
Yes, sir.
One moment.
It's the White House.
Yes. Hello, Mr. President.
Are you okay?
It's just hard to lose a friend.
Yes. Thank you, sir.
Just one moment.
Well, I'm sorry, Mr. President.
We can't seem to locate him
just at the moment,
but I will pass on
your personal congratulations
on another mission accomplished.
Thank you.
I hate to interrupt, but we have
a situation developing in Syria.
I need you back in
the control room immediately.
Yes, sir.