Did you make
your list of amends?
Yeah, yeah.
Got 'em right here.
-Here you are.
-No, please, read aloud.
Number one,
to see my daughter,
get her to talk to me again.
How long has it been now?
Eight years.
Number two,
get my gig back at the club.
Playing piano down at Drake's?
Yeah.
Number three,
get my family
to forgive me.
-Which are you doing first?
-My daughter.
What are you going to do?
I got a plan.
You have
one unheard message,
sent today
at 9:35 A.M.
Hello, Othell.
I got your voice message,
and my answer is no.
No, I will not
help you see Nima.
She doesn't want to see you.
She doesn't need to see you.
She's good now.
And I'm...
I'm good, too.
Don't call me again.
And don't contact Nima.
Hey, baby.
What are you working on?
Just some new projects.
What are you up to?
Here's your lunch I promised.
Did you make this?
I did. Try it.
Turkey. That's good.
Do you think I'm thoughtful?
I was reading this article
on perfect partnerships,
and it says that a good
partner is always thoughtful.
That's why I'm asking you
if you think I'm thoughtful.
Yes, I think you are
very thoughtful.
Absolutely.
You know, I think about all
the thoughtful things you do
and the thoughtful
person you are,
and I just...
I get misty-eyed.
Stop it.
Go on, eat.
Eat it right now?
With you watching me?
Just take a bite,
I want to see if you like it.
Yeah.
I was thinking...
Do you think having your father
walk me down the aisle
is going to look weird?
Would you rather
your father do it?
Not unless there was
a firing squad at the other end.
Okay.
Are you picking me up
for dinner?
-Absolutely.
-I'm gonna go finish up
the music for my concert.
How's that coming?
It's good.
I'm just a little bit nervous.
It's the first time
I'm composing several pieces.
Don't be.
You're great.
You are talented.
You're beautiful.
I'll see you tonight.
Absolutely.
Eat all your lunch!
-Bye-bye
-bye!
How can I help...
you.
-No, there's no need for that.
-Security.
I need you in here right now.
You don't need to do that.
I just want to talk to you
for a few minutes.
I know how it looks.
Just wait right there.
Security!
I know you're thinking
it's something else,
but I just need
a few minutes of your time.
-Security!
-You think you can give me
a few minutes
of your time, sir?
You don't really know me,
you know,
but you do kind of know me.
-Come with me, sir.
-Look, I'm Nima's father!
We got a breach.
Nima Simone Babineaux,
born September the 20th, 1985.
She has a scar on her knee
that she tells people
comes from climbing a tree
when she was 8.
I mean, that girl's never
climbed a tree in her life.
-He's okay.
-You sure?
Yeah, that girl
don't climb no trees.
I'll be right outside.
Mr. Babineaux.
So you're Nima's father.
Yes.
Well...
What can I do for you?
I need you to help me
find a way
that I can see Nima.
You know, I really wish
I could help you,
but I don't think
she wants to see you.
I need you to make it
so that she does.
Mr. Babineaux...
I'm just meeting you
for the first time,
and Nima
barely mentions you.
Let's say...
I'm dying.
Are you dying,
Mr. Babineaux?
A little.
You're dying a little.
I don't follow.
My counselor told me
that I could have died
if I didn't stop drinking.
You could have died.
Did you stop drinking?
Yes.
But...
I could have died.
Can we play that up?
No, I'm sorry.
I wish I could help you,
but I really can't.
My counselor...
Wanted me
to work on this list.
I'm sorry, I...
I wish I could help,
I really do.
I just have way too much
on my plate right now.
I'm sorry.
Babe, how was your day?
Interesting.
Why? What happened?
Nothing, just had to
turn down a project.
Busy with more important things.
Well, don't be mad.
I paid for the flowers today.
I just wanted it done.
No, you just...
You just didn't trust me to do
what I said I was gonna do.
I told you I was gonna
take care of the flowers,
and you decided
to handle it yourself.
Spence, let's not get in
an argument over calla lilies.
It's not about the flowers,
it's never about just flowers.
It's... I told you I was...
Hey, Nima.
Mr. Babineaux,
what are you doing here?
I thought maybe
we could talk.
Right now probably isn't
the best time.
Nima?
Geez. Nice.
Nima!
How do you know him?
I don't.
He showed up at my office today.
-Did you invite him?
-No.
He came by to ask
if I could help him talk to you.
You just listened to
what he had to say?
I mean, yeah.
After everything
I've told you.
Baby, all you ever said
was that he wasn't around.
Any time his name comes up,
you get so angry,
we can't even have
a conversation.
What else
would I have to say?
What did you expect me to do?
Can you please take me home?
Are you mad at me?
Just take me home.
Mr. Babineaux.
Well, y'all will never believe
who I saw yesterday.
Who?
My father.
What?
Yes.
My father.
Did you shake him?
Did you toss hot grease
in his lap?
Did you open-palm slap him?
I need details.
Okay, Rochelle,
she would never do that.
I would absolutely do
all of that, Tiffany.
All right...
But I didn't.
I just left.
Why was he there in the first
place?
Spence claims that
he came by the office to see him
and he asked for his help
in repairing our relationship.
Cute.
No.
Exactly.
Nima, it's... it's time for
you to fix things with him.
Sweetie, you're getting married.
What does getting married
have to do with any of that?
Because you're starting
a new life,
and, typically, you want
all to be well in your world.
All is well.
You know, you just...
You don't understand.
Okay, I see.
It's because I have a dad,
right?
Is that what it is?
-Yes.
-Okay.
You two, I...
But Rochelle and I have
the better version of dads.
Okay, what's that?
They're called moms.
Whatever.
You know what?
Boo!
Othell Babineaux.
Come here, man!
Benny Mitchell!
How you doing, brother?
What's happening, cat daddy?
Man, I ain't see you in what,
five years?
We were in that Mexican jail.
You were in
that Mexican jail. Stop.
You playing anywhere?
Well, you know, I'm...
I fix cars.
All that talent
and you changing oil?
You got something here
for me, Benny?
Man. I can't...
Not after the missed practices,
showing up to gigs drunk.
I mean, you punched a guy
in the audience, Othell.
He was heckling me, man.
He was clapping, o.
Look...
I need this, Benny.
I'm clean.
How long?
Two months, four days,
and seven and a half hours.
O...
I'm rooting for you
more than anybody.
But you gotta prove you can be
a reliable musician, man.
Yeah, we got another spot
for a piano player,
but I can only
give it to someone
who's gonna show up on time,
come to rehearsal
without a bottle in his hand,
and not throw up during a set,
brother.
That happened once.
It was on the bass player.
Jimmy's still mad
about that?
The suit was new.
Look...
If you can stay clean
another month,
come back and see me.
You know, I can look at you
and tell you ain't ready yet.
Let me introduce you to my wife,
Martha, while you're here.
Hey, baby.
You have got to be
kidding me.
You still stalking me?
I want you and Nima
to come to
my mama's 80th birthday party
in Savannah.
Yeah. Well, good-bye,
Mr. Babineaux.
Wait, wait, wait, Spence,
please, just give me a minute.
You know, I made it
very clear to you before...
I can't help you.
And instead of sitting down
and figuring out
what you could do
for your daughter,
the first thing you do
is ask her to do
something for you.
You're everything
she always said you were.
You're selfish.
Then don't do this for me.
Do it for Nima.
Come on, Spence,
you're a good man,
but we both know
that deep down inside,
Nima wants to fix this, too.
You're a psychologist now?
No, no.
But I let my issues
with my daddy ruin my marriage.
Well, I'm not gonna let that
happen to ours.
You can't control
how people respond to pain.
I don't want to hurt her again.
I just want a chance.
Will you give me that?
Are you gonna...
Finish this?
Baby, you want a drink?
No, I'm fine.
Babe...
What's the story
with your dad?
I need to know.
You know what?
I don't like talking about him.
Not even for me?
Please?
Why this sudden interest?
It's not sudden.
I always wanted to know.
Baby, that's in the past.
That has nothing to do
with you and me.
Mwah.
Except that it has
absolutely everything
to do with you and me.
What does that mean?
Baby, you don't trust me.
Yes, I do.
Not with your whole heart.
You remember
when your grandfather
was terminally ill?
You didn't tell me
for two weeks,
and you claimed it was
'cause I was busy at work,
but I'm never too busy for you.
You don't trust me
emotionally.
Okay. Wait.
Where is this coming from?
Did you talk to him again?
A little.
You talked to him a little?
Look, he came by my job today
when I was having lunch,
and we talked.
He's actually getting to you.
These are my feelings.
They're not his.
He's a conniving liar,
Spence.
What did he say?
Okay, I know this is
out of nowhere
and it's last-minute,
but he said he wants us
to go with him to Savannah
for your grandmother's
80th birthday party.
No!
Do you know how selfish that is
for him to even ask me that?
But I want to fix this.
I want to fix this.
No, no, no, no.
You're trying to fix me.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go.
I have to leave.
-Babe.
-Okay? Good night.
Baby?
Where are my shoes?
I live here.
You go.
Okay.
I knew you lived here.
I didn't know
what you were doing.
Did you think about it?
Yeah.
And?
Yeah, you know, I just...
I don't... I don't want to.
I have no desire to mend
my relationship with him.
I know that sounds horrible,
but it's true.
-Baby, he stalked me.
-I know.
No, I want you
to think about that,
almost to the point
of getting arrested.
He stalked me for three weeks.
Baby, he wanted me to lie
and tell you he was dying.
He's crafty.
No, baby, he's desperate.
So maybe you could
look deep inside
that beautiful heart
of yours
and do this
because he needs it.
Not because you do.
Look at these.
It's pretty.
What you reading?
My favorite magazine.
Are you really ready
to do this, Nima?
I thought about it all night.
But I've decided
I'm going to go to Savannah.
It should earn me
double heaven points.
-Heaven points?
-Yes.
When you perform selfless acts,
you get points
that help get you into heaven.
Everyone knows that.
Who's here?
I'm not expecting anybody.
It's probably Charles.
Charles? Charles who?
He's just a friend of mine.
Why is Charles at my door?
He doesn't live far from here,
and since I was coming
to see you...
Well, it didn't make sense
for him to drive across town.
You are looking
too good today.
Good afternoon!
You must be Nima,
the beautiful daughter
of this beautiful woman.
And you are?
Charles, Covington,
Dr. Charles Covington.
You work with my mom
at the hospital?
Yes, yeah.
I'm a gynecologist.
Of course you are.
Where are you taking my mother?
I've had the finest
restaurant downtown shut down
just so we could dance alone.
Romantic?
Sounds like a waste of money.
My dear,
nothing is a waste of money
when you have enough.
Yeah, you're like the p. Diddy
of reproduction.
Diddy?
Yeah, I like that!
No.
Could you wait right here
one minute?
Maybe.
What is wrong with you?
Mama, who is that crazy dude?
He's my date.
He is a bad decision.
Yeah.
I'll be right with you.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I want to use
one of the pianos.
Yes.
Just sign in right here.
Miss Babineaux.
What are you doing here?
I thought it was your day off.
It is.
Did I leave
my music sheets here?
-Yes, you did.
-I think.
Thanks.
Does that say
"Othell Babineaux?"
Spence told me
to give you this
whenever you found out.
He paid for some gentleman
to use the extra piano
to practice for some gig.
Of course he did.
He was only supposed
to be here on your day off.
Hey! Mr. Babineaux.
You know, I thought I said
I could come get you.
Well, you know,
I wanted to show you this.
Okay.
I guess that saves time.
Othell?
Well, you're looking better.
You look
really nice yourself.
It's really good
to see you again.
I gotta go.
Hi.
Hello, Nima.
It's gonna be a long trip.
Finally getting on the road.
Would anyone like
a Lancaster soft cream?
You used to love caramel, Nima.
I love these things.
Yeah, I used to...
Okay.
Is he okay?
-Mama! Mama!
-Hey!
Mama!
You made it!
Go on back to the table,
Melinda.
All these extra people.
I'm so happy to see you!
How are you?
Well...
I'm doing fine, mama. I'm fine.
You put on a few extra pounds
there, son.
Yes, I have. I have.
Well, who are these
young, attractive people
you got with you?
Mama...
That's Nima...
And her fiancé, Spence.
My granddaughter.
Baby! Honey!
I been waiting my whole life
to meet you.
Well...
Please, go on in.
Y'all just in time for dinner.
Look who's here!
Hey, everybody.
Y'all not gonna say hello?
-Hello.
-Hey, bro.
Well, o brought his daughter,
Nima.
And her fiancé, Spence.
Well, this is your uncle James
and his wife, Denise.
People used to always say
that James and Othell
looked the most alike.
This is your uncle Joseph
and his wife, Nancy.
Joseph is
the quiet one of the bunch.
And this is my second oldest,
Melinda.
And my youngest, Marvin.
His family couldn't make it.
Well, y'all go on and sit down.
His family never makes it.
Well, y'all know
that I'm not much for words.
Right, mama.
But I just wanted to say
thank you, all of you,
for coming out to my
80th birthday party.
I want to thank my second-eldest
Melinda.
She did a beautiful job
with this party.
Thank you.
And I want to thank
James and Joseph for the cake
and the lovely portrait
for the living room.
But I am most excited
that Othell
and my granddaughter Nima
are sitting at this table
together.
Nima and Spence,
I'm so glad to have you here.
Let's eat!
Yes!
Mama, did James tell you
about his good news?
No, baby, what happened?
Well, mama, I was offered
a position at hennig and white.
My baby brother now works for
the largest law firm
in the country.
Soon to be walking in
his father's footsteps,
becoming a judge.
Well, congratulations, baby.
Joseph has good news, too.
Go ahead, Joseph.
Go on, tell her.
I passed the bar.
Congratulations,
baby brother.
Now, let's see.
Dad, god rest his soul,
was an esteemed judge.
Mama, a retired nurse.
I'm a doctor.
We have two lawyers.
And, Marvin,
he's a top financial advisor.
Yes.
Good.
Othell, what do you do?
Your brother's fine, Melinda.
Mama, I know he's fine.
It's just been such a long time.
I haven't seen him in years.
I don't remember what he does.
I have a...
A car repair shop.
You have, or you had?
-Melinda!
-No, mama.
This is a special day
for family.
Not for a man
who was too drunk
to attend
his own father's funeral.
Would you shut up?
How could you ruin
my birthday party
with this your stupid,
stuck-up ways?
-I'm sorry, mama. I'm sorry.
-Shut up!
Just shut up.
Hey, what do you say
we take a walk,
check out the pond?
Now, I haven't seen the pond
in years.
Sure.
It's still there.
All right, I'll get something
out of the car.
I'll catch up with you.
All right.
-A lot of memories down here.
-Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, there is.
What you been up to, man?
I tried to...
I tried to call you
a couple of times.
Your number keeps changing.
Well, I ain't been doing
nothing, man.
Did you ever get your...
Your gig back at the club?
No.
I got a promotion on Friday.
$10,000 raise.
My wife...
She's pregnant
with our third child.
Good things are happening.
And I... I hate it.
I... I hate my life, Othell.
What?
I hate my job.
I hate...
I don't like my wife...
Very much.
I'm living a life
I ain't choose.
That's 'cause
daddy chose it for you.
I... I didn't like it, but...
I understood
why you didn't come
to the funeral, you know.
I mean, you were
the only one out of all of us
who ever went after your dreams
instead of just doing
what senior told us to do.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
and he hated me for it.
Y'all all did.
I don't.
You... you shut me out.
I was always envious of you.
You know, I can't keep a job
to save my life.
I'm an alcoholic.
I lost my wife...
My best friend.
And my daughter wishes
that I was dead.
You envious of that?
Yeah.
At least you chose your misery.
Man.
You're crazy, man.
You're crazy.
Daddy, he...
He just didn't
understand you, Othell.
You scared him.
He was a man of routine.
He knew one way
to get to success.
We all just fell in line.
You refused.
You know, the day he died...
I started rummaging through...
Through his closet
in the library.
Remember, he didn't let anybody
go into it?
He kept these.
Those are the playbills, man.
He was proud of you, brother.
He just didn't know
how to show it.
Thank you.
Thank you, man.
Come on, now!
Wait, wait!
Come on, man.
Are you out of your mind?
What's going on?
What's going on, Nima?
Your daughter slapped
Melinda.
-She did?
-Yes.
Say something else about
my mama and I will do it again.
You better get this
little illegitimate cheat
out of my
mama's house!
Illegitimate?
Enough! Enough!
Enough, enough!
Quit yanking on me, James.
Lord, have mercy.
You want to kill me
on my birthday?
No, ma'am.
Now, quiet, Melinda.
Now, this...
Is your brother.
This is your blood.
He is family.
Well, where was family
during daddy's funeral?
Melinda...
-Where was blood then, mama?
-Melinda.
Where was he when daddy
kept calling for him
when they took
him off that machine?
Melinda, it is over.
This is done now.
Melinda...
not a day goes by...
That I don't regret...
Not coming to
daddy's funeral.
O, you don't even
have to do that.
No, mama, mama, please.
Let me say this.
I should have been there.
But I let my pride...
And my anger...
Stop me.
I let my pride
ruin a lot of things.
James...
Joe...
Marvin...
Melinda...
Man, I was so foolish.
And I'm sorry.
I'm really...
I'm really, really sorry
that I hurt my family
like that.
That's enough, o.
O, that's enough, baby.
That's good.
Now, we gonna put
all of this behind us!
Now, Nima and Spence,
y'all gonna stay
in the guest rooms.
No, no.
We made a reservation
at a hotel.
-Good.
-Not anymore.
Yes, ma'am.
Now...
Who is gonna have
some cake with me?
Today was a mess, Spence.
Tell me about it.
I can't believe you smacked
that woman in the mouth.
She earned that slap.
You know, it's funny
how the remark
that preceded the slap
was about Othell, not your mom.
No, it wasn't.
Yeah, it was.
Yeah, I was standing
right there,
and she said that
Othell was worthless and...
You know, it doesn't matter.
Came up with some new names.
They better be good
this time.
Kennedy for a girl
and Josiah for a boy.
I actually love those.
Yeah?
Well, I think we should
get started on them
right during the honeymoon.
Hey, no!
We said two years, remember?
I don't remember saying
two years.
I think that's something
we should start right now.
What do you think?
Yeah, we should start on that
right away.
Spencer,
your room is upstairs.
-But, see, we usually...
-Not in my house.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll pack my stuff.
I'm gonna go upstairs.
I thought we made up.
No, we haven't.
When are you gonna
get over this?
Yeah, you gave me money
to start my car repair shop,
and it failed.
Businesses fail every day.
No, you fail every day.
You know, you hated me
since we were little.
Yes, I have.
I got straight "as."
I got awards.
I got accepted into
one of the finest medical
institutions in this nation,
and my father complained
the whole time about you.
He couldn't even acknowledge
our accomplishments
without saying that he was glad
that they were not
your failures.
You were his beloved project.
He reveled in your dysfunction,
the tortured artiste,
while we worked hard
for his love,
and he showered you with it.
Daddy hated me,
and you know it!
He didn't hate you!
You always opted
to go to the pain,
to go for the darkness.
You know,
you lived in that space.
Was it easier?
Is it easier than trying?
Is it easier
than being successful?
Is that easier than being loved?
I try, Melinda.
I try, I try.
You tried?
What about
when I paid for you
to go back to school
10 years ago
and you quit?
What about when I paid
for your first car?
You were too cheap
to pay for the insurance.
What about when I paid
for the bulk of
your wedding
to my best friend?
Jeannette was my best friend,
and you ruined it!
I've...
Already apologized
for all that.
Yes, but you still refuse
to do anything with your life!
You look.
I'm through talking about this.
Nima?
Little boy...
What do you need at this hour?
I... I left my toothbrush in...
I left my toothbrush
in Nima's bag.
I packed it in there.
Just a minute.
Toothbrush.
You know, mine,
it has the little...
Good night, Spence.
This will work.
Come in!
Well...
Since you're up...
I thought maybe we could talk
for a minute.
Yes, Ms. Babineaux.
You can call me grandma
if you want.
We love you, Nima.
I wish you had answered
one of those letters I sent you
when you was in college.
I understand.
When your parents split up,
Othell came
and lived with us.
And he tried.
He really did.
He tried so hard.
But then he just...
He gave up.
Then...
My husband
just kicked him out.
But we should have...
We should have tried harder.
We should have forced our way
into your life.
And for that,
I am very, very sorry.
Thank you, baby.
Now y'all get home safe, now.
You take care of yourself, son.
I will, mama.
And take care of Nima, too.
Thank you for the...
Hospitality, Mrs. Babineaux.
You're welcome any time,
Spence.
Bye, everyone.
Nima, can I talk to you
for a moment?
I wanted to make sure
you had these before you left.
He spent his whole paycheck
on them
on your 10th birthday.
But he just didn't make it
to your party.
I've had them here ever since.
Sapphire.
It's my birthstone.
I'm sorry, I can't...
Take these.
But they're yours.
They're from your dad.
I know.
I can't. I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Okay.
You make it home safe, now.
Listen...
I know I told you
I needed to see more,
but the owner want to fill
this spot as soon as possible,
so I'm putting myself
on the line here, o.
Look, Benny, man...
I ain't played in a long time,
you know?
Man, I'm still practicing.
It's like
riding a bike, baby.
You got this, you know?
Yeah, I know, but...
See, if I had known
you were gonna...
Hey.
I'm Othell Babineaux.
All right.
Let's go.
It's been a, you know,
it's been a while.
See, most of the time, I like,
you know, fix cars and...
So it's been a while.
Stop wasting my time.
Damn.
Jeannette...
It's o.
Can we talk?
Hey.
Hello.
You look beautiful, as usual.
You have 10 minutes.
Jeannette,
can't we chat a minute?
Now you have nine.
Well, Nima hates me
a little less after Savannah.
Perhaps.
Did she tell you
that she slapped Melinda?
Yes.
How is Melinda?
She misses you.
Still no drinking?
This is water.
Almost three months.
Well, actually, it's been
two months, 12 days,
and three and a half hours.
You cannot mess this up.
You've never even given me
a chance to mess up.
What about the club?
I went to get my gig back
and froze up.
What did you want to show me?
I know it's Nima's birthday
Tuesday.
Yeah?
What is this?
I want to do
something special.
You want to take her
to the bistro?
You think she'll go?
I'll see what I can do.
Nima?
Nima, I thought we were
meeting at the restaurant.
You remind me
so much of your mother.
I know you want to know
why I wasn't there
and why it seems
like I didn't try,
but...
I don't have those answers.
I ask myself
the same thing every day.
I always...
thought you
deserved a father.
Just one much better than me.
I know this...
Won't be worth
much to you,
but you're
the kind of daughter
a father
would dream of having.
Smart...
Talented.
Just...
Just some things...
I needed you to know.
Have a seat.
What's up, man?
Well, I called you down here
because...
I thought about it
a lot.
I talked to Jax.
I let Jax know that
you're working on being clean,
and you're succeeding.
So I got you
another audition tomorrow.
Come on, man.
We go way back.
We done played
hundreds of gigs together.
It's just
a walk down memory Lane,
except you're clean
this time.
Well...
I... I am clean, you know,
I'm clean, I'm clean.
No shakes, no nothing, but...
Ain't no buts, brother.
Tell me you got it.
-Tomorrow?
-Tomorrow, 10:00.
All right, I'll be ready.
Why can't they sit
next to each other?
Trust me, they shouldn't.
Has your boss rsvp'd yet?
Yeah, they're right here.
They want fish and steak.
Good job!
-We're done?
-We're done.
-All done?
-All done!
Finally!
Excited?
Did you finish the music
for your concert?
Yes.
I did.
And you're inviting your dad?
No.
I'm not inviting him.
Okay.
Don't even think about
doing that.
What? What did I do?
I know you.
Just don't.
I'm not gonna
invite your dad.
No, I mean it.
Benny?
It's Spence.
Right, yeah.
It's good to hear.
Hey, listen,
Nima's doing a small performance
for friends and family.
It would mean a lot
if you were there,
but I need you
to wear a suit.
Yeah.
Yeah, between you and me.
All right.
You ready?
Time to shine, baby.
All right.
Thank you, man.
Don't thank him yet.
Looks like we found
our new piano player.
That's right!
Congrats, baby boy,
you're back!
But they didn't do
a good job.
No, I know.
-Hey, babe.
-Hey, ladies.
Hey, how are you?
That's my seat.
You were late.
Sit right here, hon.
Snooze you lose, I'm sorry.
I get the nice view for once.
So...
She was telling me that
she likes her father again.
Okay, no, she's not saying
that she likes her father,
she's saying
that she's trying.
Okay, don't do that.
She needs to reconcile with him.
This is a good, mature decision.
-No.
-Yes.
He had his chance.
Why does he get
the best part of her now?
He missed the teenage attitude,
and the impoverished
college years.
She's all
shiny and grown-up now.
All right,
maybe you didn't hear that,
but Nima told us
his whole life story.
The man is damaged.
That accounts for his absence.
Come on, now, he's trying.
I think she's setting
herself up to get hurt again.
Okay, you are such
a hypocrite.
You spoke to your father,
remember?
Yeah. Because he was dying.
Othell still has some time
to suffer.
Okay, the point is, okay,
she's making some huge
emotional strides in her life,
and we need to be there for her,
okay?
Well, is he coming to
the wedding?
I'm permitted to speak?
Yeah.
No, he's not.
It would be weird.
Okay.
Fine by me.
Now, can we talk about
something less depressing?
-Like boys?
-No, I said less depressing.
Okay.
Come on, man.
I...
I thought I had a suit
in here.
-Thank you.
-Hey. Sweetie, how are you?
-Well, hello.
-Hey.
I can't wait to hear
your music.
I can't wait, either.
Before you get started,
I got something to tell you.
What?
I...
I invited your father.
He said he was coming.
Okay.
I guess that's okay.
Yeah?
Okay.
You'll do great.
Shoot!
I want to thank you all
for coming.
It means so much.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
It's okay.
Could everyone please
give us a minute?
Nima, listen, I...
Shut up.
Just shut up!
I'm tired of talking about
what you don't do.
Let's talk about what you did.
I'm a mess because of you.
I can't love my fiancé
the way I want to
because of you.
I am curt, I'm mean,
and I'm dissatisfied with life
because of you.
I so desperately wanted
to be a daddy's girl.
I clung to my mother's father
for dear life.
And when he died,
so did a piece of me.
I've put the burden on my mother
to be my everything
because of you,
and you know what kills me?
I keep waiting
for Spence to leave.
Because I can't possibly
wrap my mind around
why he would stay!
Because you didn't!
You're my dad!
Dads are supposed to be there.
Because I'm yours!
Don't ever contact me again!
Jeannette...
You're never going to tell her,
are you?
I'm okay.
I just had to get that out.
You sure?
I don't want to
talk about it.
But aren't you, like, at
least a little concerned
about why he didn't show up?
Are you serious?
Why don't you ever take my side?
It's not about taking sides.
I'm not taking anybody's side.
It's just that we were making
some really good strides,
and all of a...
"We"?
The last time I checked,
I was the one who was given
the ultimatum
about getting to know my dad
or losing my fiancé.
I never said that.
I didn't...
I never said those words.
Spence, look,
I grew up without a father.
And surprise, surprise,
it has affected me negatively.
Do you know
how many books I've read?
How many articles
I have combed through
trying to be better?
I have made peace
with the fact
that I am not gonna be the girl
who has a dad!
You haven't made peace.
You're the opposite of peace.
You make war, Nima.
You make war with me every day,
you make war with yourself.
You're not at peace.
Spence, I am broken.
I didn't ask for you
to make me whole.
I just want you to love
the pieces.
You think I don't?
But you... you can fix
those pieces.
You could fix them
if you chose to.
I don't even know why
we're getting married.
What did you say?
-What did you say?
-You heard what I said.
I don't think
we should be getting married.
I mean, look at us!
You don't want
to get married?
No, I don't want
to get married.
You don't want
to get married to me?
Look at us! I don't want
to get married like this.
-You don't even like me.
-Fine, fine!
Fine. Fine.
Can you please just stop
the car so I can get out?
No, I'm not stopping, no.
No, you're not gonna
run away from me.
Stop the car
so I can get out!
Can you stop the car now?
Hey, what can I get for you?
I'll be back with you in a sec.
What in the world
are you doing
in a place like this?
I should knock you out,
right here in this bar, man.
You... You ruined
my relationship...
Just like you ruined yours.
I missed
the performance tonight
because
if she does forgive me,
I ain't got nothing
to give her.
I don't care anymore!
Everything all right?
So what you having, man?
Nothing.
He's an alcoholic.
Hey, get off me!
You're not going anywhere
like this!
You're not driving anywhere
like this.
I said... I said get off me!
You're not driving anywhere
like this.
Now, give me them keys.
Give me the keys!
I'm taking you home,
and you're gonna sober up...
and go apologize
to your future wife.
Now, you come on.
Come on, son.
Come on.
Rough night?
Rum.
I think I had too much rum.
It's not funny.
Baby, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Spence, I don't want to be
in a marriage
where you won't let me
be my true self.
I know, me, too.
And giving you my everything...
It isn't hard,
but it's scary.
It takes courage for you
to love me the way you love me,
and I always
want to reciprocate that.
You do, and I'm sorry if I...
if I don't make
you feel like that.
I'm so happy.
You have to know that.
But you have to let me...
Let me do things on my own time.
Okay.
Baby, do you still
want to marry me?
Yes.
How much rum did you have?
A lot.
This is so nice!
It actually is, mama.
There is no way
that I would ever
come to my grandbaby's
wedding without you.
You need to be here.
Let me look at you!
Look at you!
You haven't aged a day!
Well, neither have you.
Look at you!
My goodness.
I'm just here because...
You are her father.
Jeannette and I,
we had a long talk last night.
She's gonna make it right.
Today.
I am.
Hi, baby.
Hi, mama.
Come here, sweetheart.
I want to talk to you
for a minute.
What's wrong?
This is so hard for me to say.
I've been lying to you
about your father.
What do you mean?
I know I've made it seem like
he never tried to...
To see you or call you
or send you cards
on your birthday.
But he did.
He sent you letters for years...
along with...
Little gifts on your birthday.
And he sent you money,
whatever he had at the time.
Mama, why would you
hide this from me?
I loved your father so much,
Nima.
And when he left,
he took my heart with him.
I was just so mad.
All I wanted was him.
I didn't care about the money
or any of that.
I just wanted him,
but he never got it.
So when he left,
I just decided
that I would make him feel
the same pain that I felt
by keeping you away.
You tell me this
on my wedding day?
I'm so sorry, sweetheart.
I just want you
to have a fresh start.
Thank you.
You know, one day,
you just wake up
and you decide
not to be mad anymore?
Today is that day.
Sweetheart, he's here.
It's Mrs. Parcell.
Nima, are you ready yet?
You have to help me
fix my face.
Okay.
Today is your day to make
the memories that you want.
Who gives this woman away?
She does.
Well, I mean, I do,
but, mainly, her.
We do.
Okay.
Sheila!
This...
This is really
a beautiful wedding.
Yeah, it actually is.
You look wonderful.
Thank you.
You do, too.
I love that dress.
You always did
look good in pink.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
I've really missed you.
Well, I missed you, too.
Girl!
I'm so happy for you.
She's gorgeous...
And feisty, too!
Do you know that she hit me?
I heard!
My god!
I told her, too, I said,
"I'm gonna get you!"
I could not believe that
when they told me.
I am so sorry.
God, that's okay.
It's quite all right.
It's so nice
to get to talk to you again.
I know, you, too.
We have a last-minute
surprise for the happy couple.
For their first dance,
we'd like to serenade
them in style.
Please let me introduce
the bride's father...
Mr. Othell Babineaux.