Mind yourself.
Oh, my God, Tara.
Your water's broke.
Her water.
Tara!
Marry me! I'm your man!
Thirty flooded acres!
Go away and leave us alone.
- I'm talking to Tara.
-Go away, Mick.
Who else'll have you now?
- Huh?
-Home, now. Sleep it off.
How are they?
Fine, thank you, Sergeant.
It's Mick and the sergeant
at it again.
They're like tomcats.
They'll only
come near me at night.
At least we've a man
on our side from now on.
Aren't you the lucky lad, Jimmy?
This dump is going
to be all yours one day...
if you're not careful.
Oh, Tara.
I couldn't bear to touch it,
the poor wee thing.
Mrs. Ryan.
I'm only here
because I feel sorry for you.
You can spare your sorrow
for yourself.
What can we do for you?
A button. A fairly big one
that's fairly small...
with four holes,
as opposed to two.
I'm making my niece a dress.
She's emigrating.
Lucky bitch.
What about this?
It's the latest fashion,
you know.
She's my niece, not a trollop.
- Would this do?
-Sixpence.
God love us.
Poor wee bastard.
Shut your gob.
Who's the father?
There'll be no luck about
this place until you own up.
If everyone around here
owned up to their sins...
there'd be a queue at
the confession box a mile long.
Come on! Pull!
Holy God. Why me?
Since you gave up the drink,
has it been any easier?
Worse. Far worse.
Drink's an anesthetic.
It takes away the feelings
for a while, the pain.
And the joy.
I can't remember.
God sees your suffering
and understands.
Then why can't she?
You're not the only man
who wants to marry her.
Is it Mick you're talking about?
If he so much as
lays a finger on her...
I'll strangle him with me--
Don't commit murder
in your heart, man.
May God forgive me, Father...
but that's the way I feel
sometimes.
Mick has blown his brains out!
Come on!
The rain drove him crazy.
- Why?
-'Cause his cows was dying.
He had no wife, that's why.
In the name of the Father
and the Son and the Holy Ghost.
Give us a hand, you two.
You should've seized the gun off
of him, Sergeant.
The state he was in.
Revoked his license!
Leave me be.
Scandal is a contagion.
And one sinner...
can infect an entire community.
Tara Maguire...
name the man who wronged you...
or the whoremaster
will bring down...
yet more corruption and disaster
on the heads of us all!
Tara?
Tara!
Tara, my dear child...
trust in your neighbors
and your friends...
and in the Lord!
She's not a leper.
You're flying
in the face of the parish...
and Mick's suicide
was the last straw.
That's one mortal sin
they can't nail on me.
I wish to God
I was in Dublin or London.
With a baby
tucked under your arms?
You wouldn't last five minutes.
- Leave it there.
-Don't be stupid.
Own up.
Whose baby is it?
Ask your husbands.
He's my baby! Mine!
Look!
"Murder in the Red Barn."
- Will there be guns in it?
-Is it a cowboy?
There's guns in it, all right...
and an axe...
and a boy and a cow.
I wonder what "The Nun's Story"
will be about.
It's about a nun.
What do you get
if you win the raffle?
The first prize...
is a pound of butter
and a packet of tea.
We have a double bed.
Could sleep three easy.
Is that right?
“The Crappy Boy.“
“The Crappy Buy.“
Come here to me, you.
Did you not wash behind
your ears this morning, lad?
How much is six pence?
For you, three pence.
Only for you, though.
What is that?
I bet those flowers
are for Tara.
Morning, Father.
Just like all the other men
in this place.
Scared to death of the priest.
Scared to death of you,
more like.
I could have gone...
to the ecclesiastical
outfitters in Dublin, Tara...
but I'd rather
you had the money.
If you're not too proud
to take it, that is.
What's your inside leg, Father?
I don't understand
your question.
Here, hold this.
Up higher. That's it.
You still angry at me?
You read me from the pulpit,
and I'll never forgive you...
but I need your money.
He looks like a tough
wee customer right enough.
I'll have it within the week.
Do you want the same--
Exactly the same, if you please.
Change is a dangerous thing.
Change of fashion,
change of heart, of mind...
change of religion...
it's all a sign
of these shallow times.
Mick's death
could've been avoided, Tara.
He killed himself
over bad money...
and rotten land,
not for my sake.
But the sergeant,
now, there's a man...
who could be relied on
by anyone.
Indeed.
He's just the person to set you
on the straight and narrow.
What do you say?
I'll be needing half the cash
in advance, by the way.
Tara, don't drive another soul
to drink and despair.
What the hell are you doing?
Woodwork, sir. It's me hobby.
I wish I had the time
for woodwork.
If ever you do, sir,
I'll lend you me tools.
Let me smell your breath.
Get out on patrol-now.
You're supposed to be
a policeman, not a carpenter.
Tara...
up to your old tricks again?
What do you think?
Once a smuggler,
always a smuggler.
It's food, that's all.
And a suit for Father Malone.
It's time he changed out of
sackcloth and ashes anyway.
Would you look at the two of us?
The lawbreaker and the lawmaker.
I'm earning a bit extra
for me and the baby.
You trying to make life
more difficult for us?
There's nothing I want less.
Let me go, then.
What's happened to your hand?
Just a little nick,
cleaning me bicycle.
Marry me, or I'll go mad.
I'd go mad if I did.
Let me look after
the two of you.
We don't need looking after.
You will.
Splendid. Splendid!
Do you know, I can smell money.
Vonnie, dream's over.
Back to reality.
How are youse?
Youse are welcome.
Youse are welcome here, too!
Thank you, Seamus.
Thank you, Gerry.
- I've got a piano.
-So have I.
You can give them
all the Shakespeare you want.
They won't know the difference.
- You coming to the show?
-Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
In front of the children.
Vonnie.
Looks like
the last place God made.
Isn't that what you said about
the place we were last week?
- I was wrong.
-Will you shut up, Vonnie?
You're always grousing.
Let's get this show
off the road.
I got first tabs on her.
You can have the sister.
With a bit of luck, man...
we'll have a great time, huh?
If these chancers on the green
cause you any trouble...
you've only to say the word.
They're only trying
to scrape a living...
same as the rest of us.
Ah, Sergeant.
Complimentary tickets...
for yourself...
and your family?
I'll be there every night...
on duty.
What do you think you're doing?
Hello. I'm Tom Casey.
I'm from
the Department of Agriculture.
We're investigating
these chickens...
for the old epidemic...
and I can see you don't believe
a word I'm saying.
I was stealing
one of your chickens.
Right.
I'd better call
Sergeant Hegalty, then.
No, no. Wait a minute.
I'll pay you for it.
Ten bob.
What? You must be joking.
It's not worth two bob.
Sergeant! Sergeant!
Wait a minute.
Will you hold your horses here?
Wait till I see
what I have for you here. Now...
- Five bob do it?
-No.
For now.
I'll owe you the rest.
I'll give it to you
after the show tonight.
I want the five bob you owe me
before the show.
You must think
I'm a terrible idiot.
Oh, no, no, no.
I can see you're not.
Good.
Hope you taste better
than you look.
You bloody chancer.
We don't want more trouble.
He flew right under me jacket,
I'm telling you.
Behave yourself this year,
or I'll tell John-Joe.
You can talk.
At least it'll bring
a bit of custom into the shop.
We made five bob already.
Would you?
I would.
My mother, she said
put your shirts back on.
It's not decent half-naked.
Tell her to come over here
herself, will you?
One, two, three.
Up. There she goes.
What's the new sergeant
like here?
He's nice.
He's after Tara Maguire.
Is he, by Christ?
Who's after the sister?
Blacksmith.
So you're out of luck there
as well.
It's a woman driving.
I hate hanging around
on these jobs.
The place is crawling
with customs men.
Relax, Richie.
If they put you in jail,
I'll bake you a cake.
Do you know what this is?
Sure. Wireless with pictures.
Is this more cloth
for His Holiness?
'Tis.
Let's hope he gets
another year in Purgatory...
for saying Mass
in smuggled clothes.
Come on, Tara.
Just for old times' sake.
One extra.
For a man named Cassidy.
He'll be passing your way.
What is it?
Second-hand false teeth?
Razor blades.
I hear you're marrying
the sergeant.
Good move, Tara.
Where'd you hear that?
Father Malone.
He told
the wife's sister's auntie.
If you believe all you hear,
you'll eat all you see.
Smuggling with a baby.
That's a new one.
Best to start 'em young,
like gamecocks.
You coming to the show tonight?
Didn't we see it last year?
Might be even better this year.
That wouldn't be hard.
Jesus.
That's not another one of mine,
is it?
Sure. Hasn't he tattoos
all over his bum?
Your razor blades.
Thanks.
They're cheaper in the north.
I use them in an act.
Razor blades, my foot.
We'll definitely
have to go now...
see the old armchair
up on the stage.
Why are you always
following me around?
Because you're
as slippery as an eel.
And remember, I know what
happened to you in Dublin.
Nobody knows
what happened in Dublin...
so shut your gob.
Hope he doesn't
electrocute himself.
Look at him now.
Good man, eh? Good man.
It's not the first time
he's stole electric.
I'd be lost without you, Tom.
Ba njaxed.
You're banjaxed with me,
Freddie.
So what's the difference?
'Tis I, Hamlet the Dane!
Romeo!
Wherefore alt thou, Romeo?
Is this a padre
that I see before me?
How are you, Freddie?
Good to see you.
How long are you here for
this time?
Well, a week or two...
depending on the box office.
Grand. I'll announce it
from the pulpit.
You'll pack out, Freddie.
We'll make the usual donation.
Grand.
One thing, mind. Legs.
No unseemly display of flesh.
Is that clear?
Of course, Father.
Grand.
Are we late?
Not at all.
They can't start without us.
Next, please. Sixpence.
Thank you.
Come on, boys.
Down by the Sally Gardens
My love and I did meet
Sir, we never had anything
to do with insurrection.
We're a law-abiding family, sir,
and always have been.
Well, now, honest to God, sir.
I cannot believe a word
coming out of her lying lips.
No. Now, you can, sir.
I told me son...
that if he ever wanted
to fight for his country...
there was no use in him coming
to me for the old gun.
I have it well hidden, sir.
In the thatch.
Out of harm's way.
Can you speak
somewhat slower, man?
I can hardly understand
a word the damn fool says.
Will you shut up, you idiot?
Don't worry, sir.
if I hear anything...
coming out about
the rising of the moon...
'twill be the first thing I do
is let you know...
and that's God's truth, sir!
I have to agree with that.
That's God's truth, sir.
Only one son of mine
ever bore arms...
and that was me first born,
you know, Douglas.
He was shot a while back,
the yeoman of Wexler.
Easy, easy!
What's the damn fool saying?
He's a bit soft
in the head, sir...
since the mule kicked him.
That's why he rambles on.
I think we can proceed, sir.
I have searched
the premises thoroughly.
The only thing to be caught...
in this godforsaken hole
is the cold.
You'd catch more than that
if you knew where to look.
- What did he say?
-No idea, sir.
You're next.
Our hearts are broke
with the murder...
mayhem, and general debauch.
Rebellion
is a hanging offense, madame!
Nonetheless, I compliment you
on your choice of armchair.
Fit for the king himself.
Captain Williams,
let us proceed--
Where is the damn boy?
I saw him going out
that way, sir.
Maybe to join
his regiment of friends.
God bless him.
Watching without paying.
I caught you.
We're even, so.
You wouldn't have the loan
of a few pounds, would you?
I'll give it back to you
before Christmas.
Are you Tara or Brigid?
Tara.
The one with the baby?
Aw, Christ.
Of all the luck.
I've sworn to capture
every Croppy Boy...
that dares show his face...
and the rest
I'll hunt down like foxes!
And furthermore...
there will be scaffolds
on every hill...
from here to Sligo!
The battalion has returned.
It's raining buckets, Captain.
Tara.
Tara, it's me, Brendan.
Can I touch?
For a quid.
Come back tomorrow night.
The show's always different.
That tire's as bald as an egg.
Shouldn't be on the road.
Dear, oh, dear.
I just simply hadn't noticed.
Oh, Tom.
Did you enjoy the show, Sarge?
Do you have the insurance
documents for these vehicles?
We do, of course.
We have the death certificate...
birth certificate,
dog license. The lot.
Right away, showman.
Actor, if you don't mind.
This isn't a circus.
As near as, damn it.
Oh, now,
my dear sergeant...
let's be Christian about this.
Bear with me while I take off
my tatters and greasepaints...
and we'll have
a drink together...
to celebrate a successful
first night.
I'm not a drinking man.
Oh? You surprise me.
I want those documents now.
I'll post them to you
first thing in the morning.
You'll have them
by the end of the month.
I'm only joking, Sergeant.
Tara, it's Sergeant Hegalty.
He wants to talk.
You're looking grand, Tara.
Lovely.
What's that
you brought with you?
It's a...it's a crib.
I made it for you and the baby.
I can't take it.
I only want him to sleep
in my crib, that's all.
No.
Please, try to understand.
I can't put him in there.
Why?
Look at it, won't you?
It's beautiful.
You know why.
I don't like
what you're trying to do.
It won't eat him.
It's wood.
That's all it is.
Please!
Wood.
Leave us alone.
Nqw!
It's only wood.
I can wait.
At least it can keep him
warm for an hour.
Seven...
Cassidy.
Dear boy.
Thank you so much.
Now my little princess.
Bravo.
Thomas?
Well-earned, well-earned.
Here we are.
Thank you so much indeed.
Thank you for
a lovely performance last night.
There we are. That's it.
- And what about Timmy?
-it's my job.
That last pile...it's my son's.
He doesn't qualify yet
for a share.
I was ten years on the road
before I got a penny.
And you did it all
on a one-wheeled bicycle.
Will you play fair, Freddie?
Play fair?
This time last year,
you were in the gutter, lad.
This time this year,
we're all in the gutter.
Where's the gold you owe us
from the Fair of Muff?
It's like getting blood
out of a turnip!
But just think!
I mean,
the price of petrol...
running repairs
on the tent, income tax.
Income tax?
That's the best one yet!
You do all right, Rachel.
No one asks you
to share your perks.
How dare you?
Unhand me, or I'll evict you
from your parts!
Holy God,
every week the same.
We're all
in the same leaky boat.
I'm warning you, Freddie,
I'm ready to jump overboard.
In all of my years...never!
Ingrates!
I could've gone to England,
made a fortune...
but I stayed here
to preserve the genius...
of our Irish theater!
I promise to make stars of you!
We're not
peasants in the fields!
Dead souls in factories!
We are actors!
Tom...
I realized years ago...
there's no crock of gold
in this life.
There's just two magic hours
up here, every night.
Ah, Freddie.
We're only dreaming.
Give up that dream, Tom,
and you're finished.
Maybe we're finished anyway.
Tom, when I retire...
all this can be yours.
I'd better go get
a needle and thread, then.
Hello?
Hi.
How do you do?
Listen, I'm truly sorry
I put me foot in it yesterday.
I had no notion
you were married.
Since when?
I didn't want an old husband.
I just wanted a baby.
Liar. You didn't even
want a baby...
till the baby started
wanting you.
He's no fool, that baby.
Look, I'm only here for a week.
What are you doing
for the rest of the day?
Cheek!
Clear off, you buck idiot!
Hey! This is me Sunday shirt!
Give us a break, will you?
I'll break your head,
that's what.
Are you mad? Get out of here!
Get out!
You're the idiot.
I'll see you
in the front row tonight.
Let you in for half price,
if you're lucky.
Are you stone mad entirely?
Will you leave me alone?
Never.
I'm staying here all day
and all night...
until you come out
for a walk with me.
Go away and take
a running jump for yourself.
Take a running jump, huh?
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
Stop that, or you'll be sorry.
Where's the man
that's going to stop me?
In there with you?
I'm sure
it's not the first time...
you've seen a man
without his trousers, huh?
How are they from behind?
Try the jacket.
Yeah, that's grand.
Grand.
That's a...
a nice lipstick
you're wearing, Tara.
Unusual.
How are you, Jimmy?
How are you?
He's great. Lovely.
That's five pound you owe me.
If you're
not getting married...
that child ought to go to
St. Jude's Orphanage in Dublin.
The nuns there
will look after him...
body and soul,
better than you can, Tara.
I could bury him alive.
How would that suit you?
You can't fly
in the face of God, my girl.
Sergeant Hegarty...
you could redeem that man.
We can only redeem ourselves.
What is it you're after?
I heard about the daddy.
What did you hear?
Heard he killed himself...
after the baby was born.
Lord God, that must've been
terrible for you, Tara.
What are you collecting
the feathers for?
A hat I'm making.
Oh? Going somewhere special?
- Look at her.
-She's gorgeous.
Look at that hat on her.
Stop this!
Stop!
I distinctly requested...
that no short skirts
were to be worn.
Yes, but the flesh
is well covered.
There'll be some Shakespeare
after the interval, Father.
Will there?
Weak minds are easily twisted
by wanton imaginings.
Why do you think
God gave actresses legs?
Keep God out of this, showman.
Jeez, anyone would think
we were dancing naked.
You're worse than tinkers.
Interval!
You can do all your fighting
outside of the tent!
But this is
better than the show!
Father, I've got
lovely chocolates and...
Come on, move out! Come on!
Come on.
Oh, hello.
I didn't think you'd come.
Are you enjoying it?
It's a great gas so far.
What's this?
Tell me, are you long at it?
No. No, believe it or not...
it's me first time on the road.
Thought as much.
It'll be me last time,
you know.
The way I'm thinking...
soon as this season's over...
I'm going back to America.
- America?
-Yeah.
Excuse me, my dear.
That's a splendid hat.
I made it meself.
Do you sing, as well?
Thomas, "Othello" tonight.
"Othello"?
We must keep the Vatican happy.
I'll see you later.
I don't know the lines yet.
Don't worry.
I'll prompt you.
What's all this?
Play actors, sir.
The IRA exploded a bomb
this evening.
Nobody from
this district, sir.
The boys around here
couldn't blow up a balloon.
And I've had reports of
a rash of smuggling going on.
The border's miles long.
You might as well try...
and stop the wind
from crossing over and back.
This is your last chance,
Hegalty.
Next time,
it won't be a transfer.
You'll be cashiered.
It's a waste of time, Sergeant.
There's not
an IRA man for miles.
To hell with all men.
And women.
...thicken other proofs
that do demonstrate thinly.
I'll tear her all to pieces.
Tell me but this...
have you not sometimes
seen a handkerchief...
spotted with strawberries
in your wife's hand? Huh?
I gave her such a one...
'twas my first gift.
I know not that...
but such a handkerchief--
I am sure
it was your wife's--
did I today see
Cassio wipe his beard with.
O, now, forever...
farewell the tranquil mind!
Farewell content!
Farewell the plumed troop...
and the big wars
that make ambition virtue!
O, farewell!
The spirit-stirring drum...
the ear-piercing fife...
and all quality, pride,
pomp and circumstance...
of glorious war! Farewell!
Othello's occupation's gone!
What are you going to do
when you grow up, huh?
What am I going to do
when I grow up?
If I grow up.
Here.
There you are, now.
We can tell your mammy
you're on the wireless.
There's the smile.
Give us a kiss.
Put him down
before you drop him.
He's fine.
Well, are you coming or not?
Why should I?
Come on.
Make hay while the sun shines.
Will you look at this?
Jesus, Mary, and Joseph.
My own first cousin
That did me betray
And for one fair guinea
Swore my life away
As I was mounted
on the platform high
My aged father was standing by
My aged father did me deny
And the name he gave me
Was The Crappy Boy
I'd stand in the snow
listening to you.
With a voice like that,
you should be somewhere else.
Sure. Didn't he go
all round America last year?
Well, halfway around there.
Halfway round.
What happened?
Did your bicycle get a puncture?
Well, I was
in a nightclub there...
and I drank a drink
they had there...
called a Screwdriver.
By God, it'd make poteen
taste like holy water.
And that was in Philadelphia.
And I woke up the next day,
I was in San Francisco.
I'm telling you,
that's the only way to travel.
That settles it.
I'm going meself next year.
I wish you would.
Go away.
Come on...
while the day's in it.
- See you.
-Yeah, all right.
Tara, you're too fast for me.
You don't do it right.
I nearly burst into laughing
when he led you and Jimmy...
up the hayfield
on that old donkey.
The Blessed Virgin wasn't in it.
He's the maddest fella
ever I met, I tell you.
And best of all,
he's been to America.
What would you say
if your little sister...
ended up in Boston?
Tara, easy now.
You don't know who he is
or where he comes from.
You're a terrible woman
for galloping ahead of yourself.
I'm late. I'm late.
Oh, here.
Who are you waiting on?
What's it to do with you?
It's everything to do with me.
Steer clear, man.
She's spoken for.
Is that right?
She said nothing to me about it.
She wouldn't. She's frightened.
Frightened of you?
Frightened of the truth.
What truth?
The baby's mine.
Ask her.
Quiet.
You're waking the dead.
Back in your box.
What are you doing here,
sitting in the dark?
What's eating you, man?
I can't wait to see
the back of this dump.
Did her ladyship stand you up?
You're safer counting on
racehorses than on women.
I left a wife in Tralee
30 years ago.
Never regretted it.
A woman, a baby,
and a mystery man for a father.
It's dynamite.
They say the paramour blew
his head off with a shotgun.
And maybe she drove him to it.
She won't drive me,
I'm telling you.
Where the hell are we next week?
Tullyvin.
The crack'll be mighty, eh?
"The crack'll be mighty."
How many times
have I heard that before?
"The crack'll be mighty."
Will you look at us?
We're nothing but
a bunch of cut-price tinkers...
married to the road
and a bottle of booze.
I'm packing this in.
You really need to go careful
in this life.
You give up one kind of magic,
you find you need another.
Rather a waste. I was hoping
you'd bring the girl along.
There's bags of sewing
to be done.
And if she can sing as well...
I could sack Vonnie.
Tara.
Brendan?
I've told him the truth.
You're lying.
Why?
Why do you think, woman?
If you won't have me,
you'll have nobody.
Let me go.
I'll never let you go.
You're destroying my life,
Brendan.
I love you.
Get your hands off her.
Now, one of youse is a liar.
Which is it?
Tara?
You're out of your depth here.
Clear off.
I'm not asking you!
I'm asking her.
Tom...
Brendan, you're crucifying me.
We lay together
not fifty yards from here.
You offered yourself to me.
Show me the man
that could've refused.
I've kept your secret
from that night on...
because you begged me to.
It was
a beautiful summer's evening.
I was walking in the orchard.
When he first came here
from Dublin...
he was the most powerful man
I'd ever seen.
I didn't know then...
the way drink
had nearly ruined him...
nor the danger burning in him.
I was nervous of him...
but flattered...
so I laid down with him
on the grass.
A few weeks later,
I knew I was pregnant.
I was in turmoil.
When I told him,
he begged me to marry him.
I couldn't.
He promised
he'd keep the secret.
Then just before
the baby was born...
he started coming to me...
always in the dead of night...
like a hunter.
Then you should marry him, so.
I don't love him.
How could I spend my life
locked up in that barracks?
Him of all people.
To hell with it.
To hell with you, then!
It's our last night here
tomorrow night.
Where are you heading?
Tullyvin, then on to Dublin.
Could you give me a lift
to Dublin?
If I got you as far as Dublin,
you'd never get rid of me.
You've never been married?
No.
For who'd have me?
Maybe some poor soft idiot
with another man's child.
You know, kids don't scare me.
And if he's lonely,
I know how to get him...
a brother or sister
to keep him company.
This is Heaven.
And I never thought I'd make it.
It's not bad on a good day...
but it's no good on a bad day.
California...
now, that's the place for us.
The sun shines there
24 hours a day.
Dreamer.
It's a lucky woman
who catches a dreamer.
Why did you come back here, Tom?
From America.
Fate, I suppose.
Holy"-
Look out, we're sinking!
Let's go. I'm frightened.
Tara, come here.
No. We mustn't be
caught together, Tom.
Down by the lake.
Then into the hay with them.
Naked to the world. Aye.
Her hair spread out.
That's what you call the aerial.
Higher! Higher, man!
Up in the air,
where the pictures are!
A pint and a small one.
Huh?
Don't make a song and dance
about it.
There.
Look at that.
Holy God.
Didn't I tell you so?
Like a hound out of Hell.
Can you hear me,
creature of the darkness?
Yes, master.
Raise the needle.
Approach the subjects.
Flesh to flesh.
You powers
of light and dark...
invest this vestal creature...
with a gift that raises
mind above base matter.
For you,
there can be no rest...
until you have sewn
flesh unto flesh.
Begin!
Sew, creature, sew.
It's a fake.
It's candle wax or putty.
I wouldn't count on it.
No blood.
Light shall battle dark,
and dark shall be defeated!
Mrs. Smith?
I can see.
I can see!
That man is a miracle worker.
Nonsense. It's only a trick.
Mercy.
Sergeant,
will you do something?
Keep order, man.
She can see.
Thank you, sir. Bless you...
and reward you forever.
There'll be queues
at the box office...
for weeks to come.
He might have
a cure for the lumbago.
All out! All out!
See the greatest show
on earth!
Come along, everybody!
Come along, that's it!
Here we go!
The greatest show on earth!
I'm going
to shake his hand.
Freddie P. Fitzgerald!
As seen on screen and radio!
Come on!
Come along, everybody!
Touch the healer!
Touch the greatest healer
in the world!
Brigid,
did you find me other shoe?
I've come to see you
on official business.
That's...that's mine.
Give it back.
No. It's evidence.
I've committed no crime.
Your playboy has.
Last winter, he served
three months in Mountjoy Jail.
Liar. Last winter,
he was in America.
He's the liar.
I telephoned Dublin Castle,
and they checked up on him.
Three months
for bigamy and desertion.
You'll be going nowhere, girl...
not with my child.
Your child?
Marry me.
We could put in for a transfer.
We could set up house in Dublin,
if that's what you want.
Please leave us alone.
I can see the fright
in your eyes, girl.
Believe me...
you're not half as afraid of me
as I am meself.
Brendan...
I have no feelings for you.
You don't have to love me.
I love you.
Can't you see?
I just need you about the place.
I can't let you escape...
not with that fella.
Are you blind, woman?
He's a criminal.
A foul, dirty criminal.
Get out of my house.
God forgive me
for telling you...
but you must be saved.
There is a rational explanation
for everything on this earth...
unless God and the Church
declare otherwise.
What happened
to Mrs. Smith last night...
it was the cataracts
on her eyes falling off.
The artist
has a kind of power...
for good or ill...
but God's power is paramount.
There will be
an immediate procession...
of the Blessed Sacrament
throughout the village.
The hour of The Playboys
is past!
Henceforth, dear brethren...
frequent not dens of iniquity...
nor palaces of sin!
Let's go!
What the hell
are you playing at?
Don't move, you two!
You put the heart across me!
Where did
you get the explosives?
You could've
got yourselves killed!
The truth, boy!
The Playboys, sir!
We took it out of the caravan
when he wasn't looking.
Which one?
- You're a liar.
-Huh?
You've never been to America
in your entire life.
Last winter, you were in jail
in Dublin for bigamy.
What?
Who told you that?
Who do you think?
Tom, if you think
I'm going to gamble away...
my future
and my baby's future...
on a chancer like you,
you're mad!
I picked the wrong man
once before.
I'm not making
the same mistake again.
Wait, Tara.
Wait until I give you
the truth of it.
It was me brother
who committed the bigamy.
I just took the blame
for him.
Why?
So he could go back
to the wife and the kids...
the ones he left behind
in America.
You're full of cock and bull.
Tara, all you have to do
is ask anyone in Dublin.
I'm not in Dublin.
Is it Joe Cassidy you're after?
No. The other bloke.
Hold it. Hold it.
You're under arrest, man.
What's he done?
Possession of explosives,
offenses against the state.
Aw, codswallop!
Have you and the whole parish
gone mad entirely?
March.
I know why you're doing this.
Oh, yeah?
Out with it, then.
Come on, man.
You have the guts?
No one knows better
than yourself, Sergeant.
John-Joe, no.
It's about time he owned up.
There's your secret.
Move, you.
Your days are numbered, boy.
You'll be locked up
for ten years.
Conspiring to cause
an explosion...
membership of
an illegal organization...
endangering the lives
of innocent children.
He's your baby, Sergeant.
You're not fit to touch
the hem of her garment.
You and the other fella are
not wanted in me house anymore.
It's too risky altogether.
Go away, you,
you dirty dog!
What are we going to do
without Tom?
We're banjaxed.
He isn't an IRA man, is he?
Freddie, he's no more
an IRA man than I am.
This afternoon,
the entire company...
will visit
the nearest picture house.
Good thinking, Freddie.
We're not beat yet.
Can't you wait downstairs?
Father!
Now you listen to me, Tara.
My only concern...
is for the salvation
of that child's soul.
You must marry the sergeant.
He's the natural father.
Do you know what
I'm going to tell you?
You still owe me two quid
on that suit.
Out of my way.
Tara!
Come on. Come on!
- Beautiful.
-Oh, dear.
I wish I could see it
all over again.
You will tonight
when you're in it.
Will we get away with it,
I wonder?
A civil war
in this neck of the woods?
It'll go like a bomb.
Clearly, Vonnie must play
Scarlett O'Hara.
Rachel shall take the part of
the long-suffering Melanie.
In the regrettable absence
of poor Tom...
I myself will portray
Rhett Butler.
Freddie...
you're too old.
Cassidy...
will portray
the part of Rhett Butler.
I, myself...
will play...
as cast.
She's a little beauty, Tara.
If she ever left...
this place would be
as dead as a doornail.
Will they fetch enough
over the border...
to pay our way to America?
Will you hold your horses?
You and me
aren't through customs yet.
If you get caught,
your brother will take the rap.
Wait a minute, now.
It's the God's truth I told you.
He was desperate to see
his wife and kids in America.
I had to help him out.
Besides that, he slipped me
200 quid for me pains.
You lying bigamist.
Tonight only!
The world famous film
of "Gone With The Wind!"
Performed in person...
live on stage...
with The Playboys!
Adventure!
War! Romance!
Did you see that?
What's Cassidy
doing in the priest's car?
That's the least of our worries.
When did you last see the truck?
This is the customs patrol.
We're banjaxed.
Let me do the talking.
Customs.
Anything to declare?
Detective Constable
Freddie Fitzgerald...
Enniskillen.
We're transporting
a load of pigs.
Can I see your identification?
Rats...
the place is crawling with them.
Would you look
at the two of them?
It looks like somebody
is enjoying themselves.
Laughing eyes and curly hair
Singin' polly wolly doodle
all the day
Fare thee well, fare thee well
Fare thee well, my fairy fay
We're gain' to Louisiana
Eur to see my Susyanna
Singin' polly wolly doodle
all the day
A grasshopper sit-tin'
on a railroad track
Singin' polly wolly doodle
all the day
Pickin' his teeth
with a carpet tack
Singin' polly wolly doodle
all the day
Act spontaneous, can't you?
improvise.
There's Tom.
Thank God.
Cassidy's disappeared.
There's half a packed house
waiting out there.
- What are they waiting for?
-"Gone With The Wind."
Here, quick.
You're playing Clark Gable.
I can't play
everything myself, can I?
I haven't even seen the film!
It's the same as "Othello."
Boy meets girl
with a war going on.
If in doubt,
pretend to be wounded.
Where's that bastard Cassidy?
IRA business, I expect.
He is an idiot.
We'll still be on the road...
when their little squabble
is long forgotten.
Come on, get dressed.
Bring those clothes, quickly.
Ashley...
Ashley!
I'm going to marry Melanie.
Kiss me, Ashley.
You're not a gentleman, anyway.
And you're not a lady, either.
Oh, lawdy, lawdy.
Lawdy, lawdY!
Is you warm enough,
Miss Scarlett?
Why is all of them
fighting all the time?
They are fighting
for our freedom.
The freedom to be slaves?
Do I come on yet?
Strictly speaking, no...
but you may as well trot across.
I wasn't doing anything!
Jesus.
I thought it was me mummy.
Sergeant?
She won't leave without you,
me boyo.
For God's sake, man,
what are you--Jesus!
You go away! Go away!
So the saucy rebels said,
and 'twas a handsome boast
Had they not forgot, alas,
to reckon with the host
While we were marching
through Georgia
Hurrah, hurrah
We bring the jubilee
The flag that makes you free
So we sang the chorus
from Atlanta to the sea
While we were
marching through Georgia
To be quite honest, honey...
I don't give a twopenny damn.
He's stolen the baby!
Sergeant Hegalty,
he's stolen the baby!
There he is, Tara! There!
Sergeant!
Hand him over. Come on, man.
Move an inch,
and you'll be sorry.
Hand him over.
You'll all be sorry.
You'll be
sorry most of all, Tara.
I love you.
Please.
Brendan, whosoever harms
one of my little ones...
shall be cast into
everlasting fire.
For God's sake,
lads, will you stop it?
Right.
Yeah. That's it.
Come on.
If the passion of the people
could be bottled...
we could all of us
sail to the moon.
Come on! Get in there!
Come on, Sarge.
Come back to him.
Come back, come back.
Stop it, Brendan. Stop it!
Come on, Sergeant.
Get up, get up.
- Get up!
-Hit him, Tom!
Get up!
If I was sober, you'd be dead.
You'd be dead if I was drunk.
Give it up, Sarge.
Help me, can't you?
We came lighthearted.
Lighthearted we shall depart.
Thank you.
Good luck.
Allow me.
Fair lady, you're in the way.
I'm only going
as far as Dublin, mind.
That's what
I said when I joined.
Good-bye!
Bye!