*
Please,
think of your son.
[Gasping]
Baby, please.
Think of your son.
Hold it.
Hold down, baby.
Hold it down.
Please, baby.
Please think
of your son.
Come on, baby,
just... Please.
Please. Please.
Please, baby.
[coughs]
Baby, please.
You're OK. Please.
Please, no. Please.
Look at me.
Look at me, baby.
Look at me. OK.
I'm right here, OK?
I'm not gonna leave.
I'm sorry.
All right,
please just don't
leave me now.
Please, baby.
Please.
Baby, please.
No. No.
Hurry!
[knock on screen door]
WOMAN: Parole!
Open up!
Oh, shit. Shit.
What's up?
Get up.
What?
Shit.
Can't believe
those... these fuckers
found me.
Shut the...
Fuck.
[Pounds on door]
Parole!
Open the door!
They're knocking.
Just chill. Just get dressed.
I'm gonna stall 'em.
I'll stall 'em.
All good.
Just put your clothes on.
I'm gonna hop out
this window right now.
Fuck.
Don't even trip.
[Clanging]
Damn it. Shut the... Really?
God.
Told you to get rid
of that fucking thing.
Knock again, Webster.
I know he's in there.
I can smell him.
You know the drill.
[pounding]
Go! I got your back.
That's why
you're my bitch.
Heh.
Will you fuck me later?
What the fuck's
your problem?
Parole. Where's Kapone?
He isn't here,
you fucking bitch.
He's running!
Get out of my way.
Fuck you, cunt!
Parole!
Pacheco!
[Groans]
Pacheco! You're
only making this
worse for yourself!
[Panting]
[Dog barking]
[Gunshots]
[Officer panting]
We almost had him.
Never had anybody
get away from me
like that, nobody.
Used to be a track star.
He straight
outran your ass, man.
Fucking little Mexican
can run, huh?
What I tell you
about profanity
on the job, huh?
Keep it clean.
Sorry. It's a fucking habit,
all right?
Yo!
Yo, homey!
Hey!
Yo, what's your
fucking trip, fool?
Ha ha!
Yo, relax, little homey.
Had to make a quick exit.
From the cops?
Yeah, my dawg.
Yeah, those two knuckleheads
are my P.O.s.
They're trying
to take me back to do
a little stretch, dawggie.
I got your back
on this one, though.
Good looking, man.
Yo, you coming back
later?
Do a little
something-something
with my sister?
Tcch. What you know
about me and Baby Girl?
I can't help it.
All night,
I hear through
the damn wall,
"Oh, Kapone.
Fuck me good, papi.
Fuck me good."
Yeah, you shouldn't be
listening to that shit.
What are you,
a little pervert or what?
Yo, dawg, I got
plenty of bitches, too.
Hey, dawg.
Hey, don't call women bitches.
They don't like that shit.
All right,
point is I know how
to treat my women.
All right, all right.
Hey, well, peep this.
Don't tell anybody
you saw me.
I'm trying to keep
a low pro, all right?
[cell phone ringing]
Yo, like I said,
I got your back,
big dawg.
Good, good. Shit.
What now?
It's my P.O.
I'm gonna ignore his ass
Till I'm ready
to negotiate my freedom.
Hey, tell your sister
I'll be by later.
Yo, for sure.
I'll let her know.
All right?
Pacheco.
Who's this?
Who do you
think this is?
This is Ardmore.
I want you
to turn yourself in.
I ain't going
back to the joint,
Not right now.
Well, you should
have thought of that
Before you missed
3 meetings with me.
That's a direct
parole violation.
Mmm...
I've been busy.
Give me a break
on this one, Ardmore.
I don't give breaks,
Pacheco.
You know that.
Rules are rules.
Yeah, OK.
Fuck your rules.
Pacheco?
H-Hello?
Hang up on me.
Heh.
He's around here
somewhere.
Can you feel it?
Not really, but, hey,
knock yourself out.
He might be clever,
But I'm smarter.
Let's go.
Oh, shit. Hey,
what's up, big dawg?
Ah, shit. Get the fuck
out of my way, Georgie.
Hey, you got
a knickknack
on my sac, homey?
You fucked up, man?
What's the matter
With you, man?
I'm in a hurry.
Why you fucking
tripping, dawg?
Don't play me
like a bitch.
5-ball is all
I'm looking for.
I got Ardmore on my ass, man.
What'd I just say?
You're fucked.
I hate fucking Ardmore.
He's a fucking bitch.
Exactly, so I gotta
get the fuck out of here.
Nah, nah, but trip out,
homey. Hey.
Let me get some, dawg.
Break me off before
you roll, player.
Dawg, you keep
your fucking hands
off of me, all right?
Hey, come on, man.
We're boys, dawg.
Hey, man,
what'd I just say, man?
Man, can't you see
I'm hurting?
Yeah, you hurting
'cause you a dope fiend.
That's on you, not me.
I'm out.
Man, don't fucking
judge me.
You ain't shit, Kapone.
Motherfucker,
you gonna learn, bitch.
You'll get yours,
motherfucker.
[Winces]
I had a feeling
I was going to be
tested today.
What happened
to all this big talk
About we're gonna get him
by the end of the day?
Tested doesn't mean
defeated, Webster.
We'll see about that.
You're forgetting
I haven't lost one yet.
Well, if you ask me...
I didn't ask you.
I will have
Pacheco in custody
by the end of the day.
That's guaranteed.
[Dog barks]
[Dogs barking]
Hey, who the fuck is that?
No one.
What the fuck?
It's me.
Kapone?
Yeah, dawg.
Ah, shit.
My bad, homey.
What the fuck's
the matter with you?
Fuck, homey, I just...
I been up for,
like, 3 days, dawg.
Just spun
like a motherfucker.
You're tripping hard,
dawg.
Yeah, my bad, homey.
Fucking... You want
to take a blast?
Nah, dawg. I don't do...
I don't do that shit.
Fucking-A. Hey, man,
There's somebody
after me, homey.
Who?
I don't know, homey.
I... I been seeing him
a lot, eh.
I don't know who the fuck
it is, though.
Marcos,
it's in your head, man.
Nobody's following you.
All right, man. I'm out.
Fuck. Hey, homey, homey.
Hold on. Hey.
Hey, you don't want
To just chill
and kick it for a...
I'm gonna take
a quick hit, fool.
Nah, dawg.
I got my P.O. after me.
I gotta get the fuck
out of here.
Come on, homey.
Hey, man...
Stop that shit.
Fucking ranker.
How are you, huh,
little boy?
Want this football?
Yeah.
Yeah, take it.
Come on.
There's your mommy
right there. How are you?
Oh, now you
decide to show up.
Huh?
Where you been?
Hey, relax, Marisela.
Don't start with me.
I was with my homeboys.
All fucking night?
That's bullshit.
You were probably
With your
damn tramp,
fucking Baby Girl.
I'm not stupid.
Hey, relax.
She's just a friend,
all right?
You're gonna
make Junior cry.
[Coos]
[Dog barking]
Hello? Excuse me.
Yeah, now what's up,
motherfucker?
Do you know
this address?
[Exhales]
Oh, snap.
Fucking Marcos.
Freeze!
WEBSTER:
Fucking hands up now!
ARDMORE:
Don't move, Georgie!
Let's get over here
to the car.
I-I didn't shoot
that bitch, homey.
[Speaking Spanish]
Get on the car.
Put your hands
on the car.
Slowly.
Nice and easy,
Georgie.
What woman are you
talking about,
Georgie?
That bitch laying
back behind that car
over there.
Yeah?
What happened
to her?
I don't know.
I just ran up
on this shit, man.
Yeah? You get it?
I'm gonna go
check this out.
Got any weapons
on you, Georgie?
Nah. Hell, nah.
Nothing sharp
in your pockets?
Nope.
You know
your parole officer
came through
Looking for you
earlier?
Go play, baby.
Yeah, I know.
They want me
to turn myself in.
Again?
When are you gonna
learn you're not
a little boy anymore?
Why?
Don't you think I know that?
No, I don't
think you do.
You're in and out
of jail all the time.
I'm done with this shit.
I'm tired.
It's fucking hard
out there, all right?
And I'm trying.
Not hard enough.
Are you gonna
turn yourself in?
Eventually,
when I'm ready.
Yeah, you're good
with your damn
cat-and-mouse games.
[Sighs]
I'm fucking over
this shit already.
Listen, I got
a lot of stuff I gotta
take care of right now,
Real important shit.
It's just not the time
for me to turn myself in,
So right now I just...
I just need you
to have my back, OK?
No. You know what? No.
Get out! Leave, OK?
I don't need
fucking cops coming in
And waking my son up
in the middle
of the night, OK?
I have a son to raise.
Oh, what, and I don't?
Just leave.
Just leave
before my mom comes.
She doesn't want you
here anymore.
Oh, it's like that?
Yeah,
it's like that.
Get used to it.
Is it bad?
Not good. Dead woman.
This isn't
a good situation,
Zambrano.
I didn't do shit.
I'm gonna call this in.
Wait a minute.
OK, Georgie...
What'd you see?
I didn't see shit.
I just ran up
on this shit.
I didn't even
have a fucking gun.
Yeah, yeah.
I got that part
already.
I want to know
the nitty-gritty,
The juicy part.
I want to know
what you saw.
I know
you saw something.
I didn't see shit. No.
No, huh?
Nah.
You're not giving me
the truth here, Georgie.
You know I only operate
from truth, pure truth.
And I ain't lying.
I'm telling you the truth.
Let me see your eyes.
I said let me
see your eyes.
Let me see your eyes.
Man, quit trying to do
that fucking voodoo shit
on me, dawg.
[Breathes deeply] No.
See?
Truth is in there.
I could see it.
You need to release it
to me, Georgie.
Man, fuck you, man.
You'll feel a lot better.
Give me a name,
I'll let you walk.
Just like that?
Yeah, just like that.
And you ain't
gonna violate my parole?
For what?
You didn't do this,
right?
Hell, no.
Nah.
Nope.
It's greater good here.
You know
what I'm saying?
Believe in
the greater good,
don't you?
Yeah. Yeah, I believe
in the greater good.
That's what I thought.
Why don't you
call this in now?
Ahh. Hey, quit yanking
on my shit, man.
Quiet, sir.
What the fuck, man?
Ahh! Gotta make things
fucking hurt?
Hold on. Hold on.
Shit!
Man, it's...
I'm gonna fucking
get a lawyer.
I'm gonna sue
you guys, eh?
Yo, dawg.
It's cool?
Hollywood,
I've known you
for a long time,
And you know I don't
cosign for anyone.
I just want it
to be clear
That if you get
this opportunity,
There's
no turning back.
You know that, right?
Heh.
I know.
What the fuck
do you think you know?
'Cause you
don't know shit.
Get those
fucking gloves
off my table.
What you should know
Is that if you
fuck this shit up,
I'll send for you.
So make sure you
don't regret this day.
Is that clear?
Loud and clear.
Familia, we got
a good deal on the table.
Good family involved.
Good for us.
You guys know the deal.
I already ran it
by you all,
And I say we do it.
Yea? Nay?
How many yeas?
Say yea.
Yea.
Sure.
Let's do it.
HOLLYWOOD:
Vámonos.
[Dog barking]
Hey, how'd
the cops know it was
my little brother, huh?
Someone dropped a dime,
homey.
Got a snitch.
Well, you gotta
find out what's up.
I'm on it, homey.
'Cause I'll tell you
straight out, dawg.
We got a snitch,
we gotta take him out.
or what?
Hey, we would have heard
if anyone was talking.
[Speaking Spanish]
You know what, homey?
Nobody in our hood's
Gonna be talking
to the placa, ¿no?
[Deep breath]
You call yourself O.G.?
You guys don't know shit.
You better fucking show me
something real soon, homey,
'Cause right now,
you guys make me
fucking sick.
You know what,
homey?
My primo was
in the alley
When the coroner
picked up the body.
Maybe he
saw something.
We should
go ask him.
Orale.
All right.
And when you do,
let's find that vato
And take him out.
[speaking Spanish]
Yeah. That's what
I'm talking about.
What's up, dude?
What's up?
Looks great.
All right, dawg.
Hey, hold up. Hold up.
Hold up. Hold up.
What's up, Ghost?
Your cousin Eddie Boy
told me you were
In the alley when they
smoked that bitch.
Yeah, blood everywhere.
Shit was nasty.
You see anyone
talking to the cops?
Not really.
Everybody around here
Knows better
than to do that.
You sure about that?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
I mean,
Georgie was there,
But his P.O. had him
and then let him go.
Georgie.
Yeah, that fool's
Always in the alley
shooting it up.
All right,
little homey.
You did good.
Get the fuck
out of here.
What the fuck's
your problem, dawg?
Shut the fuck up.
Hey, homey, what
do you know about
my little brother?
I don't know shit
about Marcos, man.
Hmm.
Why you asking me?
Because my little
brother's sitting
In a jail cell
right now, dawg.
Some little motherfucker
ratted his ass out.
That's why
I'm asking you.
I'm one of the O.G.s
from this clique,
And you know that.
You ain't nothing
but a dope fiend
to me, ese.
Hey, dawg, don't...
don't fuck around
like that.
Y-You know
I wouldn't do that shit.
Let me blast
this bitch.
Hey, Ghost,
hold up, man.
Let him talk.
Wait up.
You know what?
I know who did it.
Hey, little brother.
Hey, what's up?
Yeah, what's up?
Get me out of here.
Yeah, don't worry
about it, all right?
Gonna get you a lawyer
and hook you up,
But I gotta ask you
a question.
Did you see, uh,
Georgie or Kapone today?
I just saw Kapone, eh?
I only saw Kapone.
Ah. OK.
Well,
check it out, homes.
You know not to say
anything inside,
all right?
Yeah, don't tell them
who does nothing.
I won't say shit
in here.
All right.
All right, man.
You stay strong,
all right?
All right. Later.
Al rato.
So what's up,
homey? We letting
this fucker go or what?
Nah, not yet.
What happened?
Well, Marcos said
that Kapone was around.
I don't think Kapone's
about that, homes.
[Scoffs]
People get desperate
When they're
facing time, homey.
Kapone just buckled,
dawg.
He's a peewee.
[laughs]
[Chuckles]
I tell you what.
I'll be right back,
But for now,
you keep an eye
on him, all right?
* Oh, shit, I only
got 9 hours left... *
"Peewee." Heh.
* ...to see my kids
* And hopefully
with no drama *
* 'Cause she's a bitch
* Fucking bitch
* Damn, we started arguing
* Fuck
* I only got 6 hours left
* So I hugged the kids,
Angel and Bams *
* Told 'em to be strong
* And to be more than I was
and that I am *
* And to always
take care of their mom *
* Even if they resent her
for doing their dad wrong *
* Oh, shit...
What's up, Rudy?
What's up, Crow?
I'm looking
for Kapone, ese.
He ain't around right now.
Come on, now.
I know he comes around
to visit your sister.
All right.
He actually told me
not to say shit,
But I think
he meant the cops.
You one of the homeys,
so you cool, right?
Yeah, you're good,
homey. What's up?
He's on the run right now,
Something about his parole
Hitting up his cellphone
to negotiate his freedom.
[Chuckles]
Is that right?
You positive
about that?
Yeah, I'm positive.
OK.
All right.
* ...all this gangster
in me to give *
* I got so much gangster
to give *
* With only 13 hours
to live *
* Roll up and get
my brother Smiley *
* 'Cause you know I gotta
have him right beside me *
* We're Heckle
and Jeckle... *
Get the fuck
out of here, man.
Go. Get up.
I told
you fuckers...
Get the fuck
out of here, eh!
What's up, homey?
Kapone's the rat, ese.
I found out
from Little Rudy.
But Rudy's a kid, homey.
You trust him?
Yeah, I don't
give a fuck, man.
He's not
gonna lie to me.
I'm telling you.
Kapone's name
keeps coming up, homey,
So it's up to you,
big dawg.
All right, we're gonna
bring in Sick and Blind
on this one.
I don't know, homey.
Think they're soft.
That's all right, ese.
It's time for them
to put in some work.
WOMAN: Hey, you hear
about the party
on the weekend?
Who, Maria's?
Yeah, that bitch.
Fuck Maria.
You know what she did?
She tried hollering
at my man Carlos.
She gets
at every fine dick.
Do you know what she did
to Jennifer, though?
Who? What'd she do?
She fucked her man.
[Scoffs] I believe it.
That fucking bitch.
I swear to God, I...
Uhh! I wish
I could have her...
Like fucking choke
her ass, but I can't.
You'll get
your taste of dick
around here.
I know.
Fucking dick lover.
You know
how she is already.
Slut.
[laughs]
I know.
Let's get some beer.
Hey, there's Kapone.
What the fuck is
that little bitch
doing here?
Fucking rat.
Let's get him.
Fuck this bitch.
What's up?
Bitch, I heard
you snitched.
Yeah, you fucking bitch.
Yeah.
Heard you're
a fucking snitch
on the street.
You should get
the fuck out of here.
What the fuck are you crazy
bitches talking about?
You know what
we're talking about.
Get the fuck out of here!
Get that
motherfucker!
[Dog barking]
What's up, Crow?
What's up is I need you
to put in some work,
eh, the both of you.
What's up, dawg?
Kapone, eh,
he ratted out Marcos.
Man, that's fucked up,
homey.
What you want us to do?
I want you
to take him out, homes.
It's as simple
as that, all right?
Man, you want us
to take out
our own homeboy?
Kapone's making us
look weak,
And we ain't weak.
Hell, nah.
We gotta
do something
strong, dawg.
Now, you two are
the motherfuckers
I want on it, all right?
Hey, homeys,
you already know, dawg,
I'm down for the hood.
That's what's up.
What about you, Blind?
You in?
Man, you sure
Kapone's a rata?
Yeah.
I checked it out myself.
Yeah. I'm in.
What the fuck
you still doing here?
Get the hell out of here.
Let's roll, eh?
Thanks, babe.
Hey, papi.
[Sighs]
You don't have to buy
groceries for me, hija.
I can shop for myself.
Cup O' Noodles
at the liquor store's
Not really
buying groceries.
I'm just saying
I can take care
of myself.
Dad, I like
to take care of you.
[Kisses] OK?
[Sighs]
You still seeing him?
Daddy, don't start.
I told you he ain't
the guy for you.
I love him, papi.
He loves me.
That's all that matters.
That's what you think.
Daddy, you know,
you forget that...
That Mom wasn't
the person you thought
she was either.
That was different.
No.
It was the carga
that made her
act that way.
No. Stop making excuses
for her.
She made us both suffer.
That's the point.
I don't want you
to suffer.
Dad, what's so bad
about Ghost?
Mija,
He's not the man
you think he is.
Well, you know,
We've all done bad things.
Right, Dad?
Hey, fool...
What's up?
Check this shit out,
dawg.
Oh, whose is that?
It's my cousin
Crow's gun, dawg.
He gots lots of 'em.
I can get it
anytime I want, fool.
Let me hold it,
Fernie.
Handle that.
Bah! Bah!
Heh heh.
It's fucking bad, dawg.
I wish I had
one of these, though.
Hey, whenever you want
to borrow it, fool,
Just let me know, dawg.
For sure?
Yeah, yeah, fool.
Heater me, dawg.
Man, what the fuck
are you gonna
do with that?
What the fuck you think
I'm gonna do with it?
I'm gonna blast someone
with it.
You ain't got the balls
to do that, homes.
What?!
You heard me, dawg.
I don't have
the what?
Hey, homey, hey,
keep the fuck
back, homey.
Hey, man...
I don't give a fuck.
I'll blow this bitch away.
Hey, keep back.
Kick it, eh?
Dare me.
Go ahead.
Dare me, homeboy.
Bah!
Punk bitch.
Hey, dawg.
I heard Kapone snitched
on one of the homeboys,
fool.
He wouldn't do that
to his own, fool.
Shut the fuck up
before I slap you, dawg.
Hey, fool,
I heard Crow telling
the other homeboys
He gave up Marcos, fool.
That's some straight-up
bullshit, dawg.
I don't believe that.
Hey, fool, they want
his ass dead, dawg.
Straight-up bullshit, dawg.
I'm gonna go ahead.
I'm telling you
what the homeys
told me, fool.
You heard wrong, dawg.
FERNIE:
Where you going, dawg?
Just kick back, fool.
Yo, fuck the both of you.
I'm out of here, eh.
Hey, that's
one crazy vato, eh?
Almost pissed
my fucking pants,
homeboy.
You're a fool, dawg.
[Dogs barking]
Man, this shit don't
feel right to me, ese.
Kapone ain't a rat.
I just know it.
He's always been
a straight-up vato with me.
No wonder why they
call your ass Blind.
Man,
I'm just saying, raza,
One day,
you're a fucking hero,
And the next,
you're a rata.
That shit don't make
no fucking sense to me.
Don't even need
to make sense.
¿Qué no?
Kapone.
What's up with you, dawg?
Damn crazy bitches
just tried
To rush me
at the liquor store.
I thought you said
not to call girls bitches.
Nah, trust me,
these bitches
were bitches.
Yo, I'm looking for you.
They're after you, man.
They say you're a rat.
Wait. A rat?
Who said that?
Fernie.
He was ear hustling,
Overheard his cousin Crow
talking about you,
That you gave Marcos up
to the cops.
What the fuck is
happening around here?
Didn't you hear?
Marcos shot up the lady
in the morning.
See, I knew that fucker
was gonna flip out.
Y-Yo, you ain't no rat,
though, right?
Nah. Course not.
All right. I got you.
Pull over at this house.
Pacheco sometimes
hangs out here.
This should be fun.
Um, Webster, wait.
Take off
your safety.
[Car door closes]
What's up, pig?
You sure you want
To roll up
in here like that?
[Sighs] We're
looking for Kapone.
Kapone who?
One of
your homeboys.
He ain't one
of our homeboys.
So you haven't seen him?
Hey, we're looking
for him, too, ese.
Well, if you find him,
Tell him to turn
himself in to Parole.
I don't think
he's gonna be around
much longer.
What do you
mean by that?
You know what time
it is, pig,
So if you ain't gonna
take nobody to jail,
Why don't you get
the fuck out of here?
You guys have
a nice day.
Yeah, fuck you, too.
Yeah, yeah.
Get the fuck out of here.
We said
get the fuck
out of here.
Hey,
you could stay.
Why come
around here for?
Yeah, you could stay.
Come here.
What the fuck?
Something's
not right here.
They definitely
had something
against Kapone.
What do you think?
I don't know.
But I bet you
our boy Georgie has
something to do with this.
Heh. That guy would
give up his own mother.
You know it.
Look how he sang with us.
[Heart beating]
[Gunshot]
Fuck, homey!
Fucking
bitch-ass Kapone.
Fuck. Shit.
He got away.
Let's get the fuck
out of here.
Let's roll, dawg.
Come on.
Yo, fucking hood rat,
dawg.
Fucking murky as fuck.
I'm fucking pissed,
homey.
[Birds chirping]
Yo, dawg, not you, too.
Motherfucker, you scared me.
What's up, fool?
Man, what's up, Fresco?
- Hey, dawg, have you heard?
- Heard what?
Everybody in the hood's
tripping on me, homey.
What the fuck
you talking about?
All the homeboys, man.
They're trying
to take me out.
Yeah, Sick and Blind
shot at me in the alley.
Are you fucking with me?
Nah, man. Wish I was.
Nah, they think
I'm a rat.
My name's all over
the walls, 187.
What the fuck did you do?
I didn't do
a damn thing.
Have you talked to any
of the other homeboys?
Nah. Hell, nah, man.
Who am I gonna trust?
[Scoffs]
Man, if I was you,
I'd go talk to Wizard.
That motherfucker knows
everything that goes down.
Yeah, no shit.
Wizard, man.
Yeah, maybe he knows
what the fuck's
going on,
'Cause I sure
as hell don't.
I'm out.
All right, my boy.
Here, dawg.
Take this shit.
You might need it.
What? Nah, man.
You know that ain't me.
[Scoffs]
It's a violent world,
homeboy.
Yeah, but I ain't
a violent man.
[Siren blaring]
[Siren continues]
I know you ain't no rat.
I taught you better.
I'd never drop a dime
on my homeboys,
Never.
I know you
ain't about that,
But the neighborhood's
gonna believe
Whatever the fuck
they want to believe.
How in the fuck
did this happen?
I'm hearing it started
with Georgie.
Georgie?
Yeah. The word is
he put you at the scene.
Fucking weasel.
He did me dirty.
I gotta find him
so he can clear me.
That ain't
gonna happen.
We're talking
about a fucking
dope fiend here.
He's only
out for himself.
He don't give
a rat's ass
about you.
I gotta do something.
The only thing
you gotta do right now
Is stay alive.
* I don't give a fuck
whose life I'm taking *
* I'm not thinking about
the mistakes I'm making *
* I'm about to be
a thing of the past... *
It's such a waste.
I don't understand
Pacheco.
Such a bright guy,
but he keeps
Placing his energies
in the wrong place.
Why?
He's just a thug
up to no good.
No. There's more
to him than just
the average gangbanger.
I mean, you remember
the time he came in
for his drug test
With the rubber penis
strapped against
his thigh?
[Scoffs] Yeah.
That was fucking disgusting.
Disgusting, but smart.
Don't fool yourself,
Ardmore.
You don't see it?
They're all the same to me.
Hey, Mom.
What do you want?
Can I come in?
No. I told you
I didn't want you
coming here anymore.
Yeah, I know.
I just...
I need some help.
I need some money.
I need
to leave town.
¿Qué te pasa?
What's wrong?
Are you in trouble again?
We're supposed
to be family, right?
Your gang is
your familia, remember?
You left me
a long time ago for them.
I never left.
That's what you think.
So tell me,
where's your gang
now, huh, mijo?
Where's your gang life now?
I'm sorry, son.
No te puedo ayudar.
I can't help you.
I can't help you, mijo.
I can't.
Whacking Kapone is gonna
make us look good. Watch.
Man, who gives a fuck
about looking good, ese?
Kapone's always been
a straight-up vato
with me.
Don't even matter,
though, homey.
Today's Kapone's last day.
I'm telling you.
Man, this shit
ain't right, ese, no.
Kapone ain't
no fucking rat,
dude. Shit.
I got all kind
of crazy shit
Rolling in my head
right now, dawg.
I don't know
what the fuck to think.
You ain't gotta think,
homey.
All you gotta do
is get the shit done.
Now that's
just the fucking
thing, perro.
We're like little
fucking puppets.
Just 'cause
they tell us
we gotta jump off
And do something,
we gotta do it?
And what's
fucking me up,
They got us killing
our own homeboy.
What kind of shit
is that?
"What kind
of shit is that?"
Now you sounding like
a fucking pussy, homey.
Man, fuck you, Sick.
Man, fuck you, homey.
Stop being a bitch,
And let's get
this shit done, dawg,
Straight up.
What's up, Blind?
You with it
or what, homey?
Whatever, motherfucker.
Gotta do it.
[Hip-hop playing]
There he is, dawg.
There he is.
Man, what the fuck?
Look at all the damn kids!
Run!
Pull it up, bitch!
Gonna fucking hit somebody!
[Gunshots]
WOMAN: Matthew!
Matthew!
Matthew! Papi!
Oh, my God!
Somebody help me!
[dogs barking]
Papi, wake up.
[Sirens blaring]
Ay, mi hijo.
Help me!
Papi.
Papi. Help!
[Sobbing]
Help me!
Matthew!
[Man pants]
Fuck, homey.
Shit, dawg.
My body's getting colder,
homeboy.
But fuck it, homes?
* I got 13 hours to live
* What will I do with all
this gangster in me to give? *
* I got
so much gangster to give *
* With only 13 hours
to live *
* I got 13 hours to live
* What will I do with all
this gangster in me to give? *
* I got
so much gangster to give... *
Stop the car.
Park it! Park it!
Park it!
Don't move, Pacheco!
Don't even think
about it, Pacheco.
ARDMORE:
Don't move!
Ardmore, they'll
kill me in there.
I won't
last a week in Chino,
and that'll be on you.
WEBSTER:
Now, motherfucker!
Don't be stupid,
Pacheco.
WEBSTER:
Walk over here,
And put your hands
on the hood.
I'm better off dead.
Move your ass!
Come on.
You got any weapons
on you?
Cuff him.
Put your hands
on your head.
She said
put your hands
on your head!
Oh. Ooh.
Ah, yeah, baby.
That's tight.
Ah, yeah.
That's good.
Feels good.
You like when a man
tells you what to do?
Fuck you.
Shut up.
Heh. Don't you two have
anything better else to do?
I ain't no murderer.
No, but you like
to steal, Pacheco.
That's why you're
on parole, isn't it?
Actually, I don't steal.
I borrow things,
And then I return 'em,
like a library book.
Heh.
You're a funny guy.
Yeah, I try.
I told you I was gonna
catch you, didn't I?
That's cool. It's cool.
I understand. Yeah.
Hey, but before you
throw me in the car,
You want to hear a joke?
[Chuckles]
All right.
Go for it.
Better be funny.
The circus elephant
Is bothering
a group of ants,
So the ants climb
on the elephant's back
And begin biting him
to death.
The elephant gets pissed,
And he tosses off
all the little ants,
Except for one.
This one poor
little, tiny ant
Manages to grab on
to the elephant's throat.
He looks down
at the other little ants,
And they're all
yelling at him,
"Jump! Jump!
Don't do it!"
And this poor
little, tiny ant says,
"Nah, I think
I can choke him to death."
Heh.
"Choke him to death."
[Sighs] Oh, I get it.
Little ant,
big elephant.
Yeah.
It's actually
quite humorous, Pacheco.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know what else
is humorous?
What's that?
What the fuck?
Pacheco!
Why...
This is your fault.
Hey, I didn't know
We were dealing with
gangster Houdini here.
Come on, Webster.
Take some responsibility.
If you would have
just secured his cuffs
like I told you to,
We'd have him
in custody by now.
I did secure 'em.
He squeezed
right through them.
Because you're incompetent.
Hey, come on, man.
Stop worrying about
Your stupid perfect
fucking record.
I take my job seriously.
Maybe you should, too.
Who the fuck do you
think you are?
You're just some
sorry-ass parole officer
That thinks
he's perfect.
Get out of my face,
Webster.
Or else what?
You gonna
write me up?
Do it.
What do you want?
Marisela,
I need your help.
I already told you
just leave me alone.
Listen to me.
Everybody's
after me.
Who's after you?
Everybody.
My homeboys,
The neighborhood,
everybody.
Your own homeboys?
They're trying
to pin me as a snitch.
How'd that happen?
Look, I don't have
time to explain
All the details
right now.
It's not safe
for me here.
I have to leave town.
Can you help me? Please.
I told you already
I'm done with you.
[Car engine approaching]
ARDMORE:
Lieutenant.
Ardmore. Webster.
So what's going on
with Pacheco?
Yeah, we have
some good intel
on him, sir.
He should still be
in the neighborhood.
I know he's
I'm not
asking you to search
the whole state for him.
He's a pretty
slippery guy, sir.
Well, we need to find
something on him.
Let me know if
we gotta put another
apprehension team up.
Sir, you don't
have to do that.
We'll have him in custody
by the end of the day.
I need to see
some of that college
athleticism, Ardmore.
We'll get him.
You know
how you asked me
Why I didn't
turn myself in?
What about it?
My father's
really sick right now.
I had to miss
three parole appointments.
I was the one
taking my dad
to his treatments.
Who else
was gonna do it?
And I don't want
to be behind bars
when he dies.
Why didn't you
say anything?
You always
keep everything inside.
That's just me.
Let me call my sister.
Maybe you could stay
with her for a while
in Bakersfield.
I'll call you later
and let you know.
I appreciate what
you're doing for me.
I'm not doing it for you.
I'm doing it
for your son.
[Sighs]
You know, uh...
This guy, he, uh...
Goes to the barber
for his monthly haircut,
Gets in the chair,
and tells his barber,
"I want two quarter-sized
bald spots on my right side"
And, uh, three on my left
"And one in the back."
Barber looks at him,
like... like he's crazy,
You know, looks at him
in disbelief, saying,
"I can't give you
a haircut like that."
The guy says,
"Well, why not?"
You been giving me
the same damn haircut
for the past 10 years.
"Only thing is
I haven't told you."
[Chuckling]
You know what's funny?
What?
You actually thought
that joke was funny.
* Can you tell me
what's left for a soldier? *
Let's go get Kapone.
* Can you tell me
what's left for a soldier? *
* Tell me
what's left for me *
* Is he still brave
* When he's in his grave
* Does he hear a damn
when it's over? *
GHOST: So what's
the story, homeboy?
Got away.
What you mean
he got away?
[Sighs]
It was
this fucker, man.
We could have
got at Kapone, but
this fool's driving
Like a straight
little bitch, dawg.
Homey,
I was on that fool.
Is that right, Blind?
Why don't you
talk to me, homey?
Nothing, man.
I... I was...
I was driving
the best I could,
But there was kids
all over the place,
man. I...
Yeah? So?
I don't want to run
the kids over or nothing.
Shoot...
You didn't want to what?
Heh.
Showing weakness, homey.
Weakness, dawg?
What the fuck you
want from me, ese?
I want you to take out
Kapone's old man.
That's what I want.
Take out a dying man?
That's some dirty shit,
homey.
Well, we gotta
do something strong
For the hood.
You feel me?
You make me sick,
homey. Just do it.
You know what?
Fuck this shit, ese.
I'm done with this shit.
You motherfuckers
sit around
Telling us what to do,
kill this guy,
kill that guy.
Why don't
you motherfuckers
go and do it?
You kill
these motherfuckers.
I'm done.
[Chuckles]
You know,
I like you, homey.
Renegade motherfucker,
Nobody tells you
what to do.
You're your own person,
right?
Heh. Remind me of me
back in the days.
Heh. I like that.
I like that so much,
I'm gonna give you a drink.
[Gagging]
Fuck.
[Panting]
What do you
want to do with
the body, homey?
Burn him.
OK.
Yo, sick,
You go with Ghost.
Me?
Yeah, you, ese.
Why, you got
a problem with that?
Nah, nah.
I ain't got no problem.
Heh. Attagirl.
Let's go.
Take care of that.
[Music playing]
[Birds chirping]
Hey, babe.
Hey, baby.
Ready to go?
Yeah.
Um...
I want to ask you
something, OK?
What's up?
And I want you
to tell me the truth.
Heh. I already told you
I wasn't fucking that bitch.
She's just my friend.
Baby, no, come on.
I'm over that shit.
Then what's up?
Have you ever
killed someone?
Come on, man.
What kind of shit is that?
Just be honest, OK?
Tell me the truth.
Oh. It's your old man.
He's talking shit
again, huh?
Baby, h-he worries
about me.
He needs to mind
his own fucking business.
Just answer
the question.
Have you
killed anyone?
Man, what the fuck's
it matter, man?
[Sighs]
Come here.
What? What?
Fucking come here!
Baby, what the fuck?
Let me go.
Yeah, I've killed fools.
So fucking what?
Let me go.
You're hurting me.
Shut the fuck up.
Yeah, now you know.
What you gonna do about it?
Nothing.
I just want to leave.
Oh, now you want
to fucking leave me?
No, I didn't say that!
But you thinking it, right?
No.
Listen to me. If you ever
try to fucking leave me,
I don't give a fuck
where you are or
who you're with.
I'll kill you, bitch.
You understand me?
Yeah.
Don't fucking touch me.
You hear anything?
[Sighs]
It's not looking good.
What is it?
It's Victor.
What, my old man?
What about him?
He's not safe
anymore, mijo.
Man, no, man.
Don't tell me that.
Wizard, man, he's dying.
I know that.
But Crow's pissed,
And he wants
to flush you out.
The way he sees it,
You fucked up
his family,
So now he wants
to fuck up yours.
How can my own gang,
my own people do this to me?
These fools don't give
a fuck about nobody.
I learned that lesson
the hard way...
When I got shot.
And I was
in the hospital
lying there, paralyzed.
You think
any of the homeboys
came to visit me?
Not one.
It was my Evita
Cleaning up after me
when I'd wake up
In the middle
of the night
in a cold sweat
After pissing
all over my bed.
And then
I got locked up.
Eight years.
You think the homeboys
sent me any money
Or packages to survive?
Or even accepted
my collect phone calls?
Fuck, no.
At the end of the day,
mijo...
The only ones who really
give a fuck about you,
Who really care
Are your familia.
I gotta go.
Keep trucha.
Don't trust anybody.
* ...gangster to give
* With only 13 hours
to live *
* Roll up and get
my brother Smiley *
* 'Cause you know I gotta
have him right beside me *
* We're Heckle and Jeckle
* Coyote to Wile E.
* Enough talking
* I'm literally
a dead man walking *
* And I'm walking
to the police station *
* Start aiming, putting bullets
in their brains *
* Till there's
no heartbeats remaining *
* 'Cause I don't give a fuck
whose life I'm taking... *
Johnny.
Oh, Johnny,
So good to see you.
Oh, my God.
Hi, Grandma.
I miss you so much.
I'm so glad
you're here.
Smells good, Grandma.
Oh, yes, good.
Here.
[Sighs]
Let me make you
something to eat.
Nah, I'm OK. I'm fine,
Just thirsty.
I'll take some water.
Sure. Coming up.
Here we go.
There you go, sweetie.
Thanks.
[Sighing]
You look so much
like your father.
Has anybody been by
to visit him?
Nobody,
Only you, sweetie.
Is he getting worse?
A lot of pain.
Yeah. How much longer?
[Sighs]
I don't know.
I want to see him.
I haven't seen you
for a while.
I was here two days ago,
remember?
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
Hey, I was just coming
around to tell you that
I won't be around
for a while.
Are you in trouble again?
No, not this time.
I'm doing real good
right now.
How's your son?
He's big.
He looks like you.
Be there for him always,
Not like me.
Yeah, we don't need
to talk about that
right now.
No, I'm sorry
I hurt you so much.
Yeah.
Yeah, you did.
It's OK.
It's OK, Pop.
[Sighs]
Mijo, I'm so tired.
Yeah,
I know you're tired.
You OK?
Nah, I'm not OK.
It's like
the Wild, Wild West.
They're shooting up
the hood trying
to track you down.
I got nothing left.
Hey, dawg, I... I need
to ask you something.
This is
between me and you.
Ain't nobody
gotta know about this.
You got my word.
What is it?
Did you
drop dime on Marcos?
What do you think?
I just need
to know for sure.
You've known me
since we were kids.
It's all good.
Forget about it.
Forget
I said anything.
We cool?
Yeah, we cool.
Like I said, I just
needed to know for sure.
Well, now you know.
Have you heard anything?
They want to kill my dad.
Who told you that?
Wizard.
[Scoffs]
Man.
That's some crazy shit.
Yeah, Crow's not
fucking around.
It's like
one fucked-up nightmare.
Take the fucking gun.
Nah, man.
That ain't me.
You know that.
[Sighs]
You gotta forget
what happened to you.
You gotta
let that shit go.
I can't let it go.
You sure about that?
Yeah.
I'm sure.
Take the fucking gun,
Kapone.
Please.
* Hold your head up high
* Yeah
* Come on, man, yo
* Royalty is what it is
* I'll be the one to lead
* My people
straight across that bridge *
* We gonna get it,
we don't have to... *
Baby, I'm scared.
Nah, we're good.
But I got no choice.
I gotta leave town.
Can you help me?
All I got
is about $80.
It's yours, baby. Heh.
You're the best,
Baby Girl.
Fuck me before you go.
No.
I gotta get going.
Let me suck your dick
real quick.
No. No.
I gotta go.
But I'll
remind you later.
[Groans]
What's up, Rudy?
What's up,
little homies?
You OK?
Yeah, I'm all right.
Fuck that fool, man.
I'm sorry you got
caught up in this.
Guess you're right.
Fools got me so mad,
Just wish I had a gun
to blast all them fools.
I don't want to hear you
talk like that.
You listening?
He didn't mean it.
Nah, that shit
ain't all right.
Real gangster
needs a gun.
You don't see me
with a gun.
You should have one.
[Sighs]
When I was your age...
My dad kept this gun
under his pillow...
And I would play
with it all the time
With my best friend
Ricky.
One day, we were
fooling around...
And I put the gun
to his face.
You killed
your best friend?
Yeah.
Yeah, I killed him.
I got your back,
big dawg.
Take care
of your sister,
all right?
Heh.
[Cellphone rings]
Hello.
Who the fuck is this?
It's Crow,
you little rat.
What the fuck
do you want?
I want you dead, ese.
That's what I want.
Hey, why don't you
come and get me
Instead of sending
your punk-ass bitches?
Yeah, it's just
a matter of time, eh,
Before we catch up
with you, all right?
All right.
All right,
we'll see about that.
[Screen door rattles]
[Scoffs]
What the fuck
do you want?
Where's Kapone?
I don't know.
I haven't seen him.
You're fucking
lying, bitch!
Fuck you!
Fuck you, bitch!
Bitch!
Who's a fucking bitch?!
Hey.
Y-You OK?
Yeah, we're fine.
Are you?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm good. I'm good.
Hey, but you and the baby,
you're not safe here.
You gotta get out of here.
They're coming after
me and the baby?
Uh, yeah.
I don't know. Maybe.
Nah, it's all good.
Don't even trip.
[Sighs] OK.
Well, my sister said
We could stay with her
in Bakersfield.
All right, that's good.
That's good. Pack a bag.
Get the baby ready.
OK. You're coming
with us, right?
Fuck, yeah,
I'm coming with you,
all right?
I'm gonna call you
in a little bit,
Tell you where to meet me.
Where are you going?
Just got one thing
I gotta take care of
before we leave.
[Sighs] OK.
Be safe, OK?
Yeah.
Better watch
who you hang with,
little homey.
Sis!
Get up, Sis.
Get up! It's OK!
Sis!
[Crying]
Fuck! I'll be back.
Rudy!
Don't go!
Fuck.
Rudy!
[Crying]
[Dogs barking]
What the fuck, man?!
Watch where the fuck
you're going!
You almost hit me!
You hear me?!
You almost hit me,
I said!
All right...
You almost hit me!
You better
handle this.
What the fuck's
your problem?!
I'm not good
with kids.
Come on!
I got this.
Why can't you
fucking watch
where you're going?!
That's bullshit!
Yo, watch where
you're fucking going.
Hey, buddy, relax, OK?
Nah, fuck that.
You almost got me.
Watch where you're
fucking going.
Just calm down,
and maybe we can talk
about what's bothering you.
Fuck that. Yo,
I'm having a really
fucked-up day, OK?
Well,
I'm sorry about that.
Now, what's your name?
I'm Rudy.
Well, it's nice
to meet you, Rudy.
I'm Parole Officer Webster,
And this is
my partner Ardmore.
Sorry for talking
all that shit.
Don't even worry
about it.
You need to let loose.
I got a son, too.
Yeah. Does he
talk shit like me?
Ah, all the time.
Well, I gotta
get going, Webster.
All right.
Hey, you take care,
Rudy.
And be careful.
[Dogs barking]
Wow.
That was, eh...
That was good.
Yeah, I get
a lot of practice
with my son.
GHOST:
Damn, I put a beating
on that bitch, homey.
[Chuckles]
Just how I like it, homes.
Hell, yeah.
Gotta shine these up.
Check out
this little fucker.
[Sighs]
What's up, ese?
I got time to kill
right now.
Think you're a man,
don't you, homes?
Oh, I get it.
It's about your sister,
right?
Let me tell you...
Don't ever put your hands
on me again, ese.
That'll be
your last mistake.
Man, you know what, ese?
Man, you think
you're all that, huh?
Let me tell you
something, homes.
Heh. Oh, you're ready
to cry, huh?
Ready to cry, right?
If you're a real
motherfucking gangster,
You're ready to die
for that shit.
Man, get the fuck
out of here, man.
Fucking youngster.
CROW: Bitch!
GHOST:
That's some shit.
RUDY: Kapone! Kapone!
What the fuck
happened to you?
Crow fucked me up.
And your sister?
They beat her up
pretty bad, too.
Fucking putos.
[Gasps]
Come on. Let's go.
KAPONE:
Oh, shit.
Come with me?
You OK?
Come on.
Get up. Get up.
Come on, Sis.
Careful. Careful.
Be careful.
Sis.
Baby,
it's gonna be OK.
It'll be OK, Sis.
OK, all right?
He wouldn't stop.
He wouldn't stop!
It's gonna be OK.
It's OK, Sis.
[Crying]
It's...
He kept hitting me
a-and hitting me
And hitting me
and hitting me.
It's gonna be
all right.
Rudy, I got
some business I
gotta take care of.
You stay here
with her.
RUDY:
What are you gonna do?
Get a gun and kill
some motherfuckers.
* Fuck, no
* I got 13 hours to live
* What will I do with all
this gangster in me to give? *
* I got so much gangster
to give *
* With only 13 hours
to live *
* I got 13 hours to live
* What will I do with all
this gangster in me to give? *
* I got so much gangster
to give... *
Hey, Fresco, it's me.
* I got two hours left...
Yeah, I'm gonna need
that gun after all.
Meet me at Wizard's.
Yeah, OK. OK.
He's going to Wizard's.
That's good, ese.
That's real good.
You know,
as a matter of fact,
That's so good, homeboy,
I think it's time
to reward you.
[Gasping]
They don't
make gangsters
like they used to.
Marisela, it's me.
Meet me in the alley
next to Wizard's house
in 20 minutes.
Where's Kapone?
Why?
Answer the fucking question.
You passing judgment, ese?
You fucked up.
Kapone's a snitch.
You're his little bitch.
You don't know shit,
Other than what Crow
feeds your punk ass.
I know he's no good.
You took him in.
Heh. We don't
hide snitches
in the hood.
I ain't gonna lie.
Kapone's been down here,
But I'm gonna
tell you something.
That boy ain't no rat,
And you fucking know it.
Crow fucked up on this.
[Chuckles]
That's not
your call anymore.
Maybe not,
But I'm gonna say
what I need to say.
Your opinion
is gonna cost you.
So be it.
You don't run this gang
no more, homes.
Them days are long gone.
Now you're just
a fucking washed-up,
Crippled veterano, homey.
You ain't shit.
As a matter of fact,
The hood ain't
got no use for you
no more, homeboy.
[Gasping]
Who's Isabella's daddy now?
Get the fuck up,
motherfucker!
I'm gonna
fucking kill you!
Motherfucker!
Get the fuck up!
I used to run this hood,
motherfucker!
What the fuck you doing?
I am this hood!
You don't fucking
run shit, Georgie!
You're a motherfucker!
It's all good.
You know the shit
you put me through today?!
Do you fucking know, huh?
Get up. Get up, Georgie,
you motherfucker.
Get the fuck up.
Aw, fuck.
Ah, shit, Georgie.
Nah, don't you
fucking do this.
Get up. No.
Georgie, wake up.
Wake the fuck up, man.
Don't fucking trip.
Come on, Georgie.
Get the fuck up. No.
No. Fuck.
Please, Georgie,
don't fucking die.
Don't you fucking die
on me, man.
Don't you
fucking die on me.
Come on.
We gotta make this right.
Fuck.
Shit.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, we got him
this time.
What's up now,
homey?
What's up now?
[Gunshots]
What the fuck's up, ese?
You should have took
the gun when you had
the chance, homeboy.
Where's Fresco?
He's down there
with Little Wizard, bitch.
That's what the fuck
happens to little
bitch-ass motherfuckers.
You a dirty
motherfucker.
Is that right?
That's what happens when
they try to show no loyalty.
Let me tell you
something, homes.
You a rat, ese.
Don't believe
everything you hear
on the streets.
You know, you fucked
with my family,
My brother Marco.
Now it's time
you get yours.
Do what you gotta do,
But you a bitch.
Yeah, and you
a motherfucking snitch.
[Gunshot]
Yeah, what's up,
punk bitch?
Fuck you
gonna do, ese?
They call you
a gangster?
I'm the real
motherfucking gangster.
[Gunshots]
[siren blaring]
[Tires skid]
ARDMORE:
Rudy, drop the weapon.
Put the gun down, son.
Put the gun down.
Rudy, come on.
Please.
It's gonna be OK.
[Gunshots]
Johnny!
Oh, my God. No!
He's still
alive.
OK, then you
gotta get him up.
Come on.
Easy.
OK, come on.
Come on, baby. Please.
MARISELA: Hurry!
Oh, my God.
Please, no.
Please.
Look at me.
Look at me, baby.
Look at me. OK.
I'm right here, OK?
Don't give up,
Johnny!
Look at me.
OK?!
No, don't close
your eyes!
I'm sorry.
Please just don't
leave me now.
Open those eyes!
Come on. Come on.
Open 'em!
Come on. No.
Please.
Please. Please.
OK, come on, Kapone.
Almost there.
We're close.
Just hang on
a little more.
Just a little
more, baby.
We're close.
Please, just
a little bit more, baby.
Please think
of your son.
You're stronger
than that, Pacheco!
Please. I need you, OK?
I can't do it
by myself.
Junior needs you, OK?
Please. Please, no.
Please. Look at me.
Look at me, baby.
Look at me.
[Music playing,
dialogue fades]
[Bird screeches]
[Music fades]
[Traffic rushing]
[Instrumental playing]
KAPONE: When I was
in the emergency room,
I kept thinking of my son
And how much
I wanted to hold him.
I don't remember too much
Once I was
on the operating table,
Except seeing this...
This bright, warm light
And my father
walking through that light.
I kept trying
to run towards him,
But he kept telling me
that it wasn't my time yet,
Because my son
still needed me.
For whatever reason,
I was given a chance
To be a father
one more time.
* You're the air
I breathe *
* You're the reason I sing
* You're the burn inside
* In a perfect night
* An inky night
* Yeah
[New song playing]
* Come on
* Let's go
* Hold your head up high
* Yeah
* Come on, man, yo
* Royalty is what it is
* I'll be the one to lead
* My people
straight across that bridge *
* We gonna get it,
we don't have to take it *
* They gonna give it to us
* 'Cause they
can't deny their place *
* We holding victory,
I'm royalty *
* I'm the ghetto,
the grime *
* I'm the bling, the shine
* I'm Decatur, Atlanta
* College Park, the SWATS
* I'm Brooklyn, Harlem
* Queens, and the Bronx
* I'm Compton,
South Central *
* Inglewood, and Watts
* I'm a slow getter
* But no matter
how I get it *
* I'm a go-getter
* Faster cheddar
don't make you better *
* I know real cats,
done hard time *
* Really, you ain't hard
* So don't try to play God
* Just stay royal, man
* Royalty is what it is
* I'll be the one to lead
* My people
straight across that bridge *
* We gonna get it,
we don't have to take it *
* They gonna give it to us
* 'Cause they
can't deny their place *
* We holding victory,
I'm royalty *
* Royalty is what it is
* I'll be the one to lead
* My people
straight across that bridge *
* We gonna get it,
we don't have to take it *
* They gonna give it to us
* 'Cause they
can't deny their place *
* We holding victory,
we royalty *
[New song playing]
* So I call my baby mama
to see my kids *
* And hopefully
with no drama *
* 'Cause she's a bitch
* Fucking bitch
* Damn, we started arguing
* Fuck
* I only got 6 hours left
* So I hugged the kids,
Angel and Bams *
* Told 'em to be strong
* And to be more than I was
and that I am *
* And to always
take care of their mom *
* Even if they resent her
for doing their dad wrong *
* Oh, shit,
the things I'm gonna do *
* In this short time,
I got nothing to lose *
* I'm gonna rob a bank
with no mask *
* Find an amazing blast
* Live for the day,
fuck the past, fuck it *
* Where's the crack?
Once again, take a blast *
* Fuck a fat bitch
in her fat ass *
* Fat ass
* She can have
a fat fucking ass *
[Laughs]
* I got 13 hours to live
* What will I do with all
this gangster in me to give? *
* I got
so much gangster to give *
* With only 13 hours
to live *
* I got 13 hours to live
* What will I do with all
this gangster in me to give? *
* I got
so much gangster to give *
* With only 13 hours
to live *
* Roll up and get
my brother Smiley *
* 'Cause you know I gotta
have him right beside me *
* We're Heckle and Jeckle
* Coyote to Wile E.
* Enough talking
* I'm literally
a dead man walking *
* And I'm walking
to the police station *
* Start aiming, putting bullets
in their brains *
* Till there's
no heartbeats remaining *
* 'Cause I don't give a fuck
whose life I'm taking *
* I'm not thinking about
the mistakes I'm making *
* I'm about to be
a thing of the past *
* Like Kevin Bacon
* Ha ha
* Or better yet,
like that movie "Breakin'" *
* Go see my sister,
my mom, and my dad *
* And ride,
ride, don't cry *
* Just think about
the good times... *