HAROLD ASAILIAN,
SR.: What do you
Want to do when you grow up?
[Chuckle]
To be or not to be,
that is the question.
Shakespeare.
Goddamn genius.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: So
you like the classics, huh?
Hell, yeah.
That's where it's at, man.
I mean, my goal is to be Hamlet.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: That
would be quite a challenge.
Yeah, let me tell
you something.
I made for the classics.
[Moaning]
Mrs. Robinson, Mrs. Robinson.
Oh, God.
I got a cramp.
OK, cut.
Cut, that's enough.
Towel.
[Background chatter]
You OK?
I'll be OK.
Mike, do you have
the Listerine?
No.
Who's got it?
Go check with [inaudible]
I'll be right back.
Hi I'm Harold
Asailian, Jr. And I've
Just checked into
this hotel room
In Los Angeles, California.
16 years ago my father,
Dr. Harold Asailian, Sr.
Had a dream of
making a documentary
About an ordinary person's life.
His concept was to take
a six-year-old child
And film him.
And then film the same
child 16 years later
And see how he turned out, a
sort of anthropological study
Of an average person.
The child picked
for this project was
Rich Longfellow of Perry, Ohio.
My father chose young
Rich by randomly
Pulling is file
card from the office
Of a local elementary school.
He then sent a letter to Rich's
mother, explaining the project
And after meeting my
father, she gladly
Agreed to let him film her son.
My father's previous
experience as a filmmaker
Involved documenting
wild animals.
This was the first
time he'd ever made
A film about the human species.
This is Dr. Asailian,
the one I told you about.
He's a doctor?
Yes.
Is he going to give me a shot?
No.
No, I'm not that
kind of doctor.
As you see here, he
had a difficult time
Getting the child to open up.
I don't want to talk.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: Before
he could develop a real rapport
With the young boy, my father
was temporarily called away
To work on a project with the
"National Geographic," where
In Mozambique, he was
trampled to death by a herd
Of migrating wildebeests.
A few days before his death,
he wrote this in his journal.
Upon leaving young Rich,
the subject of my film,
I feel that the child was
just about to open up to me
And finally tell me
everything he feels.
I'm looking forward to filming
him soon, after I complete
My duties here in Mozambique.
Bye, Dr. Asailian.
Obviously he never made it
back to realize his dream.
But it's 16 years
later, and I've
Decided to pay homage to my
father and complete his dream.
Using his actual camera, I took
a leave of absence from my job
At the Perry Department
of Water and Power
And enrolled in a film class
of Perry Community College
With Professor Amec Johnson, a
fine filmmaker his own right.
Professor Johnson
agreed to let me shoot
This as my big class project.
So I located Rich
Longfellow, now age 23,
And found them in
sunny Los Angeles.
I'd never met Rich before and
when we finally got together,
We really hit it off.
REO Speedwagon.
Hey, you like the
oldies too, huh?
Yeah, I like 'em.
(SINGING) Time for me to fly.
Yeah.
I'm gonna keep on lovin' you...
Today, Rich is an actor and
a newcomer in the business.
He's just moved out from
Ohio only three months ago
And he's graciously
agreed to let
Me film him, his
life, and all those
Who surround his environment.
Well, here I am,
ready to make my film.
Before I start though,
I'd like to say
Something on a personal
note to my father.
Dad, I hope this film
makes you proud of me.
This is for you, Dr.
Harold Asailian, Sr.
When we first met, you
told me that a career plan.
Can tell me a little
about that Now
Sure, I figure I'll do a
couple more adult videos.
Then I'll do some major
movies here in Hollywood.
And I figure, maybe in about six
months, Shakespeare at the Old
Globe in London, England.
OK, so we have some of your
Shakespeare stuff set up here.
You want to show it to me?
Yeah, sure.
I got this book here,
the Shakespeare book.
It's got photos.
It's got... there's a good
picture of when he was young.
Yeah, here it is.
This is the man himself.
That's Shakespeare right there.
That's a young picture of him.
Nice.
Isn't he cool looking?
Yeah.
Handsome guy.
And I got... look at that.
I got this.
That's a cover from the movie.
It's a publicity
still, they call it.
That's Laurence Olivier.
This is Hamlet.
Do you think he
was a good Hamlet?
Yeah, well, he's my idol.
That guy.
This is wiener dog.
That doesn't belong.
Check this out.
Shakespeare coloring book.
Oh, that's great.
That's supposed to be
Shakespeare right there.
[Inaudible]
And then I did that.
See how I painted that,
colored that purple.
Is it finished yet?
No, it's not finished.
I've got to still
do this and that.
Check this out.
That's a sword just like his.
Bet I can do that.
Oh, yeah, that looks good.
Would you want
to play that role?
Yeah, if I can use
my sword, I can.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is the place.
Gwen.
Are you Rich?
Rich, this is Gwen.
Hi.
Hi, it's really
nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I've seen a couple
of your films.
OK.
I've put a sign up,
saying the laundry
Room is under repair today,
so no one should bother you.
Excellent.
This is just like a
typical day on the job, huh?
Yeah.
I got the acting bug.
So, interesting people
that you're surrounded by.
Yeah, I've been really lucky.
They're really cool people.
OK, you guys come on down here.
Just go right down these stairs.
All right, we're here.
What do you think?
[Inaudible]
As far as my character
goes, am I shocked?
Or do you want me to pretend to
be surprised when he comes in?
No.
You're just basically
really turned on, OK?
That's pretty much
what it's all about.
Let me ask you, is it
strange at all to have sex
With someone you don't know?
It's no big deal.
Most of the time,
I'm not even turned
On by the guy or the girl,
but I just rise above it
And act my part.
Take your clothes off and
put them in the washer.
How about if I take your clothes
off and put them in the washer?
Action.
Hi, um, you didn't happen to
find a sock in there, did you?
I'm always losing my socks.
No, but go ahead and check.
Thanks.
Oh, is this what
you're looking for?
Although it's kind
of big to be a sock.
I don't see it, so...
Oh, Rich.
Ah, this character's
name is Bob.
OK, oh, Bob.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.:
Rich's youthful enthusiasm
Was amazing.
After shooting the same
scenes for hours on end,
He wanted to spend
the rest of the day
Studying some of
the more established
Veterans in the business.
Ah, that didn't quite work.
Can we do it one more time?
[Kissing sounds]
[Moaning]
That's Rod Blank.
He's the best in the business.
I'm trying to learn from him.
Shh, quite on the set, please.
[Moaning]
Oh, baby.
Let us go to my
friend's chateau.
Where we will drink some wine.
Fromage.
And passion.
[Moaning and kissing sounds]
Cut.
What's with the accent, Rod?
It is a French accent.
I have been working on it.
Just do it normal, all right?
You don't need an accent.
But look, this
is a French movie.
Yeah, we're dubbing it
to an American audience.
But my character is supposed
to be of the French persuasion.
What do you find to be most
challenging doing voice overs?
Well, capturing the essence
of the culture you're doing
Is extremely important.
For example, French passion
may sound something like, ooh.
Whereas in Germany,
it sounds like ooh.
So then subtitles would
be out of the question.
Love making is an
international language.
It doesn't need subtitles.
So maybe you could talk
about yourself a little bit,
And your background
and then mention Rich.
You want me to talk, huh?
Sure.
Well, let's see.
My name is Lee Fernandez.
I'm the producer of
Rich's the latest movie.
Rich is a good kid.
He just recently
started working for me.
And I take full credit
for discovering him too.
I mean this could be
actually one of the greatest
Discovery stories of all time.
Want some?
No thanks.
Let's see, I um, I
went into the men's
Room to use the urinal.
I noticed next to
me is this kid.
I could tell right
away he was talented,
So I start talking to him.
Come to find out, he's a young
actor, looking for experience.
Let me tell you something
about Rich Longfellow.
You keep your eye on him,
because he's going to be big.
I mean, he's got that, got
that certain special something
You know that makes him
stand out in this business.
How long have you
been making movies?
Well, made my first
one about 13 years ago.
Was that a porno?
Well, you see, I do
public service films,
For people, to help them
enhance their lives.
I mean, these movies
benefit the public.
Right now, we're
working on something
That's selling like hotcakes.
It's called America's
Home Made Sex Videos.
What's that?
Well, they're
amateur sex movies,
They were made at home
by everyday people
On their home video cameras.
They're very popular.
And where do you
get the video's from?
Well, we make 'em.
Didn't you say that
they're supposed
To be made by amateurs,
like average people?
Well, who'll know
the difference?
I mean, besides, we're
average people too.
I mean, it'll look
very realistic.
Nobody know the difference.
Hi, I'm Ed Jones.
This is my new bride, Thelma.
Hi, we just got back
from our honeymoon
And opened up our gifts.
And what do you know?
We got a video camera.
Well, honey, I
finally figured out how
To use our new video equipment.
You did?
Good.
'Cause I'm real horny Let's
get one in before the neighbors
Arrive for pot luck.
You betcha.
[Moaning]
Lee's is a real nice guy.
And well, he's kind of like
the father I never had.
When I first came out
here, he was the only one
That believed in me.
This is my man right here.
This is my man.
[Chuckling]
You ever get shy on the set?
I guess at first I was a little
shy about doing nude scenes,
But after a while, I
got used to it and Lee,
He makes you feel comfortable.
I figured I needed some
experience on my resume,
Some acting on my resume.
Well, he told me about to
Othello, the nude scenes
In Othello. 'Cause I
told them about how
I wanted to do Shakespeare.
I figured acting was acting.
[Knocking]
Hey, Rich.
Good, morning.
How are you?
I'll be with you in
a sec, all right?
Let me finish this.
OK.
Then we'll go.
Feel free to walk
around if you like.
OK.
Have you heard
anything from Lee?
No, he didn't say
anything to me.
Did you read the script yet?
Yeah, it's a great script.
Hope I get it.
Good.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, that's Betsy.
- Hi.
Are you the film guy?
Yeah.
That's cool.
I'm Betsy.
Oh, Harold, nice to meet you.
I met Betsy about a month ago
and she's my first girlfriend.
I almost had a girlfriend
in high school,
But that girl wouldn't
go out with me.
How does Betsy feel about
you doing sex scenes?
Well, uh, I think that's what
she likes about me, because I'm
An up and coming movie star.
Has she actually seen
any of your movies?
Hey, honey.
Here's your orange
juice, freshly squeezed.
Did you filter out the pulp?
Yep.
LM372AKR26.
F13U12C62.
What's that?
Oh, that's kind of personal.
But um, T125L.
That means you're
so sweet to me.
Well, uh, T125F.
That means, you deserve it.
[Phone rings]
Oh, D43N?
Oh, sure, honey, excuse me.
So, you've been together
with Rich about a month now?
Uh, huh.
I have my own apartment but I
was thinking in a few weeks,
We'd move in together.
I haven't told him yet.
RICH: Hey, Blane, what's up?
Oh, we were feeding ducks
by the artificial pond
In Culver City.
It's something we do
every Sunday now together.
That's nice.
Yeah!
Well, how do you feel about
him doing these sex scenes?
I'm sorry, what?
How do you feel about Rich
doing sex scenes on the set?
Um, it's just something
he's doing temporarily.
I'll get him out of it.
RICH: Whew!
You know my friend, Duane?
The one I told you about?
He's coming in from Sandusky.
Oh, man, it's going to be great.
He's going to stay here.
I'm glad it pleases
you, Richard.
Betsy's wonderful.
She seems really nice.
Yeah, it's funny.
The first time that I met her,
seen her at the duck pond.
And I wanted to go
talk to her, but I
Was just a little too nervous.
And I just kept on throwing
bread and next thing I knew,
She comes over to me.
And like I was still
a little nervous.
But we go along so well.
And she asked me
for my phone number.
Really?
Yeah.
You don't have to do this
now if you don't want to.
I think she'd want me to.
That's my mother.
She passed away
about two years ago.
This is my favorite
picture of her.
It was only until I got older,
and I realized how hard it was
For her to raise me on her own.
She's the one that took me
to my first Shakespeare play
And at first, I admit I was
a little reluctant to go.
Get up.
Come on.
We went and saw Hamlet.
And it was magic.
I didn't understand a single
word they were saying,
But I understood everything.
All I remember is
running out and saying,
I want to be Hamlet.
And one day, I came home from
school, it was dinnertime
And there was this
cup by my dinner plate
And I asked my mom,
what's this cup about?
And she said that,
this is a magic goblet
And you have a magic gift.
And someday, you going to
be the Prince of Denmark.
I'm going to make it.
Well, wish me good luck.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.:
Rich is on his way
To meet with one of the
hottest directors in porn
Today, Carmichael
Astune, director of Lee
Fernandez's next production.
Earlier in the
morning, Rich showed
Me a secret script
of the project,
Which is currently untitled.
A huge step up from the
so-called amateur videos,
This is a big budget, feature
length, two part series,
Complete with three
acts, costumes,
Sets, and overseas distribution.
Rich is convinced
that working on it
Will be the greatest
training he's ever received.
Rich, I'm glad
you could come in.
It's good to meet you finally.
It's nice to meet
you too, Mr. Astune.
Please call me Carmichael.
I been looking at some
of your work lately.
It looks really good.
I'm impressed.
You have a real sense
of inner continuity.
So what do you think about
illuminating your potential.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: Carmichael
Astune's greatest triumph
As a director, came at the
helm of such period uplinks
As "Spartacome" and
"Pilgrim Poontang."
He considers himself
an actor's director,
And was quite eager to
demonstrate this for us.
[Loud moaning]
No, you're losing
the illumination.
[Moaning]
That's perfect.
Were you filming?
If you felt it,
then it is reality.
You see?
You are capable of
feeling that way.
And that's the beauty of film.
That's why I'm a film auteur.
He's brilliant.
I've never met anyone
like that before.
He just... the man
qualifies as an artist.
I get to work with
Carmichael, it'll
Get me that much closer
to the Shakespearean
Classical training that I need.
HAROLD ASAILIAN,
JR.: Apparently Rich
Was a top contender for
a part in the project,
But Lee and
Carmichael were still
Considering others
for the part and held
Some last minute auditions.
Well, I played Tevye in
"Fiddler On the Roof."
And I was the corpse in
"Arsenic and Old Lace."
Ah, sounds good.
Plenty of stage work, huh?
Oh, yeah, it's great training.
Good, good.
So, you feel ready
to try a reading?
Sure.
OK, turn to page nine.
Start at the top and
whenever you're ready.
I've never wanted
a woman so badly.
This is going to be great.
OK, cut, wonderful.
I'm very excited
about this project.
It's a much bigger than those
home videos I've been doing.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.:
Will you cast Rich?
Well, I can't
really say that now.
I have been looking at some
other actors with Carmichael.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.:
Regarding Carmichael, he's
Considered quite actor's
director, isn't he?
Yeah, yeah.
That's what they say.
Well, my other investors wanted
to bring him in, you see.
Hey, if it makes me money...
[Chuckles]
What I'd like you to do for
me is to tell me about one
Of the more horrifying
experiences of your life,
Or one of your past lives.
Um, but I memorized the lines.
That's OK.
We don't need that.
Just relax.
Think about that particular
moment in your life, and then
When you're ready, begin.
I was walking down
the street, and on
This is about eight months ago.
I was going over to
a friend's house,
And we were going to
get something to eat.
And then decide what to do.
So I was on the was to her pad,
and this dog, this huge pitbull
Was on the other
side of the fence,
And he had chased a poor
little kitten up a tree.
It was horrible.
I remember the dog
was just standing
There, laughing and laughing.
The dog caught the kitten?
That is horrible.
No.
The kitten was OK
up in the tree.
But it was horrible that
the owner of the dog
Could just stand
there and laugh.
Oh, at least the kitten was OK.
That is horrible
about the owner.
Atta girl.
Good.
Good girl.
So, you're OK.
I'm OK.
We're all OK.
That's touching now.
Now, could you please
take off your shirt.
Yeah, I'm really psyched
about my friend coming out.
We grew up together.
We were inseparable.
Man, we did everything together.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: Rich is
talking about his long time
Best friend, Duane
Brickton, shown
Here in my father's footage.
My father was eager to
film the two boys together,
Hoping that young
Duane's presence
Would help young Rich open up.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, SR.:
So, you're Duane, huh?
You two boys friends?
Do you go to school here?
Do you like school?
How come you don't like school?
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.:
Duane is flying out
To LA to become a theater
and movie director
And to work with Rich.
Duane's really excited about
my progress here in Hollywood.
Eventually, Duane's
going to direct
Me in a Shakespeare play.
And then we'll want to do
the movie version together.
We first met around
kindergarten.
But we didn't
become best friends
Until first grade,
when we both got
Sent to the principal's office.
We got in trouble.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: How
did you guys get in trouble?
Well you hit what
was her name, Sarah...
Baldwin.
Yeah, you hit Sarah
Baldwin in the stomach.
And I flipped off the teacher.
But I didn't really
flip her off.
I just raised my hand and she
thought I was flipping her off.
Yeah, that's true.
Hey, you got an H?
Yeah, I think.
You got a D?
Yeah, right here.
Anyway, we became best
friends and remained
That way through high school.
Actually we stayed friends
and were in the same school
District for 12 years.
13, if you count kindergarten.
Yeah, that's true.
This is a film I made at
Little River Community College.
And, are you ready?
Yeah.
Get the lights, please.
[Projector running]
Here we go.
All right.
[Dramatic music]
RICH: Whoa.
That is so true, man.
DUANE: Yeah.
[Whistling]
Man, that film kicks ass.
Boy, I'm telling you, that is
like, that's better than half
The crap out in the theaters.
So you want to be a director?
Well, yeah.
But I'm willing to
work up the ranks.
Yeah, well, I'm going
to get a job on the film.
Yeah.
[Knocking]
Oh, hi.
You must be Duane.
Yeah.
How are you?
Hello, Harold.
Come on in.
Bring the camera in if you want.
You a friend of Rich's, huh?
Yes, sir.
Have a seat.
He tells me you're
quite a filmmaker.
Well, I've got a lot
of learning to do.
I tell you what.
There may be an
opportunity for you
To learn what making movies is
all about on our next project.
If you're interested, I
might be able to work out
Some sort of apprenticeship.
That would be great.
Well, I wouldn't be able to
give you any remuneration right
Now, of course.
But you will gain an enormous
amount invaluable experience.
I mean that's what
I need right now.
This is going to look
really good on your resume.
For this project, your title
will be production assistant.
Wow.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: So,
Duane, now that you're out here,
How does it feel, the big move?
It feels good.
It feels really good.
I mean, I've been here less
than a week and I already
A production assistant.
Frank.
Hey, Mark.
Hi, baby.
Carmichael, he, uh, he
likes you very, very much.
We discussed it and, uh, I've
decided that you go the part.
I'll have the contracts
drawn up tomorrow.
I can't wait to
tell my best friend.
This a major project.
You're a very lucky young man.
I can't believe it.
I'm going to be in "Aristotle
and his Horny Time Travels."
That's great.
Thank you.
You're welcome and
congratulations too.
Thanks.
Woo, hoo!
It's time to celebrate.
Ooh, here you go.
Here's yours and here's mine.
To me.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: Finally
the big shoot has arrived.
Rich, Duane, and
the others gear up
To begin production
for "Aristotle"
And his Horny Time Travels."
[Background chatter]
Hey, cut me down
a three-footer.
Can you spot that
one to the right?
Yeah.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.:
As mentioned earlier,
The production values are
to be much higher than those
Of the amateur videos, and
as such, several top class
People in the industry
have been hired.
When I first got
into this business,
The biggest challenge
was the asses.
It was um, they were
still covered with zits.
There's an example of my work.
This is before.
And this is after.
And I swear there was no touch
ups to these photographs.
This is the period
piece sequence
Of the film where
Professor Aristotle
Has his famous dream sequence.
Notice, great,
great grandfather.
What year is that
supposed to be?
Not sure.
The 1700s or something.
This is Modigliani, right?
He's from the late 19th century.
So will that still be
appropriate for your set?
I mean, it's supposed
to be a dream, right?
I mean, who knows what
dreams actually mean, right?
Right.
You don't like this painting?
Oh, no, no, it's fine.
It's good.
Um, Alex, I'd like to
ask you a few questions
About cinematography.
As you well know, light is part
of the visible electromagnetic
Scale.
There also lights that
are part of the invisible
Electromagnetic spectrum,
such as infrared and
Ultraviolet light,
which I seldom use
Because no one can see them.
Now, in sculpting a scene, or
better yet painting a scene
To create a certain mood, I
make sure to always balance
Huygen's theory of light
reflection and refraction,
Which explains that light
in the 440 nanometer
Range to the 500 nanometer
range is perceived by us
As red, a color I would
tend to use when lighting
A scene, a hot, sensuous scene
between characters that have
Been previously established
as powerful sexual partners,
Sort of, we need to have each
other, although we are aware
Of the circumstances
type people.
But of course Planck's theory
of light as actual measurable
Particles or quanta, proves
that light is more of a wave
Particle phenomena than anything
else gives me the opportunity
To interchange these colors.
And very few people
would be able to tell
The difference consciously.
Uh, huh.
Of course, of all the people
on the set, the most important
Is the director.
Imagine where you were when
you were feeling that way.
If there are smells, fragrances,
odors, what are they?
Perhaps it's the
perspiration from a lover.
Or maybe there's
a hint of jasper.
What the hell's going on here?
How dare you?
Can't you see what's going on?
How much footage have you shot?
Don't change the subject.
Oh, how much footage...
We haven't shot anything yet.
Are you serious?
I've been rehearsing
the actors and taking
Them through exercises.
What... you mean to
tell me you have spent
The last five hours rehearsing?
You haven't given us
any rehearsal time,
So we're doing it now.
You don't need any
rehearsal time, Carmichael.
All these people
are getting paid.
I am feeling anger.
I am feeling hostility.
CARMICHAEL: The
first day of shooting
Is often a very
hideous experience.
Everybody's tense and nervous.
That's why I always
like to start out
Each movie with an easy scene.
First, Misty makes love
to you behind the bar.
Then you get up,
come over, and make
Love with Lucy on the chaise.
Then Misty gets up
from behind the bar,
Sees you, gets
jealous, comes over
And you make love with her.
Then they make love with
each other, which gets
You hot again, so you join in.
All right?
OK.
Good.
Action.
Young Aristotle.
Madame Monrovious.
What a surprise.
What are you doing?
I'm studying.
What are you doing here?
I have come to help you study.
How can that be?
Well, young Aristotle, though
you are a wise young guy,
There is still one philosophy
that you know nothing about.
This is true.
There is still one
thing you have to learn.
Although I am a genius,
I'm willing to learn.
Are you sure you're
ready to learn?
Yes, I am.
I'll take notes.
Oh, no, young Aristotle.
The first rule is
that you must relax.
Let me help.
HAROLD ASAILIAN,
JR.: I noticed Lucy
Had some problems
with your costume
During the dream sequence.
RICH: Yeah, but it was
exciting, because we
Improved the hell out of it.
Carmichael taught us
about improvisation
For when something goes
wrong during the scene,
You're supposed to
just keep going for it.
You just do it and you don't
worry about if something
Happens, you just go for it.
Yeah, it's cool.
Cut.
Wonderful.
[Clapping]
Rich, why don't
you take a break.
Duane, let's get one
of the stunt props up.
We have to shoot some close ups.
Stunt props, you're up.
You want to turn on a monitor.
Hi.
You're a stud.
All right.
My name's Shaunie.
This is Liz.
I'm Rich.
Rich, they need
you in wardrobe.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Hey, Duane, can I
talk to you for a sec?
Hey, no problem, sorry.
Hey, Duane, don't forget
to turn out the lights
When you're done.
No problem, man, I'll see you.
Hey, you betcha.
Hey, see you, Mike.
So what's up?
Do you think you can you
get a ride with [inaudible]?
I thought we were going to go
get some beers or something.
- Yeah.
- Take care guys.
- Night, Vince.
- See you.
Yeah, well, me and some
of the actors, we're
Gonna get a bite to eat and then
we're go to Carmichael's and do
Some rehearsing.
We're not getting as much
rehearsals on the sets, so...
Can I come?
Just to watch or something?
That would be cool to me, but
Carmichael just wants to keep
It actors only, you know.
Cool.
I understand.
You know, private thing.
No problem, don't
worry about it.
I gotta go, so.
OK I'll see you
back at the place.
Bye.
Be home about 11.
OK.
How about you?
Are you learning a lot?
Is it going well?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it's incredible.
I mean, Carmichael
is inspirational.
I mean, just, it's
like, it's like osmosis.
You know, being around
him, you learn so much.
I mean, the other day, the other
day, we went to a movie theater
To see one of his movies.
And I thought he went
there to see his work.
But we get there and he watches
the audience's reaction.
He watched the
audience's reaction.
[Sounds of sex from the screen]
Come on, come on,
everybody, let's go.
Time's a-wastin'.
Let's hurry up and
get this next shot.
Duane, where are you?
Duane, come on, we need this.
Get it.
Move it over here.
This over here.
I told you this before.
Get up off your ass.
Let's go.
You're the one.
I noticed on the set
the last few days,
You've seemed preoccupied.
Well, I don't think so.
I'm very relaxed.
I mean, look at me.
You can get any more relaxed
than this, now can you?
Listen, uh, you're going to
have to cut some of the scenes.
Cut?
Well, we're running
over budget already.
Now, distribution wants
this video in by the 5th.
I don't make a damn
cent on this thing
Unless it's in by the 5th.
I'm concerned about
the fog effect.
I told you we can't
afford the fog.
You promised me fog.
You're ruining the whole
elasticity of my movie.
It's absolutely necessary for
the 18th century European mood.
Like I said, we
can't afford it.
OK?
Good, go in there
like an animal, Bruno.
OK, everybody, and action.
Woo, hey man,
how'd you get here?
I'm young Aristotle and
I'm traveling through time.
Groovy.
Wo.
Where am I now?
You're in the middle of 1967,
baby, the summer of love.
1967.
Why has this period been
christened the summer of love?
Haven't you ever heard of
free love, young Aristotle?
I have no recollection
of that term.
Well, my wife and I will
show you and share with you
Our bodies and our souls.
Share your wife?
Hey, we share everything
in the commune of love.
I guess that is groovy.
Hold it.
Hold it, hold it.
Everybody freeze.
OK, get that adjusted.
This is just the lights.
Where did you
say you were from?
Studio seven.
Hurry up, hurry.
So Rich, I've been wanting
to ask you something.
Sure.
You know, I've been on the
set and watching you shoot,
And I read the script.
And I'm just kind of wondering,
how does all this fit
Into your goals as an actor?
Fine.
What do you mean?
OK, well, let me
give you an example.
Here in the script, Breezy
says, we share everything
At the commune of love and
then young Aristotle says,
I guess that is groovy.
I mean, is that...
How does that... is
That challenging to
you as an artist?
It's experience.
You know, to go into the lines.
What do you know
about acting anyways?
Well I don't think...
I'm not claiming
I know anything about acting.
But I'm wondering... I know you.
I'm wondering how it
fits into your goals.
Have you ever acted before?
No, I haven't.
How do you know what's good for
me and what's not good for me?
I'm not saying I do.
I'm just... I want to know
how you feel about it,
What you're doing.
We've talked many
times about your goals.
Is this helping you get
to where you want to be?
Yeah.
All right.
I gotta go put my makeup on.
OK.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: This
was a big day for Rich.
Well known co-star,
Lucy "Lace" Liebowitz
Brought him to the shooting of
a public service announcement,
Where Rich could
schmooze with some
Of the most illustrious
names in the business,
Such as Toby Barr
and Gemini Peeks.
I'd like you to meet Rich.
This is our new costar.
Bill.
Cody.
Gemini.
Hi, Rick.
Hi!
You just come in, and
then you deliver your line.
I had to lose my
virginity, right.
So I did. And then
I thought, but wait,
I want to have an orgasm,
so I accomplished that.
And then I though,
well, what's... multiple,
Multiple orgasms.
So I did.
Incredible.
Now I've got my family.
And it's so beautiful.
And there's never a dull moment.
He's always trying to bring
out my inner virtuosity.
And that's it.
The thing is, I
need to talk to you.
The life four five
four three two
Hi, you may not recognize
us with our clothes on,
But you've probably seen us in
some of your favorite movies.
We represent ASS, the
Association of Safe Sex.
As you know, there's an
epidemic sweeping the world.
We're here to remind you that
safe sex is good practice.
I practice whenever I can.
Safe sex is the best
way to say I love you.
Practice safe sex.
Remember, practice
makes perfect.
[Knocking]
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: I was
hoping to meet with Rich,
So I could finally get his
perspective on the new shoot.
This was the second
time Rich had stood
Me up for an interview since our
misunderstanding over his work.
I was a little worried
about it and how
It would affect my film.
And I couldn't
help but think how
My father felt when
the younger Rich
Was too shy to talk to him.
My father thought of
himself as a failure
And I wasn't about to let
the film fall short now.
Professor Johnson?
Hi, it's Harold, calling
from Los Angeles.
How are you?
I decided to call
Professor Johnson back
At Perry College for
some advice regarding
Rich's evasive attitude.
He told me to be patient,
yet persistent, and most
Importantly, not to lose focus.
Rich, there you are.
Hey, Harold, what's up, man?
Are you ready
for the interview?
What interview?
1:30 on the nose, like we
talked about, remember?
Oh, uh, they're filming
a story about my life.
- You're kidding.
- Yeah.
Cool, huh?
Oh, my god.
I'm like, a little
tired right now.
Do you think we could do it
some other time, like tomorrow?
I mean you promised.
The thing is that you've
already put me off before.
I really... I want to get you on
the set with this new project.
And...
Yeah, I know.
It's just a good thing.
I'm really tired.
I've got an idea.
Why don't you go
interview the crew people,
You know, the little people
that make everything possible?
I bet they'd love
to talk to you.
OK.
Thanks, man.
Oh, shit.
Pretty cool, huh?
God, that's... oh, my
god, I had no idea.
Yeah, it's pretty fun.
Uh, huh.
I bet.
So where were we?
I was asking you about your
job at the landscaping company.
You know, I was wondering
how long you guys were
Going to be doing your film?
Um, another couple of weeks.
Don't you have a girlfriend
to get back to or something?
Back in Ohio or
wherever you're from?
RICH: Hello.
Hi.
Where have you been?
Sorry.
Yeah great, sorry.
Meanwhile, I'm stuck
having to entertain him.
Look, I'm sorry I know you
don't want to hear this,
But I gotta get back to the set.
Carmichael is really working
us ragged, and overtime,
So... brought some bread though.
May be you and Harold
can feed the ducks?
What?
Harold, you want to...
Shit.
I can't believe you.
Here, you take
the fucking bread.
I said I'm sorry.
What can I do?
It's the business.
I'll see you tonight.
[Whispering]
So what, you're actually
going to be able to perform
Tonight or something?
No, we've got nothing to hide.
What do you think
about this, Harold?
Can you believe this shit?
Can I talk to you?
Well, I think you
guys talk it out.
No, I want to hear
what you have to say.
(WHISPERING) I'm sorry.
OK?
[Whispering]
[Knocking]
Betsy?
Um, Look, I'm just
going to leave
The bread over on the couch
here, over on the armrest?
Listen, um, he's blown me off
for a bunch of interviews.
So I know how you feel.
You know, I think
he's just tired.
You know, I agree with
you, that's no excuse.
Of course, I'd be
tired too, with all
The female fans
coming around the set
And all the sex and everything.
I was just kidding about that,
the female fans and the sex.
What I'm saying is, I
don't think he's screwing
Around or anything like that.
You want to come on
out and talk about it?
No.
OK.
Could you just leave, please?
Sure.
OK, look, I'm going to leave the
bread over there on the couch.
OK?
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: With Rich
busy at private rehearsals,
Duane wanted to introduce
me to a new self awareness
Group he'd recently discovered.
I was anxious to get
more footage of Rich,
But I felt sorry for
Duane, and I decided
To tag along with him,
hoping I could get
Out there as soon as possible.
Duane.
How are you?
It' good to see you.
Good seeing you.
Remember I was telling
you about this documentary?
Yes.
Yes, they're here.
Yeah, this is Harold.
This is Wolf.
Hi, Wolf.
Nice to meet you.
Gee, this is neat.
Sorry, you can't film today.
I'd love to, it's just that
I didn't tell the group.
And you understand.
I completely understand.
Relax over it.
We won't get upset.
I'll mention it at the meeting.
And we'll film another time.
OK.
OK, Duane, Harold.
But I'd love to tell you
about Growl, if I could.
I told Duane and he's here.
Wonderful, it's wonderful.
It's... let me say hello
to an old Growler.
How are you?
Grr.
Growl helps you realize where
you should be in life, not
Where you were coded to be, or
your family said you should be,
Or where you think
you should be.
But where you really should be.
DUANE: The meeting was amazing.
I learned so much
about myself, about why
I do the certain things I do.
It's got to help
me as a director.
Rich.
I think Rich would it.
I gotta tell him all about it.
Sorry.
RICH: Yeah, I've done a few.
Oh, God, Rich.
You're wonderful.
Asshole.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Hey, what's going on?
You're not leaving, are you?
Hey, wait, come back.
Hey, let's talk about this.
So, what's her name?
Her name?
What are you talking about?
[Door slams]
What did you tell her?
What?
You told her, didn't you?
Why would I tell
her anything, man?
You're jealous.
What?
I get all the chicks I want.
You couldn't get
laid if you tried.
Hey.
Her car's here.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: You've
already said that, Rich.
I was little sorry for
Rich's predicament,
And I felt it was
very important for him
To patch things up with Betsy.
Furthermore, I felt it
make for great scene
To capture the drama on film.
Let's go.
Where you going?
I know.
This is the perfect... you been
trying to reach her all day.
Here she is.
Betsy... she doesn't
like the camera, OK?
Come on, she never
reminded before.
Come on, let's go.
Are you nervous?
No.
What's the deal?
I thought you were
going to go in there.
I've got some things
I've got to do tonight.
I'm busy.
I've got to watch Michael
Caine's acting video.
Oh, come on.
You're making excuses.
Look you want to talk to her.
She's in there.
Go knock on the door.
What is it?
Come on.
What's your rush?
Let's just go.
Look, the truth is, you've
been blowing me off, OK?
I called my professor and he
told me to show, not tell,
Show the drama, don't tell it.
So there's, there's
a drama in there.
Go knock on the door
and show me the drama.
Let's just go, OK?
Let's go.
Please?
Unlock the door, please.
[Soft growling sounds]
What's going on?
What the hell's going on?
It's Growling, man.
Look, everybody keep
going, keep growling.
Look, I thought you
were rehearsing, man.
We'll be done in an hour.
No, man.
I'm supposed to
watch Michael Caine's
Acting technique on the video.
And I'm tired and I
want to watch it now.
Why don't you join us?
Relax with us.
It's wonderful.
It'll help you find
where we want to be.
Who the hell... who
the hell is this?
Look, look, I'm
sorry about this.
I'm really sorry about this, OK?
We'll be done in an hour.
Why don't you just
go to your room and...
No, no.
Fuck that.
I'm not going into my room.
This is my apartment.
I live here.
I'm letting you live here.
I pay the rent and I'm
going to watch my video now.
Oh, hey, what are you guys,
you guys to wake up now, huh?
Well, it's time to leave.
What, don't they
understand English?
What the hell is the
matter with you, man?
You wouldn't help
me with my lines,
But you got time for this shit.
That makes a lot of sense.
Look, I'm really sorry that
my roommate here's an asshole.
Goodbye, goodbye everybody.
We'll all meet at my house.
Goodbye, good night.
I'm sorry.
Buenas noches.
Good night.
Adios.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.:
So Lucy said this might
Be your last file for a while.
Is that true?
Yeah.
How come?
I'm going to have a baby.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: Really?
- Yeah.
HAROLD ASAILIAN,
JR.: Congratulations.
Yeah.
This time I'm going to keep it.
Her name will be Eleanor.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.:
Really pretty name.
You already know
it's a girl then.
Well, not yet.
But I have a feeling.
But I love the name Eleanor.
I used to have a little
puppy by that name.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.:
Really what kind was it?
I don't know.
It was one from the pound.
So, which one of these
guys got you pregnant?
What?
Which one of the studs
is gonna be a dad?
Oh shut up, you asshole.
What I do on the set is work.
This child is a result of love.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.:
Don't worry about him.
Hey, Max, you don't know where
the hell Duane is, do you?
Uh, no.
He hasn't show up yet.
All right, well, when he
gets in, tell him to call me.
I got some things I need
him to pick up, all right.
You don't know
where he is, do you?
No.
Damn it.
[Pin ball sounds]
You know, I was looking over
some of my father's old footage
Today.
I couldn't help thinking
about you and Duane,
And how it must feel now
that you have had a fight.
We didn't fight.
He moved out.
You don't know where he is.
So?
He's your best friend.
It would be good to talk to
him about Betsy. Or something.
I just learned something.
You've got to look
for number one.
I don't need Betsy.
I don't need Duane.
All I got to do is
worry about Carmichael's
Acting technique and my acting
career and I'll be fine.
Duane!
A couple days later I
received a message from Duane,
Saying where I could find him.
We'd planned to
meet, but I was late.
I caught him just in time.
How the heck have you been?
Where were you?
I was trying to track
you down, you know?
Yeah, I know.
It's... [inaudible].
Yeah.
Hey, look at this.
Look at that.
Shakespeare for seniors.
What is it?
It's a program.
I'm directing it.
It's like a thing
where we do Shakespeare
For senior citizens.
And you know, I'm doing Hamlet.
Hamlet, huh?
All right.
Can I do it now?
What?
Can I tell him who I am?
Oh, sure, go ahead.
Thanks.
Hi, I'm Rosie Mitchell, of
Rosie's Catering Service.
I specialize in film shoots.
And as you see, we have
a variety of specialties.
Today our specialty is
tortellini trevigiana.
Thanks.
Sure, my pleasure.
Good.
Yummy.
I mean, I'm so think
of these cheap bastards.
I don't give senior citizen
discounts, you know?
You should have heard the
proposition I got last night.
How come you're not
shooting right now?
They're still setting up.
Are you serious?
What the hell's going on here?
What the... what is this?
I thought I told you... my god!
Who rented this fog?
I rented it.
I told you we
couldn't afford it.
And I told you it's
essential for this scene.
Oh, that's nice, Carmichael.
That's real nice.
Now who's going to pay for this?
That's not my concern.
It's my job to make
the best film possible.
Oh, well, you're sure
as hell right there.
It's not your concern.
Just get out.
Yeah, that's right, get out.
You're not directing
this film anymore.
Out?
This film isn't going to have
any more artistic integrity.
Oh, is that right?
Well, what are you
standing there for?
Get in your places, positions.
We'll shoot the scene.
Come on.
[Loud moaning]
Oh, yes!
Cut.
Roll that one back for me.
That's good.
What the hell is this?
Alice, get your ass over
here and explain this to me.
You missed the ejaculation shot.
Well, what the hell you
doing on his face, Alice?
You missed a perfectly
good money shot.
You told me to shoot
the facial expressions.
Shit.
Do I still get my bonus?
You got to remember
that things like
That happen in this business.
I don't deny that
Carmichael is an artist.
But he has to remember
that I'm his employer.
We have a responsibility
to our investors.
HAROLD ASAILIAN,
JR.: So do you feel
Confident that you can direct?
Yeah.
I been in this
business a long time.
What kid of comment is that?
Look, Rich, what
I want you to do
Is I want you to look at her
breasts when you say that line.
Really?
Yeah.
That's not what
Michael Caine said.
Michael what?
He said, pick an eye.
What are you talking about?
Well, Michael
Caine's acting video,
He says, pick eye
of the other actor
And concentrate only on that.
And that makes your
performance more believable.
Also, if you pick just one eye,
not both of them, just one eye,
The you're more focused and you
don't seem shifty and nervous.
Look,
I don't give a shit about that.
You are horny, and I want you
to look at her tits, all right?
Jesus.
Maybe you should just pick one
and then your eyes won't shift.
What a shitty director.
Yeah.
Why don't you direct?
No, thanks.
Look, I just don't need
him in here anymore.
Just get him out of here.
All right, but Alice said
that he could be here.
Alice said.
I don't care what Alice said.
I don't want him and
I can't afford him.
Just get him out of here.
Excuse me.
Trouble.
I don't care.
Could I talk to
you for a minute?
Yeah, you take care of that
for me, Mike, all right?
OK.
OK, what's up?
I want to talk to
you about Carmichael.
OK.
Me and the other
actors were talking
And we think you should
hire Carmichael back.
You do?
Yeah, it would be
really important to us
Because he's like the best
director we've ever worked for.
So...
Oh, you think that would
be good for the actors?
Yeah.
You think that would
help the performances?
Get some chemistry in there?
Right, you know, it's
like well, he helps us-
Find your motivation?
Yeah.
That's good, I mean,
It's important to us.
Well, that's something
to think about.
That's all I can do, is ask.
Can I ask you
just one question?
Who the fuck do you
think you are, Rich?
[Sigh] I don't fucking
care what you think.
I don't give a shit
what you think.
I don't pay you to think.
I pay you to fuck.
Jesus.
What the fuck you got
riding on this shit anyway?
Nothing.
That's what you
got, nothing, Rich.
No.
You know what you got?
All you got is right down there.
And that's all I need from you,
know what you've got, Rich.
And know your place.
Hey, Rich, Rich, come on, man.
Look, he didn't
mean any of that.
He's just stressed out.
All he thinks of me is a cock.
He's like a father
figure to you.
You said it yourself.
Doesn't he know I'm an actor?
Yes, he does.
Things just got out of hand.
I'm just a cock to him.
I'm want to talk to Betsy.
I think that's a
really good idea.
There's a phone right up there.
Why don't you give her a call?
I'm going to talk
to her in person.
This time she'll
know I'm serious.
[Knocking]
Hi, what are you doing?
What are you doing here?
I thought I'd... I
want to talk to you.
Haven't you ever
heard of a phone?
Yeah.
What's going on?
It's OK.
Just go back and
watch the game, honey.
I'll be in in a minute.
OK.
Hey, look, um, I wanted
to tell you that I'm
Sorry about the affair.
She didn't mean anything.
So you did have one?
I was bluffing.
Look, um, take care.
Come on, man.
Let's go play some foosball.
Let's get your mind off it.
Let's go have some fun.
It is cheaper here.
Doing all right?
- I'm doing OK.
- Good.
It's going to be all right, man.
It's going to be all right.
You know, life is,
well, it's life.
I mean, you've got to not
be afraid to experience it,
You know?
I just think you're doing a
damn, hell of a good job, man.
[Knocking]
Excuse me.
Lady, your pizza's here.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: Obviously,
Rich was very depressed.
I tried to cheer him up by
watching some of his videos
And showing interest
in his work.
But looking back, I should
have realized that he
Didn't want to talk about that.
What happened to Dr. Zhivago?
I haven't seen this
one, so I popped it in.
You haven't seen this one?
Huh, uh.
Actually Lucie
told me about it,
But you never showed it
to me, so I saw the label
And popped it in.
The ones I haven't seen.
We don't want to
watch Dr. Zhivago?
Yeah, sure, later.
You know, it's
interesting to see this
Because now that you're
working on a feature,
It's really
interesting to see sort
Of the evolution of where
you've come from there
To here with real budget stuff.
This is the first time you
worked with Lucie, right?
Must have been kind of
exciting to know she was a star
And you were just starting out.
Let me ask you something.
Was she pretty good?
Yeah, great.
You know, you're
good here, but I
Can definitely see
where you've taken
Your craft to another level.
This is the best time I've
ever had delivering pizza, lady.
Look, man, let's
call it a night.
What?
Sure?
Yeah.
I kind of wanted to
catch the rest of it.
I'm tired.
What about Dr. Zhivago?
Let's do it some other time.
Really?
I'm tired.
And then what
happened in your dream?
You unbuttoned my pants
and pulled them down.
LEE: Come on, Rich, come on.
OK, cut.
Cut.
Don't waste any more footage.
What's the deal here, Rich?
I'm sorry.
Look, you know I'm behind
on this damn thing already.
You're obviously
having a problem again.
All right.
Quiet on the set.
Get ready.
Just get ready to roll the
camera whenever Rich is ready.
Come on, Rich, we go
the shot, come on.
Come on, girl, come on.
Ah, Jesus, Rich.
Damn it.
All right.
Take five.
Take five, everybody.
Roll camera.
Speed.
Scene 12, take 2.
OK, act.
And then what
happened in your dream?
You unbuttoned my pants
and took them off.
That's it.
[Heavy breathing and moaning]
Yeah, that's it.
Oh, yeah.
Here it comes.
It's getting bigger.
Here you come.
Oh, it's so hard now.
I love the way you taste.
Mm/ Such a big piece of meat.
Oh, God, you are such a stud.
I quit.
Where the hell
you going, asshole?
Get your fucking
ass back in here!
You son of a bitch!
Fuck you, son of a bitch!
God damn it!
Turn that camera
off, God damn it.
Jesus Christ!
Fuck!
I told you to turn
that fucker off!
Shit!
God damn it!
Asshole!
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: Rich
locked himself in his apartment
For the next few days.
He wouldn't let the camera in.
I decided to bring over the
Shakespeare for Senior flyer
That Duane had given me,
along with some groceries.
Rich said, quote,
"There's no way in hell"
I'd even do Duane's play.
"In fact, I'm quitting
acting forever."
Unquote.
[Church bell rings]
When audition time
rolled around,
Rich called to tell me that
maybe he'd be trying out.
Just in case, I decided
to have my camera
Ready at the audition
site, held at St.
Andrew's Lutheran church.
Name?
Rich Longfellow.
Is that with one L or two?
Two.
Thanks a lot for coming in.
Really great to meet you.
Yeah, I really liked
what you did there.
Thanks.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to audition.
There's no pay.
It's Shakespeare.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.:
How did the audition go?
RICH: It was a little
nerve wracking at first.
But then I just tried to
focus in on the character.
Duane helped me a lot too.
He talked about
Hamlet's motivation.
And he just really
coached me really good.
I think I gave a
pretty good reading.
You know, I'm very lucky to
have a friend like Duane.
Thanks a lot.
Uh, who's next?
Rich Longfellow.
Rich.
How you doing?
Great.
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: Rich
landed the lead in Hamlet
And the company was soon
touring the senior citizen
Recreation centers of the
Greater San Fernando Valley.
This is it.
I just want to I tell
you, I know we've worked
Long and hard on this show.
And I think it's been worth it.
I think we've got to
come together now,
And I've done all that I can do.
I mean, it's your show now.
It's your baby.
It's ours.
We've earned it.
Let's just go out there and
let's just do everyone proud.
Have a good time with it.
[Clapping]
How smart the lash that
speech doth give my conscience.
The harlot's cheek, beautied
with plastering art.
Is not more ugly to
the thing that helps it
Than is my deed to
my most painted word.
Oh, heavy burden.
I hear him coming.
Let's withdraw, my lord.
To be, or not to be.
That is the question.
Whether 'tis nobler in the mind
to suffer the slings and arrows
Of outrageous
fortune, or to take
Arms against a sea of trouble,
and by opposing, end them.
To die, to sleep no more.
And by a sleep, we say
to end the heartache
And the thousand natural
shocks that flesh is heir to.
'Tis a consummation
devoutly to be wished...
HAROLD ASAILIAN, JR.: As
Rich realizes his dream,
I hope I helped my father
realize his own dream
By completing this film.
Wherever he is, if he can
somehow see his finished
Product, I hope he's pleased.
In any case, I dedicate
this with love,
To the visionary behind
it all, my father,
Dr. Harold Asailian, Sr.
[Applause]
[Music playing]