(bass heavy rock music)
(tires screech)
(gunfire)
(screaming)
(sirens blaring)
(gunfire)
(loud crash)
(explosion)
* Wild, crazy,
and out of control
* Her dad is insane
and her mom is too
* That girl will
be the end of you
* She's wild, crazy,
and out of control
* Six gun, blackjack,
she's naughty and nice
* She'll risk it all
for the toss of the dice
* Helter Skelter
across the floor
* You kiss her once
and she'll ask for more
* Wild, crazy,
and out of control
* Yeah yeah, wild,
crazy, and out of control
* Her dad is insane
and her mom is too
* That girl will
be the end of you
* She's wild, crazy,
and out of control
* Bad girls, good
times, she's ready to go
* It's not wrong if
her mama don't know
* (mumbles) let's go,
now don't look down
* Turn me over
and spin me around
* Wild, crazy,
and out of control
* Yeah yeah, wild,
crazy, and out of control
* Her dad is insane
and her mom is too
* That girl will
be the end of you
* She's wild, crazy,
and out of control
* Yeah, she purrs like a
kitten when you pick her up
* She takes what you got,
but it's never enough
* She starts and she
stops, she turns on a dime
* She spits and polish,
but she won't shine
* Wild, crazy, and
- Come on.
* out of control
- [Rhino] Hello?
- Oh thank God!
Really?
Rhino!
- [Vixen] Call's
disconnected, bitch!
(dramatic synthesizer music)
- Listen, please, don't kill me.
We can work something out.
(laughing)
- We already tried
that, remember?!
Besides, what do
you have to offer
besides dirty drugs
that kill buyers?
- Okay, so I've got some
bad customer service skills.
I'm sorry!
I'll clean the stuff up
and we'll split the profit.
Anything you want!
- You should've thought
about that before
you started selling to
kids and pregnant women.
- Hey, I only sell
to women in their
first trimester,
I've got standards.
Please, I'm begging you.
I'm not ready to die!
(screaming)
(laughing)
* Snap twerk pop, snap
twerk pop, snap twerk pop
* Your mama from the valley,
she twerking' like Natalie
* I'm from Arkansas, but
I'm showing out in Cali
* I'm parked in a Denali,
right there in the alley
* She like to call me
daddy, I'mma get money at it
* Drop it on the floor,
twerk it up some more
* You wanna see some care,
baby, show you who's a ho
* Get it how you live,
twerkin' in high heels
- (mumbles) the door, dumbass.
Get in the back.
* Twerk snap pop, make it
roll like them (mumbles)
* Song on repeat,
that pussy I'mma beat
* Long as you got (mumbles)
- [Voiceover] What
a load of bullshit!
This thing doesn't
even have a radio face.
The chop shop's
not gonna give us
shit for this piece of junk!
- Shut up, it's a
cash money job anyway.
It's not like we need the money.
(car revs)
- Yeah, yeah!
What the fuck?
- Shit!
Kane, he just called me!
Fuck!
- It's been a long
time, honey, hasn't it?
- Vixen, what are you doing?
- Just cleaning up the streets
and taking out the trash.
- You just started a
war, you dumb bitch!
(guns cock)
(gunfire)
- The war's over!
We won!
Let the others know that there's
a new queen in
town, and it's time
to clear out of her
territory, biatch!
- Woo!
- Yeah!
- [Voiceover] Woo!
* Be cool be cool, just
move with the groove
* Fucking hear the
beat way too smooth
* Let's just do
what we came to do
* Just vibe with
it, vibe with it
* Vibe with it, vibe with it
* Be cool be cool, just
move with the groove
* Fucking hear the
beat way too smooth
- You're Vixen, right?
- The one and only, honey.
- You deal down in Echo
Park, what brings you
to my neighborhood?
- Well I was thinking
about moving up
in the game, I thought you might
be the man I need to talk to.
- Well Kane runs
this end of town,
so Kane is the man
you need to talk to.
- I hear he doesn't
have a head...
For business.
- What do you have a head for?
- [Vixen] Definitely more
pleasure than business.
* When the mic touch this MC
* Without the mic
this MC feel empty
* I'm telling you now,
it's the lyrical recipe
- Why don't you step into my
office and we'll have a chat.
* Accept and expect
no less than the best
* Inject and collect
without disrespect
* Be cool be
- Are you crazy?
- We're taking over
this town and either
you're with me or
you're against me.
Well?
- You're such an amateur.
I'm gonna stick with Kane.
You're a loser.
- I killed him, looks
like he's the loser.
- You killed Kane?
Cool, then I'll go independent.
- No you won't, and you're
gonna lose something too.
- Do it.
(gun clicks)
You're out of your mind.
And my gun is out of bullets.
Now it's loaded,
and you just ran
down a dead end alley.
(suspenseful music)
Woo hoo hoo hoo!
Oh yeah!
Time to die, amateur!
Did you really kill Kane?!
Well that's life
in the big city.
Such a pretty amateur.
Too bad you're gonna die.
Time to die, amateur!
- Hola, cabron.
- Oh shits.
- Like I said before,
I'm taking over
this town and you're
either with me
or against me, so
what's it gonna be?
- Give it up, Vixen,
just let me go
and I will disappear.
- Yeah, you'll disappear okay.
Into dumpsters!
- (sobs) No no no,
just let me go!
Just let me go.
- What, is this too
"amateurish" for you?
(car engine revs)
(laughing)
- No!
No!
Noooo!
- [Vixen] What's wrong?
It's not like this is nothing
we ain't never seen before.
- I just really hope you know
what you're doing, Vixen.
- What's up your ass?
(singing in Spanish)
Woo, let's party!
We taking over this town!
- Woo...
- What's up?
- Nothing to celebrate I guess.
- What do you mean
there's nothing
to celebrate, we just took out
Kane and some of his best men!
What!
- Where's Sarita and Katie?
- Who knows, they're doing
their own celebrating.
Woo, woo, woo!
(laughing)
- I love you.
- You're such a fag.
(overlapping Spanish music)
- Stop camping,
you fucking noob!
- How long have we
been playing this game
and you're still
complaining about campers.
- I don't care, these
assholes want to
play the game, they
(mumbles) fucking douchebags.
- Vixen, we need to talk.
- Can't it wait?
- No, it's important.
- We're in the middle
of a game and we're
(mumbles) these assholes!
- Vixen, please?
- What's so important?
- I want out.
- Want out?
We just made a huge power play.
It's smooth sailing from here.
- They're gonna
retaliate, Vixen.
It's gonna be a bloodbath.
- Those pussies
are nothing without
their precious leader.
If they know what's
good for them,
they'll get out of town.
- Vixen, you're
underestimating their loyalty.
I'm just, I'm sorry, but I'm not
taking that chance, okay?
I'm done.
- What?
You're done?
After all I've done for you?
Bullshit!
- I'm sorry, Vixen.
- Fucking bitch.
She'll be back.
(remixed rap music melody)
- Boss, here's the
latest batch for you.
What do you think?
- Bonzai.
- What the hell
is wrong with you?
- Vixen and...
- Calm down and tell
me what happened!
- Vixen threw Kane's
head in the window!
They killed Crash and
Bulldog right in front of me!
- Those stupid
(mumbles) bitches!
What the fuck they
were thinking about?!
We're going to make them pay!
All right, we will
make them pay!
- How are we gonna do that,
they took out half our crew!
- Let me show you how.
- Grrr!
- Sir, we have a situation
that needs your attention.
(singing in Spanish)
- [Voiceover] Another
death at a local
high school has a
community on edge.
It appears that a
new, high powered
form of methamphetamine
is hitting
the streets causing
an unprecedented
amount of overdoses.
Anyone with any information,
please call One Police Plaza.
I'm Doctor Drew Sterling and
I'm here to help your kids.
Stay tuned.
- We have to do something
about CainKane's dirty drugs.
We can't just sit
back here and watch
these kids get caught
up in this shit.
- What can we do?
- Hit up the streets,
see if we can
find some dealers
that still have
some death meth left to sell.
- I mean we know
they're associated
with Kane, it
shouldn't be that hard.
- Okay, let's do this.
Electra, you come with me.
Sarota, you take Katie,
you know what to do.
- Where's Kandy?
- She's not happy with the way
we're doing things right now.
She said she wants
out, but I just
think she needs some
time to herself.
Let's just focus at the
task at hand right now.
- All right.
(singing in Spanish)
- Help, I need help please.
- What the heck's
wrong with you?!
- I need, I need, I need you to
get the fuck out the car.
Get out, get out,
get out, get out!
Get out, that's
a nice ass dress.
Those shoes don't match though.
- Hey, that's my car!
- So you got it?
- Yeah I've got it.
You got the money?
- Let me see it.
- (mumbles) see it.
- Let me see the
shit man, come on.
- How long have we
been working together?
Of course I'll let
you see the shit.
I don't want you
dealing, messing with the
death meth anymore.
All right?
- All right, all right,
all right, I got it.
- This is clean shit.
- All right.
- It better be good shit.
- It's good.
- I'm outta here, later.
* Straight out the hood
* Ladies and gentlemen
* Put your hands together
* For the one, the only
* My man, your man too
* Brad
- Oh, how's it
going, Big Elliot?
- Nothing man, how you
doing there, Big Baby?
- Yeah!
- You got that meth?
- You know I got it.
- Sweet dude, this
has been really
happening me out
with my weight loss.
- I'm glad it's helping man.
- You know what I
mean, sprinkle a little
bit of this on my fried chicken?
Woo hoo hoo hoo!
It gets me crazy
(mumbles) running around!
- Elliot, Elliot I
gotta go, okay Elliot?
- Yeah yeah.
- I gotta go, okay?
- Don't run too fast.
- You should get out of
there too, Elliot!
- Don't run too fast!
- Get out of there, Elliot, go!
- Easy big boy,
don't wanna slice
an artery with this.
- I don't want any trouble.
- Too late for that.
Say adios to your
balls, muchacho.
- Wait wait, what do you want?
- You're gonna answer
a couple of questions.
- Sure, what do
you need to know?
- What is the
capital of Montana?
- How the fuck should I know?
- Sarita, remove the balls.
- No no, ask me
something I know.
- Have you been
pushing that shit
that Kane's been dealing?
- [Voiceover] Fuck no!
- Don't lie!
- [Voiceover] I'm not
lying, that shit is deadly!
I need my customers to come back
for repeat business or
I'm out of business!
I'm not lying, I swear
on the life of my
pet rat Spunky that I'm
not dealing that shit!
- Fair enough.
Do you have any idea who
has been dealing that shit?
Keep in mind your
answer to this very
important question may very well
determine whether
you can fuck again.
- Oh I know who it is.
It's this tall chick
with gigantic tits.
She deals it by the liquor store
near Echo Park, do you
know where that is?
You're not gonna miss this girl.
This is the girl who's
been dealing that
shit at the schools
and that's fucked up!
- Thanks for your cooperation.
- No problem.
- Now run along, puto!
- Si, senorita!
- Oh yeah, that fits the bill.
Hey!
- What's down, Foxy Brown?
- We're looking for something to
make us feel a little happy.
- You're not a couple
of 5-0s are you?
- Fuck no.
Ain't nobody here the po-Pos.
- Yeah, okay.
I got something
that'll knock your
pretty little heads off.
- Yeah, me too.
(suspenseful music)
- (mumbles) fuck, okay?
Fuck!
- Welcome to the S.S.
Vixen, I doubt you're
gonna enjoy your ride.
- What in the hell
is this all about?
- Fasten your seat belt.
(coughing)
- Do you work for Kane?
- Yeah, I did until some crazy
fucking bitches cut his head...
I mean Kane was an asshole.
- Don't get smart.
Have you been dealing his meth?
- Well yeah, I work for
Kane so I deal his stuff.
- And you've been pushing
that shit in schools, correct?
- Yeah, but it wasn't my idea.
Look, I'm just a small
time drug dealer, lady.
I just take my orders
from higher up.
- From Cain?
- Well yeah.
- That's wasting, baby.
- Whoa whoa whoa whoa, stop!
But I get my stuff
from someone else!
I don't know his
name, but he's the
middle man between Kane
and all the dealers.
They keep that shit locked
up tight in a warehouse.
It's like some
kind of a fortress.
- Are you sure you
don't know his name
or the location
of this fortress?
- No, I'm sure.
I'm sure, I've been
honest with you.
- Then you're no use to us.
- But I told you everything
you needed to know.
- Well you can tell that to
the kids you sold drugs to.
Oh wait, no, you can't.
Electra?
- No!
(gunshot)
Ahh!
- Hey!
You forgot something.
- Oh yeah, that's right.
(laughing)
(dramatic rock music)
- Kane?
Dead?
God!
Bitch!
Cunt!
Lesbo!
That's not mine, I
have to pay for that!
- No more death meth!
You're dealing us
stuff you know.
- The hell I am.
All right, all right,
I'll deal your stuff.
I'll deal your stuff until
The Phantom deals with you.
- Who the hell is The Phantom?
(laughing)
- Nobody knows who
The Phantom is.
He's totally
underground, you'll know.
He'll get you, you've opened up
a can of scorpions, Vixen.
- You know, that's what
everyone's been telling me.
I don't care.
- There's still time.
(laughing)
Can I go?
- Sure.
- Not thataway.
Go down the street.
- What?
- Yeah, Katie's
taking your whip.
- That's bullshit!
Ahh!
(remixed rap music melody)
- We need to get more
information on this
middle man and find out
where the warehouse is.
Electra, you and Sarita
hit up the street
and see if you can
get some information
on this middle man.
- Think Jennettie
knows anything?
- He's been working
this case for a year
and a half, he better
know something.
- All right.
- Freeze, titcock!
- Jesus Christ!
You can't keep doing that,
you're gonna give
me a heart attack.
- Calm down.
You're the one who
wanted to see us.
- Yeah, and we have a
favor to ask you too.
- What can I help you with?
- We've been recently
investigating the death
meth overdoses and I
think we have a lead.
- Investigating?
Isn't that my job?
- Yeah, and we could use
your help to solve the case.
We could use your help putting
the final pieces into place.
- Pieces?!
You mean what, like
pieces of bodies you
crazy broads are leaving
all over the street?!
(laughing)
- What are you gonna do?
Give us a ticket for littering?
- No, but someone's gonna give
you a bullet in your back.
You gals are playing
a losing game.
Good thing I like you.
What information do you have?
- Apparently
there's a middle man
between Kane's men
and the dealers.
I need his name, and
there's a warehouse
where they keep the dirty junk.
- Well the "middle man" really
isn't the middle man at all.
It's Sabu, Kane's
second in command.
He helps distribution
run smoothly.
- What about the warehouse?
- As far as I know it's just a
storage unit on the
upper East side.
- They're storing their drugs
in a fucking storage unit?
That stupid asshole
called it a fortress.
- Fortress?
Pretty lame, right?
- Lame is an understatement.
What did you need
to see us about?
- Well the higher
up's gonna pull
me off undercover soon
and start cracking
down on the meth
distribution in the area.
I'm gonna need you girls
to lay low for awhile.
- Are you kidding me?!
We just made a power play to get
the dirty shit off
the streets and
you're telling me you
want us to lay low?
- Listen, I can't do
anything about it.
They're putting
together a task force.
And they're not gonna play nice.
- You better find a way to
keep them off our backs.
We'll hate to let your captain
know you've been
letting us slide.
- Is that a threat I heard?
I don't want you
girls to get hurt,
but this isn't my call.
- [Vixen] Your concern?
It's noted, sweetheart.
We can't do anything about the
middle man at the moment,
but they're storing
their stuff at a storage
unit in LA Storage.
- Seriously?
What the hell is wrong
with these idiots?
- [Vixen] Your guess's
as good as mine.
Listen, Katie's gonna meet you
outside her place and I'll meet
up with you guys later.
- Okay, see you soon.
- I gotta get a
couple things from
the clubhouse and I'm gonna meet
up with you guys later.
- All right, okay.
- All right.
- (low distortion)
This is The Phantom!
What the fuck is going
on with my town?!
I want these girls dead!
I want these stones
out of my shoe!
Do whatever you have to
do, get rid of these girls.
I want a ton of the death
meth on the streets tonight!
(ominous music)
- [Katie] Let me out of here!
- [Sarita] What is
(mumbles) coming from?
- I don't know,
but she acted like
it wouldn't be long.
- All right, I guess we're
just gonna have to wait then.
- Will you stop that?
You are making me nervous.
- No, I won't, not until you
tell me who we're meeting.
* He got a Can-Am
and pistol grip
* He got the right tires,
he can make them stick
* He's the king of
the slot car track *
- Andre!
- Sabu!
- So good to see you
again, my friend.
- You too.
- You look good.
- [Andre] Hey, all right.
- You know what, I just wish it
was under better circumstances.
- God, you were always such
a good friend to my brother.
I just wish he'd
come to me for help.
So damn stubborn.
If I'd have been there, none
of this would have happened.
- Don't blame yourself.
We were all blindsided
by those bimbos.
- Those little
bitches have no idea
what they've gotten
themselves into.
Okay, they've unleashed
the dogs of war.
- Exactly.
- Listen, enough talk.
We're gonna make
those whores pay.
Starting with this little
slutbag right here.
(rock music)
(laughing)
- What are you doing here?
- I was just grabbing
some of my things.
Hey, I want you to
know this doesn't
change anything
between us, okay?
I still and will always think of
you as the big
sister I never had.
- So you're really gonna
go through with this?
- Yes.
Please don't hate me.
(phone rings)
- I don't have time for this.
Katie, incoming call, go to PC?
- Hello, Vixen.
It's nice to have a face
to go with the name.
- Who the fuck are you and how
did you get Katie's phone?
- My name isn't important.
But what is important is
that you killed my brother.
Now you're gonna pay.
You're all gonna pay.
You see, I take protecting
my own very seriously
and you, well, you took
the only family I had left.
So now I'm gonna take
something from you.
(dramatic sting)
- Please don't hurt
her, it's me you want.
- That's very noble of you.
I do want you.
I want you to suffer.
I want you to know
that, because of you,
all your friends
are gonna suffer.
And after you watch
all of them die,
I'm gonna give you the
gift of sweet release.
I'm saving you for last.
(laughs) See?
I'm not such a bad guy.
(laughing)
Oh, so where was I?
Oh yeah.
You're gonna pay for your crimes
with the lives of
everybody you care about.
- She had nothing to do with
the death of your brother.
It was me.
And it's me who you want,
so just let her go please.
- Oh yeah, I will have you.
You can bet on it.
But first, I think
I'll have some
fun with your
little friend here.
Say goodbye 'cause this is the
last you're ever
gonna see of her.
(laughing)
Katie, anything you'd
like to say to Vixen?
- Vi--
- Oh, oh, she's speechless!
(laughing)
Tell your friends to be ready.
'Cause they're next.
Hey Katie, wanna hear a joke?
- Bye, Vixen.
Vixen?
- You were right.
Everything's gone to shit!
I need your help.
- [Andre] There's this
rich guy, all right?
He's gonna marry
one of three women.
So he gives each one
of them 10 grand.
The first broad spends
it all on herself.
The second broad
spends it all on him.
And the third starts a
business and gets rich.
So who did he marry?
- The one who got rich?
- He married the one
with the biggest tits.
You're overthinking
it, it's a guy.
Guys like big tits!
Let's see what you got.
(ominous music)
- Hey girls, want a hit?
Stole it from the evidence room.
- [Vixen] Just tell
us what you found out.
- [Jennettie] His name is Andre.
He worked at Thousand Oaks
with a small group of thugs.
(groaning)
- [Andre] Ha, look
at that, Lakers.
- We don't have a
last name, but we do
know he's one mean
son of a bitch.
He once set fire to a liquor
(phone rings)
store while the owner
was still inside all
because he didn't have the
right brand of tequila.
- [Sarita] Jesus
titty fucking Christ,
why the hell aren't they
answering their phones?!
- I don't know, but Katie
should've been here by now.
- You know what, fuck this.
Let's just go by
the storage lockers
and we'll try to get
a hold of them later.
- [Electra] Sounds like a plan.
- [Vixen] Let's go, Kandy.
Thank you, Jennettie.
- Girls, be careful.
(rock music)
- Get the hell off of me!
- I used to do porn.
You know what you
gotta have for porn?
- I think you've
already shown me!
- They call it
the rule of eight.
Eight inches.
Feel it?
You feel it?
(screaming)
Oh, and you gotta live
in the 818 area code.
See?
818 number.
And you gotta go 80
minutes before you pop.
See, we've been at it for 90.
- Feels like 900 years!
* He's an eight lane
demon burning up the track
* So don't you mess around
* He's the master's
trigger in this here town
* Look out buddy,
he'll shut you down
- Shit, oh shit, I'm
gonna pop, I'm gonna pop!
Point of no return!
* He's the king of
the slot car track
- Oh shit, oh shit,
here it comes.
There she blows!
(gunshots)
- If you wanna keep breathing,
you'll tell us where
Andre's hanging out at.
- I haven't seen him in weeks!
- Well you better
tell us something,
or my friend here, she's
gonna make brain slushie.
(gunshot)
- Oh man, that was a good lay.
Who's up for sloppy seconds?
Sabu, this pussy's
still warm and wet.
- She reminds me of my ex.
Just dead and laying
there, I think I'll pass.
(laughing)
- That's funny.
That's funny, hey, you
ever skull fuck your ex?
- I never really wanted to.
- Super, more for me.
* Snap twerk pop, snap
twerk pop, snap twerk pop
* Snap twerk pop,
snap twerk pop *
- That must be it.
- Now if you work that
corner right there,
guarantee you'll
make a lot of money.
- Really?
- Especially in that
outfit, it's great.
Look at that, man.
These things here?
Oh my goodness gracious.
- Cheeky.
- (laughs) That's great.
Right over there in
that corner, all right?
Turn into that corner.
Oh shit.
I'll handle this.
- [Voiceover] Okay.
- I don't want no trouble.
* That booty look nice
* Twerk, snap, pop, make
it roll like some dice
* Song on repeat,
that pussy I'mma beat
- [Vixen] You know everything
that goes on in this town.
I need some
information from you.
- Well maybe I can help
you and maybe I can't.
Word is you girls'
time is about out.
- You work for Kane.
- Worked until you killed him.
- I need to know
where the meth lab is.
- Really?
You really want to know?
Look at this.
No thanks, can't help you.
- Can't or won't?
- Can't!
You girls are hotter than a nest
full of rattlesnakes
in Death Valley.
You know there's a
contract out on your lives.
- I'm desperate, and my
friend, she might die.
- If I told you
what you wanna know,
I'd be dead tomorrow.
Aw hell, I could be dead now for
just talking to you!
- You are not help.
- Wait.
You really oughta just move.
Leave town!
Forever!
You're not really wanted here.
I know this neighborhood.
This community doesn't need you!
Doesn't need you,
just go, leave town!
It's a nice place, you know?
Just go and don't come--
(loud crunch)
Ow!
Oooh, oh, open the
door, open the door!
My dick is stuck in the
Ow, ow, open the door!
- Where is she?!
- [Huggy] I don't
know where she is,
look, my schmeckle's
gonna fall off!
Open the damn door!
- It's gonna fall of
then 'cause (mumbles)!
- Oh my God!
- Where is she?!
- I know where she
is, open the door!
My schmeckle's gonna fall off!
- [Vixen] You know where she is?
- I know where she is, I
don't know any meth labs!
- I don't believe you!
- I don't know any meth
labs, I don't know!
Now stop the car,
give me my dick back!
- You better tell
me fucking now!
- I'm bruising my cock,
would you open the door?!
Please, please, please!
(screaming)
- Oh my God!
(sobbing)
Help me please!
- Huggy!
Somebody help me!
I lost my dick!
(suspenseful rock music)
- [Sarita] Fuck this,
I'm tired of waiting.
- Let's just do this.
Now's our chance.
(dogs barking)
(groaning)
(music intensifies)
- Boom, bitch.
(loud explosion)
- Nothing like a good skull fuck
session to ease the
tension of day-to-day life.
Sabu, I need you.
- Yes Andre, as long as...
You're not going
to skull fuck me.
- Look, I left so much DNA,
the CSI scanners would explode.
Okay, I need you to make sure
nobody ever finds her body.
You got it?
- All right, consider it done.
- Looks like me
and you are gonna
be spending some
more time together.
- Yes Andre, that's what
I've always wanted, you know?
- (distorted voice)
This is The Phantom.
Congratulations on
eliminating one of the girls.
But there are four left.
Get to work!
- [Sarita] What the
hell is going on?
You nor Katie showed
last night and
me and Electra took out
the drugs by ourselves.
Plus Katie never showed up.
And she didn't answer
her goddamn phone,
what the fuck gives?
Well?
What the fuck?!
- Sarita, you need to chill.
- Where's Katie?
- Katie was
kidnapped last night.
- Oh my God.
- By who?
Where is she?!
What the fuck are we
doing to get her back?!
- She was kidnapped
by Cain's men.
I did everything I
could to find her, but--
- [Electra] But what?
- [Vixen] We'll
never see her again.
- [Electra] And you
didn't think to tell us?
What the fuck is
wrong with you?!
- I did everything
I could to find her!
I hit up the streets, I checked
his old stomping grounds.
Nothing, I came up with nothing.
- Are you telling me she's dead?
- I'm sorry, but I
think she's gone.
- You're sorry?
You're fucking sorry?!
Fuck you!
You killed her!
You wanted to push Kane
out of those streets
and take over everything,
that was your call.
We were fine before
then, but no,
you wanted to save
the children and take
the dirty drugs off
the street leaving
Electra and I killing
thugs and burning
drugs while Katie
was in trouble!
- Guys, come on,
we all knew what
could happen when
we took out Kane.
- Why don't you just shut
the fuck up, all right?
Because we are drug dealers.
We don't fucking go
out saving people!
So fuck them and fuck you!
- Sarita!
- [Sarita] That fucking bitch,
I need to kill
that fucking bitch!
Fuck her, fuck her!
(door slams)
- So if you wanna tell
me you were right, don't.
I didn't know Kane
had a brother.
- Vixen, I just
think that we need
to lay low for awhile and just
let things go back to normal.
- Lay low?
Lay low?!
Kane's brother is coming
to kill us one by one!
If anything, it's
time to strike back.
- Or run.
- I am not for running.
I am for killing that
son of a bitch right now.
- Vixen, you know
that I would follow
you to the gates of
Hell, but this is
a neverending cycle, okay?
We kill one of
them, so they kill
one of us, and then
we kill more of them,
where does it end?
We need to just think
beyond our guns for once.
(rock music)
* They get some hot chicks
'cause they think he's cool
* He used to go
to my high school
* He's the king of
the slot car track *
- Listen, I have some bad news.
(video game beeps)
- What would that be?
- Someone broke into
our storage and set
fire to a large quantity
of drugs last night.
- Wasn't it your
job to make sure
that that didn't happen?
- So they took out (mumbles).
You know, when I was
getting of the girl's body.
- Are you making excuses?
- No sir.
- I'm not sure I believe you.
Tell me who's at fault.
- I guess it's me.
- So something's gotta be
done about this, right?
Some sort of punishment?
- I'm sorry.
- What does sorry get me?
(gunshot)
- Let this be a warning.
You fail me again and
you'll end up like...
Whoever the fuck that was.
You understand?
- Yes sir, thank you.
- Before you told
me the bad news,
there was something
I was gonna say.
Ah, yeah, that's the right.
My men have arrived,
they're already out
on the street looking
for Vixen and her crew.
Everything's going
according to plan.
Soon the taste of sweet
revenge will be upon us.
Well, not everything's
going according to plan.
- So what's our next move?
- We're gonna flood
the streets with
out final batch of death meth.
Release it all at once,
create a huge panic.
And the best part?
We're gonna pin it all
on Vixen and her crew.
- Are you sure
that's a good idea?
How are we gonna deal drugs if
all our customers are dead?
- Oh, you got a better idea?
- Yeah, why don't we make some
really good meth, like
on that TV show with
the bald guy who makes
the really good shit?
What's that thing called?
He has that really clean setup.
- Is it on The Disney Channel?
(record skip)
- No.
- I only watch The
Disney Channel.
Lot of cute little young
girls on The Disney Channel.
All waiting to grow up to
become stupid little whores.
- Yeah, yeah, that's
a great idea, Andre.
We'll pin it on
those stupid whores.
It's a great idea, guys.
- Good, I'm glad we're all
on the same TV channel.
Now let's get that
last batch of death
ready for deployment.
Sabu, please clean that up.
- Yes sir, I will.
(exotic trance music)
- Let's go kill those assholes.
So I've been thinking
of a way to get
back at Andre and get
vengeance for Katie.
I know it's not
gonna bring her back,
but it's the least we can do.
You guys in?
- I'm in.
- Count me in.
- [Vixen] I just wanna
try this one thing.
If it doesn't work
we quit, run away,
lay low, whatever.
Kandy, I need you on this.
- Come on.
Do it for Katie.
- I really think we
should just lay low.
- Kandy, I can't do
this without you.
You or your brother Rhino.
- Rhino's your brother?
Are you fucking kidding me?!
- I haven't spoken to
him in over a year.
- Talk about a switch hitter.
- How do we know this
bitch isn't a mole?
- She's one of them,
we can't trust her.
- Guys, I have been
with you for over
two years now and
nothing like this has
happened until someone
decided to wipe out
the competition which I
was against, all right?
Now Vixen, what's the plan?
- If we get Kandy
to get her brother
to lure Andre and his whole gang
out into the open, then
we can ambush them.
- Wait, including Rhino?
- What about him?
- I don't want my
brother getting hurt.
- Well if he's a part
of the problem then...
- Well he won't be.
Something tells
me that he doesn't
want any part of
this war either.
- Okay, he won't get hurt.
You have my word.
Okay, Kandy, you
call your brother,
let him know you need to
meet him somewhere private.
Everybody okay with this?
Otherwise we lay low.
- Got it.
- No problem.
- Well I prefer that we lay low.
But all right,
let's do this shit.
(phone rings)
Hey big brother, it's
been a long time.
- Kandy?
- Yeah, it's me.
- I've been thinking a lot about
you lately, how have you been?
- Listen, we need to talk.
It's important,
somewhere private.
- I agree.
Can you meet me at the old
junkyard in say two hours?
- Yeah, and make
sure you come alone.
- I will.
I love you, sis.
- Love you too.
- Interesting.
(dramatic rock music)
- It's great to
see you again, sis.
- Yeah, it's great
to see you too.
It's been a long time.
- I wish it were under
better circumstances.
- I know.
I need your help.
Well actually, we
need your help.
- We?
Who's we?
- Vixen and the
others, we're in huge
trouble, they took Katie--
- Yeah, I know, I know you are.
Andre is a crazy
fuck, and if you guys
didn't kill Kane
he'd still be up
in Thousand Oaks
trying to kidnap
young girls with
an ice cream truck.
- Wait, you knew that they had
Katie and you didn't tell me?
- Well what was I
supposed to do?!
That's not gonna happen to you.
I promise.
- Well well well well
well, what do we have here?
A family reunion?
Ah, how touching.
Rhino, my man, I
want to thank you
for leading her to us.
You know your sacrifice
won't go unrewarded.
- How could you?!
- No, Kandy, I--
- Rhino, I think
it's time for you
to be a good little
soldier and peace out.
I got it from here.
This will put me
back in with Andre.
- Listen, Sabu, Andre's
wheels are off the rails!
He's gonna ruin everything!
- I know.
Then you and I will take over.
Until then, just
hand me the bitch.
- All right, you want her?
(gunshots)
(bass heavy rock music)
(groaning)
- She's not here.
- Hey, you fall back, all right?
- Hey raghead!
(gunshot)
- Merry fucking Christmas.
(gunfire)
- Fuck these (mumbles)!
- Don't let him get away!
(gunfire)
- Vixen!
- So long, bitches!
- All right, so we're
gonna make this death meth.
I'll show you how, don't
screw it up, pay attention.
I got all your things
you're gonna need,
you got your flasks, your
beaker, boiling flask,
mix all that shit together,
it's gonna look like this.
What the hell happened to you?
- [Sabu] Rhino has betrayed us.
I set up an ambush to
kidnap one of Vixen's crew.
He shot me, he fucking shot me!
- You did this
without my approval?
- Boss, I had no time.
I grabbed some men and
followed them to the meeting.
- Men?
Whose men?
- Your men, sir.
- Sabu, where are my men?
- Vixen showed up
and kill all of them.
- You're 20 times the fool!
How many times
you gonna fail me?
- [Sabu] Sir, I'm
sorry, never again.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm sorry--
- That's right never again.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- Goddammit, I don't
know why, but I like you!
I would've shot somebody else,
but we got so few men left.
Okay, we end this now.
I got reliable intelligence
on where Vixen's hideout is.
Go get yourself patched up.
You, back to work.
All right, where were we?
(remixed rap music melody)
- [Jennettie] What
is it with you girls
and sneaking up on people?
You okay?
- [Kandy] Not really,
I've been shot.
- Shit.
Was it .38?
- Oh my God, does it matter?
- Let's go to the hospital.
- No no no no, not
a hospital, please,
can you just patch me up
yourself or something?
- Patch you up?
Am I a fucking doctor?
I'm a cop!
- Please, please Jennettie.
- Get in the car.
- Thank you.
(groaning)
- [Electra] Easy.
(Vixen screams)
It doesn't look so bad.
- It looks like
there's still some
shrapnel stuck in there.
- I stabbed the shit out
of those motherfuckers.
- Shh.
(sirens wailing)
- Where's my sister?!
Oh shit.
Go get some alcohol.
- [Electra] How bad is it?
- Doesn't look like
it hit anything vital.
(inaudible)
(dramatic rock music)
- Shit, here comes
the hit squad.
- We gotta go.
Come on, let's go.
(gunfire)
- Outside.
- Go, but take her alive!
- Wait, where's Sarita?!
- Stayed behind to
buy us some time.
- No, I'm the one
who deserves to die!
- The one who deserves to
die is that fuck Andre.
- Back off or I'll
cut up his throat!
- [Rhino] Gotta get
you back to my place
to get that bullet
out and find Kandy.
(gunshot)
- Well this didn't go
as planned, did it?
Too bad I didn't have more time
to play with my
little latina lesbo.
- (mumbles).
(loud hissing)
(loud explosion)
(siren wailing)
- I'm gonna take
her to the other
room and get her patched up.
Keep an eye out.
Let me know if
anything feels off.
- Okay, will do.
(siren wailing)
- [Vixen] Ahh!
- Sorry.
This is gonna hurt, but
you're gonna be okay.
(screaming)
You're right, it hurts
like a motherfucker!
- [Rhino] You know
I've missed you.
You don't have to
feel the same, but...
I never stopped loving you.
- [Vixen] We made
our choices and
we have to live with them.
- Choices?
You made a choice.
I had to live with it.
- I'm sorry!
I didn't know what to do.
I didn't think we were ready.
- For you I was always ready.
- Wow, Stevie, you
do really good work.
- Thanks.
(siren wailing)
- [Jennettie] Should
be good to go.
You need some rest.
- Thanks, I owe you one.
- So what the hell's going on?
How many bodies are
around this time?
- Hey, do you have any cigs?
Or is all you have is a
bunch of drugs and guns?
- It's right there.
- All right, so basically
shit is hitting the fan.
I tried to stop it
all, but Vixen is
making all these
horrible decisions
and I don't even have
my phone with me.
Mind if I use yours?
- Sure.
It's right there.
- Thank you.
- [Jennettie]
Listen, I gotta go.
There's word of a large
influx of death meth.
It's supposed to be unleashed
upon us pretty soon.
I've been taken off
undercover duty.
Now I'm leading the raid
on a supposed location.
You're welcome to stay
here as long as you need.
- [Kandy] Thanks.
But really, thanks
for everything.
Seriously, I won't forget it.
- Rest up, I'll
check on you later.
* Be cool be cool, just
move with the groove
* Fucking hear the
beat way too smooth
* Let's just do
what we came to do
* Just vibe with
it, vibe with it
* Vibe with it, vibe with it
- [Rhino] Glad to see you've
made yourself at home.
- Yeah, thanks.
- How's Vixen?
- Sleeping.
- [Electra] Good.
- Gotta take care
of a couple things.
You guys stay here and rest.
- What are you gonna do?
- Gotta find Kandy and
see what Andre's up to.
- You think he saw
you at Vixen's?
- I don't think so, he
came in pretty late.
- What about Sabu?
- Andre's been
pretty pissed at him
lately and after
he scene he caused
at the junkyard
he's probably dead.
All right, I'll see you later.
Keep an eye on Vixen,
make sure she rests.
(mumbles).
- [Electra] Okay.
Hey Rhino?
- [Rhino] Yeah.
- [Electra] Thanks
for everything.
I don't understand how we ever
ended up on opposite sides.
- Go where life takes you.
Well, life took me
somewhere I didn't wanna go.
- Well I'm glad
you're with us now.
- Yeah, me too.
* I accept and expect
the whole (mumbles)
* Inject and collect
without disrespect *
- [Andre] Where the
hell have you been?
- Out gathering intel.
Did you hear about what
happened at the junkyard?
- Yeah, Sabu told
me all about it.
- Sabu's alive?
- We had a little
disagreement about whether he
should've done to the
junkyard without asking me.
Let's just say I
won that argument.
- Well I had
everything planned out
and he fucked it up!
I was gonna bring
you Vixen's head on
a silver platter and he came in,
showed his ugly face
and started shooting
up the place, I had to bail!
- I understand.
Sabu was an arrogant prick,
already failed one
too many times.
But you?
You're a smart guy.
You know your role.
- Thank you.
Look, we're prepping the drugs
and we're getting
to unleash Hell
on the city at
around four o'clock.
We're gonna meet at
the same junkyard
where Sabu fucked everything up.
Now I expect you'll be there
to help oversee things?
- It would be my pleasure.
- Good, now if you'll excuse me,
I've got some things
to take care of.
- Yes sir.
- This is gonna be glorious.
My shining moment.
Gonna shove my fish so
far up those bitches'
assess I'm gonna rip
out their fucking heart!
(phone rings)
- Hello?
- Rhino?!
- Kandy!
Oh my God, I'm so
glad you're okay!
I've been calling your phone but
it goes straight to voicemail.
- I know, I know, I'm sorry.
Is everyone okay?
- Vixen and Electra are fine.
Sarita didn't make
it, but we don't
have time to worry about that.
Andre's about to
flood the streets with
dirty drugs and we have
to do something about it.
- I agree.
It's time to end this.
- Great, I have a
plan to sneak us in.
Meet me outside the junkyard
where we had our meeting.
- All right, and
hopefully it goes better
than our last meeting
at the junkyard.
All right, bye.
(soft beat rap melody)
- You okay?
- Where is Rhino?
- Went to go see what
Andre's planning.
Then he's gonna look for Kandy.
- How long has he been gone?
- A few hours.
- He hasn't checked back in?
- I haven't heard from
him since he left.
Whoa.
- Where's your phone?
(phone rings)
- Hello?
- Rhino, have you
found Kandy yet?
- Yeah, she's fine.
- Oh good.
Both of you need
to get back here
so we can plan our next move.
- No, you and
Electra stay there.
I'll take care of everything.
It's gonna be all right, you
should stay there and rest.
- What are you gonna do?
What are you talking about?
- What I should've
done a long time ago.
I love you, Vixen.
And I always will.
- What?
Rhino!
(sobs) Rhino!
- What's wrong?
Vixen, what did he say?
- He's gone.
- What do you mean?
- He's trying to save me
like he's always done.
I never let him.
You know I didn't want this.
- I know.
You just wanted what
was best for all of us.
- When I was a
kid, I had to watch
both my parents struggle
to make ends meet.
My dad worked 80 hour weeks just
to put a roof over our heads.
When I was 10, he lost his job.
We were already behind on
rent, the car, everything.
He couldn't take it.
He shot himself.
I lost both my parents that day.
My mom was still alive, but
inside she left with dad.
She took care of us,
but she wasn't the same.
As soon as we all left
the house, she died.
(snaps fingers)
Like that.
It was like she was
waiting for us to be okay.
- Vixen, I never knew.
I'm sorry.
- I told myself that I would
never struggle like that.
That when I grew up,
I'd make them proud.
This wasn't the path that
I was supposed to take.
Rhino tried to tell me
that, but I never listened.
I just pushed him away
and look where we are now.
Never again!
I'm gonna finish
this and I'm done.
You, me, all of us are
meant for so much more.
It's time we live up
to our full potential.
- All right.
So what's the plan?
- Let me make a phone
call, and then we ride.
* Feels like I'm losing my mind
* All of my life
* I've been helping
you get yours
* Think it's time
for me to get mine
* All of my life
* It seems I've gotten
(mumbles) in line
* Feels like I'm losing my mind
* All of my life
* I've been helping
you get yours
* I think it's time
for me to get mine *
- All right, before
we go any further,
what happened to Sarita?
- Andre and his men
ambushed us as Vixen's.
She made sure we all got out,
without her we'd all be dead.
She sacrificed herself
without any hesitation.
- I should've been there.
- No, you're here now and
that's all that matters.
- All right, so what's the plan?
- We're gonna sneak in there and
take these motherfuckers
out once and for all.
- You sure this is gonna work?
- It should work long enough for
us to blow the top off
this whole fucking thing.
- All right, let's do this.
- [Phantom] (low distortion)
This is The Phantom.
Your payment will
be in my personal
attache case which I'll provide.
Don't fuck this up, Andre!
(snorting)
Woo!
Yeah!
(laughing)
(remixed rap music melody)
- All right.
Got it!
- If everything goes
according to plan,
Vixen and her crew will be dead
by the end of the day.
Sweet (mumbles)
revenge will be mine.
- That's right.
(chuckling)
- Rhino, this place is
crawling with crooks.
You sure this is gonna work?
- Here's my plan.
- Really?
All right, we're going
home in trash bags.
- Hey you!
- Who me?
- No, the 10,000
assholes behind you.
What are you doing here?
- I work for Andre.
Come on.
- Yeah, we're just here
to see Andre is all.
- Rhino.
- He told us to just come by.
(gunshot)
(music intensifies)
* It has begun
* Our moment in the sun
- Oh what fun.
(laughing)
- Boss, shooting on
the West perimeter.
- I know, that's
Rhino and his sister.
Go take care of it.
- We're gonna take
these assholes
out once and for all.
- Rhino?
So nice of you and
your sister to join us!
I thought you gonna
miss the whole party!
Still, I'm a little disappointed
your friends couldn't make it.
But hey, the night's young.
- Wouldn't act so cocky, Andre!
- You're outmanned
and outgunned.
I think we all
know how this ends.
Good for me, very bad for you.
(gunfire)
(laughing)
- Mazel tov, son
of a biscuit eater.
- Vixen!
- Backup has arrived.
- Andre, what are we gonna do,
they got all our guards,
we're surrounded!
(gunshot)
- [Vixen] Hey Andre!
You missing something?
- Shit.
(rock music)
* I heard the news,
the king is gone
* He got rolled
up by the Vietcong
* He was the king of
the slot car track
* Now I'm the king
of the slot car track
- (mumbles) your
little spic friend.
She killed a bunch of my
whores with this knife.
Gonna be appropriate
to gut you with it.
(groaning)
Damn it!
* Now I'm the king
of the slot car track
* Yeah I'm the king
* Yes I'm the king of
the slot car track *
(loud explosion)
(gunshot)
- Kandy!
- Fuck.
- No!
He's mine.
You killed my sister,
you motherfucker!
- Are you gonna
shoot me from behind?
You gonna shoot me from behind?
Be a man, motherfucker!
(gunfire)
- [Vixen] Kandy?!
Oh God!
- Vixen, just promise me you'll
stop with all of this, okay?
The drugs, the killing,
just stop, please just stop.
- I promise I'll stop.
- [Kandy] Good.
That's all I wanted to hear.
- No, Kandy.
- The death meth has been taken
off the streets and destroyed.
Most of the gangs were killed in
a shootout on Crazy
Pete's Auto Yard.
There's one member
of the gang left.
He escaped.
They're trying to find him.
And we're gonna find him.
I promise.
- [Voiceover] Officer
Jennettie, one question please.
How do you address
the rumor that you
were aiding these
women, they were your
own personal
vigilante hit squad?
- No comments.
- [Voiceover] Officer Jennettie,
Officer Jennettie,
please, one more question!
- Welcome to the
Vixen/Jane Rehab Center.
We're gonna help you get
your lives back together.
- Somebody's got to.
(phone rings)
- One sec.
Hello?
What?!
That scumbag?!
No, we're on our way!
We gotta go.
- (mumbles) what
the fuck is that?
- What are you doing?
Stop texting, they're behind us!
(dramatic rock music)
No, really?!
Shit!
We're fucked!
(laughing)
(gunshot)
Ow!
God!
You think I'm sorry I
killed all your friends?!
- No, but I'll make you sorry.
- Oh like hell you will!
See this town?
That's mine!
- You know, it didn't
have to be like this.
We could've worked together.
But you had to have it all.
- I owe a little on
my American Express,
I'm behind on the rent.
- By the end of this
jingle, you better kill me.
Kill me if you can.
* But the fact still remain
there will be no respect
* For those that's
disrespecting, neglected to see
* Got the problem,
ain't correct it
* So let's get in the
right place and never exit
* To find inner peace need
war to find peace to rest in
* Won't be known for
sitting next to my throne
* If I have to I'll walk
this whole road alone
* All of my life
* Seems like I've
been waiting in line
* Feels like I'm losing my mind
* All of my life
* I've been helping
you get yours
* Think it's time
for me to get mine
* All of my life
* Seems I've gotten way in line
* Feels like I'm losing my mind
* All of my life
* I've been helping
you get yours
* Think it's time
for me to get mine
* All of my life, all of
my life, all of my life
my life, all of my life *
(gunshot)
(groaning)
- You think I've lost?!
It ain't over until
the black lady sings!
Surprise!
(laughing)
- Dynomite!
- Run!
- Oh my God, are you okay?
Are you okay?
- I always wanted a sister
that I could molest.
- [Voiceover]
Don't, please don't.
Oh no!
- Ahhh!
(loud explosion)
- We running this
town now, y'all.
(sirens wailing)
Hey Ashley, you want
this piece of shit BMW?
* Wild, crazy,
and out of control
* Her daddy's insane
and her mom is too
* That girl will
be the end of you
* She's wild, crazy,
and out of control
* Six gun, blackjack,
she's naughty and nice
* She'll risk it all
on the toss of the dice
* Helter Skelter
across the floor
* You kiss her once
and she'll ask for more
* Wild, crazy,
and out of control
* Yeah yeah, wild,
crazy, and out of control
* Her daddy's insane
and her mom is too
* That girll will
be the end of you
* She's wild, crazy,
and out of control
* Bad girls, good
times, she's ready to go
* It's not wrong if
her mama don't know
* (mumbles) let's go,
now don't look down
* Turn me over
and spin me around
* Wild, crazy,
and out of control
* Yeah yeah, wild,
crazy, and out of control
* Her dad is insane
and her mom is too
* That girl will
be the end of you
* She's wild, crazy,
and out of control
* She purrs like a kitten
when you pick her up
* She takes what you got,
but it's never enough
* She starts and she
stops, she turns on a dime
* She spit and polish,
but she won't shine
* Wild, crazy,
and out of control
* Big time, first class,
she's second to none
* You better stand back
'cause here she comes
* Look out, too late,
there's no turning back
* When she chugs like a
train coming down the track
* Wild, crazy,
and out of control
* Yeah yeah wild, crazy,
* Her dad is insane
and her mom is too
* That girl will
be the end of you
* She's wild, crazy,
and out of control
* Wild, crazy,
* Wild, crazy, and
out of control *
(electric guitar music)