Intruder located
in sector d.
Thanks, oracle.
Come on, girls.
It's hero time.
Huh?
Where's the snooze
button on this thing?
- Mmm.
S... supergirls, up!
Up and away!
Time to save the day.
Or night.
Drones, swarm.
Your hood, miss batgirl.
Pow! Action on!
- Oracle shows
the intruder is close.
-He must be hiding.
-I'll look in the classrooms.
And I'll check the lockers.
--Ugh!
Any sign of
the criminal, Bumblebee?
No. But an old pumpernickel
sandwich in beast boy's locker
just committed a crime
against my nose.
In there!
Oh.
Mr. bones,
aren't you looking trim?
This way.
Big barda.
How'd you get back here?
Wonder woman? I...
--Whoa!
Hey!
You mess with the bee,
you're gonna get stung.
Truce?
Big barda, you're going
back to belle reve
juvenile detention.
No!
Oh! Sorry. I...
--Ha! Got her!
What's going on here?
Principal waller.
We captured known
criminal, big barda.
Girls, this is
new student,
big barda.
What?
She tricked you,
principal waller.
Her plans to take over
the school are right here.
"Ap weaponomics, 8:30,
"intro to super suits, 9:30."
My class schedule.
I was making sure
i knew where all
my classes were
so I wouldn't be tardy
on my first day.
You let her into
super hero high?
But this is a school
for superheroes,
not supervillains.
Maybe big barda
erased your memory when
she helped brainwash everyone.
I trust big barda
has reformed just like
vice principal graw did.
So, please, make her
feel at home.
At my home,
this would call for
an olive branch, but...
Would this do?
Yeah. Thanks.
This is your dorm room.
Wow.
You can trick it out
with whatever decorations
you brought from home.
Home? This is all I got
from apokolips,
but that's not
my home anymore.
Darkseid's got a zero
tolerance policy for
girls gone good.
I guess that
makes me a stray.
-Like blondie.
-Me?
Uh, granted getting ousted
from apokolips is
less dramatic
than your whole planet
going kablooey like...
Krypton kaboom, right?
Oh, sorry,
I'm not good
with small talk.
I just never had
much time for it
between combat practice,
avoiding the abyss of anguish,
and working on my evil laugh.
That last one was a joke.
I guess I'm not good
with jokes either.
We better get some rest.
There's lots to do tomorrow
for the big hero of the year
celebration this weekend.
I thought I was the
only night owl here.
-What're you doing up?
-Couldn't go back to sleep.
- Wow. Who were they?
- My parents.
I don't want to forget
what they looked like.
But art's not my thing.
I can't get it right.
Come on.
State-of-the-art police
sketch program.
But it'll work for this, too.
It looks just like them.
-Hi, commissioner Gordon.
-What's up, comish?
-Morning.
-Babs, I saved you
a seat up here.
Dad, I'll be fine
in the back.
But, babsy bugs,
you might miss something
in my lecture
about the three aspects
of a crime
that must be established
to determine guilt.
Means, motive and opportunity.
I have the means
and motive
to sit by my friends.
So, I'll take this opportunity
to use this desk.
Besides, dad,
we'll have plenty of time
together this weekend,
since you're my date to the
hero of the year ceremony.
- Aw.
All right, students,
for today's
forensics assignment
everyone needs a partner.
Partner?
--Oh, yeah!
Cyborg, do you
want to be partners?
Sorry, hawkgirl,
me and katana
make a mean team.
-Starfire?
-I'm enjoying the
dynamic duosity
of being the partners
with miss martian.
Ivy.
Frost?
Supergirl?
Wonder woman!
Oh, no.
What up, partner?
Beast boy.
Let's get forensicin', mama.
I gots it!
You solved the assignment?
Nah, I finally got that itch
i couldn't reach.
Oh, yeah.
That's the spot.
We have an assignment to do.
-Stop monkeying around.
-I wasn't monkeyin' around.
This is monkeyin' around.
I can juggle like that.
Beast boy,
get down from there.
Aw, man.
Everybody's always
gripin' at me.
It's, "stop that!
Don't go there!
"Get your tail
out of my soup,
beast boy."
If you want people
to take you seriously
as a proper hero,
you can't be so wild.
Could you teach me?
Me? No way.
You need a lion tamer,
or a horse-whisperer,
or something.
Please?
I'll think about it.
Yeah, mama!
- Oh, fabulous work, Ivy.
-Thanks, Mr. crazy quilt.
They say you shouldn't
gild the Lily,
but they didn't say
anything about roses.
Oh, spectacular sparkling,
sapphire.
Thanks. I love sparkles.
Cheetah! Put that trophy
back where you found it.
"Put that trophy back
where you found it."
This is Lois Lane,
live at super hero high
where everyone is busy
preparing for the annual
hero of the year ceremony.
There are two of
the nominees now,
hawkgirl and cyborg.
Good morning, Lois.
Hey! Shout-out to
all my fans out there.
Can I get a "boo-yah?"
And there's another
hero of the year
nominee, katana.
And here's lady Shiva.
Lady Shiva, what's it
feel like to be nominated
for hero of the year?
The joy I find in this honor
is nearly as great
as the pride
that swelled inside of me,
when I defeated the army
of rampaging boogey beasts,
using nothing but
my left pinky toe.
Intense.
Ooh, there's flash.
Uh, is that camera on?
Got to go!
And this year's
final nominees,
wonder woman and Bumblebee.
What will you do if you win?
I never really
thought about it.
I mean, I got a sweet
suit that lets me fly,
shrink and Bumblebee blast.
But this isn't the
"best dress awards."
As far as hero-ing goes,
my fellow nominee and bestie,
wonder woman, here,
is straight up on fleek.
Aw, thanks, Bumblebee.
Supergirl and batgirl,
as new students,
you didn't meet
the minimum time
to qualify this year.
So, who do you think
should win?
-Well, uh...
-Harley Quinn here.
I first dreamed of being
a hero when I was
a babbling baby!
And I saw
a superhero
on the telly.
Suspicious activity
detected at the amethyst.
Come on!
Ew. It looks infected.
Mmm. No trace of trespassers.
I saw the alert.
What's the status?
Breaking news,
something's going on
with the amethyst.
Thank you, Lois.
But we have top secret
matters to discuss.
I'm here for the
top secret meeting.
-How did you know?
-Lois' report.
I've never seen the
amethyst do this before.
It could be natural.
A gem fungus
or parasite.
But until we know
what's going on,
we'll post a guard
around the clock.
I call dibs on
the first shifts.
Excellent, hawkgirl.
Wonder woman, coordinate
the guard schedule.
You got it, principal waller.
We don't know
what's behind this change
with the amethyst,
but we need to be
extra vigilant.
Okay.
I guess my invite
to the party
got lost in the mail?
Big barda!
Lead warrior in
the female furies
and active
in the attempt to conquer
super hero high.
Stand down, lady Shiva.
Big barda is
a student here now.
Where's the
hidden camera?
Huh?
Is this another prank, Harley?
I wish.
That would have been a doozy!
Seriously?
Principal waller
let her in?
Mmm-hmm.
Don't mind lady Shiva.
She's still smarting
from that time
when you brainwashed
her father
and, generally, threatened
everything she loves.
Yeah. Sorry.
But whatever you need now,
I'm up for it.
Thanks, barda.
You can relieve hawkgirl
after her shift guarding
the amethyst.
-Cool.
-Really?
She wants to help,
and we need help.
Just in case, everyone needs
to be prepared.
-Swords sharpened!
-Hmm!
- Electric stings charged.
Nunchuks, uh...
Chucked?
Batgirl, could you
fix my shield?
It got cracked last night.
Whoops!
This is beyond my expertise.
You need someone
who knows metal.
Hmm. Sounds like a job
for the master alchemist
of Themyscira.
Who's up for a field trip?
-Right on!
-Me.
Can we take the batjet?
You know how
freaked out my dad gets
about me flying
halfway around the world.
Technically,
Themyscira isn't halfway
around the world.
It's more like
a third of the way.
Your dad won't even
have time to worry.
We'll be back by
lunchtime tomorrow.
I'll fuel up the batjet!
I call shotgun!
-All right!
-Yeah, honey!
Hiya, newbie!
Name's Harley Quinn.
You probably heard of me.
-Um...
-Of course you have.
As our newest student,
you have qualified
for the spectacular,
amazing, undeniably unique
Harley Quinn tour.
Can I get a whoopie-whoopie?
-Whoopie?
-Perfect.
I'd like to thank
my parents for being
the wind beneath my wings.
Or rather, for passing down
the family heirloom,
my nth metal belt
from thanagar
- that enables me to fly.
I couldn't have won
this award without it.
Brava!
Who are...
Attacking a student,
two demerits.
Only two? That will never do
for an overachiever
like myself.
- How about 200?
Nth metal from
the planet thanagar.
What a wonderful start.
Aunt Martha,
it's just a quick trip
to Themyscira.
As long as
you're all still coming
to the farm for dinner
after the big
awards ceremony.
Wouldn't miss it.
Your mashed potatoes
are the bomb!
Thank you, Bumblebee.
Supergirl will get
plenty of those while she's
here over school break.
Oh, I don't know, aunt Martha.
Are you sure
you want me there?
I don't want to put you out.
Of course.
Supergirl, you know
you can make yourself
at home with us.
We love you, dear.
I, uh... I appreciate it.
Bye, aunt Martha.
Talking to the kents again?
You know the drill.
A call every day.
Speed delivery for supergirl!
And a cookie care
package every week.
Lucky! I call the
snickerdoodles.
You may have just
met the kents
a few months ago,
but points to Martha
for already having all
your favorite foods down.
Yeah. My mom still
insists that I love olives,
just like she does.
But olives...
The texture. Ugh!
To Themyscira!
-The Princess has returned!
-Oh, she came back! Yes!
-Welcome home, Princess.
-This is wonderful.
-Mother.
-Diana.
I can't stay long.
I just need
my shield repaired.
The only one
who can repair
such damage
to themysciran ore
is the master alchemist.
It will be my honor, Princess.
Come on, I want to show
you guys my home.
Home.
Mom.
Welcome home, Kara.
How was your ride?
Amazing. We found this.
A mnemosyne crystal.
Once we get this polished,
it will be very powerful.
Hurry up,
supergirl!
I hear the ambrosia
here is delish.
Um, coming.
And that's the royal spa.
Sweet.
Is that
a pedicure chair?
My toes are tots in need
of some tlc.
Hey, batgirl, I think
there's something weird
with my necklace.
I touched
the mnemosyne crystal
and saw something.
Krypton.
Interesting.
I can do some tests
when we get home.
Supergirl, over here!
If you stay here
during school break,
this will be your room.
Oh, yeah. Nice.
I thought you'd
stay at the kents
over the holiday.
I haven't decided.
I mean they say I'm welcome,
but maybe they're
just being nice.
I don't want to be
a charity project.
Come on, the throne
room is this way.
Diana, you're skipping over
the best room.
Mom, they don't want
to see that.
It's embarrassing.
Embarrassing?
Well, now we have to see it.
Lead the way,
miss queen hippolyta.
Whoa. This room is gleamin'.
Are all these awards yours?
-Well, you know...
-These are just
from the past year.
We had to build a whole wing
on the other side
of the palace
for Diana's elementary
school honors.
Come, look at this.
It's the key to the
city of Metropolis.
Wow.
And I thought that my dad
driving around with that
"my daughter is
hero of the month
"at super hero high"
bumper sticker was bad.
Shh. Don't let my mom
know those exist.
She'll plaster
her chariot with them.
Diana, I want to
show you something.
Wow!
An invisible trophy?
No. This is where we'll put
the hero of the year trophy.
But I haven't won yet.
The competition is
really fierce.
I think Bumblebee
has a good chance.
Girl, look around you.
You got the hero of the year
prize in the bag.
Precisely. And to celebrate,
we feast.
Come along, girls.
Aw, mom.
Who wants olives? Diana?
Mom, I don't like olives.
Since when?
It's in our blood
to like olives.
- More for me.
Mmm.
Your shield, Princess.
It's perfect.
Thank you.
I wish it serves you well
in your quest to win
the hero of the year award.
Of course, she'll win.
I was going to give you a gift
after tomorrow's ceremony
but why wait? Come.
The tiara of triumph.
Oh, hello.
Oh, my hera! The Ruby!
Hey!
There!
It's gone!
Down there!
What is that thing?
We'll find out
when we catch it.
--Whoa!
Bumblebee!
--Thanks for breaking
my fall, guys.
What just happened?
I don't know.
I think my power cut out.
Talk about
a major buzzkill.
Anybody see which way
that thing went?
No, it's gone.
The Amazons will find
that creature
and reclaim your Ruby
for the ceremony tomorrow.
Thanks, mom.
My heart
is filled with pride
for your
hero of the year triumph.
I'll do my best.
-Bye, mom.
-Goodbye, darling.
Godspeed, sweet Princess.
Barbara!
There you are.
What took you so long?
For Peter Pan's sake,
i was worried sick.
Your third period
forensics teacher told me
you missed class.
Dad, you're my third period
forensics teacher.
You knew I had
an off-campus pass
from principal waller.
Well, I approved that
before the hullabaloo
with that supervillain
attacking students.
A supervillain?
What happened?
Big barda found hawkgirl
unconscious.
Apparently, someone came out
of the amethyst
and stole her
nth metal belt.
- What?
-Oh, no!
The emergency meeting of
the junior detective society
is now starting.
So, someone came out
of the amethyst and
stole hawkgirl's belt.
Plus something stole
wonder woman's Ruby.
That makes two cases
of grand larceny.
Hawkgirl! Principal waller
said you were resting
in the nurse's office.
Heroes never rest.
Write that down,
that's important.
You got it, mama.
Don't call me, "mama."
Write that down.
You got it, not-mama.
- Whatchu doin', beast boy?
Hero of the year
rule 10.1.234.
Nominees may receive
hero of the year points
for helping
other heroes succeed.
I'm training him to be
a proper rule abiding hero
like me.
Whatever you say, teach.
That villain may have stolen
my nth metal belt
but he will not steal
my chance at hero of the year.
Now, I've done some research.
Show them, beast boy.
Aw, man, I must've left this
in my pants last week!
Mmm.
Pumpernickel.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, the research.
Get this, our amethyst is
an old portal to gemworld.
It's been inactive
for decades.
But that changed
this morning.
That's our fugitive.
-Dark opal.
-Dark opal?
Sounds more like
a jewelry store
than a villain.
Yo, dark opal's
a legit wickedy-wack
wicked dude.
He has some
mean magic stored
in that gem on his chest.
Gemworld? Gems?
Supergirl's crystal.
Maybe that has something
to do with all this.
And this is
capes & cowls cafe.
Home to all your favorite
superfoods from awesome
acai bowls to...
Large double spinach, sardine,
and pickleberry smoothie.
Ugh.
Yucko, bucko.
Mmm! Tastes just like
my favorite
Kryptonian dessert.
We need to
check your crystal.
Hmm.
Where did you get the crystal?
From my mom.
Go, Kara, hurry!
Mom, dad, come on!
-Sorry, Kara.
-This way,
I'll always be with you.
What do you mean?
No! You have
to come with me!
The spaceship can only
hold enough supplies for one.
-I love you, Kara.
-I wish it didn't have
to be this way.
Goodbye,
my dearest girl.
Supergirl, you okay?
Your crystal got all glowy
and you went to la-la land.
Not la-la land.
Krypton. My home.
Strange. There's this
repeating pattern.
It's almost
like morse code.
Could be signaling someone.
My mom said she gave me
the crystal so she could
always be with me.
Maybe she programmed it
so when she got
off Krypton
she could find me.
But weren't your parents
on Krypton when the planet,
you know,
exploded?
Maybe not.
They were
really smart scientists.
Maybe they built another ship.
Supergirl, we should wait
until we can learn more
before jumping to conclusions.
I have to tell Martha
and Jonathan!
My parents are coming for me!
And it's a signal!
If it just started doing this,
that means someone
is looking for it. Right?
Well, I don't know much
about those frequency things.
Yeah, of course,
uncle Jonathan.
But my parents
were scientists!
I'm gonna have a family again.
It's always good to have hope.
Well, we'll see you tomorrow.
I'd love to see that
hologram-brain-video
whatchamacallit
now with your crystal.
I haven't figured out
how to make it
turn on, yet.
Hello? Power on.
Open sesame.
As soon as my parents
get here, they could
teach me how to do it.
Oh, calamity,
look at the time!
We better be getting to bed.
We love you, dear.
Um, sure. Thanks.
Goodnight.
I'm waiting for you.
Mom and dad.
A hero is always polite.
A hero is vigilant
and prepared.
A hero greets his fans
with a firm but
not too firm handshake.
Excellent progress, beast boy.
Our guarding shift
is complete.
But training shall resume
at sunrise.
Sunrise? On a Saturday?
Uh, it will be my pleasure to
experience this interesting
time of day with you.
Bumblebee, you left your
hero history homework
in my room.
--Bumblebee?
Bumblebee? Um, okay.
It's... it's a movie.
Uh, three words.
Uh, if we're gonna
play charades,
pop back into regular size,
okay?
Argh! Batgirl, help!
My suit's busted, I'm stuck!
Can you see
why my suit went kaput?
Looks like there's
something wrong
with your battery.
That shadow creeper
must've damaged it
when he knocked me over.
So we just need
to get you a new battery.
I've got aas, 9 volts,
an old watch battery.
Not so easy.
Of all my powers,
growing takes the most energy
and I don't have enough power
left in my suit to get big.
But when I'm this size,
there's no battery
small enough
to fit in my pack.
Yet powerful enough
to make me big.
It's impossible!
I'm gonna be small forever!
Before you built
your super suit,
did anyone think
it was possible
to have a suit that
enabled someone to shrink?
No, I guess not.
You did the impossible once
and we'll do it again.
Yeah, honey!
- Ha!
They should have returned
with the artifacts by now.
Patience, dark opal.
We have waited many moons
for the crystal key
to reveal itself.
Soon, darkness will rule.
They're ready.
Earthen steel.
Mega metal of apokolips.
Sapphire of zamaron.
Plus the nth metal
of thanagar
and the Ruby of Themyscira.
Where's the key?
Where's the crystal
of Krypton?
The crystal is guarded
by a powerful protection aura.
It cannot be stolen.
It must be freely given
by the girl.
But I'll find a way, eclipso.
Of course, you will,
dark opal.
You're the Jewel sorcerer
of gemworld.
I upheld my end of the bargain
and I trust you will
uphold yours.
You will get the crystal.
Now, bring the alchemist.
You will combine
these treasures from
across the cosmos
into a scepter which will
let us rule the universe.
Never! I will not
betray my home.
Mmm. My black diamond
says otherwise.
Yes, master.
Now get the crystal,
dark opal.
Give the girl whatever
she wants in return.
Opal, show me what she wants.
Yes, of course!
Whatever she wants.
Hey,
who took my mega-rod!
Someone stole
my throwing star!
My ring! I've been burgled!
It's chasse, chasse
and pirouette,
then we leap like
graceful gazelle
galloping through a field
on her way to meet
her gal pals for lunch.
Cheetah, please.
I said gazelle in field.
You're doing more of
a wildebeest trumping through
a sticky swamp.
Start again, from the top.
--Five, six, seven, eight.
Yes!
Feel the dance in your feet.
Stick it in your socks,
let it seep between your toes.
The detective club discovered
that all the stolen objects
were precious metals or gems
from the supers' homes.
Principal waller!
I found big barda trying
to leave school grounds.
She must be the one
behind this.
I was just out
for a walk.
Lady Shiva,
do you have evidence
for your accusations?
The amethyst was infiltrated
the night of her arrival
and she's the one that
so conveniently found hawkgirl
after she was attacked.
Hard evidence, lady Shiva?
Not yet. But I won't stand by
and let my school,
my friends, be invaded again.
Heroes must take
preemptive measures.
Barda, you may go.
Argh!
Heroes serve justice,
not hunches.
And then you throw your hands
in the air like your
armpits are on fire.
Crazy quilt.
No, don't say it.
If you cancel the show
because of one villain,
the criminals win!
I'm not canceling
the ceremony.
But we're on high alert.
And must increase security.
We need extra bodies
for sentry duty.
Oh, but each dancer
is a unique snowflake
in the blizzard
of my production.
You can have cheetah.
Hey!
Has batgirl learned
anything more
about supergirl's crystal.
Nothing yet.
In light of the recent
supervillain activity,
the normally festive lead up
to the hero of the year
-has been subdued.
Who are you?
Vice principal grodd,
it's me, Lois Lane,
intrepid reporter.
You've denied my request
for interviews about
a million times.
Hmm. How do I know
you're not some villain
disguised as Lois Lane?
Can you confirm the identity
of the villain?
Is it true that the villain
came out of the amethyst?
Did you have any run-ins with
this villain during your time
as a criminal?
Yeah, you're Lois Lane,
all right.
Wait, tell me more about
how principal waller
got you out of prison.
Official paperwork says
it was part of some
work release squad.
Mom, is that you?
Oh, it's just starfire.
I have examined the airspace
but have not witnessed
any suspicious activity.
I did however have a run-in
with a gull of the sea.
Oh, sorry.
Hey, alphabet soupie!
We's doin' the overs
and unders on
the big award. You in?
No thanks, Harley.
I'm supposed
to take over for katana.
Have you seen her?
I think she's guarding
the park.
Thank you.
Katana!
Mom?
Mom!
Mom, it's me.
Your crystal.
Give it to me.
Is something wrong?
Are you okay?
Just hand it over, supergirl.
Supergirl?
My mom never...
You're not my mom.
No! That's mine!
Oh, fine...
Magic disguises are
so hard to maintain when
the fighting begins.
You're the one
they're looking for.
The downside of fame.
You get recognized
everywhere you go!
Give me the crystal.
No!
Supers! Help!
Help!
He's here! Help!
You're surrounded.
No, you are.
Fight!
- Huh?
I see you swipin'
and I raise you a left jab
right in the kisser.
You gonna be a Thorn
in my side.
Oh, poor sapling...
Oh! For the love of
goose grass!
The sun. It destroys them.
I always liked sunlight.
Retreat! To the palace!
Ugh! I hate hit and runs.
You failed!
Well, as evil partners
in this venture,
it's more like we failed.
We made a deal!
Oh, but the adrenaline
was pumping,
my heart was racing.
Who remembers
the exact terms?
I do.
After them!
Hurry.
What's the point?
They'll find us.
My magic is weakened
in this forest.
We can't fight them.
--They have us surrounded.
-We're going to be banished.
-Hide.
Eclipso, dark opal,
by order of the Princess,
show yourselves!
Everything is ruined.
We'll never rule gemworld.
It's over.
It's not over.
There has to be another way.
No, nothing. Not unless we...
Oh, no. That will never work.
What? Tell me.
There's a gem
more powerful than anything
in gemworld.
The prophecy says,
"when the last gem of
an extinct planet
"is bound with treasure
from across the universe,
"ultimate power shall reign."
Ultimate power.
How do we find this gem?
There must be clues
in the ancient texts.
I will need to remain here
as the royal sorcerer.
I could study the ancient text
and locate the gem.
Then, with its power,
we can rule
not just gemworld,
but the universe.
But I can only do that
if I weren't banished
because Princess amethyst
found me blameless
in the coup.
I will claim that you were
under the spell of
my black diamond.
When you find the gem
of ultimate power,
use the amethyst portal
to find me.
Together we will rule.
You take the blame,
I'll get us the gem. Deal?
Eclipso.
Where is dark opal?
Uh, where am I?
What happened?
I feel woozy.
Your little sorcerer
has been under my spell.
Oh, Princess amethyst?
Is that you?
What's going on here?
So you acted alone
in this treason?
Yes.
Then, by the power
of the 12 houses
of gemworld,
I banish you.
You gave me your word
and you didn't deliver.
I tried.
"A" for effort, right?
We will get that crystal.
Even if I have to go
to earth myself.
You're leaving
your nook?
But you can't!
There's light out there!
Darkness will
overcome the light.
Shadows to me.
See anything?
Nothing suspicious.
Sorry, I haven't seen him.
Thanks for
taking a look, Steve.
Batgirl, wait!
What is it?
Do you have an idea
about how to fix your battery?
Um, no.
I just wanted some grub.
Detective work
makes me hungry.
Now, back to
the hero of the year pre-show.
I'm all about
the classic thinkers.
Plato, Aristotle and
my main man, socrates.
But when we get into
19th century idealism,
I'm like,
I immanuel kant even.
Ew! Enough with
the highbrow humors.
Back to me!
Shouldn't you be
heading to the
hero of the year ceremony?
That villain tried to
steal your crystal.
I won't rest or party
until we get him.
Another dead end.
Well, what now?
Should we go back to
school and check
batgirl's surveillance?
We don't have to
go back to school
for that anymore.
What's this have to do
with surve...
Cool.
Amazing.
A super hero is
always prepared.
I have a few batcaves
around town.
Where are you,
dark opal?
There!
That's centennial park.
Come on!
- Bumblebee!
My suit's
losing more power.
When you're feeling rundown,
you always got a shoulder
to sit on.
-Thanks, batgirl.
-Come on!
You're mine, dark opal.
That's what you get
for messing with my friends.
I didn't do anything, please!
Why were you running?
I'm late
for my steampunk
cosplay group.
Is that a crime?
No, sorry.
-What now?
-We keep searching.
If we split up,
we can cover more territory.
Bumblebee and
i will take downtown.
Anyone seen
wonder woman, batgirl,
supergirl or Bumblebee?
-Nope.
-Did you check the garden?
I have not seen the girls
you are looking for.
Last I saw,
they were still looking
for dark opal.
Thank you, hawkgirl.
We can't start the ceremony
without two of our nominees.
Lois, you have to stall.
A mission from
principal waller. Yes!
- Miss martian!
I've been wanting
to get a few words from you,
but I can never find you.
Um... um... eek!
I got a few words for ya.
Harley Quinn. Superstar.
I told ya.
I don't know anything
about a dark opal
or dark topaz or
even a dark cubic zirconia.
She's telling the truth.
Now, I gotta get back
to my community service.
Hey! That's my car!
Shouldn't have parked in front
of the fire hydrant.
Pick it up at impound.
What do you see?
Nothing.
No sign of dark opal.
Find anything?
Yeah. A "buy one, get one"
free smoothie coupon
at capes & cowls cafe.
But no intel on dark opal.
Bumblebee how's the suit?
My battery's draining fast.
Every flutter of my wings
takes the power further
into the red.
And once the battery dies,
bye-bye super powers.
There's gotta be
a better battery
out there, somewhere.
Supergirl, your crystal.
Kara, my brave
and courageous girl.
Mom?
We are sending you
to earth and I'm sorry
we cannot go with you.
I have programed
this crystal,
so that you may remember us.
But, mom, why...
The crystal's powers
will activate when you're
old enough to understand.
When you need to
hear from us,
- our love, family...
A merry good evening
to my favorite hero trio.
It's dark opal.
He hacked into
my comm-bracelet.
Well, that's hardly
the greeting anyone
wants to hear.
But, nonetheless, I'm calling
because I've found
something of yours.
-Don't listen to him, babs.
-It's a trap.
Supergirl, stay where you are.
-Dad!
-Mom!
I thought about
keeping them as pets.
But I can't deal
with the maintenance.
The feeding, the walking.
It's just not for me.
So you can have them back.
I want supergirl's crystal.
But I couldn't be sure
if she'd give it up
for the kents alone.
So, wonder woman
and batgirl, I had
to drag you into this.
As her besties,
I bet you'll be
very persuasive.
You three meet me
at booster's gold mine.
Come alone
and tell no one.
Come on, girls.
Sorry, Bumblebee.
He said only the three of us.
And with your
battery running low,
you should conserve
your energy.
You guys. I'm not
letting you go meet
a super villain alone.
Batgirl's right.
Our parent's lives
are at risk.
We have to do exactly
what he says.
Okay, not much
i can do small anyway.
I may not have
a lot of power left,
but I'm still...
A hero.
Your plan won't work.
Supergirl won't give
you her crystal.
Argh!
Alchemist.
Bring me the scepter.
Master alchemist?
But you're an Amazon.
We're sisters.
Not anymore.
I serve darkness now.
No! Argh!
Once the crystal of Krypton
is set upon the scepter,
ultimate power will be yours.
Long live eclipso.
And dark opal, too!
Long live us!
- Aunt Martha.
- Dad.
- Uncle Jonathan.
- Mom!
Uh-uh.
No parents for you,
until I get my crystal.
-Who are you?
-This is eclipso,
my business partner.
Now that
we're properly introduced,
it's gift time.
No, supergirl,
if you give them the crystal,
they'll use it against you.
But if you don't hand
the crystal over,
they get it.
Argh!
Leave us, supergirl.
Save yourself.
You can still make it out.
Take it.
Now release them.
Diamond vanish.
-Dad.
-Mom.
Are you okay?
And reappear.
I call it the eclipso
rule of relativity.
"Whatever the black diamond
vanishes must reappear."
- Another one of
my diamond's tricks.
The eclipso explosive.
- No!
- Don't do it.
Stop!
-I won't let you
hurt my daughter!
Try that again
and I'll make it
even worse for them.
Now, for the last
and favorite trick of
my black diamond,
I'll need a volunteer or four.
- Mom!
- No.
- Dad!
- No, stop it!
What are
you doing to him?
Meet your new, improved,
evilified league of guardians.
Hail darkness.
-No!
-What's happening?
Don't!
Oh, no!
I gotta get that diamond.
Excellent.
You'll be coming
with us.
Our first minions.
Welcome to the eclipso family.
I said you're coming with us!
-Mom.
-Uncle Jonathan.
-Daddy.
-Aunt Martha.
Please.
Stop!
Get out of my head!
What happened?
My diamond
has never failed me.
-Supergirl.
-Oh, dear.
I'd never leave you.
Oh, fine. If you
love them so much,
stay here with your babies
to meet your doom.
Hurry, eclipso.
Before we meet our doom, too!
Whoa!
Whoa. Are you getting this?
Now, to bring these supers
into my Minion fold.
With an army
of evil heroes
at my disposal,
no one will dare
protest my power.
My diamond. What?
Doesn't matter now.
You have the scepter.
Yes.
The scepter.
Darkness, fall!
Hey.
-Who is that?
What happened?
-Whoa! What happened?
What is going on?
Greetings, supers.
Eclipso and dark opal.
I should have known
you two were working
together...
Not another step
from any of you.
I can't deactivate it.
I'll get you out of there.
-Hippolyta!
-I got ya.
-We have to save them!
-How can we get past it?
I'm on it.
Bumblebee.
If the diamond can create it,
it can break it.
Bumblebee sting.
Oh...
- Oh, mom.
- Dad.
Barbara.
My wonderful daughter.
You're okay.
-You did it.
-You set us free.
Hey, are you all right?
Battery's dead.
Can I catch a ride with you?
All aboard
the batgirl express.
What have I done?
It's all right, my sister.
Come on,
we have to get out of here.
That gem will never hurt
anyone again.
Thank you all,
for making this such easy
one stop shopping.
The artifacts from your
distant planets
will allow me to control every
sector of the universe.
Get them
while they're blabbing.
You're proper hero, yo.
Just like hawkgirl taught you.
Uh, excuse me.
But we prefer if you left,
so, good day to you,
sir and madam.
Oh, please.
Ah!
Nice catch.
-No!
-Stop him.
-You can't.
-We will not let you do this.
Get them!
Batgirl, get them to safety.
We'll meet you
back at school.
Now, I will be ruler of all.
You mean we.
Partners in darkness?
Co-rulers? Remember?
For my first act as
queen of everything,
I will make
that fiddling Princess
pay for banishing me.
I will destroy
the detestable land
of gemworld.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey now.
Gemworld wasn't all bad.
The citizens of gemworld
mocked me.
In their insolence,
they dare banish me.
And you,
you let me take the fall.
Eclipso!
Put down that scepter.
I thought I took care
of you already.
Darkness, attack.
What's happening?
What are these things?
They're everywhere!
Ugh! Shadows again.
Oh, did you come to play?
Who else wants to play?
We were
just getting started.
And you should have
a front row seat.
Hey!
Oh! You are
malleable like the gum
of the bubble.
Incoming!
You say it's your birthday?
I've got a present for you.
Don't crowd!
There's plenty for everybody.
- Who's next?
Ha!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo!
Beautiful darkness.
--Give me the scepter.
You promised we'd share.
Eyes on the prize.
Sorry, mom.
You're not getting away.
Whoo-hoo! That's our girl.
Kicking some villain keister.
Martha. Language.
Sorry. I'm still mad as a cow
over that evil diamond thing.
Boo-yah!
Freezer burn.
Frost passes it
off to Harley.
And it's Harley
for the win!
That's how we do it
old school.
Where did eclipso go?
Palace. The home.
Do I look like
the Internet to you? Details.
- It's...
It's on the moon!
-Anything else?
I shouldn't have become
a super villain.
I should have
followed my heart
and been a theater major!
Ugh.
No! My power!
My magic!
You go after supergirl.
I got this one.
Thanks, batgirl.
--Look what the bat dragged in.
Dad, call in
the special crimes unit.
I got one up here for ya.
Careful, babs!
You could...
...pull a muscle!
-Dad!
-I mean,
that is some
mighty fine police work.
Batgirl, light destroys
the shadows.
You need to fix
the electricity!
-I can do that.
-Hey, wait.
Could you put me down first?
The batgirl express is
on a one-way trip
to motion-sickness-ville.
Oops. Sorry.
You'll be safe here.
Terra firma.
What a day.
My belt.
Beast boy, can you get it?
- Well, certainly, madam.
I'm back in action.
Um, this is truly
a terrible predicament.
What is a gentleman to do?
Beast boy,
your way was better.
You gotta go wild.
Well, really?
Well, your wish is
my command, my lady.
-Yeah.
-High eight, momma!
My ring.
Ooh, love hurts.
Ha!
You wanna play games?
How about whack-a-shadow?
Help!
I'm coming, shivs!
Nice. I owe you one.
Nah, it wasn't a favor.
It's what friends do.
You really have changed.
Shh. Don't tell anyone.
If people start believing
I've gone good,
I'll have to show up
to birthday parties,
hand out Valentine's,
and help people move. No.
It's gross.
They're scared
of the spotlights.
You're looking succulent.
Ha! Right in the keister.
Come out, eclipso. It's over.
The crystal's gone.
Lucky you.
I wanted to destroy
my home world.
- But you've already
had that done for you.
Get up! I'm taking you in.
Huh?
You okay?
-Yeah. Now that you're here.
-Where is she?
There!
- Watch out!
Huh?
-Where is she?
-There!
23 degrees on your left.
--Oh, yeah. We won.
A piece
of supergirl's crystal.
She's going to want this.
Let me out of this lasso.
I'm scared of going to prison.
Those fluorescent lights
so bright! I hate bright.
I'll take it from here.
Let me out of here!
-I don't want to share
a ride with her!
-Ugh!
I don't want to share a ride
with you, more.
You let children
defeat us again!
Supergirl!
I found a piece
of your crystal.
Thanks, Bumblebee.
Goodbye, mom.
I miss you.
Nothing can destroy
this crystal.
Because nothing can destroy
my love for you.
Take that love
into your new world.
When you share our love
with others,
you'll create a new family.
Thanks, mom.
Are you all right, dear?
I am now.
It's good to be home.
Ooh! I love you guys.
What is it, oracle?
Group hug detected
in sector j.
--You okay?
Yeah, I was just thinking,
if that crystal had enough
power to charge the scepter,
i bet it could power my suit.
Maybe we can make
a battery that replicates it.
Hold that thought.
I couldn't help but overhear.
You really think my crystal
could fix your suit?
Maybe. If we could
study it more and see
how it generates power,
maybe we can make
a synthetic version.
Why wait?
One sliver of crystal
coming up.
But it's your crystal.
Mom did say to share.
Thanks, supergirl.
Let me help.
Beast boy, can I borrow
your monocle?
Keep it.
I don't needs it anymore.
- Whoo-hoo!
Welcome to
the hero of the year gala!
Hold for applause.
Hello?
Hey, yo, blanket dude!
We gots to get you
to the party!
Whoo! What a week!
Isn't this lovely?
You're all heroes of the year
in my book.
Now dig in
before it gets cold.
Tell me when.
When!
I brought macaroons!
Wonderful!
Oh, thank you, Mr. quilt!
And this, young lady,
is for you!
You all did some magnificent
hero-ing this year.
But we have considered
what happened today,
and Bumblebee
tipped the scales
with her sacrifice.
Congratulations on winning
hero of the year!
- Me?
-Go, Bumblebee!
--Right on, Bumblebee!
Good job!
-You're the girl, Bumblebee!
-Congrats.
Great hero-ing, Bumblebee.
-Way to go, honey.
-Up top, baby girl!
-Thanks, mom and dad.
-Well deserved.
Even when you had problems
with your suit,
you persevered
and your heroic heart
stayed true.
I had a whole speech
about the smallest hero
making the biggest difference,
but I guess everybody's
rumbly tummies couldn't wait.
You're not mad I didn't win?
It's just a trophy.
You will always
be my hero.
Ah! There's an olive
in your salad.
-You don't like olives.
-Aw. You remembered!
Aw. No pumpernickel?
Good thing I brought my own!
Mmm.
Armpit pumpernickel's
my jam!
So good!
If you like this,
you should be here
for the holidays
when Martha
really goes all out.
That's a great idea!
Barda, why don't you
stay with us over
the holiday break?
You're invited, too,
lady Shiva.
Yeah! I'll be here
and there's an extra
bunk bed in the attic.
So, wanna stay with me
and my family?
-Uh, all right.
-Okay.
Hey, shivs.
I'll rock paper scissors you
for top bunk.
One, two, three.
-Paper!
-Uh, what?
On what planet
does paper beat rock?