Hey!
Hey.
Someone's still in bed.
Hey, babe,
what if we stay in
for dinner tonight
and I cook?
Just the two of us?
Man:
Instead of going out?
Yeah, sure.
Whatever you want.
Really?
That's cool.
I have chicken.
- I like chicken.
I'm a chicken man.
Woman:
Hi, mom.
Oh, how are you?
Mahjong?
You don't play mahjong,
do you?
I gotta go.
Let me call you
in a little bit.
All right,
i love you.
All right. Bye.
Rachel?
Oh, my god.
Oh, um.
Woman on TV:
...San Francisco private jet
to Georgia...
Hey, man,
how's it going?
- Man: Joshy called me.
- Woman: Is he okay?
Do you remember
when I put
the deposit down
on that house in Ojai
for his bachelor party?
Well, I guess the person
that owns the house
called, uh, joshy,
and they were like,
"what are gonna do?"
- Right.
- So, um-- so then
he called me.
And was like,
"what do you wanna do?"
'Cause you can't get
the deposit back.
And he's like,
"well...
We have the house."
- Are you gonna go?
- Mm, I don't know.
Are you stoned?
Hey!
Hey, man.
- How are you?
How are you?
What?
What the fuck
was that?
Be careful!
I was saying
"how are you?" Before.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
It just-- it obviously
wasn't the best time.
Yeah.
Joshy!
Joshy?
Hmm.
Dude...
Don't touch it.
It's a fucking
sniper rifle.
It's a bb gun.
See?
It's loaded.
Goddamn right it is.
Man:
Think about what it
would have been like
as a child in 1939
or 1964
to get taken
by your parents
to the New York
world's fair, right?
So they take you
to, I don't know, say,
the Chilean pavilion.
And you're
smelling Chilean food
for the first time.
You've never even
seen it before.
- You're seeing people dressed
in traditional Chilean garb--
hey, guys.
Ari? Adam?
I'm Eric.
- Oh, hey, man.
- Oh, yes, dude.
So funny on
the reply alls, man.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Oh, thanks, man.
I like to set
a little tone
over email
just to let people know
what kind of bro
they're gonna get.
- No, it was hilarious.
- For sure. Tone set.
I don't know if Joshua
gave you any background
on me,
but I live with him
in the same housing complex.
Lived with him.
But that's actually what
i think this weekend's
gonna be great for.
It's, like, just
cleansing the palate.
Keep it light,
keep it fun.
Yes, keeping it light,
i think, is Paramount.
You brought a bunch
of board games.
Awesome.
Yeah, this is kind of
the big one that I'm
looking forward to.
"Mecha dungeon crawl,"
have you seen this?
No.
It's a really big, long
complicated co-op game.
That it'll take
a couple hours to
go through the directions.
- So it's like "cranium"?
- No, it's not like "cranium."
It's a lot more
complicated than that.
More like
"apples to apples"?
No, it's not like that
at all either.
We got a portion of time
that will be perfect
for, like, these games.
Like, you and Josh
can do that.
- And, like, you and I can...
- Get high?
- Burn it up.
- I have a one-hitter.
Actually, do you guys mind
not doing that in here?
You know, I just wanna
be able to come in here
and get in bed
and sleep
and not have ash
and detritus
and paraphernalia
everywhere.
Okay, no detritus
in this room.
I'm a backpack hip-hop kid,
you know?
- Oh, of course. Uh-huh.
- J5, dilated peoples,
- like, everybody, you know?
- Yeah, I love
tribe called quest.
- Stone's throw.
- Yeah, stone's throw is cool.
But I also like t swift,
you know?
- Josh: Hey!
- Hey, Joshua!
Hey, Eric.
Oh, my god!
Holy shit.
Hey. Hi.
I'm katee.
- Hey.
- Thanks for coming, dude.
- Yeah, yeah, thanks...
- Heard so much about you.
How are you?
You okay?
I don't know who you are.
I like hugging you, though.
- I'm katee.
- So, uh,
are you, like,
the property manager here?
- No.
- Of the prop--
no, no.
- No, no.
- No, I'm just--
I'm katee.
- Yeah, katee from Ojai.
- Katee from Ojai.
- Friend from Ojai.
- Just met last night.
Do you wanna hang out?
We're gonna get into a Cypher.
- I should probably go.
- Okay.
But you have fun.
Have fun.
- I'll walk you to your car.
- Oh.
- Bye.
- Katee: I'm so glad
I got to see you.
- Um, yeah.
- Yeah.
She seemed
really cool, man.
- Who, katee?
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, she was, she is.
She is very cool.
- How did you meet her?
- I got here yesterday.
- Right.
- So I was here
before anyone else,
and, uh,
i had nothing to do.
- So I went to
the bar in town.
- Uh-huh.
And I don't know.
I just, like,
was at the bar
and she came up to me,
starting chatting,
and it was, like,
super easy to talk to.
"It was." She was
Good for you, man.
I'm really happy for you.
Well, look, she's cool.
She really is.
I mean, we're not gonna
get married or anything,
but...
Who else are we gonna
be able to celebrate
this, uh,
sexual victory with?
Yeah, when is
everybody else coming?
Um, this--
this is
actually the crew.
Everybody else
kind of flaked.
I know it's
only four of us.
Is that weird?
No, no,
it's not weird at all.
I think, um-- I think
a small crew is cool.
Yeah, we're gonna
be like the Beatles.
We are like the Beatles.
- You're like John and Paul.
- I'm Ringo 'cause
i keep it light
and I look a little bit
like a possum.
And I'm George
'cause I'm stony
and I, you know,
can't get enough of the sun.
I'm, uh,
I'm George Martin.
Yeah, the integral
fifth beatle.
I love
meeting new people.
This guy's
got fucking blow.
You're dropping
squirt bombs.
This guy won't
get in the pool,
but he will.
- If it's weird,
say it 'cause I know...
- It's not weird.
Ari:
Hey, what are you
doing over there, man?
I'm still trying
to get the Wi-Fi to work.
Yeah, we're in
a cabin in Ojai.
The Wi-Fi's
not gonna work.
Yeah, but, I mean,
i can't not be accessible
on the Internet
and also up here with
no cell phone reception
- for an entire weekend.
- Who cares?
It's the weekend.
When I got off the 101,
i called shauna
and I was like, "okay,
I'm going where there's
no reception.
- Love you."
- Yeah, but I didn't
make that call to Marissa.
So she doesn't know
that I'm here
and she doesn't know
that I'm unreachable
should she be trying to call
or email me or whatever.
Why doesn't Marissa know
that you're here?
She just,
you know, decided
that she needed
to be somewhere else
that I don't live
for the time being.
Oh, shit.
I'm sorry, man.
She's just basically
coming at me
and saying, you know,
that after 10 years almost,
that there's
an entire life
that she feels
like she's missing
and that she sort of
needed some space,
and i
responded to that
by being what I felt
was very attentive
and what she felt
was clingy.
I'm sorry.
It's-- it's gotta
be really hard.
- Break-ups are tough.
- It's not a break-up,
you know,
at this time.
- Okay.
- I think that
there might be
some benefit here to having
some friends around.
And maybe, you know,
we're talking about it now
and I'll talk
about it with Josh
as soon as I get a chance.
I wouldn't tell Josh
about it, I think,
because we're
on thin ice here.
There's only four of us.
No one showed up.
It's just that he's hurting
and he's been going
through a lot
and now
I'm hurting, too,
and I feel like we sort of
are going to relate
to each other
in a way that
i don't expect you to get.
Let's not compare
the hurt of a break-up
or whatever it is
with what joshy
went through.
Okay, so everybody gets one
of these character cards.
And I'm now going
to go into the attack
and defending portion.
You ready?
"Attack abilities
and attacking a monster.
The type of symbol
shows whether it is
a melee ability
or a ranged attack
ability."
Uh, yes. Adam,
i have a question.
Is it-- okay,
i can answer it
because I think I know
what you're going to say.
- What?
- If you're wondering
why the part on the bottom
of your figurine
is an octagon
and it's standing
on a hexagonal shape
that connects
to the center one,
I promise you
we're going to
get to that
- very, very shortly.
- Was that your question?
That was not my question.
Here's my question.
Should we be playing
this game right now?
- Yeah, definitely, 100%.
- Yeah.
Eric;
Can I just pose
another option?
We go out tonight,
we go to this bar
the lone Angus.
I've done a bunch of research
on yelp and trip advisor.
It's a fun local bar.
It's, like, divey,
but not too divey.
Maybe the time
to go to the bar
would be, I don't know,
tomorrow afternoon
for happy hour
or something,
when, you know,
it's light out
and they have the windows open
and the drinks are cheaper.
What's the deal with you
and the windows open at a bar?
It's just nice
to get that bar smell
wafting out a little bit.
Okay, let's say we go
to the bar tonight,
have some drinks,
mellow, nothing crazy.
Come back here,
wake up in the morning,
we're sitting
around the table,
we are ready to settle in
to a full game.
Josh:
Well, just to be clear,
Adam and I have been
coveting this game
for quite some time.
We even actually
helped crowd fund it.
We just opened it
tonight.
Right, or we could
go to the bar,
and if the bar
is not cool,
then we could
just come back here
and play tonight.
I mean, how fun would that be?
Like a late-night game.
If you're serious
about doing it
tomorrow,
then, yeah,
i mean, the--
it's something
to consider, I guess.
Eric:
So I have a lot planned.
We're gonna do
a little dinner tonight,
we're gonna
go to the casino,
play a little cards.
- Josh: Yeah.
- Yeah.
Have a bite to eat.
We're not gonna
just drink, though.
- We're gonna have
a nice dinner.
- Welcome to the lone Angus.
I will be your waiter.
My name is Greg.
- Nice to meet you, Greg.
- Right on.
So I got four
Tequila shots here
- and a diet coke
on the rocks.
- Sweet.
We didn't order those
Tequila shots, though,
- so I think we're good.
- Well, that's, uh,
not what the bartender
is telling me.
It's okay, though.
I mean, like, we're...
- Yeah, we'll take them.
- Right, but we didn't
order them,
so I don't think
we should have to
- pay for them.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa,
speaking of which,
did you guys order
these drinks
that you already have
at the bar?
Yes, because
you weren't here, so...
Yeah, but there's
table service here.
Yeah, but you weren't here.
We waited for 15 minutes.
I was here. No, I've
been here since 5:00.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, I've been here.
It's okay, okay.
We'll take the shots.
- ...like every asshole does.
- Oh, we're assholes now?
- Yeah, you're an ass...
- Eric, Eric.
Maybe you could bring me
a windshield wiper
because you just spit
all over my fucking face!
Greg:
Why don't you take
that windshield wiper
and shove it
right up your ass?!
- Oh, what's up, man?
- Hey, man, how you doing?
Greg:
That was great.
Hi, guys.
You should see
your faces right now.
We just fucking
pranked you guys.
That was one
of the best ones
we've ever done.
You guys,
this is my boy, Greg.
I invited him to join us
for the weekend.
This is Josh, this is Ari,
this is Adam.
Adam, nice to meet you.
Greg.
Ari? Greg.
Josh, the man
of the hour. Greg.
Sit down, sit down,
sit down.
Thank you guys so much
for including me.
- Thank you so much.
- Definitely.
- Not a problem.
- Thank you for...
And my boy here told me
there was a bachelor party,
and I was just like,
"oh, can I come?"
He was like,
"you got it."
Yeah, no, I, uh--
it's just that, um,
i was gonna get married,
but I'm not anymore,
so we're kind of just
salvaging the weekend,
- and it's just for guys.
- Yeah, yeah, we're just, uh--
we're treating this
like a boy's weekend.
I thought you said that
this is a bachelor party.
- Um...
- You're not even
getting married?
Well, no, he's--
but we're treating it
like the fun
of a bachelor party,
but it's just
a boy's weekend away.
You know what? Yeah,
we're not even really
using that word.
- You guys break up?
- Essentially, I was
gonna get married,
- but now it's
not gonna happen.
- I just can't stress enough
- that we should just move on.
- It just sort of
turned into--
- kind of like a guy's weekend.
- Live right now
in the moment.
Hey, man,
that's all I'm doing.
That's what all I'm about.
Let's just do our shots
to-- to nothing.
- Yeah, to nothing.
- To nothing.
- To nothing is a great idea.
- For the weekend.
- Fuck that bitch.
- She doesn't deserve you.
- Eric: Again, not...
- Yeah, maybe.
- So as I mentioned,
I actually invited Greg
to join us for the weekend
as we have
that extra room
because this guy
brings the party to 11.
Yeah, thanks so much
for having me.
- Well, you know...
- It's so gracious
of you guys to include me
on this very
special weekend.
I was thinking because
we have fewer people
than we thought
that we would
kind of spread out
so no one has to
share a room,
so we don't actually have
an extra one anymore.
Yeah, and, like,
since you guys are boys,
maybe you guys could
just share a room.
Ooh, oh, no,
i can't do that.
I can't, uh, I can't
room with somebody.
And trust me,
none of you want
to room with me
'cause I just
got diagnosed
with sleep apnea,
- and I gotta wear that mask.
- Yeah, dude's like bane.
Hello, would you like
your dick sucked?
- Whoa! Yeah.
- Classic bane joke.
- Terrible bane.
Let's cheers it up
to new beginnings.
- Ari: To new beginnings.
- Love it.
- To new beginnings, right?
- Oh, my shit's empty.
- You know, whatever.
- Hey, waiter,
why don't you
go get another drink?
Fuck you!
Ari:
Excuse me, I don't want
to speak to no doctor!
I want to speak
to a pharmacist!
Yeah, man.
Oh, goodness.
- Oh, yeah.
- Shockingly cold.
Greg is a trip, huh?
Dude, Greg
is the best!
I'm kind of
a big fan of him.
- Yeah.
- He's so intense.
- Yeah!
- I'll send it to you.
What's your number?
- Please do.
Are you cool?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I'm great, how are you?
I'm good, I'm good.
I mean, I just
wanna make sure
that--
that you're good
with all of-- with all of
how everything is going.
Yeah, yeah, no.
This is, um, lining up
to be a fun one.
It was just, like,
scurrying all around
the floor,
and we had, like,
an English muffin
we didn't want to--
Eric:
You know, turtles are,
like, an aphrodisiac.
You wanted
to eat the turtle?
Woman: In retrospect,
you could've just
picked it up
by the little shell
on the sides
and been
completely okay.
Eric:
My buddy
will pick you up...
...backlogs of nonsense
that go back two years.
Right, but why
is this the time
to be bringing any...
But wh-- but it just--
it's not even relevant
to what we're
talking about anymore.
It's not a part of what
I'm trying to discuss,
and to say that
it's something
that I've been
willingly or intentionally
neglecting is insane.
I'm happy
you guys are here.
- Are you kidding? Yes.
- I think we're being followed.
No. I'm sorry.
- I'm looking...
- What is happening?
Who are you?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm looking
for my phone.
- Okay.
- Oh, okay.
Did you guys see
a phone?
- Um, did it have a case?
- Woman: No.
- Ugh.
- Caseless.
I haven't seen it.
I'm sorry,
this is Josh.
- Oh, hi, Josh.
- Oh, yeah, I'm Josh.
- I'm Jodi. Hi.
- Hey, Jodi.
- I'm Ari.
- Hi, Ari.
- How's it going?
- Oh, do you want me
to hold that for you?
Yes, please.
- Can I hold it in my lungs?
- Yes, please.
Um, you are cold.
- You need a...
- How can you tell?
Maybe, um...
- I'm gonna give you
my sweater.
- Oh, well, thank you.
- You're such a gentleman.
- Oh, here.
- Have two.
- Thank you.
No, I don't need it.
- No, have two.
- Don't please.
Look what's happening.
Double the warmth.
Double gentleman attack!
- What?
- I'm sorry.
Are you guys
murderers or what?
No, not at all.
We are not murderers.
- Yeah.
- What are you doing
here in Ojai?
Yeah, what brings you here?
Are you local?
I'm here for, like, a big
birthday vacation weekend.
- I'm turning 30.
- Both: Wow, awesome!
- You're with friends?
- Yeah.
- Okay, cool.
- They're not cool right now.
They're real--
they're real shitty.
Well, we're having
sort of a weird--
not weird,
but, like, a party thing.
Nothing like
a weird party thing.
I think all party things
are kind of weird.
- Hello.
- Jodi: Well, hello.
- Hey, this is--
- hi.
Did someone say
"weird party thing"?
Hello,
my name is Adam.
My name is Jodi.
We are all robots.
Well, I'm single now,
so, you know, um...
- What the fuck
are you doing?
- Adam, really?
- What?
- Are you okay?
Well, I got a couple bars,
so I made a phone call.
Uh, I'm sorry to drag you
into my business.
Jodi:
No, I actually
am into it.
Yeah, 10 years of my life
just went down the shitter.
- We talked about this.
- No, man.
- We talked about that.
- Yeah, but everything's
changed now.
It's all different.
It sucks now.
- Everything's worse.
- So you and Marissa, no?
Yeah, no, no go.
You know, 10 years
right in the shitter.
It's fine, but, hey,
on the other hand,
Eric has found
some casino near here
that he says
is the best in the area.
- Ari: Well, that sounds fun.
I would go to a casino.
- There's a casino here?
Didn't expect you guys
to actually be
so excited about that.
You look so cold
and stupid, both of you.
Do they look
like murderers, though?
- Yeah.
- Here, I don't need this.
Thank you very much.
I don't need both, yeah.
Total enthusiasm
for Eric's casino idea?
No one just kind of thought
we were gonna go home
after this
and, you know,
have bedtime and...
- Have bedtime?
- Hey, Adam, is this...
Well, what do you call it
when it's time to go to bed?
- The time I go to bed.
- Are you okay?
Yeah, I mean, you know,
of course not, but...
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
to come out here
and just blurt, I mean...
- No, no, that's big.
That's huge.
- I just got off the phone.
And looked over and I saw
Eric
and what's-his-name
and you guys over here,
and I just kind of
felt like I had to
say something to somebody,
but i
shouldn't have. I...
Well, look, if you need
to talk about it, you can.
- No, I'm good, thank you.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- I could go like that.
That does feel warmer,
but I'm actually...
And your arms
are weirdly heavy.
I'm a big, thick
kind of oxey Jew.
You kind of are.
You look like
someone's cousin
or, like, a boy from camp
who was, like, my crush.
Oh, what camp
did you go to?
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, 'cause I went to camp
back east, so I...
- Me, too.
- Where?
- Blue star.
- Shut up.
I went to blue star.
- You shut up now.
- No, you shut up now.
- Prove it.
- Blue star
where the Jews are.
Yeah.
- Both: Hey!
- Oh, damn it!
Oh, snaps.
Guys, we're gonna
go to the casino.
Do you wanna come?
- Me?
- Yeah, you should come.
- Adam: Yeah, we need
a lady luck.
- The more the merrier.
I'll be
your lady luck.
But I really wanna
find my phone.
And I'm actually
kind of feeling like
i left it in my house.
Like, I did not even
bring it here
to begin with
'cause I'm chill
and I wanna unplug.
Yeah, of course.
Get out of the matrix.
Do you think you
would walk me down
just to see
if it's there?
I don't actually
wanna get murdered.
Uh, yeah, well,
i would love to,
but joshy's actually,
um, like, used to
come up here as a kid.
- He's knows the area
pretty well.
- We'll go to the casino.
You come
meet us later, right?
- You, too.
- No, I will gladly
walk you home.
Jodi:
Did you ever hear about
when there was
a pyramid of tampons
that got set on fire
and then pushed down
into the middle
of the lake?
Shut up.
That was you?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Oh, my god.
That thing, like,
almost burned down
a couple of boats.
And it stunk
because it was
like a chemical fire!
Like, what are the odds
that you as a child
saw the same things
that I saw as a child?
Actual same summers?
No, it's crazy.
Similar summers.
- Yeah.
- Similar summers.
- Tonie!
- Eric: Tonie, positive vibes,
positive energy.
- I should be careful.
- Adam, look at this.
You got exactly
what you wanted.
We're all sitting around
playing a game together.
I wanted to play,
like, a co-op game
that we could all
sort of just work
together as friends.
But we are
playing together.
We're all
cooperating together
against tonie here.
It just kind of
feels to me like--
like a little bit
of a monkey's paw
at this point.
What does that mean,
monkey's paw?
Well, like, I wished
we were all playing a game,
and now I got my wish,
but it's like
the saddest, weirdest,
worst version of that
because I'm
just losing money
and I'm stressed out.
So it's like if you went
to a monkey seller
and you said,
"hey, give me a monkey,"
and then he just
gave you the hand?
No, I mean, I think
you're thinking of it
too literally.
- The hand is cursed.
- Eric: Like a leprechaun.
You know, you get them,
and then they fucking--
- they're kind of shady.
- Greg: I thought
they were shady
before you caught 'em,
but once you caught 'em,
- they were, like, your slave.
- Well, ta-da.
This is actually--
this is amazing.
- Yeah.
- You should see
the place I'm staying.
It's like a--
a turquoise dealership.
It's like
a kidnapper shack.
Yeah, oh,
very much so.
Yeah, I'm imagining
like the sock
that a teenage boy
uses to, like,
- jerk into made
into, somehow, a house.
- Jerk off into?
That is pretty--
pretty accurate.
Ew.
Thanks for the, um,
walk back here.
It was very nice.
No, thank you.
It was, um,
so weird to meet someone
from blue star.
- I know.
- It's so crazy.
Yeah. You know me.
Um, I'm gonna go inside,
but I'll give you this.
- Oh.
- 'Cause I'm not a thief
even though I probably seem
really rough and tough,
I'm not a thief
and I'm not gonna
steal your sweater.
- Okay, good night.
- Good night.
- Thank you.
- Yeah. No, thank you.
Are you waiting there
for me to get in?
Hmm? Yeah,
i don't wanna leave
till you get in.
That's so nice.
That's what you do.
Um, i--
I don't have my key.
Sorry, I forgot.
I smoked your weed,
my fault.
- Okay.
- I didn't think about
- whether or not
i had a key.
- Okay.
And I feel
really embarrassed.
Like, oh, some girl
i met in a bar.
- Come on, let's go
back to the bar.
- But I don't have my phone,
- and I don't have my purse.
- We're gonna go back
to the bar.
- There's a lot of things
to be embarrassed.
- I'm your friend.
Dude, this guy
used to fucking go
to the parking lots
at dead shows--
- I fucking did, man.
- And fucking run
drum circles.
Dude, I ran
I sold acid
for, like, five minutes,
and then I got freaked out
and I stopped.
I saw the last
grateful dead show.
I saw the last one they did
at the meadowlands.
You were not
at the last show.
I was at the last show.
Don't try and hitch
onto my thing, okay?
- That's not cool.
- Joshua?
Joshua, you seem kind of
down and gloomy doomy.
- No, no.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- 'Cause I got the solution.
-  And it's more combo.
- What did you do?
- It's called dramarama,
but ours is fake
and it was, like--
it was
the first day of my period
and I had a heavy flow.
And I put my pad in the trash
at my friend's house,
but then her French poodle
took the pad out of the trash
and her hot brother
saw that, like,
my pussy bleeds
or whatever.
- And it was just, like...
- It was like penthouse letters
- for chicks
who get their period.
- What's penthouse letters?
Oh, my god.
Hello?
It's super twin peaksy,
and I fucking hope
my shitty friends
took my purse.
Well, I don't know
what you're doing now,
but you can come hang out
with my shitty friends.
Uh, yeah, I'll hang out
with your shitty friends.
- Like, do they suck?
- Oh, yeah, they suck so bad.
- Cool.
- Yeah, you will
hate them.
And they're all
going through some
real hardcore emotional shit.
- Oh.
- So it'll be a good hang.
How could I resist?
You have been convicted
of the crime
of stealing
a loaf of bread!
Greg:
No, no, please!
You've already
burned down my
jewelry store!
Oh, god!
Holy shit!
Ow! God, that hurt!
- - Oh, but it was so good.
It was so funny.
Hey, it's the girl
from the bar!
- Hey!
- Jodi.
- Hi.
- Hi, Jodi. I'm Eric.
- Jodi?
- Hey.
- Greg: Do you spell it
j-o-d-i?
- You okay?
Here. For that,
let me kiss you
- like the Europeans say hello.
- Okay, okay.
- No, I'm just
gonna say hello...
- You are saying hello.
- You are saying hello,
all right?
- Oh, okay.
- Jodi: Hi, hi.
- Greg: I get it,
I get it, okay.
- You wanna smoke weed?
It's right here.
- Yes, thank you.
Very unsettling.
He's pointing
a gun at me.
- Jodi: I don't want that.
- It's a bb gun!
Oh, same thing.
It's always weird.
Josh, we have
some guests now.
You still seem a little
boo-boo-boo-boo.
- I'm fine.
- Here, can I make
a suggestion?
Oh, well, how are we
stepping it up, kemosabe?
The g-rock over here
is gonna shoot me...
- In the dick!
- Greg: Oh, yes!
Yes, he's gonna shoot me
in the dick hole.
I'm gonna hold the cup
on top of my head,
but then
he's gotta shoot me
- straight in my dinger.
- Okay, all right!
You really want me
to do that?
And if--
if the cup falls,
the he gets to shoot me
in my bonanza hole.
The bonanza hole?
You know what I think
a butt hole looks like?
Is it just--
i think it looks like
a chimp victim's eye.
Joshua, could I have
a little Harry Carey
play-by-play
commentary, please?
Oh, perfect.
That's great,
that's great.
Well, I was
just thinking
a year ago,
we were all here--
here with our ladies.
You know, uh, Marissa
and shauna and--
and Rachel.
It's interesting that,
I don't know.
I was just thinking
about that.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- I'm sorry.
Josh, Josh, Josh,
look at me.
It's not okay.
It's not okay
to be sad!
You understand?
You are meant to be happy.
That is who you are.
This sad person,
that is something
that you think that you are,
but you're not that!
If you were
meant to be sad,
being sad
would feel good.
But it doesn't, does it?
What feels good?
Being happy!
And you should feel good,
so be happy!
Be who you are.
- Sorry. I...
- No, no, no, no.
- I didn't mean to--
- no, no, no.
Look, you're not
allowed to apologize
the rest of the time
that I'm here.
Thank you
for that, Greg.
Eric:
Yes, Greg!
Good pep talk!
How about, Joshua,
that we create
some new memories?
- What do you mean?
- Joshua,
I'm about to get shot
in my dick hole for you.
So please just give me
a little commentary.
- Do Harry Carey.
- Uh, Greg,
now lining up
his-- his rifle.
He's got it lined up
to shoot Eric in the penis.
If the red cup falls,
Eric's gotta get shot
in the bonanza hole.
Right where
the chimp victim's eye is.
That's beautiful!
Oh, my god!
Ooh-hoo-hoo-hoo!
It didn't go in my d-hole,
but it clipped
my yam sack!
Oh, my god,
you clipped his sack!
A fucking bet is a bet.
The cup fell,
so it looks like
you're gonna be shooting me
- right in my fucking bonanza.
- All: No, no, no!
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah!
- Rules are rules.
- Adam: You know, maybe--
I mean, do you
really wanna be shot
in the bonanza?
Maybe we could
do something that
everyone is involved with.
Like, you know,
with six of us,
we could just get
a short campaign going
of mecha dungeon crawl.
Mecca?
Mecca dungeon cr--
like, this is islamic?
- No, it's, like, mechanical.
- It's a very complicated
board game.
We could just
play through it quickly
and with so many people,
it would go pretty fast.
I think
that it's bad for me
to play a game that's
very complicated
right now
because I smoked tons of--
ripped so much.
I had a bong and I feel
like it's not my preference
to play a game.
And I'm not gonna be able
to get there with you.
We could play the very,
very complicated game
that could last
six to seven hours
with a couple of strangers
who are all fucked up on pot,
or we could
go into the hot tub.
I'll go in the hot tub!
The lady
wants the hot tub.
- Hot tub.
- The gentleman
wants a hot tub.
- Joshy?
- Yeah, well--
great. Hot tub time.
Here, I'll just
take this from you.
Greg:
Yeah, take it.
I don't want it.
- Eric: All right, man.
- Jodi: We're ready
for bubbles.
- Oh! Okay.
- Gee, man.
- Oh, my god.
- There's a slight problem
with the hot tub.
It is not
currently hot.
- Oh.
- There's steam
coming out of it.
Well, that's just
because the water
is warmer than the air.
All right, well, let's
fucking party inside.
Uh, not so fast.
Got a satellite view of
the entire neighborhood here.
Found the appropriate
neighbors' hot tubs,
and I think I found
our spot right here.
Are you talking
about to sneak in?
Uh, yes, we're gonna do
a little sneaking.
And we're gonna do
a little dip,
- then we'll do
a little dash.
- And it's perfect too.
It's perfect 'cause
there's none of those
security stickers
on any of the gates,
so we'll get in fine.
- Oh, ho!
- I say let's do it, man.
Ojai is communal hot tubs.
My hot tub is your hot tub.
To the hot tub!
Oh, okay,
we're going right now.
Adam, don't you
wanna come in?
No, it's not my thing.
You just snuck in
to sit here?
Yeah, well,
i wanna be around people
to hang out.
But, you know,
I'll let them have their fun.
It's not really for me.
I'm sorry I didn't
wanna do your game.
That's fine.
You know, no one
wants to do it,
so, it's, you know,
you're just part
of the gang.
Yeah, well, I know
I'm a stranger
who's, like, on drugs
and drunk and doesn't
have any pants on,
but I'm wishing you
the best.
- I hope you're okay.
- I guess you're the first
of many new
pantsless women
i will soon meet.
- Ari: Hey, Jodi?
- Sure. Yeah.
- No, it's okay.
I know you wanna go in.
- I'm sorry.
You know, I do have,
like, some okay friends.
I have a friend that
i could introduce you to
tomorrow if you're interested.
She's nice and fun.
She's not that nice,
but she's pretty fun.
Yeah? Does she like
desperate, broken men
with nothing to offer?
Most American women
like that kind of thing.
- Eric: Welcome
to the hot tub.
- Oh!
Eric:
Welcome to
the hot tub, Jodi!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You guys hear that?
What?
Oh, it's probably
the fondas.
They wanna join us
in the tub.
- Hey, Jodi?
- What?
Do you have
any words about joining
the greater tub community?
Cool, fun, new,
a surprise.
Tonight, the evening.
I love it,
strangers, scared.
- I'm really happy.
- Yay, with friends!
Adam, let's play
your board game
in the hot tub.
Well, that's
obviously impossible.
Hey, Adam,
come in here, man.
- All: Adam.
- Adam, come on, buddy.
- Jodi: He doesn't want to.
- Greg: Ari? Ari?
Yeah?
My sister's beautiful,
and she's a dental
hygienist,
so she has
her own money.
That's great.
- Wait, why did you say that?
You guys heard that,
right?
Did you guys--
am I the only one
who heard that?
- I did hear that.
- It's probably, like,
the fucking--
- what the fuck is that?
- Like a dog or whatever.
Greg: There is
a fucking murderer
in that bush, man.
- Eric: It's not a murderer.
- Hey.
It's Billy Baldwin.
Ari: It's fucking
Laura dern's chocolate lab
- sneaking around.
- Hey.
No, dude,
I'm serious, man.
I'm fucking serious.
- What?
- I'm out of--
I'm getting out.
- If it's a fucking--
- all right, guys.
Joshua's weekend.
- Hey, Ari, Ari?
- Whoa, we gotta go
with Joshua.
- We need to talk later.
- Yeah.
- Just a little bit.
- Yeah, no, no, no.
I don't need to be
up all night talking--
- talking about
i don't know.
- Whatever, no, no, no.
Jodi:
I just met
a bunch of strangers
-  and I talk their ear off
all night and, uh--
- and then I just...
- But I totally understand
what you were saying before
about backpack style hip-hop.
I think that that
is a distinction
of a kind of hip-hop
that does not get
mentioned that much.
'Cause you're, like,
talib kweli,
black star,
tribe called quest,
de la soul.
I really think
that hip-hop's, like,
a very important part
of our culture.
- Yes, agree 100%.
- Jodi: But haven't you
both also,
like, been to tanglewood
to see James Taylor?
- Whoa, that's funky!
- You know what's
the funkiest?
This is the funkiest
guy we know!
Dude, dude, dude.
Blow that in my mouth.
Come on, man.
It's really funny.
Blow it
in my mouth, man.
- Do it, do it.
- Come on. Blow it.
- Wow!
- Yeah! You guys
are my band!
Here's your trumpet!
So when you think about
the basic paradoxes,
you know, one of them,
the bootstrap paradox,
dictates that
no matter what happens
when you go back in time,
no matter what information
you take with you,
it's always been there.
So if you go back,
say, to yesterday
to give yourself
a great stock tip,
that means that
there was never
a version of reality
where you didn't
receive that.
- This is fucking fantastic.
- Thank you, thank you.
- Amazing.
So fucking cool.
- The other version of that--
thanks, man.
The other version of that
is the grandfather
paradox,
which means that no matter
what happens when you go back,
it's always a version
of what was going to happen.
So if you go back
and your grandfather dies,
that doesn't prevent you
from being born.
That just means
that something else
is going to have to happen
and it always did
and you would find out
that who you thought
was your grandfather
wasn't actually
your grandfather.
But what about
Marty mcfly?
He goes back
and he takes away
and he starts
disappearing.
What you're describing
is a depiction
of time travel in,
you know, pop culture
fiction.
What I'm talking about
is science.
Oh, you're talking about
something that's real.
Um, yes, I am.
Uh, Ari, you had
a question?
Adam, if time travel
existed,
don't you think
that we would
know about it
because someone would have
come back in time
to make us aware?
Excellent point.
We're living in what's
called the Alpha timeline.
And we haven't yet arrived
at the momentous event
at which
everything changes
as we know it.
So...
If that's
the Alpha timeline,
- are we over here now?
Can I just quickly
give a quick toast
to how fucking
interesting that is?
- Yes.
- And what a fucking cool
group of people
that Joshua
has put together
here tonight
for a good, solid
fucking late-night hang?
Greg:
Cheers to that.
Yeah, any--
whatever you got.
- Hey, hey, there you go.
- Totally.
- There you go.
That's the weirdest way
to wake up.
Yeah, that's my way
of saying thank you
for letting me have
a seventh-grade style,
no frenching,
no touching sleepover.
Yeah, dude,
no worries.
Seventh-grade
sleepover style.
I'm sorry that I, like,
totally dingleberried
onto your night.
Are you kidding?
That was so fun.
You crashed here.
No big deal, dude.
- Yeah.
- Why is your hand
like that?
- Move your hand.
- Because I didn't
brush my teeth.
Well, I don't care.
Come on.
What time
do you think it is?
- Okay, yeah,
you should put...
Can-- can I use
your toothbrush?
Of course.
It's the white
and teal one.
It's not like
the robot alien one
that Adam has.
- That guy has
a dorky toothbrush?
What a shocker.
Hello?
Come on in, guys.
- Boy: I'm hungry.
- Hello?
- You're hungry?
- Yeah.
Josh?
- - You think they're
still asleep?
- This is a mess.
- Oh, my god.
Hey, get him over here.
Come here, come here,
come here.
Man: There is somebody
under the coffee table.
You're right, buddy.
- Hey.
- Hey, I'm Eric.
Hey, I'm Aaron.
- Aaron, hi.
- Were you sleeping? Hey.
Are you okay?
You got...
- And who's this guy?
- ...A little--
that's my son.
Hello. Hi.
Nice to meet you.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
Are you--
did you get hurt?
- What?
- You just have a little...
Oh, no.
It's just allergy season.
There's like, a gun
sitting here, man.
Could you do me
a huge favor, man?
- Could we just kind of
get this area picked up?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Do you guys-- do you want
any of this before--
I'm joking.
- I'm all right.
- Little kids love this stuff.
- Okay.
- Aaron: Where is Josh?
Josh?
He's not
under the table.
That's the extent
of my knowledge.
I found everybody,
and I cleaned
the fucking bleed--
no, just--
- sorry.
- Woman: Ah, hey!
- Cleaned up my nose.
- Woman: How's it going?
- Here they are.
- Thanks for coming.
- Nice to see you.
- Thanks for having us.
- Yeah, man.
- Good to see you.
- Good to see you, too.
- Yeah, thanks.
- What's up, dude?
- What's up, man?
- Fucking lumberjack?
Nice to see you, man.
Thanks for inviting us.
Sorry we just rolled up now.
Looks like we missed
a lot of the action, but...
- Hi. I'm Jodi.
- Oh, hi.
Hey, how's it going?
I'm Anita.
- Hi, Anita.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yeah. Nice to meet you, too.
How do you g--
how do you know these guys?
I just met Ari
in the bar last night.
In the parking lot,
actually.
Yeah, we all met.
Everybody met.
Oh, so you spent
the night?
- Yeah, yeah. I slept.
- We took her in.
With a lot of liquor
in my system.
- Wow! That sounds
like a fun time.
- Little orphan.
Little stray.
Um, you guys hungry?
Should we, uh, keep
the breakfast train going?
You know, I'm good.
You know what, actually,
my friends probably
think I'm dead.
Truly, they probably think
i am like kidnapped
and chopped up,
- so I'm gonna go.
- Okay.
- But, please, do your
whole thing. I'm sorry.
- Oh, yeah.
- Great to meet you.
- Nice to meet you. Bye.
- Guys.
- See you, Jodi.
- Bye, Jodi.
- Do you want me
to drive you?
No, I'm fine.
I'm gonna walk it off.
- It'd be good.
- Are you sure?
- I think I should
drive you home.
- No. Why?
You're-- and now
you make me-- I'm...
- No, I'm not making any...
- I feel like I crashed
your weekend.
I'm, like, literally
not trying to stay.
- I'm gonna go.
- Okay.
- Okay. Cool life experience.
- Yeah.
- Bye.
- Over the course of the day...
- Here, you can wipe that
on here.
- Hey, Jude?
- What?
You wanna know
what your uncle Greg
does for a living?
- What?
- I make every candy
in the whole world.
No, he's not
your uncle Greg.
If you've tasted a candy,
i made it in my kitchen.
- Jude: No.
- Greg: Yeah.
How you doing, Josh?
Are you talking to anybody?
Are you seeing
a therapist?
Does tonie count,
our dealer from last night?
Yeah, that's perfect,
yeah.
Drown everything
in drugs and--
and that's just,
like, the best...
Oh, our Blackjack
dealer last night.
We went to a casino.
All I hear about is, like,
the bars you guys went to,
casino you went to.
Like, has anyone
brought this up?
Like, are you guys
discussing this at all?
Or are you just pretending
it didn't happen?
I totally hear you,
but to me,
it feels like
time and place.
I'm here to do
what Joshua wants,
and it seems to me
like Joshua got us together
to have a fun weekend
where we can just
fucking cut loose
a little bit.
Great.
Let's all go get drunk.
Let's also
not pretend, uh,
that the reason
we're here
isn't something that was
super traumatic
for our buddy.
Even if he's
going through it quietly,
even more of a reason that
it's our responsibility
to bring it up
and talk about it.
Uh, thanks
for chatting out here.
Yeah, what's up, man?
You like running
interference in there?
- No.
- You're, like,
a party wing man
- who can't get serious?
- What?
- What's going on?
- No, I'm just here
to have a good time
because that's what
Joshua seems to want
to have this weekend.
Well, I think that
the good time happened.
- Oh, okay.
- And I happened to meet you
under a coffee table
- with a fucking bloody nose.
- And I apologized about that.
Check off crazy party night.
You got it, man.
- Okay.
- Congratulations.
- Well, congratulations
for showing up
- 100% success.
- With the family.
- What does that mean?
It means this was,
like, a boy's weekend.
Where did it say
boy's weekend?
bring your wife
and four-year-old son?
Where'd it say not to?
I was on all the same
emails you were.
By the way, speaking
of my wife and kid,
I don't appreciate
bringing my four-year-old
into a room
that's, like, coated
in cocaine powder
and having to basically
pry a gun out of his hand
and move the bong
out of the way!
You think-- you think
i would have just, like--
if I knew your kid
were coming,
I would have
laid out drugs...
You offered him cocaine!
He is four years old!
- As a joke!
- Yeah, I suspect
that you would've...
My big mistake
is realizing
that your son had
the same fucking lame
sense of humor as you
- oh, yeah, that's really funny.
- And couldn't get a joke.
Yeah, that's awesome, man.
What a cool guy.
- But maybe
if he wants to get---
- hey, nice to meet you, buddy.
- Nice to meet you too, man.
- You know what?
Go fucking
do some more cocaine
and fuck yourself.
All right, bud.
Good hangs!
- Jude: Where are we going?
- All right, is he buckled up?
Yes.
- Eric: There you go, baby.
- Greg: Yeah!
- That's a capper.
- Ooh, ditty, ditty,
ditty, ditty.
I didn't mean to step
on your shit, Eric.
I just feel taking mushrooms
and chilling out is, like--
- I don't want to go anywhere.
- No. I totally get it.
And you know what?
Like, we did some
boozing last night,
and I think mushrooms
are the play.
- Hey.
- Hey, how are you, bud?
Thanks for, uh,
coming to fix this.
Oh, no problem.
It's just an
electrical problem.
It's not much wrong.
Sorry, you're kind of
getting stuck
with the only guy
who doesn't really
enjoy the hot tub.
I hear you, man.
No, but I'll get
your balances just perfect
and you'll be
in this thing in about
an hour with your buddies.
I don't really like
getting in it myself.
You know, just because
of the amount of bacteria
that lives
in warm still water
and, you know, the way
that the kind of heat
breeds a cloud
of disease that just
hovers above it.
Yeah, well,
i guess hot tubs
aren't for everyone.
Yeah, i--
i can agree to that.
- Definitely not for me.
- It was really nice
to meet you.
Do you mind
if I sit here with you
while you work
or-- or would you
rather work alone?
Yeah, whatever
you'd like.
Eric:
Can I take
a picture of you?
Sure.
- So what happened?
- What?
- With, uh,
what's her name?
- Oh, Rachel.
Rachel. What'd she do?
How'd she die?
How'd she do it,
i mean?
Well, um,
she-- she was cooking dinner
for him on his birthday,
and he went down
to the gym
and when he came back,
she was dead.
Pull!
- That's so awful.
- Yeah, it's a bummer.
Her parents are kind of
giving him a hard time.
Why? They think
he did something?
I think it must be hard
to, like,
admit that your child
is sick like that
enough to do something, so...
Oh, god, I can't believe
that I said all that stuff,
- like...
- What stuff?
Just, like,
congratulations,
- and I called her
a fucking bitch.
- Oh, don't worry, dude.
Joshy is--
- he didn't even
register it.
- He's like...
- That's what I do,
though, you know?
That's what I do.
I start talking,
and I don't
stop talking.
- How'd she do it?
- Huh?
How'd she do it?
How'd she kill herself?
Oh, I don't know if
that's the best place to...
I gotta know.
- Well, she...
- I'm just gonna be wondering
about it the whole day,
and I don't want that
to be in my mind.
She asphyxiated herself.
Oh, my god.
Are you kidding me?
What, with a bag?
I don't wanna get
into the details, man.
- I'm starting to feel...
- I gotta know.
- What, with a rope?
- A belt.
- One of his belts.
- Oh, my god, his belt.
Used his belt
to kill herself.
Oh, I'm feeling so weird
in my stomach right now.
- Yeah.
- I feel like I'm
just about to explode.
- My stomach.
- ...This'll be really hard.
- Oh, my stomach.
Greg:
There's no such thing
as time travel.
Everything is gonna
stay the way it is.
You can't
correct anything.
I can't go back
and make anything right.
They told me they were
a good idea to hire
because they're getting
something pretty to look at,
and they'd make us
look cooler than anybody else.
My father
went in a hot tub
and started feeling
something strange
in his leg
and a few days later,
it had grown to a boil
the size of
a ping-pong ball.
And my uncle
just rolled it
with a rolling pin
and when it popped,
pus hit the ceiling.
Wow, a disgusting story.
You should have never
put their pictures
online, Ari!
My marriage is over!
Greg, Greg, Greg.
Adam: It was 10 years
of being together,
and her main argument
was that she felt
like she'd missed out
on her 20s.
Not entirely,
but in a way that was scary
as she started entering
into her 30s
and just, I guess,
wondered what else
was out there.
Imagine the fun
when you meet
somebody like you
who is fully able
to commit.
- Yeah.
- You'll have something
that you never had
with this other woman,
no disrespect to
what you guys had.
No, you can disrespect her
all you want now.
For now, the question
is just where do I go?
Repairman:
You're gonna be just fine.
...look amazing.
- Amazing, like,
all the time?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- Jodi.
- Hey, happy birthday,
right?
- Hi.
- Yes, it's my birthday.
- Hey, Jodi.
Hey, thank you.
- Happy birthday to everyone.
- This is Jen and Ali.
- Happy birthday.
- Hi. Oh, okay.
- Hey.
- To my happy birthday.
- Happy birthday.
- Adam!
- This is Ari.
- Jen.
- Hi.
- Hey, how's it going?
- Hi, Adam.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- This is Jen and Ali.
- Hi.
- Jen.
Adam.
- Can I talk to you
for a second?
- Sure.
Awesome.
- Am I in trouble?
- No.
- Do you want me to sit here?
- Uh, sure, yeah. Why?
Great.
I've been wanting to
apply for this position
for a long time.
I'm-- I'm Adam.
Did-- did Jodi mention me
at all to one of you?
No?
Because we had
a nice little
conversation last night
where she mentioned
that she had a friend
who she felt, like,
might sort of be
the kind of person
who would be interested
in talking to a guy like me.
I'm wondering
if it's you.
Or if it is you?
Guys, we gotta
rally here, okay?
- Energy is low.
- I'm good.
- You're good.
- You're the only one
that's fucking good
right now, Joshua.
- Yeah.
- But this guy,
comatose Carl,
come on, man.
We gotta get some
drinks in us, all right?
Happy birthday.
- Can I open this?
- Yeah, sure.
Is this a cd mix?
Yes, it is a cd mix.
Does this mean
you have a time machine
back to 1998?
No, I just--
my computer's really old,
so it does have
the capabilities
of burning cds.
You should be more impressed
that I actually found a...
- A cd?
- A blank cd, yeah.
Oh, thank you so much.
- Just my size.
- And that is from
my private collection.
That's a big fatty.
Thank you so much.
It actually is
the loveliest
birthday present
that I ever
could have asked for.
It's very nice.
Looking at the history
of ancient aliens,
you have to imagine
that every visit from them
- kicked off
a major new phase
- oh.
In human advancement.
You know,
and there's examples of it
basically
at every huge leap
that we've taken
as a civilization.
The most notable example,
i guess, that I could reference
- is something like
the pyramids.
- Yeah.
I get it.
You're preaching
to the choir.
There's
just clearly no way
that normal
ancient Egyptians
could have conceived of...
There's no way
that humans
with human hands
can build
fucking pyramids.
It's crazy.
- I'm gonna go.
- Not only have they
lasted longer
than everything else
that was built around them,
just they're simply not
what anything would have
looked like at the time.
And here's the thing that's
going to blow your mind...
- You like that?
- Yeah, it's nice.
I usually button
in another direction, but...
Shh.
- Are we...
- Shh.
- Almost due
for another one?
- Shh.
We should have gone
to the vineyard.
That's all I asked.
It's, like, people think
i just come up
with these things
arbitrarily,
like, "let's go
to a vineyard." No.
I do the research, okay?
If we'd gone
to the vineyard,
we wouldn't have
eaten mushrooms,
you wouldn't have
lost your fucking mind.
It's just, like,
people don't listen to me.
All I'm
trying to do is
create a fun,
dynamic weekend.
I did--
i did wanna, um,
tell you
something, though.
Okay.
I didn't get a chance
to tell you last night...
But I think you
should know
that I am married.
I wanted to tell you
last night,
but everything was
a little crazy.
And it's hard.
Like, when do you--
when are you supposed to
say that?
Big time.
I'm sorry, that's--
that's my fault.
- No.
- Yeah, it's--
i should've--
there's a million things
i should-- I should have...
That's okay.
It's o--
like, I get that...
Definitely,
it is weird.
And I'm, like,
holding my face.
But it's also,
i get...
Um, you know...
Like, I know you.
Like, I know
I've never met you,
but I know you.
Well...
That's, like,
very heavy shit
to throw down
right now.
Um...
- I'm sorry.
- Well, I feel
a little embarrassed
that your friends
all knew.
- I feel, like, stupid.
- I'm sorry.
It's probably
weirder for you
than it is for me.
Yeah.
And I think
you're a nice person.
And I don't really
know what else to say
'cause I feel,
like, very weird.
But, anyhow,
I do have a birthday
to celebrate.
And you have,
yeah, you know.
Thanks.
It's cool.
You're good.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- Oh!
- Jen: Oh.
- Everything's
all right, though.
- I'm good, yeah, I'm good.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
- Do you need anything?
- Uh, nope.
You want,
like, a water
or just, like, even
a piece of bread maybe?
Jen:
No, I don't want
any water.
You might wanna watch
your boots on the couch.
We don't wanna scuff it up
and lose our deposit.
Yeah, I'm good.
I'm really fine.
Um...
I'm good, yeah.
Eric:
Hey, buddy.
- Hey, man.
What are you doing?
- Hey.
Oh, um, she passed out,
so I don't want her boots
fucking up the couch
and we lose our
security deposit.
- So I'm taking them off.
- Yeah, that's pretty creepy.
No, no,
it's not creepy.
- I just...
- No, in a good way.
- Oh, thanks.
- Where's your iPod?
- Uh, why?
- Because I wanna
put music on.
- Where's yours?
- I just have my iPhone,
and it's a streaming
music service.
I don't get
reception up here,
so just tell me
where your iPod is.
I mean, I'm sure
it's in my room,
- but I don't--
- okay, great.
But don't go
to my room. Don't...
Hey, buddy,
you're being a real
fucking wet blanket, okay?
And it's getting
really, really tough
to keep everything going
with you being
a wet blanket
and these ingrates
with no ideas
of their own.
Yeah, and everyone
appreciates that,
but, you know, like,
maybe tonight's
just a wash.
Like, it's pretty late.
People are tired.
We don't need music put on.
Maybe the night's just over.
Trust me,
the night is not over.
It doesn't matter--
- it's just...
- What the fuck
am I doing here?
I thought you were
taking me home.
To our home.
I thought you
wanted to come here.
No. I thought
you were taking me--
I thought you were
walking me home, my home.
- Where's my fucking shoe?
- It's right here.
- Did you take my shoes off?
- Just the one.
I took it off
because it was
scuffing up the couch.
- Give me that.
- As long as you
were passed out,
- you want to get comfortable.
- You took off my shoes.
You're a fucking creep.
Is that what you do?
You go to bars
and pretend like
you're a charming,
artistic nerd?
And then you lure people
back to your house?
You know, let's not start
with the name calling.
- And I'm not a nerd.
- No, you're not a nerd.
- You're a fucking psychopath.
- Everything's fine.
- Get the fuck off me!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Can I drive you home?
- No, I don't need you
to fucking drive me.
- Oh, shit.
- I know how to walk.
- Ari: Oh!
- It's a rental.
- You wanna
borrow a coat?
- What did you do?
- I think she likes me.
- Man: Eric?
- Hey, yes. Come on in.
Hi. If you could just
quickly come in here.
- How are you?
- Hey, how are you?
I'm good. Nice to see you.
I'm Eric. Come on in.
Greg?
- Oh, my god.
- Eric, what did you do?
- What did you do?
- What did I do?
- Greg, lights, please.
- Adam: Hey, that's my iPod.
- - Gentlemen, let's welcome
to the stage,
Kylie and crystal!
- Oh, my god.
- That's right.
- Hi, ladies.
Come on in!
- Hi.
- Eric: This is Joshua.
- It's his lucky day.
- Oh, you must be
the one getting married.
- Eric: Aw.
- Congratulations!
- Mm-wah.
- Lucky guy.
Wow.
- Eric: Please, unpack,
ladies, unpack.
- Woman: Okay.
Hey, will you guys
let your friend outside
- know that we're here?
- I'm sorry. What?
The suspicious-looking one.
I'm sorry,
I'm not catching
a word of this.
I mean, suspicious
compared to the way
you guys look.
- Give it a slap.
- Okay.
- Double.
- Do you want a dance?
- You don't have to,
you know?
You can just-- you don't
have to do all this.
You can just hang out.
It's just whatever
makes you feel
comfortable.
I mean, I assume
you got paid either way.
- Woman: What do you want,
though, sweetie?
- Look.
You can dance
while you're doing it
or you can just
- sit perfectly still.
- You need someone to talk to?
- Always.
- When you have
a bunch of thoughts
and you don't know
what to do with them,
just crush them.
And then you align
the thoughts, you know?
And then you make
logic of it. Look.
- You see one
thought over here.
- Yeah, totally.
- Another thought over here.
- Yep.
If we make four thoughts,
we can have two thoughts each.
Two thoughts each, okay.
You kind of look
like my boyfriend.
- Adam: I do?
- Yeah.
- Ladies.
- Adam: You're dating
someone who resembles me?
Oh, yeah.
Not only dating,
he lives with us.
He's a really good
step-dad to my daughter.
- You smell so good.
- How do we differ?
I mean, does he dress like me
or does he sound like me?
- Oh, he's Mexican.
- Okay, that's one
crucial difference.
Woman: Yeah.
I have to give her
Insulin shots every morning.
Adam, your music sucks.
We got to change to
a new song, buddy.
She also has
a really bad
lung condition.
- See what we got
on the next one.
- Adam: I'm sorry, what?
Classical?
Come on, man!
This song sucks, too.
What's on your iPod?
Well, you--
it's just on shuffle,
so I don't know what's
gonna come up.
Well, I didn't know
that when I grabbed
your shitty iPod
that all the songs
would fucking blow!
Yeah, it's almost like
when I was putting music
on my iPod a year ago,
I wasn't thinking about
fun stripper songs!
Eric:
No, you didn't do that!
You didn't plan anything
except to play
your fucking board game,
just like nobody here
planned anything
except for me!
I try to do
one nice thing
for everybody!
- Bring strippers,
fucking turn this...
- May I have this dance?
Don't insult
my fucking friendship
with somebody
that you don't
even know that well!
Where the fuck
do you even get off
coming in here
with this bullshit?
It's just-- you know what?
I don't need to stand here
and be shouted at!
I'll take my fucking iPod.
It's insufficient.
I'm sorry it's not
good enough for you.
Take your ball!
Go home and play
kickball by yourself
- with your little dickey!
- Adam, wait up.
Hey. No, that's fine.
He's, like, sulking.
I think he needs
some company.
No. He just wants
to go to bed.
He's actually kind of lame.
And I'm not being
shady right now,
but I'm gonna kind of,
like, not let you go
up there right now.
- You're not gonna
let me go by?
- No.
Crystal! Kylie!
Let's go! Vmonos.
Thank you.
- Have a good honeymoon.
- Oh, thank you.
I'm not getting--
aw, fuck it.
- Bye.
- Bye. It was good
to meet you.
Sorry, pal.
Sorry about that.
Wait. I think there's
someone out there.
Look, there's
someone right there.
Look, he's running away.
- I see him. Grab the gun.
- Who the fuck is that?
- Uh...
- Oh, come on.
Hey, come out.
Come out.
We see you, man.
We see you.
We fucking see you.
- Holy shit.
- Ow! Ow!
All right, all right,
it's cool.
Who the fuck
are you, man?
Okay, it's cool.
It's just nature.
- What?
- It's nature?
- What the fuck does that mean?
- Oh, oh, he's running.
- Ow!
- Josh: What do we do?
Do we go after him?
No, no, no.
Let's fucking
let him go.
- Oh. Whoa.
- What the fuck, man?
So I wanted to,
ahem, apologize
for my behavior
last night with you.
I was very aggressive
and yelling at you
and sort of
pushing you around.
And it wasn't cool
and so I wanted
to say I'm sorry
about that.
Yeah, i-- I appreciate
you apologizing.
You know,
i mean, obviously,
I know that
my idea of fun
isn't the same
as everybody else's,
but the fact that
you can say this
to me now
really is
much appreciated.
- So thank you.
- Yeah, and you--
- you don't have to
apologize to me.
- Okay, great.
Yeah, I'm really going
through some stuff, too.
And I just--
I'm sorry if my energy,
especially yesterday
and last night,
was, you know,
getting in the way
of you having any fun.
Sure. No, I appreciate
you guys both saying that.
I think tonight is
actually gonna be
a very cathartic release
for all of us.
- Mm.
- Adam: Yeah,
that'd be nice.
Just sort of relax.
On that note,
all right.
I'm gonna go take care
of something.
See you guys, uh,
for dinner.
I think maybe
I'm ready to get out.
I don't wanna get
swimmer's cough
or anything.
Yeah, let's get out.
- Hello.
- Woman: Hi.
- Come on in.
- Are you frank?
I am frank.
Are you...
- I'm Isadora.
- Isadora.
- Hi.
- Hi. Come here.
You look great.
This is exactly my style.
I'm not kidding.
- Really?
- I love that you guys
have paintings.
- That's so beautiful.
- I love paintings.
Do you really?
I do, too.
I prefer that.
It's like
if I see a blank wall,
it bums me out.
- Yeah.
- This is very cool.
- Oh, it's a lot of necks.
- It's very...
- It's like dogs
playing poker,
- but people.
- Right.
- And here are two other
works of art right here.
- This is awesome.
- Hi.
- Greg, Adam,
this is, uh, Isadora.
Hi, I'm Isadora. Hi.
Oh, nice to meet you.
- Hi. I'm Greg.
- Greg.
Oh, my god,
you have a twin.
My sister's
best friend Nicky
looks a lot like you.
- A woman? I look...
- Yeah, she's a girl.
You know,
i always thought
that I had
ape features.
That's how
I've always seen myself.
Yeah, you do,
but just, like--
it's like Nicky, too,
but a beautiful ape.
Apes are
the most beautiful
creatures on this planet.
- Thank you so much.
- Yeah.
You got
ape hands, too.
I do?
- It's a total compliment.
- I'm sorry.
- Did I miss something?
- Oh, um, Isadora here
is a sex worker,
and she's gonna
fuck us all for money.
- Absolutely, but not nec--
- or whoever wants...
It doesn't have to be--
if you don't wanna fuck,
if you wanna--
i got a lot of
different holes,
you know what I'm saying?
So don't worry about it.
You can do something
with my feet or anal.
Whatever you're into.
Also, I wanna say this
'cause I feel like
this definitely helps
when I say this
is that do not worry
about money.
Please put that
out of your head
right now.
Don't start tallying it up
like, "oh, can i
do this to her?"
It's gonna add it up.
Don't worry.
I just
wanna let you know
that what I'm
into doing
is whatever you are
into doing.
Whatever relaxes you,
makes you comfortable,
pleases you.
Thank you for saying that.
I appreciate that a lot.
- That is very cool of you.
- You're welcome.
I'm gonna
take you up on that.
Thank you so much.
- Hey, please do.
- I would love
to start with you
just because I feel like,
um-- is that okay?
- Um, I think
that would be good.
- Sure.
- That'd be great.
- Can I get, um, uh,
is there a little room
i can clean--
- yeah.
- Not clean up.
I'm not dirty, I swear.
Of course you're not dirty.
Nobody would ever think
that you're dirty.
I'll show you
to the bathroom.
No, no.
I'll do it.
- Eric: Great.
- Yeah.
- Isadora: Cool.
- Okay, cool.
- All right.
- Right this way.
- Great.
Thank you so much.
- Madame.
- See you in a bit, buddy.
- God, I love this.
I think I'm just
gonna go for a hike.
- This-- yeah,
this isn't for me.
- What?
I know. I know.
I-- I figured it was
worth one last shot
to see if I could
get you laid,
but I could tell
it's not your thing.
Sure, I appreciate it.
You know, it's very
nice of you
to, you know,
be thinking of everyone's
pleasure all the time, but...
She seems cool, though,
i mean, honestly...
She seems great.
I think it'll be
a lot of fun
for you guys
to have sex with her
one after the other.
- But I'll just be outside.
- Okay, buddy.
Hi, Jodi, hi.
Hi, it's Ari.
I know i--
I've been
kind of stalking you,
but i-- I, um...
No, I know, I know.
I was--
i gave him a, um--
why am I blanking?
A hand job, a handy,
whatever,
you know what I mean?
I-- and I was--
and he was
sobbing and coming
and sobbing and coming,
and it was so profound
to see what you
could do to somebody,
you know, that's
not just about--
i was, like--
I mean, obviously,
I'm sure he was
glad he came,
but to know
that it was so much
more emotional than that,
- so-- hi.
- Hi.
- Hi. I'm Isadora, hi. Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, good, this is good.
- The more,
the merrier, good.
- Oh.
- Um, all right.
- Eric: So do you
see yourself
- as like a healer?
- Yes.
But, like,
sex stuff too, right?
Yes, yes, yes!
Oh, my god.
- I love-- oh, my god,
oh, I love you.
- I love that you
said that because...
- Ahem, uh,
Rachel's parents are here.
They're outside.
- They're here now.
I'm gonna go tell Josh.
- Ari: What?
Eric:
But, like, you'll do,
like, fun stuff and...
Isadora:
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
anything that you need...
Joshy?
Joshy!
We gotta clean up!
- Oh.
- Oh, okay.
- Not on my account?
- No, we...
- Honestly, don't.
- We're gonna have you
go to the bathroom.
- We're just gonna do
a little cleanup.
- Oh, I've gone.
I'm very cleansed out
before I ever come to
any sort of...
I know.
I just want you to have a--
last looks in there.
Dude, the weed?
We gotta get rid
of this coke, bud.
- Come on.
- What are we doing?
Ari:
Sit the fuck down
and just be...
Eric:
Can I just ask
why are we freaking out?
Ari: Sit the fuck down, Eric!
Why are we freaking out
like we're in trouble?
It's just parents!
Please!
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
- Hey, joshy.
- Long time.
- Yeah.
- It's been a while.
- We knew you were here, so...
- We spoke to your mother
and, you know,
- yes.
She mentioned
that you were here
and we thought...
- That you were here
vacationing.
- Thought maybe it's time to...
- Clear the air.
- Clear the air, exactly.
- Um, yeah.
- I have pictures for you.
- Come in and, uh, sure.
- Woman: Oh.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, just some
friends are here.
- Oh, yeah, this is, uh...
- Should we just say hi
and then we can...?
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
So this is, uh,
these are Rachel's
parents.
- How are you, Ari?
- Steve and Claudia.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
I hope we're not intruding.
We're gonna go
for a-- a hike.
- Um...
- Josh: Yeah.
- Okay.
- We were just talking
about a book we read.
Have a seat.
Sorry about this.
It's okay.
- - What's that pink thing?
Oh, this?
Uh, this is, uh--
it's Ari's.
- He's trying to quit smoking.
- Oh, it's a filter thing?
- Yeah.
- My mother had
one of those.
- It was fancy.
- It's supposed to help.
Steve:
First of all,
we want
to apologize to you.
I-- I think
we were both
so, uh, shaken,
and I think
we took it out on you.
Not letting you
go to the funeral,
that wasn't--
- wasn't really right, so...
- And I hope you forgive us.
Well, wow,
i mean, uh,
honestly,
this means a lot.
I mean, yes, sure,
yeah, I forgive you.
I mean,
that was really--
that was hard.
It would help so much
if we all just talked about
what happened that day.
- It would really be helpful.
- Understanding like, you know,
- the sequence of events.
- You spoke to her
right before.
She called me on the phone.
She called me on the phone
to ask me one of my recipes,
you know, which I love,
of course
because I'm very proud
of my recipes.
So help us-- help us,
Josh, please.
Did you guys have
a fight or something
when you got home?
- Was there an emotional...
- So, yeah, I got home
and, uh, we didn't--
we talked about
what I wanted to do
for my birthday.
You came home
and you talked--
you talked to her?
So she was alive
when you got back?
- Yeah.
- This is what I'm saying.
This is different
from what you told
the police.
No, I'm talking about
when I got home from work.
I came home from work
and we started discussing
what I wanted to do
for my birthday
and then
i went to the gym.
This is the part of the story
that keeps changing
and this is
why I wanna know
what actually happened.
- We just need
to know what happened.
- Just tell us.
I-- she was depressed.
- Claudia: Depressed?
- She was.
She was distant and...
No, not Rachel.
Our Rachel was not depressed.
- Never heard that.
- Look, I tried to--
I tried to get kind of
to the bottom of it
and every time,
she'd mis--
she-- she'd deflect
and she wouldn't answer me.
She was on, um...
- Drugs? Was she?
- No.
- You guys were taking drugs?
- No, we don't take drugs.
It was medication,
you know, like,
antidepressants.
Okay, you don't do drugs.
She doesn't do drugs.
She's taking some--
some medication
from a doctor?
- Please tell me
- Josh: Yes, yes.
You know,
here's the thing.
It's just a little
convoluted for us, right?
And so
we actually paid
for a second autopsy
to be done.
The coroner said
that it was actually
inconclusive
- for it to be suicide.
- Inconclusive.
- They couldn't say...
- They couldn't say for sure
- that it was a suicide.
- Could not say for sure.
So, okay,
if she's not...
Hi. Thank you.
I really had a nice time.
I'm kind of freaking out,
so I'm gonna probably
take off.
Thank you, though.
I love your home.
So nice--
it's very pretty.
- - Who is this?
I don't know who that is.
I don't know who that is!
- I'm sure you
don't know who that is.
- You don't know who she is?
- No, I don't.
- 'Cause you don't party.
- You don't party.
- You don't do drugs.
- Let me show you something.
- Let me get this out.
- You don't party.
- Steve: What's that?
- You don't do drugs.
What is this?
You taking photos of me?
Claudia:
How about guns?
That's so much fun.
- This is a bb gun.
- Claudia: Who is she?
- Steve: Who is she?
Any idea?
- So much fun
when women strip
and gyrate all over you
when you're mourning.
- When you're mourning.
- Steve: Look at that.
Look at that.
Those marks were
made by her?
- She did not
do that to herself!
- She strangled herself?
- Just tell the truth!
- I am telling the truth.
- You killed our daughter!
- Say the truth, Josh!
I'm telling the truth.
- I didn't fucking kill her!
- Oh, really?
I knew you were
that monster.
Do you
fucking see this?
- What the fuck is this?
- Claudia: That's so we could
get all your lies on tape!
- I haven't been lying!
- Claudia: You're a liar.
- You're a fucking liar!
- Josh: Get out!
- What are you doing?
- Get out, you psychopaths.
Get out!
- Get out.
Take your photos.
- Steve: We're gonna find out.
You can keep that!
That's a little souvenir.
- - Should we go up there?
- Steve: We're on to you!
- Great, yeah, yeah.
- Is everything okay?
I don't know.
I'm just--
I guess
I'm just, um--
I'm tired of her.
I'm tired of, like--
I'm tired of her
making me feel this way.
You know, because--
I don't know.
She just-- she--
this is...
It's about her.
And, uh,
it's been
about her and...
I-- I guess
i don't know.
You know what?
I'm a little--
I'm a little tired of it.
She checks out,
and I have to fucking
deal with it!
And I have to deal
with missing her
and fucking feeling
real fuckin' sad!
And having her
fucking parents...
In case
anyone's wondering,
I didn't, and I hope
you fucking believe me
because I didn't
murder someone.
I didn't murder her.
I loved her very much.
And then, uh,
i guess she thought
that the best way
to return that
would be to kill herself
on my fucking birthday!
So, I don't know.
That's what I'm left with
and-- and, uh--
and I'm
even sorry now.
Like, you know, 'cause now
I'm dragging you guys in.
I'm pulling you guys
into this shit,
and you have
your own lives.
And everybody has
their own problems.
And now
you have to sit here
and look at me do this.
It's so fucking weird.
It's so weird.
It's so stupid.
I'm so fucking mad
at her.
I'm so mad at her.
Well-- well,
thanks, you know,
for coming.
I don't know
if you guys maybe just...
Adam, do you wanna
play your game?
Yeah, if you do.
I think that
would be pretty fun.
Greg makes great
grilled cheeses.
I do.
- Fuck it,
let's play the game.
- Eric: Let's play the game.
All right, okay.
Here.
You want a tissue?
Yeah. Looks used.
No. This is actually
Adam's, um, handkerchief
that his grandfather
gave him in the war.
- Oh?
- And I spit my gum
in it earlier,
- but it should be fine.
- Spitting his gum in it
is a euphemism
for using
his grandfather's
handkerchief
as a cum rag.
I got this problem.
I keep coming in my
grandfather's handkerchief.
I don't know what to do.
You gotta help me.
So, Joshua has just
rolled three ones,
which means that
we have been defeated
by the turtlesaurus.
However, the mechas
will stay strong.
- Hey, Ari?
- Hmm?
What we doing here, bud?
We're all waiting for--
to sign off before
we launch the attack.
That's very good.
You're half paying
attention,
- but I like that.
- Good. I'll be right back.
- Okay.
- This is why
the grilled cheese is so good.
This is what
i did into it.
Uh, uh, uh!
- Hi.
- Greg: Shit!
- Hey, man.
- Thanks for coming.
- Oh, yeah.
- Greg: What did I do?
Eric:
Hey, it's Jodi
from the bar!
- Jodi.
- That's right.
Just to catch you up,
there's been an alien
invasion.
We are the mechas.
We are the machines.
We are fighting
all these monsters.
If the monsters
continue to rise up,
specifically
the turtlesaurus,
- we're fucked.
- Great.
- I love that kind of stuff.
- Eric: The turtlesaurus
has been a real
problemsaurus for us.
We're hoping for
a core turbo charger.
Did you say
the turtlesaurus
has been
the problemsaurus?
- It's been a problem for us.
- I'm gonna focus
on defeating
the turtlesaurus.
- Ari: Yeah!
- Eric: Yeah!
Tell me
something good!
I'll use my charge bomb.
I'll use that on
my next turn.
Greg:
Should I bust out
a charge bomb?
Ari:
I don't know
if you have one.
We just needed
to have enough
in order to dislodge
the space flicker
- and all to team up against--
- you should, in fact,
use that charge bomb
because I'd love to move
at least three or four hexes
'cause this turtlesaurus
is coming out of the side.
I think that
I'm gonna probably
take a break
from my marriage.
Greg: Oh.
Okay, Eric.
I shouldn't be married.
There's no reason.
I don't wear a ring.
I've been flirting
with women all weekend.
I wanna fuck other people.
So I shouldn't be married.
So, uh, can I roll?
Great.
Pass me the die.
It's been a--
there's a lot going on.
You guys are
a hot group, you know?
15!
Yes!
Jodi: He's not gonna get
anything above an eight.
Both: Ee!
If I meant to do
half of the things
that I did,
I'd be
a fucking genius, man.
- Jodi: Cool.
- I'd be huge,
but I am what I am,
and that's all that I am.
I'm fine.
And I'll take
gen highway...
- Eric: Jen?
- Greg: Jen?
- Eric: Jennifer.
- Greg: Jennifer!
It's not Jennifer.
It's-- it's short
for Genesis.
- It's a man.
- Jennifer is a regular
basic bitch, aren't you?
It's not a woman,
and don't call me Jen.
- Call me highway.
- Eric: Okay, highway.
Thank you so much
for coming.
- Eric: We're finally
playing the game...
- Oh, you're so welcome.
- You're not feeling...
- Adam: This doesn't
seem really...
- What?
- ...Weird or anything?
- You're feeling weird.
- I'm feeling very weird.
- Yeah, it's cool.
- Okay.
It's okay.
I wouldn't have come
if I didn't want to.
- Oh!
- Greg: Oh, yes!
- Whoa!
- Greg:
Fuck, yeah, Jodi.
Okay, guys.
The game basically
comes down to this roll.
Jodi, we need
at least a 17
or the game is over.
Turtlesaurus
is victorious,
eats us, and then hides us
under his mutant shell.
17 is pretty hard.
It's, uh--
out of three dice,
that's only two in 18,
one in nine chance.
I want victory
right now.
This turtlesaurus
is not gonna get
into my life,
not tonight.
Ready?
Here we go.
Come on, Jodi.
- - And?
- All: Oh.
- Fuck!
Jodi:
I'm so sorry. Shit!
Shit, man!
We played-- oh,
we've been playing
this fucking thing all night
and that happens?
Goddamn it!
- Fuck you! Fuck you!
- Hey, Greg, Greg, Greg.
Well, since
it's mostly, um,
like, ruined,
i think I should go.
I'm okay.
I just had to let it out.
Goodbye, gentlemen.
- Eric: Bye, Jodi
from the game!
- Bye!
Sorry that
i lost the game.
You know, it's a hard thing
to fight a bunch of robots.
- You did good.
- No, it's okay.
- It's not okay.
I know I could...
- You're embarrassing me.
- You're embarrassing.
- We'll talk about it
in the hall.
- Josh: See you later, turd!
- Bye, joshy.
- Josh: Bye.
- Greg: Bye, Jodi!
- Bye, guys. Cool weekend.
- Greg: Jodi, I'm on your side.
- Whatever, Greg.
- Eric: I would still argue
that mafia is
the best board game.
Yeah, well, mafia
is not a board game.
There's no board.
There's just sort of...
- Okay. Well, then, uh...
- ...Social fun
and nonsense game.
Well, good game,
asshole.
- Good game, sore loser.
- Yeah.
Yeah, i--
okay.
No, I'm sorry.
That is confusing.
Yeah.
And whoa!
Okay, yeah.
Okay, okay.
All right.
- Hey, Joshua.
- Thanks for coming, man.
I gotta say, Eric,
this was
a really fun weekend.
Thank you.
- Greg?
- Hey, I'm here.
Be in touch,
we'll get something planned.
I'm gonna plan a game weekend
with you, buddy.
- Let's do it,
a whole tournament.
- I love games now.
- It's your new thing.
- Yeah, so fun.
There's a lot
of great literature
about them online.
Very critical
community, so...
- Hey.
- You, too, Adam.
- Yeah.
- You, too.
- Eric: Come back.
Come back
and hang out.
- Sure, yeah,
I'd love to.
- Okay.
- I'd love to.
- Thanks.
Greg:
I'll probably never
see you guys ever again,
but that doesn't
take away from the fact
that this has been
one of the most important
weekends
of my entire life.
And I thank you.
I thank you for that.
I don't know if
you guys knew this,
but Greg was
a bit of a mess
before he got here.
- Ha.
- Okay.
- See you, man.
- Josh: Bye.
- Bye, guys.
Hey, guys?
Positive vibes,
positive energy!
positive energy.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Okay.
I'm gonna take off
as well.
Sure, man.
I'll see you.
- Thanks for coming.
- Yeah, of course, buddy.
- Bye.
- See you.
Ari:
Take it easy, man.
It was good
to see you.
Yeah.
Thanks for coming, man.
Sure. I would--
I would come again.
I will--
i will always be coming.
- Coming 24 hours a day.
- I can't stop coming.
- All right.
- Uh...
- Yeah. Okay.
- Yeah?