Subtitles by explosiveskull
What can you tell me about
this supposed haunted house?
The one on Cedar Road.
To stay away from it.
Why?
Because it's haunted.
It's a stupid old urban
legend made up by kids.
So it's not real?
No.
If you live there...
...the other ghost or demon...
...starts to slowly start
to get inside your head.
I guess the paranormal
activity in the house
is so terrifying that...
...every family that's
tried to live there...
...has left less than, what,
21 days after moving in.
And... when they leave,
which is usually in
the middle of the night,
they leave all their belongings, but...
...take the time to...
Take the time to cover up all the mirrors.
It owns you. It's...
It's claimed your soul.
Well they say that the ghost or demon
follows them to the next
place where they live,
threatening to kill them
if they talk about it.
The house was built in 1890.
It was the site of a
major, major land dispute
between the local Indians and the family
who had moved there after buying
the land from the government.
The Samuels.
The Indians had
claimed for a long time
that the land was rightfully theirs.
That it was the site of
this ancient burial ground.
And legend has it
that the family only lived
in that house for 21 days...
...and then they were gone.
Everything was there.
Their possessions,
their horses. Everything.
Like, they had planned to come back
and just stepped away for a little bit.
But they never did.
No, I don't think the house is haunted...
...or cursed.
Most likely, I think the Indians
probably massacred the family
and buried their bodies
there on the property.
Or maybe up in the local mountains
so they'd never be found.
Well that really doesn't explain
all of the strange circumstances
for any of the families
that have lived there since.
Oh, you mean the-the Warner family.
Yes. They moved in there in 1977.
The Warners. They were
such a nice family.
The little girl, Tricia,
I went to school with her.
She was just the
happiest kid, but then...
...her personality
started to change.
She became more remote.
She didn't talk much.
And then, on what would have been their...
...19th day living in the house,
the family left abruptly
in the middle of the night,
and they didn't take
anything with them.
They never went back.
They let the house be foreclosed on.
They would never talk to
anybody about what happened.
The little girl went mute.
People say she was institutionalized.
I guess she still is and...
...the boy, Cory Warner,
was tragically killed in a car accident.
I'm told on his way
to talk to a reporter
about the house.
And what about the tenants
who lived there most recently?
Within the last two months
they moved out, I think?
Right, right. Lisa Thompson...
...and her nine-year-old
son, Jonathan.
Just shortly after they moved in,
her little boy went mute.
This little boy went mute...
...just like the family
that was living there
back in 1977?
Yes.
Uh, they moved in, uh,
but only stayed for...
...20 days before...
...they moved out.
Is she still in town?
Oh, yes, she is. But she won't talk to you.
She won't talk to anybody about the house.
There she is.
There she is, there she is, there she is.
Come on.
Lisa?
Lisa Thompson?
Who are you?
My name's Jacob Anderson. We're filmmakers.
Get the fuck out of my property!
Why did you leave the house
so soon after moving in?
Only 20 days.
Why was that? You left abruptly.
What happened to you and your son
while living there?
Lisa?
Lisa, why did you leave all
of your belongings behind?
Get the fuck out of my property now!
Lisa, please!
Let's go back to the car.
What the hell was that?
Hey. You see that?
Isn't that that mother's kid...
...in the window?
Oh, yeah. What's he doing?
Guys, I don't have a
good feeling about this.
We should leave.
She's obviously not gonna talk to us.
But why not?
Why won't she talk about the house?
I don't know, man. Dude,
she-she seemed scared.
No shit.
Scared by what?
Who?
Wait, didn't that last woman
say that the demons or ghosts follow them?
Shit!
Turn off that camera!
What the hell?
Oh, my God!
Crazy!
Crazy bitch!
- The fuck?!
- What the fuck was that?
That was insane!
What if she hit on of us?!
We're not going back there again.
Who we gonna go interview next?
Shit.
Next time you do the interview, Kurt.
All right man.
Well, dude the rock was right by my head!
You saw that.
Probably aiming for your head.
- Shit.
- Big ol' head.
I had the window open.
If she would've hit you... Oh, my
God, I don't know what I would've done.
Dude, that was terrifying.
You got this, Shauna.
Hello?
Hello. Mrs. Warner? Mrs. Carolyn Warner?
Who is this?
Um, my name's Shauna Roberts.
I'm a filmmaker working on a documentary.
Mrs. Warner, what exactly happened
to your family when you were living there?
You left after living
there for only 19 days.
What happened to your daughter, Tricia?
We understand she went mute
just like the last little boy. The other...
Leave my daughter out of this!
Fuck!
Great job, Shauna.
Oh, shit.
So from 1977 'til now,
no one's lived there?
No, no. People were scared off.
You see, every time someone even
talked about buying the property,
the local Indians
would pay them a visit.
Tell them all kinds of stories
about how the land was evil.
That anybody who lived there
would have some tragedy befall them.
What's with the 21 days?
It takes 21 days for the demon
to fully enter the soul of the human.
The others left in time...
...with their souls intact.
But their lives were never the same.
Before abandoning the house...
...the two previous homeowners...
...covered all the mirrors.
Why was that?
To keep the demon from entering the soul.
See, when the mirrors are covered,
the demon sleeps.
He cannot capture your soul.
The belief by many in town...
...is that your people scared
off the previous homeowners
because you believe the
land is rightfully yours.
And...
...because you believe it sits
on an ancient burial ground.
We do believe the land is ours.
It sits upon a vortex.
A portal to the underworld:
the Devil's playground.
There are some places so dark, so evil,
...no human, no living being,
should ever dwell there.
Good to know.
It's not the dead in
this town that's scary...
It's the living.
Yeah, no shit.
Why I am glad that I brought this.
- Dude, what the fuck?
- A little protection.
Jacob! I can't believe you brought a gun!
Yeah, are you that kind of jerk
that just brings a gun around everywhere?
Jesus Christ, are you kidding me?
After some of the people we've met?
It's like fucking Deliverance.
You'll be glad I brought it. Trust me.
This is it.
It's in through on of these trees.
Yeah, here we go.
Yeah.
This doesn't scare you Jacob?
- What? Trees?
- Yeah.
No. No, it doesn't. Nothin' scares me.
Yeah.
Gotta let your imagination run wild, man.
You know, you always are
filled with the craziest ideas.
You're not gonna film me
putting cinnamon in my mouth.
Come on, man, have a little fun.
That's pretty nice, actually.
This must be the, uh, guy from the bank.
He's gonna let us in.
Look how proper he looks.
Hey, there.
Is that thing on?
That thing is on. He's our main cameraman.
Wow, wow.
He's gonna make you look good, though.
You gonna get us in there?
Uh, let's get you in there right now.
Okay, show us the way.
Follow me this way.
Duck your heads, everyone.
Well, I gotta say
it doesn't seem too creepy from here
except for spider webs.
- Creepy?
- It seems really beautiful, actually.
Thank you so much.
After you, sir.
Everything's pretty much
the way the last owner left it.
Oh, my gosh.
Guess the, uh, banks
aren't really responsible
for cleaning the place up.
No.
It's gonna be on you Shauna.
- Dining room.
- Are these their packing boxes?
They didn't even finish
unpacking before they left?
I guess so.
- Hm.
- Huh.
Hey! Who knows? Maybe...
...we'll end up taking this place.
It could be our dream house.
- This is a good house.
- Shut up.
And so, who technically owns...
...all the belongings in here? The bank?
Right now, the bank.
Wow. There's some pretty nice things.
- Wanna check the bedrooms?
- Yeah.
I'd love to.
One of the smaller rooms right there.
Wow.
Whoa.
It looks like somebody was just in here.
- Goodness.
- I know.
This was his room.
Oh, my God.
Oh. This picture.
He's not gonna let us get one
night's sleep. It's gonna be...
Done checkin' out the bathroom?
Really.
This thing's huge.
- Huh.
- I really like this fireplace.
This is the master bedroom.
Oh! I want this room.
- It's so pretty.
- The kid's room, and that room
and then this room.
It's... one too many.
Hey guys. Did you notice
that all the mirrors are covered
exactly like they told us they would be?
That's what they said. Yeah.
Lisa Thompson, she really
just... Her and her son...
...left all of her stuff behind
and didn't come back for anything?
Um, nope.
That mirror's covered, too.
Fuck.
Holy shit.
Hey, come here. Look at this.
She even left most of
her and her son's clothes.
- Whoa.
Weird, huh?
Did she ever say...
...what happened to her in this house?
What scared her?
Nothing specific. Only
that the place was...
...haunted and that no
one should live here.
She immediately forfeited
the rights to the place.
Sending it into foreclosure.
We're gonna find out, man.
We're gonna find out what
happened in this house,
and we're gonna get it all on camera.
This basically just says
that if anything happens to us
or we die in the house,
the bank or town... won't
take any responsibility.
I'm leaving a few windows open just an inch
for fresh air to come in.
This is the best way... um...
In the event of an
emergency, like a fire...
...you're gonna have to break
through the windows to get out
because everything will
be completely barricaded.
This us, uh... at your request.
You know those reality shows?
They stay in a haunted house for a night?
We're gonna stay in this house for 21 days.
And when we do that...
...we're gonna be the
longest lasting residents
to have stayed here more than 20 days.
So, I mean, honestly...
...we just want to disprove
or debunk, or whatever,
the urban legend that surrounds this house.
I know it's not haunted.
Hey. That reminds me, actually.
Before we get hermetically
sealed up in this place...
..Kurt, why don't you take Shauna and, uh,
go see if you can find that...
...Indian burial ground?
I'm gonna go check out the barn.
- Sure thing, dude.
- Thanks.
Thanks, man. Thanks a lot.
Thanks, guys.
Looks good.
Holy shit.
Jesus.
I don't see any headstones.
Kurt, it's an ancient burial ground.
Not gonna see any headstones.
What's it gonna look like
so we know what the hell to look for?
I don't know. Mounds or rocks or something.
What the fuck?
They're everywhere.
Hey, didn't that guy yesterday...
Didn't he tell us the dream catchers
are used for catching evil?
Why are they placed in
the ground like that?
Dream catchers are supposed to be hung.
Not scared yet, are you?
We-we really can't get out?
Nope.
Hey, thanks guys!
We're officially locked in this house.
21 days and 21 nights.
All right, so basically,
the whole house is covered.
All of the cameras...
with nighttime vision.
Now this is going to allow us...
...to see in low light
or even no light environments.
Now, I've also placed what
is called an EMF meter,
better known as a ghost detector,
in each room.
Now this turns it on.
And this will basically light up and beep
if someone or something passes by
disturbing that electromagnetic field.
I also placed
a digital still camera in the barn.
You can see it right there.
And what I'm gonna be doing
is I'm gonna be taking a still digital shot
about once every hour.
It should be noted that...
...the barn has also been barricaded
to keep anybody from getting in.
Now, this is going to allow us
to see if anything moves or changes,
or just if anything
peculiar happens at all.
I found all these crazy
things... in the barn
that belonged to the people
who used to live here.
Paranormal researchers usually
call these trigger objects,
meaning they might trigger something
in the spirits of the
people who lived here.
Awesome.
Or... the objects themselves
may have some kind of residual
memories of what happened
and just being back in the house
might trigger some sort of...
...paranormal reaction.
- Somebody's been doin' their research.
- Yeah.
- You found all of these in there?
- Sweet.
- Like... full train set.
Hey, guys.
Guys?
- Grr!
- Shit! The fuck, dude?
Oh, my God.
Don't do that, man!
So remind me why you're
putting this in my room again.
So the spirits will come
out and play with this.
Okay, that was... that was pretty cool.
I think he looks a lot like you.
All right.
Oh, gosh.
You know, since none of the past owners
will just tell us what happened here,
maybe their belongings will.
Right, Raggedy Ann?
What happened here, huh?
Guys, this is creepy, though.
What?
They covered all the mirrors.
Well, not for long.
You ready?
Didn't the Native Americans to us not to...
...you know, uncover these mirrors?
Dude, they warned us not to.
Oh, you know what? You're right.
Let's just scrap the whole thing.
Let's just call the bank
rep and have him let us out.
Is that what you want? That what you want?
No. All right, all right.
Cry me a river.
Seriously.
- Oh, my God! My hand!
- Shit.
Jacob!
Those Native Americans...
Wait, get Raggedy Ann.
All right, Kurt. That
can be your room here.
You know what my room reminds me of?
My grandma's house.
All right, well... if
this is Grandma's house
you've got one demonic, demented grandma.
My room, too?
That's the deal.
God, that's weird that they
just left all that stuff
laying around like that.
It's a lot of mirrors they covered.
You don't scare anybody...
...little bitch devil.
I don't see any demon in here.
Are you in here, demon?
Do you wanna suck my soul?
You can suck my soul.
Guys, I took 'em all off.
Hey, Shauna!
Hey, they got a tub in here.
You should totally use it.
All this talk of demons has got me horny.
So I created a timeline
of the three families
who tried to live here.
Um...
Some of these are really creepy.
Especially of the last two.
- Built in 1890.
- Awesome.
You get these pictures from the historian?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
That's cool.
They all covered the mirrors.
I wish something would happen.
Why are you whispering?
I really wanna start
to see some, you know...
...activity.
You're crazy. Careful what you wish for.
Come here, come here!
Check this out! Come on!
Ooh.
What's goin' on?
I was-I was, uh...
I was checking the still images
from last night in the barn.
Yeah?
All right, so this is, like, 12 o'clock.
One o'clock.
Two o'clock.
Three o'clock.
Oh, my God.
That is pretty cool.
And you're sure you checked
the surveillance camera
and nobody got in there?
No.
The place is totally locked down.
There's no windows, so there's no wind
that could've came in or
blown it across or anything.
It just moves. It... Watch.
That's insane!
You checked the EVP recorder, right?
Yeah, yeah...
Dude, if there's a sound,
man, the baseline will spike.
It's-it's flatlined.
Jacob?
Kurt?
Hm.
Wh...
It's on the inside, dude.
The hand print. Look.
- Fuck.
- It came from inside the house.
It's crazy.
Dude, where's Shauna?
What the fuck?
Was this the only thing
that was in the box?
Yeah.
There's nothing else in there?
I just saw the pictures.
It looks like they did it in blood.
Come on, it's not blood.
It's probably, like, magic marker
or something. You're ridiculous.
You fucking kidding me? That's blood.
Zoom in on the photo.
It's blood. Look at it.
Okay, okay, cameraman.
Well... whatever it is,
who would even do this?
Where did we find these?
Kurt, doesn't it look
like the symbol we saw
on the dream catchers we saw outside?
Kinda looks like a... pentagram.
But not quite.
I dunno, man.
There's a reasonable explanation for it.
There always is.
What's the explanation? Tell me.
How am I supposed to know?
Why don't we go look at the fact
that we have the entire house recorded
and see that there's nobody who did this,
so they were probably
stashed there by somebody
to scare off every other
person who's been in the house.
Look.
The symbol is almost exactly identical
to the symbol we saw on
the... on the pictures here.
Look.
Those two Native American
dudes we met the other day,
they probably marked up these pictures.
No, Jacob.
Sure they did. To scare us off.
Well, why in the hell did they put them
all the way in the back of the closet
if they wanted us to see them?
Yeah, and, I mean, how do
you explain the hand print?
That came from inside the house.
Who the hell turned on the water?
It's an old house with faulty pipes, Kurt.
But that doesn't explain the hand print.
Look. I think all this
weird shit we're seeing,
it's just a result of these
guys wanting to scare us off.
Just like they did with the other families.
I mean, if it was those guys doing this,
we would see it. But we don't.
The hand print, it-it just appears.
Well, first of all...
...we can't even see the handprint
from the angle of the
surveillance camera, okay?
It's Shauna's handheld where we pick it up.
Come on, dude.
Look. I don't know how they did it,
but I'm convinced they did it.
There's nothing evil here.
There's no demon.
I know. I just can't wait
to get out of this house.
I know.
Yeah, we can go get fro-yo, or something.
Hey, Jacob, Shauna, come here!
You gotta hear this!
What's goin' on?
So... I was looking at the EVPs last night.
Well, you got to look at your other camera
if you got something.
Listen to what happens in the barn.
Sounds like something, but...
...I can't-I can't
hear what. What is that?
Exactly. All right. Now, check it out.
This happened last night
right before Shauna
discovered the hand print.
Shauna!
- Come play with us.
Oh, my God.
Shauna? Come play with us?!
Holy shit.
Kurt...
...bring up the, uh,
still image from the barn.
Get that?
Yeah. It's right here.
What's with all those orbs?
Okay. Now, uh...
...compare it to the one from last night.
I just wanna see something.
Holy shit, the scythe in
the corner of the barn.
It's gone.
What happened to it?
I don't know, man.
It probably just fell out
of camera range, you know?
Check-check the outside camera.
Kurt, make sure nobody broke in,
took it or... You know?
Something reasonable. See what happened.
Dude, it's... it's totally locked down.
I don't know.
No one got in.
It's-it's fucking gone, dude.
Holy shit.
Let me take the camera.
Where are you goin'?
I wanna go check out the window
where we saw the hand print.
Hm.
- What is it?
- What's going on?
Did you...
- What the fuck?
- Holy shit.
Did you... Did you guys do that?
What?
What are you talkin' about?
Did you guys put that there?
Shauna, what the fuck?
Get a grip. We're locked in here.
This is from the barn.
Oh, my God.
Then how the hell did it get in here?
I don't know.
Baby. Baby, here, look. Hand me the camera.
OH, my God. You're shaking.
Relax. Get some rest, okay?
We'll check this out.
It's okay.
I'll be right here.
How the fuck did this get in here, dude?
Shauna must've been so terrified, man.
Hm. She's a big girl.
Did you just see that open?
No.
Did you see that? Did you see it open?
Hm, I dunno. Kind of.
Oh, man. Dude, you got to admit
this makes for some pretty
fuckin' good footage, though.
And I can smell the money now.
This is exactly what we needed, dude.
This is exactly what we wanted.
That is going to have
the network pick it up.
That alone.
I mean, if they even believe
that we didn't fake it ourselves.
It's not what I wanted, man.
Well, what is it exactly that you do want?
Nothing? Nothing to happen?
We just stay in a house for 21 days
for no fucking reason
and just come out of
here broke with nothing?
You say some stupid ass shit sometimes.
It's nothing to be worried about.
Look at your face. Pussy face.
Look at your face. Look how stupid that is.
It's a man's face.
That is not a man's face.
- Look at that face.
- That's a shit face. That's a face...
Look at the money in my mouth.
Laughing all the way to the bank.
Look at you... meditating.
Look at me. Let me look in your eyes.
Are you the devil?
You know, I'm tired of
fuckin' hearing you talk.
Seriously.
Damn it. Chill out.
Hey, babe.
How ya feelin'?
Sweetie.
It's gonna be fine.
Everything's gonna be fine. I promise you.
I'm gonna figure out
what the hell is going on.
No. Just leave it alone, Jacob.
Leave what alone? I
just wanna figure out...
Seriously, like...
That symbol...
That circular symbol.
I looked it up on the internet.
And it was fucking appearing on rocks,
drawings on rocks thousands of years ago.
And depicting some...
...like, the underworld.
Some demonic place.
Baby, okay. Okay.
Just...
Whatever is in this house...
...just fucking... just leave it alone.
Okay, baby. We'll leave it alone.
I promise.
I'll leave it alone.
So, um...
See anything last night?
Hear anything?
No.
I don't know, man.
Everything's pretty quiet.
You know what I mean?
Last-last night I was, like,
laying in bed, you know...
...and then, you know,
when you, like, lay in bed
and you kind of get
that feeling that like...
...something weird going on. So you get up.
I checked it and there was nothing.
All right. So you didn't hear anything.
That's good. I'm just...
...worried about her.
How she doin'?
She's all right.
Wants to leave.
- Yeah.
- But... not an option.
I mean, I can't blame her.
Yeah.
What? Do you wanna go too?
You know, I'll... I'll stick it out.
Gotta stick it out, man.
Hear that up there?
Hey.
Why-why are you stompin' around out there?
It's not me.
- Do you hear that?
- Yeah, yeah, I do hear it.
- What the fuck is that?
- Shh.
Sounds like it's comin' from...
It's coming from one of the bedrooms.
Holy shit.
Guys, I don't know where
that was coming from.
Whose room.
It's upstairs somewhere,
I know that for sure.
Kurt, bring it up on the
surveillance cameras quick.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'll check it out.
- They up?
- Dude...
The EMF meter, look, it's going off.
Oh!
Holy shit.
Everything's fine there.
- That one?
- It's goin' off in your bedroom.
All right. All right. You guys stay here.
I'm gonna go check what's going on.
Careful.
He's goin' in.
Shit.
What the fuck?
What the fuck was that?
I swear to God I just
heard something in here.
Holy shit.
Hey Jacob! What's going on?!
What the frack?
Jesus.
Hey, guys, it's nothing.
The breeze must've blown
open the medicine cabinet
or something.
What's going on?
Holy shit.
What?
Is this some kind of
sick fucking joke, Kurt?
Dude, what are you fucking talking about?
What the fuck is the matter with you?
Don't you see he's fucking
freaking out right now?
Why the fuck would you do this shit?
I'm totally not prepared
to create that, dude!
At all!
These pictures weren't here
five fucking minutes ago.
So tell me what happened.
I don't know, man.
Oh, my...
The picture...
They took it off my phone.
Shauna. Shauna, stop it.
Calm down, okay? Kurt did this.
He's fucking around.
You brought some kind
of fucked up printer...
- Dude!
- ...that allows you to do this shit!
What the fuck are you
talking about, asshole?!
I told you! I did not do this, okay?
It's just like the others.
We're gonna die here.
Shauna, we're not gonna die here.
- We only have five days left.
- God damn it!
What happened to those other
people is happening to us!
We gotta get the fuck out of here!
Now! We have to go!
- What are you doing?
- Where the fuck is she going?!
Jesus Christ!
Calm down!
Calm the fuck down!
You're hurting me!
Shauna!
What am I supposed to do?
Let her just smash the fucking window open?
Destroy everything we're here to create?
If they see that we maybe got out of here,
no deal!
We get nothing!
Is that what you want?
It's this house, dude.
It-it-it's fucking
making me go insane...
It's not the house. It's fucking you.
I cannot deal with this shit.
I need to fucking check on my girlfriend
who hates me now
'cause I'm trying to
keep this shit together.
Because you guys cannot fucking
figure out what you're doing.
What the fuck is wrong with you?!
The fuck is wrong with me?!
Fuck you! Son of a bitch!
Get the fuck off of me!
Ow!
Son of a bitch!
Get your fucking hands off of me!
Fucking get the fuck off of me!
Don't you fucking start
that shit with me, man.
- Fucking...
- Don't you fucking do that.
Don't.
Leave me alone.
Come on, guys.
You have said... anything
to me in two days.
You gotta admit, things
have been pretty calm.
Nothing's happened.
Last few days, it's been all good.
You know, we only have three days left.
- You know?
- I know your sorry but...
I just can't, like, pick up and...
Just have everything be
like it never happened.
I know I fucked up.
Once we finish this...
...it's gonna be huge for us, Shauna.
It'll be a new start.
I promise.
I know.
Sleepin' in Kurt's room?
Yeah.
I swore to never mind that I noticed that.
- Fuck.
Shit's happening in there, dude.
Yeah, I know. I know. Don't wake her.
Fuck. It's fucking dark as shit out.
All right.
Something's not right.
What the fuck was that, dude?! Fuck!
Jesus Christ!
- Jesus...
- Are you all right?
What the fuck.
What the fuck?!
Shauna ripped these fucking pictures up!
No, dude!
These photos were fucking
taken over a year ago!
Dude, don't touch it.
Dude, fuck! It's blood, dude!
It's fucking... It's fucking blood, dude!
Fuck!
What the hell?
- Oh, my God.
- What the hell is that, man?
Holy crap.
Dude, Kurt, what is that?
I don't know, I don't know.
Shit!
Oh, God.
The hell?
What the fuck is going on?
I don't know.
Put it down. Put it down, put it down.
We gotta get the fuck
outta this house, man.
We need to get the fuck out!
No, no.
What are you doing?
Shauna can't know about these.
She'd freak out. It would kill her.
Are you-are you fucking kidding me, dude?
We have to tell her!
No.
It will be too much for her.
She wouldn't be able to handle it.
We only have two days left.
It's the best thing?
Fine.
Is everything cool?
Fuck!
Yeah... yeah. Everything's fine.
I'm gonna head to bed.
Okay.
I'm just gonna stay up
for a little while longer.
See...
...if anything's going on.
Anything happens...
...come get me.
You got it.
Jacob, Shauna! Get in here now!
You have to see this!
What's goin' on?
Shauna, you... you don't need to see this.
No, no, no. She has to see this.
You have to.
What the hell is that?
Dude, what happened?
Where the hell did he go?
The EMF meter, I mean...
...it's right at this point
where the kid crosses frame.
What?
I-I still don't understand,
dude. What happened to him?
He went inside of the house.
What?
What do you mean he
went inside of the house?
It's still barricaded
shut. That's impossible.
I know it is.
But I mean, the-the
door, you know, it's...
it's right beyond the
frame. So, you know...
...he-he basically just goes in
as if it were fucking open, dude.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's roll back the footage.
I wanna see the kid's face.
Wait. Freeze the frame.
Oh, my God.
You know who that is?
No. Who?
That's Lisa Thompson's son.
Her nine-year-old
mute son.
Dude, there is no fucking
way that is the same kid.
What the fuck is she talking about?
Why are you having...
Look.
Holy shit.
What the fuck is this kid
coming here in the middle of the night for?
Who're you calling?
That lady that... The historian.
- Hello?
- Hello? Clarice?
Clarice Johnson?
Yes?
Hi, um. This is Shauna Roberts.
I'm one of the filmmakers.
We interviewed you a few weeks
ago about the house on Cedar Road.
Yes, it's Clarice
Great, uh, you...
...don't by any chance
have Lisa Thompson's number,
do you?
Something really weird happened.
Her son... it looked
like he was on our porch
at, like, 2:30 in the morning last night.
That... that can't be.
What do you-what do you mean?
Lisa and her son were
killed last night
in a car accident.
It happened on the 99
Freeway outside of Fresno,
about three hours away from here.
Story's in the local paper today.
Oh, my God.
Uh, hello?
Hi, hi. Th-thank you.
Thank you.
Okay, bye.
What the fuck?
That cannot be possible.
- They died?
- I need to see the article.
No. Bullshit. I...
Pull it up online.
It would-it would be online if
something like that happened.
We should look it up.
- Yeah.
Here it is. Here it is. Okay.
"Lisa Thompson, 35, of
Fillmore, California,
and her nine-year-old
son, Jonathan,
were killed last night in a car accident
while traveling on the 99 Freeway
outside of Fresno."
Um...
"Witnesses said the car
inexplicably veered off the road,
plunging off a cliff.
Authorities claim neither
weather nor alcohol
were factors in the accident.
Mother and son were pronounced
dead at the scene at...
...12:30 AM."
12:30.
Kurt...
...bring up the image from, uh,
when that kid entered the frame.
Jesus Christ.
Do you guys remember...
...the teenager who lived
in the house in the '70s?
Dated February 1st, 1978.
"Cory Warner, 20, of San
Francisco, California,
was tragically killed last night
when his car inexplicably
veered off the road,
plunging over a cliff.
Witnesses and police said weather
was not a factor in the accident
and that it appeared Warner intentionally
drove his car over the cliff.
Sources claim the victim was
en route to speak to a reporter
about a home he and his family
had recently lived in that was
reportedly the site
of unexplained paranormal phenomena."
No one can convince me
that those two accidents are coincidence.
What... is going to happen to us...
...if we stay in this place?
What's going to happen to us
when we decide to leave?
I mean, we already got
fucking demonic pictures
and shit, like, all over
the fucking walls and shit!
What the hell's up with that?
What are you guys talking
about? What happened?
Nothing. He's overreacting.
I've had enough. 20 days. I'm done.
Yeah, well the deal with
the network is 21 days,
and we're staying here 21 days.
- I don't care!
- Jesus Christ.
I want to get out of this
fucking evil-ass house!
- You're overreacting.
- I mean, fuck, man!
The-the-the kid. He-he was in
a fucking car and he-he died,
and now apparently
he's showing up at our fucking door step,
pronounced dead!
It's not the same kid.
Some other fucking kid
who lives around here
who looks like him.
Look at the fucking pictures! It's him!
He fucking died and now his
soul, or whatever the fuck
is going on in this god damn house,
is living in here!
His soul, or his ghost, or whatever, Kurt,
is not in this house.
It's not him!
It can't be him!
- Drop it!
- Fuck!
Nothing happened.
Yeah...
- He's so freaked out!
- He's freaking out!
He's always freaking out.
All through college he freaked out.
I am not freaking out!
Just calm down, dude.
I just don't want to
stay in this house, dude.
Just chill out. We have one more day.
One day, dude. Please.
Get a grip!
You're calling me on your cell?
Check the monitor.
What's happening in your bedroom?
Bedroom One.
Something or someone
just went in that room.
Fine, fine, fine. Hold on.
You know you could've just
probably come down here yourself
if you wanted to.
In my room?
I'm looking at the monitor now, Shauna,
there's nothing in there.
Do you want to talk to Kurt
'cause you don't believe me?
Oh, my god. I'm gonna
show you the playback.
You seriously are gonna have
to buy me lunch after this.
- Here.
- What?
Shauna has a question for you.
Hello?
What are you talkin' about?
Everything's cool, Shauna, there's...
...there's no one in the room.
Yeah.
Okay. I'm here.
Oh, my God.
How?
How did this happen?
That's me.
Oh, my God!
Jesus Christ.
Let me out of here!
Let me out!
- Shauna!
- Let me out!
What's going on?
What the fuck?
Holy mother of Christ.
Those fucking photos, dude.
They're of me as a fucking kid.
How-how the fuck did these get here?
Oh, my God.
How did these fucking get here, dude?
It's fucking impossible! How
is this happening in here?
What the fuck?!
What the fuck is
happening with this place?!
What the fuck, man?!
It-it-it...
it's wet.
The other night...
...we found the photos... of us downstairs.
They had the same bloody circles on 'em
I didn't wanna frighten you.
I burned them.
I hate you! Why would you
not tell me about that?!
I didn't wanna scare you!
Shauna!
Shauna, wait!
Wait! I can explain it to you!
I just didn't want to scare you!
Jesus Christ, Shauna!
Stop it!
What the hell is wrong with you?!
Bullshit! We are so fucking outta here!
Jacob!
What the fuck, Jacob?!
Are you out of your mind?!
Look...
I know...
...a lot of really crazy
shit has been happening.
Really?
You fucking think so?
But we're okay.
Nobody's hurt, nobody's dead.
Jacob, we're not dead yet!
What the fuck are you gonna do, huh?
What the fuck are you gonna do?
You're gonna shoot us? Huh?!
You're gonna fucking try and kill us
if we try to leave?
Is that what you're gonna do?
Shoot you.
Don't be fucking stupid, Kurt.
Oh, fuck!
Goddamn it, Jacob! You
took our cell phones too?
As I said...
...we only have 12 more hours...
...and I'm not have gone
through all this time and shit...
...for nothing!
Don't!
Don't touch.
Just 12 more hours...
...and it's all over.
It's okay.
He's not gonna hurt us.
It's gonna be okay. All right? Okay?
You're filming this right now?
Seriously?
It's the only thing that's keeping me sane
at this point.
Also, wanted to make sure
that we record everything.
In case our evil friend comes back.
I'm not talking about any of the ghosts...
...but rather, your fucking boyfriend.
Ex-boyfriend.
Where is that demonic prick anyway?
In his room.
Fucking asshole locked the door.
Look.
It's 12 o'clock.
- So?
- You don't know what that means?
21 days.
We made it.
Everything's gonna be okay. All right?
The bank rep is gonna be here in six hours
to let us out of this fucking place.
But six hours feels like
an eternity in this house.
Listen. We're gonna be fine.
Where is it coming from?
What room is that coming from?
It's coming from the living room.
Here, hold this. Hold this, okay?
Oh, Kurt, please just leave it alone.
It's okay. Look. I'm gonna be back for you.
I promise. Just stay here, okay?
Everything's gonna be okay. I promise.
Where is it coming from?
The fuck?
- Your phone.
- Where is it?
Get your phone.
What the fuck is that?
Kurt, please just don't go any closer.
Please don't go any closer.
Please don't. No.
Where the hell did she go?
- I don't know.
- Where the fuck did she go?
I swear she fucking came
in here. I swear to God.
Oh, my God,
Where is she?
What the fuck? Do you see that?
What?
That... can't...
Oh, my God.
What?
That's-that-that's the girl we
just saw on the rocking chair.
She lived here 35 years ago.
That's... that's fucking Tricia Warner.
But that's impossible.
Fuck!
What the hell is happening?
Call 911! Call 911!
Call 911 now!
Try-try-try
calling again!
Call anyone! I don't fucking care!
- I can't see!
- Check your phone book!
You gotta see something in there!
Check!
I-I-I'm trying!
I'm trying!
It's ringing. It's ringing. It's ringing.
Come on.
- Hello?
- Hello? Who is this?
Please! We need help!
This-this is Carolyn
Warner. Who is this?
Oh, my God.
Hello?
Uh, Carolyn Warner who used to live here?
Who-who is this?
We're-we're at your
old house on Cedar Road!
I have nothing to say to you.
No, no, no! Please!
Don't hang up the phone!
We need your help! Please, please.
Listen very, very carefully.
Your daughter is in this house with us.
Do you understand me?
Your daughter when
she's eleven-years-old
is in this house with us right now!
My daughter is dead!
What?
She-she died an hour ago
in St. Mary's Psychiatric Hospital.
Then why is she here?!
What is she doing...
What happened to this house?!
She's dead. You... you
uncovered the mirrors!
What? What do you mean?
The mirrors!
They unleash the evil that
resides in that house.
Whoever uncovers them,
which my daughter
did 35 years ago...
...gets possessed by
the evil, the demon,
and he beckoned them back to
reclaim all of their souls!
Well, what am I supposed to do?
Cover the mirrors!
And don't talk to the entities!
What-what do you mean?!
Oh, why didn't you
leave when you could?
Please just call the police!
Call 911! Help us get out of here!
It's too late.
No! No, it's-it's not too
late! It's not too late!
21 days.
No, please!
Help us! Help us! We need your help!
May God have mercy on your soul!
Hello?!
No!
No! She hung up!
Fucking out of here. Hold this. Hold this.
Okay? All right?
Kurt, where are you
going? What are you doing?!
Kurt, where are you?!
Help!
Help us!
Why won't the windows break?!
Why won't they break?!
Someone will come get us.
Someone will come get us out.
Kurt...
Where are you?
Kurt?
Oh, my God!
What the fuck was that?
Hey.
Oh, my God!
Shauna, let me see the camera.
You scared the shit out of me!
- Hold the flashlight.
- Okay.
You take the light.
Oh, my God, Kurt I'm so scared!
So scared right now!
Wait, shh.
Do you hear that?
Jacob?!
Jacob, is that you?!
We have to cover up the mirrors.
Right now, Kurt, we just gotta get these...
Jacob!
Go! Let's go! Come on!
Oh, my God.
Fuck!
Holy shit!
- Shauna...
- I need your help!
Fuck! Fuck!
Ow!
Come on! Come on!
Come fucking here!
It's no good, it's no good.
Okay, they're covered. Come with me!
Fuck!
Jacob!
Are you in there?!
Hey! Look-loo-look!
Okay. I can-I can...
I can bring it up on the, uh,
fucking surveillance camera, okay?
All right?
Oh, no!
Jacob!
What are they doing with him?!
They're in there with you!
Jacob, they're in there with you!
You have to get out! You have to get out!
Oh, my God!
Jacob, seriously!
Please just leave the room!
Do not talk to them, okay?
Do not talk to them! Just...
Just fucking stop doing this!
They're fucking coming towards the door!
Shauna! They're fucking coming!
Come on! Get out!
Shauna! Get away from the door!
All right, we gotta block the door!
We gotta block it! Pick this up!
Got it! Come on!
Right there!
Fuck!
Go!
Oh, my God!
Oh, fuck! Shit!
Fucking go!
What is happening?!
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Kurt, don't go any closer!
Please, no!
Jacob, what's wrong with you?!
What's happening?! Why are you doing this?!
Oh, my God!
Oh! Oh, my God!
I wanna get out!
Let me out of here!
Please work...
Our father, who art in Heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done
on Earth as it is in Heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread,
and forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
And lead us not into temptation...
...but deliver us from evil.
Amen.
Hello?
Hello!
We're here to let you out!
Guys?!
Hello!
Where are they?
Maybe they're still sleeping.
Let's check upstairs.
Hello?
Look at this.
The bag. They packed.
Maybe they forgot it?
Carl, there's no sign of them leaving.
The house was barricaded shut
and their car is still here.
They're gone.
Well, what the hell
happened to them then, Joe?
I don't know.
God damn it, Carl! Stop filming!
Carl, come on! We need to go!
Yeah, yeah. I'm coming!
Holy shit.
The fuck?
Carl, I'm not gonna say it again!
We're leaving now!
Coming! I'm coming!
Subtitles by explosiveskull