In less than 24 hours,
I'll be dead.
I don't know it yet.
That's why I'm talking
like this.
I'm the only one
standing behind a fence,
watching the parade race by.
Then it's gone.
I don't believe in love.
STARCROSSED
Subrip: Pix
Baby, can you
zip me up?
I... I talked to
the travel agent this morning.
Bora Bora, one week.
You and me.
I don't need that.
No. Come on.
I don't want that.
You're mine.
I know you're trying hard
to hold it all together.
Look.
It takes time.
This is... It's a process.
Doesn't happen overnight.
Just don't do anything
irrational.
I gotta go.
The company can't lend you
anything else right now.
We need to keep
our current staff afloat.
I don't wanna lose anyone.
I'll manage, Laz.
I always do.
Hell, you can tell Lucy,
in reality
it's her father
that's pressing this.
I'm sure she can
help you sort it out.
Let's talk tomorrow.
You know, I've never worked
in all my life.
In all my life,
I've never worked.
I've been thinking about that.
What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
You did too.
You said I was very fond
of expensive things...
Furs and jewels and things.
Did I say that?
I guess you and I have been,
more or less, used to...
a life of pink champagne.
Could you?
Anthony.
You all right?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
My father says
he's been trying
to
Get a hold of you.
Says you haven't
returned his calls.
You know, I hate talking
business with you two.
I'll call him.
Thank you.
Talked to Nathan today.
He's excited about tomorrow.
Dance with me.
-We have to go.
-No, no.
We have to go.
I'm gonna take my own car.
I'm gonna have drinks
with Valerie after.
Fucking dick!
Thanks.
Is, this seat taken?
Well, it's fate.
I don't believe in that,
but I'll take the seat.
Pity.
Scotch, please.
Miss?
You can't smoke in here.
Sorry.
Come on.
What's your name?
I'm called Kat.
Ben.
Rawlins.
You don't look
like a Ben.
It's a middle name.
I will not release this
into your custody...
until you tell me.
It's just gonna go out.
Then I'll just wait
until you light another one.
Letholdus.
Now, that...
That sounds
like a middle name.
It doesn't sound
like any kind of name.
Well, I smell a story.
Letholdus was the
first knight
over the wall
of Jerusalem
in the first crusade.
So it's noble.
No one calls me that.
Why not?
I don't know.
Why are you so interested?
You know, it's strange.
We're out here listening
to the world go by,
and we know
there's people out there,
even though we can't see them.
I always wonder
what their story is.
I'm still curious
why no one calls you that.
Fine. I'll find out
sooner or later.
Wait.
You've got an eyelash.
Make a wish.
Quickly!
Guys, you can't smoke
out here either.
I'm not...
We're not smoking.
Dude.
I used to dance to this
when I was little.
It always used to
make me feel so free.
I don't feel that way anymore.
So, what are you then?
What would you find
more enticing...
The answer
or the mystery?
To mystery.
Cheers.
Another one?
Yeah, please.
I'm gonna start
charging you for those.
I don't pay for things.
Another piece
of the puzzle.
I wouldn't try
to solve me.
Come on. Everybody
wants someone
to solve them,
don't they?
Not me.
Why not?
'Cause everything important
gets taken away.
Good evening, sir.
Ma'am? Could I
get something started
for the two of you?
Gin with tonic
and your driest Pinot Noir.
Right away, sir.
Hello.
You know him?
You remember Bailey Steinfeld.
It's her cousin, Ben.
From Kentucky.
She wanted me
to show him around the city,
so it's the least I could do.
Nice to meet you, Ben.
Nice to meet you.
I don't hear an accent.
We...
We moved around a lot.
Aren't you going
to introduce me?
-And you are?
-I'm Kat.
Maddox.
Kat's
Rommel Lazarus's niece.
Yes. My mother's
his sister... Lily.
We were just gonna go,
get a table and have a drink.
Why don't we join you?
Sure.
-Here you are, ma'am.
-Thank you.
Sir? Gin and tonic.
Enjoy.
Waiter.
You can call me Gerry,
sir.
Gerry, this has
too much tonic in it.
I asked for gin with tonic.
"With" means 10% tonic.
-So sorry.
-A real drink.
-I'll fix it right now.
-A man's drink. Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
You don't need to do that.
Look, I know what I want.
And now he knows what I want.
Now he's gonna get it for me.
Alright you don't need
to talk to him like that.
Was I wrong, Ben?
Was I wrong?
No,
you were not wrong.
Here you are, sir.
Gin and tonic.
Ten percent.
Perfect, Gerry.
So, how did the two of you
get thrown together?
Well,
he was gallant.
Rommel. Someone's
actually named that?
I thought I had a bad name.
What are you talking about?
Your name is Benjamin.
Well, no, it's not.
Erwin Rommel.
He was a Nazi field general.
Considered to be the most humane
and ingenious of his kind.
Still a Nazi though.
I'm going to go
to the bathroom.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
I have to use
the restroom too.
If you guys
will excuse me.
My shift ended.
Have a good one.
Have a good night, man.
Really?
You okay?
You know,
I have this theory.
You can tell a lot
about a person
when you see them
standing alone.
That right?
I learned a lot.
About?
I don't think
I should tell you.
Go on. Tell me.
You're hiding something.
A secret.
Maybe more than one.
The trick is, you've learned
to hide the hiding.
You know this based
on what exactly?
Well, it takes one
to know one.
You wanna
get out of here?
Me and you.
I mean, it's just...
It's kind of a lot
to handle right now.
You wanna just...
cut out maybe?
I can't.
Don't leave me alone
with them.
We were getting ready
to send out a search party.
Ben and I were just saying,
it's about to get busy in here.
Maybe we should just
continue this at your place.
Our house?
-Lucy's meeting someone later.
-I can cancel.
Ben.
What do you say?
I'm sure he has
somewhere better to go.
Actually, I don't.
Nothin' better at least.
Anthony, why don't you take Kat,
and Benjamin will ride with me.
I want him to see
the city at night.
Shall we?
I'll get the check.
Who is she?
I don't know.
If you ever...
I swear to God...
-I...
-What?
I'm sorry.
I'm just happy
that you're here.
I don't believe you.
In my house?
You better not
say anything to her.
Nothing.
You promise me.
Promise.
You've a beautiful home.
Thank you.
We're very comfortable here.
It's been in the family
for years.
Please... sit down.
Make yourself
comfortable.
Anthony, darling.
Why don't you make Ben
a drink?
We should,
just stay here.
Nonsense.
Just make him the...
Perfect drink.
Kat?
Will you join us?
I'm fine here.
Benjamin?
Is this your son?
That was taken
in Jackson Hole
a few summers back.
Sweet face.
That was preschool.
Are you a cognac man?
Not really.
This one.
You have good taste.
This was bottled
before my father was born.
It cost me $77,000.
It's not polite to talk
about
the cost of things
with company.
Lucy would say that.
It's funny.
That a thing so rare
can be so insignificant.
Do you have a family?
No, not really.
You? You got kids?
Yeah.
We adopted a son, Nathan.
He's away at camp.
Have you been
enjoying my wife?
What was that?
Lucy.
She's showing you
the city, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, she has.
How do you like it?
The city.
I tend not to stick around
anywhere too long.
See, I'm just
the opposite.
When I have something,
I can't let it go.
I stay too long.
Funny accident
how we all
found
each other tonight.
Should...
Should we head back?
Ben has great taste.
The '29.
Lucy was just telling me
about your son.
He's learning
how to play tennis.
Is he?
He's very athletic
and he's so smart.
-Ladies?
-Cheers.
Benjamin?
Thanks.
Nazdarovya.
To a good night.
So is he here?
Your son.
Is he sleeping?
Should we be quiet?
-Actually...
-Lucy.
Can I talk to you?
Okay.
-Now.
-Excuse us.
We'll be
just a minute.
Why are you doing this?
So rude.
What are you doing?
I want to smoke.
What if this
is my last one?
Well, then I'd
take it from you.
What's your fantasy?
There you are.
Well, what is it?
To be free.
Of what?
I don't know.
What's yours?
To die young.
You didn't really
mean that, did you?
What are you doing?
You're not coming in?
I...
I just wonder
where they went.
You really care?
No. I just...
They could be fucking.
No.
They haven't in months.
He told me.
He told you that?
I just think...
I don't...
People's private lives
should stay private.
See, that's your problem.
You want everything
to be like a dream.
But it's not a dream.
Sex is sex.
Fucking is fucking.
Don't be such a prude.
I'm not a prude.
You afraid to jump?
So, where does she
keep you?
What?
Where does Mrs. Bishop
keep you?
I know you don't work.
I'm a writer.
Right.
I am.
Have I read
any of your work?
'Cause I read everything.
I was published.
How long ago?
Four years.
So you don't work.
I'm not judging.
You're imagining things,
Kat.
I can smell
one of my own kind.
Don't.
It's not like that.
Why? Why not?
Some writer.
You're with
a married man.
-It's more complicated than that.
-Is it? Is it?
What is it,
like some kind of act
or something?
It's all an act, Ben.
We give people
the versions of ourselves
they need to feel safe.
I give him what he needs,
so he gives me what I want.
What does that mean?
It means
he pays for my life.
For all of it.
So you're a whore.
Don't do that.
No, say it with me.
Say it with me.
"I'm a whore."
You're one to talk.
Lucy's showing me the city.
I bet.
So, where does he
keep you?
Where does he keep
his whore?
A loft in the marina.
Your turn.
Why should I have to
tell you anything?
Because I can't stand
a liar,
and I liked standing you.
Downtown.
She keeps me downtown.
I like we're being honest.
Honest?
Back there...
Things are getting
quite serious, aren't they?
Let's go look around
some more.
I don't wanna look around.
You're beautiful.
Sometimes dirty things
have a kind of beauty.
This can't lead anyplace.
I know.
Now that I've found you,
I don't want to let you go.
We really should
get back downstairs.
Anthony?
What?
Are you listening to me?
Yes.
Where did you get this?
What?
This bra.
I don't think I've ever
seen you wear it before.
What's this?
This...
is a tattoo.
Come on.
It's...
It's the name of a song that
my father would sing me
when I was a kid to
put me to sleep.
"Szerelem."
It, means "love" in hungarian.
Well,
what's the song say?
It's in hungarian.
Tell me your favorite part.
Favorite part is...
"I would do anything
for my old lover.
I would dip the water
of the sea.
I would pick shells
from the seabed,
and I would sew a wreath
for my old lover."
Tell me about him...
Your father.
He was, you know,
the strongest man in the world
to me when I was a kid.
You know how you think
when you're a kid.
He was...
He was a superhero to me.
You know, my book
was about my parents.
Tell me about your mom.
My mother... passed away
when I was seven.
It crushed my father.
It devastated him.
He...
He lost it... all that...
That strength
that made him great.
And I watched it all melt away
when I was a kid.
He would cry to me.
He would cry to me,
a seven, eight-year-old kid.
And he'd be sobbing,
telling me how much
he missed her,
how much he needed her.
I wouldn't know what to say.
You know, why would...
How would I know
what to say?
And everyone else,
they were telling him
that it wasn't his fault,
that she was just
an unhappy person.
But...
he wasn't hearing it.
He took the full weight of it.
He blamed himself.
You know,
I remember having
the distinct thought that...
how is anything in the world...
worth that much pain?
And from that point on,
you know, he...
It was like he had
two different lives.
There was the life
while my mother was alive,
and there was the life after.
Whatever it was,
I stayed in this life.
Letholdus.
I was supposed
to see him today.
But you didn't?
Tell me something
about your parents.
Your family.
Don't.
Come on.
All right.
This sounds like Stravinsky.
We danced to Stravinsky
on our wedding day.
Why's that
so important?
I used to love Stravinsky.
Dance with me, Mrs. Bishop.
So that's why we're here.
I remembered us.
I remembered the day.
Can't a man love his wife?
Anthony,
you can't just change
everything back
the way it was
because you want to.
All this... what we have...
Is nothing.
You're nothing.
What are you doing?
You act like a cunt,
then I am going
to treat you like a cunt.
Stop... Stop it!
No!
Get out!
What?
You gonna swap me out
for the boy?
He's more of a man
than you.
Fuck. You get up.
Get up!
Fuck you.
What, are you
gonna shoot me?
Go ahead.
Go ahead and shoot me.
Wait. Stop!
You didn't want
to dance with me,
so you're going
to dance for me.
Do you understand?
Come on.
Yeah.
Harder. Harder!
That's right.
Yeah. Harder.
Harder.
Fucking harder.
Fuck.
Yeah.
That's right.
Now turn around.
Please. Please. Please.
Please.
Baby, please.
I'm sor...
I'm sorry.
Anthony.
Yeah, hi. Hi.
I need a cab
as soon as possible.
Yeah.
54 Alighieri Drive.
Thirty minutes?
Thank you. Thank you.
Hey, Laz.
It's-It's Lucy.
I-I really need
to talk to you.
Can you come by later?
I got a cab.
I told you...
I can't.
You've gotta stop running
at some point.
You pigeonholing me?
I mean, what are you
doing here, Kat?
Why are you
with this guy?
You don't know what
you're talking about.
I know you're better
than this.
You're better than
what he makes you into.
There you two are.
Everything okay?
Benjamin, would you
excuse us?
What's going on?
Nothing.
I know you, Kat.
You don't do nothing.
Where were you?
You fucked him,
didn't you?
No, say, "No, Anthony,
I didn't fuck him."
He can hear you.
That's not an answer.
Anthony, don't...
Kat.
I need you.
What about
what I need?
I give you everything.
No, you don't.
You give me nothing.
Not what I want.
I'm your whore.
That's all.
Please.
Give me what I want.
I don't have him.
He's not here.
You were gone a while.
Did you get lost?
Not... Lucy, not right now.
Anthony might see.
Anthony doesn't
see anything.
You remember
our story?
I would do anything
for you.
You know that,
right? Anything.
Anything you want.
You took care of me.
You want her.
What? What?
No.
Then why... why'd you
tell her your name?
What are you talking about?
Your real name, Ben.
Your real fucking name.
-You told her.
-What are you... Chill.
Don't you fucking...
Don't you fucking
tell me
to shut up!
What's gotten into you
right now?
You are mine.
I will take what is mine.
-Will you fucking tell me the truth?
-Calm down.
Stop.
What are you doing?
Just tell me the truth!
Anthony, Laz is here.
What is he doing here?
I'm gonna
take care of it.
What did you do? I can't
believe you called Laz.
Laz, how are you?
I am well, Tony. Thanks.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
Everything's great.
I got your message.
What was so urgent?
-I'm sorry about that.
-Lucy and I just had an argument.
It's okay.
What about the company?
What's wrong
with the company?
Nothing's wrong.
Laz, it was just
a misunderstanding.
We're fine.
Good to hear.
Laz, what...
How's Katherine?
My poor daughter, Kat.
She's been a mess
for some time now.
My first wife raised her
in England of all places.
She doesn't talk
to anyone in the family.
They called me
when she tried...
Tried...
You never met her
after all these years?
I think...
we should continue this
in the living room.
I guess I could stay a bit,
now that I'm here.
You know what?
Let's just stay here.
No, actually, you know,
the living room is much
more comfortable.
Yeah, we can listen
to that...
Stravinsky you
used to talk about.
I just prefer
to stay here.
I lied to you before.
About?
"He thought she must
be bouncing
between the most
beautiful dreams,
as her eyes fluttered,
threatening to wake.
We were stripped bare
in every sense imaginable.
Very rarely did I smile
after those days but,
who could help it?
We had made such
beautiful poetry together."
That's mine.
I loved your book.
It didn't drone on.
It had a beginning,
middle and end.
I told you
I read everything.
What do you want
from me?
Everything.
I can't help you.
Look, Kat, this-this fantasy
that you want to live in...
There's no future in it.
Don't do that.
Stop it.
There's no future in it.
Stop!
-There's no future in it!
-Stop it!
There's no future, Kat.
Stop it.
No!
Nathan!
No.
Nathan's your son.
And Lucy
doesn't know?
It's his birthday
tomorrow.
And no one
helped you.
Anthony and I...
I had a problem.
They took him from me.
They said I wasn't fit.
To be his mother?
To be his anything.
I signed the paper.
I signed it
with this hand.
They'll be back soon.
-We can tell them.
-Tell them what exactly?
Kat, I...
I know you now.
Now I don't want
to know you.
Hey.
I'm going downtown.
How are you two?
I know Nathan's
back tomorrow.
How was it
having him away
at camp
for the first time?
You really want to know?
Really?
Lucy.
I don't care anymore.
This isn't my business.
Anthony and I have both
been having affairs.
That's why we're in here,
because our lovers,
well, they're in
the living room.
Right now.
I should be going.
No, no, no.
You asked...
Really. It's late. I gotta...
I should be getting back.
No, Laz.
She's telling the truth.
You ever stop to think about
the millions of little things
in people's lives...
that pull them apart?
See, in life,
we bleed for people.
I mean, that's what
love is... blood.
So we bleed until
there's nothing left.
Lucy, she's...
You've taken all the blood
I have for you.
I'm dried up.
Nothing.
This isn't you, Kat.
This is bullshit.
You and me, we're not.
Didn't you feel it?
No, you fucked me.
He fucked me too.
Is this shit
all you care about?
Your-Your allowance
and your-your penthouse?
And-And your fucking
Jimmy Choos?
Is that what you
want to hear?
At least
it'd be honest.
I want my son, Ben.
I want to watch him sleep!
I want to smell him
in the morning!
I want...
I want to wipe his tears.
I need him.
Look at me.
I can help.
Why do you want
to help me?
You know who I am.
There's no one out there
for people like us.
Who's this?
Laz, let me explain.
Laz, what are you doing?
Shut up, Lucy.
Come with me.
Take my hand.
Katherine.
Don't call me that.
You can't tell me
what to do.
You only care now
because you're here
and you see me.
-Come on.
-Just...
You're a fucking sperm donor.
You're not my father.
Just leave me alone.
Kat.
I thought your book
was sad.
Everyone said that.
"There's no life
without you."
You stole that
from someone.
I can't remember who.
You know, I never
understood
why he stayed
and she didn't.
He had a son.
He lost his love.
He was pointless.
Give me that gun.
And then we'll...
Me and you will go
right now, okay?
Let's get out of here.
I... I'll take care of us.
What's your fantasy?
I could love you.
You already did.
No, no!
There was a book I had as a kid
about the monarch butterfly.
How it became itself.
The caterpillar
forms a chrysalis,
then dissolves into nothing.
It dies.
Inside isn't a prison.
It's an ocean of freedom...
that stretches beyond
the stars in the sky.
It shows us the future.
Then when it's ready,
it rises from nothing,
spreads its wings
and flies away.
Now I can walk
the Great Wall of China.
And go to Spain
and run with the bulls.
I could start something new.
And wake up with the sun.
I could love.
And love and love.