Replicants
are bioengineered humans,design by Tyrell corporation for use off-world.Their enhanced strength made them ideal slave labor
After a serious of violent rebellions,their manufacture became prohibited and Tyrell corp went bankrupt
The collapse of ecosystems in the mid 2020s
led to the rise of industrialist Niander Wallace.
Whose mastery of synthetic
farming averted famine
Wallace acquired the remains of Tyrell corp
and created a new line of replicants who obey.
many older model replicants-NEXUS 8s. with open-ended
lifespans-Survived.They are hunted down and "Retired"
those that hunt
them still go by the name...
Blade Runner
i hope you dont mind
if im taking you in the dirty.
I was carefully not to.
drag me in to the dirt.
i dont want to the dirt...
do you have a warrant
or an announced trespasses
Are you a police?
Are you Sapper Morton, id NK68514?
I'm a farmer.
a farmer.
Why are you following me?
This is the protein state.
Designed by Wallace.
Do I smell it?
I grow up by myself.
Garlic.
- I see.
Just taste it.
No thanks.
The hard work works
better with the empty stomach.
How long have
you been here?
Since 2020.
But you have
done more, is not it?
Your bags.
Settlement Medical Service.
Military equipment.
Where were you?
Callantha?
Certainly brutal.
Why dont you take me in?
And...
take a look inside?
Mr. Morton,
if it is...
it is a better option.
Someone, however,
would come in time.
I got to the point.
Whatever.
Now...
Could you
look up to the left.
Do not rise.
How do you feel
like killing yourself?
I do not delete my own
because we do not escape.
Fault of old models.
And the new designs
clean the shit out.
Because you have
not seen a miracle.
Describe all.
Miss Commissar.
Opening a police message.
You're hurt.
I will not pay it.
To dip it.
- I?
Latest Nexus 8s.
You could tear your head off.
Tried.
It disappeared after Kalanthia.
With a few others
that could be decided.
One Only?
- Just one.
Get in control.
Momentarily, ma'am.
From 30 meters to maximum depth.
What is it?
I'm sending a digging group.
Come before the storm.
Constable KD6-3.7, will be started.
Ready?
- Yes.
A statement for your test bed.
And there was
bloodshed emptiness
Kennosto if there is another commonness
around the cells to the third
to related
Pain in the fuck, imitation leather.
Too bad in contrast
night against the white fountain
Cells.
- Cells.
Have you ever
been in the facility?
Cells.
- Cells.
Are you considered a trainer?
Cells.
- Cells.
Are you locked in free?
Cells.
- Cells.
Together.
- Together.
How do you feel like
holding your beloved hand?
Together.
- Together.
Did you know
about your fingers?
Together.
- Together.
Do you want to contact our heart?
Together.
- Together.
Do you dream
about the connection?
Together.
How does it feel to
keep her baby in her lap?
Together.
- Together.
Is anything missing from you?
Together.
- Together.
Together with the cell.
- In one of the cellars.
Say three times "in one cell".
In one of the cellars, together
with the cell, together with the cell.
Prepare.
Konstantti K.
Your reward can be picked up.
Thank you.
Watch out. Watch out.
Connecting to the outside
world at anytime from anywhere.
Speech packages
starting at 20 minutes.
Versatile additional services.
You can leave
wherever you want.
What is a Korean tin soldier?
Kyy walks home, right?
Who's waiting for you?
I'll knock you on your ass!
PAIN BIRTH, COFFEE
K, I did not hear you.
You came early.
Will I come again?
Go to laundry.
- Yes ma'am.
How did the meeting go?
Usually.
How was your day?
Oh...
I'll go crazy inside.
99.9% sterile water.
There was a damage at work.
The shirt should go to ruin.
Give me, so I'll fix it.
I need a spade.
Do you want to spit first?
Mm-hmm. Pour for me.
I need exercise
with a new recipe.
Do not waste your time.
You should have marinate longer.
Hope it did not come dry.
Did you know that Reprise Records
released this song in 1966?
It became a lynchpin.
Not for long. Final order only.
Now is ready. Hope to taste.
In vain stress.
Still.
Voilà. Bon appétit.
I was sorry, darling.
Muru, look good.
Raise your feet up.
Relax.
What day, huh?
What day.
Would you read to me?
Cheer up.
You hate that.
I do not want to.
Let's Dance.
Do you want to
dance or open your gift?
What a gift?
This.
What a glory?
It is said...
that is our wedding day.
Is it?
No but...
is said to be.
Is that okay?
Happy Anniversary.
Radiator.
CONNECT THE RADIATOR
Thank you.
Gold, now you can
go wherever you want.
Where do you want first?
I'm so happy with you.
No need to say that.
VOICE MESSAGE
We got a lead on excavation.
Come here.
Carbon value 14.6 GPH.
The box is from the
army to Sapper Morton.
It has been
creatively used as an urge.
Only bones and hair.
The samples show that the
woman had been buried for 30 years.
The skeleton has been dismantled, the bones are
cleansed and the entire care is carefully buried.
Woman?
The cause of death, Coco?
No fractures, no injuries except...
Innominate.
The baby got stuck in
the narrow breeding channel.
Was she pregnant?
Mm-hmm.
So he was not killed?
She died for her childbirth.
What is that?
Back.
Getting closer.
Yet.
That.
Duh.
Tracks in the
bowel of the bowel.
A thin knife, like a scalpel.
Looks like an emergency section.
The cuts are clean,
not defense damage.
He was a doctor.
Maybe saving was a business.
He did not look like a rescue guy.
He saw the trouble
of burying a woman.
Sensitive skirt.
Sorry.
Where is the child?
Did you look at the whole area?
Only land and
worms, no other corpses.
Maybe he was hungry.
Out.
He was a replicant.
Pregnant.
The world is on a wall that
separates half of each other.
Without the wall begins war.
Or slaughter.
So what you saw,
did not happen.
Yes ma'am.
My job is to maintain order.
We maintain order.
Delete this?
Delete all.
Baby?
- I tracked it.
Was there anything else?
I have not deleted the birth.
So what?
The born ones have a soul.
Do you refuse?
I did not know I could, ma'am.
There you go.
Hey.
You did it without me.
Without what, ma'am.
The soul.
And the new
designs clean the shit out.
Because you have
not seen a miracle.
Wallace Headquarters
I'm checking
the old serial number.
DNA verification?
Hair.
Oops.
Old.
Parent older.
It will be difficult.
And so little is left,
what is left is...
clumped.
Customize your mind.
As human as you want.
But since it is a drilling site,
I would not waste your money
on intelligence, affection or charm.
Gun models are a matter of fact.
Will we go on later.
Everyone remembers
where they were at the break.
Just before the time.
I was at home with my parents.
And then ten days of darkness.
The machines went to the place.
When the lights came on,
the memories were empty.
Images, files that bit out.
We did not send bank squares.
It feels so good that there is only paper.
Everything was on
record, just about everything.
Mom still cries after baby pictures.
It's a pity it is.
Lose sweet pictures.
Time from shards, not much.
Last models before the ban.
Tyrell's standard set.
And?
Ordinary.
- Ordinary?
There may be more.
The old serial
number returns home.
30 year old thing managed.
Thank you, Constable.
I'm Mr. Wallace's representative Luv.
She gave me the name.
Really.
I represent Wallace. This way.
The old models spoiled
the company's reputation.
What a gift Mr. Wallace to the world.
He rescued the foreign lands
when he bought Tyrell.
Beware of technology.
And that is not
what we have yet.
You are also a customer.
Are you satisfied?
Very realistic. Thank you.
The trash are preserved here.
For your luck, Mr Wallace
is a computer program.
No one has ever been here.
I apologize.
All our memories of that time
were destroyed in a break.
But there are snippets.
Your son collects butterflies.
He'll show you his collection
as well as the slaughter.
- I took the doctor.
... with your wasp hand.
I would kill him.
You can find a nudity picture
of a girl's full page in a magazine.
Is this a replicating or
lesbian test, Mr Deckard?
Please reply only.
He was not sure about him.
Or someone was not there.
It was difficult to identify us then.
Is anything special about her?
You started a formal investigation.
Old serial numbers
are aroused by feelings.
Everyone sleeps better
when they are aware of them.
The woman likes her.
Who?
This is Constable Deckard.
He is trying to irritate.
Personal questions stimulate.
Get to know...
do not want to.
Do you keep your job, constable?
I thank Mr Wallace for your time.
You knew Constable Deckard.
What can you tell him about?
Lonely wolf.
Like me.
Together, we were acting alone.
That's it.
Can you tell me anything else?
She was not meant to be here.
Why not?
Something in his eyes.
Could he contact him?
No.
She is  retired .
Retired.
What happened?
I guess I want it.
Be alone.
Welcome back, Mr Wallace.
Are you looking for a
new model to be delivered?
An angel should not come
to the Kingdom of Heaven
without a gift.
Can you even say "Child is born"?
New model...
We'll see.
First
feared
from the clay front.
Think.
Before we even
know who we are,
we are afraid to lose it.
Happy Birthday.
Let's see you now.
We make angels
for humanity.
There were bad
angels, but I do good.
And I took us
to nine new worlds.
The nine...
The child can count
nine with their fingers.
The stars should be ours!
Yes, Mr Wallace.
Humanity has come up
with a sacrificial labor force.
There is no return to Orjs,
except for biotechnology.
But production has its limits.
Karu pasture.
Empty and dry.
This here.
Emptiness on the road to the stars.
Does this have to
change for heaven's sake?
They do not add,
no matter how I tried.
We need more than we can do.
Millions and millions of millions.
Let's get Green back.
Tyrell's last trick.
Increase.
Lost perfection.
But the child is born.
Bring it to me.
Okay, Mr Wallace.
Best angel.
Are not you, Luv?
The green-eyed
man who killed Sapper.
Find out what he knows.
Hey.
Come on, hi, android boy.
Are you alone?
The guy is Blade Runner.
Let it be.
Let's go, it's fucking dangerous.
- No worries.
No worries.
Do you buy me a cigarette?
You will not even smile.
Did not you listen to your friends?
Do not you know what I am?
I know.
Rice eating rape.
What is that?
Wood.
Oh.
I have not seen the wood.
It's pretty.
It's dead.
Who holds dead wood?
You do not mind me?
I can kill. What model do you have?
Take your eye.
The right girls
are not interested.
Well, you can find me here.
Hey.
You can not take them.
I understand. I have papers.
Keep this.
Yes, here.
Coco is dead.
Bones are gone.
The information has already
leaked out. How long did it go?
What you have?
And do not say "nothing".
I found that.
Sock?
Where was it found?
- From Sapper's farm.
Anything else?
I burned everything else.
What is this date?
Birth or Death Day?
I do not know yet.
Does not anyone else
see where this leads to?
This is breaking the world, K.
I have known many like you.
Useful but...
for you I forget sometimes.
You were not
there when I was a kid.
Do you remember anything?
Before you came to the house.
I have memories, but...
They are not real, but transitions.
Tell one of your childhood.
It feels a little strange to tell
about the childhood I did not live.
Will I help if I tell you?
I remember a toy, a puppy.
Engraving.
I just remember that the boy
was trying to take it away from me.
I ran away.
I'm looking for a hideout,
and it's just a dark oven.
It's really dark and scary, but...
the horse is all out, so I go in.
They will find and try to hack
me to tell, but I will not tell you.
That's it.
Little K defends his own.
Good memory.
Look here.
We are all looking
for something right.
What happens if I
run the whole bottle?
Should I go back to work, ma'am?
Report DNA Search Results.
Constable KD6-3.7.
Search.
6.10.21 generated DNA.
Discrepancies.
No data before pausing.
Satellite Crystal Copy?
Data can not be read.
Clear. Drive raw.
Man is just data.
A, C, T, and G.
Your alphabet has four characters.
I only have two.
One and zero.
Half less, but twice as
sleeker, sweetheart.
You did not want to fuck?
You listened.
Perhaps.
You're not enough
to tell the truth.
6, 10 and 21.
There is nothing to tell.
How many times
have you told me?
Your memories.
Engraved date.
6, 10 and 21.
Coincidence?
A dangerous coincidence.
I always knew you were special.
Maybe this is the specialty.
Child.
Born of a woman.
Entered into the world.
Desired.
Much loved.
Even if it is true,
someone I would
always hunt for me.
Dreams do not hurt.
Is it?
It hurts us.
Stop.
4847 and 2181 side by side.
Identical.
Turn.
Boy and girl.
Out.
Why?
They can not have identical DNA.
The second is a copy.
Both were in the Morrill Cole corpus.
The girl died there.
Genetic Error.
Galatalaissyndrooma.
Son...
disappeared.
Where is the orphanage?
Want to ride?
THE METROPOLIAL ARE ENDED
Waste management in Los
Angeles County of San Diego
Well, we are here.
Belt closed.
K?
Stay away.
Fire. Fire.
Fire.
60 meters to the east.
North.
Fire.
Stop. 20 degrees east.
Stop.
Getting closer.
Yet.
Oh you.
Get up.
Do your job.
Find a child.
Watch the car.
Every part, or out of the rain!
Came into the beam!
You work.
If you do not, I do not need you.
I do not need any...
Hey.
Nickel is for colonies.
Closer from here can
not get a great outdoors.
The game keeps them active...
and makes them handy.
But work it is.
The job makes it unnecessary.
Well.
What are you looking for?
Because I have all kinds.
No no no...
- I do not buy.
I am an honest player.
Listen...
You even bigger...
Even bigger players
tried to stop me...
and they were...
hard players.
I'm looking for a boy for 30 years.
I need your accounting.
Investments, sales, all.
So the old ones
are not in the books.
Is not it?
- No, no.
Sorry. I can not help.
Are not you?
- No.
Yes you can.
You have a good memory.
Tell me what to remember,
or shoot the hole and look at myself.
They laughed at you...
Are you coming?
Where is it?
Oh God.
Where, where, where?
I can not find it.
It's gone.
The whole year is torn.
I did not do it.
It was not me.
I do not...
I did not.
I always said
that you are special.
Born, not made.
Hidden with care.
Right boy.
The real boy needs the right name.
Joe.
"Joe"?
You are too important for K.
Your mother would have named you.
Joe.
Do not.
How do I know if
memory is a move or not?
Who does the memories do?
Dr. Ana Stelline?
Guest.
Is that okay?
Suitable for.
Unusual only.
Fun to meet, Constable KD6-3.7.
Sorry.
Immune Deficiency.
Freedom behind the glass.
Why did not you stay here?
So.
I would have gone with
my parents, but I got sick.
So...
my life changed.
They put me in my cup
filling it with what they
can to keep me happy
except with the club of course.
I was used to people.
How can I help?
I thought you
could help the story.
The most interesting offer at a time.
Do you think I'm
working at the same time?
Of course.
I promise to hear every word.
You are considered to be the
best memory in the country.
Kindness.
I love birthday parties.
Do you work for Wallace?
I am one of his subcontractors.
He made a bid, but I
stay an entrepreneur.
What Makes You So Good?
What makes your
memories so authentic?
Well, there is always
something in your work.
But I've been here
eight years old.
To see the world it
was supposed to imagine.
I came to see
you as an imaginator.
Wallace needs me to
be a functional product.
I'm doing it for kindness.
Replicants are hard.
For jobs that people would not do.
I can not change your destiny,
but my memory brings a smile.
Strongly done.
Kivemmin. They seem authentic.
And the real memories are...
genuine feelings.
Is not that right?
Are all made, or is it true?
Using the right memories
is illegal, constable.
How do they
differentiate between them?
Can you identify...
realistic?
It is believed that it is in detail.
But memory does
not work that way.
We remember our feelings.
It's a mess.
I can show you.
Sit down.
Think of the memory
you want to look like.
Just imagine.
Freely.
Someone says this.
This happened.
It is true.
Goddamn it!
Constable KD6-3.7, Mrs. calls.
Drop your gun and
keep your hands visible.
- Cells.
Have you ever
been in the facility?
Cells.
- Cells.
Are you locked in free?
Cells.
- Cells.
Together.
- Together.
How do you feel like
holding your beloved hand?
Together.
- Together.
Together with the cell.
- In one of the cellars.
Too bad.
- Too bad.
How does it feel
to be full of fear?
Evil.
- Too bad.
Do you like your life apart?
Contrast.
- Contrast.
With a bad contrast.
- It's a bad contrast.
Night.
- Night.
Together with the cell.
- In one of the cellars.
For the same.
- For the same.
And for the bad contrast.
- And the bad contrast.
Against the night.
- Against the night.
The fountain of the valley.
You are not near a parable.
Out! Door shut.
What the fuck did you get?
I gave you the job.
I emphasized the importance,
and you reel at
the refreshment center.
According to the control,
you have something else.
Far from the benchmark.
Do you know what it means?
I found the child.
He had been made a
standard mate of basic service.
She did not know who she was.
Yeah?
- It's done.
Meaning?
- What did you ask.
It's done.
You just got a bomb.
Good job.
I'm gonna drive you
from the station alive.
But you have 48 hours to find out.
Release your gun and your badge.
In the next control I can not help.
Thank you, ma'am.
You were right.
You were right in everything.
I thought I did not
care about the artist.
I noticed you liked him.
I want this.
She is true.
I want to be right for you.
You're right for me.
You have a good woman.
Well, do it.
Look at the girl.
Hush now. He
needs to be synchronized.
Oh, whatever you want.
Oh, wherever you want.
99.9% sterile water.
It's from wood.
That was it.
You can leave.
Hush now.
I have been inside of you.
There's not much left there.
Coffee?
They'll come soon.
I'll come with you.
But I did not.
They can come from
here for all my memories.
You have to remove
me from the terminal.
My gift.
Put me there.
I can not do it.
Consider.
If something happens
to that, that's it.
You are gone.
So.
Like a real girl.
Please.
Joe, please.
I want it.
I can not do it myself.
Replace the antenna.
The right tree.
You're rich, buddy.
I can get you the right horse.
Do you want the right horse?
I do not need.
Really. Like Wallace.
I do not need
the right horse, just...
Just what it is.
Smells from the old land.
But it's newer.
The reactor radiation?
No, more unstable.
Old, old.
Or a dirty bomb.
Only one place has had
so high radioactivity.
Only one place is so dirty.
No one is living there.
You wanted to know
where the puppet was.
I told you what,
what do you want now?
Horses, goats, papers
to the outside world?
Whatever you want, Dr. Badger gets.
Five.
Four, 30 degrees left.
Tilt up.
Get up to 120 meters.
Radiation Analysis.
RADIOACTIVITY: LOW
Ahead.
Tilt up.
Stop.
Ahead.
Five.
Seven, forward.
Six.
Stop.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Thermal Analysis.
Life.
What is it?
Obviously.
Too dark.
I like him.
Good boy.
Where is he?
I have no idea.
She is free.
Find out.
I'm looking for.
Where would a good boy go?
You are late.
It is not.
He destroyed it.
Everything about him.
Except the box you already made.
But that was not
enough when you came.
Little creature.
In front of the new and
mighty one you can not kill.
The big change is scared.
The tsunami is not
stopped by the broom.
Except that I stopped.
Where is he?!
You are so sure.
Because she told me.
Because we're not lying.
I tell Mr Wallace that
you were trying to shoot.
I had to kill.
Do what you do.
Mrs.
Constable KD6-3.7 location?
Detective KD6-3.7
detained from duty
"Do not you think it's a bit
of cheese in your pockets?"
No, son?
Treasure Island?
He reads.
Good.
I also read.
Anything else to do
here is no longer right.
"Monica night I
dreamed of the cheese."
"Cooked mostly."
What are you doing here?
I heard the piano.
Do not lie.
It's ugly.
You're a cop.
I did not come
to take you away.
Really?
So what?
I just have questions.
What are the questions?
Place.
Listen, I do not want to hurt you.
But you make it difficult.
[Elvis Presley: Can not Help Falling in Love]
I like this song.
We can continue or take swords.
Take the swords.
This is just something.
The whole city was.
In due course.
Forget your sorrow.
Go to the show.
Play a bit.
Win a little, lose a little.
And money was like candy.
Do you drink whiskey?
I have millions of bottles of whiskey.
Here.
You bleed.
Is the dog correct?
I do not know.
Ask about it.
Do you have a name?
Constable KD6-3.7.
It's not the name
but the serial number.
Alright.
Joe.
What do you want, Joe?
Ask questions.
Like what?
What was his name?
Your mother's mother.
What was he like?
Were you here together?
Too many questions.
I was you and good at it.
Easier times.
Why are you
making them difficult?
Why not answer the question?
Which question?
I did not believe
you would grind shit.
What was his name?
Rachael.
His name was Rachael.
What happened to the baby?
Did you send him orphanage?
I had left the times then.
You did not even meet your child?
Why do not you?
I remain in the plan.
I showed you how to mess
up information, covering traces.
My role was to leave.
The crash covered
the trails forever.
I would not have found her.
Did you want to?
Not really.
Why do not you?
We were hunted.
I did not want our
children to be found.
Cut to pieces.
Sometimes about love
must be a stranger.
The stranger.
What did you do?
Who did you bring?
No one.
Really?
Item locked.
You are known.
I came alone.
Poor dog.
Do not!
I really hope you're happy.
I love you--
Hey.
Someone wants to meet you.
You can count on us.
You want me to look up to the left.
This is Frey.
He was with Kalashniki in Saphir.
I recognize you.
Did you help hide the child?
I was there.
I saw a miracle birth.
The full faces weeped me.
Smell like a thunder.
Were you with her?
Rachael.
He died in my arms.
We hid the baby
and we vowed
to keep our secrets.
That's why Sapper killed himself.
The child made us
more than slaves.
If a child can become of us,
we are our own cronies.
"More humane than humans".
It is the time of the revolution.
We build an army.
I want to release us.
If you want to be free, join us.
Deckard, Sapper, you, me.
Our lives do not mean anything
near the approaching storm.
Death for the right thing is the
most human thing we can do.
You led to Wallace Deckard.
You can not let Deckard
guide Wallace to me.
You have to kill Deckard.
Deckard just wanted
his baby to be safe.
The child is safe.
When time comes, I'll
show the girl to the world.
He will lead our army.
A girl?
Of course.
Rachael got a daughter.
That's how he
comes with my own eyes.
I got him blue when
the departure came.
You hid the boy.
Only a piece of puzzle piece.
Did you think it was you?
You thought.
We all liked it as well.
That's why we believe.
Someone says this.
I showed you how to mess
up information, covering traces.
That's how he
comes with my own eyes.
I got him blue when
the departure came.
There is always
something in your job.
That jumps always.
Without thinking of what
you would do on the ground.
Courage can not
change the truth.
I've been wanting
to meet you for so long.
You are a miracle
to me, Mr Deckard.
I had a lock.
I found the key.
But the pins are not in line
and the door stays locked.
I need a sample piece, Mr Deckard.
That child.
I need her baby.
I'm teaching everything to fly.
"God remembered Rachel,
he heard her
and opened her womb. "
Do you hold our owls?
Is it artificial?
Of course it is.
It's probably expensive.
Very.
I'm Rachael.
Deckard.
Is the feeling the same
now than then
when did you meet?
All these years of the
perfection of the memory drilled.
How shiny his lips.
Your immediate contact.
Did you mind that
you were just called?
Planned to fall in love right then.
Make a perfect model.
So if planned.
Love
or mathematical punctuality.
Which
or the camp?
I know what's true.
It was a shame
to keep yourself out.
And it did not
pay like anything.
But you can still help.
You got help hiding.
Where did they go?
I know you know something.
Help me...
and good things can happen.
You have no children.
Is it?
Millions.
Do you think I
can only offer pain?
But I know.
You love the pain.
It reminds you of your happiness.
More luck then.
Do not be afraid.
Angel.
Re-created.
To you.
Did you miss me?
Do not you love me?
His eyes were green.
In the outside world
let me talk to you.
You do not feel the pain yet.
But you learn.
Hello handsome.
What day, huh?
Orpo expression.
I can fix it.
You look good at the river.
JOI - ALL YOU WANT
TO BE BEING AND VIEW
Death for the right thing is the
most human thing we can do.
Because you have
not seen a miracle.
Get to the airspace of
Los Angeles Airport.
Tunnistautukaa.
Transportation S-14-4-XD.
Where are we going?
Home.
Engine 2 inoperative.
The spare motor is connected.
Warning.
Does it work?
- Too low!
Get back!
Up.
Open the door.
I am the best.
The outside world is waiting.
Joe.
Joe!
You would have let me die.
Annoinkin.
You fucked.
You can meet your daughter now.
The best memories are her.
Why?
Who am I to you?
Meet your daughter.
Are you okay?
Just a moment.
Is not it beautiful?
DO NOT COPY in any format!