Check out
the yo-yo.
What a dork.
There's the
yo-yo kid.
Oh, my gosh.
I can't believe he brought it to school.
Will!
How's it
goin'?
Great, chuckie.
Positively great.
Really? Isn't today
report card day?
Yep. And once again,
i'll show you
that the will browning
method of sliding by
just can't be beat.
Such confidence. I love it.
Watch and learn, chuckie.
Watch and learn.
Oh, hi, will.
Is this your locker?
Maybe. Why?
Well, i moved my
locker here.
I wanted to change
my lousy spot.
So, will, i was just
wondering--
i mean,
with the junior social just around the corner--
sorry, heather. I don't
know how to dance.
I gotta go. We'll talk
sometime, though.
Do lunch.
Really? When?
Uh, sometime.
Do lunch? Who are
you, tom cruise?
It's an expression. It means,
maybe next millennium.
And as i give you
your report cards,
i think this is a good
time to remind you
that your science projects
are due in three weeks.
I got it covered.
For some of you
the project is very,
very, very important.
Because if you don't get
at least a "b,"
i'll be seeing you again
in this class next year.
That bad?
Nah. It's no biggie.
Watch it, browning.
Scottie desota.
Man, does he
hate you!
I get the guy in
trouble once
and he holds a
grudge forever.
Trouble? You got
him suspended.
There's a
difference.
Let's get out of here.
I better get home and work
on my science project.
Whatever it is,
throw it away
and do a real
one, will.
You gotta nail it.
Come on. Who needs
an "a," anyway?
Uh, you do.
Voila!
Does it have
a name?
Oh, it's oat bran with
some varietal tree bark.
It promotes healing, peace,
and togetherness.
Honey, we have
no plates.
No, no. We don't
need plates.
This is a common pot.
We all eat from it.
It's a family
bonding thing.
Yeah, right.
Maybe with some glue,
you could bond
me and goofball.
Allana.
So, where are we going on
our next family vacation?
I love it when we
travel together.
Anyone want to see
my report card?
I can hardly
wait.
Um, allana, this
is terrific.
I guess it runs
in the family.
Right, will?
Allana.
There must be
some mistake.
A "d" is science. An "f"
in social studies?
Social studies, will?
You can get at least a
"c" in social studies
if you answer every
question "washington."
And the same comments over and over again.
"Doesn't apply himself."
"Not enough effort."
"Not trying."
I try. You know i try.
But, will, if
you're trying,
why do all your teachers say you aren't?
You leave us no choice--
we have to go to plan "b."
Plan "b"?
I'm not gonna like
plan "b," am i?
Camp sparticus.
Yes!
No! Please!
Anything but that!
It's a prison camp!
It's a highly respected
summer boot camp for boys.
It's not a punishment.
A summer at camp sparticus will
teach you discipline and responsibility.
It'll teach you to
push yourself.
It'll turn me into a mindless,
uniform-wearing machine.
Cool.
No more discussion, will.
Unless we see a significant
improvement in your grades,
you'll be spending the
summer at camp sparticus.
It's up to you.
Sparticus, the camp of
misery and despair?
What am i gonna do?
How 'bout school work?
Maybe start with your
science project.
I mean, apply yourself
for a change.
Who are you,
my annoying third parent?
No, just a guy who doesn't
want to spend his summer
without his best friend.
[Knocking]
i gotta go. Bye.
Mom, do you think camp sparticus will still let me in
if i can somehow make one leg shorter than the other?
It's a pretty
clever idea.
Maybe you should use
some of that brain power
on your school
work, huh?
Whatta ya think?
Sorry, mom. Allana
gets "a"s, not me.
Sweetheart, i don't
care about "a"s.
I care about effort.
And so does your dad.
He cares very much.
Just try, will.
That's all we ask.
Don't hold back so much.
You are a wonderful,
smart, talented guy.
Let people know about it.
That's all i wanted to say.
Goodnight, sweetheart.
"Grow your own fun!"
Hello, science project.
"Ocean pups"
one becomes two, victor.
Hypercloning.
The greatest advance in
science in 100 years.
We're gonna be filthy rich.
Conrad, how many times
do i have to tell you?
It's not about the money.
It's about everything
we can buy with it.
That's right.
Soon we'll be out of
this miserable place.
We won't have to use
this company as a front
to hide our research anymore.
We're gonna work in a
hi-tech laboratory.
With real white lab coats.
And lab assistants.
With name tags.
Grape juice?
Hmmm.
Yes!
"Science has never
been this much fun."
"These pets are sure to amaze."
I'm ready to be amazed.
"The water temperature
must be more than 68
but less than 75 degrees."
Perfect. 72 degrees.
Next, the eggs...
don't let me down, boys.
My summer rests on
your little legs.
Or whatever you got.
Weird-looking things.
Where's the stirrer?
Guess a little of my
hair won't hurt.
Now what?
"You should see some results
within the next 48-72 hours"?
Two days?
Or less.
Customer service.
I need customer service.
[Ringing]
ocean pup. "You provide the
water, we provide the fun."
Yeah, hi. My name's
william browning
and i just used a
kit i ordered--
was it satisfactory?
I don't know.
I mean i got flashing
lights and water spouts--
lights and spouts?
Ok, mr. Browning, let
me get my handbook.
[Both screaming]
aaah!
Mr. Browning, there's
nothing in the handbook
relating to your
particular problem.
What?!
Well, i've done an
exhaustive search
through all of our databases.
I also checked the indexes of
earlier manuals for our kit--
what?!
I even consulted our
research department
and they confirmed
that the handbook
doesn't say anything
about lights and spouts.
Don't!
No, it don't.
Maybe you could describe
your problem again.
No. Put it down.
No?
No!
Sir, are you there?
Yep. I'm here.
Sir, hello?
Gotta go. Love
your kit. Bye.
We gotta talk.
For starters...
put that on.
No. Not like that.
Like... that.
You look just like me.
Me?
You speak?
Speak?
This is too weird.
What's going on?
I mean, where'd
you come from?
Miss pinkerson talked about
something like this in science class.
"Cloning: the creation by laboratory
technique of an organism
that is an identical
copy of its parent."
Holy "a" in science class!
I made myself a clone!
The greatest science
project ever!
"The science of cloning is
still in its infancy."
You can read?
Intense.
My parents are home.
All right, listen up.
In a few minutes i'm gonna
have to go downstairs
and scarf some dinner.
Scarf?
Eat. Consume.
It's all in there.
Read about it.
And stay here.
Put on some clothes.
Keep quiet.
And keep quiet. Shhh.
It was a strange
phone call.
I mean, the kid, he
sounded so strange.
I thought it was worth
saying something.
I don't know what you guys
are doing in there, anyway.
I told you we should've
gotten rid of these animals!
Game over, pal. That's it.
Our secret's out.
Poof. Gone.
Gone to some kid named...
will browning.
The kid just got a
weird reaction.
It doesn't mean anything.
What if he accidentally
clones something?
His dog or his cat?
We don't have
patents, remember?
"We don't need them
yet," you said.
"No one will ever find out about
hypercloning," you said.
Feel better?
Much better.
Sorry about that.
So what's our
next move?
We're taking a
road trip.
Well, will,
what's the science project you've been working on?
I'd rather not say.
I don't want to
jinx it.
Ha. Ding, ding, ding.
That means, for our home
viewing audience,
that will isn't working
on any project at all.
I happen to be working
very hard on one.
Done!
Done.
We have a winner
and a new champion.
And here are your prizes.
A brand new refrigerator,
a brand new freezer--
yeah, cranking it
up on the dark side
is the new shawn peak kicker,
with his latest fabled addition
to his multi,
multi-platinum catalog.
Now stay in there,
little bigbees.
Bigbee.
We've got lots more
hits coming your way.
[Both screaming]
what? What's wrong?
Uh, nothing. I'm fine.
Will, you screamed.
Screaming implies
something bad.
No, i just screamed.
A little.
May i be excused?
Before dessert? I made
rutabaga popsicles.
Tempting, but can i go?
Hello?
Where are you?
What are you doing
down there?
Who's that?
That?
It's just a mask.
It's not real. See?
Oooooh. Grrrrr.
It's fake.
Just pretend.
For halloween.
It scared me.
I screamed.
Whoa. Talk about scary.
The underwear goes
in the inside.
And you gotta kill
the tie.
Kill it?
Take it off. Lose it.
You know, i screamed too.
At dinner.
Well, why did you scream?
You know how twins
can supposedly
communicate psychically
or something?
No.
Yeah, well...
never mind.
What were you doing in
the closet, anyway?
I told you to look
at the book.
I finished that book.
You read the whole thing?
No way.
Yes way.
The chapter on the classification of matter-- intense.
All right, tell me
about azurite.
Azurite. A blue mineral with
the formula cu3 (oh) 2 (c03) 2.
It is often associated with
the green mineral malachite,
since they've both been used as
pigments and as gemstones.
You're a genus!
Now what?
I need to scarf.
Oh, right. I mean,
you must be hungry,
being new to the
planet, and all.
I'll get you some food.
It'll only take a second.
So stay right here.
Will?
What do you
call this?
It's a picture
of my family.
And my family?
No. My family.
Although, if you
want 'em...
now get back in my room.
I've got to keep you hidden until i
know what i'm gonna do with you.
Allana: you better not be in the bathroom.
My sister! Come on.
And stop talking to
yourself, dip boy.
You're not that
interesting.
Shhh. Quiet.
C'mon, c'mon.
Stay close. Follow me.
Honey, this calculator's
dying on me.
Batteries are in the utility room.
Right hand door.
Get over there.
Pssst. C'mon.
Find 'em?
Found them.
Oh, no.
Oh. Hi, will.
How's it goin'?
Fine.
Aah!
Weren't you just...
why are you...
didn't you...
weren't you just wearing--
no, no. I'm just...
honey, could you just...
open the fridge door?
Please?
Where are you going?
To the kitchen.
Why?
To get a snack.
You just ate dinner.
I'm hungry.
Snacks are
bad for you.
Are you kidding?
With your mother's
cooking,
snacks are what
keep me alive.
Right.
Excuse me.
Ooh.
Of course
you can.
I'll just reheat it.
What are you
trying to do?
Just stay with me.
Wait a second. Weren't...
what's your mother putting in this food, anyway?
Upstairs. My room. Go.
Oh, cholesterol.
Sweetheart...
hi, honey.
Will?
Honey, what are you
doing down there?
I... dropped a...
thing.
I'll be leaving now.
Just, uh, eating some...
yummy leftovers.
Yummy.
It's even
better cold.
Sucking up to mom to
save your life
when your grades tank?
I know what you're up to.
Allana, you can't begin to
fathom what i'm up to.
Hmmm.
Enjoy that, huh?
Uh-huh.
I guess it takes
all kinds.
[Burps]
i'm losing air.
That was a burp.
A belch. Perfectly normal.
You've got no leaks.
Watch...
[burps]
see?
Anything you want to know about
bodily functions, just ask.
[Yawns]
what was that?
A yawn. It means you're tired.
All that running around
must've gotten to you.
You've had a big day.
Was it a big day
for you too?
The biggest day of
my life, so far.
Even bigger than when i
got my tonsils removed.
The tonsils play no part in the human body.
They and the spleen
are the only organs
that can be removed
with no concern.
That's what your book said.
It's so amazing.
You look like me,
you talk like me,
but you have a
computer brain.
It's your brain too.
It's gotta be.
I'm your clone.
Hey, whatta i call you?
The other me?
Will two?
Twoie?
Twoie.
William?
[Knocking]
honey, are you
asleep already?
I love you, sweetheart.
Goodnight.
She thought you were me.
I am such a genius.
Get some sleep, my friend.
'Cause come monday,
you're not going to school
as my science project,
you're going to
school as me.
[Sighs]
oh!
Don't tell me we're
actually here.
You and your
computer maps.
I'm not in the mood.
So let's just
raid the place
and figure out what
the kid cloned.
[Blows horn]
two words-- breaking
and entering.
They're bad when you
use them together.
First, we observe.
Observe?
We drove halfway across
the country to observe?
Observe what?
We look for two of anything.
Two poodles, two house cats,
two hamsters...
where are we going now?
To load up on coffee
and poorly prepared
fast food.
We are on a stakeout.
A family of grizzly bears has
chosen this spot to test the fishing.
The family unit is essential
to the survival of the cubs,
who are just beginning to
explore the world around them.
Somebody say amen.
Amen!
Amen! Amen!
Did i hear you
shout "amen"?
Maybe.
Well, we're waiting for you,
so hurry up.
All right, now listen up.
I've gotta go visit grandpa
mordechai in the nursing home.
He's your family?
Yep. Old, old,
old family.
Family is good.
The family unit is essential to
the survival of the cubs.
The family units are what
send you to boot camp.
I'll be back in
a few hours.
Just watch tv.
Family.
Like the grizzly bear,
i must explore the
world around me.
Hi, dad.
Hey, mordechai. How
ya doin' today?
We brought the kids
along, mordechai.
Hi, grandpa.
Hi, gramps.
He's in his
zone again.
Twoie?
Ok, think. Where
could he be?
Hey, can i play? Can i play?
Grass...
picnics.
The park!
All right, go get it.
Nice catch!
All right, bring
it here, boy.
Hey, can i play?
Mom!
Twoie.
Twoie!
Hi. Isn't this
place great?
I told you not to
leave the house.
You said,
"watch tv."
I did that.
You gotta start
using your head!
I couldn't find you.
How did you know
i was here?
It just came to me.
Like when you were
scared and i screamed.
Same thing.
Do i have a family?
No, i have a family.
You... you're just a clone.
Let's get outta here.
Stay a block behind me,
then wait in the garage
till i get you.
I've got to start teaching you
the fine art of being me.
Now, show me the walk.
Ok.
Let's see some
attitude this time.
How was that?
Up... down...
yooo! Ow.
Ray corning. He's
in math class.
He smells like
cabbage.
Next, scottie desota.
We got him suspended.
We don't like him.
Very good.
You'll be ok.
All right, high five.
Oops.
Sorry.
My fault.
No, no, no. You don't
just walk up to girls
and say, hey, baby.
But the man on
television did.
That was an old movie.
Didn't you notice it was
in black and white?
You mean new york city
doesn't look like that?
Sometimes you
sound so smart,
i'm afraid you're gonna make
me look like a geek.
And sometimes...
i'm sorry, will.
I'm really trying.
My sister!
Twoie!
Uuh!
What are you trying to do,
give me a heart attack?
What's your malfunction, toad?
Dark.
What?
You are multi, multi, all
the way to the peak kicker.
You are one crankin'
little bigbee.
All the way to the
fabled addition.
Oh, i just hope i'm around
when you do that in public.
How did a clone like you
know stuff like that?
A thing called a
music video.
Yeah, well, you've got to learn
to keep that stuff to yourself.
I mean, she laughed at you.
That was the worst.
Why is that the worst?
Why?
Well... because it
is. Trust me.
Now we've still got a
lot of work ahead of us.
Who's this next to me?
Chuckie. He's my
best friend.
Who's this on
the other side?
Heather johnson.
She's got a righteous crush on me.
Perfect. Now, my mom's
in the kitchen.
Cruise through.
Say, gotta go.
Give my mom a kiss,
go out the door.
Gotta go, kiss, out
the door. Got it?
Got it.
Hang it over one
shoulder.
Will, honey, i made sprout
muffins for breakfast.
Gotta go. Kiss.
Out the door.
What did you say?
Gotta go. Kiss.
Out the door.
He's gotta be from a
different gene pool.
Will! Hey, buddy.
Chuckie?
I mean, chuckie.
Hey, what happened
to you this weekend?
I called a few times but
you never called back.
What were you, busy?
Yeah, busy.
And now i feel like something's crawling in my stomach.
Did you eat
something bad?
No, i just feel strange.
Nervous, excited.
You sure you're ok?
Sure, peak kicker
to the max.
Ok, then.
So far, so good.
This place looks great.
Why do i hate it
so much?
Maybe because you're constantly on
the verge of failing every subject.
This is gonna be cool.
♪ I'm trying to dance with
my feet on the floor ♪
♪ seems a little like i've
never done that before ♪
♪ this smile, it
just won't quit ♪
♪ today's my day ♪
♪ and i'm taking it ♪
♪ feels like i'm walking
on the moon ♪
♪ or floating high in
a big balloon ♪
♪ everything feels like new ♪
♪ there's a jump in my step ♪
♪ i've got nothing to lose ♪
♪ everything feels
like new today ♪
♪ and i like it like that ♪
will, man, what
are you doing?
Done!
♪ So much fun seeing
through these eyes ♪
♪ the world can hand
me anything ♪
♪ i'll try it on for size ♪
♪ got the sun, got my friends ♪
♪ hope this day never ends ♪
♪ it's crazy but you
know that it's true ♪
♪ yeah, yeah ♪
♪ everything feels like new ♪
♪ there's a jump in my step ♪
♪ i've got nothing to lose ♪
♪ everything feels
like new today ♪
♪ and i like it like that ♪♪
pizza, right?
Um, yes, will.
Dough baked at high
temperatures,
tomato sauce and cheese.
Sometimes they're
topped with meat,
like pepperoni
and sausage.
Ok, that's it. Look,
we gotta talk.
You've been acting
strange all day.
If you're trying to
pull somethin',
you know, like to get
your grades changed
on account of
being crazy,
let me know so i
can back you up.
But if not, i'd appreciate it if
you'd tell me what's going on.
You're angry.
Are we still friends?
What?
Yeah, of course,
but friends have to be
able to tell each other
when one is making a really
big bonehead of himself.
So i guess we're
good friends.
I guess so.
Yeah, we are.
This is delicious!
It's only a frozen pizza.
No. I mean, i've never
tasted anything
so unbelievably delicious!
Frozen pizza rocks!
Uh, will...
all right.
♪ Bringin' da noise ♪
♪ bring down the house ♪
♪ we came here to turn
the party out ♪
♪ say come on, come on ♪
♪ let's raise the roof
and give 'em proof ♪
♪ that we can get loose, y'all ♪
♪ bringin' da noise ♪
♪ bring down the house ♪
♪ we came here to turn
the party out ♪
♪ say come on, come on ♪
♪ let's raise the roof
and give 'em proof ♪
♪ that we can get loose, y'all ♪
♪ we need to get down ♪
♪ the scene is set so right ♪
♪ everybody's in the
house tonight ♪
♪ lose your mind ♪
♪ let your body take control ♪
♪ you've got to feel
it in your soul ♪
♪ i've got that feelin', baby ♪
♪ you know it drives me crazy ♪
♪ and all i want to do
is hit the floor ♪
♪ i wanna shout it, y'all ♪
♪ so make it louder, y'all ♪
♪ and turn it up some more ♪
♪ bringin' da noise ♪
♪ bring down the house ♪
♪ we came here to turn
the party out ♪
♪ say come on, come on ♪
♪ let's raise the roof
and give 'em proof ♪
♪ that we can get loose, y'all ♪
isn't that
your brother?
It can't be.
♪ Say come on, come on ♪
♪ let's raise the roof
and give 'em proof ♪
♪ that we can get loose, y'all ♪
something is going
on with him.
He's actually
acting cool.
♪ Bringin' da noise ♪
♪ just shake it, girl ♪
♪ and enjoy the ride ♪
♪ do what you feel inside ♪
♪ 'cause it's your world ♪
♪ all you want and more ♪
you wanna come up?
♪ So, baby, go and get yours ♪
♪ i've got that feeling, baby ♪
♪ you know it drives me crazy ♪
i thought you said
you didn't dance.
I move to the groove.
How 'bout the social?
I don't suppose you'd like
to go with me, would you?
Will there be pizza there?
I'll bring some with me.
Ok.
Really?
Really. 'Cause i
love my pizza.
♪ Come on, come on,
let's raise the roof ♪
♪ and give 'em proof... ♪
i think i'm having an
out-of-body experience.
♪ We came here to turn
the party out ♪
♪ say come on, come on,
let's raise the roof-- ♪
you guys gotta try this.
Park it here, desota.
Well, look what
we got here.
Browning butt in the flesh.
Isn't that nice?
Is it? I'm not
really sure.
Someone said i was
in big trouble.
Not as big as the trouble
you're gonna be in
when i get you alone
one of these days.
You're still mad about me getting you suspended.
But it wasn't right of you to steal my lunch money.
What did you say?
Although i shouldn't have been
afraid to talk to you myself.
Rather than telling
a teacher.
I mean, there's nothing
to be afraid of, right?
Yeah. Right.
I'm sorry.
But i should've
been braver.
Dude, there's something
seriously wrong with you today.
So, what did you do
to get here?
I started a riot in
the lunch room.
That was you?
I bet your old man's gonna
go medieval on you, huh?
Old man?
I mean, like, your dad.
My dad?
Your father, stupid.
I mean, you do have a
father, right?
I don't really know what it means to have a father.
My dad left me and my
mom when i was two.
I don't really know what it
means to have a father, either.
You know what,
browning?
You're all right, man.
[Bell rings]
guess who's been
practicing.
So, how'd it go?
Tell me everything.
Oh, it was great.
I made lots of friends.
I love school. I want to
go again tomorrow.
My friend, you have
my permission
to go every day until
the end of the year.
What are you doin'?
Our homework.
Am i a genius or what?
[Phone rings]
hello.
Hi, will. It's heather.
Heather?
What are you planning
on wearing?
Wearing to what?
Wearing to the social, silly.
The social?
You know, next weekend.
Heather, i've gotta go
take care of something.
I'll call you back.
You invited her
to the social?!
No, she invited me.
Uugh! It doesn't mean
you have to say yes!
She's bringing pizza.
Six years spent avoiding
heather johnson
destroyed in one day.
[Doorbell rings]
stay here. Don't
talk to anyone.
If the phone rings,
don't answer it.
Stay!
[Both scream]
got something for
you, browning.
You left this at the
principal's office.
I did?
Yeah. Thought i'd
drop it off for you.
You did?
It was cool talking
to you today, man.
It was?
I'll catch you
tomorrow, browning.
You will?
What was with that weirdness
today at lunch, dough brain?
You have to teach me
that dance, ok?
Everybody's been asking
me where you learned it.
I'm kind of like a
celebrity sister.
Mike carmichael
even asked me out.
What is going on
around here?
Excuse me.
Are you william browning?
Who wants to know?
Uh, we're from the
ocean pups company.
And, uh, we're...
we're here...
here. Responding
to your call.
Responding to your call
of a few days ago.
That's right.
Oh, that's nice of you.
It was nothing, really.
Uh, well, we
understand that, uh,
that your kit-- you
experienced
some strange reaction.
Weird things going on?
No, it wasn't
that strange.
Look, we're here
to help you.
Yeah.
So just tell us
everything,
and help us
help you.
No, really.
Everything's fine.
The kit was lame. I
don't need your help,
but i'd take a refund.
Uh...
well, we'll get back
to you on that.
Yeah, we'll have
to do that.
I'm kinda busy helping my dad in the backyard.
Dad, i'll be right there!
Oh, no, that's fine.
We're sorry to have
bothered you, and bye.
Ok.
Do you think the kid's
telling the truth?
Think? I don't
need to think.
This device analyzes
voice patterns
and creates a detailed profile of
whatever subject i'm studying.
And according to this,
will browning is...
a nervous, four-foot-tall,
rabid chimpanzee.
Let's just get
outta here, ok?
Whatever it is he's
cloned in there,
after three weeks,
it'll be history.
The built-in lifespan
will end.
Hasta la vista. No
more hyperclone.
Our problems
will be solved.
No, no, no.
I'm not going anywhere
until i find out exactly
what he's cloned.
Now we're already committed
a tactical breech
by announcing our presence.
If we want to continue
with this stakeout,
we need to blend in
a little more.
We need... camouflage.
Will: check out
what's in that van!
Looks like the cia
just arrived.
What is all that?
Electronic stuff,
like for spying or something.
I've got a feeling
those guys
are into a lot more
than ocean pups.
Whatta ya mean?
I kind of used an
ocean pups kit,
but instead of getting
ocean pups, i got you.
You think they're
here for me?
Hey, relax.
We've just got to keep an eye on 'em,
that's all.
Can i still leave
the house?
Hey, we're talking about my grades here.
You still like
school, don't you?
Totally.
Good.
After you get my butt out of summer boot camp,
you can go back
under cover.
But now, the
main thing is,
you and i can never, ever,
ever be seen together by anyone.
Especially
those guys.
Deal?
Deal.
Will, awesome job
on this exam.
"A+"! We're so proud
of you, honey.
[Yawns]
whoa! Sorry.
Hey!
Ok.
I've read this one, already.
Like six times.
You're late.
Where were you?
Oh, chuckie and i went out for
pizza with scottie desota.
I brought you back a slice.
A slice of pizza?
I've been living like
a prisoner here,
and you bring me back
a slice of pizza?
I'm just doing what you
asked me to, will.
You did think this up.
Yeah, and if your
grades weren't so good
i'd un-think this
up right now.
I'm sorry you're
so upset.
I wish i had time
to talk about it.
What do you mean?
Oh, chuckie and i are
meeting heather
and some of the kids
down at the arcade.
Forget it. You're
staying here. I'm going.
I think i deserve to
have a little fun too.
Why?
Why? Why?
That's what you do
all day is have fun.
I'm the one that does all
the work around here.
Fine. Go.
Whatever.
Look, will,
i thought staying home all day,
eating junk food,
watching television,
and not going to school
was your dream.
It was my dream.
My dream stinks.
$200 for the ice
cream truck rental.
Fifty bucks for a
portable freezer.
We weren't doing so bad.
We would have broken even in a couple of months.
I didn't come here to
start a small business.
Not to mention the fact we
didn't get any spying done.
Conrad, when hypercloning hits it big,
we're gonna look back
at all this and laugh.
My island we buy
with all that money.
I want a little
ranch house,
a picket fence, fluffy
white pillows.
It's not
possible.
Which part?
Look, look, look, look.
Down on the driveway.
What's up, man?
Victor: the bedroom window.
One there, one there.
Two of them!
Two will brownings!
Both:
he's hypercloned himself!
A human hyperclone!
Conrad, do you know
what this means?
If we grab hold of that
specimen and run some tests,
we'll be able to
hyperclone humans.
This is the greatest
day of our lives!
Now all we have to do is figure out which will is will
and which will
is the clone.
Why don't we just
grab them both?
No. That's kidnapping.
Whereas, the last
time i checked,
there were no laws
against clonenapping.
So we wait until the
clone is alone.
Exactly.
We've still got three days.
You sure you want me
to do this?
Hey, if you can hang out with my friends at the arcade,
you can hang out with grandpa mordechai.
Besides, it's just for a couple of hours.
Just act more or less normal and you'll be fine.
Grandpa mordechai
is your family.
Today he's all yours.
You'll love him. He's a
load of laughs.
Is that what old
looks like?
That's what very
old looks like.
All right,
let's just go watch television with mordechai.
Hi, dad.
Look who came to see you.
Hi, mordechai.
Hi, grandpa.
Go on, dufus. Say hi.
Does it hurt?
Being old?
Not today.
Will?
What took you so long?
Tell me you didn't
mess anything up.
You were right about
grandpa mordechai.
He's a lot of fun.
We had a long talk.
Grandpa mordechai
doesn't talk to anyone.
He talked to me.
[Knocking] will,
can we come in?
Oh, you changed
your clothes.
Yes. Yes, i did.
Honey, your dad and i
just wanted you to know
that that was the sweetest
thing you have ever done.
It meant so
much to me,
you being nice
to grandpa.
You know how much
family means to me.
Anyway, i just
wanted you to know
you are a very
special person.
Don't you ever forget that.
And i want you to know
that your mother and i
are very impressed
with you lately.
I mean, the changes
you've made at school,
and your grades
are up,
your attitude's
improved.
It's like you're a
different kid.
I guess we got
through to you.
And since the changes
happened with you so fast,
summer boot camp is not
an issue anymore.
The summer is yours.
Do anything you want.
Goof off, hang out
around with chuckie,
anything. You
deserve it.
What if... the new me
was only temporary?
What if i went back
to how i used to be?
You'd still love me...
right?
Honey, loving you was
never the question.
C'mon, you knew
that, didn't you?
Huh?
Where do you think
you're going?
Um, to school?
Not today. I'm going.
You're staying here.
Do not leave this room.
Uh, will...
maybe i should fill you in on what's going on in school.
Things are a little
different now.
You know, with your
friends and everything.
I think i can figure out how to talk
to my friends in my school, ok?
Ok.
The nerve of that guy.
"Maybe i should fill you
in on what's going on."
Please.
Looks like his clone head is getting a little swelled.
Hey, there's
will!
What's going on, will?
Hi, will.
Hi.
My friends, my life.
Hi, will.
Thanks so much for helping me rearrange my room.
It was so nice of
you to stay late.
This is my school, not his.
Will!
Chuckie, did i really
stay after school
and help miss pinkerson
move her furniture?
Don't you remember?
Sure, i do.
I just don't
remember why.
Why?
'Cause it's you, man.
You give. You're always
up for new things.
In these last couple of weeks
you've become pretty, ah...
i guess the word i'm
lookin' for is popular.
Yeah. Right.
Will, my man.
My mom scored some tickets to sunday's ball game.
Right behind home plate.
Wanna come?
Sure.
Hey!
Looks like you have
some cleaning up to do.
But it was an accident.
Grip it, punk. And pick it up.
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
Thanks, buddy.
So, think about the game.
We'll talk about it at lunch.
Save your seat?
Thanks.
Cool. See you later.
You too, dude.
Will? You ok?
What time do you want
to meet tonight?
Tonight?
The junior social,
remember, silly?
No, heather, i
forgot. Duh.
How's 7:00?
I wanna be there early--
so we can talk and stuff.
It's settled then.
7:00 in the gym.
See ya later, william.
I'll see ya... william.
Oh, man.
What happened to my life?
Twoie?
Tell me you're in here.
I realized you were
making very poor use
of your available shelf
and closet space,
so i increased the total
storage capacity of your room
by 12.4 cubic feet.
Want to see the chart?
No.
Thanks.
You're mad.
Wow. You're absolutely
brilliant.
You sure you
have my genes?
Every last one
of 'em.
Then how come
you get "a"s?
How come grandpa mordechai talked to you?
How could all of this
have happened for you
but never for me?
You're me, aren't you?
Of course i'm you.
I'm no better or worse.
Yeah. Well, everyone
thinks you're better.
No. Everyone thinks
you're better.
No one knows about me.
What do you do
that's different?
I try hard. And
i'm not afraid.
I'm not afraid
of anything.
I think you pretend not to
care about grades and all.
But really, i think you don't
try because you're afraid
you might not do so well.
Oh, come on!
And it's not just grades.
If i want to do something
like dance, i dance.
I don't care if people
laugh at me. You do.
Why don't you care?
Why should i?
I'm not hurting anyone.
I'm just being me.
If people like me
for that-- great.
And if they don't-- well then,
there's a lot of other
people out there
who i can be friends with.
All i know is that you've messed up my life.
You didn't like
school today?
I did. That's the problem.
And now,
everyone's expecting you tonight at the junior social.
And they're gonna get me.
I should have let you
get me a few good grades,
then taken you to the
mall and dumped you.
You're right.
I am?
I've thought about
this more and more,
and i don't
belong here.
This is your family,
not mine.
Twoie, i--i--
i was thinkin', if
you don't mind,
maybe i'll go to
new york city.
See if it really is
black and white.
But--
i've decided, will.
I'm leaving tonight.
Look, there's that
junior social thing.
I was gonna go, but maybe
you should go instead.
See everyone and hang out
with them for one last time.
This is a big night
for all of us.
You, at your dance.
Us, taking grandpa
mordechai to a movie.
Ok. Ok. How about a big
smile for posterity, huh?
Look at you.
I remember my
first dance.
I was so
nervous.
Something about a
school dance.
[Drinking straw gurgling]
there's that
static again.
There we go.
Look. There's
one of 'em.
Let's go!
Good-bye, twoie.
Hey, will!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Why did you stop me?
How's it goin'?
We don't want
any witnesses.
Besides, did you see
how he was dressed?
He's going to that
school dance.
That's the real will browning.
We don't have time for
speculation, victor.
Either the clone
drinks this tonight,
or he turns into ocean
pup eggs in the morning.
Ocean pup eggs.
Well, you're the one that put
the four-week lifespan on it.
Security precaution.
Yeah. Well, at least we
know that the hyperclone
is somewhere in the
browning house. Right?
Umm. Gimme that.
Gimme!
I want it.
The clone!
Ok. He's gone.
We know where the real
will browning is.
We'll grab him. Pump
him for info.
Where there's a
will, there's a way.
So, how ya
feelin', man?
Great. What's that?
Ahh, that would be
the school mascot.
He must be very important.
Yeah. Right.
Wow. This is nice.
I've never seem anything
so... white... and so sparkily.
♪♪
hi, will.
I brought the pizza.
Wow. Thanks.
This is gonna
be great.
How come no
one's dancing?
Come on, man. You know
no one wants to be
the first geek on
the dance floor.
Where are you going?
Come on. Browning
needs backup.
Heeey! Hey, dude. Will you
hold this for a second?
I'll be right back.
Great.
I can't even be mad at him.
Yeah.
Where are you going?
Uh, i'll be right back.
Maybe i can show you
guys a new dance step.
Will, why'd you change?
And how'd you do
it so fast?
I didn't change.
It was never me.
It was my clone.
You're somethin' else.
I mean, i asked you why
you changed your clothes,
and you've gotta come up
with "that was my clone."
Man, you crack me up.
Listen to me!
You're not going to want to believe this,
but it's true.
So i need your
help. Ok?
You're doin' it again, man.
You're beginning
to freak me out.
I haven't even started.
Uh-oh.
What?
Let's move. We'll
walk and talk.
What the...
gold leader to blue one.
I have a visual.
Wait. I thought i
was gold leader.
Over by the dj.
It's the hyperclone.
We got him.
Time to go.
Hi, will.
I thought you might be thirsty after all that dancing.
Nice clothes.
Much more you.
So, you promised us
a new dance step.
I did?
[Kids chanting]
will! Will! Will!
Go find him, ok?
Bring him back to my garage.
I'll be right behind you.
All right.
And, chuckie, be
careful, man.
You got it.
[Chanting continues]
do you guys want a
new dance step?
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Well, get real close
so you can see me.
What's he doing?
Huh?
Yo-yo.
Plunge.
Tongue twister.
Walk the dog.
You're the best.
Although, i've known
that for years.
You don't think i'm better
now than i was before?
No. I knew you'd come around.
I gotta run. But i'll call you.
Promise?
Yeah.
Oh!
Hello?
Blue one. I've lost visual.
You mean you can't see him?
No. I can't see him.
I'm goin' in.
Yo!
Rotate.
In 5, 6, 7, and...
turn.
Got 'em.
Where?
Over there. Twelve
o'clock high.
This way.
Hey, will.
You're not in the bathroom.
I mean, he's not in there.
I mean, what do i mean?
Wait a second.
What are you doing?
Sometimes we can communicate psychically.
You know. We can hear
each other's thoughts.
If one of us is really
stressed or something.
Shoot! Nothing.
That's it. You're making
all this up. I know it.
Chuckie, you've
gotta trust me!
Look in the gym.
Then go to my house.
You take the shortcut.
I'll take the long way.
That way if he's
out there...
...one of us
will find him.
This is one heck of
a junior social.
Hey!
Gotcha!
Hello, my little
hyperclone.
Lemme-- lemme go!
Bus now boarding
for new york city.
Now boarding for new york city.
Help! Help! Help!
Hold 'em, man.
I've got 'em.
Lemme go!
Let's go, kid.
Hey. While i'm young.
Hyper little hyperclone,
aren't you?
Let's get some dna.
What are you guys,
crazy? Let me go!
No, my little atm card,
we're not crazy.
But thanks to you, we're
gonna be very rich.
No! You'll be in jail!
This is kidnapping!
Uh-ah.
Clonenapping.
You think i'm
twoie, don't you?
Yeah, well, you got
the wrong one!
I'm the real will.
Yeah! All right now.
If you'll let me go right now, i
won't tell anyone about you, ok?
Would you excuse us
for a moment, please?
Yeah.
What if he's
telling the truth?
If we give a normal kid the serum,
no telling what might happen.
I think we have to
get the other one.
Run some tests.
That's the only way
we can be sure.
Oh, yeah.
Check the ropes. Gotta
keep this one here.
Ok.
Don't go away.
Help! Somebody, help me!
Big trouble. I'm in big trouble.
If i ever get outta here, i--
twoie was right.
What was i waiting for?
Now i'll never get a chance to dance,
or see chuckie or heather, even.
Or allana, or mom and dad.
I love my mom and dad.
I can't believe it.
I miss my family.
Tell me about it.
Twoie!
In the flesh.
I was at the bus station,
and i knew you were scared.
And then the name red jack
motors flashed in my head.
You came back for me.
Why are you so surprised?
You should be mad at me.
Will, if it wasn't for you,
i wouldn't have
ever tasted pizza.
I owe you one.
Twoie, i gotta tell
you something.
If you don't drink
some special liquid
those creeps in
the van have,
you might turn back
into ocean pup eggs.
That's why i've been
feeling so weird.
We've gotta get it
back from them.
Well, that was stupid, conrad.
Come on!
"We don't need gas," you said.
"It runs for three miles
on empty," you said.
He's gone.
All right. He's
gotta be in here.
No way out.
Right.
[Whistles]
we better split up.
Come on!
Well, well, well.
Looks like we finally
got our hyperclone.
I'm will.
We switched clothes.
I don't think so.
You don't need to be afraid.
We've got your best
interest at heart.
You need us.
See, without this--
you'll be nothin' but...
cheap caviar.
It's already started. You
can see it in your face.
What are you gonna do with that?
Oh. Oh!
Ooh! You got me.
Ow!
Oh, no!
Stop the--
victor?
Victor?
Aaahhhh!
Get me a parachute, boys.
You're gonna have to
do better than that.
Aahhhh!
Ow!
Those little creeps
assaulted me!
Come on!
You go. Go!
Get 'em! Get 'em!
Gotcha!
I gotcha, twoie. Come
on! I gotcha, buddy!
Whoa... ow!
Two-- twoie!
Twoie! Twoie!
Twoie! Let him go!
I'll call the police!
What are you
gonna do? Huh?
Tell the police that the bad
men stole your hyperclone?
Who's gonna
believe ya?
The window. The bathroom window.
It's time to take
your medicine.
Come now!
This solution will keep
you running forever.
You do want to
live, don't you?
Why? So you can
experiment on me?
Why shouldn't we experiment
on you? We created you!
Do you have any idea how many years
we slaved to make you possible?
Hold him still.
This won't hurt a bit.
But this will.
Oh.
Mommy!
Oh, that smarts.
Aaahh!
Is there a problem here?
That's private property.
Ow! Oh!
Twoie?
Come on, twoie. Drink this now!
Come on.
Sorry, will.
No! Come on!
Drink it!
Twoie?
[Burp]
wow!
Wow! Wow! A-a-you!
And you!
Neither of you were lying!
How did you guys
know to come here?
I stopped by the
school on my way here,
and i told them to get help.
Ok. This doesn't
concern you children.
Children? Grip it, einstein.
Aahhh!
Come on! Let's go!
Oh, no.
Officers, there's
another one over there.
Oh, that's my--
watch it--
come on, honey.
Will! Honey, are you ok?
Will, what happened?
Are you--
two of them?
My worst nightmare.
We're not criminals.
We're scientists!
That's our clone in there!
Remember that science
project i was working on?
Yeah, well, he's it.
I'll explain everything
at home, but please,
you guys gotta cover for us.
Please?
Look, i know this is gonna sound
like a bit of a crazy question,
but, ah...
you two...
are... cousins.
Identical cousins.
I'm will, and this is...
gill.
Gill.
Uhh, pupman.
We're cousins like he said.
I'm from belgium.
Cousins?
Yep. Cousins.
Identical.
Belgium.
They're clones! Identical
genetic subjects!
Yeah.
Every cell's the same!
Officer, that man's crazy.
We made him!
Outta nothin'!
Yeah, yeah.
Clones? We're cousins.
Never could tell them apart.
Right, mom? Dad?
Well, ok,
but we're gonna have to take some statements.
Eh... tomorrow.
The, um, cousins have
been through enough.
But...
uh... tomorrow.
Gill,
let's go home.
Will, i think this is the beginning of a beautiful friendship.
So, this whole time he's
been living in my room,
doing my homework and stuff.
But the weird thing is,
he changed me.
Even while he was being me.
I-i-am very confused.
I am so confused.
So...
can gill stay?
What do you want, gill?
A family.
Well, as long as you're
living under this roof,
you're going to have to maintain
those excellent grades.
This is cool.
Weird. But cool.
Ahh, but we tell no one.
Ahh, gill is a cousin
who now lives with us.
Right?
An identical cousin.
Anyone who says any different...
will have to deal with me.
Well, ok. It's settled then.
Welcome to the
family, gill.
Just don't go taking twice as
much time in the bathroom.
Ok, then.
I'm hungry!
And i don't want anything with tree bark.
Pizza?
Pizza!
Pizza.
Yes.
Captions made possible by
the disney channel
captioned by
line of sight captions