[Theme music]
[Music - spanish rap]
[Heavy breathing]
Carlos, wake up!
Go and look for a job.
[Speaking spanish]
CARLOS (VOICEOVER): Shit!
That was a bad ass dream, man.
Tired of living like this.
Shit... man, someday
if I work at it,
I'll get all that,
and some, homes.
Give me the fucking money, man!
Hurry up!
Hurry up, bitch!
Come on, man!
[Glass shatters]
Don't fucking do it, man!
Don't fucking do it!
[Gun shots]
NICK (VOICEOVER): Carlos Sanchez
was just released from here.
But I never really got a
chance to give him that helping
Hand that he needed.
These are fucking animals
we're dealing with.
What are you doing
going out behind my back
And writing for
another field visit?
Look, I just wanted to try
something different this time.
What are you doing?
Don't you know you're
still on probation?
One more screw up, and
you're the one who's
Going to be behind the bars.
NICK (VOICEOVER): In 1984,
there were 20 murders
Committed in Los Angeles.
Now, the number of
exceeds 2,000 a year.
Our prisons are packed.
Most convicts get out
early, with only 7%
Of them actually
being rehabilitated.
Kids are killing kids.
When will it stop?
What ya looking at, fool?
What's it to you?
What, bitch?
[Inaudible].
[Grunt]
Sit your stupid ass down.
Until no fucking trying
to get up on somebody.
Man, I didn't do shit.
I tell you, I'm
fucking innocent.
Problem is, it's
the white man trying
To keep the black man down.
You know that.
Do not let those
niggers push you around.
Don't do it.
What should I do?
Danny thinks you
gotta shank one.
better do it soon.
[Speaking spanish]
What's your problem, man?
Where you from?
I'm from nowhere.
Well, if you
ain't from nowhere,
How come I see you
hanging with 17th Street?
No, no, no.
But if I was, what
the fuck's it to you?
What's it to me?
[Yelling]
Stand against that wall!
Get up!
Get against that wall!
[Yelling]
For fuck sake, cut it out!
Get against that wall!
Danny thinks this
guy is GI Joe?
Get against that wall.
[Murmuring]
All right, man.
We're moving.
OK, my name's Nick Tagalano.
I'm the counselor here.
Hello, Nick.
[Laughing]
NICK: You're my property now.
Says who?
NICK: You were sent here for two
reasons... one, to be punished,
And two, to get rehabilitated.
You guys act like animals,
you'll be treated like animals.
[Barking]
[Laughing]
I'm going to pair you
up in groups of two.
Mario and Gustov, you're a pair.
Hey!
You're a pair.
Noah and Danny.
Fuck that!
I ain't going with that
punk ass white boy, man!
Chill out.
NICK: [inaudible].
You're a pair.
Steven G... and Eric?
Mike didn't make it.
They told me they just found
him in the shower room.
He was stabbed 20 times.
[Interposing voices]
[Yelling]
Hey, Hesse.
Thanks for backing me up, homes.
Hey nothing, buddy.
I just didn't want
to see you get hurt.
I know, homes.
I can take care of myself.
So how long you
been in the gang?
Just about eight months, man.
I'm a [inaudible],
my [inaudible]
Jumped me in and shit.
How about you, homes?
I ain't in no
gang no more, man.
Got my girl, and a kid
on his way to look after.
Homey don't play that.
That's cool, homes.
Look at this shit.
Hey, [inaudible].
Listen, bro.
Danny doesn't have any
problem with your kind, OK?
OK?
Damn, he thinks every
white man should own a few.
Hey fuck you!
Fuck you!
Hey!
Listen, can't get
in no fucking fight.
Six months from fucking home.
Why are you all here?
It's all about the rush.
Danny's just here because he
got caught, like everybody else.
I'm the real victim.
Shit... doing
someone else's time,
Just wasting my life away.
Got a balloon here.
In this balloon exists energy.
If it's not controlled,
it can be lost.
Like you.
Now where do you guys see
yourselves in the future?
Just drinking 40 ounces, Hesse.
Haven't figured that out yet.
Finding a nice lady.
Fuck on that.
I'm gonna make myself
a whole bunch of money.
Give me 50, Mario.
50 what?
50 push-ups.
From this moment on, there's
no vulgarity in this room,
Or you'll pay.
Just give me 50, Mario.
Continue on.
Hey yo, I don't care what
the word on the street
Is, but look, I just
know, ain't nobody
Going to faint and drink.
Yeah, respect is something
all people deserve.
But it's something
that you have to earn.
Your dreams are your own, but in
order to achieve those dreams,
You have to have a plan.
Like working hard, going
to school, setting goals.
Most important...
Conquering the fear.
The fear that'll keep you
from reaching those goals.
You show me that you have
a change in your attitude
In the next few months,
and I'll get you
Out of here on a field trip.
We'll do war games.
It's up to you.
Come on, kick that thing.
[Grunting]
Higher!
Come on!
Again!
Fuck man, that hurts!
Come on, come on!
Higher, let's go
a little higher.
[Grunting]
There you go.
Beautiful.
One more time.
There you go, good.
Use that hand... use
your hands in it.
Combination.
OK, any number that's
squared is simply a number
That's multiplied by itself.
For instance, what's 3 squared?
9.
Good, 3 times 3.
How about 3 to the third power?
Is it also 9?
Good guess, wrong though.
27.
Very good, Gus.
Come up here to the blackboard
and show us how you did it.
I just paid attention.
Very good, very good.
Thank you.
How's that?
Something like that.
You're doing good,
you're doing good.
Hang in there.
You're gonna get this.
Ah, this is your stuff, huh?
Yeah.
Ah, you're really getting
the hang of this thing.
It's just easy, man.
Damn.
Hey, man, why
don't you calm down?
What did you say?
You know what I
said, mother fucker.
Why don't you mind your
own fucking business.
Take your black ass to
the basketball court...
Want to take this shit outside?
Let's calm down,
calm down calm down.
Let's go.
We're on the computer.
Come on, get back to work here.
Basketball.
What the fuck do you
know about basketball?
What good is a brother
that can't play basketball?
At least... at least you
could fucking [inaudible]
Because you sure the fuck
not going to make the NBA.
Damn, getting schooled
by a white man.
Schooled by a white man.
I can't wait to go back
in the cell [inaudible].
[Music playing]
You didn't clean here.
Man, you didn't ask us to.
You don't just clean for
me, you clean for yourself.
What about my bed?
No dinner for anybody tonight.
ALL: [angry murmuring]
ALL: [chanting] Bull shit!
Bull shit!
Danny wasn't hungry anyway!
Me, neither.
[Growling]
MAN BEHIND CAMERA:
What's up guys?
Yeah, whoo!
Everybody having a good time?
Hey, Jim!
Car's looking good, man.
Don't forget the windows there.
Hey, watch it there.
Hey... man, that's looking nice.
Uh-oh.
Wassup, punk.
MAN BEHIND CAMERA: What
the fuck do those guys
Think they're doing, man?
Shit.
Hey, Jimmy, I think those
guys are coming back, man.
[Gunshots]
Damn!
What the hell, man?
How do you guys feel about
the film you've just seen,
Getting murdered on television?
Man, I didn't feel
sorry for the bitch.
He deserved to get smoked.
You know man, the fucker that
shot him, man, was pretty cold,
You know. 'Cause
I would have said,
Say hello to my little
friend, you fucker, pow!
Pow!
No fucking, man.
I don't give a fuck.
Shit.
There's no other way for
you to avoid conflict?
It's either gonna
be me, or him.
And it ain't gonna be me.
But your life wasn't in danger.
Only his.
And now he has no life.
And no future.
You haven't grown
up on our streets,
And dealt with our pain.
It's fucked up.
You just don't get it.
Who really just doesn't get it.
Damn, what's up with him?
MAN BEHIND CAMERA:
What the hell, man?
Somebody call 911!
Somebody call 911 now!
Oh, god, what happened?
This can't be happening.
Go!
Go call, go!
OK, I'm going to put you
guys in groups of four.
The first group... Danny,
Eric, Steve and Gus.
Group one.
Andre, Noah, Eddie, group two.
Yeah.
In group three, I want
Cartoon, Mario, Joker, and T.
You boys grab your weapons.
The rest of you guys
get off the field.
Let's go.
[Interposing voices]
You're playing [inaudible].
What is it with
this war games shit?
[Inaudible]
OK, you guys ready?
Yeah, I'm ready.
We're ready.
[Shots]
[Screaming]
This is bull shit, man.
You didn't give us a chance!
Do your enemies give you a
chance on the street, Danny?
That's the way it goes.
[Interposing voices]
I'm taking your ass out.
Not if I get to him first.
Group two, you ready?
Yeah.
One of you guys just go that
way, and I'll try to cover.
Fuck you, [inaudible] man.
You go your own way.
Us black brothers got
to stick together, man.
Fuck you, [inaudible].
Fuck you.
And you, too, brother man.
Fuck you!
You're on your own, fool.
Cool.
Here tiger, tiger, tiger.
Here, tiger, tiger, tiger.
[Shot]
[Scream]
[Groan]
[Shots]
What's up, Joe?
[Whistles]
Here, kitty, kitty.
Hello?
Ah!
Come out, [inaudible].
[Clanging]
Ah!
No teamwork.
Next group.
All right, man.
Let's get these cock suckers.
[Inaudible], Hesse.
Right, you and me, Cartoon,
we'll go down this way.
Joker, you go down that way.
Distract him.
See if you got
the shot, take it.
If you don't, just cover
us from there, all right?
All right, let's do this.
Let's fucking do this.
[Whistling]
Counselor... come out, come out.
[Shots]
Ah!
Fuck!
[Groaning]
[Shot]
Oof!
ALL: Yeah!
[Interposing voices]
Yeah, this is a game, for fun.
But in the real world, it
would be quite different, guys.
[Non-english speech]
[Groaning]
Come on, come on.
Come on, guys.
[Non-english speech]
[Bag rustling]
[Heart beat]
What the fuck?
What is it, homes?
Damn, I see it.
It's a fucking king-sized rat.
[Heart beat]
Get that little fucker.
There it goes.
MAN: There, man, there!
Hey man, he got it!
ALL: [yelling]
ALL: [cheering]
NICK: Stop!
Stop it!
You know, some people
are wounded by fear.
And they want to
destroy the things
That they don't understand.
They base their
prejudice on race,
Color, creed, where somebody
lives, what they look like.
Anything they don't understand,
they want to destroy.
All they know, is what
they've been told.
NOAH: What you working on, man?
Looks like you're trying to
access some unauthorized files.
Can you get in?
Sure, I can give it a shot.
Shit.
How the fuck you got
in Tagalano's file?
Check this out.
There's six months
in the state pen...
And he's still on probation.
No fucking way.
For what?
Obstruction of justice... took
a group out from cell block
A out on a [inaudible] retreat.
Four officers were killed,
and they left Taka for dead.
Did any of them get away?
Nope.
They tried to.
They were killed.
Can you find out where we're
going on our little trip?
To the zoo.
San Bernardino Zoo.
Zoo?
Yep.
They say it's been closed
down for awhile now.
Really?
Can you pull up a map?
The energy inside of you
is neither good nor evil.
Cartoon, Eddie, give me that
wood, hold it for me over here.
That's exactly what
you make that energy.
Ah!
That sort of energy will
help you achieve your goals.
Mark, set, go!
We come down this way, we come
this way, we come this way.
But what's the most
[inaudible] here?
Take it down!
Get low!
Get high!
Go!
[Inaudible yelling]
Higher than that.
I taught you higher.
Come on.
There you go, there
you go. [Inaudible].
Yeah!
Side kick, [inaudible]!
The derivative
of the exponential
Squared times x to the
fourth power is 1,692.
NICK: Correct.
Ah, fuck yeah, I got
that shit, too, homes.
Fuckin' A.
[Sighs]
[Non-english speech]
Hey, let me help you with that.
That's all right, man.
Come on, [inaudible].
[Grunting]
Damn, this is heavy.
What... what happened
to your arm?
Nah, nothing
happened to me, I just
Thought it would get me
out of this bull shit,
You know what I mean?
Thanks, man.
Hey, any time.
Cartoon, get your butt in here.
[Screams]
Come on, [inaudible].
NICK: Teach you [inaudible].
Good, good.
I can't believe you're here.
He looks so much like you.
He has your nose and ears.
I miss you.
When are you coming home?
I'll be out in just
a few more years.
I miss you.
Oh, god.
You don't know how
much I miss you, too...
How much pain I have inside.
Not being able to... to touch
you, feel you, and kiss
You, and watch our son grow.
He needs you.
I need you.
I'm getting tired of waiting.
Hey, what's up, dog?
How's it going, man?
All right.
Got a light?
So, tell me.
I can't believe sometimes,
you're my baby brother.
So how's Mom?
How come she didn't come?
She's got a new boyfriend.
You should be happy for her.
Yeah, I guess that's cool.
I told you so.
Stay off the cocaine.
But no, you don't
want to listen.
Hey, man... I'm working on
computers and stuff now.
I know Lotus, Word Perfect, I'm
going to do some programming.
Yeah, that's really great.
Listen, I got to get going.
I told Mom I'd stop by.
Hey, why'd you come anyways?
If you guys abandon me
then, you're doing it now.
You act like I'm some kind
of cripple or something.
Don't even bother, man.
Don't even bother coming back.
That fucker's from
17th Street, eh?
[Inaudible]
What happened to the
troops, [speaking spanish]?
Man, fuck the troops.
[Inaudible] when they
took our eight ball.
Fucking got eight-balled, too?
Yeah, eh, and Cartoon?
You ain't do shit now, man.
Fuck.
What the fuck now, homes?
The [speaking spanish]
you put in the hospital
Didn't make it, Hesse.
Fuck you, Sal.
You told me he was
making it, homes.
pulling through, Hesse.
CHEWIE: Nah, eh.
You know what, eh?
Now they're trying to
pull that first degree
Murder on you, shit.
No way, homes.
I'm fucking 20 years old, Sal.
I'll fucking be in
here forever, homes.
Fuck that, Hesse.
You're supposed to
watch out for me, homes.
You, too, Chewie.
Fuck you guys, homes.
Shit.
Sorry.
Why do I have suffer, too?
I didn't do anything wrong.
I know.
Do you think I like
coming to this place?
You think I'm going
to bring Junior here?
Sorry.
I don't know
about this anymore.
Maria... Maria!
Shit!
Yeah, Hesse, tomorrow
we're going on
Retreat to the woods,
[speaking spanish].
Check it out, Hesse, that's
a gato, from 17th Street.
[Speaking spanish]
Hey, fuck you, homes.
That motherfucker killed
Frank and then [inaudible].
That mother fucker's going down.
You know that herd
you're going to take
On that little girly
nature trip of yours
Is gonna screw you
just like the last one.
Look, they need to
escape, just for a day.
They have to find out the
value of what they have,
And what they can become.
You're a dreaming
fucking idiot if you
Think that trash in there
is ever going to change.
Get it through that
thick skull of yours.
What's up, homes?
Hey, man, they're
breaking you out today.
Why, Hesse?
Listen, if they
decide to prosecute,
You're looking at 25 years
or more instead of the two.
You got to go.
You're right, homes.
Thanks, Hesse, that's cool, man.
Got this to help you out.
Right, homes.
Remember, when the shit goes
down, you take el gato out.
Hey, homes, what if he's not...
Listen, Hesse... you
take his ass out.
Don't fuck this shit up.
[Music - spanish rap]
Hey, where the
hell is Sal, man?
[Inaudible].
[Speaking spanish]
VOICE ON RADIO:
The young man who
Was swinging the
broom handle was shot
Nine times by an LAPD officer.
Shot nine times,
mostly in the chest.
OK, wait, are we going
to be there anytime soon?
I hope so.
It's probably right up here.
We've been walking
for awhile, so I'm
Sure it's just right up here.
It's right up here, for
like an hour and a half.
- We're having a good time.
- Maybe we should turn around.
I'm really hungry.
I want to go swimming.
There's a great river up there.
You know what?
My friend was here one time,
he said saw some dead animals.
So we like, could find you a
possum, we'll cook it for you.
Dead animal?
All right.
Let's go.
You want to tan, so
let's just go up here.
It's got to be right up here.
We've been walking for an hour.
Five more minutes we'll walk,
and then if we don't find it,
We'll turn around.
OK, we'll turn around.
Hey, Taka, I'm starving, man.
Oh, yeah, me too, man.
Tak, I've got to
go to the bathroom.
NICK: Calm down, calm down.
There's a restaurant coming up
here at the end of the road.
We can stop in there
if you guys behave.
It's up to you.
It's up to us?
Hey don't anybody
fuck up, I want...
If you don't to do
push-ups back there,
Watch your language.
OK, what the fuck is
this place, you guys?
Wow.
Look at this.
Hey, don't touch that.
It's just candles.
Guys, stop it.
[Screams]
What?
It's a skull!
OK, this is some
weird cult bullshit.
Let's get out of here.
It's probably just a bunch
of kids playing around.
Wait, let's just have a look.
Look.
What is it?
OK, let's get out of here.
What?
Oh, my god.
What is that?
Let's get out of here.
[Screaming]
Tell you what... people just
don't appreciate what they got.
[Inaudible] some real food.
Better [inaudible] food
we eat every day, man.
Hell, yeah.
Hello, how are you?
Hey, tell me something.
Tell me if that girl over
there is looking at me.
Don't look straight at her.
Yeah, yeah, all right.
Yeah, all right, Hesse.
She's looking at you.
This guy thought he was
going to fake me... me... out.
He's faking to the left,
he's faking to the right.
Shh... I picked his
sorry ass up and slammed
Him down like a sack of beans.
I was thinking of
trying out for volleyball
At my new school.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
That's great.
I never told you how much I can
bench press either, did I. No?
It's incredible.
It's a miracle.
I'll tell you
about it sometimes.
I bet you surprise yourself.
Always.
I'll be right back.
I know man, I know, but
I'm too fucking nervous.
What am I fucking going to do?
I don't know,
Hesse, but you better
Come up with something quick.
Cause you only got
one shot at this.
All right, all right.
I'm going to make a move.
[Music]
Hi.
Hello.
How you doing?
Good.
How are you?
OK.
Did you need something?
No, I just haven't seen anyone
so beautiful in a long time.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
So, why are you all
dressed up like that?
Or are you on some
kind of retreat?
Yeah, we're on a
college retreat.
College.
For a PE class?
Or...
Yeah, yeah,
actually we're doing
Some research for a report.
A report, yeah, yeah.
Well, I go to [inaudible].
Where do you go?
I go to Cal... Cal
Taka, actually.
Call Taka?
Yeah.
I've never heard of it.
Is it a private school?
Yeah, I guess you
could call it that.
It's pretty private.
Well, my name's Susan.
My name's Mario.
Pleased to meet you, Susan.
Pleased to meet you.
Well, I better get back.
Maybe some time you can show
me your report or something.
Yeah, maybe.
Well, it was good to meet you.
Same here.
Susan?
Yes.
Have a nice day.
Thank you.
Hey, Susan, come on.
Food's ready.
Let go of me.
What is...
Hey, man, why don't
you let go of her.
What did you say to me?
What did you say to
me, fucking prick?
Hey, man, back up.
I don't want to start anything.
You know what man?
Fuck you.
[Grunting]
Let go of me, you dick!
I didn't fucking
do nothing, man!
Man, I can't believe that.
I got so nervous.
Shit.
Susan, yes?
Have a nice day.
Ah, I sounded like
a fucking geek.
Hey, Hesse, the broad
told me to give you this.
Yeah.
Hey, who's truck is that?
That ain't one of ours.
Chico, stop kicking
with the others,
Go see who the fuck that is.
Peso, who set up the
road block? [Inaudible].
[Rhythmic music]
Enough.
Come.
Now we must prepare.
Your drink, my lord.
Before the black
angel's death, he
Took upon a sacrifice,
killing it... taking of flesh,
Giving unto his worshippers,
saying, take, eat.
We, too, shall
offer a sacrifice.
We do this in remembrance
of the black angel.
Please, let me go.
Please don't do this.
I'll do anything, please.
I don't think so.
What's wrong with
you people, please.
Let me... please just
don't this, please.
You know, I always
get what I want.
I want you.
[Organ music]
[Moaning]
[Screaming]
[Gun shots]
What the fuck?
Who the fuck shot?
No!
They'll pay.
Hey, I see them coming!
[Gunshot]
ALL: [yelling]
What the fuck's going on, man!
[Interposing voices]
Damn... fuck, man!
[Yelling]
[Gun shots]
Go!
Come on!
[Gun shots]
[Screaming]
[Yelling]
ALL: [yelling]
[Gun shots]
[Yelling]
[Grunting]
(WHISPERING) Hey,
come here, man.
No, no... fuck you, man.
I ain't letting nobody
play me for no fool.
Hey, guys, where you going?
Get the fuck out here, man.
Run!
Go your own way!
Just do it, man!
[Screaming]
[Inaudible screaming]
[Non-english speech]
Wait up, eh?
Wait up... oh, shit!
Johnny, [inaudible],
where you at?
Oh, fuck!
[Gun shot]
Check it out, check it out.
What's up, homes?
OK, [inaudible] we're
going to split up here, OK?
The team is what
we need, Hesse.
That's what we've got to do.
Stick together, man.
[Speaking spanish] Why
you two want to break up?
[Speaking spanish] has some
unfinished business, OK?
What about the other homies,
man, we got to go back.
MAN: Fuck that shit,
I ain't going back.
Shut up, man, shut up!
Shut up, all right?
Francisco's back there,
Hesse, and they're
Probably on their way there.
So we'll meet there, OK?
And don't let anybody
leave anybody behind.
Hey, [inaudible], I don't
know about this shit, man.
What the fuck you
don't know about, Hesse?
Eddie's fucking
Mexican like us, man.
He's fucking from our
hood, homes, why we
Got to take him out and shit?
He ain't one of us, Hesse.
You gotta be what you gotta be.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Come on, vato.
You one of us, Hesse?
All right, then.
Cartoon, we'll
split up here, OK?
Smart, homes.
And Cartoon, and if you see El
Gato, you call out for me, OK?
Right.
Rolo!
Hey, Rolo!
[Yelling]
So you going to come after me
and shoot me after everything,
Huh?
Go ahead, then.
Go ahead.
All you are is a back-stabbing
fool, who gets played
Like a puppy with his master.
It's not what you think, homes.
All you want is what
I'm going to give you.
Let's pick up the gun, huh?
Shoot me!
Finish what you started!
I don't want you-
Pick up the gun.
I don't want you
to go down, homes!
(WHISPERING)
[Gun shots]
Go around and cut
him off, Hesse.
Hey, wait up, Joe!
[Heart beat]
Get your fucking asses up!
Come on.
Get in there.
Easy, man... easy!
Shut the fuck up!
Disciples, today we
have gotten the fate
To dispose of these
deserving persons
With diseased minds, who seek
to slander and work against us.
Oh, you mother fucker!
We will kill one now,
and the rest at sunrise.
Follow us!
ALL: [yelling]
Fuck you, mother fucker!
Fuck you, bitch!
[Whimpering]
[Gasp]
Did you see anything?
No, man.
I don't... I don't know
where everybody's at, and I
Don't know where we are.
But I know one thing
for fucking sure...
What's that?
We ain't getting out up that
way, it's a fucking cliff.
Hey Danny?
What?
Do you believe in God?
In God, man.
No, man, Danny
doesn't believe...
I don't know fucking know.
Well, I do.
It's funny, when you don't
need him, you forget about him.
But when your ass is in a world
of trouble like right now,
You start believing in him.
Well, Danny doesn't know
about all that mystical shit.
For all I know, the bible is
just some all time, worldwide,
Best-selling bull shit.
[Yelling]
Steve, you moron.
[Grunting]
Fuck, you all right, man?
What are we going to
do about fucking Noah?
Fuck, man, I ain't
going down there.
Fuck that.
[Yelling]
Get them!
Shit!
This way, guys!
[Yelling]
This way!
Hey guys!
Over here!
[Yelling]
[Screaming]
Don't, Danny, don't die!
Danny!
[Sobbing] Danny!
Please don't die.
Danny!
[Sobbing] Danny?
[Interposing voices]
What's up, homes?
This mother fucker
still alive, man?
[Grunting]
Yeah, he's still alive.
Well let's [inaudible]
his mother fucking ass.
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
What?
What are we gonna use.
What, man?
What the fuck you want?
I've got a better idea.
I got it.
Hell, yeah.
Move, man.
[Grumbling] Punk ass bastard.
How you like, mother fucker?
Get this bitch ass out.
Come on.
Come on!
Come on, shit!
Listen, everybody... we have
to pull ourselves together.
We're all gonna
die, just like Danny.
Man, will you shut the fuck up.
How we gonna get out of here?
Both of you are
acting like bitches.
[Music playing]
Would you cut that out, man?
Somebody's going to hear us.
Shit, this shit can
save your life, man.
Hey, yo, vato...
Hey, what's up, man?
Hey, where'd you
you get the gun?
- From my homeboys, man.
- What?
That's what we need.
Who's your homeboys?
- I haven't seen them.
- Can they help us?
No, man, I haven't
fucking seen them.
They probably didn't
make and shit.
Shit, man.
There's not fucking hope.
We're fucking assed up.
[interposing voices]
Where is everyone, man?
Stevie's back there, man.
He's helping Mario, he's hurt.
We're supposed to stay, one
of those guys was captured.
Yeah, man, fuck... Taka,
Joker, and some other people
May have been held captive
down at some damn ritual
Ground and shit.
And Danny's killed.
What?
Yeah, man, they got Danny.
Oh, fuck, man.
[Mumbling]
Well, we better do something.
And let's do it quick.
No, what we better do is go
save Taka and the rest of them.
[Interposing voices]
Hey, fuck it, we can do it.
[Inaudible].
I tried to stop it, man.
Those fucking...
Don't worry.
Saved [inaudible].
All right, Hesse, check it out.
I talked to Mario
and Steve, man.
How's he doing?
Mario don't look good, man.
But I think I got a plan.
Let's hear it man.
All right, check it out.
Spill it out.
All right, Steve said the
cars are about right here.
OK... Andre, where's
the grounds at.
About right here?
Yeah, about right there.
That's cool?
Yeah.
All right, then.
I think if we cause a
distraction up here,
We can get in there,
man, and take off.
Fuck... that's suicide, man?
Sir... as you know, I've
been trying to reach
The group for hours now.
They were supposed to be
back at 11:30, it's now 4:30.
I think it's pretty
safe to say that we
Might have a problem here.
Damn!
I knew I shouldn't
have let him go.
Send in a search party.
OK, do you want
me to organize it?
Dulep... get it
done immediately.
Absolutely, sir.
[Inaudible]
We're gonna need these.
Now we're gonna... just have to...
[Gun shots]
MAN: I can see the camp.
We can fucking make it, man.
I don't think so.
We're being hunted, man!
You all go ahead, man.
I'll hold them back.
That's too fucking many, man.
Hey go ahead, man,
I'll hold them back.
Hey, Hesse, you can't
fucking take them...
I'll do it, man!
You just get in there and you
save Taka and the rest of them.
Remember what he said,
it's what's in here, man.
Hang in there, man.
You fucking take care.
You know it, man, just survive.
- Let's go, man!
- Do it!
Go!
Come on, let's do this, man.
Hey you, redneck
mother fuckers!
Come out you mother
fucking devil worshippers!
Come on!
[Whispering]
VOICE: Sometimes they have to
kill us... they have to kill us,
Because they can't
take our spirit.
Threat to people we are.
We know the difference
between the reality of things,
And the illusion.
[Gun shots]
[Music]
[Yelling]
[Screaming]
Come on, let's go man!
[Gun shot]
Ah!
Shit!
[Gun shots]
[Gun shot]
Hey, where you guys at?
TOGETHER: Here!
Here!
Over here!
Get us out!
[Grunting]
[Grumbling]
[Yelling]
Come on, T!
[Gun shots]
Ah!
ALL: Shh!
Be quiet!
(WHISPERING) They're
going to hear us!
(WHISPERING) Come
one, man, they're going
To know we're here.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck!
TOGETHER: No!
Shit!
(WHISPERING)
[Heart beat]
As time passed by,
their wounds healed,
And they were able to once
again fly away and take back
Control over their destinies.
Bryan, he became a DJ on radio.
Noah, well he works for
a large Aircraft Company
Here in California.
He's a computer engineer.
Gus, he runs a really
good restaurant.
Andre, he became
a film director.
Mario got himself engaged
to a girl named Susan,
And they're both attending
college together.
Eddie, who didn't learn,
got out and did more crimes.
And currently he's serving
time in county jail.
Cartoon, well, he
recently got out
And wants to become a counselor,
just like me, one day.
Warden, there's a
riot in cell block two.
Let's go.
TOGETHER: Bull shit!
Bull shit!
OK, calm down!
Calm down!
Calm down here!
[Music playing]