- ( Car revving )
- ( rock music playing )
( Woman laughing )
Woman #2:
Rae, can you slow down
a little?
Rae:
mmm, I've got a need
for speed, ang.
Angela:
yeah, I got a need
to not throw up.
( Rae continues laughing )
- Rae: did I leave
my gym bag back there?
- ( Truck honks )
Gross.
Haley, switch.
Haley:
no way!
I called shotgun.
- Angela: rae.
- Rae: She called it.
Let her have it
for once, ang. Jeez.
Yeah, fine, whatever.
I'll just hold my nose
the whole way there.
O.m.g., rae,
did I tell you what
I did at the d.M.V.?
Did you actually
just say, "o.M.G."?
I guess I did.
( All laughing )
Do you laugh
by saying "l.O.L."
Over and over again, too?
Sorry, sorry, I meant,
"lol, lol, lol, lol."
( Laughing )
How much further
is this party?
I cannot breathe
back here, rae.
Almost there.
Taking a shortcut.
Will there be
alcohol there?
Uh, if there is,
you're not gonna have any.
( Rae laughing )
check the glove box.
- ( Bottle swishing )
- Haley: Oh, wow.
- Angela: rae!
- Rae: Relax, ang,
there's plenty
for everyone.
- Haley: thanks, rae.
- Angela: She's 15!
Rae:
like we didn't drink
when we were 15.
- Angela: look out!
- ( Car crashing )
( Ominous music playing )
( No discernable dialog )
( Sizzling )
- ( Gasps )
- ( Acoustic guitar
music playing )
Man on TV:
Wouldn't it be nice
if every day
was just as beautiful
as today?
Because that's
our goal at baier corp.
Because not only
do we care about you,
we know who you are
and where you live
is just as important.
Join me now as I show you
all the ways that baier corp
is making a difference
in your community.
( Eagle screeches )
( Sighs )
( Gasps )
shit!
- ( Train horn blaring )
- ( bell ringing )
( Train horn blaring )
Ugh, how many cars
are on this fucking thing?
- Language.
- ( Elise sighs )
( Sighs )
That was a long pee.
A gallon of water a day.
'Cause I read that if you drink
a gallon of water a day,
you'll have clearer skin
and you'll be skinny.
Well, why don't you
just borrow a diaper
from Deb's shit machine?
( Laughing )
Elise!
Mommy loves you.
- ( Elise whispers )
- ( baby laughs )
Um... Angela?
I think the train is...
Oh.
( Baby coughs )
( Whirring )
( Shower running )
( Muffled shouting )
And here it is, ladies.
What it lacks in looks,
it more than makes up for
in complete isolation.
Ang, I love it.
It's like--
it reminds me of home.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
- Oh, rae.
- Hi!
Oh, you look gorgeous.
Uh, yeah.
I always try
to put on my best.
I had no idea you guys
were gonna be here so fast.
It's so good to see you.
Hang on, I've got goodies.
- Goodies?
- goodies.
Wow.
Pop-pop has not
changed a thing.
Well, there's the new TV.
Maybe one day
he'll even get a computer.
Rae:
doubtful.
It was nice of him
to let us use the place
for your party, though.
Right?
What can I say?
He loves me.
Man, it is so weird
being here after
all these years.
Oh, yeah.
This is way better
than Vegas.
I thought it would be,
for more privacy.
- I'm just
teasing you, rae-rae.
- How are you?
- ( Laughs )
- less chance
of s.T.D.S or jail.
- Are you sure?
- I didn't say, "no chance."
I said, "less," so--
- rae: how are you?
- Elise: It's good to see you.
- Rae: oh, you look great.
- ( Deb coughs )
No smoking, Elise.
There is a child.
Well, you know, I can't
smoke in the car,
I can't smoke in the house.
Where the fuck is a girl
supposed to smoke?
Elise Patricia west,
what did I say
about language?
Jesus, Deb, how do you
even know my middle name?
( Coos )
Well, I guess you're
just gonna have to quit.
Elise: hey.
No smoking
in the house, lise.
I'm sorry.
Hey, you know,
don't apologize.
Your tit got burnt, so...
He is so precious.
( Laughing )
Where did you park
the beast?
You said you were
keeping that car
until the wheels fell off.
Yeah, um, I'm kind of
between cars right now.
( Coughing )
i don't know how you can
smoke those things.
I'd be afraid
of getting cancer,
emphysema or something.
Oh, congrats, Kimmy.
You know, is there anything
that you're not scared of?
Hmm?
"Is there anything
you're not scared of?"
Jordin, right?
You must be
the cousin.
Yes.
Angela told me
everyone's name
the other day at the office,
- but i--
- oh, um, rae.
You have
a lovely home, rae.
Oh, it's not mine.
It's pop-pop's.
Pop-pop?
Oh, my grandfather.
We just
call him pop-pop.
( Laughs )
It's still lovely,
even if it's not yours.
( Cooing )
Did someone make
a stinky?
( Sniffs )
Yes, you did.
Oh yes,
you did, honey.
Natural part of life, dear.
Is it natural to stick
your nose in his ass?
Not in.
Motherly duties.
You'll know them well
soon enough.
Look, he's not gonna
cry all night, is he?
Once he's fed and in bed,
he won't make a peep.
Don't worry,
he won't ruin your party.
( Chuckles )
that's not what I meant.
Do you have
any extra blankets?
Um...
Downstairs, first hall closet
should be nothing but blankets.
Thanks.
Hard to believe
we were that young.
Yeah.
I'm--
I'm happy
for you, Angie.
Thanks.
( Frame clatters )
( Clears throat )
thanks for doing this...
For me.
Sure.
( Both chuckle )
( Clears throat )
Excuse me, ladies.
What do you want,
smokey?
Um, this is
a party, right?
( Laughing )
- ( Loud cheering )
- fucking party!
( Rock music playing )
( Gagging sounds )
That was really fun.
I've never done that--
oh my god.
Are you okay?
Looks like we've got a bit
of a lightweight in our midst.
Shut up, Elise.
Do you need
a trash can, dear?
- No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
- ( Distant bang )
Just had one of those
"almost" moments.
- ( Distant explosion )
- ( women gasp )
What was that?
Probably just some hunters.
Hunters?
Oh, Kimmy.
You have to remember
the hunters.
( Deb laughing )
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Oh, come on, Kimmy.
- Nope.
- tents in kerr park,
hunters in the distance...
( Laughing )
...your soaking wet panties.
I didn't pee my panties.
I swear, I didn't.
- I didn't.
- Angela: Jordin,
I swear she did.
I swear to god she did,
and it wasn't
the first time.
- ( Laughing )
- don't worry about it, Kimmy.
- It's okay.
- ( Bangs, clatters )
That wasn't hunters.
Is someone out there?
No way.
We are miles
from anyone.
I mean, it's probably
a raccoon, a possum,
- or something.
- That wasn't a possum.
Where the hell
are you going?
911!
( Laughing )
- ( Bangs loudly )
- ( women scream )
Ryan, you asshole!
Jerk! you probably
woke up Aidan!
Freakin' asshole.
Chase, why the hell did you
have to bring him here?
( Whispering )
Angie, I'm sorry.
Who is ready...
To get naked?
Hey, nobody wants to see
your tiny pecker.
- ( Laughs sarcastically )
- Angela: Get him out of here!
( Moaning )
Chase:
i will, just calm down
for like two seconds.
- ( Chattering )
- I wanted to see you.
You are not a guest.
You are a pest.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
( Slurring )
don't worry about me, okay?
Let's worry about this one.
How are you, beautiful?
Hey, you just
ignore him, okay?
He has every s.T.D.
Known to man.
And he is retarded,
to boot.
- Oh, retarded...
- Mm-hmm.
I keep thinking about it.
You know, not nerves just--
I just can't stop
thinking about how great
you're gonna look
in that tux.
( Drink spills )
- Rae: oh my god, Ryan!
- Oh shit.
- ( Sighs )
- I'm sorry. That shouldn't
have been there.
- Elise:
way to treat the party.
- This table is... not steady.
( Whispering )
it's okay, it's okay.
Rae.
Hi, chase.
- Been okay.
- Still working at Russell's?
Oh no, that was jobs ago,
but I'm going back to school.
- Nice.
- oh yeah, it's great.
It's community college,
right, rae?
Yeah.
How do you know
all that?
Angela:
my mother.
( Dance music playing )
Oo-oh!
Shit, man.
This is my jam.
Come on.
Dance with me, rae.
- No.
- come on, rae. Rae.
- "Oh Ryan."
- Ryan!
( All shouting )
All right.
You, back to the bar.
And leave you guys
up to whatever shenanigans,
tomfoolery, and/or hijinks
y'all have planned.
Hey, you know,
you're not even
supposed to see her
this early.
It's bad luck.
Do you still want
to marry me?
If you're lucky.
If you need me, I'll be
on the other side
of the tracks.
Behave.
All right...
I'd like to propose
a toast.
To...
Angela.
Because we're--
we're all gathered here
to celebrate...
A toast to--
well, you know.
To the future
Mrs. chase Harding.
We're so very happy
that you found each other,
and that you found a reason
to return to sinclair valley.
And even happier...
That your whorish vagina
is now under lock and key.
- Cheers.
- cheers.
So eloquent, lise.
I'd like to propose
a toast.
To those who couldn't
be here tonight.
Deb:
that's it, ladies.
I'm checking out
and checking on Aidan.
- Mmm.
- bed sounds like
a really good idea.
All right.
Come on, let's go.
Hmm?
- Well, one more
won't kill us.
- No.
Jeez.
( sighs )
( Coughs )
( Yawns )
( Coughing )
- Told you those things
were bad for you.
- Oh!
Jesus, Kimmy, you scared
the shit out of me.
Well, what are you
doing out here then?
( Coughing )
well, I wanted
some fresh air.
Elise:
looks like a storm.
Ugh. what's that smell?
Is that bleach?
What the fuck is that?
- Ew, Kimmy, no.
Don't touch it.
- Eww!
Go inside, go.
( Kimmy and Elise coughing )
God, it is way too early
for noise.
( Coughing )
way to go, Kimmy.
What are you guys
doing up?
There is something weird
going on out there.
- What?
- yeah, it's foggy.
- Oh, and it stinks...
- Mm-hmm.
...like bleach
or something.
( Coughing continues )
It's supposed to be
beautiful all weekend.
No, it's ugly.
Oh, and there were
these dead birds.
What?
( Deb screaming ) no-oo!
He's not breathing!
My baby can't breathe!
Don't you fucking touch him!
- I'll call 911.
- ( Keys jingling )
Don't just stand there
like an idiot, Kimmy.
Go with her.
- ( Car starting )
- uh, I need my coat.
Forget about
your fucking coat, go!
- I can't dial out.
- What's going on?
- Deb, Deb, hold on.
- ( Car driving away )
What are you
waiting for? Go!
- Where's she going?
- ( Coughs ) it's too late.
What? she left alone?
I mean, why didn't
somebody go with her?
Well, why didn't you?
I was calling 911.
Yeah, and?
It's busy.
I couldn't even get through.
Will somebody please tell me
what's going on?
I can't get a single bar.
No 3g, nothing.
Rae, what service
works out here?
I don't know.
I don't have a cellphone.
No, Elise, you still cannot
smoke in here.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
We got dead birds
and dead babies.
I think that smoke
is the least of our concern.
Dead babies?
( Violent coughing )
Jesus, Kimberly,
is that necessary?
Will somebody please tell me
what the fuck is going on?
Nobody knows what the fuck
is going on, jordin!
Don't you think somebody would
have answered you if we did?
Jordin, we don't know
what's going on, okay?
None of us do.
I mean, right now
we just--
- what are we gonna do? Hmm?
- Look, I don't know what
we need to do, okay?
I'm just thinking maybe
we're overreacting
a little here.
( Groans )
Let's check the news.
( TV humming )
Disaster strikes
the sinclair valley.
A train wreck
early this morning
has spilled an unknown number
of highly toxic...
...elements are not known
at this time...
- ( Static )
- ...Contagious.
Our experts... advising
all of the sinclair valley--
- oh my god, the train.
- ...Possible.
- All sinclair valley
residents...
- ( Static )
...remain at home
and stay clear
of the contaminated area.
Oh, are you
fucking kidding me?
You gotta fix it.
They have to tell us.
Kimberly:
did anybody try
their cells?
I don't--
i don't have any signal.
Very important information
for all sinclair valley
residents.
- ( Static )
- ...The wreck have
contaminated each...
...elements in the air.
But it is now believed...
- Oh god.
- The specific details
as local authorities are...
...worse injuries
and several fatalities,
all related to the toxic--
highly toxic--
what does that mean?
- ( Coughing, bangs )
- ( women yelp )
Please.
- God, it's Ryan!
- Open the door.
- Rae: is there blood?
- ( Lock clicks )
- What are you doing?
- ( Panicked breathing )
( Stammering )
look, I don't want him
getting in here
if he's infected.
He'll get us all sick.
What?
( Stammering )
the reporter, he said
the air is toxic!
That doesn't mean
that he's sick.
He looks
pretty sick to me!
( All gasp )
( Ryan coughing )
Open the door.
What's wrong with him?
I don't know.
Get away from that door.
I'm trying
911 again.
Elise:
where is he?
( Banging )
Rae:
oh my god.
Don't you dare
open that door.
Look, I am just as scared
of this shit as you are,
but we have to help him.
What if that shit is
some sort of fucked-up virus,
- disease or--
- what?
It is really hard
to breathe out there.
And it killed those birds.
Look, terrorists could
have gotten him sick,
what? terrorists?
Are you kidding me?
It's still busy.
Angela:
Kimmy, Kimmy.
Downstairs there's
a basement door.
Go make sure
that it's locked.
- Okay.
- now!
Are we really gonna
leave him out there?
I mean, are you serious?
What if it was chase?
Chase is not stupid enough
to be out in that shit, okay?
Wherever he is,
I'm sure he's fine.
I don't--
I don't want him in here.
I don't want
anyone to die. Okay?
Not even an asshole
like Ryan.
But if he's sick,
I don't want him in here.
I'd rather him out there.
Jordin:
you'd let him die?
Look, you weren't
out there, okay?
There is something
in the air and it is--
it's not natural.
Where is he?
It looks
like death out there.
( Water running )
It's getting
really hazy out there.
Can't see anything.
Rae:
there's something
out there.
What's out there?
Hey. hey,
look what I found.
Great.
Did you find
the antique TV that they
plug into, as well?
What?
They don't work
on plasma tvs, Kimmy.
Oh.
There are nicer ways.
( Rattling )
Where did you
find this, by the way?
Closet downstairs.
Uh, what room?
I mean, did you
check all the rooms?
It's back!
TV, TV!
Reporter:
I'm getting new information
coming in that
the chemical elements in the...
Are highly deadly,
and residents should
stay insi...
- ( Static )
- ...Windows and doors locked.
Affected areas include
all residences
from Clifton county
out to 23 1/2 road.
That's like
the entire valley.
...inside with the windows
and doors locked...
Sinclair valley
fire and rescue squads
are making their way...
-( Static )
- ...Safety.
Wait for the rescue workers.
Under no circumstances...
Residents leave their home.
- ( Static )
- ( beeping )
No no no no no,
you have to fix it.
They have to tell us
what to do.
He just told us
He said stay inside.
Oh my god.
Maybe we should
go look for him.
No. no, no one's
touching the door.
Okay?
There's dangerous
contaminates outside.
We'd end up
just like him.
And we'll be safe in here?
They said to close
the windows.
I heard them say that we
should close the windows.
I think we should
do more than close
the windows.
What are you
talking about?
We should seal 'em up
somehow.
Oh, what are you,
a survivalist now?
Did you learn that
in community college, rae?
- Where are you going?
- To help.
Okay.
- Okay.
- what do we got?
Hmm.
All right.
So...
Do you think--
do you think that this
is all for real?
I mean, do you think
that we're overreacting
with this crap?
I don't know.
( Sighs )
but Ryan-- I...
Yes.
Ooh! oh, help me
with these.
Yes, yes, yes.
I think that's it.
Goddamn terrorists.
Really?
Who else would blow up
a train besides fucking a-rabs
that hate America?
You mean like--
like al-qaeda?
In the valley?
That's why they call
them terrorists, Kimmy.
They can strike anywhere
at any time.
Well, maybe someone
should be watching the TV
for when it comes back.
Let's start
in the kitchen.
Um, look, I'll be
up there in a minute.
Okay.
What are you doing?
( Stammering )
i was just-- you know--
( chuckling )
Yours?
I had one just like this...
In college.
I gave it up to goodwill,
though, when I got
my career started.
( Stammering )
it's just temporary.
It's not like
it's permanent.
I'm not actually--
it's not like
I'm living here.
Do you remember
Haley's dog missie?
I mean,
she loved that dog.
We all did, I guess.
It was so dumb.
It was just
the dumbest dog.
You remember?
I mean, you know,
we treated it like
a normal dog.
We petted it
and fed it,
took it to the vet
when it got sick, but...
We all knew--
everybody knew
that there was no hope.
And then one day
missie got hit by a car.
So sad, right?
No. nobody cried.
We didn't even
blink an eye.
It's not that
we weren't sad.
We didn't care.
Everyone expected
that dumb dog to die
a stupid death,
so when it did--
( chuckles )
no, don't cry
over that.
Nobody cares
when a dumb bitch
fails at life.
Save your tears for something
that matters, rae.
A loser will always
be a loser.
( Door closes )
Hey, do you think
Deb and her baby are okay?
It's been like two hours.
I'm sure
that they're fine.
The hospital
isn't that far.
- It's like 15 miles.
- They took the car.
Do you think
this is like...
A disease breakout
or something?
Like with that movie
with the little monkey,
- or something?
- I don't know.
I don't think so, though.
But how do you know?
I mean, I have this headache.
Ebola virus symptoms
start with a headache.
They do?
Elise:
come on.
Ebola?
Headache, nausea,
and then you start
to throw up.
But it's not just
regular vomit.
You puke up everything
in your stomach
until there's nothing left.
And then you don't stop.
You just keep
dry-heaving anyway.
Gross.
And then finally,
you start to throw up
something else.
( Gulps )
Pieces of your
own stomach lining.
No, stop.
Stop.
God, I'm gonna
be sick.
What the hell
are you guys doing?
We're sealing up
the windows.
I just can't believe
that this is happening.
I mean, I'm supposed
to be getting married.
( Scoffs )
Okay, Kimmy, come on.
Let's finish up this window.
( Groans )
I think I need
to take a second.
Uh, hello?
Help, please.
Help me.
We're almost done.
( Crying )
( Gags )
( Air blowing )
( Clicks )
( Rustling plastic )
( Clears throat )
Need any help?
( Sighs )
I thought you crawled
off somewhere and died.
- ( Rae chuckles )
- ( air conditioner whirring )
Um...
This should be
the last of the windows.
Hey, lise, did you get
any of the--
Elise:
um, so...
Should I fill
the sinks with water?
I saw it
on some TV show.
No, no.
There's a cistern out back.
I mean, we should
have plenty of water.
You sure?
Look, we are not
gonna be here
that long.
I mean, the rescue teams
are probably on their way.
Doesn't your grandfather
have a dog?
Yeah, but pop-pop
always takes riggs
with him when
he goes fishing.
Elise:
yes, but isn't there
a doggy--
- doggy door!
- Yes.
( Kimmy coughing )
( Sighs )
( Heavy coughing )
- ( Wheezing )
- ( sizzling )
( Knocking )
( Whispers )
( Groaning )
( Wheezing )
( Coughing )
( Thuds )
( Coughs, pukes )
( Sobbing )
( Faintly )
Angie?
Angie, it's locked.
An-an--
it's locked, Angie.
( Rattles )
Angie?
( Crying )
Where's Kimberly?
Kimmy!
( Both coughing )
- Rae: get her in.
Get her in here.
- Oh my god.
Elise:
oh my god.
Rae:
be careful, be careful
of her arms.
Okay?
Okay, all right.
One, two, three.
- Is she okay?
- Does she look
fucking okay?!
You let her
back in here?!
She's gonna
infect us all.
Rae:
she's your friend.
We don't know
what this is.
She could make us all sick.
- You don't know.
- Rae: Exactly!
We don't know.
We don't know anything.
She's still
breathing.
Oh god, she'll be okay.
She'll be okay.
( Crying )
- She'll be okay.
- ( Wheezing )
Elise: rae.
Maybe we should move her
to another room.
No, I don't think
that we should move her.
I think that we should
let her rest until they come.
What if no one
knows we're here?
They know.
Of course they know.
There's other people
out here.
Pop-pop knows.
Where-- where is he?
I don't know.
- ( Groans )
- I don't-- I don't--
- ( groans )
- they'll come.
Lisey, listen,
they'll come.
they'll come, okay?
Yeah, but how
do you know, rae?
I guess I don't
know, Angela.
That were out here
when this thing started.
( Heavy coughing )
Lisey, are you okay?
I just-- there's just
something in my throat.
( Coughs )
Do you think
it's contagious?
We don't know that.
We shouldn't panic.
Okay?
I mean, this--
this probably happens
more often than we realize.
I mean, you saw the TV.
Someone's coming.
They have a plan.
Yeah, but why should
we take chances?
Why should we assume
that it's not contagious?
You know,
and sit here breathing
some shit-spewing
virus into our lungs.
You don't know, rae!
( Sighs )
like ebola.
( Laughs nervously )
We don't know that.
Look, all that we know
is that it has something to do
with the train accident,
okay?
So we have no choice
but to just wait.
Nobody goes outside.
Okay?
Yeah, the train--
the train--
it could have been
carrying a disease.
Scientists, they work
on diseases all the time.
I doubt the disease
travels by train.
Oh, I'm sorry, Elise.
Are you some sort of viral
transportation expert now?
- You know what, Angela?
Could you just please--
- Angie, in all seriousness,
if it was
a contagious disease...
We'd all be infected
by now.
You don't know that.
You don't know.
( Coughing )
Do we have any medicine?
What, like anti-fog medicine?
Let's go raid
the bathrooms.
All right.
( Gunshot )
- What was that?
- ( Laughing )
nothing, I'm sure.
Maybe it was one
of those hunters.
Jordin, honey,
if there were any of those
dumb-ass, inbred rednecks
still out there,
they'd all be dead by now.
( Coughs )
Well, it's not much.
At all.
Hey, don't use it all.
We might need
to ration that.
I know.
My throat's just
a little dry.
Honestly, we might--
we don't even know
if it's any good.
Then why did you
even bring it out here?
( Coughs )
Ugh, I think this stuff
might be bad.
Let me see that.
It burns a little
when it goes down,
but I think
it might work.
- Here.
- um, I think maybe
we should use different spoons.
You know...
- Just in case.
- Mmm.
( Wheezing )
Come on, Kimmy.
Come on.
This will make you
feel better.
Come on, this will
make you feel better.
( Wheezes, coughs )
Elise:
oh my god.
Angela: what?
( Sizzling )
Angela:
ew, fucking ew.
I guess we don't have
to worry about
feeding the fish anymore.
Maybe we should
flush 'em.
I'm not fucking
touching them.
( Gasps )
it's ringing!
( Sighs )
it's just a recording.
- ( Sighs )
- ( beeps )
Male voice:
All lines are
currently occupied
in the sinclair valley area.
Please remain calm.
Do not, under any
circumstances, go outside.
At this time, rescue teams
are making their way
through the valley.
All lines--
well, I guess that means
that they know we're out here.
Could have been
recorded hours ago.
They said stay dry.
So it's gotta be
some sort of...
Chemical reaction
or something--
oh god, great.
Community college lessons.
High school.
It's pretty basic
chemistry, actually.
I'm sorry,
i wasn't such a nerd
in high school, okay?
Elise:
where the fuck
are the rescue teams?
Maybe no one's coming.
No.
They're coming.
And I'm sure
that they're checking
every single house.
That could take forever.
Yeah, what do you--
what do you suggest
we do then, rae?
We wait.
They'll come.
( Coughing )
( Coughing continues )
We wait, ladies.
And that's all
that we can do.
Elise:
how's Kimmy?
She's fine.
She's sleeping
peacefully...
For now.
Angela:
wish I was.
( Elise clears throat )
oh god.
I think I could
fall asleep
standing up.
( Rae laughs )
I don't think that's such
a good idea right now.
What?
Look, we were--
we were up late
last night partying
and, uh...
It's not like we're going
anywhere anytime soon.
What's the big deal
with a little nap?
I don't think last night's
what's making us so sleepy.
Nobody's coming.
It takes time, jordin.
They're coming.
I'm gonna go
lay down for a little.
I'm exhausted
and I'm getting married.
No one has a problem
with that, do they?
I'm with you, rae.
I'm tired as fuck,
but there's no way
that I'm gonna be
another dead baby
not waking up.
( Coughs )
- Whoa.
- whoa.
- Whoa. are you okay?
- Oh wow.
- Are you okay?
- Mm-hmm, oh, yeah.
I think I was just
sitting down too long.
- We just need some coffee.
- Yes.
Okay.
Rae:
and some sugar,
lots of sugar.
- Elise: okay.
- And make sure you brew
with the bottled water.
( Distorted breathing )
This is all your fault.
You should have been
watching the road.
No. no.
( Sizzles )
I want
my baby sister back.
Fucking murderer.
No, no!
( Gunshot )
( Sizzling )
( Coughing )
Is it morning?
I think something's wrong.
Kimmy?
You okay?
Oh, you're fucking kidding me.
( Wheezing )
Rae: Kimmy?
Kimmy?
Has she...?
- ( Choking )
- Kimmy, it's gonna be okay.
- ( Gasping )
- maybe we should get her
back to the couch.
Okay. okay, Kimmy,
we're gonna move you
to the big, comfy couch.
It's okay.
No, Kimmy!
( Rae and Elise grunting )
Put her on the couch.
Move. Come on.
( Choking stops )
Kimmy? Kimmy?
Kimmy, what is it?
Kimmy,
what is it?
You can tell me.
It's okay.
( Crying )
Kimmy.
- ( Puking )
- ( screaming )
( Gurgling )
Somebody help me!
- Help me!
- ( Choking )
( Crying )
Is she...?
Dead.
No. no.
God, she's gonna die.
I can't hear anything.
( Sobbing )
No.
( Blows )
( Coughs )
( Gasping )
one, two, three.
One, two, three!
Breathe, Haley, breathe!
( Sobbing )
What did you just say?
I was just trying
to save her.
( Wailing )
I'm sorry.
We're all gonna die.
You can't think
like that.
It's been
over 24 hours, rae.
No rescue team,
no one at all.
It's just us.
No one will come.
- Someone will.
- We're dead.
( Screams )
Shut the fuck up!
- ( Sobbing )
- rae: Elise.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
It's okay, come on.
Elise:
I'm sorry.
( Coughing )
- Elise: she tried
to tell me something.
- Rae: What?
Kimmy, she tried
to tell me something,
and i--
and I couldn't hear her.
( Sobbing )
i couldn't hear her.
I didn't understand.
Oh, Elise.
( Cellphone ringing,
buzzing )
Oh god.
Oh, chase.
( Crying )
oh god, it's so good
to hear your voice.
Please, come get me.
( Coughing )
I miss you.
Do they still know
we're here?
Angela:
tell them that we're here.
Please tell them
I'm here.
Please.
Please, tell them
that we're trapped.
Tell them we're dying, chase.
Please, baby.
Baby, you're breaking up.
Baby, I can't hear you.
Tell them we're here.
Hello, chase?
Angie.
The battery's dead.
It didn't charge.
Angela, the power's out.
Angela, take it out.
Oh god!
You're covered
with blood.
Oh...
Please.
( Crying )
The power's out.
Angela, the power is out.
I know!
I heard you the first
fucking three times!
My lungs are burning.
( Coughing )
My eyes are burning.
It's been over a day
and no one's come for us!
And that
fucking bitch, Deb--
she took our fucking car!
She probably didn't
tell anyone
that we're here.
We're all gonna fucking die!
Calm down!
Just calm down.
We're not gonna die.
Okay?
We didn't go outside.
It's probably
clearing up.
We just need to hold out
a little longer.
- Okay?
- "hold out"?
Fucking hold out?
( Coughing )
Kimmy was fucking holding out
real well, rae.
- ( Crying )
- ( coughing )
( Rattling )
We ju--
look, we just--
we just gotta
focus on the basics.
You know, like maybe--
maybe we should eat...
( Sniffles )
something.
"Eat something"?
You cannot be serious.
"Eat something."
How can you eat?
( Sobbing )
after...
( Screaming )
( Clatters )
( Coughing )
( Gasps )
my eyes are burning.
I have Kimmy
all over me.
Come on.
Shh.
She's burning my skin.
Okay, shh.
It's gonna be okay.
We're all burning.
- We're all burning.
- She's burning me.
Lisey, we're all burning.
It's not Kimmy,
it's the--
I wanna get her off.
I want to wash it off.
No no no, honey.
I don't think
that we should--
I don't think that
that's a good idea.
- I think--
- I don't want her on me!
( Wailing )
i don't want her on me.
Okay.
shh, shh.
okay.
Okay, lise.
Lisey, okay.
Okay.
You hungry, jordin?
Jordin?
Someone's out there.
What?
Where?
i don't see anything.
Angela:
you're still jealous
he picked me over you,
aren't you?
What?
Is this about chase?
You never wanted me
to be happy,
because you never
got over him dumping you.
That's ridiculous.
No, it's not ridiculous.
- I don't think it's ridiculous.
- Oh, Angela, there is
more important things to be
worried about right now.
You are so unhappy
with your boring
failure of a life.
You had to ruin
my perfect one.
This has nothing
to do with you and me.
It's all about
you and me.
Do you see him now?
Rae:
get down, get down!
( Thumping )
( Crying )
( Whispering )
what if it's the rescue team?
With a gun?
( Gasps )
( Groans )
( Screaming )
( Crying )
- ( Shower running )
- Elise?
Both:
one, two, three.
( Both cough )
Elise?
( Gags )
( Groans )
what the fuck happened?
Some sort
of reaction. I--
( crying )
The chemicals absorbed
into her skin or something.
And the water...
( Coughing, gagging )
Must be some sort of--
someone should turn
the water off.
( Rae gasps )
oh, jordin.
Why are you
holding a knife?
Jordin?
The fruit...
Tasted rotten. I...
I wanted to cut off
the bad parts.
Yeah, but that's
a big fucking knife.
Angela:
oh god!
God...
( Footsteps )
( Whispering )
jordin,
did you open the door?
Jordin.
I know
i shouldn't stare.
What the fuck did you do?
( Yelling )
don't fucking touch me!
- Shh.
- ( Clattering )
( Footsteps )
( Glass breaking )
( Clattering )
( Drawers opening, closing )
( Whispering )
get the gun.
- Get the gun.
- What?
- ( Shouting )
- what the fuck?!
Get off me!
Please!
I'm not--
I'm not here--
I'm not here
to hurt you.
What the fuck
are you doing?
( Stammering )
i just-- I just want
the same thing as you--
why are you breaking shit?
I apologize.
I'm a little under the weather.
( Laughs nervously )
( Coughing )
I'm sorry.
- I was just looking
for supplies.
- Don't move!
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Please, I'm just hungry.
I need some rest...
Away from...
The haze.
What the hell were you
doing out there?
I was hunting...
With chewy, my dog.
We hunt rabbits sometimes.
Well, look,
look at my rifle.
So where's your dog now?
Is he still out there?
He, uh...
He...
I'm sorry.
Man: so...
Does anyone...
Happen to have
a cellphone?
( Angela coughs )
I always prided
myself on being
prepared for anything.
I have a bomb shelter,
I got army supplies
and I got gallons
of water.
How do you prepare
for this?
You can't.
( Crying )
Chewy was--
he was in pain, my dog.
I'm sorry.
Howard.
my name.
Rae.
and she's Angela.
Angela.
Where are your clothes,
Howard?
Uh...
Okay.
I know this looks
a little ridiculous
right now,
but I had to get out of those
as quick as I could.
I was starting to sweat.
And you do not want this stuff
on you if you're wet.
You gotta stay dry.
Weren't you wearing
a gas mask?
Yeah, that's the only thing
that kept me alive out there,
but the plastic
started to melt.
It's no good anymore,
not enough to get me home.
And I'm pretty sure
the filter's shot.
I started tasting
the chemicals.
And then I saw this place.
- I'm jordin.
- Jesus, jordin!
Can we put
a fucking bell
on her or something?
Nice to meet you,
jordin.
Howard.
Uh...
Is anybody hungry?
( Spoons scraping )
( Scoffs )
How did you
even get in?
The door
in the back
was open.
I came up
through the basement.
( Scoffs )
I was just gonna go
yell at Kimmy
for not locking the door
like I told her to.
Hey, Angie, maybe you
should let Howard
- have his gun back--
- no!
It's just really comforting.
That's it.
It's okay.
I fired the last
of my shells hours ago.
Why?
Why did I fire it?
( Sighs )
Um, last time--
to attract attention.
Get some help.
And the other times?
Before the cloud...
( Coughing )
Hunting...
with my dog.
He ran into the lake,
after a bird
or something.
I had to put him down.
I had no choice.
Rae:
it's okay, Howard.
We know exactly
what that feels like.
I have to use
the bathroom.
I won't disturb Elise.
You ladies wouldn't
happen to have
- any batteries?
- Why?
I came across...
This.
( Coughing )
oh god.
Maybe-- maybe
in the basement.
( Laughing, coughing )
( Angela clears throat )
One sec.
What the hell
are you doing?
For you.
Congratulations.
Go ahead, open it!
Go on.
Rae!
I'm jealous.
And...
Just so you could
use him right away.
That's very thoughtful.
I'm supposed
to be getting married.
Don't give up yet,
kiddo.
I may know a way
out of this mess.
You can get us
out of here?
Maybe.
How?
Down the road,
there's a car.
- It's broken down, but--
- and you can fix it?
I looked it over briefly.
I think I know what's
wrong with it.
With the right tools,
it shouldn't be a problem.
The basement.
( Stammers )
pop-pop, he has like his own
personal warehouse
down there.
How far is the car?
Well, SUV, technically.
It's just down the road.
I can make it.
Jordin:
you won't make it.
( Screaming )
Radio dj:
All right, folks,
joining me now
of the sinclair valley
rescue team.
( Radio fades in and out )
...have any idea what
kind of chemicals we're
dealing with at this time?
Captain Carter:
We're still unclear
on the exact chemicals--
- ( static )
- no, it was an accident.
It was an accident.
I didn't--
he said it wasn't loaded!
Preacher:
then, when Jesus came--
- ( static )
- ( Carter, distorted )
there were a few deaths
the train carried
very few passengers.
We haven't come across
any fatalities from any
valley residents.
Where do you
think you're going?
This is all your fault.
You scared me, you freak!
( Music playing on radio )
Captain Carter:
We're in the middle
of a massive
cleanup effort right now.
And the most important thing
was that we were able
to evacuate the valley
rather quickly.
- ( Distortion )
- evacuated?
They forgot about us
no. no no no no.
It's a mistake.
Captain Carter:
We are not allowing
anyone else into this area.
It's just
far too hazardous.
They don't even know
we're here, do they?
They have to.
They'll come.
Man:
you'll get all choked up.
Radio dj:
Thank you again, captain,
for joining us.
We'll check back with you
in a little bit.
Of course we like to have
an open phone line
if you have anything
to report.
- We're dead.
- No, we're not.
We're not gonna die,
jordin.
What-- what about firemen?
What about rescue workers?
They're still looking,
okay?
( Shouting )
there's no way--
no possible way--
that they could have
checked every house!
Tell me
you're still coming.
Tell me.
Angie.
They'll come.
No one's coming.
That's not true,
jordin.
Someone will come.
Not before we're dead.
That's not true!
Rescue workers have to
check every house.
- They have to be sure.
- They sounded
pretty fucking sure
on the radio!
We're still here!
There are dead people
all around us!
Come and save us!
We're still here,
all alone,
and we need your help!
( Softly )
easy, jordin.
It's not a two-way radio.
We're gonna die
without your help.
Jordin.
( Static )
They can't hear you.
So now you get it?
( Static continues )
So you want
to kill yourself?
There's plenty
to go around.
Jordin, look,
there's no need
for desperate measures
just yet.
Okay?
I mean, we're all
still alive.
We are?
Can I have them back now,
please, rae?
I asked nicely, rae.
I even said "please."
Don't make me
ask you again.
No, jordin.
I'm not letting you
give up.
I'm sorry.
We're all dead,
anyway.
No. no,
we're not dead yet.
Chase'll come.
He'll come for me.
- Chase is dead.
- ( Angela sobs )
No, he's not.
Don't say that.
Chase is fine, Angie.
Okay?
I'm sure of it.
He's gonna come for us.
- I can still get married?
- Yeah.
Can't marry
a dead man.
Fuck you,
you crazy bitch!
- ( Grunting ) stop!
- Oh my god. Stop!
Stop it, you guys!
- Stop it!
- ( Grunting continues )
( Angela shouts )
Oh, my nose!
You fucking whore!
- ( Gasping breaths )
- ( Sizzling )
( Breathing shakily )
Jordin.
Jordin, jordin,
just calm down, okay?
( Screaming )
No!
Rae:
we'll help you, okay?
Just--
- no! no!
- ( Static )
Oh my god!
Shit! Basement.
- Basement, come on.
- ( Jordin screaming )
( Air whooshing )
( Both coughing )
Angela:
it's seeping in.
It's seeping in.
( Coughing, crying )
Maybe we should patch up
around that window.
What's the point?
What?
( House creaking )
Remember when we were kids,
we'd have sleepovers
here in the summer?
We used to fight
over the top bunk.
I guess there could be
worse places...
And worse people.
I'm sorry I burned
your pixie jam doll
in the backyard.
You burned her?
( Laughing )
( Coughing )
I didn't know how
to get rid of the evidence.
( Laughing )
I looked for her
for like a year.
I'm really sorry.
I'm really sorry,
too, rae.
For what?
For chase.
I lied to him.
I stole him
away from you.
No, ang.
Chase is
a grown man and--
I seduced him.
You what?
That weekend you went
to Vegas with Elise,
we went out--
oh god--
to fucking applebee's,
for Christ's sakes.
Don't worry,
it was really
against his will.
Had to get him
good and drunk.
When I thought that
he was wasted enough,
I told him that
you went to Vegas
to meet up with Tyler.
Tyler Jarvis?
( Scoffs )
i haven't seen him
since high school.
He never told me
any of this.
His heart was broken
and my bed was open.
You are so selfish, Angie.
You are
a selfish cunt.
What did you say?
Even now...
When all your friends
are dying...
The only person that
you care about is you.
How did you
expect me to act
when you killed
my sister?
I did not kill her.
- Who was driving the car, rae?
- It was an accident.
Yeah, whatever helps
you sleep at night,
you murderer!
( Yells )
( Both grunting )
( Shouting, grunting )
Ow! ow!
- Ow!
- holy shit!
Stop, stop.
Wait.
( pants )
Oh my god.
- ( Angela shrieks )
- ( groaning )
I'm still alive.
I'm getting married
tomorrow.
to my fiance.
( Clears throat )
I-- i--
i have a future.
I have chase.
( Clears throat )
You have nothing, rae.
You have nobody.
Nothing changes.
Nobody cares
if you die.
( Rustling )
( Rae groans )
( Coughing )
( Grunting, coughing )
( Coughing intensifies )
( Choking )
( Trees creaking )
( Angela grunts )
( Coughs )
( Engine sputtering )
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on!
Start!
( Screams )
( Glass shatters )
- ( Panicked breathing )
- ( sizzling )
( Puking )
( Splattering )
( Gagging )
( Chokes )
Haley.
Oh my god.
They're leaving you,
rae.
Leaving me?
Time to go,
or you're gonna
miss them.
( Coughs )
( Inhales deeply,
mutters )
( Screams )
( Engine idling )
What was that?
( Faintly )
she's still breathing.
Came from over there.
Can you hear me?
We need to get her
back to the truck.
( Heart monitor beeping )
- ( Pages turning )
- ( chase grunting )
- Hey.
- chase.
Yeah, hey.
How you feeling?
( Mumbles )
I'm sorry.
( Sighs )
I wanted to...
I wanted to
help you guys.
I tried to go back,
you know,
but they wouldn't let me
past the barricades.
You know, and I told them
you were still out there,
but they swore to me
that they checked.
You're the only one
that made it out.
Hey.
Are we gonna be okay?
Yeah. yeah.
We're gonna be okay,
all right?
You hungry?
- Yeah?
- yeah.
Cool.
i mean, not-- not that.
( Laughs )
There's burger joint
across the street.
- Sound good?
- Yes.
Be right back, okay?
Okay.
( Chase sighs )
I'll be right back.
I promise.
Ms. strano?
You are awake.
Oh my.
Sincerest apologies.
My name's Doug.
Doug robertson.
I work
for baier incorporated.
We're here to, uh...
Clean up
this whole mess.
- You did this?
- ( Scoffs )
Well, I would argue,
actually,
an extremely negligent
and lazy train operator
caused this accident.
But yes, we are
the manufacturer
of these chemicals
that, uh--
well, now those chemicals--
they were never meant
to be mixed together.
Baier corp, we always
go through the most...
Proper and well-researched
safety techniques.
So if you'll just
sign your name here, please,
we're gonna take care
of everything else.
Everything's gonna
be just fine.
Rae?
You know, at baier corp,
we're fully aware
that money can't replace
some of the things
that you lose in life.
Doesn't mean we won't
provide you financial
compensation, anyhow--
you know, try to get
your life back together,
piece by piece.
You know,
at baier corp...
We apologize
from the bottom
of our hearts
for all this pain
and suffering you've
had to endure.
I mean, I can't even
imagine what you must
be going through right now.
( Heart monitor beeping
loudly )
( Faintly )
everything's gonna be
just fine.
( Heart monitor beeping
quickly )
But if you
just sign your name,
we're gonna
take care of you,
your loved ones--
- god damn it!
- ( Yelling )
( Heart monitor flatlines )
( Blood splattering,
choking )
I'm just trying
to help you.
I'm just trying to help.
( Emphatically )
fuck you.
( Soft violin playing )
( Rock music playing )
♪ Never turn
your back on me ♪
♪ never turn away
♪ why don't you want
to believe ♪
♪ I will never
leave you ♪
♪ you say you won't leave me
♪ but I say I don't care
♪ I'll never lie again
♪ you'll never love me again
♪ you may think
I am a liar ♪
♪ thinking you're
the one who prayed ♪
♪ in all your dreams
I'm there. ♪
( Sizzling )