Whew. Good job.
- [laughs]
- Thanks.
So on our TV show,
- will it show us
- having sex?
Oh, yeah, like, a lot.
Yeah.
I guess I feel
two ways about that.
I mean, I think
it's very important
to show two women...
I don't know...
Being casually intimate
with each other.
But also, like, it's us,
- and we're, like,
- real people.
We're a couple.
Yeah.
Well, but if
we don't do it,
then it's like
no actual lesbians
are on TV having sex
with other women,
and then there's
no women on TV
also, like,
- having sex with
- other women period.
- I mean, like,
- maybe that happens,
But then, like,
or they both die.
one of them dies,
- Like they're warlords,
- and then they die,
Or they, like,
and then they die,
sleep with a man,
- or they're, like,
- at school, and they die.
- They are - an art professor,
- And they die.
Was she a professor?
Anyway, my point is
I just want us to live.
[music playing]
- CAMERON: You know - what else we should
- Talk about
Is that when we drove
RHEA: Mm-hmm.
out here, we had...
- We drove two cars - in tandem with
- Walkie-talkies.
- And we pulled off
- At a scenic...
- Like, in Utah?
Where we in Utah?
Who can ever tell?
- Somewhere scenic,
- and then this car
- Drove up behind...
- Third car.
- To be in this rest area.
- Indeed.
And then two dudes
got out of it.
And they were like,
on your walkies,
"Hey, we heard you
so we got off here,
to meet you."
and we wanted
And we were like,
- "We're gonna
- get killed here."
"We're gonna go."
I also wonder who had
a scarier surprise,
- us...
- Us or them?
- Or them?
- Were they were like,
- "These seem like women - that might be
- Interesting."
- "Oh, check out
- these chicks."
- "Let's get off
- and meet these chicks,"
- And then there's
- just these haircuts.
So would you mind
if I weasel my way
- onto your show
- for 10 minutes?
Oh, my God. Maria,
we'd love to have you.
- Just yesterday,
- Rhea and I watched,
- Like, four hours
- of your videos.
- We only stopped
- 'cause my phone died,
- But then I just kept
- acting them out,
- 'cause I know them all
- by heart.
Ohh! So Rhea's
your girlfriend?
Yeah, and my cohost
on the show.
Oh, you're both comics.
Yikes.
I mean, I mean,
that's great.
There's, um...
a lot of built-in
competition and...
Oh, it doesn't come up!
- We never
- talk about that.
- I'm so excited to meet her.
- [cell phone rings]
- Oh, you know what?
- I gotta get this.
It's, uh, my mom.
I sing her to sleep
every night with a lullaby.
- [like rock ballad]
- ♪ Yeah... ♪
- Why didn't you
- introduce me?
I'm sorry.
She took a phone call.
- It's fine. - Just add it
- To the pile.
- Oh, my God.
- This is not that.
- She totally
- girlfriended me.
Not on purpose.
- People only
- ever talk to you.
"Thanks for
your show, Cameron."
inviting me to do
- "Oh, you're - such a great host,
- Cameron."
- "Hey, do you
- want the rest
- Of my peanut butter - banana milkshake,
- Cameron?"
I love peanut butter
banana milkshakes.
- And I'm
- lactose intolerant,
So the milkshakes are
kind of a fuck-you to me.
I am more than
just your girlfriend.
Agreed.
- I am my own person.
- Totally.
- And you are
- your own person.
And your person
my Whitesnake shirt.
is wearing
Well, I like how it
makes my arms look.
I can't even
under my jacket.
see your arms
But I'm still flexing.
- Men and
- women anymore?
- Don't you think
- that's stupid?
- Am I right?
- Danielle's coming tonight.
- Oh, great.
- So your agent
- Is gonna think you
- like Whitesnake.
I like Whitesnake.
Yeah, she's here to,
like, show an actor friend
- me doing stand-up
- so that, like,
- There's a potential
- opportunity.
- I don't know.
- I'm pretty sure
- I'm gonna be in a movie.
- Great.
- Can Kent even do
- less than 20 minutes?
- I've never
- seen him do it.
- I know.
- Give me your phone.
Come on. Nothing?
Do you foot the bill?
Nothing on double lights.
- And I know you're,
- like... you're wishing...
Hey, Danielle's here.
- Oh, my God.
- She's with...
Melina Marquez.
She didn't say
her actor friend was
- Melina Marquez
- is at our show.
- I love every movie
- she's ever been in.
You love her arms
she's been in.
in every movie
- It's like she's always
- wearing a Whitesnake t-shirt.
Okay, thanks.
- I'm Kent.
- You were fine.
[applause]
[gags]
- Okay.
- That seems extreme.
One more time
taking his time.
for Kent, you guys,
Oh, well,
- we got a great
- next comic for you.
- You guys
- are gonna love her.
- Let's hear it
- for Sam Jay!
- Sam Jay.
- [cheering]
Have a great show.
I am so glad
to be here, guys.
Cameron,
that shirt is dope.
I got that shirt
17 years old
when I was
- at a thrift store
- for $2.00,
And then I lost it
of my dresser
in the back
- until my mom
- found it.
- I cried when she
- shipped it to me.
And now some woman
in a sundress
is gonna
of you in it.
post a picture
Oh, my God.
about this shirt.
I don't even care
- I just care
- about Melina Marquez.
Just switch with me.
I... Okay. I mean...
[groans] God.
- Still technically
- my shirt.
Ah, so?
Oh, you look cute
in your little undie shirt.
- This is
- sexual harassment.
I am at work.
Well, you should sue me.
- Well, your dad's
- my lawyer.
Sounds like a real
conflict of interest.
Mm-hmm.
[sniffs]
That smells like you.
Veggie bacon.
- KENT: Dude,
- I'm telling you, man.
- It's like Pryor,
- then Louis C.K.,
Then you, dude.
You're right there.
Thank you.
Yo, Cam,
- why is your audience
- so chick-heavy?
Seriously, there were,
in the front row
like, three girls
- giving me
- resting bitch face.
Like the whole time
the 17-minute mark?
or after you hit
- Please don't say,
- "Bitch face."
Why not? You know what?
I'm glad you said that.
- Explain to me
- the rape fantasy then, okay?
- 'Cause women,
- you're in bed with 'em,
- They want you
- to call 'em bitch,
- But then, like,
- when you're anywhere else,
- You can't
- call 'em bitch anymore?
I don't even
unpacking this for you.
know how to begin
- I'm not gonna try.
- Please don't.
Just explain what the fuck
this is instead.
RHEA: Uh...
[laughs] Shit.
Rhea, you look
like James Dean.
Sorry for the insult.
Oh, God.
Why does Kent exist?
But seriously, though,
what is that poster?
- Oh, I had it made
- for the theater,
- 'cause we're more
- than just girlfriends.
We're comics
with our own show.
We're James Deans,
remember?
He doesn't even realize
that's a compliment.
It is a bit much.
I like it.
I'm gonna do time, okay?
- I just feel like
- Melina's here.
- Honestly,
- I'm thinking about it
As if it's an audition
for her next movie.
- Of course. - Why wouldn't
- A stand-up comic
Go into outer space
with Melina Marquez?
- Yeah, that's what
- I'm saying.
[cheering]
Hey. Hey,
sorry I'm late.
Oh, hey, Dave.
What the fuck is that?
- Hey, Rhea,
- I'm next, right?
Yep. Mm-hmm.
Oh, Bob,
do you know Dave?
No.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Mr. Bob Herzog.
- Give it up for Bob.
- [cheering]
Hello, you gorgeous,
soulless fuckers.
Cameron Esposito,
everybody.
She's kind of funny.
[laughter]
- Sexual assault's
- been in the news lately.
- I don't know
- if you've noticed.
If this year's
taught us anything,
it's that society
a woman's been raped
will not believe
unless 48 other women
by the same guy.
claim they were raped
Yeah.
That's why I only
raped 47 women.
[laughter]
Cut it off right there.
That is it.
- I'm gonna go
- to the bathroom.
- Okay.
- I'll be back.
Yeah. I got it in here.
- Okay.
- Like a certain person
That... I don't know...
not have heard of.
You might or might
[laughter]
Oh, I'm sorry.
We thought this
restroom.
was the women's
I am a woman.
Oh, of course. I...
- You're in
- a different shirt.
Yeah. It's my shirt.
They're all my shirts.
- Oh.
- I'm sorry.
Oh, no, no, no.
Come on in. Have a seat.
This is my office. Heh.
Yeah. So I'm so sorry
about earlier.
- I feel like
- I blew you off.
- I didn't know
- you were you.
- Oh, no,
- Cameron is right.
I'm too quiet.
- She would never - let herself
- Be ignored
Or seen
in her own clothes.
If I could tell myself
not to fall for people
that I would have
for the rest of my life,
to be telling jokes with
I wouldn't, you know?
Maybe one.
Six.
- But that's
- how I found myself
And a very good remedy
for U.T.I.s
and my comedic voice.
Wow.
I love your voice.
It's how I imagine
God's voice would sound.
Ohh.
There is no God,
but that's why you need
to speak up for yourself,
'cause you're super-duper.
You're fantastical, okay?
And, uh,
you can use my office.
- Pens are free.
- Great.
- What's the Wi-Fi
- password?
Uh, officepeepo.
Great.
Do you want to stay
for the rest?
Please no. Honestly,
I like comedy.
I don't think
RHEA: Ah, come on.
Oh, you're funny, though.
Thank you.
Hey, you wanna go home
and watch "Carol"?
- For the third time
- this week?
Okay, Therese.
[cell phone chimes]
Oh, God,
must be so hard.
being a stand-up
- I could never
- do that job.
Yeah. Babe, can you
drop me at the E.R.?
Some idiot broke his jaw
in a bar fight.
Sure. I'll spend time
without you.
with Cate Blanchett
Hey, are you okay?
Oh, yeah. I mean,
- I just got sirred
- in the bathroom,
- But I did get to talk
- to Maria, so...
- Sweet.
- It's okay.
I don't understand.
to use the word "bitch,"
If I'm not allowed
then what am I supposed
a crazy bitch?
to do when I meet
Ooh, I'm not okay
"crazy." Yeah.
with you using
Me either.
- I'm surrounded.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, man.
- Read the room.
- Uh, Maria,
- you are on next,
So what do you need
to get pumped up?
- Like French fries,
- waffles?
- Like, nothing.
- Water?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
- You know what?
- I'll take a water, Cam.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
Thank you.
We gotta go.
[cheering]
[Bob continues indistinctly]
you know,
off the top of my head.
- You guys are okay.
- I was awesome.
- Have a great night.
- Thank you so much.
[cheering]
Oh, guys.
Keep it going
for Bob Herzog.
Man.
Hoo.
Spicing up the stage.
- Spicy.
- Speaking of which,
- I'm wearing
- a different shirt.
- This shirt is also
- a little spicy,
'cause it used to be
on your body. We switched.
We switched, 'cause
Whitesnake is a band
that only Rhea
knows about apparently.
[laughter]
Right, Rhea?
Oh, I'm sorry.
- I'm just, uh, reliving
- past personal trauma
- Through the, uh,
- rape jokes
And rape conversation
tonight.
that's been going on
Oh, yeah. Yeah,
at this show.
a lot of rape
Not... That's
to say that,
the wrong way
- but onstage and
- conversationally.
Why is it that
the only dudes
that will talk
dude comics,
about rape are
- and then it's just,
- like, all the time?
- All the time.
- I mean, it is...
- It's dude comics,
- but then it's also,
Like, dude TV writers
and dude screenwriters
and dude book writers,
you know, writer writers.
Right, comic books,
all that stuff.
claymation,
All that stuff.
I think
is entertainment.
it's because rape
Yeah. I mean, what would
female characters be doing
- if they weren't
- getting raped?
Oh, um, wait.
- Marrying a man...
- Mm-hmm.
Or having a baby...
Yes.
- Or she marries
- a woman,
Then she cheats
with a man,
on the woman
- gets pregnant,
- has that baby,
- Kisses a woman,
- dies.
[laughter]
- Those are
- the stories.
- Those are all
- woman things.
[laughter]
- Oh, but you know
- what is not...
- Hmm?
- Just a woman thing?
- Rape.
- Oh, yeah.
- That's
- for everybody.
Rape is for everybody.
Kind of nice gift
to us all.
From statistically
mostly men.
Yeah, mostly men.
- Gotta bring that up
- at the end.
- You guys, - we got a great
- Final comic...
- [cheering]
- on the show tonight.
- You are
- gonna love her.
- She's a personal
- favorite of mine.
I admire her very much.
She's a real legend.
Let's hear it
Maria Bamford.
right now for
[cheering]
- [growled whisper]
- Gonna get you.
I'm getting you.
[laughter]
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I would love
with someone.
to sleep in
- That sounds
- so romantic.
I don't know.
But we are
fostering a rooster,
and he knows
his job, okay?
Is there anything better
than Maria Bamford?
No, not at all.
It's like the show's
bananas all night,
and then just Maria.
I love doing this show.
I know.
I love doing this show
with you also,
'cause I love you.
Hey, gang, here's
I just overheard.
a funny thing
- Um, "Final comic
- of the night."
- "Final comic
- of the night"?
- Oh, Dave,
- we forgot about you.
- Guys, I blew off
- a Sadie Hawkins dance
- For this
- that I was chaperoning,
And you know how much
at school
I like the energy
- when the girls are
- asking the boys.
- Ah, Dave, I'm sorry.
- Hey, uh,
We'll go
tell everybody
out there and just
- we have a surprise
- headliner,
- And you can go on
- after Maria Bamford.
- Oh, fuck you. - I can't follow
- Maria Bamford.
- Come on.
- Yeah.
- Actually that's, like,
- legitimately a bad idea.
- Is that funny?
- How long you been doing this?
- Like three years?
- One year.
- Rhea, don't...
- I'm looking for something.
Oh, there. I found it,
looking for.
found what I was
MARIA: And if you're not...
- You're being
- a little baby.
Shut up.
- No, you say that
- for every show.
- Just stop. Stop.
- Shut up. All right.
- I'll see you. I'll see you.
- Yes. Call me.
- Peww peww peww.
- Girls.
Cameron.
Hey, Danielle.
- Oh, my God.
- Kent was just talking
About how wonderful
you are. He's so sweet.
- He was?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, he...
- He's a huge fan of yours.
He's the reason I saw you
in the first place.
He said you were, um,
reckoned with."
"A force to be
Um, okay.
Yeah.
Hi, Rhea. How are you?
Hi. Good.
I love Whitesnake.
- I mean,
- w-whose shirt is that?
- Is that yours?
- It's mine.
- Okay. Well, this is
- Melina Marquez,
And I think
that the three of us
- should have lunch
- next week.
Such great stuff. Heh.
Yeah. No, you just
have such, um...
Like a presence.
It's great.
I... I like every movie
you've ever been in.
- Okay.
- [laughs]
She's...
- Okay, we'll set up
- the lunch.
Oh, this is Rhea.
This is Rhea.
Kent likes me?
That's what
of this situation,
you're taking out
that Kent said
about you?
something nice
Not that
just touched you
that hot woman
- and studied
- your pupils?
Did she look in my eyes?
Ecch. Yes, a lot.
- You have to get
- Maria offstage.
Okay. I'm coming.
Ugh. I know.
Oh, those hands
have been to space.
Fake space.
[cheering]
- Give it up
- for Maria Bamford!
You guys.
- So good.
- And actually
- while you're at it,
Why don't we keep it going
you saw tonight.
for everybody else
[applause]
- I'm Cameron Esposito.
- I'm Rhea Butcher.
- Thank you, guys,
- so much for coming out.
Have a great
rest of your night.
[applause]
Oh, thank you so much.
Yeah, for sure.
Maria, thank you
so much for doing the show.
- Great job, you guys.
- You were so wonderful.
- Be careful.
- Don't get raped.
It's not as funny
as you think.
Yeah. That is good advice.
- Let's go home...
- Mm-hmm.
And watch
movie.
a Melina Marquez
Sounds great.
- Which one? - Where she goes
- To space?
- I don't know.
- Or the deep sea?
How about when she's
in deep sea in deep space?
I know! How'd they get
the water out there?
[overlapping chatter]
There you go.
Ugh. That isn't
staying here?
No. I showed it to Mike.
He was like,
"No, I don't want that,"
and laughed and walked away.
- God, some people
- have no taste.
- Well, I don't know
- about that.
- You guys valet?
- Don't you know
Medicaid's gonna dry up
by the time you're 40?
Hey, uh, Bob, sorry
onstage tonight.
we dissected your set
- Super rude.
- I don't give a shit.
- You're welcome
- for the new material.
Oh, if you're
around this week,
- maybe the three of us
- could get dinner.
That sounds terrible.
Also, I'm going on tour.
You know, theaters,
several thousand seats,
- you know,
- venues worthy of me.
Actually, Cameron,
I don't have an opener yet.
Do you wanna come?
- Yeah, that would
- be awesome!
- Cool.
- Is that okay?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, totally.
Cool.
And, Rhea,
- sorry for whatever
- you went through.
- I didn't know you were
- a survivor of assault.
Thanks.
I am, too.
Wow.
Okay.
You still want to come
on the road, though, right?
Yeah, of course.
Sweet.
- Do not bring
- that poster.
[sighs] God.
- Nobody likes
- the poster.
[jabbering]
Live... Madison Square...
Live from Madison Square Garden,
it's Marilyn Bamford.
♪ Yiii, yiii ♪
♪ Yii ♪
♪ The blood of our fathers ♪
[growly]
♪ Puts us in eternal sleep ♪
[growling]
♪ Yeah ♪
Good night, Mom.
You still... You still awake?
Okay.
♪ Oh, yeah ♪