My young friends, you're among the best
and brightest in the land,
but are you willing to obey and go?
Are you willing to head the call?
It matters not the field of service.
What matters is your willingness to obey
the Lord's command as found in Isaiah
chapter six.
Are you willing to take your talents and
place them on the alter and say,
"Here am I, Lord. Send me."
It was a terribly painful moment,
more painful than I care to remember.
I felt I had nothing to offer God but
a string of failures.
What could He possibly want from me?
The answer to that question will probably
surprise you because there's a strength
that can come from weakness.
There's a strength that lies hidden in failure.
You might not think so, but there is.
I'm living proof.
Uh, where's ma?
She's up at the hill with your dad.
They're about ready to move the house.
They are?
Don't go gettin' any fancy ideas.
Your mom said you need to stay here
and do your chores.
Chores is done!
Josh, come back here!
I had known for a while
they were going to move the house
but I didn't know exactly when,
and I was so excited.
How were they going to do it?
I was just a kid, what did I know?
Was a helicopter going to come
down from the sky, or airplanes
fly over to lift the house up
and take it away?
This house belongs to me
and it's stayin' here!
Now I want you boys off'a my property!
Keep working.
Ain't you gonna do something?!
I want these men off'a my property!
- I'm sorry, Wllmot.
According to this court order
that house now belongs to Junior
and he can move it if he has a mind to.
I built that house!
- And promised it to your son.
The hell I did!
- You were too drunk to remember!
I have witnesses.
Come on, we're taking those bushes.
You ain't taking no bushes, Junior!
Get! Get on out of here!
I had no idea of the conflict
unfolding that morning.
I just figured the crowd I saw
at the top of the hill meant we were
going to have some kind of celebration.
But instead of a party,
I came face-to-face with the misery
and dysfunction of my family
played out in front of all of our neighbors
and so-called friends.
They had turned out to support
my brother, Junior, against our parents.
It was completely shameful
and embarrassing and something
inside me just broke me that day.
I blanked out at that moment.
My mind went numb.
I think emotionally I snapped
because I can't remember what happened
over the next several minutes
But my last conscious thought...
I remember running down the hill
in front of everyone
just crying and screaming.
They're all lies!
If you cared, you wouldn't do this to me!
Have you ever felt abandoned?
I hate you, God! I hate you!
Have you ever felt nobody cares
whether you live or die?
And I hate you dad!
That's how I felt at eleven years old
when I was hiding in the silo.
I felt I had no one to turn to.
I hate you! I hate you!
And I became angry.
I became angry at God if God even existed.
And I damned him.
I called him every name in the book.
And I cursed and damned my father, too,
because I felt that he had abandoned me.
My father was an alcoholic.
He was the town drunk.
My mother was so overweight
she was practically an invalid.
One of my sisters committed suicide.
My other sister joined the Army
just to get away from home.
My oldest brother, Wilmot,
He actually sued my parents
in a court of law.
It wasn't a very happy home,
and I can remember so often just
feeling alone.
Like I was just completely alone.
I was in that cell for about 3 hours,
maybe more.
And no one even came to look for me.
Finally, I was just so hungry and thirsty,
I climbed out and went home.
I slammed the door shut on God that day.
In fact, probably one of the greatest hurts
was - is that I never ever wanted to go
to a friend's house again.
I felt such shame.
I think I just gave up on the notion that
love is patient, or kind, or even
rejoices in the truth.
And to be honest with you,
I never thought that door would ever
open again.
Josh, what are you doing out here?
You need to start your chores, boy.
Hurry up, now.
All right cows, let's go!
Come on, go! Come on, come on!
Oh, what, what is that man doing
with them cows now?
It's worse than dealing with a small child.
Him and his liquor!
What the hell?
I got chores of my own!
I've got to come out and do
your chores, too, I can see!
What is going on here?
Oh, Lord not again.
Wilmot McDowell!
Are you milking these cows
or just trying to kill them?
I got my own chores to do!
Do I have to do everything around here?
All you do around here is
getting fatter by the day.
- Useless old drunk!
This cow's milked out right here, this one!
You can't even take care of a cow
for heaven's sake!
(Edith screaming)
Got your chores done, Edith? Huh?!
I'll kill you!
- No, Josh!
Do you hear, me?!
I swear you'll pay!
You'll see!
Josh!
Oh, Josh.
Mom.
You can't do it. You can't do it.
Just go get Wayne.
Mom.
He's, he's gonna change, son.
I know he's gonna change.
Just, just go get Wayne. Just get him.
Crying's not going to do anyone any good,
Josh.
Wayne Bailey was used to my dad hurting
my mom.
It's your mother again, ain't it?
He was used to me asking for his help.
He worked in the house because
mom was just too slow and too heavy
for most of the household chores.
I suppose he handled that side
of things well enough.
It was the other things that he did.
As far as handling my dad was concerned,
I didn't need help from Wayne
or anyone else.
When you grow up on a farm,
You learn to do a lot of things as a kid.
You also get pretty strong.
If I knew friends were planning to come
by the house, I took matters
into my own hands.
Partly to avoid embarrassment
from my dad, who was always drunk,
and partly to pay him back
for what he did to my mom.
Josh, what are you doing?
- Just stay there!
What are you doing -Ahhh!
Josh I didn't mean to.
Josh...
Josh, I'm your father, Josh.
Jo.
Some father you are.
Now, don't you make a sound.
You hear me?!
Hello Mr. O'Brien. Hello Mrs. O'Brien.
Howdy, Josh. Where's your dad?
He, uh, he had to go into town,
but my mom's inside. She's expecting you.
Thank you, Josh.
Come on in, folks!
Come on in.
Just in here taking the chicken out
of the oven. Have a seat over there.
I would leave my dad in the barn all night.
I don't know how many times I would do that.
But I would do just about anything
to humiliate him.
I can remember watching him go out
to hide his wine bottles and then
I'd go out and urinate in them.
One time the police pulled me off my dad
when I was trying to choke him underneath
the water in the bathtub.
I hated him so much.
I used to go to the bathroom and then
stick his head in the t-
...stick his head in the toilet and flush it.
And as a kid, all I ever wanted
was to stop my dad from hurting my mother,
and I couldn't do it.
He never retaliated directly.
He could have. I mean I was still a kid.
I think when he sobered up,
even thought he didn't stay sober long,
he must have realized what he was doing
to my mom and the family.
I think he was ashamed.
I don't know for sure, but life went on.
You got them rolls in there?
Ah, here we go.
All right, fellas, we got some nice hot rolls
for you. Here we go.
And if you want to start that butter
down this side.
And Josh, your father and I have to talk
to you after supper.
How are you, my darlings?
Yes?
Yes? Oh my.
Yes. Beautiful. I have something for you.
I want you to obey Wayne. No excuses.
How long will you be gone?
Well, I don't know, a week maybe.
Ten days at the most.
That's a long time.
What ails you, son?
Your dad and I have made trips
like this before.
Wayne knows how to take good care of you.
You just do what he says.
Why don't I come with you?
I came with you once before.
- Joslin David McDowell,
You cannot go with us.
You're starting school next week!
And I want you to listen to me.
When I get home, I am going to ask Wayne
how you behaved and if I hear you didn't
listen to him, I'm going to give you
a good thrashing. Do you understand me?
- Yes, ma'am.
Oh, all right. Well,
now you go onto bed.
I need to see if Wayne washed those dishes.
How long will you be gone?
A week maybe,
ten days at the most.
That's a long time.
(Radio) Presenting Superman!
Up in the sky! Look!
It's a bird! It's a plane! It's Superman!
Josh.
Relax. Relax, Josh.
Just relax.
It's all right.
Josh. Stay with me.
Yeah, it's all right.
You know how you like this.
Twice I tried to tell my mother,
but she wouldn't believe me.
You know, back then people didn't
talk about these things, or
at least they weren't supposed to exist.
But Wayne Bailey severely abused me
sexually from about 6 to 13 years of age.
If you ever touch me again, I'll kill you,
you understand me?!
He must have stayed another
two or three years. Then he left.
He knew I had a temper,
and I would've killed him.
As I grew older, sports became
a vital outlet for me,
especially football
and basketball.
Every once in a while, my
mother came to one of my games,
but she never saw me play.
All she ever did was sit in the car and cry
because she was too heavy to sit
in the bleachers.
(Edith crying)
Where is he? Where is he?!
No, Josh, don't, don't.
Just - just let it go.
There's only one thing I want before I die.
Die? What are you talking about, mom?
I just -
I just want to see you graduate
from high school.
Mom, I'll be out in two months.
You know that.
Well I, I know son.
Jo- Josh, you have to promise me three things.
You got to promise me that you will never
ever be an alcoholic,
and you won't swear.
You promise me that you'll be
the kind of son that I can be proud of.
Sure, mom.
No promise me, promise me.
I promise.
Just rest now, okay?
When I graduated from high school,
I joined the Air National Guard
with some of my friends.
That was the summer of 1957.
And then, because I couldn't get into basic
training at the same time as my buddies,
I joined the regular Air Force.
That allowed me to be with my friends
for two weeks of active duty training
at Lackland Air Force Base.
When two weeks were over, my friends
went back to Michigan, but Airman Josh
McDowell still had 10 more weeks of basic
training and three years and nine months
of regular duty; and all that just to be
with my friends 2 more weeks.
After basic training,
I was assigned to Dover Air Force Base
in Delaware.
Now, on paper I was a mechanic working on
C-124 aircraft, the big cargo planes,
but it seemed like my real job was to play
starting guard for the base basketball team.
- So yesterday, remember in practice,
We put that play in. That one play
is going to get Josh open for that shot
when we need that shot.
That's what we're going to run right now.
We're going to run this pick so that
Josh can get open.
- My first Seargent was really proud of me
For being a starter on the team.
All right, and you guys popping it out.
Make it pop hard. Get there, open quick...
in a lot of ways. But I still had to work.
Sometimes things just happen.
Paging Dr. Stateman, Dr. Stateman, please.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Michael Crawford, 3-4-0, Michael Crawford,
please call 3-4-0.
Airman McDowell?
Yes, sir.
I'm Chaplin Gardiner.
Yes, sir? W- what is it?
It's about your mother.
My mother?
What about my mother?
Your mother's dead, son.
I just want to see you graduate
from high school...
and then, I want to die.
I can't go on, son.
Your father's broken my heart.
Where you going?
Union City.
Come on, get it in.
They say you can't die of a broken heart,
My father's abuse broke my mother's heart,
and she lost the will to live.
I, on the other hand, well,
my heart turned hard
and I decided to take everything I could get.
I recieved a medical discharge
from the Airforce and began making plans
for another life.
I mapped out the next 30 years of my life
and went to Kellogg Community College,
determined to become Governor of Michigan
or maybe even U.S. Senator.
It was all about me and who I could use
to climb to the top.
I had become a hardened young man,
cynical about life.
I found Christians, in particular,
worthy of utter disdain.
- Grabs the nightstand and throws
It out the window too!
Now, the girl's pretty perplexed,
you know, but being a pro, she figures
he's got some sort of fetish or something
like that, so she continues to disrobe.
I think we should change the subject.
Why?
Those students over there are Christians
and so is the professor.
SQ?
They might be offended.
Well, why would they be offended?
They probably won't even get the joke.
I mean Christians have two brains, don't they?
One's lost and the other's out looking for it.
So, you want me to finish the joke?
I got a better one for you.
A man is stumbling through the woods,
totally drunk, when he comes across a
preacher who's baptizing people in the river.
He walks up to the preacher who smells
the alcohol on his breath and says,
"Are you ready to find Jesus?"
To which the drunk replies, "Sure thing."
So the preacher grabs him by the neck,
dunks him in the river, pulls him up
and says, "Have you found Jesus?"
The drunk spits out some water and says,
"Nope, nope.'"
So, the preacher is a little shocked.
So he grabs the man by the neck,
dunks him in the water again
and holds him under a little longer,
pulls him up and says,
"For the love of God, my brother,
have you found Jesus now?"
The drunk wipes his eyes, catches his breath
and says, "No sir, I can't find him anywhere.
Are you sure this is where he fell in?"
Like my joke?
Perhaps you have a better one.
Or maybe a really good story like, uh,
Jonah and the whale?
Now there's a Whopper.
Or what about Noah and his oceanliner?
Welcome to our table, Mister...
McDowell, I believe it is.
That's right, good to be here.
You know, what is it about you Christians?
What do you mean?
Well, I mean everyone knows who you are
and there's only about a half dozen of you,
and uh, plus you and another professor.
And I've been watching you.
Is that so?
Yeah. One thing I can't figure out.
What makes you think you're so different
from the rest of us?
Different?
Yeah, well some of you are good looking,
I'll admit it.
Very good looking.
And, uh,
you seem to be happy most of the time.
Maybe you're brainwashed, I don't know,
probably are.
We have new lives.
New lives, what, like you're
reincarnated or something?
How do you get a new life?
- Through Jesus Christ.
Come on, don't give me that garbage!
Garbage?
Yeah, the Bible and church,
that's just religion.
And if there's one thing I can't stand,
it's religion.
Well, I didn't say religion, mister.
I said Jesus Christ.
Jesus Christ, how lame is that?
We have new lives through Jesus Christ.
Jesus Christ, what?
Even if he did exist,
how could a man who lived 2,000 years ago
possibly influence someone's life today?
Well, I guess that's what you'll need
to find out.
What's there to find out?
Read the Bible and put your faith
in fairy tales?
Come on, Dolly, you can do better than that.
Actually, if you were to disprove
the resurrection,
You would fully prove your point.
What?
The resurrection.
That Jesus Christ physically rose
from the grave.
If you were to prove that never happened,
you would debunk Christianity.
Prove it to be what you claim it to be,
myths and fables.
Now, there's an idea.
I'm quite serious about it, actually.
Yeah? Well, so am I.
See where your investigation leads.
Yeah, well nice talking with you.
We look forward to seeing again,
Mr. McDowell.
The name's Josh.
Josh.
And next time, be more prepared.
Prepared? You gotta' be kidding me.
I couldn't be more serious.
Yeah, well let's see what I come up with.
And don't get mad at me when I make
all of you look foolish.
Not at all.
Well, have a nice day.
You know, I'd ask you to vote for me
in the student elections, but, uh,
there are so few of you I guess it wouldn't
make much of a difference.
I was really determined to prove
those students and professors wrong
about Christianity.
I kind of wanted to rub it in their faces,
if you know what I mean.
The problem for me was I couldn't find
enough material at Kellogg College Library
to prove my main points.
And funny how these things happen...
I began to get the idea of going to Europe
to study original manuscripts that I knew
were housed in some of the libraries
over there.
It was early summer 1958.
I had my own money, that wasn't a problem,
so I flew to England and just began to read
everything I could get my hands on.
I read the works of many well-known skeptics.
I also examined the writings of a smaller
group of individuals, all of them proficient
in their areas of expertise,
who started out as unbelievers
and later became Christians.
This intrigued me,
and I wanted to find out why.
What led them to change?
There was Lord Lyttleton, who
later became Chancellor of the Exchequer,
Gilbert West, Sir William Ramsey,
Frank Morison, C.S. Lewis...
all of them educated successful men
- and skeptics -
who became believers after carefully
studying the evidence.
On the same trip, I went to Germany,
France and Switzerland.
I'd go into various museums and libraries
and look into the glass display cases
holding rare books and manuscripts.
I couldn't read Greek or Hebrew,
but I knew those manuscripts were real.
And significance of each one.
I made my way back to England,
and just a day or two before my return
trip to the States, I went to a library
on the northeastern edge of London.
It was a small library
someone had told me about,
and it had several books and manuscripts
I wanted to study.
By this time, I was tired, really tired.
I remember it was about 6:30 in the evening,
and I leaned back in my chair,
put my hands behind my head
and said out loud,
- It's true.
"It's true"
I said it again
It's true.
...And again.
- It's true!
...and again.
Shhhh...
I had started my journey as an obnoxious,
agnositic university student
who thought Christians were airheads.
I had set out to refute their beliefs
and disprove the resurrection.
But after all my research,
in spite of my prejudice,
I realized I didn't have a valid defense.
The historical evidence all pointed
the other way, and I realized
my rejection of the Bible and Christianity
was based more on emotion than intellect.
I wasn't ready to become a Christian,
but I had to admit there was
compelling evidence to consider,
evidence that demanded a verdict.
There came one running,
and kneeled to him, and asked...
- Back in Michigan,
I continued my college studies
and began attending a small church called
Factoryville Bible Church.
The Pastor's name was Fay Logan.
He knew what I'd been going through, and
one day he prepared a special sermon
Just for me.
But let's be clear,
God's salvation is not an intellectual exercise.
We are saved by faith and trust in Christ.
So, let me ask you,
are you ready to recieve the gift
of eternal life that Jesus is offering you
right now? Do you believe?
Are you ready to commit?
Let's review what that commitment
will involve.
I acknowledge I am a sinner
in need of salvation.
Secondly, I believe in my heart
that God did raise Jesus from the dead.
Thirdly, I confess Jesus as my Lord
and my God.
I knew I needed to respond, but I couldn't.
I was afraid.
By receiving Christ as Savior and Lord,
I'd be committing intellectual suicide.
I was also afraid of what my friends would say.
I was afraid of what they'd think.
The Holy Spirit welcomes you to come
and trust Jesus as your personal
Lord and Savior.
Who will come?
And then, thank God, one of those friends
leaned over and asked me a question.
Do you want me to go with you?
People think I became a Christian through
the intellectual route. That's not true.
All the study, all the research,
that was God's way of getting my attention
and I don't downplay it because without it
I would never have considered
the Bible's message.
Josh, this Bible is for you.
The door I had closed on God as an
eleven-year-old, cracked open again
and I began to learn that God is love,
and he loves me.
That he's passionate about having
a relationship with me.
And from that day forward
with Pastor Logan's help
I began to learn about the Christian life.
But it wasn't the evidence that brought
me to God.
It was his love.
"I have loved you with an everlasting love;
with tender kindness I have drawn you."
That's what God in his mercy did for me.
There he is now.
Josh, this is my girlfriend, Gail.
Nice to meet you.
I did not want to love my father
or forgive him.
I wanted to continue to hate him.
I believed he had killed my mother
and destroyed our family.
For years, I'd gone to bed at night
dreaming up ways to kill him
without being caught by the police,
and here I was, a new Christian,
still determined to hate him.
So...
- Dad, I have something to say to you.
Dad, I love you.
I don't I know who was more in shock,
him hearing what I said,
or me saying the words.
That's when I knew it was true.
I was used to loving those I loved,
but I never had the capacity to love
someone I hated.
I hated my father, and now
I was overcome by love for him.
Christianity was real.
- Josh, how is college?
Knowing it was true, however,
even knowing that God
loved me unconditionally
didn't make some things any easier
to deal with.
I can't, Pastor. I just can't.
It goes too deep.
Josh.
If this is Christianity,
maybe I should hang it up.
I can't.
I'm sorry, Pastor.
This is just too much to ask.
I'm not asking you, Josh.
No one understands.
"And when they were come to the place
which is called Calvary,
there they crucified him and the malefactors,
one on the right hand
and the other on the left.
Then said Jesus, 'Father, forgive them
for they know not what they do."'
Altogether, it was a process
of about six months.
And without Pastor Logan's patience
and wisdom, I'd never had done it.
Even when I did, I had no emotion about it.
I did it by faith, out of obedience,
knowing it was the right thing to do.
I remember hoping I wouldn't be able
to find out where he lived.
But I did find out,
and I called him up and I told him
I was coming to see him.
Josh...
Wayne.
Wayne, what you did to me was evil.
And you know it was evil.
But I've-
I've come to know Christ as my Savior,
my Lord.
And I've come here to tell you...
I've come here to tell you that
Christ died as much for you as he did for me.
I forgive you, Wayne.
One more thing, Wayne.
Don't let me ever hear of you
touching a young man again.
You'll regret it.
In Hebrews, Jesus is accepted...
Well, the bridge, Josh, I think is love.
It's not a line in the sand.
It's a relationship - a personal relationship.
I like what Martin Luther said,
"God writes the gospel not in the bible alone
but also on the trees and the flowers;
on the clouds and the stars."
I've been thinking, Josh.
Uh-oh.
I think you need to transfer
to Wheaten College.
Wheaten College, where's that?
Outside Chicago.
- Yeah?
- Oh yeah?
It's where Billy Graham went to school.
Hmm...
It'll demand a lot out of you academically,
but I think you're up to the challenge.
You know, Pastor,
I've been thinking of studying law?
Really?
Yeah.
Well, whatever you decide to do,
Wheaten can help you excel. I, uh...
At Wheaten, I had time for two things:
Study and work.
I had a part-time job in the afternoons
delivering administrative records
for local high schools.
As a result of the accident,
the ligaments in my neck were torn loose
and my lower back severly injured.
After four days in Intensive Care,
I spent another week and a half
in the hospital.
The doctors realized my recovery would be
gradual, and they decided
I should go home to mend.
Ironically, the man who hit me
was a drunk driver.
The plan was for me to stay at home
where I'd be looked after by a nurse,
but the nurse was late the day of my arrival.
My father met the ambulance, instead.
Bring him in here, fellas.
We've got, uh, the furniture out.
Thank you.
About five minutes had passed
when my dad entered the room.
He didn't actually walk into the room,
He stood in the doorway.
I couldn't move my head,
but I could just make him out
through the corner of one eye.
There were two things I noticed right away.
One, he was sober,
and the other, he was crying.
I couldn't move any part of my body
except my eyes.
He just pace back and forth,
no dialogue, nothing.
I just followed him as best I could.
Josh...
HOW.
How could you ever love a father like me?
Dad...
I've learned one thing.
God became man, and his name is Jesus.
Jesus is passionate to have a relationship
with you.
He left the room and was gone.
I don't know, maybe
forty-five minutes passed.
Then, he came back into the room.
Josh,
If Jesus can do in my life
what I've seen him do in yours,
then I want to know him.
You need to ask him into your life, dad.
Open your hear to him and pray.
God,
if you are God,
My dad just prayed a simple prayer,
a farmer's prayer I call it,
very down to earth.
All I could do was cry.
Then, please,
come in.
When I came to Christ, my life changed over
about a period of a year; year and a half.
But when my father made that decision,
the change was immediate.
I saw him change right before my eyes.
It was like somebody reached down and
turned on a lightbulb in his life.
And you know, only once after that
did he ever touch alcohol, and he got it
All of you remember the way I used to be,
I was the town drunk.
I was an embarrassment to my family.
Tom, you were there on the hill that day
when Junior was moving the house;
stumbling, falling down drunk.
I was an embarrassment.
And you know my wife is gone now,
I can't make it up to her, but I can tell you
one thing, and it happened right
here in this diner, was when my son, Josh,
said to me, "Dad, I love you."
And those were his exact words,
"Dad, I love you." And that's...
As a result of my dad's decision
to trust Christ, scores of people in our town
and the surrounding area came to know
Jesus Christ as savior and Lord.
All because of the changed life
of the town drunk.
I just wish my mother could have seen it.
Fourteen months later, my father died.
Three-fourths of his stomach had to be
cut out, his entire liver was destroyed
through thirty-some years of drinking.
I was at Wheaten College when I got
the news - which brings me back
to where our story began.
I had run out of Edman Chapel that evening.
"Who will go?" the chapel speaker had said,
quoting the prophet Isaiah.
"Who will make their abilities available
to God?" It sure wasn't going to be me,
even if I was a student at Wheaten College.
I still had feelings of inferiority,
I still carried the scars of abuse
and violence and family brokenness.
Yeah, sure, I might succeed in hiding these
things from others, but how could I
hide them from myself?
I remember thinking,
"Well, maybe I should jusk walk away.
Maybe I should leave the faith."
All I'd ever heard as a Christian was that
for his glory.
That created a huge problem for me.
I felt I had nothing to offer God
but weakness and failure.
My life story didn't have a fairy tale ending.
And then I did something I thought
I'd never do. I stopped and said,
God, all I have are failures
But if you can take my weaknesses
and glorify yourself through them,
I'll serve you with every breath I breathe.
And that's the story, my friend.
That's the story of how God saved me
from destruction.
How he chose the foolish and simple things
to confound the strong and wise.
The rest, I guess you'd say, is history.
Maybe you can identify with pan of my story.
Alcoholic or drug addicted parents,
abuse,
or that sense of loneliness where
you feel like it wouldn't matter to anyone
if you lived or died.
Or that hopelessness
that comes from that feeling that
God just can't forgive me
or it's too late.
I want you to understand something,
it is never too late.
One of the barriers that I had
in ever coming to God
might be your problem, too.
It was the image of my earthly father.
You see, people would tell me that
your heavenly father loves you,
and that didn't bring joy into my life.
That brought pain.
You say, "Why?"
Because I was not emotionally able to discern
and an earthly father.
Growing up to me - fathers hurt.
One thing I had to realize, though,
is that Christianity is not a religion,
It's a relationship.
You say, "what's the difference?"
You see, a religion is men and women
trying to work their way to God
through good works and religious ritual.
Christianity is God coming to us
through his Son Jesus Christ
offering us a relationship.
Most people think that I came to Christ
because of all the evidence
that I've documented in my books.
But none of that brought me to Christ,
it only showed me that it was true.
What really brought me to Christ
was God's love.
God loved me so much
that if I were the only person alive,
Christ would still die for me,
and the same is true of you.
You might be saying,
"Josh, I want to know Christ personally.
I want to know that I'm forgiven.
I want to know that if I were to die today
where I'd spend eternity."
And you can.
We come to Christ by faith
through prayer, expressing that desire
of our heart.
And maybe the prayer that I prayed
would help you
to express that desire to God right now,
to invite Christ into your life.
I don't ask you to bow your heads.
I don't even ask you to close your eyes.
Because years ago, I learned the key to prayer
is not in the position of the body,
but in the attitude of the heart.
This is a prayer that I prayed:
"Lord Jesus, I need you.
Thank you for dying on the cross for me.
Forgive me and cleanse me.
Right now, I trust you as Savior and Lord.
Come into my life.
Thank you that I can trust you.
In Christ's Name. Amen."
If you just prayed that prayer with me,
and you were sincere,
I want you in the next few days
to find a follower of Jesus
and share with him or her
the decision you just made.
And then do something that I did.
Find a Bible,
turn to the third Chapter of John,
it's in the New Testament,
Matthew, Mark, Luke and John
and read John 3, three times.
And then I want to help you grow.
I want to help you see Christ
truly change your life from the inside out.
Go to my website,
it's josh.org/undaunted.
Josh.org/undaunted
And I will be able to share with you
many things through my site
that can help you to see
God change your life forever.
Thank you so much for letting me be a part
of your life.