Have a seat.
Now this is highly irregular, Agent Thorn.
Never had to recall this type of
specialist back into active service.
Desperate times call for
desperate measures.
Saved more lives than
he could possibly know.
Smart, loyal, keen military instincts.
Best I ever served with.
And the family?
Very Supportive.
No, the Wincotts are
military through and through.
They were only happy to lend him to us.
He looks good on paper,
but he's been out of the game for a while.
How do we know he's still got it?
(SCREAMS)
(GROWLS)
Agent Thorn,
meet Max.
Welcome to the Secret Service, Max.
(BARKS)
And Russian president Vladimir Bragov
will be arriving later this week
to attend President Bennett's
first state visit since taking office,
an event that's set to kick
off a full week of arms
negotiations at presidential
retreat Camp David.
These two leaders
couldn't be more different.
The question remains
if Bennett's laid-back style
can handle Bragov's stronger,
- more aggressive stance.
- What?
Critics will be watching...
Stronger?
Just because the Kremlin
cowboy hunts tigers,
it doesn't make him strong.
Dad, can I talk to you about something?
It's about school.
Look, these things, they just take time.
You're the new kid on the block.
Look, TJ. Why don't you
invite some of your
new friends over to the White House?
I mean, how many kids your age
have their own bowling alley?
No, I'd love to invite
my new friends over.
If I had any.
Okay, you know, it's kind of
hard to make friends
when every time someone comes
up to you, they get frisked.
We know this is hard, TJ.
It's a big adjustment for all of us.
It's more than just an adjustment, Mom.
It's like living in a fish bowl,
and I'm the only one
who didn't ask for this.
PRESIDENT BENNETT: Son.
(SIGHS)
There have been a lot of kids
who grew up here,
and I'm sure every single one of them
felt exactly the way you do right now.
But I will bet that
they wouldn't trade that experience
for anything in the world.
You know, so,
maybe, do your mom and I a favor
and just try to give it a chance.
(SIGHS)
I guess.
That's the Bennett spirit!
FIRST LADY BENNETT: Go have a good day.
TJ: Bye.
- Bye.
Baby bird, hold on.
Don't forget your lunch.
Baby bird? Seriously?
Oh, man. I've gotta get
a cooler code name.
Hey! You're new here.
(WHIMPERS)
And well-trained!
Well, I guess I know what you want.
Who's a good boy?
Who likes his belly rubbed?
- What's your name, fella?
AGENT THORN: His name is Max.
And he's not here to play.
I wasn't playing with him,
Agent Thorn. I was just...
Okay, maybe I was
playing with him a little.
What's he doing here?
Max is one of the country's
highest-trained tactical canines.
He's been called to duty
to replace Charlie,
who's out on maternity leave.
Hmm. Charlie's a girl?
Let's go, Max.
Now, if you'll excuse us.
We have work to do.
Max, come.
Nice to meet you, Max.
Good luck in the fish bowl.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SIREN WAILING)
Hail to the geek.
(CHILDREN LAUGH)
(TJ SIGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
You know that's cheating, right?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SIGHS)
Does anyone want to trade for a PB&J?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
TJ: Hit me! You can hit me!
Come on! They're not gonna
do anything to you.
Come on! You can hit me! Someone hit me!
No!
FEMALE TOUR GUIDE:
And fun fact number 41...
GIRL: It's TJ.
(CHATTERING)
FEMALE TOUR GUIDE: It's
First Son, TJ Bennett.
I told you we might get lucky today.
FEMALE TOURIST: I love you, TJ!
TJ: It's bad enough that
I had to dance with my mom
at the inauguration.
But now I'm a part of the tour, Coop.
I live here
but I feel like I'm on exhibit
365 days a year.
At least a gorilla in the zoo
gets Christmas off.
COOP: Look at the bright side, T.
At the zoo, they don't let
you feed the animals.
Think about it.
Worst case, you're only gonna
be here for eight more years.
Less if your dad gets impeached.
Thanks for cheering me up, Coop.
I do hear what you're saying, T.
But for some reason, they put a really
high value on security here.
Did you know that they X-ray
everything that comes into the kitchen?
Even the grapes.
I mean, what can you hide in a grape?
But it's not just that.
I miss my old life, my old friends.
I didn't run for office, you know.
Might just grow on you, T.
Why do you think so many presidents' sons
go into the family business?
Like you said, at least
the food's good here.
I mean, what do you put
in these things anyway?
Secret ingredient. Hold on.
That one's still probably
- a little bit hot-
- Hot! Hot!
(CHUCKLES)
(DOG BARKS)
Hey, Max! Come here, boy!
- Come here, boy!
(BARKS)
Hi.
(CHUCKLES) Good boy.
MAN: We'll get right on that.
I want someone on the ground
at 0800 hours for this situation.
Hey, TJ.
Who's your new friend?
Sit, Max, sit!
Good boy. Meet Max, our newest addition
to the White House staff.
Well, hello, Max.
I hope I can count on your
vote in the next election.
Oh! Yes! What a good boy!
Yes, what a good boy!
Uh, Dad, I don't think
Agent Thorn wants anyone to
be playing with Max like this.
TJ, come on.
I'm the President of the United States.
I'm pretty sure petting any dog
I want is in the constitution.
Isn't that right, Max?
Yeah, isn't that right?
(CHUCKLES)
AGENT THORN: Mr. President,
I apologize. Our new security canine
shouldn't have left his station.
We're still getting him up to
speed on his duties here.
Good, then it's not too late.
Too late for what, sir?
To add a few more duties.
Like playing with TJ on his off hours.
Sir, as head of White House security,
I must voice my concerns.
This is an important week.
And I would hate for the dog to get
confused about his purpose here.
PRESIDENT BENNETT: Noted, Agent Thorn.
But I'm sure a man with your abilities
can find a way to accommodate
this simple request.
Otherwise, I'd have to
issue an executive order.
Get the Supreme Court involved.
You know, it can get really messy.
Of course, Mr. President.
Thank you, Agent Thorn.
Well, you see that, TJ?
This morning, I told you
things would turn around for you here.
And President Bennett always
delivers on his promises.
Thank you, Dad. Come on, Max!
Come on, Max! Let's go!
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
War hero, veteran, and now Secret Service?
Tactical canine Max
is on loan to the White House this week
to help out with the Russian state visit.
And by the looks of things,
he's making himself quite at home.
Who wants the ball? Who wants the ball?
Who wants the ball?
Hey!
TA: Good boy!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SIREN WAILING)
Let's go, Max.
- I'm TJ.
- Alfred.
- Max, security detail.
- Cool.
Lunch today'?
Yeah. Yeah, thanks.
That's cool.
(SONG PLAYING ON PIANO)
Mom, Dad, can I go to a party tonight?
A kid at school invited me.
Oh. I'm sorry, honey.
Tonight really isn't
the best time for this.
TJ, you know that the Russian
president is gonna be here...
What's that gotta do with me?
Look, I know that this
has been really difficult,
but we are the First Family and that
job has responsibilities.
And you know what?
We were hoping that you could help us out.
See, President Bragov's
wife couldn't make the trip,
but he is bringing his kid, Alex,
- who just happens to be about your age.
- TJ: Wait.
So you want me to babysit
some Russian kid?
Well, we were hoping that
you would see it more as
being our "goodwill ambassador."
Well, I was hoping
I would have a vote
on anything that goes on in my life.
It's not fair and there's no
way I'm dressing up
in a fancy outfit and smiling
for the cameras
just so you can get your poll numbers up.
Look, I'm sorry, nope.
I am just not doing it.
- TJ, what is on your face?
(SIGHS) Mom.
- Mom!
- Hey, hey, hey,
Dad, she's a girl.
Yes, Alex is short for Alexandra.
I hope that's not a problem.
President Bragov, it is an honor to
have you here as my guest.
Honor?
You seem to have changed
your tune since campaign
when you called me, what was it?
"Crazy Kremlin cowboy."
(LAUGHS)
You must be tired, let me
show you your quarters.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
- He seems nice.
- Yeah.
(SIGHS) I'm supposed to be nice to you.
I am to be polite, nothing more.
My name is Alexandra Bragov,
but you may call me Alex.
I'm TJ.
I know, I had briefing about you.
They say you are very
resourceful and fine player of baseball.
Also a big fan of spy movies
and always eat ice cream too
fast and get brain freeze.
They know all that about me?
My papa's people are very thorough.
- But no mention of dog.
- Oh.
This is Max.
But he's not my dog.
I mean, I guess he is now,
- but, um, not later or before.
- Do you know what breed he is?
Oh, he's a Secret Service dog.
I mean, I know it's not a breed.
- He's a...
- Belgian Malinois.
How'd you know that?
I am, how you say? Dog person.
Oh, yeah? Me too.
Tell them to put that in my file.
So, TJ, do you think your "dog-for-now"
could help us sniff out something
to eat other than boring state dinner?
I think I know just the place.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Oh! No, no, you Malinois!
In borscht, we slice
beets thin like paper.
- My president...
- Dimitri!
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
I misspoke.
It is honor to be in
such beautiful kitchen.
Even if you do not belong here.
I assume he came with you?
TA: Hey, Coop.
Meet Alex, she's from Russia.
Call me Coop, I'm from Brighton Beach.
Pleasure.
TJ: Say, Coop,
would you like to whip us up a
couple of the house specials, please?
Why, of course, sir.
Anything to get me off borscht detail.
(CHUCKLES)
Mmm.
ALEX: Such flavor!
Why is this grilled cheese so good?
Sorry, secret ingredient.
It's classified.
You do not know, do you?
Nope.
So what do you do for amusement here?
Well, do you like to bowl?
Not particularly.
Me neither.
There's all kinds of stuff here,
but they're no fun to do alone.
And under 24-hour watch.
And let me guess, many
important "responsibilities."
No kidding. Sometimes,
I feel like I'm just here for photo ops.
At least you do not have to stand for
eight hours at the Victory Day Parade.
Doesn't even compare to
visiting the Iowa State Fair.
They make sculptures out of butter.
- Why?
- I think there isn't much to do there.
(CHUCKLES)
I was actually invited
to go to a party downtown tonight.
But I can't go 'cause I have
to entertain our guests.
Well, I hope they're at least nice.
Not so bad so far.
I know how this goes.
You can't go to your party because your
parents are making you go to their party.
It's not fair.
Just 'cause we're the presidents' kids
means we don't get to have any fun?
(SCOFFS)
Sneaking out to party would be fun.
It would, wouldn't it?
But if we got caught...
Siberia?
I was going to say Guantanamo.
Same difference.
But do you always obey your parents?
Me? Not always.
Sometimes.
Okay, pretty much always.
(SCOFFS)
I just thought I was in
"land of the free and
"home of the brave."
Don't worry, Max. We'll be right back.
Let's go, come on.
Tomorrow morning, we'll be
heading to Camp David.
I know how much you love the outdoors
and I thought it would
be a more informal venue for our talks.
We will see.
Of course, the brunt of our time will be
spent discussing the arms treaty,
but we've got all sorts
of great events planned for your visit.
My beautiful wife here
is an esteemed concert pianist.
She's agreed to perform
an evening of Tchaikovsky.
- Pyotr Tchaikovsky?
- Yes.
I love Tchaikovsky.
But everywhere I go,
they play me Tchaikovsky.
I was hoping for Bon Jovi.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I hope the kids
are getting along better than we are.
(GASPS)
ALEX: TJ.
TJ: Don't look down, Alex.
(GROWLS)
I told you it was gonna be easy.
(GASPS)
Come on.
(SNEEZES)
(RUSSIAN AGENT
SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
I'm allergic to dogs.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hats.
Okay, ladies first.
(SIGHS)
You know, we could get
in a lot of trouble here.
My father always says,
"There is no reward without risk."
Mmm. Mmm.
Thomas, Maureen,
I hope you are enjoying the
borscht as much as I am.
Well, I have to say,
this is the best borscht I've ever had.
It's wonderful.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
All righty. Now, say hello
to President William Henry Harrison,
who caught pneumonia at his inauguration,
and, fun fact number seven,
died 31 days later.
And we're walking.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(BARKS)
(WHINING)
Hey, kids. Who wants some hot...
Oh, fudge!
(MAX BARKING)
(HORN HONKING)
(LAUGHING)
- You think they're looking for us yet?
- Probably,
but it's only a few more blocks.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
ALEX: Look out!
TJ: Go, run!
(ALEX SCREAMS)
ALEX: Help!
(KIDNAPPER GRUNTS)
(BARKING)
(GROWLS)
(SCREAMS)
(KIDNAPPER SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(KIDNAPPER SCREAMS)
(GROWLS)
(KIDNAPPER SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
ALEX: TJ! Run!
Come! Come on, Alex!
(BARKS)
(BARKING CONTINUES)
Mom, you should've seen Max out there.
He was like, like, like a superhero.
We were worried half to death.
Agent Thorn, how is this even possible?
Unfortunately, sir,
due to the restoration, the alarms on the
windows have temporarily been turned off.
I'm really sorry, Dad.
Let's go through this again.
Is there anything you can
remember that might help us?
(SIGHS)
Okay. I didn't wanna
say anything in front of our guests
but I think I heard one of
those guys say something in Russian.
Max bit one of the guys on the ankle.
Dad, you have to check every one of
those Russians for bite marks.
Son, let's just let the
Secret Service handle this, okay?
You mean the Secret Service
who can't keep track of
two 12-year-old kids?
Okay, I think that you have
caused enough trouble
for one evening, young man. Don't you?
- But, Dad, all I'm...
- No, I don't wanna hear it.
I want you to go to your room, go to bed,
we will discuss your
punishment in the morning.
Fine. Come on, Max.
If he did hear someone speaking Russian,
maybe there are bad
players on the other team.
PRESIDENT BENNETT:
We can't make unsubstantiated
accusations with the entire
world watching, Agent Thorn.
But, Thomas,
if somebody is looking to hurt...
It's okay, Maureen.
PRESIDENT BENNETT:
We'll be fine at Camp David.
FIRST LADY BENNETT:
You mean, we're still going?
- I'm working.
AGENT THORN: My agents have been on site
securing the grounds for the past 30 days.
If there is something going on, there is
no safer place for us to be right now.
Yeah, no safer place to be, because you
and I are gonna be there. Right, Max?
TJ: Come here, Max.
TJ: Sit, Max.
Pick up.
(SIGHS)
- Good boy.
AGENT THORN: Max, come.
Perimeter search.
Go on, boy.
(SIGHS)
- Hi.
TJ.
What's going on?
Why are you being so weird?
I was thinking we could get together later
and talk more about
what happened last night.
No.
- I can't.
- What?
Why not? What's going on?
(SIGHS) I don't know.
Maybe 'cause the only person who knew
I was going to that party was you.
In fact, you pretty much made me go.
TJ, why would I kidnap myself?
How better to make it look
like you're not involved?
Um, just off the top of my head,
maybe not sneaking out with you
in the first place?
That's exactly what
a Russian spy would say.
(SCOFFS)
PRESIDENT BENNETT:
I'm so glad that you decided to continue
the peace talks, Vladimir.
I'm hoping that
we can jump into it right after lunch.
No, no, no, after lunch, we ride.
We... We ride?
My people, many think best way
to keep Mother Russia strong
is to keep Uncle Sam weak.
But I think strong can work with strong.
So we ride as men.
Then, I know how strong you are.
Okay.
Come, Mr. President!
Let us feel the wind on our faces!
Atta boy!
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(LAUGHS)
We ride like men!
Yippie Jovi yo ki yay!
I'm serious, Coop.
If one of the Russians does
wanna stop the talks,
it'd have to be someone
who came with Bragov.
Someone who's not happy to be here.
Someone like...
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
- Him.
"Authentic Jovi Alfredo!"
Even their food is bland and
stolen from other countries!
You sure about this, T?
Think about it. He was also in the kitchen
when Alex and I were sneaking out.
And he sure doesn't seem like
a fan of America. Does he?
Careful with this, T.
You never know where things can lead.
Don't worry, Coop.
A Bennett delivers on his promises.
(GRUNTS)
(WHISTLES)
(HUMMING)
Max, I think we're finally
barking up the right tree.
(BARKS)
(GRUNTS)
(SNAPS)
Come on, Max.
Let's find out what's in that box.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(RUSSIAN CHEF SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(CONTINUES SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(GRUNTS)
I wish one of us spoke Russian.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Max, we gotta do something.
(GRUNTS)
Drop the knife!
(MAX BARKING)
(GROWLS)
Are you crazy, little boy?
What are you doing?
What does it looks like? I'm making famous
homemade Russian rye bread.
- Bread?
- Da.
Finally put stop to dry,
tasteless monstrosity
your buddy, Coop, insists on making.
Now you ruin surprise and dough!
Security hear about this.
And then I tell your mama.
Wait, no. I wasn't here
to ruin the surprise.
I was here because... I... Um...
Because the US President is allergic.
Alex?
- Allergic?
- Yes.
That is why American chef make dry bread.
It's gluten free.
Oh, oh, yeah. My dad gets
real sick if he has any gluten at all.
Didn't you hear in the last campaign?
It was a huge scandal.
The wheat growers association
wouldn't endorse him.
The pizza lobby picketed his events.
I just wanted to stop you
before you got in big trouble.
Yes, you owe this boy
a great debt and apology.
Don't you?
(BARKS)
My humble apologies.
Now, come on, TJ. Weren't you going to
give me a tour of the grounds?
(GROANS)
(CHUCKLES) What did you think?
He had body in box?
I don't know. l...
That was stupid, right?
Not as stupid as thinking
I was behind the attacks.
Sorry about that. I didn't
know who to trust and...
It's okay.
You knew I was innocent. Didn't you, Max?
Uh, how did you know we were out here?
I was doing my own
investigation and saw you doing yours.
You were investigating me?
Someone is looking to hurt
both of our families, TJ.
You think I am not worried, too?
You would have known this if you
actually talked to me this morning
instead of putting me on Most Wanted list.
(SIGHS) You're not gonna let
me live that down, are you?
Not until it stops being fun.
So, who do you think is behind it?
Her?
ALEX: Before trip, I heard Olga say
she thought arms talks with your country
were terrible thing.
Would make my country weak.
In America, everyone is
innocent until proven guilty.
I also saw her applying
antibiotic ointment
to her ankle this morning
like she has fresh wound.
Hope she looks good in orange.
Stop staring at her.
Well, if I'm not staring at her,
how am I supposed
to know she's doing anything suspicious?
(SIGHS)
Would anyone like to sample
today's blue plate special?
- Thanks, Coop.
- She's cute, T.
Honey, do you want me
to get you some more ice?
A glacier wouldn't help.
(GRUNTS)
Oh. Morning, Vladimir.
How was your sleep?
The sleep of 1,000 men. You?
Who wouldn't feel great after
a four-hour ride on Diablo?
Good, then, well rested.
We go white water rafting today.
White water rafting.
You know, I was hoping that we could just
jump right into our talks.
No, today we ride the rapids.
BOTH: Like men!
Maybe I'm not hating
him as much as I thought.
Seems we're having more
in common all the time.
- I'll send for your chiropractor.
- Thank you.
Yeah.
Morning, kids.
- Hey, Dad.
- Morning.
Come on, let's follow her.
TJ. Maybe we should tell
somebody about this.
We will, as soon as
we've got proof. Come on.
Wait.
Are you scared?
Aren't you?
Why should I be scared?
We've got Max.
(GROWLS AND BARKS)
(GRUNTS)
ALEX: What do you think she's doing?
I don't think she's
listening to Katy Perry.
ALEX: I do not think we can get
close enough to see her ankle from here.
Maybe Max can.
We'll be able to see everything Max sees.
TJ, you're much cleverer than
your file had indicated.
Max. Go, go.
(LAUGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
MAN: Olga!
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
What about Max?
(SIGHS)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(LAUGHS)
What are they saying?
They're spying on my
father's First Secretary.
Why?
My father always says trust is weakness.
(SIGHS)
TJ: That's no bite mark,
she just got a tattoo.
Of a unicorn?
(GASPS)
(SNEEZES)
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
(GASPS)
(MAX BARKING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
I am very disappointed in you, TJ.
As am I, Alex.
Maybe you are
not my precious little angel after all.
If you cannot control your son,
I will control my daughter.
Okay. Bragov, it takes two to tango.
That is true, but I must do this.
Hand it over, Alex.
Hand what over?
What you got from your
Alfredo for Christmas.
(SIGHS)
There will be no more of this foolishness,
and you are not
to be around this boy without supervision.
- But, Father, I...
- No.
I was wrong to bring you on this trip.
I thought it would be good for you.
But now, I can see it has
been quite the opposite.
(SCOFFS)
Uh, Vladimir, are we still going rafting
or would you like to just
jump into negotiations?
PRESIDENT BENNETT: Okay.
This is... This is great.
I thought we agreed that you
would stop spying on people.
But they're spying on people, too.
That is their job!
My job is to protect you.
- Mr. President...
- Agent Thorn, please.
With all due respect, sir.
I think perhaps we should consider
bringing in another tactical canine
to replace Max.
He's clearly been confused
by his time with your son.
Agent Thorn,
that is your way of saying
"I told you so"?
Very subtle.
(SIGHS) Sir.
(CLEARS THROAT) TJ,
I think it's time that maybe we made
- a change with Max.
- No, Dad. It's not Max's fault, it's mine.
Yes, TJ, that may be
true but I have some...
You can't take away my only friend.
- Please, Dad.
(WHIMPERS)
He makes me feel safe.
Let me still hang with him.
I'll drop it, for real this time.
I promise.
Okay.
PRESIDENT BENNETT: Fine.
But I want you to stay
out of trouble, okay?
Both of you.
Deal?
Yes.
Okay.
(SIGHS)
(GROANS)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
COOP: You done, pal?
TJ: (SIGHS) I'm finished, all right.
Don't let it get you down, T.
Your dad will let up,
once negotiations are over.
Maybe, by then...
That cute one will be gone?
(SIGHS) Yeah.
At least you still got me, right?
(EXCLAIMS SOFTLY)
TJ, you ready to go?
Go? Go where?
(TJ CHUCKLES)
You're more strong. Come on!
- Give back my shoe. (CHUCKLES) Max.
(GRUNTS)
TJ: Come on, Max!
- Max!
(GRUNTS)
AGENT THORN: Come.
TJ: Go on, Max.
Do your job.
(GRUNTS)
How about over here?
Who'd like some water?
- Here you go, darling.
(EXCLAIMS)
- Good, yeah.
- Lovely.
(CLEARS THROAT)
- I will be coxswain.
(CHUCKLES) Co-coxswains.
- TJ, come on!
- Alexandra.
AGENT THORN: Positions, everyone.
Eagle's about to take a dip.
Ugh!
(ALL CHEERING)
PRESIDENT BENNETT:
(SHOUTS) Come on, paddle!
PRESIDENT BENNETT: Quickly!
(EXCLAIMS)
- Wh oo!
- Quickly!
Attaboy, TJ!
PRESIDENT BENNETT: Good job, guys!
(SHOUTS) Look out!
PRESIDENT BRAGOV: Back paddle!
Back paddle!
Back!
(ALL GRUNT)
(PRESIDENT BRAGOV GRUNTS)
PRESIDENT BRAGOV: Paddle!
(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
Whoo! We did it!
(ALL CHEERING)
Everybody, high-five!
(ALL EXCLAIM)
(MAN CHEERING IN DISTANCE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
PRESIDENT BENNETT:
Looks like our countries
can work together when we need to, eh?
Da. (PANTS)
I believe in peace.
PRESIDENT BRAGOV:
But there are those in my country
who think peace is weak.
They think any talks
whatsoever with your country
amounts to treason.
What do you think?
(SIGHS) I think...
(SHOUTS) Here we go again!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Well done, Alexandra!
PRESIDENT BRAGOV: Stay in the middle!
Stay in the middle!
Hang on, Alexandra!
Paddle!
(EXCLAIMS)
PRESIDENT BENNETT:
(SHOUTS) To the right!
- Paddle!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
PRESIDENT BRAGOV: Paddle, Alexandra.
PRESIDENT BENNETT: Harder, TJ!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(SCREAMS)
(CRIES)
- Alexandra!
- TJ!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(SHOUTS IN RUSSIAN)
(SCREAMS)
(SHOUTS) Dad, help!
PRESIDENT BRAGOV: Alexandra!
TJ: (SHOUTS) Help!
AGENT THORN: All agents, move in now!
TJ: Dad!
PRESIDENT BENNETT: TJ!
- I'm coming!
(GASPS)
Alex!
(SHOUTS) No!
No! Alex!
Save Alexandra!
Help!
(SCREAMS)
- Dad!
PRESIDENT BENNETT: TJ!
TJ!
(SHOUTS) Papa! Help!
Alexandra!
Papa!
TJ: Dad!
Hold on!
Dad!
Okay, I got you! I got you, you're okay.
I got you! Come on!
(SHOUTS) Help!
(SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN)
(OLGA SHOUTS IN RUSSIAN)
(SCREAMS)
- Help!
OLGA: Alexandra!
ALEX: Help!
Papa!
Help!
ALEX: Help!
Papa!
(GASPS) Max!
Max!
Oh!
(GRUNTS)
(COUGHS)
(PANTING)
Oh.
(CRIES) Thank you, Max!
Yeah. Thank you, boy.
Alexandra. (SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(CRIES) Alexandra.
- Alexandra. (SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
- Papa“.
- Alexandra.
- I'm okay.
I'm okay.
(PANTING)
(ALL YELLING)
(SHOUTS) Enough!
My daughter was almost killed.
I do not want to hear any more
of your sincere apologies.
We inspected the raft
fully before embarking.
It must've gotten caught on
a sharp rock or some flotsam...
Or someone tried to sink it on purpose.
TJ, on purpose?
We went over this.
Dad, did you feel us hit anything?
Because I know I didn't.
And do you really think it's a coincidence
that we were all attacked...
Okay, TJ, enough!
You heard Agent Thorn, it was an accident.
- But I just...
PRESIDENT BENNETT: Don't!
I don't wanna hear another word. Drop it.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(SOFTLY) Go on, Max, give it to Alex.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING CONTINUES)
TJ?
- Over here!
(GASPS)
Don't scare me like that.
Sorry.
Did anyone follow you?
Just you.
Payback for when you followed me.
I think I know who's trying
to stop the talks.
Agent Thorn.
(EXCLAIMS) That's a relief.
I thought you were going to say
something crazy, like Agent Thorn.
I'm serious.
Think about it.
Where was he when we all
went overboard today?
And it was his job to check the raft.
And it was his job
to follow up on all leads
for both attacks.
Exactly. And all that stuff about Max
not spending time with me?
He probably knew he'd sniff him out.
He also could've intentionally
let us sneak out to go to that party
so you'd get attacked.
I knew it, an American is behind this.
Wait. Who said he was American?
He could really be a Russian in disguise.
A double agent.
Remember the accent we heard that night?
He was probably faking that accent
to make it seem like he was Russian.
An American posing as a Russian.
A triple agent.
Or he's a quadruple agent.
Really a Russian,
faking the accent of an American,
doing a Russian accent
so we'd think he was American...
Okay. Maybe we should
stop at double agent.
Russian or American.
I can live with that.
So, wait.
Are we really accusing the head
of your presidential security...
Of what is basically treason
with almost no proof?
My dad will think I'm crazy.
And as much as my papa would like to
embarrass your country,
I think he would, too.
So, we set up a trap to
expose him to our fathers.
Saving the arms talks.
BOTH: And the world!
(BOTH SIGH)
Yeah.
But how the heck are we gonna do that?
I think I know.
MAN: All right. Take it up, man.
Up. Yes, that up. Good.
MAN: There we go.
Yeah... That's good.
Now, tie that off.
MAN: Make sure you tie it off really good.
(TJ GROANS)
My tummy hurts.
(GROANS)
Well...
You do feel a bit warm.
Yeah.
I think it was the borscht.
It's, uh, really rushin' through me.
(CHUCKLES)
(GROANS)
Well, I'm sure your mom will understand.
Max, make sure he drinks
plenty of liquids, okay?
All right, get some rest.
Alex, Alex.
Over. Alex!
(BUZZING)
PRESIDENT BRAGOV: I do not understand.
Why can you not tell me
what is wrong with you?
Well... Uh...
If Mama was here, I could tell her.
Oh.
I see.
(NERVOUSLY) Well...
Feel better, or rest up.
Thank you, Papa. I will.
(DOOR CLOSES)
TJ: (OVER RAND) Alex, Alex, over.
TJ, what are you doing?
ALEX: I said I would call you
when I was ready.
- My papa almost found out I had this.
TJ: Sorry.
You good for tonight?
ALEX: Do not worry.
My papa will not
check on me again tonight.
Or probably ever again.
Good, then Operation
"Catch-a-Quintuple-Agent" is a go.
You couldn't leave it alone, could you?
Nope.
Thank you for coming, Bragov.
It's my pleasure, Mr. President.
I am afraid Alexandra
will not be joining us this evening.
(AWKWARDLY) She's not feeling Well.
Your son is not coming, either?
Uh...
No.
Also not feeling well.
Maybe they have the same ailment.
I do not think so.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(ALL APPLAUDING)
I've always believed
that music was a universal language.
A language that we all speak.
A language of humility,
love,
and, most importantly, peace.
(PLAYING TUNE)
(SOFTLY) Okay, remember the plan.
When Max lures Thorn,
you pretend to faint,
- and when he bends down, I snap.
- I know.
It's my plan. Remember?
Your plan? But I'm the one who...
(SIGHS) Forget it.
Go, Max, fetch Thorn.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(GASPS) Quick!
MAN: All clear, backstage.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
Was this part of your plan, too?
(NERVOUSLY) I don't know.
- Um...
- It's okay. It's good part.
You're right.
Her Tchaikovsky's not half-bad.
Well, half-thank you.
(MAX GROWLS)
Max, what are you doing here?
(GROWLS)
(AUDIENCE SHUSHING)
Shh!
Leaving my post.
TA: Well, no security detail.
We're alone.
Yeah? And how does it feel?
(NERVOUSLY) Very
secure.
I feel same,
also, hot and worried about
running out of air.
But secure, that, too.
(DOOR THUDS)
(GASPS)
Make that very worried.
(WHIMPERS)
(GROWLING)
(SNARLS)
(DOORS RUMBLING)
(MAX BARKING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLING)
(MAX GROWLING)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH PANTING)
(MAX GROWLING)
Mom, look out!
(SCREAMING)
(SHOUTS) Maureen!
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH PANTING)
(MAX BARKING)
(MAX BARKS)
(PANTING)
It doesn't matter that we tricked you.
If we weren't here,
Mom could've been hurt or worse!
I don't understand.
Who could've done something like this?
Him!
Excuse me?
TJ: Look at his ankle, Dad.
He'll have the bite marks
from the day Max saved me.
(SIGHS)
(RELUCTANTLY) Agent Thorn, I'm...
I'm sorry, this is really awkward.
It's no problem at all, sir.
But, no, it's not possible.
TJ.
Alexandra,
it is time for us to go.
ALEX: Go where?
To the safest place on Earth,
Moscow.
- Go. Go!
(STUTTERS)
Vladimir, you're leaving?
Do we, at least, have a deal
on the drawdown?
As I said,
if you cannot protect our children,
how can you protect our children?
Come, Alexandra.
I'm sorry, TJ.
Vladimir!
PRESIDENT BENNETT: Well.
Great.
(SIGHS)
Well, it seems who was ever trying
to sabotage the meetings
has finally succeeded.
Mr. President, our new security canine
has clearly been corrupted
by his relationship with your son,
as I feared.
Permission to terminate his service here.
What? No, Dad, you can't do that!
TJ, you've brought this upon yourself.
Thomas!
Agent Thorn,
permission granted.
(METAL CLINKING) Thank you, sir.
- Dad!
- Please, no.
- Max.
- Mom.
- I'm sorry.
(WHIMPERS)
Let's go, Max.
(METAL CLICKS)
- Come on.
- Dad, please.
- Let's go. Max.
(WHINING)
(MAX HOWLING)
- Come on. Come on.
- Come on.
(MAX WHIMPERS)
Max! Come!
(WHIMPERING)
- Come on. Come on.
Let's go, Max. Come on.
Max, wait. Don't go!
(WHIMPERS)
(WHIMPERING)
TA: I'm really gonna miss you. Max.
I'm really gonna miss you, boy.
I'm really gonna miss you.
- Let's go, Max.
(WHIMPERING)
Come on, come on.
(MAX YELPS)
AGENT THORN: Let's go, Max.
(WHIMPERING)
In.
(WHIMPERS)
(BARKING)
Hey.
You're up early.
Couldn't sleep.
Ah.
I know you're bummed the Rooskies
are leaving early.
But I gotta tell ya, that Russian chef,
bigger dictator than Bragov.
Nice try, Coop.
You can't beat yourself up about this, T.
You followed your gut, you saved your mom.
But now, I'll never know
who was really behind it,
and that's not even the worst part.
My dad can barely even look at me.
I'll never see Alex again,
(SIGHS) and who knows what they'll do
to Max, now that he's been "corrupted."
Look at it this way, T.
At least you got the first chapter
of your memoirs figured out.
As usual, Coop,
you're the only one around here
who makes me feel any better.
(SPOON CLANKING)
- Oh!
Oh. Hey.
Let me help you with that.
(NERVOUSLY) Uh,
I guess I better start packin'.
Oh. yeah?
Are you sure you don't want a smoothie?
Nah, I'm cool.
No worries, see you back at WH.
Uh, yeah, the White House.
T,
You know I can't let you leave,
not after what you just saw.
(NERVOUSLY) What do you mean?
I didn't see anything.
Nice try, kiddo.
Coop, what are you doin'?
Oh, yeah.
My name's not really Coop, T.
That's just a good friendly
American name, no?
What? You're Russian?
You've been behind all this?
- Why?
Because peace is weak.
The people I work with will not allow
my country to surrender its weapons,
not for your country, not for anyone.
I will keep Mother Russia strong,
not men like Bragov.
So, now,
I'm going to give you a choice.
You can keep trying
to play the hero, or...
(GRUNTS)
(MUFFLED GRUNTS)
You have made your choice.
(GRUNTS) om
- This time, you'll not get out so easy.
(GRUNTS)
(SHOUTS) Let me out!
WOMAN: (OVER PHONE) Da?
Time for insurance policy, Olga.
Yeah, privy to Alexandra.
Olga. (GRUNTS)
I'm really sorry it had to come to this.
I really enjoyed our talks
over these months.
And,
FYI,
the secret to a great grilled cheese
is to add just a touch
of Russian dressing.
(LAUGHING)
(SHOUTS) Help! Help!
Can anyone hear me? Help!
TJ: (SHOUTS) Help!
Sweetheart, wake up.
Your papa, he wants to see you now.
- What? My papa?
- Yeah.
- Put on your slippers.
(GROANS)
Let's go.
(GROANING)
That's it.
(SHOUTING) Help!
(GRUNTING)
- Come on, Alexandra.
(GROANS)
Careful, now.
Wait, Olga.
What is my father doing out here?
- No more question.
(SCREAMS)
(OLGA SHUSHING)
(MAX SNARLING)
TJ: (SHOUTS) Help!
(SIGHS)
(SIREN BLARING)
(SHOUTS) Get the dog!
(BARKING)
MAN: Block him off!
- What is going...
(MAX BARKS)
Max? Come here!
- Where is it?
- Close in!
Max! Max!
PRESIDENT BRAGOV: But you're security,
you can't even stop a dog!
TJ?
- Max!
(BARKING)
TJ! Thorn!
- TJ, come here.
- Oh, my God.
- Are you okay?
- What happened?
(PANTING) I'm fine, I'm fine.
Max! Max!
You saved me again, boy.
You saved me again.
Alex, she's in terrible danger.
Alexandra.
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
- The Hawk's on its way, sir.
We'll have eyes in the sky
in less than 10 minutes.
They can't have gone far, so, I set up...
They'll never find her at this rate.
AGENT THORN:
Depending on which direction they've gone,
we'll have to split up our resources.
- Come here, Max.
(SNIFFING)
Seek, Max, seek. Seek, Max, seek.
(BARKING)
Everybody!
If you wanna find her, follow Max.
MAN: All right, men, move out. Go, go, go!
There's Max!
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS) No!
Stop!
- Argh!
(GRUNTS)
PRESIDENT BENNETT: Stay With him, Thorn.
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
(PANTS)
(GRUNTS) Don't!
(GRUNTS)
Tsk, tsk. It's not safe
for you to be in woods alone.
ALEX: (SCREAMS) Help!
(BARKS)
PRESIDENT BENNETT:
Pull up, pull up! Stop!
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
- Look what Max found.
- That is Alex's.
TJ, get in, come on!
(GRUNTING)
(YELLING) Wait till my father
gets his hands on you two!
(CLOSING DOOR)
- Rotten door.
- Told you not to get an American car.
(ALEX GRUNTING)
Go, go, go! Come on!
Max, find her, please!
All units! We need to cut off
all access routes north of the river.
(GRUNTING)
Shut her up!
(ALEX SCREAMS)
- Naughty little girl.
(SCREAMING)
OLGA: (GRUNTS) Naughty!
Naughty!
- I got her!
(SCREAMS) No!
OLGA: I got you!
ALEX: Stop, stop!
I hate that dog!
(SCREAMS)
(BARKS)
- Argh!
(SNARLING)
(BOTH SCREAM)
- Argh!
(GRUNTING)
(COOP GRUNTING)
(MAX GROWLING AGGRESSIVELY)
(SHOUTS) Get him, Max!
(GRUNTS)
(MAX GROWLING)
(MAX YELPING)
COOP: Stupid dog!
(GRUNTS)
MALE FBI AGENT 1: Out Of the vehicle!
(BARKS)
(GRUNTS)
(SHOUTING)
Get him off me! Get this animal off me!
MAN: Take her away.
We would've gotten away with it, too,
if it wasn't for these meddling kids
and the dog!
TJ: Hey, Coop.
I know everyone in maximum security's
gonna love your grilled cheese!
Listen, TJ,
I am so sorry that I didn't listen to you.
- It's okay, Dad.
- No, it's not okay.
We may be the First Family,
but we are a family first.
(PANTING)
I know how difficult
this must've been for you to be
ripped out of your old life.
(SOFTLY) I promise you,
I am going to do everything I can
to make your new one a little easier.
Oh...
I love you.
PRESIDENT BRAGOV: Alex, I am flying in
my personal physician
to make sure you are all right.
Papa, that is not necessary.
But there is something
that you can do for me.
Just say the word, my precious angel.
(OVER SPEAKERS) I'm pleased to announce
that we've come to terms
on a historic nuclear arms treaty.
One that will keep
both our countries strong.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(SHUTTER CLICKING)
(OVER SPEAKERS) And one more thing.
We wouldn't be here today
if it weren't for someone very special.
Now, this may be a little bit unorthodox
but also incredibly deserved.
I am pleased to present
the very first ever K-9 Medal of Honor
to an amazing dog named Max!
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(SHUTTER CLICKING)
You really have to leave tonight?
Why, do you want to accuse me of
another conspiracy before I go?
You're not gonna let me
live that down, are you?
Like I said, not until it stops being fun.
(SIGHS) I was right about one thing,
though.
What is that?
A Russian was behind it.
But he was undercover as
American in White House.
So, we call it even?
I'll take it.
(CLEARS THROAT)
- What was that?
(CHUCKLES)
Excuse me.
Sorry to interrupt.
But I'm afraid
Max's time with us has come to an end.
I'm really gonna miss you, Max.
We all are.
TA: I know you're gonna miss me too, boy.
Go on.
(ENGINE STARTS)
He sure is some dog, huh?
Yeah...
It's not gonna be the same
around here without him.
TJ?
Why don't you come with us?
I think we may have something
that'll cheer you up.
Come on.
PRESIDENT BENNETT:
These are Charlie 's puppies.
(PUPPY WHIMPERING)
- Take your pick.
(ALL WHIMPERING)
I want them all.
Hi, guys.
- Who wants to play with TJ?
(ALL BARKING)
Come on! Come on, guys.
(GIGGLING)
You got my ear. (LAUGHS)
(GIGGLING) So ticklish!
(GIGGLING CONTINUES)
aLDEN @ Symbianize
English - SDH