[Non-english speech]
Stop.
[Moaning]
He won't do anything.
I'm serious!
Grandpa, I just want him to do
one trick, and he won't do it!
You'll never got a
job with the circus!
Sit down.
Roll over.
Give me a high five.
[Bark]
Up, up.
Dad, should I lock it up, or
are you gonna come with us?
Yeah, I'm coming.
What do you think?
Billy, come on.
Let's go.
In the car.
Come on.
Can I bring Shaq?
I can train him at the park.
How many times have I told you?
That dog is untrainable.
You're wasting your time.
But you haven't seen him.
He's doing better.
Speak.
[Bark]
Please!
Sure.
Come on, Shaq!
Oops.
Where are your shoes?
In the truck.
Why aren't you wearing them?
They hurt my feet.
They're too small?
My feet are too big.
I told your mom to
buy 2 sizes bigger.
Now another 20 bucks wasted.
You know, when I was your
age, I had three jobs.
I'm not gonna be
a gardener, Dad.
I don't really want
you to be a gardener.
I want to teach you
something... to be responsible.
What do you think?
All right.
Let's talk price.
You made the right choice.
It's a wise investment and
the buy of the century.
You get a Ford product
with a Japanese engine,
Which means you get comfort
and performs for 5,000 less.
Let's go.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Hey.
You test drove this.
I hate foreign anything.
I only buy American.
No, no.
It was made here.
It is American.
You said a Japanese engine.
It's a Japanese engine made
here in our Georgia factory.
Let me introduce
you to my manager.
[Non-english speech]
What woman would not want
to buy this piece, huh?
And what man wouldn't want
to take it off, huh, Don?
This piece was inspired
from the red corvette.
It's hot.
It will not stay in your stores.
[Non-english speech]
Don't tell me.
You're on your way,
but you're running
15 minutes late, which
is 45 in real time,
And you can't pick Johnny up.
I got stuck.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't leave.
I was with a client.
What time does the game start?
Well, it's at midnight.
They moved it just for you.
Richard, why are you
being so difficult?
Because I'm busy, Irene.
Because the game is
always at 2 o'clock,
And you know that
because you failed
To pick him up five times.
Now, I gotta get out of
here and get him there
Because you're not there again.
I'll make it up to you.
I've got a customer
who's been waiting
30 minutes for a meatloaf.
If he doesn't get
it in 30 seconds,
He's walking outta here.
OK, OK.
I... I gotta go, Irene.
Thank you.
You think I parked too close?
Yeah, I mean, I hit other
car when I opened the door.
I better not have another dent.
The first dent was
with your parking.
You hit a pole at
the supermarket
While you were on the phone.
I know how I got
the dent, Derrick.
I don't need you to
remind every day.
I don't remind you every day.
But you still use a cell
phone while you drive.
I wasn't even on the phone.
No, you weren't on the phone.
You were dialing.
You know something?
I don't need this.
OK?
I have a very bad day.
In fact, I've had a bad month.
I had four ups.
I didn't sell a single car.
No sales, no
commission, no money.
I blanked.
I'm sorry you're not
selling any cars, Daddy.
Oh, look.
There's Daniel.
Daniel!
Oh.
Oh, sweetie, I missed you.
You just saw me yesterday.
Did I?
Can you have dinner with me?
Oh, I wish I could, honey,
but tonight's not my night.
Come on, Billy.
See you later, Mom.
OK, I'll be
watching you, honey.
OK.
Hi.
Hi, Linda.
Move, Derrick!
[Cheering]
Focus, Billy, focus.
Let's go.
Get at it, Billy.
Move your feet, Billy.
Come on.
Way to go.
Way to go, son.
That's my boy.
Go!
OK, let's go.
Come on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Way to go.
Come on, guys.
Billy, run faster!
Run, run.
Move your feet!
Feet, feet, move your feet!
Get on your horse.
Move.
Run, run, run.
Come on.
Feet, feet, feet.
Billy, you're not tired.
It's a mind thing.
You're never tired.
Never get tired.
Don't stop moving.
OK, yeah, yeah, yeah.
MAN: Give it what you got, guys.
Come on, guys.
WOMAN: Hustle out there.
Come on, you guys.
Keep it moving.
[Whistle]
It's all right.
Oh man.
Keep moving.
[Whistle]
Come on.
Good job, man.
Daddy, we lost.
You can't win them all.
You did good.
Let's go to the store,
get something to eat.
What you want?
Pasta, I guess.
Daddy's famous pasta?
Billy, keep the ball in motion.
Don't let it stop
completely, OK?
Come on, Billy.
Don't let it stop.
Dad,
I'm tired.
Come on.
Just try.
Can we stop, please?
Just five more minutes.
Now kick the ball.
I don't want to!
Don't whine like a
little girl, all right?
Just kick the ball.
All right?
OK.
Kick the ball!
Hey, Burt.
The kid's tired.
Give him a break.
Let him rest.
Who cares about the ball?
And when do we eat?
I'm starving.
You think that was
funny, young man?
It wasn't funny.
Now walk the dog 10 blocks, OK?
You raise him.
Come on, Shaq.
Let's go for a walk.
Come on.
Here we go.
Yeah, it's a pretty day.
Don't you think, Shaq?
Don't overcook the pasta.
You know I like it al dente.
Tried to do a good job, master.
Here.
Go on.
They're good?
They're al dente?
Go sit at the table, man.
Linda?
Come, come, come, come, come.
Sit down.
[Non-english speech]
Dad, can I have a soda?
No.
You drink your milk.
Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah.
Wait for your mother, so we can
all eat together like a family.
But I'm starving.
And she's late.
That's more of
a reason to wait.
God, please bless this
food we are about to eat.
God, bless Mommy and Daddy.
God, please heal the
sick, give joy to the sad,
And hope to the hopeless.
Amen.
That was great, Derrick.
Thank you.
You know, the sauce could
use a little more oregano.
I'll remember that next time.
Perfect.
Dad, are you worried because you
haven't sold any cars lately?
No.
No, remember we
talked about this.
In sales, we have
mountains and valleys.
We've been in a valley
for over a month.
I hear from my manager
all day, Derrick.
I don't need to
hear it from you.
You're the one who
keeps on mentioning it.
I do that?
A lot.
I'm sorry.
How can I explain it.
It... it's like soccer.
You know how you guys might go
a few games and don't score?
And then bam... three
goals in five minutes.
We scored three goals today,
and we still lost the game.
Bad example.
How's the pasta?
It's OK.
It's almost as good as Mom's.
Right.
She called today.
Is she coming back?
She's here!
Dios mio!
What happened?
[Non-english speech]
Who... who did it?
It's our summer release.
What do you think?
Well, if all the men have the
same response, we'll go bust.
Why are you still mad?
I said I was working.
I had a $75,000 order to design.
You know, that's funny.
Because you design, you
create, you make art.
You didn't talk like
that till you partnered
With that prick Pierce.
Oh, here we go
with the jealousy.
I am not screwing him.
I am trying to seduce you.
I am not jealous
of that French fuck.
I don't give a shit
how good looking he is,
Or that he does Pilates.
But I'm sick and tired of
him talking down to me!
He doesn't talk down to you.
Richard, Richard,
how's your... how's
Your little restaurant doing?
How many cheeseburgers
did you sell this week?
Well, I tell you what.
If it wasn't for that
little restaurant,
You wouldn't have a company.
Am I gonna hear this again?
I said I was working.
I'm sorry.
I mean, what do
you want from me?
Blood?
Come here.
I just... I just don't
like it that Johnny
And I are not as important
to you as your career.
That's not true.
Let me finish.
Now, I know you make a
lot more money than I do.
You should be happy
for me, for us.
You should be happy.
I am happy.
I'm proud of you.
I love you.
We just want you to spend more
time with us as a family, OK?
OK.
Mario.
Wow, cleats!
Thank you, Mama.
Thank...
Hey, hey.
Enough.
How was the game?
We lost, but I
scored two goals.
It was excellent.
I would have loved
to have seen it.
Come on Sunday.
I'm sorry, Mario,
but I have to work.
Not Sunday.
We need the money.
One day, when I'm a
professional soccer player,
I'm gonna buy you a big
house with a huge garden.
Your father will love that.
His own garden.
And his own gardener too.
I want my dad to take it easy.
Well, it's OK.
We'll get our own gardener, and
our own maid, and chef, just
Like Mrs. Rafiki.
And we'll all go live
in Beverly Hills.
[Non-english speech]
Hey, hey.
I didn't hear you come in.
Come on.
Let's go to bed.
I'm so sorry.
I would never leave you again.
Shh.
I don't think we could
have made it without you.
I missed you so much.
Can you ever forgive me?
[Glass shatters]
Look, why don't you
jump in the Humvee?
Take a spin, get some fresh air.
It'll make you feel better.
Can't leave my post, sir.
That's an order.
Stop, I said stop.
Stop.
[gunshots]
[Moaning]
Dad?
Wake up.
I'm gonna be late for school.
Come on.
Wake up.
Come on, Dad.
I'm gonna be late for school.
Thank you, Marta.
You're welcome.
Marta, what happened to you?
Oh.
No, I got robbed.
- You got robbed?
- No, no.
It's OK.
It's nothing.
Just some kid.
He took my money.
Are you OK?
Yes, yes, yes.
I should call my doctor.
No, no, non.
Thank you.
I'm OK.
You're sure?
Yes, it doesn't hurt.
It's nothing.
OK.
Dad, I'm gonna be
late for school.
Hmm.
- Wake up.
- All right, man.
Come on.
Give me a second.
Come on!
All right.
I'm up.
Ugh.
OK, what you want for breakfast?
I already ate two bowls of
cereal your coffee's ready.
I can smell it.
It smells pretty good.
Wait a minute.
Did you just say you
had two cups of coffee?
No.
Two bowls of cereal.
I had a crazy dream
that you dropped me off
At school on your way to work.
Cool, I was driving? 'Cause
I already know how, Dad.
I believe it.
I'm not even gonna
ask how you learned.
It's gonna be a great day.
Today is gonna be a great
day full of opportunities.
In fact, I bet I'll make
my first sale before noon.
Well, then, you
better hurry up,
Because I don't think you're
gonna go to work like this.
I guess I should change my
clothes and take a shower, huh?
Give me 7 minutes.
You always say that,
but you take 15.
Not this time.
Time me.
Where's my toothbrush?
Mrs. Rafiki, um, can I
ask if I can work more?
I could use more hours.
Even Sunday.
No, you work hard
enough already.
Please.
If you need me, I can
work nights for you
If you have dinner parties.
Here.
Take this.
No, no.
No, I'm not looking for charity.
It's not charity.
It's a raise.
I wanted to give you a raise
last year, but I couldn't.
Don't tell Mr. Rafiki.
All right.
I've warmed up.
OK, who you gonna be?
I'm gonna be Shaq.
No, no.
'Cause I'm bigger,
and I'm stronger.
No, no, no.
People will mock
you if you're Shaq.
Who you gonna be?
Come on?
I'm gonna be Kobe.
You're gonna be Kobe?
Well, then bring it, Kobe.
Come on.
Bring it.
Oh, Kobe shoots!
Oh, he's coming in, and
he's clearing the lane.
High percentage shot.
Oh no.
Will Kobe shoot again?
Is that Shaq?
I'm Shaq!
You're Kobe!
[Shouts]
Let me dribble it away.
Yeah, he's gonna shoot.
He's gonna shoot!
I'm making the Johnny Special.
OK, Dad.
Remember, no mayo.
I hate mayo.
Does this look like mayo?
No.
Come on.
I'm a professional.
Bye, you guys.
Bye, John.
Mwah.
I beat Dad 20 to 14.
20-17.
Remember I hit the three
pointer towards the end, and...
Dad, I won.
Yes.
Wow.
Are you traveling like that?
Like what?
Well, I mean you usually wear
a sweatsuit and no make-up.
We're meeting clients
as soon as we check in.
We?
What is with all the questions?
Just kiss me goodbye
and wish me luck.
All right.
Good luck, honey.
I... um, sweat.
Bye, Mom.
Have a nice trip.
Bye, sweetie.
OK, bye.
Good morning, ma'am.
Hi.
Is it your first?
My third.
We need a bigger car.
You like this one?
Has plenty of room.
We should take it for a spin.
You'll love the way it drives.
I should wait for my husband.
Is that the man
who dropped you off?
Where'd he go?
He forgot our checkbook.
He went home to get it.
Are you OK?
Would you like some water?
No, I'm OK.
Does it have a good stereo?
I need a good stereo.
I love music.
Oh, yes.
Me too.
There's no way I can
do even without it.
It has six speakers,
AM/FM stereo,
Plays DVDs, MP3s, has a CD.
Why don't you sit in here.
You're gonna love
it when you hear it.
[Music plays]
Hey, sounds good, right?
Let me go around and get
in that side with you.
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey!
Hey!
Come on.
Hey, stop the car.
Come back here.
Stop!
She stole the car.
Hey, call the cops.
Oh come on, man.
Lately, all I see is how
wonderful and sexy you look.
Stop it.
The fact that Richard
met you first is... it's
Not gonna stop me
form loving you.
You have three models a week.
Two hours, you'll
have another one.
Please, Irene.
If I had you, I would never
touch another woman again.
Oh, you're good.
Any other woman would
have melted by now.
Then why do you lead me on?
- Lead you on?
- Oui.
You lead me on.
What are you talking about?
What am I talking about?
The sexy clothes, the
beautiful hair, the perfume,
The pretty jewelry, hmm?
You didn't have to dress sexy.
We're not seeing any
clients, you know?
I like to look good.
For me?
Pierce.
Gracias.
Oh, that's for one load.
We did two loads.
No, no, no.
600.
All right?
You said $600.
For one load, senor.
$1,200 for two loads.
No, you said $600.
I said clean everything.
Now get out of here before
I call the immigration
Office or the police.
I don't care who you call.
You're gonna pay us
the money you owe us.
You threatening me
with a deadly weapon?
You know, just for
pointing that at me you can
Get 10 years in prison, amigo.
OK, so if I stick it in your
fucking stomach like this,
How many years do I get, amigo?
[Non-english speech]
Stop.
Hmm?
Now, please, pay us for
our work what we agree on.
Get off my property.
Pam, call 911.
OK, forget it.
I'll just take the 600.
Yeah, I thought you would.
You're gonna let this small
man get away with this?
You're gonna let him
rob us like this.
Let's go, Gerardo.
It's not worth it.
Shame on you, sir.
Get off my property, wetback.
You too, beaner.
OK, Gerardo.
There you go.
200 for you.
Oh no.
200, that's too much.
No, no, no.
That's what I told you.
It's good working with you.
You need a lift?
No, I'm OK.
OK.
Thanks a lot.
Billy, I'm gonna give
you three guesses.
What do you think they
had on special this week
At the grocery store?
I don't know.
I'll give you a hint.
On Monday, we had carrots,
and peas, and hot dogs.
On Tuesday, we had potatoes,
and coleslaw, and hot dogs.
And what do you think
we're having today?
Hot dog?
It's filet mignon.
Because that's what these
taste like to your dad.
It's mind over
matter... the military's
First line of defense.
Billy likes hot dogs.
You think everything you
push on Billy he likes.
It's not true.
Tell him, Billy.
You like hot dogs.
Don't you, Billy?
They're all right.
I like hot dogs too, but
not three times a week.
We got hot dogs
coming out of our ass.
Stand up to him, Billy.
Tell him you're sick of
hot dogs... and soccer.
He told me so himself.
I hate soccer too.
It's a faggot sport.
Come on.
Watch your mouth.
Watch what you say in
front of your grandson.
And soccer's not a faggot sport.
It is too.
It is not!
It is.
It's a faggot sport.
Football is a manly sport.
Look what the players wear...
Helmets and body armor.
They're like soldiers
going into battle.
In soccer, they wear little
shorts and little tank tops.
Need I say more?
In football, a
timeout is so they
Can carry players off the field
on stretchers on their way
To the hospital.
In soccer, timeout is a warning.
They wave a little yellow
card or a little pink card.
I don't know why
you want my grandson
To play a faggot sport.
I tried to teach
him how to box.
I tried to teach him how to box.
I don't like to hit people.
See?
He doesn't like to hit people.
You have to hit people!
It's always you or
the other guy, OK?
Now, if I didn't
have this attitude,
I'd be dead right
now, and so'd he.
You understand?
Jesus Christ, Burt.
The kid's 10 years ago.
He's still trying
to find himself.
I don't care how old he is.
I mean, you fought in war, Dad.
I just fought in one.
In another 10 years, he'll
be fighting in one, and it...
It's my job to get him ready.
I don't wanna go to war.
Three civilians were
beheaded yesterday,
Oil workers from Kansas.
Well, if they didn't
wanna be beheaded,
Then they shoulda
stayed in Kansas.
And who's going
to rebuild Iraq?
You?
Do you think their sole
motive was to rebuild Iraq?
I mean, they're getting paid
three times as much over there
Than they are at home, so...
It's barbaric.
It's medieval.
When we dropped thousands of
missiles on Baghdad in Iraq,
We killed thousands of kids.
And what?
It's civilized because we didn't
see them die on television?
It's not the same thing!
It's the same result.
They're all dead.
So I don't see the difference
between beheading civilians
Or dropping missiles
on civilians.
Here, here.
Cheers.
I think everyone
seemed very happy.
The meat was overcooked.
I thought it was perfect.
It was burnt.
I'm sorry.
Is that why you're
sleeping with Sooha?
What did you say?
You heard me.
You are accusing me of
sleeping with your best friend?
You are crazy.
I'm not crazy.
I saw the way you
were holding her hand.
How was I holding her hand?
Very naturally, like you've
been doing it for years.
Between Dr. Phil and
Opera, you are going crazy.
You are nuts!
Stop saying that!
What do you want me to say?
I want you to say that you're
not cheating on me, because you
Love me, because you respect me
as a wife and as a human being!
I want you to tell me the truth!
I want to be kissed, and
held, and looked at the way
You were looking at her.
How can you even ask me that?
She's your best friend.
Do you think she
would betray you?
I'm sorry.
You're right.
Sooha would never do that.
What the fuck are
you doing here?
I'm pointing a
deadly weapon at you,
Which will later be referred
to as the murder weapon.
Li... listen.
Don't you wanna know how
many years I can get for it?
Don't you wanna know?
Don't worry.
I'll tell you.
Because you won't be
around to hear it.
15 to life.
What comes out of your
mouth next will determine
How much pain I inflict on you.
I'm sorry.
Dude, I don't wanna hear
your bullshit apology.
I don't wanna hear that shit.
What I wanna hear is how you
take advantage of everyone
Around you, like you
did my friend Hector.
OK, OK.
I do.
I take advantage of people.
Yeah, because you're
a piece of shit.
I am.
I am a piece of shit.
Get up.
Ow!
God!
[Screaming]
I'll give you... I'll
give you your money.
There's $3,000 in there.
You can take it.
Just please don't hit me again.
Why couldn't you just
give us the money?
We worked for it.
And instead, all you
wanted to do was push.
Oh god!
Stop.
I just got out the joint.
And now something
like this is just
Gonna send me straight back.
I'm afraid you've been
sentenced to death.
No, no, no!
[Thud]
Excuse me, sir.
May I help you?
You know, my first
brand new car was a Ford.
Crown Victoria.
It was a burgundy color.
1983.
I was just a kid.
Oh wow.
What a beauty.
My wife loved that car.
Could you spare some change?
Sure.
You don't mind me asking, sir,
how'd you become homeless?
Life.
Life happens to you.
Yeah.
Yeah, I can understand that.
Go, Johnny.
Go, go, buddy.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Good job.
Yeah, yeah.
MAN: Keep running.
Good try.
It's all right, son!
Oh.
Is that legal?
Keep us in the game.
Oh!
Come on, guys.
Come on.
Come on!
Yes!
There you go.
There you go, son.
Yeah, that's right.
[Whistle]
OK.
Does this other guy seem older?
Come on.
It's OK.
It's all right.
Come on.
Come on, guys.
[whistle]
Goalie!
He's terrible.
He's bad.
MAN: He can't block.
Hey.
Can I fix you a plate?
No thanks.
I'm not hungry.
Richard, you haven't
eaten anything all day.
I know.
It's rare, but I'm
trying to lose a few.
Come on.
You look great.
Thanks.
You know, Kelly, you
don't have to serve me.
It's not part of
your job description.
I don't mind.
I love serving you.
Besides, a good man
like you deserves
To be well taken care of.
Yeah.
OK, I'll... I'll take a salad,
and a steak, and maybe, like,
A real small baked potato.
Yeah.
And how about a little piece
of blueberry pie with ice cream
On the side?
That'd be great.
I'll bring you
another cup of coffee.
All right.
I'll tell you one thing.
When I have sex with my
wife it's like magic.
As soon as I get into
bed, she disappears.
And the last time my
wife drove the car,
She cracked it up
and went into a tree.
She told me it wasn't her
fault. She blew her horn.
What a crowd.
Who is this guy?
Rodney Dangerfield.
Who?
He's a legend.
Rodney Dangerfield.
I tell you, my wife and
I, we never have sex.
We get undressed, we can't
stop laughing, you know?
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you, with my wife I
never know what's coming next,
You know?
Last night, she made
chocolate mousse.
An antler got
stuck in my throat.
And my kids, they
don't help either.
The other day told my
kid, someday you'll
Have children of your own.
He said so will you.
Yo, mamacita,
give me that purse.
[Non-english speech]
Give it up!
I said give it to me, huh?
How was Vegas?
Good.
Glad to be home.
Did you win?
I didn't gamble.
I was too busy with
the convention.
I called your room at
midnight, and no one answered.
I couldn't sleep.
I went down to the
lounge for a drink.
Good night.
Set it down.
Marta, sit down a minute.
Yes, ma'am.
I expected him to cheat.
It's OK.
He's a man.
He comes home with
lipstick on his shirt.
I smell perfume.
I don't say anything.
I... I look the other way.
But... but to humiliate
me with my friend?
I knew he was cheating
with her, so that's why
I hired a private detective.
Sooha?
Yes.
Sooha.
What are you going to do?
What can I do?
I was hoping I was wrong.
I wish I did not do this.
It's better not to know.
[Non-english speech]
Isn't he afraid of
losing half of his money?
Our money is all tied up in
an overseas company trust.
If I leave, I get nothing.
You are wrong.
He will never let you go.
How do you know that?
I'm a good judge of character.
And I'm sorry to say this but,
your husband, he's a coward.
He talks a big game, I watch
him argue with his friends.
And as soon as one of
them stands up to him,
He backs down.
He speaks French
to his friends.
You understand French?
I don't need to understand
a foreign language
To see through to the
heart of a person.
Here, turn.
I don't know what, but
something's still missing.
We should just forget
this one and move on.
It's totally screwed up.
This...
It's the silk.
It's too soft to support the
sleek line you're looking for.
I can fix it.
I can put a bow in
there, there, and there.
And just give me a crack
at it before you scrap it.
I love the
simplicity of it all.
It's perfect.
And I love the way it feels on.
Can I have it?
You see?
Everyone's gonna want it.
You've outdone
yourself again, Irene.
You think so?
Yes.
You know what?
Maybe it's the bows.
Get rid of the bows.
Sure.
Uh, Why don't you come with me?
You should try it on yourself.
You'll look better in it.
Try it on.
Stop it.
Oh please.
You walk out of this house,
there is no coming back!
I'm not planning to come back.
I divorce you, and
you'll never get a penny!
I swear to God!
Oh, stop with your threats!
I want a divorce.
I don't want your money!
I'll get a job, and I'll
support myself the way I
Supported you all those years.
To hell with your
money and your mansion.
When I married you,
you had nothing.
But you were a good and a decent
man who cared about people!
The more money you
made, the worse you got.
In my eyes, you are
a very poor man.
OK.
I made a mistake.
I will not see Sooha again.
It's not about Sooha anymore.
I don't respect you,
and I don't trust you.
She meant nothing to me!
You are my wife, and you're
not leaving this house!
This is not Morocco.
You don't own me,
and you cannot order
Me like a meal in a restaurant.
What happened to you?
You see?
Looks better on you.
I just wanted to say goodbye.
He did not stop you.
He did.
You were right.
Then why are you leaving?
An hour ago, I
didn't want to leave.
But now there's
nothing I want more.
I just want to get out of here.
Thank you, Marta.
So where are you going to go?
I'm going to stay with
my cousin Selma for now.
I'm sorry.
Thank you, Marta.
Irene, what the
hell are you doing?
What?
What do you mean?
Are you sleeping with Pierce?
No.
Why are you asking?
The way you guys are
looking at each other lately,
The way you respond to him.
It's that obvious?
Like a huge smoke signal.
Are you sleeping with him?
No, I am not.
But you're going to.
And that would be the
biggest mistake of your life.
No, it's... he flirts with me.
He finds me very
endearing and sexy.
I mean, it's nice to get
a compliment now and then.
God knows I haven't gotten
one from Richard in a decade.
You screw him, you
break up your marriage.
He's a calculating
son of a bitch.
It's not you he wants.
It's this business he needs.
You are so wrong.
He's crazy about me.
And please don't give me any
more advice on relationships.
Your track record doesn't
exactly speak for itself.
Fine.
Hey.
I love you, buddy.
I love you too, Dad.
You know, when I was your
age, my daddy used to tuck
Me in and tell me he loved me.
I used to say how much
you love me, Daddy?
He'd say wait and see.
I said wait and see what, Daddy?
Until you have a
son of your own.
Then you'll know
how much I love you.
Now, when I was your age, I
thought he was cracking up.
But now every time
I tuck you in,
I know exactly what
he was talking about.
You understand what I'm saying?
No.
Are you cracking up?
I walked right into
that one, didn't I?
All right.
Good night.
Mommy's not coming
back, is she/ she
Ran away because
she doesn't want me,
Because I drive her crazy.
She told me so.
Don't ever say that.
No, you drive me crazy.
I still want you.
Only reason your mom even put
up with me as long as she did
Is because of how
much she loves you.
But she called an hour.
I'm gonna go meet
her for a drink.
Yeah.
So you're gonna be
by yourself, OK?
But I have my cell phone on me,
and I'm only 10 minutes away
If you need me, OK?
Is Mommy coming back
home with you tonight?
Yeah, she is.
Wake me up when she
gets here, please.
No, I'm not gonna wake
you when she gets here.
But I'll tell you what.
Tomorrow morning, we're gonna
have a big old fashioned family
Breakfast.
And that's a promise.
All right, boy.
Mwah.
Good night.
What's wrong, Hector?
I want to go home.
But we are home.
We are American citizens now.
It doesn't feel like home.
Because of what happened to me?
It's everything.
I'm so tired all the time.
I feel so old.
Why do we have to be here?
But for our kids?
They will have a
better future here.
I can't even provide
enough for my family.
I want to take more
work, but I can't.
Last... last week, a man refused
to pay us for the work we did.
I lost faith in people.
Things are going to be fine.
Our kids won't have
it as tough as us.
They'll be educated.
They won't be
gardeners and maids.
They'll be professionals.
We have to do this for them.
Sorry I can't give
you a better life.
Oh, but you have, Hector.
You give me everything I need.
I'm proud of what we have.
Can you pick me up?
It could be.
No, it doesn't start.
No, look I think it's a lemon,
and you have to take it back.
So can you pick me up?
OK.
See you.
Car trouble?
You scared me.
I thought everybody'd gone home.
Uh, yes, they have, but I
was just doing some paperwork.
So you need a lift?
My roommate is
coming to get me.
OK.
Hey.
Uh, can I have that
teddy you promised?
Yes, of course.
It's... it's in my
office, but I had
To do some alterations to it.
Maybe you want to
try it on first?
Sure.
Perfect.
Please, come to my office.
[Singing in french]
Wow.
Putain de merde.
Tu es belle.
It's perfect.
I think it's big in here.
Where?
Here?
Mhm.
Right here.
No.
No, It's perfect.
Qu'est-ce que t'es
belle, putain.
Hey, you wanna hear
the craziest thing?
Yes, yes.
For the last two
years, I've been
Living with my boyfriend Josh.
He's a drummer in a band.
I won't tell anyone.
We have a German Shepard.
It hasn't left my side
since we got him as a puppy.
And when Josh fucks
me, the dog goes crazy.
Barks like a maniac.
I get so turned on.
You can't fuck without the dog?
Maybe you could just
bark a little for me?
Get me in the mood?
Bark?
Mhm.
Ruff, ruff.
Arf, arf!
Hmm, like a big dog.
Louder.
Arf, arf, arf, arf!
Maybe... maybe if
you get on all fours.
All fours?
It works.
Yes, yes.
Like a real big dog.
Arf, arf.
Oh, louder.
That's a little poodle.
I want a Great Dane.
Give it to me.
Arf, arf, arf!
Louder!
Arf!
Come on.
- Arf, arf, arf, arf!
- Come on.
Let me hear you.
Bark, bark!
Big dog.
It's a big dog!
[Barking]
Stop!
It's not working.
I need a real dog.
What do you mean
it's not working?
I can be a real dog.
Please, come back here!
Look.
Arf, arf, arf, arf, arf!
Please, come back here.
Merde.
Hey.
Thanks for calling.
We were worried sick about you.
I told you I wanted
to check out Vegas.
Yeah.
Yeah, you did.
But you didn't say you were
gonna have an adventure
And clean out the bank account.
I needed the money.
What?
You care more about me
or the lousy five grand?
This is a big mistake.
I don't need this shit.
Please.
Brenda, please.
We need to talk.
Just...
Coffee?
Can I see a wine list?
Uh, we have house wine.
Red or white?
What kind of red?
Cabernet?
Merlot?
Give me a break, honey?
What do I look like?
A wine connoisseur?
What happened to this town?
Did everyone take a rude pill?
Hey.
I'll take coffee, please.
Fine.
White, please.
Cup of joe and a chablis.
Thank you so much for
dining with us this evening.
Let's go home.
I have been going
out of my mind.
I have tried to make this work.
I have tried.
But I got married too early.
You got me pregnant.
I didn't want a baby at 20.
I had a singing career, but
you forced me to have it.
And I hate being a mom.
I'm not the fucking
soccer mom type.
Do you listen to
yourself when you speak?
Our son is 10 years old, and
you're still talking abortion.
Derrick is a beautiful boy.
And he misses his mommy.
Does that mean anything to you?
Don't do this to me, Mark.
Do not lay a guilt trip on me.
Christ, I need a drink.
How is he?
I was happy in Vegas.
No, I started writing
my own songs again.
And Danny wrote this
beautiful melody.
I mean, you should hear it.
It's awesome.
I sang it at the
Skylark the other night.
People went crazy.
I love being adored.
Adored?
Adored by who?
A bunch of lounge lizards?
Is that worth giving
up your family for?
You think you're the only one
with dreams and aspirations?
You think being a car salesman
was my life's ambition?
I do it to pay the bills.
Baby, if you want to
take a couple weeks
And sing wherever you
wanna sing, that's fine.
Danny and I are
moving in together.
We rented a house in Vegas.
I'm driving back
with him tonight.
I want a divorce.
What about Derrick?
You're good with him.
You're a good father.
I want you to have full custody.
You're not even gonna
say goodbye, are you?
I think it's best not to.
Best for who?
Best for you?
Normal people don't
act like this.
You wanna talk normal?
There is nothing normal
about our relationship, OK?
You should stick
to your own kind.
That's what my dad said
the first day I met you.
If I'd have listened
to him then,
I wouldn't be in
this fucking mess.
No, we have a son.
And you're not gonna toss him
out like an old pair of shoes.
Haven't you heard what
I've been telling you?
I do not want you.
I do not want our son.
I want a divorce!
That's what I want!
What are you doing?
I'm calling the cops.
[Coughing]
Ouch!
Mr. Johnson, I'm Nadia Baker.
So terribly sorry
to keep you waiting.
Can I get you anything?
My son, please.
Yes, he's fine.
Derrick's doing quite well.
May I see him?
No, actually.
Not quite yet.
I'll be straight with you.
I'm pretty new on the job.
However, I'm trying to
handle this as best as I can,
But it is a very
serious situation.
If this is proven to be neglect,
you could lose your son,
Or you could face up
to six years in prison.
Spare me what
the textbook crap,
And please bring someone in
here who is not new on the job
So I can ask them
some questions.
Like your supervisor.
In fact, I'm not
answering anything else
Until I see Derrick.
OK, Mark, I want to
reunite you with your son.
Then do it.
I can't do it.
My supervisor can't do it.
No one can do it until
the child undergoes
Psychological and physical
tests to prove it was not abuse.
Abuse?
You think I would abuse my son?
I don't know.
If you work with me voluntarily,
things will go smoother,
And it'll be over in a few days.
If you don't, you're gonna
force us to go to court,
Open up a case, and yeah,
you're gonna get a very
Experienced social worker.
And it's gonna take you
weeks, maybe even months.
Stop.
Just stop.
I can't possibly
live without him.
He's all I've got.
Do you understand that?
How often are you
left alone, son?
Is my dad in trouble?
No one is in trouble.
We just have to ask
these questions.
It's routine.
I wanna go home with my dad.
I know you do,
sweetie, but I can't
Let you do that right now.
I'm sorry.
I have to keep you
separated from your dad
While we run these tests.
It's gonna take a few days.
It's the law.
We're gonna call
your grandparents.
You'll have to stay with
them for a few days, OK?
They won't come?
Why not.
Because they hate black people.
You all right, Burt?
Oh yeah.
I'm OK, Dad.
It I'm OK.
Same dream?
Yeah.
It's that boy's face.
It's never gonna leave me, Dad.
Why didn't... why didn't
he start driving it?
I don't know.
Maybe he wanted them all to die,
and he was using you to do it.
It's not your fault. You
were just doing your job.
They were kids, Dad.
Come on.
They hadn't done nothing.
Why?
Things happen.
That's all.
And nobody understands why.
They just... they just do.
They just happen.
30 years I was in the army.
All those villages
we bombed in Vietnam,
I don't know what the
hell we were doing there.
You wanted to follow in my
footsteps and be a serviceman?
All right.
You could've stayed
here in Chatsworth,
Opened a hardware store,
some kind of a nice business,
A luncheonette maybe.
Whatever you were, you
could have done anything.
You could have saved
your marriage too.
Linda wouldn't have run off with
the office manager, whatever
That putz's name
was, if you hadn't
Been gone for a year in Iraq.
If you're trying
to cheer me up,
Dad, you're doing
a really lousy job.
Look at me.
The key to your sanity
is within your reach.
You have to stop
punishing yourself.
You just have to decide to
stop punishing yourself.
You have to let go.
Let go.
Let go of everything.
Let go of Billy, first of all.
He's not a soldier.
He's a 10 year old, a kid.
And you have to let go of Linda.
You have to forgive her.
You have to, for Billy's sake!
The boy needs his mother.
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
Yeah, yeah.
Thank you.
OK.
Please, look.
Look at that.
The workmanship is terrible.
It looks like it was
made by a blind person.
Look at these.
[Inaudible]
And we need it done quick,
quick, quick, quick.
Oh la la, another day is wasted.
You could get
down on all fours.
All fours?
Yeah, you know,
like a real dog.
No, please.
OK.
Yeah.
Just like that.
You really think he's trying
to take control of the company?
Yes.
And it's you who should
be controlling it.
Without you, there
is no company.
I feel like a total idiot.
I'm sorry.
Richard flipped
a million burgers
So I could have a career, and I
was gonna leave him for a dog.
Shaq, Shaq, stay.
Watch, Grandpa!
Watch what Shaq does.
Sit.
Now down.
Roll over!
Whoever said you can't
teach an old dog new tricks,
He had it all wrong.
I can't believe it.
I've been trying for months, and
all of a sudden he's doing it.
I know.
You'd better hurry up if you're
not gonna be late for the game.
Look, Billy.
You don't have to play today.
He doesn't have to play soccer?
I finally got it, Dad.
Just like that old dog.
Look, son.
I'm not gonna make you do
anything you don't wanna do.
But you love sports, Dad.
That's right.
I... I love sports.
I wanna go.
I wanna play today.
I think we're going to win.
Let him go.
The Tigers haven't
won a game all year.
Come on.
But Shaq never did a
trick before either.
I can feel it.
We can win today, Dad.
I wanna play.
Let's go.
Come on, Shaq.
So let me understand this.
You haven't sold of thing all
month, but you want a day off?
I'll be back.
All I need is three hours to
go downtown for a meeting.
You're supposed to
sell 23 cars a month.
The flooring on 23 cars is
$230 a day times 30 days.
You do the math.
That's over six grand.
That's what you
cost me this alone.
Last year, I was
the top salesman
For six straight months.
I've done great
for this company.
Look, Joe.
I'm having a hard time.
I have a problem.
Yes, you do.
You can't sell cars.
I can sell cars!
Well, then get out
there and sell something.
I don't have time for this.
I gotta get downtown.
I have a meeting
that I can't miss.
Hey, great.
You just stay downtown.
They got a lot of car
dealerships down here.
Why don't you get one of
them to give you a job.
Are you firing me?
You know our sales policy.
You bottom out for three
straight months, you're out.
Perfect.
Ah, Irene.
Are you ready for lunch?
Yes.
But not with you.
DERRICK: Daddy!
Hey.
Oh man.
I missed you, Daddy.
I missed you too, son.
I missed you too.
Daddy, are you crying?
What?
No, no.
I'm happy.
I'm happy, man.
Daddy, I was not scared.
I did what you told me
to do in case of a fire.
I'm so proud of you.
My little man, hmm?
Hey, I need you to
listen to me now.
This nice lady, she's
a friend of Daddy's.
I want you to listen to
her and do everything
She tells you to do, OK?
And I'll come back.
I'll come back and
see you to tomorrow.
I'm not gonna live
with you anymore?
No.
Come on.
I need to find us a house.
Can't have you move into
the motel with me, can I?
Daddy, I did not
burn the house down.
I swear!
Hey, I know, son.
Derrick honey, we have
to go to your soccer game.
I want my daddy to take me.
Can I take him?
Yeah, sure you can.
I mean, why not?
Yeah, I'm going with you, so...
How you doing, Linda?
I'm fine.
You're about to see the
first one of the season.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Absolutely.
I have some inside information.
Billy's playing well.
He said you push him hard.
Look, Linda.
I don't wanna fight
with you anymore.
I don't wanna fight anymore.
No more lawyers, OK?
I just want what's
best for Billy.
That's all.
And what is that?
For you to have full custody?
I shouldn't have
fought you for custody.
But I was angry
for you leaving me,
So I tried to discredit
you as a mother.
And I realize now that all I was
doing was hurting my own son.
I don't wanna do that anymore.
I wanna share Billy with you.
I wanna be part of his life.
I'm his father.
I wanna share him with
you, so we can give him
All the confidence
he needs to get
Through this difficult time.
I mean, we're his parents.
Thank you.
Why don't you come
inside and watch the game?
Come on.
Come on inside.
MAN: All right.
WOMAN: Come on, Tigers!
MAN: Come on.
WOMAN: Come on, Jason!
WOMAN: Let's go, Green.
Let's go.
Woo!
[Whistle]
- Ball game!
- Come on, Kevin.
Let's go!
MAN: Get after the ball!
Move your feet, Billy!
Come on now.
[Cheering]
Yeah!
All right!
I lost my job today.
You know what?
I didn't even hear that
you lost your job, OK?
OK.
Are you gonna be able
to get another job?
Tomorrow.
Are you sure?
What are you doing here?
I took the afternoon off.
We just scored a goal.
We're up one to nothing.
I saw.
Go, go, buddy.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
MAN: Billy, you're
not trying your best.
Move up!
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
OK.
Hey, I'm sorry.
For being a terrible
wife and mother.
You're not a terrible mother.
Get it?
I get it.
[Whistle]
[Cheering]
I mean, every parent
wants better for their kids
Than what they had.
You want better for
Derrick, don't you?
No, I want him to be
a used car salesman.
Come on.
Hustle, hustle!
Yes!
Hey, there you go, son!
Derrick!
Look at that.
That's my son.
All right.
[Whistle]
Hey, buddy, it's...
It's time for you to go
With Daddy's friend now, OK?
No, I wanna go home with you.
Derrick, we talked about this.
No, you lied to me.
What?
I lied to you?
Yeah, you said Mommy
was coming home.
She's never coming home.
And now you?
You don't want me.
It's not true, son.
Derrick, we have to go.
Come here.
You'll see your daddy tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow, OK?
I promise.
You already broke your promise.
Come on.
Come on, Derrick.
Mr. Washington,
nice to see you.
It's good to see you.
This Derrick Johnson.
Well, hello, there,
Derrick Johnson.
He's gonna be staying with
you for a couple days.
Well, good.
All right, honey.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow, OK?
OK.
Bye.
What do you want?
This reminds me of our
little garden in Casablanca.
I miss you.
I feel like a big
piece of me is missing.
I... I cannot imagine
my life without you!
I'm so sorry if I
took you for granted.
Son, wait till your
mother gets here.
Here you go, little one.
Bon appetit.
Whose birthday?
No one's.
But we're having
dinner together.
Just like a family should.
And no other reason?
And no other reason.
Son, who is this alien and what
did she do with your mother?
I think we should
keep her though.
Because she has great buns.
All right?
Can I play?
No.
You're not even supposed
to be in my room.
Is it true?
What?
You burned down your house.
No.
How come you're here?
My mommy's a junkie.
She was caught shooting up
in the presence of a minor.
That's me.
I know what a minor is.
I like this room.
I should ask for this one.
I'm already in it.
I've been here for a month.
I have seniority.
I'm only gonna be
here for three days.
You can have it when I leave.
That's what they told me.
Malcolm was supposed
to be here for one day.
He's been here for
over three months.
No one's ever been here
for less than three months.
Get out.
Leave.
Leave me alone, OK?
OK.
[Bangs on piano]
[Giggling]
[Shrill laughter]
Mom?
Mom, are you OK?
You're making too much
noise and I can't sleep.
I'm sorry.
Your dad was making me laugh.
Oh, I don't see him.
Where is he?
Oh.
I'm right here, son.
I was just tickling your mom
and telling her some jokes.
And I'm sorry if
we were too loud.
We'll be quiet.
No, no, no.
I like it when you guys laugh.
Me too.
Go back to bed.
- Go to bed.
- Good night, Mom.
Good night, Dad.
I better check on him.
OK, all right.
Hey, let's laugh on more time.
[Shrill laughter]
Derrick.
Come here.
Where do you think you're going?
Let me go!
Derrick, stop!
Derrick, Derrick!
[Wet piercing]
Call 911!
Oh my god!
Oh my god.
(SINGING): The lights
are still on at 4:00
On a street in
Washington Square.
The cold scared the deer
back into their holes
Till the sun brings
them up for air.
Their feet walk in boots...
[Phone ringing]
Too blind to find socks in
a silent escape in the dark.
With a song in my head, my
belly filled with lead...
[Phone ringing]
I'm not walking 'round no bar.
Look for a different
something that happened to me.
Oh, where did you
go, my sweet child.
No, don't play
these games with me.
I'm up, then I fall,
and sorry through it
All, for loving so blindly.
You came for a time, and
you weren't really mine,
So you left me
here just bleeding.
And I walk through the
snow, too sick to let go,
And I'm not ready
for the healing.
Not ready for you to leave.
You're nothing but
a ghost in my head,
Some hope I had
Something left unsaid.
And I didn't really
know you at all.
So how come I feel so small?
So small?
I can't feel you at all.
Oooh.
Thank you.
Good.
Marta, please, join us.
I have 20 orange trees
on this property.
And they carry oranges
for eight months a year.
I love orange juice.
I drink it every day.
I think it is a miracle drink.
I think we take God's creations
for granted sometimes.
With all the technology
in the world,
Machines cannot manufacture
one orange like this one.
So you see, I am very
fond of my garden.
That's why we need
a gardener like you,
Hector, one who takes
pride in his work.
If I may suggest, Hector,
you work here 4 to 5
Days a week exclusively for us.
You drive here with Marta,
and you leave together.
We will double
whatever you're making,
And plus whatever
supplies you need.
No, that's too much.
No, it is not.
That is what we are going to pay
you to take care of our garden.
Yes.
With pleasure.
Thank you, Mr. Rafiki.
Thank you, Mrs. Rafiki.
[MUSIC FRAN LUCCI, "WHERE ARE
YOU NOW"]
Perhaps to protect my old and
run-down gravestone, a black
Cloud passed in front of...
[CONTINUES READING IN
BACKGROUND]