Okay.
Good morning.
What you doin'?
Besides stalking jp,
of course.
I'm reading the news,
thank you very much.
Oh!
You're reading the news.
You're such a good liar.
Seriously, how do you know
I'm stalking jp?
Because I know you
very, very well.
Oh, wait! Did you tell
your mom 'bout calarts yet?
Yeah, I told her.
She's super excited for me
to move across the country
and go to a really
expensive art school.
Really?
- No.
- No?
No, I haven't found...
I haven't found
the right time to tell her.
Oh!
Nerve is starting.
Sorry, this is
really important.
What's nerve?
It's a game.
Here, just click on the video.
Welcome to
nerve New York City.
Nerve is a 24-hour game.
Like truth or dare,
minus the truth.
Watchers pay to watch.
Players play to win
cash and glory.
Are you a watcher
or a player?
It's cool, right?
This looks very sketchy.
Is this legal?
I don't know.
Probably not.
Just do it. Just sign up
and watch. Time's ticking.
Okay, signing up. Look, this
is me signing up to watch you.
Vee! You have to sign up
and watch me.
It's very important
that I have watchers.
Hey.
I gotta go,
my mom just got home.
I'll sign up after breakfast.
I promise.
Thank you. I love you.
I'll see you in a little bit.
- Bye.
I mean, Syd hasn't
gotten into any schools yet.
And she doesn't even care.
You know what?
Sydney doesn't have to care.
She has a trust fund.
And you have something
far more valuable than that.
Here we go.
You have drive,
you have focus.
You have a scholarship
to a local college.
And even though
we can't afford the dorm,
you get to have me
as your new college roommate.
Actually, I, um...
I had kind of
a cool idea about that.
What if we fixed up
Mike's room
and listed you
on airbnb or something?
Maybe it's time we finally
go through his stuff
and maybe give
some of it to goodwill.
And I could give you
some space.
I don't want space.
I just want you.
Okay.
I'm totally down
with commuting. I can...
I can get my reading done
on the ferry.
Yeah?
That'll work, right?
Yeah.
Let's say,
"go cougars"
on the count of 1, 2, 3.
Go cougars!
Let's go, cougars!
Hand me the zoom lens.
Here.
Doesn't it feel
a little unbalanced
if every single yearbook photo
is of jp guerrero?
It's not my fault
he's on the team.
Here.
Okay, guys.
Be careful, careful.
Let's hit it, jp!
All right, let's go!
Let's go! Come on!
Watch out,
watch out, watch out!
You got it.
Yeah, you got it.
All right, be careful.
Careful.
Yeah!
Let's go, cougars!
Let's hear it
for Sydney Sloane!
The girl with the shades.
Let's go, cougars.
Ooh, yum!
Liv! Liv!
Show 'em
what we got, cougars!
Okay, let's play...
Where you goin', Syd?
We've lost our cheerleader.
Okay, show 'em
what we got, vhs!
Are you ready?
Remember what to do?
- Okay.
- Okay. You're on!
Hey, watchers!
It's Syd baby.
I'm counting on you
to get me to the final round.
So don't let me down
and I won't let you down,
i promise.
Go, dude!
Show 'em what we got!
Show 'em what
staten island's really about!
Go cheer, baby!
Okay. Okay.
Nerd!
Ooh!
How 'bout that ass, though?
Okay. Thank you, Sydney.
Ah... you guys dared me
to eat dog food.
You can do this!
This is so gross.
Don't think about it.
Okay.
Keep it in.
Ty!
Wassup, watchers?
Oh! Money, money!
Oh. Whoa!
I have so many
watchers now.
Yeah, you do. Girl!
I just need to get
in that little box thing.
Who's winning now?
Apparently,
this guy named Ryan.
I guess he put peanut butter
on his junk
and let his dog
lick it off.
I could do that.
But you don't have a dog.
I could still do it.
Or a dick, Liv.
Ooh, they're coming up
with your next dare!
What is it?
I need something flashy
like the peanut butter thing.
- Hey.
Hey!
Hey.
My god, how weird.
How do they know
you're afraid of heights?
- What?
- That's what they do.
It's easy.
They just take all your info
from your old profiles
and put it
in your nerve profile.
That's so creepy.
You just got suspended.
I thought you were
done playing nerve.
Hell no!
The girl who won Seattle
now has millions of followers.
She is insta-famous.
- Who cares?
- I care, vee.
I don't expect you
to understand.
I'm an adrenaline junkie.
You like to stay within your
comfort zone. That's fine.
That's not true.
What about that
pole dancing class we took?
Vee, I dragged you there
and you sat in the corner
and watched.
I'm a visual learner.
Why are you attacking her?
I'm not attacking her,
Tommy.
Yeah, you are.
Life is passing you by.
You need to learn
to take a few risks
every once in a while.
I do take risks.
Really?
Okay. Fine.
Let's just say hypothetically
you're playing nerve.
What'd be a good
nerve dare for vee?
Make out with jp.
Baby steps. Baby steps.
Just talk to jp.
What?
He probably
likes you, too.
You'll just never know
if you don't talk to him.
And then everybody
that's watching you,
they would just
go on and vote.
Who wants to see
vee mackin' on jp?
Oh, my god!
You guys!
All who wanna see
vee macking on jp say, "yes."
Yes!
Yes. Yes.
I assume, "no"?
Abstain.
Thank you.
All right.
You've been dared.
Do you accept
your dare, vee?
Say, "yes." Say, "yes."
What's the point?
We're graduating. I...
All you have to do
is say, "hi."
I don't want
to say hello to him.
Fine.
I love you so much, vee.
But you're a watcher.
So watch me do it for you.
No, no, no,
Syd, Syd, Syd.
Just watch.
No, no, no! Syd, no.
Yeah! Sydney!
Why don't you show us
the front next time?
You first, Chuck.
I hear it's really big.
Guess it's average.
Uh... hey, jp.
What's up?
Um... I was wondering.
Do you have
a girlfriend right now?
No!
It's not for me.
It's for a friend.
Well, which friend?
Um...
No, it's...
She's not my type.
You're not nearly as hot
as you think you are.
Yes, he is!
And you are a douchebag.
No, don't go! Come on!
Vee! Vee!
Just let her go.
Not cool, Sydney.
I'm just trying to help her.
Let's not help her.
She'll figure it out.
Hello. Welcome to nerve.
You have chosen player.
Nerve is a direct democracy.
Watchers decide your dares.
The two players
with the most watchers
by the end of regulation
will advance
to the final round,
where the winner
takes all.
Watchers can watch
from anywhere,
but they are encouraged
to film live.
So don't be alarmed.
There are three rules.
One, all dares must be filmed
on the player's phone.
Two, there are only
two ways to be eliminated.
Fail or bail.
Three,
snitches get stitches.
Thank you for
keeping nerve a secret.
Good luck, player.
Hey, this is vee,
I'm not here right now...
Vee! You have to
sign up and watch me.
For account information,
press one.
For phone or credit card
information and payment...
Tommy.
Hey,
I'm pulling up outside.
What the hell's so urgent?
We have to go
to colonnade diner.
- We have 15 minutes.
- Why? What's going on?
I signed up for nerve and
that's where my first dare is.
What do you mean?
You signed up as a player?
Oh, man.
What?
Is that so hard to believe?
You know that some kid
supposedly died
in Seattle playing nerve?
Oh, I don't buy that.
If kids were dying,
the game would be shut down.
No, they can't shut it down.
There's not a single server.
What does that mean?
Everybody that logs
onto the game
becomes a new server.
So it's impossible
to turn the game off.
How do you even know
so much about this game?
You've never even played.
Look, I spend a lot of time
on the dark web, all right?
Oh, a lot of time
on the dark web?
Is that right, hacker boy?
Yes, that is right.
You're only accessing
10% of the Internet, you know.
Why are you even doing this?
Seriously, it's dangerous.
Is it because of Sydney?
This is not about Sydney.
I'm...
It's just not like you.
That's the point.
Kiss a stranger
for five seconds?
A stranger?
Vee, I'll give you $100.
Okay, okay.
You're just gonna
kiss some random person?
Oh...
He has a girlfriend.
Hi.
Ugh!
Just kiss that guy.
Okay. I'm gonna
kiss that guy.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Gonna do it.
Or that guy.
He reads.
Well, make a choice.
Clock's ticking.
Hey.
I'm kissing that guy.
Okay, you sit here.
Tell me when
you're rolling, 'Kay?
'Kay, it's
mission impossible now?
Just go.
To the lighthouse,
that's my favorite book.
Really?
Please, tell me they get
to the lighthouse in the end.
Um...
Actually, don't tell me.
Uh... okay,
just tell me real quick.
Yeah, they do,
but that's...
That's not really
what it's about.
The lighthouse
means something
different to each
of the characters.
It basically represents
the thing
they want most in life.
And I'm sorry that
I'm totally geeking out
and ruining the story.
No, I was the one who asked.
Um...
One
Mississippi, two Mississippi,
three Mississippi, four
Mississippi, five Mississippi.
Done.
Okay.
Okay, bye.
I can't believe
i just did that!
Shut up! Oh. Gosh,
why am I embarrassed?
Did you get it?
Yeah, it was a miniseries.
I got all six episodes.
Where did he go?
I have no clue.
"Vee, $100 has been
wired to your account."
Should I check?
Should totally check.
What is he doing?
I have no clue.
He's singing to me.
No, it's a dare.
It's a dare.
You got it.
Thank you.
Good job.
You won your dare.
Congratulations.
Back at ya.
Mine was totally
embarrassing,
but, hey, at least
i got 100 bucks, right?
I'm sorry.
I promise I didn't know
what was comin'. You mind?
Sorry, I'm sitting here.
They just told me to sit
in that booth and... sorry.
Um... some kid came by
and gave me that book.
To the lighthouse,
yeah, my favorite.
Exactly. Because
it's on your Facebook page.
They know all the information
about you, vee.
Your name's vee?
Short for Venus.
I like that.
Well, her parents,
they named her
after the goddess of love.
There's a Roman myth.
Yeah, I guess my mom
was expecting somebody else.
I dunno about that.
That was some kiss.
I got a game to play.
But good night to you guys.
Thank you.
What?
Apparently, the watchers
like us together.
I mean, you can't even
go to the city, right?
You know, I can't go
to the city, yeah.
I'm not even playing,
i was just doing one dare.
You sure? It's 200 bucks.
Uh...
She's pretty sure, man.
He always tell you
what to do?
No. No, he doesn't.
I'm gonna be outside
if you change your mind.
It's nice to meet you, vee.
See ya, man.
He thought that
those were our fries.
I could use 200 bucks.
Vee, you're not going
to the city.
You said one dare.
I'm sorry.
You know what?
Charles manson was a singer.
I was hoping you'd come.
I'm just warning you,
i don't think I'd make
a very good partner.
I'm not
the daredevil type.
You should team up with
my friend Sydney, actually.
She's obsessed
with playing nerve.
But the watchers want me
to team up with you.
The second I feel
uncomfortable, I'm out.
That's fair.
Okay.
Hold on.
I just have to
go to the bathroom.
Oh, my god.
Excuse me, ladies?
Ladies?
Hey,
where are you going?
Please, let me fart on you.
Please!
Oh, my god, oh, my god!
Oh, my god.
It's going up so fast!
I know.
Who's your favorite player?
Well, I mean,
i was gonna say you, but...
Now I don't know.
Is that vee?
Yeah, she's playing nerve
and she has, like,
a lot of watchers.
Oh, my god, girl!
Hey, try screaming.
No.
Just do it.
Let it out!
There you go.
All right, this is it.
Am I supposed
to come in with you?
Uh...
Doesn't say
anything about that.
Well, thank you
for the lift.
You gonna be okay?
Yeah, yeah, no, I'm...
I'm tired,
so I'm probably just gonna
make my way back home.
Um...
This was fun.
Yeah.
I just gotta... you know.
Okay.
You got three more steps.
If you keep up
the exercises,
you're gonna get
really strong on that.
Excellent.
Thanks, miss.
Somebody's sending
vee money.
White people problems.
What is she doing?
And you have
your receipt.
So thank you so much
for shopping at Bergdorf's.
You have a wonderful day.
Excuse me. Um... sorry.
Do you know where I can
find this dress?
Your mom's calling.
Shit!
That's very expensive.
Couture. Fourth floor.
Thanks.
Please, don't undress
the mannequin.
Sorry.
Would you like to
try this on?
Mmm-hmm.
Let me see if
i have it in your size.
Thank you.
If you could hurry up,
I'm a little bit late
for a party.
Cute.
Okay. Right this way.
If you need anything else,
just let me know.
- Okay, thank you.
- Oh. All right.
Okay. Dressed.
Hello?
Everything okay?
Everything is great,
thank you.
Hey. What's your email number?
I mean your...
What's your info?
Oh, this? This old thing?
Vee!
Oh.
Hey.
Hi.
You, uh...
You look very pretty.
Thanks. So do you.
I mean you look, you know,
hot, or handsome or...
Do you know what we're
supposed to do now?
The watchers would like me
to complete your ensemble,
mademoiselle.
Neither. Is that an option?
All right, how 'bout
my firstborn son, too? Yeah?
What are you doing, vee?
How much are they, sir?
That'll be $900, madam.
Oh, in that case,
I'll take two.
One for the city
and one for the Hamptons.
Excellent choice,
mademoiselle.
I'll wrap them up for you
right away.
Um, I'll see ya downstairs?
Uh... yeah, sure.
Okay. All right.
What?
Oh, excuse me, miss!
Did you move
my clothes in there?
Of course not.
This is not happening.
Vee?
Ian.
Hey.
Did you take my stuff? I mean,
my wallet, my clothes.
Everything's gone.
No, my stuff is gone, too.
No.
Okay, um...
No. No.
Come on, we have to
make a run for it.
Come on, let's go.
I am not shoplifting!
We don't have a choice.
Come on!
Okay, technically,
it just says
we have to leave the store.
Right?
Let's go.
Come on, come on!
Let's go!
Mmm...
Um...
Sorry, buddy, we need
to come through. Sorry.
Excuse me! Excuse me!
That's enough, that's enough.
Let's go, come on, come on.
Whoa, whoa, hey,
stop, stop, stop!
Please tell me
these are our clothes!
They kind of are.
Are these stolen?
Receipt.
We get to keep 'em?
All yours.
All right.
Hey, can I get the check?
Who paid for these?
Probably one of the watchers
with daddy's credit card.
What?
Look!
I'm sorry, was that
a wu-tang reference?
Staten island, represent!
Okay.
Saint mark's, 10 minutes?
Hello.
Tommy, what
does vee think she's doing?
Have you ever
parked a car in your life?
I got this, girl.
I have no idea, Syd.
Why are you asking me?
I'm not her boyfriend.
Well, who's this biker
she's teamed up with?
I have no clue.
She just ditched me.
She's doing what
she apparently thinks
is best for herself.
Yeah,
and what exactly is that?
Sydney! Syd!
Vee is in the top 10.
What?
She's in the top 10.
Tommy,
vee is in the top 10?
Yeah, I know.
How is that even possible?
How many watchers
does she have?
Um... like 4,471.
How many do I have?
Uh... 6,806.
Oh, okay,
i have a lot more.
Tommy, I really don't think
that vee can handle this.
I'm actually
really worried about her.
Yeah, me, too.
So get your ass to
this party and help me, okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm on my way.
What happens if I bail?
You'd lose everything
you've already made.
My mom would kill me.
What do you wanna do?
Okay, just please
no fire-breathing dragons
or knives.
No clowns.
Okay.
No snakes, no skeletons.
What about panthers
and tornados?
No!
No?
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What about this?
Just a tattoo of my dad.
He's gorgeous, honestly.
He's a nice-looking guy.
Ah... okay.
I got a better idea.
Here we go. Here we go.
You're gonna draw it? No!
Vee, quiet.
I gotta concentrate!
No! Let me see.
Back off.
'Kay.
Can you do something
like this, but less shitty?
Yes!
Yeah?
Right.
I'm laughing 'cause it's good.
You guys, come on!
Hey, you have to trust us.
That's the whole thing.
Gotta trust me.
And dirt beard.
Ow! Ow!
Okay. Okay.
Okay, you can stop.
I think you can stop.
I think we're good.
We're good.
The dare said it just had
to be bigger than a quarter.
This definitely feels
bigger than a quarter.
You're doin' great.
It's almost done.
Okay, no, I think
wherever we're at,
we can just stop.
Ow, ow, ow...
Hold on, I'm just doing
the "y" in "daddy."
What?
He's kidding.
Don't listen to him.
I really don't like
that noise. At all.
Ow!
Oh, my god.
Rockin' that gold tooth.
Stop!
Okay, okay. Ow!
Wu-tang fan, huh?
My brother used to listen
to them all the time.
Oh, yeah?
You have a brother?
Had a brother.
He died right before
starting college.
I'm sorry.
How long ago was that?
Two years ago.
He was 18.
This July,
I'll be older than him.
Older than my older brother.
Ow, ow...
Hey, hey. Come on.
Stay with me. Stay with me.
He was just
one of those people that
wasn't afraid of anything.
He always said, "yes."
He would laugh so hard
if he saw me
getting a tattoo right now.
Boom! I am done.
Go to that mirror.
Celebrate my work.
Come on.
Do I want to see?
Yes, yes, yes.
- Hey.
- 'Sup, young jedi?
Yeah, ha-ha. Hey.
Yo, we miss you
down here at the club.
Um... you're watching
nerve, right?
Yeah,
man, we all are.
All right, I'm trying to find
out more about this Ian guy.
Ian, my dude.
Man, he playin' wit'
your little girlfriend
vee, right?
Could be you,
but you're playin'.
All right, yes.
That's the problem, though.
But I'm looking
at his profile
and there's just
nothing on the guy.
Look, bitch,
you tried Google?
Yeah, I tried Google.
Guess he's a ghost, then.
Look, I need a ticket
to Aruba.
- Uh... what? No.
- Yes, come on!
No way. You're not
ready for that shit.
Yes, I know.
You're gonna
mess up my rating.
I'm not gonna
mess up your rating.
I'm not gonna buy guns
or something, man. Come on.
Tommy, no. Not happening.
I'm... look, I'm just worried
about my friend. Please.
Come on.
All right, I'll send you
a passkey.
All right. Thank you.
A lighthouse? I love it.
Thank you.
Well, a very wise person
once said...
And this was earlier today.
They said that
the lighthouse represents
the thing that
you want the most.
So, whatever that is,
i hope you get it.
How many followers
does she have now?
I mean, to be fair,
you did tell her
to take a risk.
This isn't
what I meant, Liv.
This is ridiculous.
Sydney!
Okay. Now they're asking
if I can trust you. Can I?
I have the perfect tattoo
picked out for you.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, okay,
it's not a tattoo dare.
What is it?
Just says,
"go to park and 25th."
Oh, god,
i love the Internet.
What?
Ian's played before?
Shoot it!
Don't have
to do this.
Just shoot it!
Hey, it's vee.
I'm not here right now,
so leave a message.
Here we go.
Get to 60 miles per hour.
That's it.
Okay.
All right. Easy one.
All right, let's do this.
Oh!
What did that just say?
Blindfolded?
On the motorcycle?
Yeah.
You're on your own
with that one.
Wait, wait.
I can't do this alone.
Come on, I need you
to help me navigate.
There is no way in hell
I'm doing that.
I'm sorry, I'm out.
Thank you for tonight.
I mean...
I had a lot of fun.
Got a new dress. But I...
I'm good.
Stay. Let's see
what else happens.
Yo! What's up, guys?
Venus, love your work.
Would you hold that for me?
Hold it up.
Great.
And, Ian,
see you in the finals.
Who was that guy?
I don't know.
Just another player.
Vee, come on,
do this with me.
Please, I need you.
Look, you'd be in control.
Say, "yes."
Just say, "yes."
Ah!
Who got next?
Who wanna challenge
the champ? Liv?
- No way.
- Hey, Liv, come on!
Sydney!
Syd... Sydney!
What?
Oh, my god,
you're not gonna
believe this.
What?
Are you kidding me?
You ready?
Yeah.
Chuck,
you seein' this?
All right, remember,
you're my eyes.
Okay.
Green.
Hold on.
You okay?
Yeah.
Just keep your eyes open.
Okay, okay.
Hey, I know you're scared,
but you gotta talk to me, vee.
Okay, wait,
no, no, no!
You got this, vee.
What's goin' on?
Are we good?
Taxi to the right.
Right! Right! No!
You have a sticker
on your helmet!
Thank you!
You're leaning right.
You need to go left.
- Left, left!
- Whoa, sorry!
Are you crazy?
- Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
- We good?
Okay, okay!
Too far left. Right! Right!
Okay, okay.
Okay,
i think that worked.
Yeah? Are we good?
Actually, yes.
Okay, all right,
just keep doin' that.
Just lean?
Yes, lean.
Left or right.
You are in control.
That's good.
No way she's doing this.
Faster.
This is good.
You're doin' great!
Okay, speed up.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay.
We hit 30.
We're halfway there.
Okay, the next light is...
Green!
The next light's... green!
Good, good, all right,
you got this.
Okay, the next light is...
Come on, stay with me.
What's goin' on?
Next light is green!
Faster!
No! No, no, no!
Green!
We're doin' this, vee!
Sixty seconds.
- Are we clear now?
- Still clear.
Taxi! Taxi!
Whoa! Whoa!
Oh, god.
Take it home, vee!
Yeah, vee!
Time check.
Fifteen seconds.
Speed?
Forty-five, 46,
47...
Ian, we love you!
Love you, too!
All right, let's go!
Fifty-seven,
58, 59,
60!
We did it!
Oh, shit!
Look out!
Hold on!
God, oh, my god!
Look out!
Yeah!
Best dare ever!
Vee is number one!
Oh, my god.
That was the craziest thing
I've ever done.
You were incredible.
I can't even believe
we did that.
She kissed him!
Oh, vee!
Get him, girl!
Oh, yeah!
You hungry at all?
Pizza?
Pizza...
I swear,
i was gonna say, "pizza."
Hey, watchers.
Okay, listen,
you and I both know
that I should be in that box.
So please,
stop holding back. Okay?
You guys don't need
to be afraid,
because I'm not afraid.
So just give me
a real dare.
What's up, Syd baby?
What are you doing here?
You're a good player.
You've got a lot of watchers.
I got a lot of watchers.
Maybe we could team up.
I don't need a partner.
Seems to work
for your friend vee.
What up, Syd?
You all right?
Yeah. We're just talking.
Yo, mad Max,
why don't you show
yourself out, man?
Call me.
Break down!
Captain.
Party on, man.
Hey, Nancy.
Tommy, listen,
I have a quick question.
How would I know
if I'm being hacked?
What do you mean?
Hacked. Somebody's been
depositing money
into my account
under vee's name.
That doesn't sound
like a hack.
Normally,
they would take money out
if they were hacking you.
Thomas, what are you
not telling me?
Oh! It must... it might be...
Vee got a job.
What? A job?
Yeah, that's probably it.
She did an online
poker thing.
Okay.
And she's really
great at it.
Is it legal?
Yeah, it's legal.
And she's doing great,
as you can tell
with the deposits.
But anyway, I gotta go.
I'm writing a paper right now
on motorcycle safety.
I'm gonna get goin', but...
Well, tell her to call me.
Bye.
Wanna take a ride?
Is this a dare?
Mmm-mmm. It's a carousel.
So, why are you
playing nerve?
Trying to help out
my family.
Some things happened
that I wish
turned out differently.
Like what?
This is just kinda
something I need to do.
So...
We got some paparazzi.
Hide.
What? Who is it?
So that's Sydney.
- Pick up, pick up.
- You gonna get it?
I don't wanna deal
with her right now.
Ouch!
What's goin' on?
She's just been
a lot recently.
But whatever, you don't
wanna talk about that.
If you wanna talk about it,
I'm here. Happy to listen.
I'm just tired of being
her sidekick all the time.
It's funny. You don't
seem like anyone's sidekick.
Can I see that
picture again?
Oh, uh...
Sure.
Wow.
Yeah.
Guys go crazy for her.
No, I mean the picture itself.
It's really good.
Thanks, I took it.
Yeah? You have a good eye.
I just... I can't picture
you hangin' out
with someone like this.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
She looks kind of...
Insecure. Is that mean?
She is totally insecure.
Yeah?
She makes it seem like
I'm the one who's insecure.
But really it's her.
It's exhausting.
I'm sure.
She's at this party.
Most likely drunk and needs me
to hold her hair back.
I'm just over it.
I mean, so are her parents.
They're constantly
out of town,
so she has this
revolving door of guys over.
It's sad, actually.
Hey, that party.
Should we maybe
go check it out?
What?
Why would I wanna go
to that party?
Maybe show off
your new tattoo?
Show Sydney that
you're not the person
she thinks you are?
Yo, watch out!
Heads up. Comin' through.
Yo, watch out.
Heads up. Yo!
Okay.
I got this. Okay.
Go, Sydney!
You're
better than this.
Come on, just turn around.
Come on, Syd,
you got this.
you started it,
you gotta finish it.
Come on, you got it.
You got it!
Okay.
Just take
a deep breath.
Just take a deep breath,
Sydney.
Get in here!
She's gonna do it!
Go, girl!
You got this. Okay.
- There you go. Come on.
- Yeah, there you go!
There you go.
Somebody, go get Liv!
Oh, my god.
Come on, Syd.
Focus. You got this.
Liv! Liv!
Liv, Liv, Liv,
come, come, come.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Oh, my god. Syd!
Be careful.
Be careful, Syd.
What are you doing?
Oh, my god!
Come on, Syd, you don't
have to do this. Come back.
Shut up!
Sydney, come back.
Oh, my god, Sydney!
Yeah! There you go.
Right here. Come on.
You don't have to do it.
Take your time, Syd.
Don't look down.
It's just a stupid game!
Come on,
we're right here.
You could always
turn back, Syd.
Jp, grab her.
Come on, you gotta film.
Sydney, it's not gonna
count unless you film it.
Don't worry
about the phone.
She has to film it!
She can't...
It doesn't count
unless she films it.
She has to film it.
Just bail.
Just come back.
She has to film it.
No, but she has to film it.
Shut up, Chuck!
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
This is crazy.
All right, there you go.
Don't look down.
I can't!
Oh, my god, I can't, I can't!
Sydney,
you gotta get up.
You gotta do something.
Stop yelling at me!
- Stop! You're not helping.
- Chuck, shut up!
Shut up, she's got it.
She has to get it done!
Shut up!
Syd, it's gonna take too long,
you gotta stand,
you gotta walk.
No, don't stand, Sydney.
Shut up! Shut up, Chuck!
You heard her, Chuck,
shut up.
She's gotta
get it done.
She's not gonna get here
in time unless
you get up and walk.
You have to walk.
Don't listen to him,
Syd, you got it.
She has to!
She's wasting time!
Shut up, both of you!
You got it.
Come on, Syd, you got this.
I can't,
i can't, I can't.
I bail, I bail, I bail.
You bail.
You fail.
This is so dumb.
Come here! Hold on!
You fail.
Get over here!
Oh, my god.
Oh! Look at these guys!
Vee!
- Hi.
- Hi!
Oh, my gosh. You guys
are so famous right now.
Uh-oh!
Wait until Syd sees you.
But where is she?
Oh, you guys don't know?
Yeah, she tried to walk across
that ladder and just bailed.
So she's outta the game?
Hey, let's get a drink.
Yeah. It wasn't pretty.
Have you seen Sydney?
In there.
Syd?
Oh, come on, vee,
you never even spoke to him.
It's fine.
Certainly, no surprise.
Yeah, I know
it's not a surprise.
You know
what's not fine, though?
I almost died tonight, vee,
and you were
nowhere to be found.
I'm sorry.
When you said
i should live my life,
did you mean I should
live my life in your shadow?
I was just trying
to help you, vee,
because you're the most
repressed person that I know.
Well, isn't that why
you keep me around?
Because I never
tell you the truth?
Yeah.
Come on, let's go.
I guess you don't
tell me the truth.
Because you never told me
about how insecure I am.
Or about how I just have
a revolving door
of guys all the time.
You never tell me that,
but you've told
everyone that tonight.
So please, vee,
go right ahead
and show us all
what a fiery little spark plug
you've become since lunch.
Let's go.
Shots fired.
Don't walk away from me.
Vee! Wake up!
This is a game.
Do you really think that
someone like him
is actually gonna be with you
when this is all done?
Hey, you don't know me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You really like her now?
Yeah, I do.
All right, come on, Syd,
you're just drunk.
Tommy, it is time
to get over her!
Clearly, she has traded up!
Why do you have to be
such a bitch?
Look at that!
Little vee finally
speaking her mind.
Come on!
Unburden yourself!
Do you know why
we're best friends?
I do whatever
you want all the time.
No, vee, we're friends
because I'm fun
and you're boring.
The only fun thing about you
was your brother.
What is it you think?
That playing nerve
is just gonna
magically make you
a different person?
That's not how life works.
You'll never be a player.
You're right.
I know how much you love
living in the moment, Syd.
Well, remember this moment.
Because you're
one of those girls
who peaks in high school.
And when you wake up one day,
still living in staten island,
still screwing the same guys,
wondering what the hell
happened to your life.
If you wanna know
where I am from now on,
sign up and watch me.
Wait, vee,
what are you doing?
Hey, vee,
you don't need to do this.
Look at me. Come on.
Let's just go,
let's bail, all right?
What do you have to prove?
Come on, please. Let's go.
Come on, you got it,
vee, please!
- Go, girl!
- Vee!
Oh, my god. Vee!
Whoa!
You got it, vee!
That's how you get
into first, vee!
That was messed up.
I can't deal with this
right now. I'm gonna go.
Vee, did you know
that he's played
nerve before?
What?
Yeah, it was his dare
to get you here
and fight with Syd.
That's why
he brought you here.
Look.
You still trust him?
Vee, wait. Wait.
Is it true?
Is what true?
Did you take me here
as part of the game?
Answer me! Is it true?
What are you doing?
It's more complicated
than that.
I just lost my two
best friends tonight.
How much did you
get for that?
No, no, it's not
about the money, all right?
But I promise
I'll explain everything later.
Just don't even
bother, okay?
I mean,
Sydney almost died tonight.
I almost died tonight.
Vee, I know, I know.
This game is sick.
I'm going to the police.
Wait, no, no! No!
I'm sorry, vee...
What are you doing?
I'm sorry,
you can't do that,
all right?
You can't go to the police.
Why not?
Because I'll lose the game?
No, it's not about that!
Vee! Vee!
You can't go to the police.
It's the last thing
you wanna do.
Vee, wait, I wasn't
trying to hurt you.
It just got outta control.
Move! Get out of the way!
Officer!
Officer, I need help. I'm...
I'm playing this game.
It's called nerve.
And I'm worried that someone's
gonna get really hurt.
Uh-oh.
Snitch!
A game? They playin', too?
Yeah, yeah.
There's a crime
being committed?
No, but a kid
could die tonight.
Look, here, it's all
on my phone. You can see.
What?
Snitch!
Snitches get stitches!
Mom?
Honey,
what's going on?
Mom!
Vee, where are you?
All the money is missing
from our account!
Wait, what?
Vee, honey,
are you in trouble?
Can you just, please,
tell me what's going on?
Okay, mom, I'm gonna fix this,
i promise.
Fix what?
Hello? Vee!
Hello? Vee! Fix what?
I'm sorry,
but I gotta win this game.
Hello, vee.
You broke the rules.
You are our prisoner.
We told you not to snitch.
Now we control your life.
We control your family.
We control your future.
The only way out
is to win the final round.
Go to the staten island ferry
and the watchers
will find you.
See you in the finals.
Checkin' over here.
I'm comin' for you, vee!
Vee, thank god!
Are you okay?
Am I okay?
No, I'm not okay!
You need to tell me
everything.
Okay, what the hell
is going on?
Come here, come here.
Why is this happening to me?
'Kay, that guy Ty.
We both played nerve
last year in Seattle.
We got a dare to hang
from a construction crane
200 feet in the air.
The two of us
and this kid named Robbie.
Five!
Four! Three!
Come on, Robbie,
that's enough.
Shit, he's slipping.
- Two! One!
- Climb back up, man.
- Ian, grab him.
- Grab my hand!
Ty and I, we bailed
and we went to the cops.
We tried to get
the game shut down,
but they didn't do anything.
No, they just
called it an accident.
Then the watchers, they...
They came after us
for snitching.
They messed
with my dad's job.
They leaked photos
of my sister online.
They stole
our identities, vee.
Me and Ty, we became
prisoners of the game.
Oh, come on.
What does that even mean?
It's the third category.
Watcher, player, prisoner.
I'm trapped.
The only way out is to win.
So you have to win.
No. No, you do.
What?
Vee, you're a prisoner now.
You and I, we're going
to the final round together
and I'm gonna lose.
What? No, you can't do that.
It's already done.
I told the watchers
to give me a dare
that's gonna knock Ty
outta second place.
It's gonna be me and you.
I have to go.
No, no, no.
Yeah, I wanna take you
somewhere safe. Let's go!
There has to be
another way.
There isn't.
If it's not me in the finals,
then it's Ty.
And he'll do anything
to win.
Just tell me
we're gonna do this.
Hey...
It's not your fault.
I just hope she's okay.
- Hello?
- Guys, it's me.
Oh, my god!
Vee, where are you?
I'm so sorry.
Doesn't matter.
I'm just glad you're okay.
All right, come on.
Let's go.
I can't.
What?
I have to finish this.
Are you insane?
What are you talking about?
Look, it's never gonna end.
I mean, even if
they leave me alone,
they're just gonna
do it to somebody else.
We can't stop the game
if we wanted to.
There's no one to stop.
It's just a bunch
of anonymous people.
What if they
weren't anonymous?
Ian's doing a dare that
would put him in the finals.
So it could be
me against him.
Vee, do you actually
trust this guy?
He is the person
who got you
into this mess
in the first place.
I got me into this mess.
Anything Ian's doing now
is to help me get out.
I know it sounds crazy,
but I can do it.
I just need your help.
What do you need us to do?
Tommy, you said the game
is open source, right?
Do you think you can
change the code?
It's gonna take time.
Syd, could you
buy us some?
Hey. Now climb the crane.
Syd?
Yeah?
Use a payphone.
Ah!
Hang for five seconds.
Hang with one hand.
Shit!
One! Two! Three!
Four!
Five!
- Yeah, it's over here, Tommy.
- We don't have a lot of time.
Okay, yeah. We're on our way.
We'll see you soon.
How did it go?
It went.
It went?
Yeah. I think
it's gonna work.
Yeah, better work.
I mean, god.
What is this place?
Fastest Internet
in New York City.
Hey, Tommy!
Hey, hk, we made it.
Let's get
this started. You ready?
Is the botnet
up and running?
Yeah, of course.
We just gotta enter it
into the system.
Oh, and this is Sydney.
Obviously.
Hey.
Welcome to the cloud.
Sucks you got axed.
All right.
Let's take this game down.
I got you. Yeah.
Okay,
how's this gonna work?
It's like Wikipedia,
where anyone
can edit the code
but the majority
has to approve it.
And then the botnet
can outvote everyone.
Yo, I got a army of bots here
waitin' for orders.
Hey, Nancy.
Where is vee?
What is this game?
Don't worry,
she's okay.
I want you
to explain it to me.
I'm gonna give
you an address.
Okay, if you meet me here,
I'll explain everything.
Ticket?
Better hurry up.
Guys, it's starting!
Vee! Vee! Vee! Vee!
Players, stop!
Back up.
Stop.
All right, how many bots
do we got in?
Not enough yet,
but we are getting there.
Players,
show us your weapons.
First to shoot wins.
Twenty seconds
on the clock.
Twenty seconds?
Hk, I need backup!
Begin.
Do it.
Start by just
raising your gun.
Just raise
your gun slowly.
Then shoot me
in the shoulder.
I'll be fine.
What if I miss?
I don't know
if I can do this.
Oh, come on! Just shut up
and play the game!
Vee, you have to hurry,
all right?
You have to do this!
This is the only way
the game can end.
And then
you can walk away.
Five,
four,
three,
two, one!
Boo!
I'm not doing this.
Vee, don't, you can't...
I'll do it!
Oh, shit.
They're onto us.
They're blockin'
all of our foreign ips!
Tommy, do something!
Did y'all miss me?
And I say
we do that dare again.
With someone
who's really ready to play.
Yeah!
Don't do it, Ty,
it's not worth it, man.
Stop!
Whoa, whoa, back up!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You have lost
your mind, pretty boy!
Get back!
Is this what
you really want?
For us to kill each other?
Yeah!
Of course
it's what you want!
Kill 'em!
You think that takes nerve?
Why don't you
take off your masks
and show yourselves, huh?
You, take off your mask.
Yeah, what's your name?
It's easy for you
to be brave in a crowd!
Hiding behind
your screen names.
Don't you guys see that
you're all still responsible
for what happens tonight,
even if you are
just watching?
Oh, my god! Are you really
believing this bullshit?
Play to win!
Play to win.
You guys really
want one of us to die?
For a game?
Yes!
Then shoot me.
I dare you.
Okay.
Who wants me to shoot her?
Vee, what are you doing?
Tommy, where's vee?
- All right, calm down.
- What is this game?
I want answers!
What are you doing?
You better tell me right now
or I'm calling the cops.
No! No,
Nancy, calm down.
No cops.
Do you want me
to shoot her?
Shoot to kill!
Then vote "yes."
Vote "yes" if you want me
to shoot her!
Don't listen to him!
Say, "no!"
You want me to shoot her?
Come on, guys, "no"!
Guys, vote "no"!
You! Vote "yes"!
Vote "yes"!
Let me know!
Don't listen to him!
Say, "no!"
Come on! Let's have
a little bit of anarchy.
All right, we're getting
around them.
The ips are coming in
faster now.
Vee, we need to go,
right now!
Oh, my god!
Okay, all right.
Come on, guys. Keep going.
Oh, my god!
No, no, no, it's...
Vee, please!
Please, please!
No. No, no, no.
Do you hear me, vee?
Look at me, vee, please!
Go.
Dude,
are you getting this?
That's my real name.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
No, wait, stop, stop!
My god!
It's okay,
it's okay!
Stop! It's okay.
I'm okay. It's okay.
Oh, my god!
Sorry.
You were in on this?
It was her plan, man.
Her friend Sydney called me.
That's why I'm here.
The gun... what?
Blanks, bro.
It's fake.
Oh, my god!
Oh, my god.
You scared me.
We cool?
Yeah. We're free.
She's a badass.
Watch out for her.
That's it.
The last player's out.
Did we get it?
They're out.
Think it's crashing!
We got it?
And nerve
is officially offline!
Wow! We have
gamed the game.
Whoo!
You guys are the dumbest
smart kids I've ever met.
I'm so sorry.
No, no, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for
bringing you into all this.
I just wish that we could've
met some other way.
I don't.
Oh, man!
And you.
What a rock star.
Looks like I can get
all your money back.
They don't call me
hacker kween for nothin'.
Really? Thanks.
Yeah.
Crazy first date, huh?
Is that what that was?
By the way,
my real name is Sam.
Well, it's nice
to meet you, Sam.
It's nice to
meet you, vee.
Hey, vee, it's 28 degrees
in New York!