Shh. Hey.
Bathsheba Everdene.
Bathsheba.
The name has always
sounded strange to me.
I don't like to hear it
said out loud.
My parents died
when I was very young,
so there's no one to ask
where it came from.
I've grown accustomed
to being on my own.
Some say even too accustomed.
Too independent.
Miss!
My scarf.
I lost it.
You must be Farmer Oak.
Gabriel, yes.
My aunt's told me about you.
I'm working on her farm
for the winter.
This is your land.
I'm trespassing.
You're welcome here.
Good afternoon, Farmer Oak.
Good afternoon, miss.
Come by, George.
George, away!
Enough, George!
Enough!
Stand. Stand.
George, stand.
Away!
George, away!
He doesn't know when to stop,
Young George.
What's this one called?
Old George.
So you find me amusing, do you?
Goodness,
it's Mr. Oak.
...and after that
she was gonna be a governess.
But she was far too wild.
Always has been.
Oh!
Miss Bathsheba Everdene.
I've brought you a lamb.
Oh!
Thank you, Mr. Oak.
He's such a dear thing.
He's come too soon
and won't last the winter,
so I thought you'd
like to rear it instead.
Thank you, that's very kind.
I'll make some tea.
The lamb is not why I came.
Go on.
Well, Miss Everdene,
I wanted to ask...
Would you like to marry me?
I've never asked anyone before.
No.
I should hope not.
Well...
Perhaps I, erm, I should...
Perhaps I should leave.
Mr. Oak,
there are things to consider.
Is someone waiting for you?
No, but that doesn't
mean I'll marry you.
Good day to you, then.
Mr. Oak!
Mr. Oak! Wait!
I didn't say I wouldn't
marry you, either.
I haven't ever really
thought about it.
I have 100 acres and 200 sheep.
If I pay off the money,
the farm is ours.
You could have a piano
in a year or two.
Flowers and birds
and a frame for cucumbers.
A baby or two.
Mr. Oak...
Or more.
I will always be there for you.
Mr. Oak, I don't
want a husband.
I'd hate to be
some man's property.
I shouldn't mind being
a bride at a wedding
if I could be one
without getting a husband.
That's stupid talk.
You are better off
than I, Mr. Oak.
I have an education
and nothing more.
You could do much,
much better than me.
That's not the reason.
I'm too independent for you.
If I ever were to marry,
I'd want somebody to tame me
and you'd never
be able to do it.
You'd grow to despise me.
I would not.
Ever.
Good-bye, Miss Everdene.
What is it, old boy?
Stay here.
Stay here, Old George.
George!
No!
It's all yours.
We take no pleasure in this.
We wish
you well, Mr. Oak.
Bathsheba.
What is it?
My love. It's your
poor uncle's will.
What does it say?
Read it.
Read!
He's left you everything.
It's all yours.
Oh!
Oh, my goodness.
Take care, you hear.
Walk on.
Bye.
So who will join us, lads?
Which one of you fine boys
will put on the scarlet uniform
and proudly serve
his Queen and country?
See the world.
Form an orderly line,
gentlemen, at the front.
This gentleman in the straw hat,
step forward, sir.
That's my sweetheart,
right there.
You, sir,
next to the pretty lady.
There's a good strong
figure of a man.
Join us, sir.
Go on. You'd make
a fine soldier.
Always room in the ranks for
a gentleman of your caliber.
It's a roof
over your head. Food.
Who wants a fine wage?
Excuse me.
You might try Weatherbury.
If you're looking for work,
there's a farm there
needs all the help it can get.
Yes.
The young lad there.
I will. Thank you.
And your
friend as well.
You should have a cloak
for a day like this.
Francis
will take care of me.
We are to be married soon.
Good-bye.
Come on,
a decent wage.
Make your family proud.
Food, shelter.
Who will join us?
Go and wake up
the other farms!
Get them down here!
We need more hands!
We need
more men now!
Wake them up!
Go and get
the Smith brothers first.
Protect yourself,
the fire's spreading!
Who's in charge here?
We're losing the ricks!
The rick is lost.
We need to save the barn.
Come on, help me!
Come on, get some more water!
Get some more water!
We need to push
this out. Come on!
Heave!
Come on, push!
Everybody out!
Water!
More over here!
The barn's going up!
Get the sacks out,
the root's about to go!
What's he doing up there?
We lose the barn,
we lose everything.
Joseph,
bring those brooms over
and let's get this sorted out.
Look sharp, men,
the farmer's here.
Mr. Oak, is that you?
Perhaps you want
a shepherd, ma'am?
I owe you an immense
debt, Mr. Oak.
If I'd have lost all of this,
I'd have lost my farm.
Your farm?
My inheritance.
My home, too, for a while
when my parents died.
When my uncle passed away,
he left it to me.
Of course,
it's a little ragged now,
but this once used to be
the finest farm for miles.
And I intend
to make it so again.
Perhaps you find
the idea preposterous.
I no longer have that luxury.
I'm truly sorry to hear
of your loss, Mr. Oak,
but if our reversal of fortune
causes you any embarrassment...
Not at all, ma'am.
Billy Smallbury?
9 and 8 pence.
Joseph Poorgrass?
Go on, Joseph.
Go on, lad.
Hat off.
And what do you do, Joseph?
I does general things.
And in spring I shoot the rooks
and help at pig killing, sir.
I mean ma'am.
7 and 9 pence.
And another 9 because I'm new.
Thank you, ma'am.
Now, Fanny Robbin?
Where is Fanny Robbin?
Where is she?
She's run away, ma'am.
She's gone off
with a soldier, ma'am.
Not a soldier, a sergeant.
Bailiff Pennyways?
Here is 10 shillings
and a further 10.
Why?
This ends our association.
You are dismissed.
I beg pardon, miss?
When my uncle was alive,
this was a fine,
productive farm.
Since his death,
it has fallen into ruin.
I can only assume...
Now see here, miss.
You can't get rid
of people like that.
I have resolved
to have no bailiff at all,
I have decided
to manage everything.
Mr. Pennyways, if you'll
listen to me for a moment.
Mr. Pennyways, a fire
threatened to destroy the barn
and you are nowhere to be found.
I have no use for a man
like you, Mr. Pennyways.
You are dismissed.
Get out
while you can, if I were you.
Now you've all met
our new shepherd, Mr. Oak.
You understand
your duties, Mr. Oak?
If I don't, I'll ask, ma'am.
From now on, you have
a mistress, not a master.
I don't yet know
my talents in farming,
but I shall do my best.
Don't suppose,
because I'm a woman,
I don't know
the difference between
bad goings-on and good.
I shall be up
before you're awake.
I shall be a-field
before you are up.
It is my intention
to astonish you all.
Back to work, please.
Perhaps I should wait here?
No.
Nonsense, Liddy.
You're my companion.
All of these?
All of them.
Head high, Liddy.
If they stare, do not hesitate.
Remember, we have as much
right to be here as anyone.
Good morning.
Liddy, if you lay things out.
Yes, miss.
Gentlemen, shall we
get back to business?
There you go, sir.
If you feel it,
you can feel the quality.
This is fine grain, miss.
Thank you.
Perhaps we should leave, miss.
But none of it
as good as this lot.
It's good stuff,
I'll grant you that.
Well, it's up to you.
If you wanna go elsewhere...
No, no, no...
Farmer Stone?
It's Miss Everdene.
Farmer Everdene's niece.
He talked about you
with such great admiration.
Of course, you're welcome
to try elsewhere,
but I think you'll find the
grain as good as it's ever been.
Mr. Stone?
How much?
£5 a quarter.
£3-10 shillings.
It's the same grain,
Mr. Stone.
You paid my uncle £5.
£3-10.
This gentleman
will pay me the proper price.
Apparently not, no.
£4.
£4-10.
£4-05.
Perhaps I should move on.
Liddy, would you help me
with this gentleman?
Of course.
Perhaps you'd like a sample?
How much?
£5 a quarter.
Very well.
£4-10.
Jerusalem the golden
With milk and honey blest
Beneath thy contemplation
Sink heart and voice oppressed
He's rich, he's handsome.
He sends the local girls mad.
The Taylor sisters
worked on him for two years.
Jane Perkins spent £20
on new clothes
and might as well have
thrown the money out the window.
It's said, when he was young,
his sweetheart jilted him.
People always say that.
Women don't jilt men.
Men jilt us.
Did someone jilt you, miss?
Certainly not.
A man did ask to marry me once.
Some time ago.
But I was too restless
to be tied down.
What a luxury, to have a choice.
"Kiss my foot, sir, my face
is for mouths of consequence."
It wasn't like that at all.
Why?
Did you love him?
No, but I rather liked him.
Anyway, it's impossible now.
Mr. Boldwood.
Don't shoot me, please.
I had no intention
of shooting you.
It's Miss Everdene.
Your neighbor.
Farmer Everdene's niece.
I'm managing the farm alone now.
Perhaps you've heard?
Yes, I'm sure
you'll do very well.
In the circumstances.
Well, as you say,
we're neighbors.
Look what
I've got here.
What is it?
Listen to this.
"The rose is red The violet blue
"Carnation's sweet
And so are you"
It's a Valentine's card.
I'm going to send it
to Joseph Poorgrass
just to see the look
of panic on his stupid face.
Poor boy. It's a little bit
far-fetched, isn't it?
What about
Mr. Oak, then?
No. Not Mr. Oak.
Imagine if we sent it
to Mr. Boldwood.
Ignoring you like that,
all high and mighty.
Mr. Boldwood?
Perhaps not?
Why not?
Because I don't think
he'll see the humor.
Perhaps he wouldn't,
perhaps it's too much.
Mr. Boldwood.
You're right.
Perhaps it is.
So we're gonna toss for it.
Liddy!
Come on.
Open, Joseph.
No, Jan Coggan.
Open, Jan Coggan.
Closed, Boldwood.
Sergeant Troy, 11:00.
Yes, Sergeant Troy. And?
Miss Fanny Robbin.
Welcome. Step down the front.
Where is she?
I don't know.
Here she comes.
Oh.
Sorry I'm late, old boy.
Not long now.
Dearly beloved, we are
gathered here in the sight...
I can only wait
a few more minutes.
She'll be here.
What do you
think is happening?
I don't think
she's coming, old boy.
Come on. Go on, off you go.
That's it. Go on.
Morning, my love.
Come on.
Bring them in, John.
Grab this one.
Miss Everdene's here now,
so you better do your best work.
I'm looking at you, Coggan.
Yeah,
you keep quiet, Liddy.
What you doing?
Perhaps you'd care
to lend a hand?
You don't think I would?
No, you wouldn't.
Come here.
There,
she's getting in.
Well done, ma'am.
Gangway through.
Hey, Joseph. Joseph, look.
Good morning,
Mr. Boldwood.
Miss Everdene.
Mr. Boldwood wondered if
he might have a word with you.
Mr. Boldwood.
Of course.
One thousand acres.
A mix of arable and livestock.
Adjacent to Everdene.
An orchard. Glasshouse.
I have some interesting pigs.
Some other time, perhaps.
Thank you.
You have a very beautiful house.
Mr. Boldwood?
Miss Everdene.
I want
very much, more than anything,
to have you as my wife.
Miss Everdene, marry me.
I...
I feel...
Though I respect you very much,
I do not feel
what would justify me
in accepting your offer.
I have known
disappointments before,
but I would never have
asked in this instance
had I not been, er,
led to believe...
Unless...
Unless I am mistaken.
The valentine.
No, you're not mistaken,
but I should never have sent it.
Forgive me, it was thoughtless
to disturb your peace of mind.
So you meant it as a joke?
No. No, not as a joke.
Not exactly.
It was impetuous.
I see.
Perhaps you think I am too old?
But I will care for you
more than anyone your own age.
I'm sure you would...
I will protect you.
You shall have dresses,
a gig. Uh, a piano.
I amuse you?
No.
It's only...
I have a piano.
And I have my own farm.
And I have no need
for a husband,
no matter how honored
I am by the offer.
I think I'd like to return home.
Yes, er... I'll, er...
I'll get someone to drive you.
Mr. Boldwood,
I've made you miserable.
It was very wicked of me.
Will you reconsider?
Let me think.
Yes.
Yes, I'll give you time.
I will wait.
You're working
late, Mr. Oak.
Will you teach me?
Here.
Spin the wheel.
Incline it, like that.
And slide it gently.
Spin the wheel.
Bit faster. Like that.
Very good.
Now slide it.
I... It's...
Getting stuck.
I wanted to ask,
did the men say anything
today about Mr. Boldwood?
They did.
What did they say?
That you'd be married
before the end of the year.
Come on.
Well, I'd like you
to contradict it, to the men.
Well, Bathsheba...
"Miss Everdene," please.
If Mr. Boldwood did really
speak of marriage,
I'm not going to tell
stories just to please you.
I just said I wanted you
to mention to the men
that it might not be true
I was going to marry him.
I could say that if you wish.
But I could also give you an
opinion on what you've done.
I dare say, but I don't want
your opinion, Mr. Oak.
I suppose not.
Well, what is your opinion?
That you're greatly to blame
for playing pranks
on a man like Mr. Boldwood.
Your actions were
unworthy of you.
Unworthy? May I ask
where my unworthiness lies?
In rejecting you, perhaps?
I've long given up
thinking of that.
Or wishing it, either.
But I will say this.
Leading on a man you
don't care for is beneath you.
I cannot allow a man to
criticize my private conduct.
You will please leave the farm
at the end of the week.
I'd prefer to go at once.
Then go. I never want to
see your face again.
Very well, Miss Everdene.
Whoa, there we are.
There.
What's wrong with them?
They broke fence
and ate the young clover.
Makes their stomachs swell.
Well,
what do we do now?
Nothing.
The whole flock is blasted.
You mean they're
all going to die?
Most probably.
Another one gone here, ma'am.
Only one way of saving them.
You must pierce
their side with a tool.
A hollow tube.
Pricker inside.
Well, can you do it?
This one's still alive.
No.
Can I?
Oh, good Lord, no.
One inch to
the right or the left,
and you kill the ewe for sure.
Not even a shepherd
can do it, as a rule.
Well, who, then?
Gabriel!
Gabriel Oak, wait!
Miss Everdene needs you.
Why are you alone?
Did you find him?
Yes, miss.
So what did he say?
He said...
Joseph?
He said you're to go in person
and request him civilly
in a proper manner.
Where does he get his airs?
I'll do no such thing.
He said you'd say that.
He said to reply,
"Beggars can't be choosers."
Mr. Oak.
Gabriel.
Please don't desert me, Gabriel.
I need your help.
Make room for me.
I wanna see.
No, don't you start,
Liddy, be quiet.
Find the spot.
Between the ribs.
Oh, Lord!
No, no, no, no, no.
Now...
I can see
his heart beating.
Come on.
- Come on, girl.
She'll be all right.
You all right?
You all right, Pixie?
Yeah, come on.
All right, Pixie! Pixie!
Hey! Come here!
Lay me low
Where no-one can see me
Where no-one can find me
Where no-one can hurt me
Get out.
Please, quiet.
Oh, early one morning
As I was a walking
The fields and the meadows
They looked so green and gay
The birds sang so sweetly
So pleasant and so charming
So early in the morning
At the break of day
Miss. Mr. Boldwood is here.
Thank you. Thank you, Jan.
Jan, thank you.
Mr. Boldwood.
What a pleasant surprise.
Will you join us?
Nice to have you, sir.
A song, ma'am.
I have no voice.
Come on, ma'am,
you've got a lovely voice.
Come all you fair
and tender girls
That flourish in your prime
Beware, beware
Keep your garden fair
Let no man steal your thyme
For when your thyme
it is past and gone
He'll care no more for you
And every place where
your thyme was waste
Will all spread o'er with rue
The gardener's son
was standing by
Three flowers he gave to me
The pink, the blue
and the violet true
And the red, red rosy tree
But I refused the red rose bush
And gained the willow tree
That all the world
may plainly see
How my love slighted me
I thought we were
rather good together.
So did I.
We would make a fine duo.
I wanted to thank you
for not approaching me
on that subject again.
Well, it has not been easy.
Do you wish me to, er,
accompany you back to the house?
No, I like to walk around
the farm every night
to make sure all is safe.
Then I...
I can walk with you.
I've done it many times alone.
Good night,
Mr. Boldwood.
You've been very kind.
A pleasure to see you.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
I seem to be lost.
We're entangled.
Are you hurt?
No.
I'm looking for Weatherbury.
I hope I didn't startle you.
We've got hitched
together somehow.
Here, allow me.
No. No. Please,
let me do it myself.
If you lift your
foot for a moment.
Please don't stare.
I don't think I've ever seen
a face as beautiful as yours.
You shouldn't be here.
Please let me have the lamp.
A mighty impressive
harvest this looks like.
Miss,
look.
Who is he, Liddy?
Sergeant Francis Troy.
Noble blood, full of promise.
Very sharp and trim.
Well-educated.
There was good things
expected of him.
He threw it all in
to be a soldier.
Well, I won't have it.
What are you doing, miss?
I'm going to tell him to leave.
Sergeant Troy,
I must absolutely insist that
you leave at this very moment.
I can't.
Will you follow me, please?
What angers you, exactly?
Please.
What I said
or the way I said it?
You must know.
There must be some man
who tells you
that you're beautiful.
Oh, not to my face, not...
But there is someone
who kisses you?
I've never been kissed.
Why couldn't you have just
passed by and said nothing?
Do you forgive me?
I do not.
Why?
Because the things you say...
I said that you were beautiful.
I wonder if you fight
as well as you speak.
Better.
Meet me. Tomorrow.
I can't.
You don't want to?
Yes, but...
Then you must.
I mustn't.
Nobody would know.
Please go now.
Tomorrow.
8:00.
The hollow in the ferns.
Do you trust me?
I do.
I give you my word as a soldier,
I will not harm you.
The sword is blunt,
but you must not flinch.
I'll try not to.
You cut my hair.
This sword could skin you alive.
But you told me I was safe.
And you were.
Entirely safe.
I gave you my word.
Now I will take this.
Miss Everdene.
Perhaps I could walk with you?
I'm quite happy
to walk by myself.
You should have nothing
to do with him.
He's not good enough for you.
He's a perfectly decent man.
That's not what I believe.
Why? What have you heard?
You don't know him at all.
It's all rumors.
Prejudice simply because
he's a soldier.
I like soldiers.
But not this one.
I believe him to have
no conscience at all.
Stay clear.
Don't listen to him.
Don't believe him.
Get rid of him.
And what is it to you?
I'm not such a fool
as to imagine
I might stand a chance now
that you are so above me.
But don't suppose I'm content
to stay a nobody all my life.
One day I will leave you.
You can be sure of that.
But for now,
I care for you too much
to see you go to ruin
because of him.
So if you don't mind, I'll...
I'll stay by your side.
Good evening.
Mr. Boldwood,
you have been a dear friend
to me these past months.
And it is because
I value our friendship
so greatly that I am writing.
I am honored by your proposal
and have given it much thought,
but I must tell you that,
to my own surprise,
I have undergone
what can only be described
as a change of heart
and I'm afraid
I cannot accept your offer.
I wasn't sure you'd be here.
Where else would I be?
You ready?
Are you sure?
How does this sound?
Mrs. Bathsheba Troy.
All right?
Walk on.
Gentlemen.
Ladies and gentlemen.
A short time ago,
I had the privilege
and the simple fortune
of meeting this angel.
Your mistress.
And now I stand before
you her husband,
your master,
and the proudest man
you will ever see.
So, please, charge your glasses
and sing out to
my most beautiful wife,
Mrs. Bathsheba Troy.
Miss Everdene,
there's going to be a storm.
Oak, you big lump.
To me.
There's going to be a storm.
We need to protect the ricks
or we'll lose the harvest.
I need five to six men
for an hour, no more.
Frank, perhaps we ought to...
No.
Darling, it's our
wedding celebration.
It will not rain tonight.
My wife forbids it.
Now if you'll excuse me.
Friends!
One more thing.
I may no longer
be Sergeant Troy,
But I remain a soldier
in this one respect!
The finest bottles
of French brandy,
a triple-strength dose
for every man.
Cheers! To your health!
"Pretty Polly, Pretty Polly
It's I've come a-wooin"'
She says, "Creep and crawl
through the window, then
"And let's get doin'
"And lay your leg over me
Over me, do
"Oh, me britches is tight
and I cannot undo 'em
"There's a knife
on the windowsill
"Love, take it to 'em
"And lay your leg over me..."
About 40 weeks after,
the fine baby come bawlin'
Never regretted
that creepin' and crawlin'
"Lay your leg over me
Over me..."
Gabriel!
What can I do?
It's too dangerous!
I'm coming up!
Hold it down.
Still no rain.
It'll come.
Come on, hold me!
Come here. Come here.
Come here. Come on.
Gabriel, I've been a fool.
I've always had contempt
for silly girls
dazzled by flattery
in a scarlet uniform and...
And now I've done
what I swore I would never do.
But he told me
about another woman,
a woman more beautiful
that he'd loved before,
and I couldn't bear it.
So somewhere between
jealousy and distraction,
I married him.
I don't want an opinion
on the subject, I just...
In fact, I forbid it.
Go to bed.
I'll finish it on my own.
Gabriel...
Thank you.
Sir?
Mr. Boldwood, sir!
I wanted to ensure your
mistress' crops were safe.
Good work, Gabriel.
She's lucky to have you.
Wait a moment, sir.
You seem unwell, sir.
You should go home.
Yes.
Yes, I will.
Oak.
You know that things have
not gone well with me, lately.
I was going to get a little
settled in life. But, er...
It was not to be.
I daresay I'm something of a...
A joke about the parish.
But I do wanna make
one thing clear.
There was no jilting
on her part.
We were never engaged.
No matter what people say.
She promised me nothing.
And yet,
Gabriel,
I feel the most terrible grief.
Not a word to her.
We understand each other, yes?
Yes, sir.
Damn and bother!
Sit.
Stay. Now, turn around.
Can you spare a coin, please?
No, no.
Hit him!
Come on!
Knock him out!
Hit him!
Pay up.
Pay up, Mr. Troy.
Just take it.
Sir, excuse me.
Could you spare a coin, please?
No.
Fanny?
Hello, Frank.
Hello.
You're so pale.
Oh, Frank.
Darling, your hands are shaking.
I thought you said
All Souls, not All Saints.
I went to the wrong church.
When I got there, you'd gone.
And I don't blame you,
but it's been very hard,
Frank. I...
Not now.
My wife mustn't see you.
Your wife?
Mrs. Troy is very beautiful.
No more than you.
Frank, I must tell you,
I'm carrying your child.
What?
What if I told you that
I'd made a terrible mistake,
but that I will make amends?
I swear on my life
I will find a home
for you and our baby.
You've sworn before, Frank.
No, this time... This time...
Go to Budmouth.
Stay at the Union.
The workhouse, Frank?
Tonight, just tonight.
One night.
And then meet me tomorrow
at 10:00 on the bridge.
I'll bring you
all the money I have
and I'll find a home for you.
You'll be safe, my darling.
And I promise you, I promise you
I will make amends.
Get back in the carriage.
Do you know who that woman is?
I do.
Who is she?
She's nothing.
Get back in the carriage.
Frank...
Could you let me have £20?
What for?
I need it.
If you continue to gamble,
we will lose the farm.
It's not for gambling.
What's it for?
Why should it matter
what it's for?
It's my money.
I work for it, don't I?
No. You don't.
Not proper farm work.
Don't do something
you'll regret.
The money is required
for farm expenses.
No mistake, Mr. Oak.
This was Miss Robbin's
last known abode.
Fanny was
my uncle's servant
and we shall treat
her with respect.
Perhaps we should
take her to the church,
just for tonight.
No, bring her inside, please.
What did she die of, Liddy?
I don't know, miss.
There were rumors, but...
Fanny had a sweetheart,
didn't she?
Yes, miss.
A soldier.
Please, come
and sit upstairs with me.
I seem to cry
a great deal these days.
I never used to cry at all.
Good night, Liddy.
'Night, miss.
What?
Who is it?
I can't say...
Stay, stay. Stay.
Don't kiss them, Frank.
I'm still your wife.
This woman, dead as she is,
is more to me than you
ever were, or are, or can be.
You are nothing to me now.
Nothing.
Mrs. Troy?
I'm afraid...
I'm afraid your
husband has drowned.
That's a great
responsibility, sir.
Nonsense.
No reason why a man
of your ability
shouldn't be able to
superintend two farms.
And why shouldn't there
be stronger links
between our establishments?
Think of it. Two thousand
acres under your sole charge.
A share of my profits.
Miss Everdene needs me here.
And her farm will have priority.
I'd still need
Miss Everdene's permission.
But, of course.
Of course, I wouldn't
dare do anything
without her blessing. And,
if it'll help
sway your decision,
there's an old comrade
of yours here.
Georgie!
Had to go all the way
to Norcombe Hill
to find this old fella.
You pleased?
Yes, sir, very much.
And I'll have your
decision soon, yes?
You will, sir.
Hey, Georgie.
Come on. Come on.
Come on! Come on!
Gabriel, you're
getting on in the world.
Of course you must
accept the offer.
Only with
your approval.
If I lose the farm,
there may be no future
for any of us here.
You know where my loyalty lies.
You're a man of great talent.
It's only natural
that you should rise.
I've no desire to hold you back.
Thank you.
Come on, Georgie.
Come on.
Forgive me.
I understand there are debts.
Your late husband.
Perhaps... Perhaps we should
change the subject.
Perhaps I can help.
Mr. Boldwood,
that's a very kind offer,
but I would never dream
of accepting any money.
I am a middle-aged man
willing to protect you
for the rest of your life.
You may run your farm,
if you wish. Without risk.
I'll pay your
departed husband's debts
and guarantee
its financial stability.
It can be your pastime.
Of course, we'd need to wait,
for propriety's sake.
But when you're ready,
I'm offering you shelter.
Comfort. A safe harbor.
As my wife.
You must at least admire
my persistence.
I do.
And like me?
Yes.
And respect me?
Yes. Very much.
Which is it?
Like or respect?
It is difficult for a woman
to define her feelings
in a language chiefly
made by men to express theirs.
If you worry about a lack
of passion on your part,
a lack of, er,
desire,
if you worry about marrying me
merely out of guilt,
and, er,
pity and compromise, well...
I don't mind.
When must you
give your answer?
By Christmas.
It's a terrible responsibility.
I hold that man's
future in my hands.
His sanity, too, perhaps.
Could you care for him?
You may suppose
love is wanting.
But love's a worn-out,
miserable thing for me now.
Why are you
asking me?
I need someone who's objective.
Indifferent.
Then I'm afraid you're
asking the wrong man.
Good evening, Mr. Oak.
Good evening.
That's it.
Mind.
Rejoice
Emmanuel
Shall come to thee
O Israel
O come, Thou Rod of Jesse...
I appreciate you
coming along, Oak.
Ah!
Yes, very good.
Well done. Erm...
Just more... More things.
Yes, sir.
So what do you think?
I'm not in the habit of
organizing parties.
Perhaps we should make it
an annual event.
Every Christmas Eve.
I've invited the whole village.
Do you think they'll come?
Do you think
Miss Everdene will come?
I'm sure she will.
Yes.
And you'll come too, I hope.
I know Miss Everdene
would like you to be here.
Perhaps, for an hour or so.
Look, I'm shaking.
I'm so nervous.
Gabriel, will you...
As well as you can, please.
I'll try.
Is there a knot that's
particularly fashionable?
You're asking the wrong man.
What about women?
Does a woman keep her promise?
She has promised?
An implied promise.
Once again, I'm...
Will she do what's right?
If it's not inconvenient to her.
Oak, you've become
quite cynical lately.
She never promised
that first time.
Therefore, she has
never broken her promise.
She hasn't promised
this time, either.
But she will. Tonight.
I know she will.
And when she does...
I wanted to tell you
in advance, Gabriel,
because I... I believe
I know your secret.
I've seen you together.
The way you speak to her.
And watch her.
And look after her.
And I know her, er,
profound affection for you.
You've behaved like a man,
and as the successful rival,
successful through
your kindness,
I wish to tell you
I am profoundly grateful.
The cook would like a word, sir.
Kiss me. Joseph.
No, please don't.
Liddy, don't.
Would you excuse me?
I've come to say good night.
Go back and talk to
the poor things.
You've broken their hearts.
I don't suit
this kind of affair.
No. Nor do I.
I wish I could go, too.
I must go.
Not before you've danced.
Both of you.
I insist.
Mr. Oak?
Thank you.
Tell me what to do.
Gabriel?
Do what is right.
Sorry, excuse me.
Frank.
Black suits you.
Although a little premature.
You're alive.
And here I am.
Pulled from the sea.
Some fishermen found me
and brought me to shore.
Then I discovered I was dead
and found I preferred it.
For a while, anyway.
Why have you come back?
The strangest thing.
I missed you.
You don't seem very
happy to see me.
You said I was nothing to you.
Did I?
Well, then.
Honesty at all times.
I find myself in need of money.
I gave up my profession for you,
and it seems a little harsh
that you have a farm and a house
while I'm living off nothing.
There is no money.
Then sell the farm.
Come home.
No.
I said, come home.
I'm your husband
and you'll obey me!
Oh, my God.
Let me see.
If it's
any consolation,
his life will be spared.
Crime of passion.
Morning, Liddy.
It's a
fine harvest, ma'am.
Best we've had in years.
Will we have it all over
before the dew?
We will indeed, ma'am.
Luck's been on our side.
Come, Liddy, give me a hand.
I'm sorry I startled you.
I wanted to tidy up for them.
I haven't been here for so long.
Are you going in?
Rehearsals.
I sing bass in the choir.
Yes, I've heard you.
Then I apologize.
I've been hoping to get
a chance to talk to you.
We've... We've not spoken
as much as I'd have liked.
No.
I'm leaving England.
Leaving?
Going to America.
There's a boat leaving
Bristol in four days' time.
I'll be on it.
Now that the farm is secure.
I understand I should
give you notice.
No. You must go
when you want.
I'll leave first thing tomorrow.
No fuss.
I think that's best.
Gabriel!
Gabriel.
Wait.
You'll think I'm strange, but...
I've been worried.
Have I offended you somehow?
No, not at all.
Is it money?
I'll pay you whatever you want.
I don't need money now.
A formal partnership, then?
Nor a partnership.
The farm belongs to you alone.
It's the finest farm
for miles around.
Then why else are you leaving?
I said I'd leave you one day.
Well, you must not go.
You forbid me?
Yes, if you like.
I forbid you.
It's time for you
to fight your own battles.
And win them, too.
So we should
say good-bye, then?
I suppose so.
Gabriel, wait.
Thank you, Gabriel.
You've believed in me
and fought for me
and stood by my side when
all the rest of the world
is against me.
And we've been through
so much together.
Wasn't I your first sweetheart?
Weren't you mine?
And now I'd have to
go on without you.
If I knew...
If I knew that you would
let me love you and marry you...
But you will never know.
Why not?
Because you never ask!
Would you say no again?
I don't know.
Probably.
So why don't you?
Ask me.
Ask me, Gabriel.
Come all you fair
and tender girls
That flourish in your prime
Beware, beware
Keep your garden fair
Let no man steal your thyme
For when your thyme
it is past and gone
He'll care no more for you
And every place
Where your thyme was waste
Will all spread o'er with rue
The gardener's son
was standing by
Three flowers he gave to me
The pink, the blue
and the violet true
And the red, red rosy tree
But I refused the red rose bush
And gained the willow tree
That all the world
may plainly see
How my love slighted me