- What's happening?
- Go.
Mom! Who are they?
I don't have time to explain it
to you now. You have to go.
Quick!
Mom will come after you.
Go. You have to go.
Anybody here?
Would you mind?
For sure.
- Is everything ready?
- Yes.
- Did you have any problems?
- No.
Hold it.
Hello.
Out!
Get out!
I might have you all skinned alive
once all of this is done.
Quick!
Shoot! Shoot!
Duck down!
Shoot them!
Alert the patrol boat.
I want them stopped.
What's this?
Smells good.
Get out!
Of course...
as soon as you give us the bar.
Give it up, Lara.
- I will not ask you again.
- You went too far Milenko.
Bringing these animals
into my house.
- Give it to us or we'll find it!
- Go to hell!
Get out.
Out!
Look at this fool...
I'll show you.
Just don't hurt him.
He knows nothing about it.
That's my girl.
Anybody here?
Drop it, please.
Get that rascal, he's got my gold!
Calm down, calm down!
I will help you.
Come with me!
No! I'm not a Nazi!
Just calm down... Come on.
I'm your friend.
Will you trust me?
Would you come with me?
Come on. Come with me.
Let's go.
- Is everything ready?
- Yes.
- Did you have any problems?
- No.
Come.
Keep looking.
They are here to help us, Mr. Kurjak.
Twenty pieces.
Let's go, guys!
What's that?
Do you know that this can buy
your shitty dump a hundred times?
So what?
What am I going to do with that?
I need cash!
Like this...
Here, this is what they gave me.
Have you ever seen them before?
Them? Never.
Just some punks...
Those are their plates.
What you did is very patriotic.
A very unusual and valuable item.
Where's it from?
I found it.
From now on, I'll only speak to you...
Now you'll tell me everything.
Is that her?
She won't get far.
Stay with him!
Keep going.
Gear up!
Throw the explosives.
Lower, lower!
Straight ahead!
Give it to me.