♪ [OPENING THEME MUSIC] ♪
-This is Radio Rebel live
from the underground.
You don't know who I am...
but I know who you are...
because I'm one of you.
Report cards came out today. I
got a minus in participation.
But you can't give me
a minus for who I am,
so since grades are being
handed out I think I'll give
all of us at Lincoln Bay High
an F for labeling
each other.
Jocks, outcasts, dorks, queen
bees and their fellow pops
...and newborn pops.
Guys, these are all labels,
not who we really are.
Once upon a time being
different was a good thing.
Now those differences
just divide us.
You deserve to embrace
your awesomeness, stand
up for who you are.
Reject the status quo.
I dare you.
- Okay, last night
Radio Rebel--
- was awesome?
- As usual! Reject the status
quo is my new life motto.
- Mmm...
- She's so inspiring,
so herself.
- I wish I could be
more like her.
[GASP]
- You should talk
to your step-dad!
- What? Why?
- Uh, he runs Slam
FM, the biggest radio
station in Seattle.
Maybe he could give
you an internship.
That'd be a confidence
booster right?
- Are you kidding me.
He's been married to my
Mom for what? 2 months?
He probably thinks I'm
a total step-freak.
I freak out when he asks
what kind of cereal I want.
- Mmhmm.
- I just wish I
could talk to
everyone the way I
talk to you.
Guess that's
why you're
my BFF.
- Uhm,
B-F-F-T-L-E-W-E
Best Friends For
Totally Like Ever
Without Exception.
- Catchy.
- [GASP]
You need a relaxation technique.
When I'm memorizing lines
for drama I imagine I'm
breathing in the words.
- Audrey, what does
that even mean?
- [CLEARS THROAT]
You need to breathe
...your words.
- How can you
even breathe at a
time like this.
- Problem Barry?
- Last night Radio Rebel
revealed the biggest clue
yet about her identity...
She goes to our school.
- She mentioned it at
minute 14:30 in Tuesday
night's podcast.
- Wow, obsessed
much Larry?
- Obsessed? Puh-lease!
I would hardly describe
myself as obsessive.
[PAPER SOUND]
[LAUGHS]
[CLEANING SOUNDS]
What? It's flu season.
So exciting! Someone on the
radio who's actually one of us.
- God. She
could be that
girl, or...
or her, or her,
or that girl,
that girl.
- No, no
that girl's
too tall.
Radio Rebel's
voice sounds like
5'6 to me...
and her hair
is reddish...
like Tara's.
- Nooooo.
She's nothing
like Tara.
- Hey. What's
that supposed
to mean?
- Oh we, we love
you, but...
you're nothing like
Radio Rebel who's
definitely a blonde.
- And you know
this how?
- Radio Rebel is
my soul mate.
We're connected. For
example, I also got a
minus in participation.
- How can that be?
You never shut up.
- [LAUGHS]
Exactly.
[RADIO TOY SOUNDS]
[LAUGHTER]
- Stacy
that outfit
is amazing.
- Hi Stacy.
- Honestly, it's a relief
that we broke up.
The whole long distance
relationship thing is just lame.
- Well, I'm glad you've moved on
because you've already had 3
formal asks to prom!
Alan Ackerman--
- Too short, think
of the pictures.
- Okay, how about
Jamie Wordle?
- Have you ever noticed
how pointy his head is?
It's like a triangle!
- Guys, how do we reject the
status quo when the status
quo is... status quo?
- Like Radio
Rebel said,
be ourselves.
- Audrey.
- So, next Erin Brooks is
officially campaigning
for prom queen.
I just
confirmed
it on her
fan page.
- Whatever. No
competition there.
Why don't
I have a
fan page?
- I'll get
right on it.
- Hi Stacy.
How's it going?
[LAUGH]
- This is what I
was talking about.
Everyone thinks they
can just talk to us
cause of that eternally
lame radio babble.
-Methinks she
protests too much.
- Yeah,
wethinks...
Wait, what
do wethinks?
- That maybe she's
Radio Rebel.
-Huh. Please. Like I would
ever encourage people like
you to talk to us.
- Ah ha! So you
admit you
listen to her.
- [SIGHS]
- This one's
staring at me.
Make it stop.
- Please don't stand
so close to us.
- You and I aren't
any different. Like
Radio Rebel said--
- No words. You don't
think we're different?
Watch and learn.
Principal Moreno.
- Stacy...
Is everything
alright over here?
- Actually, no.
Audrey was trying to get me to
listen to some podcast in class.
Of course I said no--
- What? No. I mean I never--
- You know that there's an
anti-distraction policy.
Let me see your bag.
[SIGHS]
- But I wasn't even
listening to it.
[WHINEY VOICE]
- Well now you
can't, can you?
You too young lady,
hand it over.
Thank you for bringing this to
my attention Stacy.
- Get it now?
Your little DJ hero doesn't
know what she's talking about.
Oh? Does her royal shyness
want to say something?
- I--
- Huh?--
- I thought not.
- Bye girls.
- Greetings to our loyal fans.
This is Gabe and Gavin or
as you know us the G's
and that's to say thank
you for voting for us
to play at your prom.
We'll make sure it
totally rocks!
- Well, well, well look
who it is. Lincoln Bay's
own internet sensation.
- Hey Stacy.
- Gavin, and Gavin's camera...
I heard you guys are
playing prom. Pretty sweet.
- Byyye.
- Dude, you are in!
- What do you mean?
- Stacy and her
college boyfriend
just called it quits,
which means as
of right now she
doesn't have a
prom date.
- I can't ask
her to prom.
[LAUGHS]
- Didn't you
see that?
[IN HIGH
PITCHED VOICE]
Hi Gavin.
- It's the band,
man. We're getting
some heat.
A little attention from the
ladies. Your stock is on the
rise and Stacy's noticing.
- Well, what would I even say?
- Listen to me, okay,
focus. Eye of the Tiger,
Don't Stop Believing. We
are the Champions.
- Are you
just quoting
song titles?
- This is your
chance man, seize
the moment.
Our fan base is
expanding to other
schools, the city--
- I still feel like that awkward
kid with the guitar just hanging
out in your garage.
- Forget that now!
Now you're Gavin
...of the G's.
We're going all the way baby,
recording contracts, sold out
stadiums, G's for life?
- G's for life!
[IN UNISON]
- Ow!
[BELL RINGS]
- Alright, everybody, today
we are going to be working
on a project with Mr.
Saul's drama class.
Oh! Here they are now.
Come on in people please.
Pick a seat, quickly.
- This is so exciting.
- Gavin, this seat is free.
[MUSIC]
- I will be pairing
you all up, and...
- What is Gavin
doing here?
- Uh, he's
in drama?
You know you could
talk to him.
You've had a crush on him
since like the first Harry
Potter movie.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, he's a newborn
pop, okay totally
wrong social bracket.
The best thing for
me is to just avoid
him all together.
- [SIGHS]
Gavin's not elitist like
that. Ask yourself.
What would
Radio Rebel do?
- You will be translating a
scene from Shakespeare...
- Hey, it's good
that we're in class
together now.
Saves me from having
to find you later.
- Oh? And why would
you have to find me?
- Cus I want to ask
you something...
about prom?
- I need a volunteer.
Who would like to write a
scene suggestion on the b--
- [SHOES RUNNING]
- oard.
[MARKER SQUEAKING]
[THROAT CLEARING]
- Oh. Did you want
to pick a volunteer?
I got excited!
[LAUGHTER]
- Drama is my life. Okay, who
wants to write a suggestion?
Let's see hands people!
- Okay hands, hands, ha--Tara!
[MENACING MUSIC]
How about you?
Come on up!
- You can do it. Just
don't make eye contact.
[MUSIC]
[MARKER SQUEAKING]
[CLAPPING MUSIC]
- I was thinking
maybe we could--
[STUMBLING SOUND]
- Hello! Uh
walk much?
- Uh.
[HEAD BANGING SOUNDS]
[GASPING]
- Ohh.
[LAUGHTER]
- Okay, people.
Settle, settle...
I still need
a volunteer.
- Tara, are you alright?
- Ohhhh.
- You okay?
[MUSIC]
- Hey Delilah. Look
at this. County Q
called me.
She told me I had
to check out this
new podcast girl.
She's, she's really
something special.
- That's for my pedicure.
- Hmm--
- That was the latest
single from You-First!
But who are you exactly?
I think we're always juggling a
bunch of different you's...
like when you're
with your friends.
Sometimes you're the funny
one, or the loud one--
- N-n-no. No. No.
[ARUGING]
- The thoughtful one...
- How about with
someone you like?
Which you shows up then?
I don't even know who
to be when I see the guy
I'm crushing on,
which is probably why
I never talk to him.
Is it just me or do you
feel like you're 17
different people too?
- Yes, I do. I totally
feel that way!
- This song goes out
to all my
fellow Lincoln Bayers--
- She's amazing right?
- Right.
- This is exactly what Slam FM
needs, a fresh new vibe to get
us out of this rating slump.
- [GASPS]
You need to ask Tara
what she thinks.
It could be a bonding moment!
- Yeah. I mean, I
could, I could do that.
Be a kind of bonding thing.
Step-Daughter, Step-Father...
- Mmhmm.
- Stop eating my foot fruit.
- Alright well, I'll do
that. I will, I'll talk to
her, or not at all.
- You can do it!
- It'll be a bonding thing.
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
[MUSIC]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[DOOR OPENS]
- Hey!
- Rob.
...What are you doing here?
- I live here.
- Okay. Thanks for stopping by.
- So what do you think
of Radio Rebel?
- What? Why?
- I just, I just want to get
your take on her. That's all.
- She's great.
Bye now.
You know what? I, I knew
that you'd think so.
I really did, you know?
[DOOR SHUTS]
We have so much in
common, you know?
- Yeah. Like we're
both super busy.
- Listen, I look, I know that
this is a really difficult
transition for you...
and with your dad working
in Taiwan, and your Mom and I,
and I just want you to
know that you, you
have a friend here.
- It's fine. I'm
fine, really. Y--
- So this is good right? I
mean here we are, we're,
we're hanging out,
and we're listening to
Radio Rebel, and together.
- Together.
- That's weird.
I'm not hearing anything.
What happened the
music just stopped.
Yours stop?
[SIGHS]
- Huh. where'd she go?
- And that rounds off the final
set for my favorite local band.
Now here's an extra
long track just for you
guys. I hope you dig it.
[MUSIC PLAYS]
- You're Radio Rebel?
- That depends.
Am I in trouble?
- No. No, of
course not.
Just I don't know how
you're doing that. I
mean you're so shy.
- I am, but she's not.
I don't know.
Just works.
- I can't believe it. I
mean, oh, I love it, I
just I can't believe it.
We're gonna take Slam
FM to the next level!
- I'm, I'm sorry. We?
- Yeah. I, you are gonna be
Slam FM's next big thing.
You're hired. That's what you
are. You're hired. Ha!
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
- I. Uh.
[DOOR KNOCKING AND OPENS]
[EXCITED SQUEALING]
- Oh, I just happened to
be eavesdropping. I hope
you don't mind.
- [SIGHS]
- O-M-G my baby is gonna take
Slam to the next level. Ahh!
[SQUEALING]
[SIGHS]
What's the matter?
- What if I mess it up?
- Oh, honey... You
have to take risks.
Like I always thought Chartreuse
was a bad color for me,
and then I tried it, and
now it's my trademark.
How do you know something isn't
fabu if you never try it, right?
[GIGGLES]
[SIGHS]
[BELL RINGS]
- Look out, you're in the
12th night group with
Stacy and Gavin.
[MUSIC PLAYS]
- No. no. no.
No, I can't.
- Talk to him. He's
just a person.
- Go on.
Go. Do it.
- Hey.
Cool shirt!
I love
that band!
You-First rules!
The G's can only dream of
being that good some day.
- The G's are totally
as good as You-First.
- Really?
- Okay! Here's our scene.
Tara is Viola. Now Tara
this role does require
both walking and talking.
Think you can manage?
Just kidding. You know
I love you. Okay and
Gavin you're Orsino.
- Wait. What about you?
- Brower has me directing, and
we've got a lot of work to do.
- If you like You-First, you
should check out Red Letter Day.
You ever heard of them?
- Uh-uh, no band talk
right now, Gav.
Sorry, but I don't want anyone
to think I'm favoring you just
cus I'm your prom date.
Speaking of, we need to work on
your Prom King campaign.
[WHISTLE]
- Of course he's
taking Stacy to prom.
- Uh, look at least
you talked to him.
For you that's
major progress.
- I barely got
2 words out.
- Come to my
house tonight.
We'll do yoga. I'll
teach you the extended
hyena pose I invented,
and we'll listen to Radio Rebel.
- I can't.
- What do you mean?
It's Radio Rebel's
first show on Slam FM.
Do you realize how
epic that is?
I mean, she was
popular before,
but now it's like the
whole world will be
listening, including us.
- I have plans.
- What plans?
- Family plans.
- You are the
worst liar.
You sound just like you did
when you said you liked that
haircut I got at the mall.
- It wasn't that bad.
- It was mullet adjacent.
Tell me what you're
hiding or I'll start
screaming in 3 seconds.
- What?
- 1--
- Audrey no, no, no.
- 2--
- Audrey--
[LOUD SCREAMING]
Well?
- ...I'm sorry. I
can't tell you.
- I thought I was
your BFFTLE.
- Without exception.
- Then why don't
you trust me?
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
[CLAPPING MUSIC]
- Gavin. 3 o'clock.
- Your 3 o'clock
or my 3 o'clock.
- We have the
same 3 o'clock.
Ohhh. He's coming
over here. What do we do?
- For the record, this why you
don't ice your friends out.
Talk to him!
- Hey Tara, what's up?
[SIGH]
So, do you want to run
lines on the weekend?
[SILENCE]
Or we can mime the lines
if you're not feeling
particularly talky?
- Mime, talky? I'm gonna
go. Me n-now.
- Uhm, okay.
- Tara.
[LAUGHTER]
- Free meals.
- Score.
[MUSIC]
- Hey Seattle. You're
listening to Slam FM.
- I want Radio Rebel
ads in every major
social network.
Just blast the internet.
Updates every hour. We want
to blanket the market.
Good. Alright. Bye.
[PHONE BEEP]
So I was talking to your Mom
about keeping Radio Rebel on the
QT and I think it's a good idea.
You know, I don't want you to
talk to anybody about it.
Radio Rebel is the shot in the
arm that Slam FM needs.
Since the last that I
produced with Snazzy Dog
crashed and burned, there's
a lot hinging on this right?
Including my job, no
pressure, right?
So your show's gonna run 7 PM
Monday to Friday, since that
was the time you broadcast
from your room,
and you'll be taking over
from DJ Funky Mac
who is now moving
to Sunday night.
Alright, so let's show
you the booth.
Tara?
[DOOR SLAMS]
- Hey Tara! Remember me?
Kimmy Q. We met at the
Slam Christmas Party.
Girl, when Rob told me you were
Radio Rebel, this was my face?
Wha--?
Cus, I, I thought you were
just this little shy thing,
but you are all
kinds of amazing.
You are fierce.
I just can't wait to see what
you got going for the--
Tara?
Are you okay?
- I can't even speak to
Gavin without freezing.
How am I supposed to
speak to all of Seattle?
- It's no different than
recording in your bedroom.
- Yes it is.
- In my bedroom, I could pretend
that nobody's listening, but
right now I know that
everybody's listening,
and Rob's putting all this
pressure on it, and Mom wants it
to be my chartreuse moment, and
I don't even like
chartreuse. I don't even
know what chartreuse is.
- Tara, come out
where I can see you.
Everybody gets nervous.
It's totally normal.
Just consider me like
your best friend at Slam.
Catch your breath.
Then we'll go out
together, okay?
[DOOR OPENS]
Alright.
- Is this whole
booth all for me?
- We call this the live room,
because when that red light
is on you're live.
If you want to move around
use this headset so we
don't miss anything.
There's your vocal
masking button.
You already know
about that.
And song selection's
up to you.
Alright?
- There's like 20,000
songs here.
- You got some time before
you go on, if you want to
practice, get comfortable.
- Practice. Right, okay, uhm.
Maybe I should play a
song just to make
sure I know how to--
[RAP MUSIC BEGINS AND SQUEALS]
No, no, no. Bad practice,
bad practice.
- Don't worry about it. You'll
be fine, and I'm right next
door if you need me.
Just pretend you're
in your bedroom.
You're on in 15.
14, 13. 12. 11. 10,
9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3,
- You're listening to Slam FM.
This is the Radio Rebel show.
- This is Radio Rebel live from
Slam FM. Listen, I gotta confess
moving the show from my bedroom
to Slam studios was a bit
terrifying, but life is
all about change right?
Maybe some people just
want to label you as one
thing, compartmentalize
you and walk away.
We don't have to let that
stop us from becoming who
we want to be.
Like that kid with the remote
control car. Maybe he's gonna
grow up to invent the first
all green rocket ship.
Or the girl who gets everyone
carnations on Valentine's Day,
just so no one feels left out.
She'll grow up to be President.
Guys, if we just drops the
labels and cliques--
Yean, yeah-- Record.
- We have no idea what
we're capable of.
- No! Uh!
- If you're with me on
this, wear red tomorrow.
It'll be like saying that
despite our difference,
we're in this together.
This next song is from
Red Letter Day.
[MUSIC]
- Ahem. Do you
like my glasses?
- You have freakishly
good vision.
- Fashion shouldn't
be functional.
Do you know why I picked
red rims? I assume you do
because of your red shirt.
- I can't believe all these
people are wearing red just
cus Radio Rebel said to.
How cool is that?
- So you did listen to
Radio Rebel last night.
What happened to
your mystery plans?
- Can you guys tell us apart?
- You guys are fraternal,
not identical, oh.
[ELEVATOR DOOR OPENS]
- Hey. We just ran a
recording of Radio
Rebel's show through
a voice analysis app.
We're closer than
ever to uncovering
her true identity.
- Picture it. Local twins
crack Radio Rebel's ID.
- Soon, I'll be able to
profess my undying love.
- We'll be famous.
We could, we could get a
reward, or at least our
own reality TV Show.
- Where she and I
could be married
live on TV.
Tara, since your
Step-Dad runs Slam maybe
you could help us out.
- Oh. I, I'm not allowed to
go up to Slam FM, while
uhm, she's there
to keep the mystery mysterious.
- The truth is Tara
doesn't have time to do
friend related things.
- Audrey. Audrey. Audrey!
- What?
Uh, you know what.
Forget it. I'm leaving.
- No, no, no.
[SLAMS]
I'm about to tell you
something so Top Secret
you have to promise never
to repeat it to anyone.
- I won't tell anyone,
I swear.
[BREATHES HEAVY]
You can say it.
- [COUGHING]
I'm Radio Rebel.
- Tara, you
have to breathe
your words.
- [MUTTERING WITH
TEETH TOGETHER]
I'm Radio Rebel.
- Louder. Come on.
Breathe the words,
breathe them.
- [CLEARS THROAT]
I'm Radio Rebel.
- Oh. I don't
believe you.
- If you're like me and
believe music can change the
world one track at a time,
you're gonna love this track
from my new favorite band.
- Wow. I can't believe
she's you. I, you're her!
I mean you're the last
person I'd expect to be
Radio Rebel, Tara.
[LAUGHS]
It's been driving me
crazy not telling you,
and of course I've been
wanting to hang out, but
I've been doing my show.
Here's the thing you
can't tell anyone. Not
even Larry and Barry,
because Slam wants
to keep it this big
secret and, so do I.
[EXCITED LAUGHTER]
- Remember Twelfth Night is all
about mistaken identity.
Tara, you character has a crush
on Gavin's character, but she's
not even from law or whatever,
so she's disguised as a
guy, and Gavin's character
doesn't know you like him.
So, you're in agony. I
need to see real pain.
Let's do the end again!
And, act!
- My sister likes this
guy, and, by my sister,
I, I mean... my sister,
not me at all, cus
look at my pants, see
I'm totally a dude.
- Does this guy
like her too?
- That's the tragic
part. She hasn't told
him how she feels, so...
she's not sure if he
feels the same way.
- What's she
waiting for?
- For him to make
the first move,
but tell me,
if she never confesses
her love does that make
her love any less real?
- Okay! Some of that worked...
and some of it didn't!
There's a fine line between
pain and constipation.
Let's take 5.
[DROPPING SOUND]
- Oh you dropped--
- Oh, thanks.
- Is this a demo
of the G's?
- Yeah! You
know, trying out
a few new things.
Actually, I'd love to
try out some more new
stuff to be honest,
like I got the song--
- We're back! Focus! Let's
go, come on get up! Get up!
Come on! Go, go go,
get in positions.
Uhm, uh, let's try it with Tara
way over here. Yeah. Mmhmm.
Perfect.
I... I love it.
- Hey, hold on.
Tara, did you want
to say something?
- She's fine.
Action!
- Cut. Tara. You listen
to Radio Rebel right?
You were wearing red
yesterday so I figured.
Rebel's right.
Life's about taking
risks, making changes.
So, go ahead. Say
what you feel.
- Well, it's just that
this scene is about...
us falling for each
other even though we
don't know it yet, and--
- and blocking like
this feels weird right?
- Right, exactly.
Yeah I mean the
audience is supposed to
get what we're feeling
from what we're not
saying, and it only
works if we're closer.
- Yeah.
Yeah. I like
that better too.
- Okay. We clearly need
extra rehearsal. My
place, tonight at 7.
- Oh. I, I can't
tonight. There's...
Wednesday's
mandatory family dinner...
with my...
family... dinner.
- Fine. Whatever.
Lunch tomorrow.
Everybody's a director now!
- Hey.
Good job!
Okay.
- You people at Lincoln
Bay High killed it with
the red yesterday.
I noticed one of you wearing
these red specs that were
the epitome of cool,
but can we talk about what's
not cool for a second.
Now the school keeps
confiscating our stuff.
I mean, I've lost 2 sets of
headphones and an mp3 player
just this term alone.
Although, I did notice
that some of us seem to be
exempt from this little...
stuff snatching epidemic.
Funny how that works, huh?
Guys it's not just our
playlists and players we're
being deprived of you know?
Music is the soundtrack
to our lives.
It's, it's where we've been and
where we're going and everywhere
in between.
Our music is who we are.
Are we gonna let someone just
snatch that away from us...
or are we gonna change the game?
Here's a new song about,
uh, trying things you
never thought you could.
Look, I've been trying to do a
bunch of new things lately,
and this song severely
inspires me, so check it out.
Vibe it. Really, really
dig on it, and then,
remember that feeling.
Tomorrow at 8 AM, stop what
you're doing, get up and
dance, just express
yourself, let yourself out.
This is "Turn it All
Around" by the G's.
[MUSIC]
[CROWD CHEERING]
- You're all gonna get in so
much trouble for this!
Radio Rebel doesn't tell
me when to dance.
- Okay.
- Time to take
your own advice?
[SHOUTS]
[MUSIC]
- This is a place of
learning, not dancing.
Anyone listening to Radio Rebel
during school will be suspended.
And Radio Rebel, I advise you
to turn yourself in now
or your future will
be radio silence.
Nice!
- Hey, Tara.
Can I talk to you?
- Uh. Oh!
- Hmph!
- Yeah...
- It's about
our song.
- We have a, we
have a song?
- The one Radio Rebel
played last night.
- Oh.
- At first... I
couldn't believe that
she likes our music.
Then I wondered, how'd
she get our demo?
Got anything you
want to confess?
- I--
- It's you,
isn't it?
- It's me?
What's me?
- You're the one.
- Which one of the,
one of the--
- You're the one
who gave the CD...
to your Step-Dad to
give to Radio Rebel.
- Yes.
- Thank You!
- That's the one I, yes,
yes, that's I'm the one,
I'm the one with the I like
your, that's a great song--
- Thanks, but, doesn't
really feel like my voice.
It's like people are
hearing me, but they're
not hearing me.
That sounded
crazy didn't it?
- Not at all. I
totally get you.
- Well.
Thanks again.
- Oh yeah.
- Radio Rebel is amazing.
- She's really... neat.
- She gets caught in
my head, you know?
It's like I'd be
able to recognize
her on the street
just from how
well I know her
from her show.
- Well that, that'd
be something.
- Yeah. Well. See
you later Tara.
- Bye Gavin.
[MUSIC]
- You're listening to Slam FM.
- That's her.
I know it. I
can tell.
- Radio Rebel is an
old guy with a beard?
- You ever hear of
disguise, Barry?
[DOOR OPENS]
[CHATTER]
[GARBAGE BEING THROWN OUT]
- Seattle's hottest DJ the
Radio Rebel Show--
[DJ'S VOICE FADES OUT]
[BLIND OPENS]
- Ah!!
Did you see the posters?
- I can't even hear you!
- Did you see the posters?
- Uh, hard to miss.
They're everywhere.
My mom just called and said
she saw me on the bus.
I was like no, I'm at Slam.
She was like no, no, no you're
on the bus, of the side of it.
- They are spending money on
marketing for you
which means the ratings
must be up. You're famous.
- No, I'm not. No,
Radio Rebel is.
[SIGHS]
Even Gavin has
a thing for her.
- That's good. We
like Gavin, right.
- Yes we do, and it was
hard enough when I had
just Stacy to deal with.
Now, I'm competing with
myself for his attention,
and I appear to be losing.
- What? Baby, you've
got fan clubs at every
school in Seattle.
I mean look at all
the petitions.
"We want a dance break every
day."
"We want more Radio Rebel."
"Don't take our music away."
- Wait, I have a
really good idea.
Okay, this is what
we're gonna do.
[BELL RINGS]
- What is
going on?
- Well, Moreno can't complain
about us disrupting class
time, because it's lunch.
- This was your idea.
[SQUEALS]
It's brill.
[GIGGLES]
[MUSIC]
[CHEERS]
- Hey, hey, hey, Lincoln
Bay this is Cami Q
coming at you live.
You all feeling good today?
[CHEERS]
[CLAPPING]
- Alright, listen up! I got
a special message
from our good
friend Radio Rebel.
- This is Radio Rebel
coming at you with a little
lunch time surprise--
- That girl invaded our
airwaves. Does she have
to ruin my lunch to?
- Now, a lot of you guys
have IMed and texted me
about the powers at be
taking away our music...
and how it feels like one of
ourselves is being taken away.
[CROWD BOOS]
- That's not gonna make
us better students.
[UNISON]
- Woah!
- And you can't punish
someone for relaxing
during their down time...
like Principal Moreno,
you stole our music and
I'm giving it back.
Text in requests. Lunch
time is our time.
[CROWD CHEEERS]
[MUSIC]
- You're on school property!
- Actually, uh, beyond this
point is city property.
Did you want to
see my permit?
- Move. Move. Move.
- This Radio hor-Rebel
has got to go.
- It's kind of
a fun dance.
- No, it's not.
Stop that!
Go vote for me for
Prom Queen again. Go!
[MUSIC]
- Wooh!
[LAUGHTER]
- Mine!
[MUSIC]
[BELL RINGS]
- Can I have your
attention please?
I want you all to know
that this lunch time
fiasco was a, fiasco.
It is time for a certain
DJ's reign of rebellion
to come to an end.
Anyone with any information
regarding the identity of
this Radio Rebel
is to report it to
me immediately
or risk facing disciplinary
actions themselves.
Now get to class.
- Principal Moreno, I just
want to say that I could
not agree with you more.
I, for one, thought the display
at lunch was disgusting.
Radio Dribble should pay for
playing a stunt like that.
- Oh. Don't worry
Stacy. Disruptions like
today are temporary,
but I can enforce disciplinary
measures that can last forever.
- Like diamonds
and rice cakes?
- Shh! No words.
- You mean you can
expel Radio Rebel?
- Well, her actions were in
direct defiance of my policies,
so there will be consequences.
- All I can think about
now is rice cakes.
- Go.
[THE G'S SINGING]
- Hey. Sorry guys,
I was thinking
[SINGING CONTINUES]
[AMP SOUNDS]
- What are you doing?
- Sorry, but I think we
can do better than this.
You know, actually say
something with our music,
something meaningful,
relatable. I was listening
to Radio Rebel--
- Oh Gavin, uhm, one you
don't stop in the middle of
a song man okay?
And two, our fans don't want a
message, they want a party.
You want meaningful, go
write a poem. Stick with
what's working, alright?
- From the top.
- Since when do our fans
determine what we play?
- It's the price of
fame my friend.
- 1, 2, 3--
[AMP SOUNDS]
Now that we've got a following,
I think we could finally afford
to take some risks and express
ourselves creatively.
- Uh, negative. We're giving
them what they want, alright?
No more, no less. K?
- ...Okay.
- G's for life?
- Sure. G's for life.
- Thatta boy. Alright
from the top boys.
[MUSIC]
- If you don't go to
Lincoln Bay High you missed
out on a rock star day.
I've never seen so
many people dancing.
So my listeners in Hoover
High were so inspired by what
went down at Lincoln Bay
they had a full on flash mob
at lunch today.
[LAUGHS]
That rocks. You guys
totally need to post a
video on my webpage stat.
I heard the mathletes
and the water polo team
at Benson High
just formed a Pops,
Non-Pops Alliance Club.
You guys are my heroes,
and I got a call today
from a guy who graduated
High School 20 years ago.
He said this show inspired him
to stand up to his boss and get
the raise he deserved.
See what I mean?
Never too late to make
a difference guys.
[MUSIC]
- Tara, uh, I have news,
but we can't talk here.
- What?
- Scuse me, could you
give us a minute?
- Uh, but this
is my office.
- So, guess who got
nominated for Prom Queen?
- Stacy?
- You did! Well, not
you. Radio Rebel.
[EXCITED SIGH]
- This is horrible!
The whole point of Radio
Rebel is that she's
anonymous, remember?
What's gonna happen if she
wins? Who's gonna go up
there and accept the crown?
I could get expelled. I have
to put a stop to this.
- Are you crazy?
You can't quit now.
[DOOR OPENS]
Not now Mr.
Margowsky.
- But I need
the broom.
[DOOR SHUTS]
- Audrey, I can't
do this anymore.
- You can.
- I can't.
[DOOR OPENS]
[IN UNISON]
- Not now!
- I need the
dustpan, too.
- Here.
[SIGHS]
[DOOR SHUTS]
- You're a hero to
people and that's why
they nominated you.
You can't turn your
back on them now.
This is your
time to shine.
- What if I don't
want to shine.
What if shining isn't
really my thing?
- As your BFFTLEWE...
I'm legally obligated to
make sure you do the show,
even if I have to
drag you there.
[BELL RINGS]
- Hey, Tara, we got
another demo on the
way for Radio Rebel.
- Oh. I'm sure she's
stoked to hear it.
- Yo, Gavin.
- Hey Gav!
- Leper, you're
friends with the girl
who's Dad runs Slam.
I like the way
you think, bro.
- Her name's Tara.
- Who cares.
- She's actually
really nice.
- Woah. Wait,
Not, you're not
like into her or
anything are you?
Cus that would
not be good
for business?
- What do
you mean?
- We have
fans now.
Dedicated followers.
Those are the kind of
people that you should
be spending time with.
- You don't
even know her.
- Okay, I don't need
to and neither do you.
Think of the
band, man. Think
like a rock star.
[MUSIC]
- Why did we have to
park so far away?
- Because we
can't risk anyone
recognizing our
car or us.
Wig me.
- Okay.
[SPY MUSIC]
- Ugh. This cardboard is
inflaming my eczema. Do
you have any aloe vera?
- Will you concentrate?
- Why do you always
get the cool stuff?
- Shh. Shh. Focus!
[GIGGLES]
- This location is
compromised. Let's move.
[MUSIC].
- Keep it steady.
- Oh, oh, up,
up, Binoculars!
- Oh, focus Larry,
come on!
- Back, back, back.
- You dropped this.
- Got them. Okay go.
- We gotta blend
in. Blend in!
- This is where the
magic happens.
[CLAPS]
- Oh, so cool.
- Right?
- Is this the famous
Audrey Sharma?
- Me.
- Nice to meet you--
- It's nice to meet you, too!
[DOOR OPENS]
- Could you girls excuse
us for a moment?
[DOOR SHUTS]
- If this is about Audrey
being here, she's the
only person I told,
and I totally
trust her, like--
- No, this is not about
Audrey, this is about you.
Principal Moreno called.
The lunch time dance
party; that was a mistake.
She wants to expel Radio
Rebel as soon as she
finds out who she is.
- Well, as long as she
doesn't know it's me, we
shouldn't have a problem.
- Well, I can't take that
chance though, can I?
- What do
you mean?
- I may run Slam
FM, but I'm your
Step-Father first,
and it's unfortunate but
this has gone too far.
- Yes, it has.
Too far to stop now.
Look, this is bigger
than Slam, or Moreno,
or even me.
I can't turn my back on
the thousands of people
who finally feel like
they have a voice,
and I'm not going back to
that shy, invisible girl
who's afraid to even speak.
Look, I know
that it's risky...
but I'm not going
to back down.
- You know, I think that's
the most that I've heard
Tara say at one time.
You're on in 2 minutes.
[DOOR OPENS]
Good Luck, kid.
[DOOR SHUTS]
- A lot of you want to
know who I am--
- Here we go, come on.
Come on to Momma--
- I get that. Maybe
it'd be easier if you
could see my face.
That's the thing. Guys,
it's, it's not about me...
it's about you, so you don't
need to know my name.
[SIGHS]
- You want to know who I am?
I'm somebody who's
tired of being afraid.
I know how it can
hold you back,
So say it out loud.
Just say what
you're afraid of.
Call in. I dare you.
I guess everyone's too afraid to
say what they're afraid of.
Maybe this song will
inspire you, it's--
[DOOR KNOCKING]
- Lines 1 through 20!
[MUSIC]
- Huh. You're on
with Radio Rebel.
- One time, I accidentally
swallowed a tiny piece of
tin foil so I'm now afraid
if I stand too close to the
microwave I'll explode.
- I'm afraid of getting cut
from the football team.
- I'm afraid Larry
might be losing it.
- I'm afraid I'll always
be a single integer.
- I'm afraid of
power outages.
- I'm afraid to do
my own thing.
- I was too.
- Was?
So what changed?
- I guess I started
doing this show
and I realized...
you're not as alone
as you feel.
If you can remember that, it'll
be easier to take a risk.
Do your own thing.
- Yeah. Thanks.
- We're gonna take some
more calls in a minute.
In the meantime you guys
are gonna seriously dig
this next song.
[MUSIC]
- Hey, where
are you going?
- Just somewhere
to do something.
- I'm afraid of
hyenas. Phew.
[MUSIC]
- I'm afraid to show
people the real me!
- Congratulations.
- What?
- Your Prom Queen nomination.
It's on the school website. I
am so excited.
- But what about
Principal Moreno?
Mom, if Radio Rebel wins
and I confess my identity
I could get expelled.
- I don't care about
Principal Moreno.
Honey, people nominated
you for Prom Queen
because you inspire then.
[SIGHS]
You're standing up for
your beliefs.
That's all I care about.
- I don't think I'm
going to prom.
- Let me rephrase that.
All I care about is you standing
up for your beliefs and prom.
You have to go. It's Prom.
- You.
- No, No--
- But if I go--
- You have to--
- Mom--
- Oh, oh, you're going to prom.
Okay, excellent. Ohhh.
[DOOR SHUTS]
[MICROPHONE SOUNDS]
- This is your Principal.
There's been some
controversy about the
identity of Radio Rebel,
and there is nothing more
distracting than controversy.
Now, I gave her the chance
to do the right thing
and turn herself in, but
she chose to hide,
avoiding the consequences
of her insubordination.
Well she can't hide
forever, which is why,
until Radio Rebel's
identity is revealed,
I'm cancelling the prom.
- What? What?
[ANGRY CROWD SOUNDS]
- For everyone!
[LAUGHS]
- She can't do this!
- She can do whatever
she wants. She's like
the principal.
- Now do you think
there's favoritism
at Lincoln Bay?
- Not Moreno. Radio Feeble,
she's destroying anything.
Why should we have our
prom taken away just so
she can make a point?
- This is bad. This is
really, really bad.
[MUSIC]
[PROTEST SCREAMS]
- Save our Prom! Save our Prom!
- Prom is a right of
passage. If Radio Rebel is
really all about the people
then she'll reveal
her identity and get
us our prom back!
[CROWD CHEERS]
- How are we gonna
get in there?
[MUSIC]
- Who do you blame for your
prom getting canceled?
- Oh look, everybody
it's Radio Rebel!
[CROWD RUNS]
- Let's go.
- Go, go, go, go, go go.
- Show us who you
are Radio Rebel.
- Who is it?
- I can't see.
- Oh, hurry!
Get inside.
- Are we live?
[GIGGLES]
- Hi out there in Radio Land.
A lot's happened since we
last hung out, huh?
Let me know what you guys think.
Call me, text me, scroll on my
wall, don't be shy.
[COMPUTER BEEPING SOUND]
- You don't know
how many dreams
you've crushed by
cancelling prom?
- I agree with the
last caller. I had
just gotten a date
and now it's over?
- This is the
last time I'm
listening to
you ever.
- Who do you think you are?
- You disappointed everyone.
- Do you even care about
anyone but yourself?
- Do you know how many
dreams you've crushed?
- I thought you
were on my side.
- Dream Crusher.
Dream Crusher.
- Do you know how many
dreams you've crushed.
[MONTAGE OF SOUNDS]
- You ruined everything.
- Okay. You guys are being
honest about how you feel.
You're on Line 2.
- I've always liked
you Radio Rebel.
Your playlists
truly rock, but--
- Go ahead. Let it out.
- It's just...
there's a girl, I was hoping
to impress that night.
- Stacy.
- Sorry about that.
- Yeah. Me too.
- Wow. Guess you guys are
pretty upset. Well, uh,
I'll just play some music.
[MUSIC]
This next song's for you guys.
Thanks for being honest with
me. Sorry I let you down.
- They're just angry. They'll,
uh, they'll come around.
It doesn't take away from
all the good things you've
done as Radio Rebel.
- Did you hear them?
They hate me.
I ruined their prom.
I feel horrible.
- You didn't ruin it.
That principal did.
- I knew she was angry, but I
didn't know that she was gonna
do something like this.
- Man that Moreno is such
a backwards thinker.
- Backwards. That's brilliant.
- What?
- Backwards.
Backwards.
Oh, I thought everyone
would be gone by now.
This calls for a professional.
- Somebody order the
meaty subtacular?
Hello?
- Uh!
- Hi, could you
do us a favor?
- Uh, you want extra
uh marinara?
- Oh, that would
be awesome--
- Audrey
- And focusing.
I am the hyena.
- You see those girls out there?
We need to get out of here
without any of them seeing us.
- You can count on me.
- I'm just sad the world will be
deprived of me in my prom dress.
It's a strapless number.
It's oh-so chique. It's
a turkey on rye?
[MUSIC]
- Hello, Seattle!
- Care to comment
on Radio Rebel?
- Yes, I would! You're listening
to DJ Dancing Sandwich.
That turn tables spinning
in a funky groover.
[MUSIC]
- Dance, Dancing Sandwich!
- Wooee! Woo!
- When I'm here, I got to
move, I got to groover.
[MUSIC]
- Would you get back
down. You're blowing
our cover Larry.
- I can't do it
man. I think I felt
a human hand!
- That was my
hand Larry!
- Ahhh!
[FALLING SOUNDS]
- Good Morning Lincoln
Bay High School.
This is Cami Q from
Slam FM bringing you a
special message from--
- Radio Rebel here, and you
guys really unleashed your
fury about the prom drama,
and I want you to know
you've totally been heard.
Cancelling prom was
monumentally unfair,
[CROWD SOUNDS]
but blaming Moreno isn't
gonna solve anything.
I want to do something
about it, and so does Slam,
which is why we're
giving you all what you
want: your prom back!
[MUSIC]
Slam FM is throwing
it's first ever Morp,
that's prom spelled
backwards because we're
turning prom upside down.
Tickets are free and
everyone is invited,
so don't worry about finding a
date, or spending your college
savings on a dress, and
a tux, and a limo. Just
come as you are cus that's
the way we like you.
- Gotcha!
[DOOR SHUTS]
- It's just ridiculous. Morp?
Whoever heard of a Morp.
- That's the whole point,
I think, to do something
totally different. It
could be great.
- You know Gavin? I thought you
would have been more upset about
prom being cancelled..
considering we were
going together..
- Well, yeah, but we can
still go to Morp right?
- It's not the same. I
mean no limos, no dresses.
What is the point?
- To come as you are.
Be yourself.
- What about Prom
King and Queen?
People were nominated.
Somebody has to be
crowned. It's like law.
- Why don't you call Radio
Rebel and tell her that?
I'm sure she'd love to hear
from her number 1 fan.
- Ha!
- We need to rehearse. I'm not
going to fail this assignment
because you two
have zero work ethic.
[BELL RING]
- I think we're in trouble.
[LAUGHING]
- So, I've been getting
a billion questions
about the Morp,
which rules cus you all seem
stoked to go, which is the
whole point right?
A party where everyone
feels like royalty?
Then again, maybe should
crown a Morp King and Queen.
I mean after all, people
were nominated.
Look, if that's what you guys
want, that's what we'll do.
Morp is all yours,
so make sure to vote for your
favorite Morp King and Queen.
Make your voices heard...
especially my number 1 fan.
- What?
[CAR ACCELERATION]
[DOORBELL]
- Hi. Is
Tara home?
- Uh, sorry sweetie,
she's not here.
- Hmm. I'm in her
English class.
We're supposed to
study tonight.
Do you know
where she is?
- Afraid not. I'm just here
trying this new experimental
cuticle rejuvenation technique.
Do you want
to try?
- No. Thanks. Uh, do
you know when Tara
might be back?
- Sorry sweetie, I
don't. I'll tell her
you stopped by.
- Ta-ta.
[BELL RINGS]
- She was dressed as
man, so we can actually
start to assume--
- Right--
- I am so parched. What
I wouldn't give for a
smoothie right now?
How bout you Gavin? Are
you ready for a break?
- Sure. Tara, do you
want anything?
- No, I'm fine.
Thank you though.
- So, Tara, I'm having a party
at my place tonight,
and in the spirit of Radio
Rebel, I'm inviting everyone.
- Hmm.
- Even civilians like yourself.
- Ah gee, thanks,
but I have plans.
- Really? Same plans
as last night?
I went by your house. I
could have sworn you said
Wednesday was your mandatory
family dinner night,
but your Mom had no
idea where you were.
Strange, huh?
- I was, uh, library.
- You were, uh, library.
Sure you were.
There's no way that you
were say, DJing a radio
show at that time?
- No, why would
you think that?
- Radio Rebel mentioned her
number 1 fan last night. That's
what you called me yesterday.
- Must be a coincidence--
- Save it.
I'm watching you Tara.
- If you think that I'm Radio
Rebel, why don't you just tell
Principal Moreno. She already
thinks you're perfect.
- Because I need proof,
and tonight I will get it.
If you don't show up at my party
tonight we'll both know why.
- Why do you even care?
- I'll tell you why. Votes.
People are going to elect
her Morp Queen because they
want to find out who she is,
but if they already know,
they'll vote for the girl
who truly deserve it, Me!
This little DJ act is
coming to an end soon.
You are my hero.
What do you think Gavin? Should
we take it from the top?
- Yeah.
- The thing about your
character--
[MUSIC]
- Ohhoo! A party
during Radio Rebel's
podcast is brilliant!
[SLAPPING SOUNDS]
Tonight the mystery
ends. Whoever
doesn't show up is--
- Hey--
- Hey, where were
you just now?
- Park.
- Are you sure you weren't
setting up a broadcast station
from a remote satellite?
- You're accusing me of
being Radio Rebel?
1, I've been helping you
search for her this whole
time, and 2, I, I'm a guy.
- Oh, ho, a perfect
cover Larry if that
is your real name.
[CHATTER]
- Who are you? I
don't know you.
- Oh, we're biology partners.
I've gone to school with you
since the 1st grade.
- I didn't ask for
your life story.
Thanks for coming.
Have fun.
- One minute till 7.
- Hmph, and who
isn't here?
[IN UNISON]
- Exactly.
- Hi. Here I am.
- Hmph. So I see, but
I'm still watching you.
- Go downstairs
and watch her.
Go.
[DOOR SHUTS]
Faster.
[MUSIC]
- Coming to you only on
Slam FM, Seattle's hottest
DJ, it's Radio Rebel.
- This is Radio Rebel coming
at you live from Slam FM.
Tonight is all about
you. Lines are open,
you know the number.
- I'm calling into the show.
- Don't be shy.
We want to hear--
- How are you
here and there?--
- You're on with
Radio Rebel.
- Do you know
you're a hypocrite?
- Hi! What's your
name caller?
- Save it. You say you're
all about the people, but
Morp is all about you.
Now you get to lobby for
more Queen votes on the
radio every night, not fair.
The other Morp queen
nominees should get equal
air time, meaning me.
- Uh play,
play track 15.
- I totally
hear you.
- You hear me. I
don't think you do.
- Track 22.
[COMPUTER BEEPING SOUNDS]
- Say what you
want to say.
- I think you're using
subliminal brainwashing to
get people to vote for you,
so I'm gonna take this
opportunity to ask the
school to vote for me,
Stacy for Morp Queen.
- Okay, k,
play 40 next.
- Hi, what's your
name caller?
- You already
asked me that.
- I said play 40.
- You said 14.
- Play 33.
- Thanks for calling.
- I'm not done with you. Sorry,
but we can't all be winners...
and I'm gonna win, despite the
fact that I don't have an entire
radio station campaigning for
me, which really makes me the
underdog, and you know--
[DOOR SLAMMING]
- Pick up, pick up.
- It's Tara.
- Patch me into the show.
[CROWD TALKS]
- Why so quiet? Does
the truth hurt?
- You want to know the truth?
- Stop hogging the bathroom?
- What was that?
- Uh...I knocked over my
chair, because I wanted to
get close to the mic so
you could hear me clearly.
- Oh, I can hear
you clearly.
I can hear you very clearly.
I can hear you so clearly
Radio Rebel that we could be
in the same building.
- Same building? What
are you crazy? What are
you here at Slam Stacy?
I don't see you, or maybe
you're hiding somewhere.
[DOOR OPENS AND SLAMS]
I'm just a little bit worried
about you Stacy.
I'm afraid that if I beat you
out for Morp Queen your fragile
ego won't be able to survive.
[LAUGHTER]
- Can you hand
me my jacket?
- What was that?
- I'm sorry, what?
- Who was that?
- That was my sound guy. We
just got brand new demo in
today called "My Jacket."
We could play it for you.
- I have a better idea. Why
don't you come forward and
stop hiding like a coward?
- Would a coward be afraid to go
up against you for Morp Queen?
Cus I'm not. I'll see you
there, and you'll see that
I'm not afraid of anything.
Thanks for
calling.
- What are you doing
in my bedroom?
- I was trying to
find the bathroom.
Your house is so--
- What are you really
doing in here?
- Looking at
your photos.
I remember you used to
dress like that every
day in 2nd grade.
I also remember being
really jealous.
- Of what? Everyone
making fun of me?
- No, how confident you
were being yourself.
I didn't know people
made fun of you.
Doesn't feel so go does it?
- I don't need a lesson
in manners from you.
Now get out
of my room!
[MUSIC]
[CHEERS]
- That was amazing.
She was freeaked out.
[LAUGHS]
And Gavin just
smiled at you.
- Oh, I think it was more
of a general smile.
- It seemed pretty
specific to me.
- Hey!
- Can not wait for this.
- We're the G's and
this is "We So Fine."
[MUSIC]
- I can't believe
there's so many
non-pops in my
backyard.
- It feels like they're
multiplying, like
cockroaches, hangers.
[MUSIC AND CHEERS]
- Ahh! Oh!!
Are you kidding me?
- I didn't do anything.
You bumped into me.
- Come to my house and you spill
your drink on me.
This cost a fortune!
- It was an accident Stacy.
Audrey would never do
something like that on
purpose, unlike some people.
- You know what
your problem is?
- You know what? I don't care
what you think my problem is,
keep it to yourself.
- Huh. I need a new
outfit. Kim, let's go.
- I'm going.
- Ugh.
- Thanks for that. Uh.
I love how Radio Rebel's
rubbing on you too.
[LAUGHTER]
[MUSIC]
- She's playing us.
I know it.
Now you just need
to prove it.
- Okay, okay, you can do
it. Just go over there.
- Hey.
- You guys put on
a great show.
- Thanks.
But it's all Gabe. He's
a good front man.
- It's not all
Gabe, trust me.
- You know ever since the
band took off, people assume
I'm this confident guy,
but I get nervous before
gigs, like really nervous.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
We're not so different, I guess,
is what I'm trying to say.
- So, how do you do it?
- I try to remember I'm not
as alone as I feel. Radio
Rebel taught me that.
- Oh. She's a clever one.
- Yeah. She is.
- Slacker. Come
help load the van.
- You should.
See ya.
- Bye.
- Pizza delivery incoming.
This pizza's for Cami Q.
Where is Studio 4?
Anybody here? Cami Q?
[DOOR LATCH OPENS]
- I'm sorry, I kind of lost
my cool in there a bit.
- Hey, don't worry, I
mean you'll get it.
Hey I'm gonna make
you a DJ in no time.
DJ Momma Rebel.
[LAUGHS]
Yeah.
- Oh, I like the sound of that.
[LAUGHS]
- I was afraid we
biffed the call.
- Uh, we nearly did
a couple of times.
- You gotta hand it to her.
I mean Tara was right,
you really can be at
two places at once.
- I'm just so glad she
asked me to help.
I sometimes think that maybe
she's a little embarrassed
by her crazy mom.
- Are you kidding? She adores
you. I mean she talks about
you all the time.
- She does?
Oh. Mascara overflow.
Excuse me.
-Oh!
[MUSIC]
- Oh! Ah!
[FALLING SOUNDS]
- Hi! Did you order the super
duper cheesy pleasy breadteroni
bread and terrabeefaroma hold
the drama.
Great choice. Mmm. I can't get
enough of this sauce, not
you? Okay sorry. Bye!
Stacy! Stacy! I
got it! I got it!
[FALLING SOUNDS]
- I think we're ready. Please
remember your goals. Get your
actor energy up.
[BREATHING SOUNDS]
- Tara, thank goodness I found
you. There have been some last
minute changes to the scene.
Don't worry you can handle it.
- But does Gavin know?
- Gavin is the least
of your worries.
- Wait, this is the
Janitor's closet.
- Yes.
[DOOR LOCKED]
- What? Stacy!
Stacy, let me out!
- Enjoy your F--
- Romeo, where are you?
I mean seriously it's
freezing out here.
Why can't you just stop
being a Montagoo, the
Crapulets are way cooler,
everybody says. My father
isn't really a bad guy. He
just watches too many movies.
[DOOR BANGS]
- Let me out!
- Romeo, this whole beauty
thing is really annoying.
- Dude, ready to
rock out with the
drama dorks?
- That's funny.
Have you guys seen
Tara? She's late.
- Move on already. Pay
attention to Stacy.
- You're turning into
a real jerk. You know
that, don't you.
- Me? You're the one
who needs to get his
priorities straight.
- Or what? You're gonna
kick me out of the band?
- Is that what
you want?
- What I want is for you
to drop this stupid rock
star act for 5 minutes
and just try, try to
be a normal person.
- Okay, I am the front man of
this band. This rock star act
is what put us on the map.
If you don't want to be
part of that, then
that's fine with us.
- What happened to
G's for life?
- Hmm. Yeah. Ask
yourself that.
Enjoy your solo
career, Gavin.
- Thank you very much.
Next up is Audrey Sharma.
[CHATTER]
- Breathe your
words. Okay, go.
[CLEARS THROAT]
- Okay.
- Alas, poor spork,
I used to marry.
It was a wondrous and
versatile utensil, a
fork and a spoon.
- Come on, come on, pick up
the phone, pick up the
phone, pick up the phone.
- Ohh! Spork!
- Stacy!
- Ah?
- Have you seen Tara?
- No!
- Seriously? Oh.
- I have no idea
where she is.
I can't believe she'd do
this to us, so un-pro.
- We have to tell
Mrs. Brower we
can't do our scene.
- No, no, no, no. Stacy
DeBane is not a quitter.
I'm not gonna fail this
assignment just because
Tara's a no-show.
- Ladies and gentlemen, I'd like
to make an announcement.
Stacy DeBane will be
performing in place
of Tara Adams
who apparently couldn't be
bothered to show up.
[BANGING ON DOOR]
- Someone let me out!
- Looks like it's
just you and I.
- Come on!
Thank you!
Oh!
[RUNNING AND BREATHING HEAVY]
- See look at my
pants. I'm a dude.
- What's she waiting for?
- I'm waiting for
you to make a move,
but since you aren't
going to, I'll make
a move myself.
[CLAPPING]
- Bravo, Bravo!
- Okay, everybody listen,
thank you very much for
all of your hard work.
We appreciate it
very much on this...
[TEACHER VOICE FADES]
- Oh no, look...
He is so disappointed
in you...
and who can
blame him?
Okay, Radio Dribble...
you were bad enough
when you didn't talk,
but trying to destroy me
on your stupid radio show.
Did you really think you'd
get away with that?
- Look, you're wrong.
I'm not her. If I--
- Save it! You're not her?
Then explain this.
- I was afraid we
biffed the call.
Tara was right, you really
can be at 2 places at once.
- That doesn't
prove anything.
- No? Then you won't mind
if I e-mail it to the whole
school and Moreno?
- What do you want?
- Morp Queen. You're
gonna make sure I win
or Radio Rebel is.
Tell everyone on your
show to vote for me,
and if you say
anything about this
little private moment,
I'll tell everyone
who you really are.
- Okay. I had a bad day. Kinda
shook me up, made me wonder...
Am I doing the right thing?
I mean is, is it worth it
if I get expelled?
or if it messes things up with
the guy I like?
I don't know, but I do know
that there will be people
out there who try and take
things away from us,
things bigger than prom,
and we can just sit back
and watch it happen...
or we can stand
up for ourselves.
I mean we all deserve to dance
to our own playlists no matter
what Moreno or anyone else has
to say about it.
Oh, one more thing, uhm, I know
a lot of you guys want to vote
me Queen to find out who I am.
I don't need that crown,
but Stacy DeBane? She
kind of, really does...
Just keep that in
mind when you vote.
[BELL RINGS]
- Stacy!
- There you are. I've been dying
to show you this bowtie I found
for you to wear to Morp--
- Stacy--
- It perfectly matches my dress,
how cute is that?--
- Stacy.
- Yeah?
- I know what you did to
Tara. Audrey told me.
- What are you
talking about?
- The closet. Don't
bother denying it.
I have a witness.
What did Tara
ever do to you?
- You don't know her
Gavin. She's not who you
think she is. She's--
- No, Stacy.
You're not who I
thought you were.
I can't go to Morp
with you, I'm sorry.
- But, we're gonna
be King and Queen.
- I don't want to be
King. I never did.
[MUSIC]
- Where's Tara?
- Uh, more to the
point, where's
Radio Rebel?
- Ah, my true love
shall be revealed.
How do I look?
- Uh a little
green. Uh, it could
be the lighting or
something worse.
We're standing in
a microbial hot
spot right now.
- Wow.
- Hey.
- You look amazing.
- Yeah
[LAUGHING]
- Oh, thank you.
Have you seen
Gavin? I, I really
should talk to him.
- Wait, what are you gonna say?
- I don't know.
- You mean haven't?--
- Not yet--
- You know you need to--
- No.
- Are we missing something?
- Conference now.
[MUSIC]
- Oh, I don't
know what to do.
I'm freaking out.
- Just breathe.
[BREATHING SOUNDS]
- Okay.
- You're beautiful.
You're a queen no
matter what happens.
[CROWD SOUNDS]
- Good evening Seattle,
you ready to find out who
your Morp Queen is?
[CROWD CHEERS]
It's time to see who
will wear the crown at
Lincoln Bay High. Yeah!
- Yeah!
[CLAPPING AND CHEERING]
- We have 2 nominations for
Morp King, but one dropped out.
- Yah.
- No way!
- What?
- So that leaves...
Gabe LaViolet.
[CROWD CHEERS]
[CLAPPING]
- I'd like to invite your
Morp Court Princesses to
join me on stage.
- Don't be nervous.
- That's like the
worst thing to say to
a nervous person Kim.
- I know, thanks,
you're welcome.
- Let's hear it for
Stacy DeBane!
[CROWD CHEERS AND CLAPS]
- And Radio Rebel!
[CROWD CHEERS]
- Radio Rebel are
you out there?
- Show your face!
- Rebel we love you!
- We want to see you!
- Well, I guess
we'll continue.
Your Morp
Queen is...
Radio Rebel!
[MUSIC]
[LOUD CHEERING]
[CROWD CHEERS AND CLAPS]
- We lost you Rebel.
- Where are you Rebel?
- Since she isn't here to
accept her crown, maybe it
should go to the person
with the 2nd most votes?
- Most of you don't know
me. I'm the girl who sits
in the back of the class,
who never raises her
hand, who's so afraid of
saying the wrong thing
she says nothing instead.
The old me would of frozen in
front of a crowd like this,
...but something happened.
Suddenly the real stuff we were
dealing with at school
became more important
than my fears.
Look, I wasn't sure I
was gonna do this tonight,
but I need to be
true to myself.
So, here goes.
I'm Radio Rebel.
- Huh Wh?
- [CROWD CHEERS AND CLAPS]
[AMP SOUNDS]
- Thank you for an
enlightening evening...
and now that I know
who Radio Rebel is--
- Tara--
[PRINCIPAL LAUGHS]
- She is definitely
getting expelled.
[CROWD GASPS]
Enjoy your Morp Tara, oh,
and don't bother coming
to school on Monday.
[PRINCIPAL LAUGHS]
- I'm Radio Rebel.
- No, I'm Radio Rebel.
- No! I'm Radio Rebel.
Woo. I'm Radio Rebel.
[CROWD IN UNISON]
No, I'm Radio Rebel.
- You can't expel
everyone can you?
[CROWD CHANTS]
I'm Radio Rebel,
I'm Radio Rebel, I'm
Radio Rebel, I'm Radio
Rebel. I'm Radio Rebel,
I'm Radio Rebel, I'm Radio
Rebel, I'm Radio Rebel, I'm
Radio Rebel, I'm Radio Rebel.
- I believe this
belongs to you.
- I mean, I guess since
we're all Radio Rebel, this
crown belongs to all of us,
so congratulations
Kings and Queens.
[CROWD CHEERS]
But there is one person who
has been dreaming about this
crown for her entire life.
Although, I'm not quite
sure if I heard her say
she was Radio Rebel.
- I'm Radio Rebel.
I'm so Radio Rebel.
- Well then.
[MUSIC]
[CLAPPING]
- Why are you being so nice to
me when I've always been
nothing but mean to you?
- Cus look at you
right now Stacy...
that dress, the crown,
...you're 100% you right now.
That's all Radio Rebel
could ask of anyone.
You are yourself and you've
never been more beautiful.
[CROWD CHEERS AND CLAPS]
- Everyone, please give it
up for Lincoln Bay's very
own Gavin Morgan.
[CROWD CHEERS AND CLAPS]
- There's a girl I've liked
for a while now.
She's the kind of girl who's
not afraid to ask a dancing
sandwich for some help.
[LAUGHS]
She inspired this song.
This song's for her.
[GAVIN SINGS]
[CROWD CHEERS AND CLAPS]
[MUSIC]
- Ohhh.
- Hi.
- Hey.
I don't know what's more
amazing, that song or the fact
that you're turkey on rye.
[LAUGHTER]
Why didn't you tell anyone
I was Radio Rebel?
- You wanted to keep it a
secret. I respected that.
- Thank you.
You know you really know how
to dance for a sandwich.
- Oh.
[LAUGHS]
Will you go to
Morp with me?
- Yes.
[SIGHS]
- So, should I call you
Tara or Radio Rebel?
- You can call me either,
they're both me.
[MUSIC]
♪ [ENDING CREDIT MUSIC] ♪