(birds chirping)
(thunderous footsteps)
(roaring)
(dramatic music)
(speaking in a foreign language)
[Voiceover] Truth
is if it's (mumbles).
(speaking in a foreign language)
(mumbling television)
(ominous music)
Mr Beezly.
Are you there?
(cat meowing)
There you are.
I give you tasty food.
(dramatic music)
(cat screeching)
Mr Beezly.
Arnie.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
You okay mommy?
(cat screeching)
I'm okay,
it's the cat.
Mr Beezly.
(cat screeching)
It's very strange.
He maybe (mumbles).
Oh Mr Beezly.
Mr Beezly.
Oh he's not breathing.
Oh Mr Beezly, oh.
Oh Mr Beezly.
Oh my god.
[Arnie] Mommy, mommy.
Mommy, mommy.
(woman crying hysterically)
Mommy.
(upbeat music)
(man growling)
But Bill,
I'm hardly putting
anything in it.
And don't you cut them
into chunks that large
or Mr Grizzly will get,
will get angry.
(upbeat cheerful music)
Now you're angry?
(man grunting)
You know what?
Leave me alone.
[Voiceover] Leave me alone.
You're crazy (mumbles).
This is not my problem.
(mumbles)
You are filthy cheaters.
But let us see,
how do you know it is our fault?
It could be a case of distemper.
Or rabies.
Rabies.
No Mr Grizzly,
my mother only by this produce.
Me (mumbles) cat not
a (mumbles) once.
So do not tell me that
it's a case of rabies.
Because not even the best
vet would believe it.
What do you want me to do?
It must be indigestion?
Indigestion?
Huh look.
Look.
(dramatic music)
[Mr Grizzly] Oh my god.
See how Mr Beezly ended up.
Due (mumbles) cat food.
On top of that my mother,
(sniffling)
my mother is in hospital,
because of heart attack.
And if she happen to die,
I will hunt you down.
What's the matter Mr Grizzly?
Nothing, nothing boys.
This madman keeps saying
that our famous cat food
is in poor condition.
Go away boy and leave me alone.
Don't play with me.
Or I'll shove the
cat down your throat.
Keep it easy boy,
it must be a solution.
A solution,
of course there is a solution.
(cats meowing)
En,
Ven,
at.
Well guys this has to happen.
Sooner or later.
But Mr Grizzly,
what is going to be come of us?
I don't know guys,
but two handsome
young boys like you,
you'll find a job right away.
These times are hard,
be strong boys.
Guys you can still live in here
until I sell the factory.
You can keep rats away.
See you.
(dramatic music)
(bell chiming)
(crying)
(mumbles),
just yesterday we were
together (mumbles).
(crying)
And just like that brothers
concludes our goodbye
to Jose Swartz
known as Lokito.
(organ music)
(bell chiming)
Psst, psst hey.
Ted, my favorite butcher,
they told me that you get fired.
Ho, don't remind me about it.
[Undertaker] Okay no problem,
I guess you've come
for your stuff.
Yeah you have anything?
Of course man.
The old Undertaker
always saves something
for his friends.
The usual right?
Do you need to ask?
Great harvest as I always say,
there's nothing
as cemetery soil.
It's the best fertilizer.
Thanks Taker.
Hey don't smoke
it all in one go.
I won't have anymore
until next month.
(whistling off key)
(birds chirping)
(upbeat music)
Hi Bill.
(Bill grunts)
(upbeat music)
I'm going to make some tea.
(groaning)
(birds chirping)
(hooter sounding)
(brakes beeping)
(upbeat music)
Hope it can help me
with the headache.
(upbeat music)
(bang)
[Mr Grizzly] (mumbles)
where are you boys?
(upbeat music)
You'll see they're
silly but they
good boys.
Mr Grizzly,
what are you doing here?
Uh, Bill, Ted.
What am I doing here?
My beloved ignorant fools.
Today I'm start
up a new business.
Oh did the judge
lift them by-law?
No you bone heads.
I sold the company.
Did you sell the company?
And where we will live now?
Do not worry you will be the
nutcases working in the factory.
I don't understand,
Mr Grizzly who did you
sell the factory to?
Mr Morris.
Let me introduce you
to the new owner.
An American entrepreneur
who saved me from bankruptcy
by buying the factory.
Which from now on will be
called Lotus Cat Food factory.
A cat food factory boss?
That's it Bandit,
because of our
experience Mr Morris
wants us to start a new era
in cat food manufacturing.
Mr Morris.
I belong to a big family
that's been manufacturing
the best cat food in America
for seven decades.
A big company,
Lotus Cat Food.
We wanna expand
and offer the Spanish
people the best cat food
on the market.
So after meeting Mr Grizzly in,
after meeting Mr Grizzly
he offered me a chance
to open up a factory.
A (mumbles).
Promise me high quality life,
good and cheap employees
and woman.
Woman?
So starting tomorrow
by using the best machinery,
made in America of course,
we will start to supply
house holds with a
new range of cat food.
Lotus Cat Food.
Welcome to the big family.
That's it,
well boys you already knew
what you have to do,
Mr Morris.
But Mr Grizzly,
what do we do with Dorothy now?
Get rid of it,
now you've got Toto.
And as I was saying
to you Mr Morris,
I will show you where you
can eat the best paella.
[Mr Morris] I
don't want paella,
I want woman.
(ominous music)
Toto?
(grunting)
(groaning)
I think we have to fine
tune it a little bit.
(laughing)
[Voiceover] Extra, extra.
News of the week.
A new food.
Extra, Extra.
Lotus Cat Food (mumbles).
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
Don't taste the sweets
that they give to us.
The Lord wanted the
Grizzly (mumbles).
What do you think about
your company Mr Morris?
What the fuck.
(banging)
Do you think we are done?
(groaning)
Then let's go try it.
(upbeat music)
You two.
Mrs Livingston.
Is there anything
wrong Mrs Livingston?
You've been hammering
whole night long.
Yes,
we've been working.
[Mrs Livingston] I had
to get up eight times.
Six to go to the bathroom
and three because you
won't let me sleep.
(upbeat music)
Friends and neighbours
of Villa Catalina
it's an honor to share
these words of joy
with all of you.
Along with affection
and warm (mumbles)
to receive this
great business man.
He will make our cats
lick of pleasure.
And of course also our pockets.
[Mrs Livingston] I'm
going to destroy you.
Look, look what I'm
doing with your machine.
Mrs Livingston,
don't do it,
or you will break it.
And Mr Grizzly will get angry.
[Mrs Livingston]
Stop my (mumbles).
Mrs Livingston.
[Mrs Livingston] Oh help me.
Turn it off.
And with no more delays
let me introduce to you
the architect of all this,
just arrived from America
Mr Morris.
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
The main objective
of Lotus Cat Food,
which comes from my
homeland is to offer all you
Spanish people a
stunning hew range
of flavor.
And taste of excellence.
Forever more it
is for me an honor
to announce that Lotus
Cat Food has been chosen
(mumbles) sponsor for
the annual cat fair.
Which is going to take
place in your town
within a week.
What have you done?
Mr Grizzly we've
had a little accident.
You told me that something
happened with Mrs Livingston,
where is she?
There.
And over there.
But what have you
done you animals?
We didn't do
anything Mr Grizzly.
She's (mumbles)
and, and, and, and, and, and
the machine switch on
and I can't understand it.
Let's see,
calm down.
That was an accident.
And the important
thing now is to get
rid of the pieces.
Shall we fully grind them?
No, (mumbles) of beast.
(cat meowing)
Mr Grizzly let go of it.
What are you saying?
Oh it's not you Mr Grizzly.
It's the cat,
named him after you.
I hope you don't mind,
as you are so nice to us.
Bunch of retarded.
He's eating Mrs Livingston.
Clean all this and
get rid of the pieces.
Damn,
I never saw you
eating so ferociously
my little Grizzly.
Do you like Mrs Livingston?
Hey, do you like Mrs Livingston?
Boys I think I have the
solution to our problem.
Tonight Lotus Cat Food
will begin his revolution.
(laughter)
(dog barking)
(ominous footsteps)
Hey howdy.
Do you have a black
cat calf here?
Spaniards.
(ominous music)
(crickets chirping)
I still can't
believe Mr Grizzly
asked us to do this.
You just had it Bill.
(growling)
There is the only way
to get out of poverty.
And whenever Mr
Grizzly say something,
he's right.
I know Bill but
do you think what
we are going to do
is right?
Now.
(meowing)
(screaming)
(bell chiming)
(ominous music)
Don't worry Mr priest,
every problem has its solution.
You want us to fix the
roof of the church,
we'll fix it and all is okay.
Money fixes everything.
(mumbles) says
judgement day is near
and sinner and
corrupted one shall burn
in the cells of hell.
Oh whatever you say.
Goodbye.
(ominous music)
Mr Grizzly we are here.
[Mr Grizzly] Shh,
keep your voice down.
You idiots.
Keep your voice down.
What do we do with her?
Lay her on the
machine and tie her up.
Come on, come on.
Tie her up.
Tie her,
tie her.
What have you done,
you mad men.
It's Sophia.
The preachers niece.
Sophia.
It was very dark Mr Grizzly.
We couldn't see who she was.
I can't put up with you.
Okay Grizzly calm down,
take it easy.
But Mr Grizzly do
you think what we are
doing is right?
(groaning)
We'll go to hell.
Listen to me,
I am the one
who say what is wrong
and what is right.
And this is perfectly right.
So let's go to work.
There are plenty
of cats to feed.
(groaning)
Come on lemon heads
put the machine on.
Quickly because she's awakening.
(ominous music)
(screaming)
Shut up you stupid girl.
Shut her mouth I can't stand it.
Shut up, shut up.
Look, look, look how the
machine is swallow her.
Grind the girl.
Okay grind Toto finish her.
Yeah grind, grind.
That's it, that's it.
Lotus Cat Food will
be rich and famous.
[Voiceover] Grinding complete.
(ominous music)
Stop, stop.
(mumbling)
(radio playing)
Mommy I'm home.
How are you mom?
[Voiceover] I'm all right son.
I'm all right.
Love you.
(radio playing)
Oops.
Mr Beezly the 2nd.
Mr Beezly.
Look what I have for you.
How hungry are you
Mr Beezly the 2nd.
Good girl.
(mumbles) walks in circles
before eating,
and now he's gone
straight to his plate.
(ominous music)
Mr Grizzly.
Can we come in?
Come in, come in.
What can I do for you boys?
Mr Grizzly
we need a rest.
What no rest.
More than ever we
must go on producing.
People want more food
and I want more money.
So we can't disappoint
anyone, right?
(grunting)
But Mr Grizzly
Bills hands hurt
and my headache is
becoming stronger.
What can I do?
We can't stop now
to keep producing.
But, but...
No buts.
Back to work.
[Voiceover] Machine on.
(laughing)
(upbeat music)
(screaming)
(thunder crashing)
I must congratulate you
on obtaining the best
results in the past 30 years.
Congratulate the
operation for me.
But as you know within
the next two days
we celebrate the
annual feline fair
which is a great
opportunity for us.
You see if the
judges and organizers
like our canned food we can
obtain a juicy fat contract.
Do you know what that means?
Money.
That's why we must
innovate the product
and make it something more.
New?
Hmm,
yes maybe.
Something more.
(mumbles)
Exactly.
We must ensure that all cats,
not only in Spain,
but all over the world
eat our product.
Let me handle this Mr Morris.
We will begin working on
a more addictive food.
The new Lotus Cat
Food golden line.
Golden.
I like it.
Perfect.
Buy now, here's the fee.
(phone ringing)
[Voiceover] Mr Morris,
the mayors secretary has called.
Tell him...
Good morning to everybody.
What can I do
for you this time?
Let's see.
I basically came to
congratulate you.
I've learned about
the great success
of the new Lotus Cat Food.
And I said I must
visit to Mr Morris
in person to deeply
congratulate him.
Yeah we're making it big.
That's right see,
we've approved a new
law at the city council
about canned food,
and of course...
How much this time?
Mr Morris you offend me.
But a 20% would be enough.
Oh outstanding.
I didn't expect less from you.
It's great to see how
money fixes everything.
Well I'm sorry I
can't stay longer
but I had to meet
with the holy priest.
His niece has disappeared.
Gentlemen see you.
Politics.
Hey boys.
(mumbling)
(cat meowing)
What do you want?
More food?
You already eat.
I will give you no more.
And don't be bad.
(screaming)
(cat screeching)
[Arnie] Are you okay mommy?
Mommy.
(crying)
(groaning)
(cellphone ringing)
It's my boss.
You better go.
Mr Gualtieri can I help you?
Can you help me?
Well can you help me.
You were supposed to
let me know the news.
And you were
supposed to inform me
of everything daily.
Okay Mr Gualtieri,
I've been a little bit busy.
These Spaniards are driving
me a little bit crazy.
And the mayor is
enacting new laws
to make more money.
Well if the mayor's
causing a problem
you already know what to do.
And by the way I'm still waiting
for you to send me the
samples of the new product.
Okay Mr Gualtieri.
Okay.
I'm going to be sending
you something very special
very soon.
These red necks
(mumbles) so bad,
but they a little bit dopey.
But they put interest.
Yeah we'll see.
Hey listen I set you to Spain
to save money on
the minimum costs.
You understand what I'm saying?
And now what,
and now you already
spent much more
than anticipated.
I gotta tell you the truth,
I'm not very happy.
Piece of shit.
Well sometimes it is necessary
to cover my (mumbles).
Shut the hell up.
Hey listen I want those samples
and I want 'em this week.
You understand?
And I want you to
start production soon.
Any more delays
and you're going to
spend the rest of
your short life
selling encyclopedias
ya piece of shit.
Encyclopedias.
(sighs)
(mechanics beeping)
(grunting)
How are you boys?
Tired Mr Grizzly.
We haven't slept in days.
My head hurts badly.
And Billy has
broken out in a rash
on his face.
(grunting)
Come on, come on.
It's not that bad.
Here you are boys,
you deserve it.
Wow Mr Grizzly
what a nice gesture.
[Mr Grizzly] You
like sweets, huh Bill.
We are very grateful.
You know that I want
the best for my boys
and even more if you are
doing an excellent job
tell me what else
can I do for you?
Now that you say it,
we'd like a uniform.
A uniform?
Yes like the ones
that mechanics wear.
All right you'll have them.
Oh Mr Grizzly
thank you so much.
But before that,
you've got to do
something for me.
Whatever you want Mr Grizzly.
As you already know
in a very short time
a juicy contract
will set on the line
on you to make a
new better product.
Don't they like
our current one?
Yes it's perfect.
But I need you to press
those moronic brains
you have and make me a new,
a new mix.
A more addictive for me.
What I need is that
the more the cats
eat our product
the more they want it.
Do you understand?
I think so Mr Grizzly.
These are my boys.
(cat meowing)
Let's see how you respond.
(cats meowing)
Hey.
(dramatic music)
(cat meowing)
That's enough.
I won't feed you more.
Arnie whose cat is that?
Why is Mr Beezly
the 2nd in a cage?
(cat screeching)
(screaming)
(whistling)
(bell chiming)
(ominous music)
[Ted] Hi Taker.
Hey Ted you want your stuff?
Let me see I think it's here.
I got it.
Here you are.
To be honest I don't know
exactly what you want to do.
Whether you want to
throw a big time party
or commit suicide.
This potion will make your
soul shoot out of your body.
What's in it?
Can't you guess?
(ominous music)
Do you think it will
be addictive enough?
You know what,
you're scaring me.
(ominous music)
(upbeat music)
(cat screeching)
What's his name?
Toby.
Oh.
It was a cat.
Don't worry,
if you see that he gets worse
don't hesitate about
calling a doctor.
Here you have his
telephone number.
Okay, thanks.
Mr Arnie Beezly.
It's me.
[Voiceover] Dr West we are
waiting for you in the OR.
Hello.
Can I come in Miss?
Oops.
Sorry.
For god sake what is this?
Is that a cat,
or did (mumbles).
Yeah (mumbles).
Well and what happened to him?
Indigestion.
Indigestion?
Yes.
Well, he climbed
through the window
and he had eaten so much
he could not keep his balance
and fell to the floor.
And (mumbles) caused this?
(mumbles)
Well what do you want from me?
[Arnie] An autopsy.
An autopsy?
Yeah.
On what part of the cat?
Hey Doctor, what I wanna know
is if he ate poison food.
(groaning)
(cat meowing)
(cat screeching)
[Voiceover] Ah shit.
What's wrong?
Your stupid cat scratched me.
Leave the cat alone
and come here.
(cat screeching)
(screaming)
(phone ringing)
Hello.
[Voiceover] Hello
this is Dr (mumbles).
Oh yeah tell me.
Well I didn't find
poisoned (mumbles).
Are you sure?
Completely.
What is weird I
found human cells
in cat blood.
(dramatic music)
Hey you what are you
doing with these flags?
Put it up.
Mr Morris.
Well, well.
What a mess hey Mr Morris.
Well Mr Mayor,
what do I deserve this
honorable visit for?
Nothing, nothing.
Just wanted to see
how things are going.
And don't forget if
you need anything
whatever it is,
I'll be here for you.
But what's new?
Talking about the that.
The city council, we've
approved a new law
that says...
How much?
Not much,
almost nothing.
50%.
Here you are.
Hey chikas.
[Voiceover] Hey Mr Morris.
Hey girls nice to see ya.
[Voiceover] It's okay?
Ah Lotus Cat Food.
Yeah for the cats
who love people.
Ah chikas, oh yeah.
(ominous music)
Listen to me carefully
and I'll hope
everything's ready.
Tomorrow is the great day
and we need tonight the
best of you to begin
to produce this special
meat we talk about.
But Mr Grizzly,
we're tired.
And you promised
us work uniforms
and we haven't get it yet.
Yes well you see
I've ordered them but
you won't have them
until next year.
(grunting)
Bill said we'll wait for
the uniforms to get here.
Your stupid uniforms
will never come,
(mumbles) that you wear.
So move you're asses
and go to work now.
We will not do anything
until the uniforms get here.
Are you idiots?
I said go to work you melons.
What are you doing?
Go away.
(arguing)
(ominous music)
[Voiceover] Grinding complete.
(cat meowing)
(knocking)
[Arnie] Hello?
Can I come in?
Hey who are you?
Well,
see,
I...
Are you from
the public health?
Yes, that's it.
Oh.
Come in, come in.
(upbeat music)
May I...
Yeah come in, come in.
You are in your home.
So.
Where do you made
famous Lotus Cat Food?
(grunting)
What did you say?
Nothing, nothing, nothing.
Only silly things.
Shh, shut up.
(ominous music)
What kind of raw
material do you use?
Raw material?
Raw material.
What kind meat do you use?
(grunting)
That's a secret.
Yeah, anyway we don't have
anymore here at the moment.
But we are just
waiting for more.
(laughing)
(ominous music)
was saying,
better if I (mumbles).
Yes that's better.
See you next time.
Bye-bye.
[Voiceover] What
is the location?
[Voiceover] The
deputies have backed off,
I need you to slow down.
Where you at?
Okay are you telling me that
the famous cat food company use
human flesh to
put in their cans?
That is something that
I was trying to tell you
for an hour.
Why do you say those things?
Dr (mumbles)
had human blood in his blood.
But this blood could be yours.
You telling me that
this cat scratched you.
Maybe, but there be more.
Inside the Lotus factory
and I see with my own eyes
a human head.
Trust me Lieutenant you must
investigate this factory
because something
terrible there.
That's enough.
I warn you again Lieutenant
investigate this factory.
(phone ringing)
Yeah who's this?
What?
Are you ready?
No I hate cats.
(ominous music)
Morning boss.
Morning.
Okay tell me the story.
Well it seems the lady
here was attacked by her cat
and a neighbour had
to come to rescue her
or she would have been killed.
Okay could you tell
me the real story now
and only the facts please.
Ah excuse me Mr Colombus,
but the lady's in shock
after what happened so,
anyway when I got here
she told me that the cat
was eating as usual
and suddenly got crazy
and attacked her.
Are you sure you
didn't hurt the animal
in anyway?
No.
Just in case what did
you give it for food?
Hey I am the one
asking questions here.
Just in case what do
you give him for food?
Uh Lotus Cat Food.
She said that ever
since she started
to feed the animal with that
it's not exactly
acting like himself.
It's behaving badly.
Badly?
What do you mean?
I told you lieutenant,
this factory smells like death.
(mumbles)
the damn thing or what?
(cat screeching)
Who hires these people?
(upbeat music)
(crickets chirping)
[Voiceover] What
are you trying to do?
What?
Who it is?
Come on,
do something useful and help me.
Wait.
Be very careful.
They can see you.
They're (mumbles) inside.
(mumbles)
They made cat food
with human flesh.
You watch too much movies huh.
Yeah, some.
But it's not what you think.
Well never mind,
I have to go catch my cat.
Wait.
Yes.
I...
Are you nervous because of me?
No.
I just sweat a lot.
I like sweating.
[Woman] Disgusting.
So are you going
to let me go in?
Yes.
No.
Wait,
listen to me.
Come back tomorrow.
All right when I
was a little girl
they always told me that
the fool of the town
is always right.
What?
It's okay.
What are you doing still there?
Come here now.
Come closer I don't bite.
Yes.
You've never been
alone with a girl huh.
No.
You notice?
Well don't,
don't worry for the cat.
We will find him in the morning.
Well I don't love him so much,
he's not mine really.
No.
He's from (mumbles).
(mumbles)
You'll meet him soon.
(upbeat music)
Lotus Cat Food is the
ideal food for your pets.
Buy new Lotus Cat Food
because (mumbles).
(upbeat music)
Don't give him that Bill.
I tell you because I
already gave him before
and he's going to
become too fat.
(grunting)
Ah gentlemen.
Oh, Mr Morris.
What a nice surprise.
As Mr Grizzly has told you
today's a great day.
We expect a lot from
the new golden line.
Great family Lotus Cat Food.
So congratulations.
And the best of luck.
By the way where's Mr Grizzly?
Mr Grizzly?
[Mr Morris] Yeah.
I don't know Mr Morris.
That's okay.
It is a great honor
for me to open this
annual cat fair.
Thanks to the cat association
of granny Rosemary
to the coordinators and
judges of the fair committee
and of course thanks
to the official sponsor
of Lotus Cat Food.
What a shame.
Today have the pleasure
to offer a sample
of his new line,
the golden line.
So let the contest start.
(audience applauding)
Gentlemen I'm
lieutenant Colombus.
Did anything
happen lieutenant?
We don't know anything
about Mr Grizzly.
Mr Grizzly?
I didn't say anything
about Mr Grizzly.
Oh didn't you?
No.
The fact is that there's
been several reports
against your factory
and some food (mumbles).
We can assure you lieutenant
that our products
are the first rate.
First rate.
What have you got in there?
[Voiceover]
Ladies and gentlemen
it's time to choose
the most beautiful cat
to be the winner.
At this moment the jury is...
(mumbles)
Get up off there.
(grunts)
(cat meowing)
Boys don't you think
it's a little bit
dirty to have cats
running around
like that?
Bunch of crazies.
(cat meowing)
What the hell is
wrong with your cat?
What the hell.
[Voiceover] Lotus Cat Food
with (mumbles)
we will become the
best brand of cat food
on the international market.
A brand made in Spain.
(screaming)
[Voiceover] Machine on.
God damn it you
better get out of here.
Don't move this is
getting interesting.
I warned you this is the end.
What is going on here?
(mumbles)
(cat screeching)
Oh my god Bill we
must get out of here.
I told you (mumbles).
What's going on?
Hello.
Oh Mr Gualtieri.
Don't say another word.
I'm doing the talking now,
do you understand?
I'm gonna put you
on speaker phone.
(mechanical beeping
drowns out speech)
And you,
you just go around playing
with these wet bags
like it's a game.
What is that noise?
Mr Morris,
oh let me go to Spain you say,
let me take care of
business you said.
Mr Gualtieri I'm not
gonna have (mumbles).
Yes that's right,
and I won't be upset over this
but you know something
it's bullshit.
It's bullshit.
Are you listening to me?
I know Mr Gualtieri.
Morris.
Morris where are you?
You listening to me?
(screaming)
(upbeat music)
(cat screeching)
(gunshots)
Move your asses
and come here now.
I said now.
(cat screeching)
Wait.
(mechanics beeping)
We better get out of here.
Hey.
(cat screeching)
Don't worry Bill,
our (mumbles) will
take us very far.
Wait, wait.
Brother.
(coughing)
(panting)
What,
what are you going to do now?
[Woman] As always
on the road again.
And you?
Me?
Oh as always call my mother.
And wait for our
word from (mumbles).
(bike engines rumbling)
Well Arnie I have to go.
Yeah, go on with your life.
(growling)
(police sirens)
[Voiceover]
(mumbles) how you copy?
[Voiceover] PS clear.
[Voiceover] 10-4 thank you.
To DEA on (mumbles)
how do you copy?
[Voiceover]
Cleared for take off.
(dramatic music)
[Voiceover] Loud and clear.
[Voiceover] Just testing
the radio on command channel.
(groaning)
(upbeat music)