And God said, "Let there be light!"
And there was light.
And with that first light,
was born the first shadow.
The shadow was not diluted by light.
The shadow remained pure.
120 proof!
Eclipse the light,
and bid the shadow... return!
Now please, Mr. Lambert.
Mr. Quinlan. There was some
mention of financial compensation?
Okay, I'm your man!
The hair, Mr Lambert.
The blood.
The likeness.
What's the matter, Mr. Lambert?
Surely you don't believe in any of this.
Hell no!
You understand, "Hell no" will
soon be a contradiction in terms.
Hell will no longer be denied.
Come out, Quinlan!
Jacob, Jacob, Jacob.
You're always so messy.
I'm here to take you back!
Vassey... Vassey...
Vassey!
You saw...
No. No, I saw nothing.
- Shadows.
- Shadows!
Dear Lord, I pray thee,
forgive them for their sins.
Receive them into
the Kingdom of Heaven.
One God, forever and ever.
Amen.
Father Vassey, were they there?
- Did you--
- Yes.
- Quinlan?
Then it's over.
I found this.
Victor Lambert.
Did you kill him too?
- No. Dead when I got there.
- Sacrificed?
You see, they have completed
the first ordeal of the invocation.
The second must take place during
the darkness of the coming eclipse.
Stop that please, he's dead.
What evil he did died with him.
Don't try to glorify it as
part of some higher design.
Archbishop Quinlan was
a political threat, that's all.
With access to the Dark Texts!
The Compendium Infernus!
Bull - shit. Bullshit.
I usually find denial
in a priest to be admirable.
You don't believe the threat is real?
There was a ticket in here
for the town of Grand River.
Lambert took a trip there and back.
You think Quinlan could have
started a cell we don't know about?
I don't know, but I'll find out.
Will you hear my
confession before I go?
Are you truly repentent?
Not exactly in the heat of the night.
Rain and just 62 degrees.
WAPR Grand River, 4:57 in the A.M.
What the...
Unit 2 to base.
Base.
Base!
Unit 2 to base.
- Base!
- What is it, Eager?
Base, I'm at the, uh...
It's 5 o'clock in the morning, Eager. We're
the only two people awake on the whole planet.
- Can't you call me Maggie?
- Base, I'm at the cemetery.
I have a, uh... uhm...
What's the matter? Forgot
the procedural code number?
I have a disturbance here.
I'm going to investigate.
I'll just log that as a 10-100.
"Officer taking a leak."
Unit 2 out.
Who's there?
...there was some mention
of financial compensation...
Identify yourself!
I'm not playing around here!
- ...I'm your man...
- Oh my God!
- What are you doing? Is it morning already?
- Sure is, sleepyhead.
Morning, aunt Jen!
Morning, tough guy! What are
you doing up there on the roof?
Building an observatory
for tomorrow's eclipse!
You sure he's not building that
observatory to spy on Ginger Kirk?
Hey Chris, Sam wan't to know if you're building
the observatory to spy on Ginger Kirk?
No, but he can come up and
use the telescope if he wants!
Okay! See you downstairs!
You really want Chris to
know that I spent the night?
Honey, he's 12 years old.
He watches Melrose Place.
I know, but I still think we should
be a bit more discrete, don't you?
We have the worst kept
secret in Grand River.
- That is not true.
- Okay.
Maybe they don't know everything.
Morning.
Morning Sam. How many pieces
of french toast do you want?
I... You know, I can't really...
I'd love to stay, but I have to go and...
- You know, that thing I'm doing later...
- Sam.
Did you remember your cuffs this time?
- Yeah, right here.
- Okay.
- See ya.
- Hi, Sam!
Morning, Mr. and Mrs. Butterman.
- Morning Sam!
- George. Caesar.
See ya, aunt Jen.
Hold up there, tough guy!
I want to talk to you about why
you're up so early this morning.
Oh, I wanted to get the observatory done.
- You didn't have any bad dreams last night?
- Only one.
That guy that came over to visit us...
can't remember his name.
- Vic?
- Mr. Lambert, yes.
He was in it. It was all dark, and there
was something else in there with him.
- What was it?
- The sun was blocked.
There was like a huge bird, only bigger.
It was black and it was coming
right for me. I couldn't move!
Don't worry, it's not like I'm
gonna need analysis or anything,
Tell you what. How about you come by after the clinic
closes and take your old aunt Jen out to dinner.
- Okay.
- Have fun today, I'll see you tonight.
- See you later.
Look at all this traffic.
- I think this Eclipse Festival is
really working out, Sam. - Sure is.
- Good morning, Sheriff.
- Good morning.
- Nestor. - Hey, Lizzie. Aren't
you looking fine today? Yes, sir!
Go blind, Nestor, you're gonna go blind.
What you don't understand Sam, is that
hammerheads like me need guys like you.
- I'm afraid to ask, Nestor.
- Guys like you are boring in the sack!
That's why so many wives and
girlfriends show up at roadhouses
all lipstick, liquor, looking for a good time!
I'm no longer listening to you. Good morning, Maggie.
Anyone run off with the town while we were sleeping?
Sleeping? Is that what
I mean by boring? Yes, sir!
The mayor called. Said someone stole his
tomato lamps. He thinks it was old man Covey.
How could he tell? The smell? Dead skunk!
Sam, Eager hasn't radioed in for a little while.
Said he was checking out a disturbance in the cemetery.
I called Jenny's, but you'd left.
Okay, I'll check on my way to Covey's.
Anything else?
Well, the flyers warning people how
to view tomorrows eclipse came in.
We need someone to distribute
them to the merchants.
Yes, sir!
- Good morning, Dr. Hatcher.
- Hi Kelly. So, what have we got going today?
- Just more of the same. Shots and trots.
- George is finally bringing in Caesar.
- A neutering? Really?
- Having boyfriend troubles again?
Can I help it if I
find solace in my work?
Larry?
Larry!
Mary Hatcher, sweet Christ!
Fuck!
Paul! Get your ass out of the road!
Creepy dude. Probably some perv.
- He's a priest, I saw his collar.
- What'd I tell you?
Sam, uh... Chris is here.
Keep him outside, will you?
I dont want him to see his mother's grave.
What about it, Doc? Is he burned?
There's no evidence of an accelerant.
You see these dried vesicles? They look
like swellings caused by insect stings.
The skin is... helio-reactive?
We have to keep the body
out of the light.
- Does that mean, no flash bulbs?
- No flash bulbs!
Harvey, get Nestor to get a
couple of tarps down here, all right?
Move it! Before that sun gets high
enough to shine down in the grave.
I remember bringing
Larry Eggers into the world.
Son of a bitch, Sam! I can't remember
the last murder in this town.
- Not in my lifetime.
- Yeah.
Bring the body to my office, Sam.
Mary's remains, too.
What the hell happened here, Doc?
Damned if I know.
In the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Spirit. Amen.
This is disgusting!
I want these curtains taken down and cleaned
properly. Now, about replacing the altar covering--
- Can I help you?
- My name is Father Jacob Vassey.
Oh yes! Your bishop called,
saying you'd be stopping by.
I'll be right down in
one moment Father, please.
- I'm Father Charlie Finler.
- You know this man, Father?
Vic Lambert. Yes, I had the
misfortune years ago.
Now what's he done?
He is dead.
Desecrated?
Yeah, looks like Larry Eggers
interrupted them. He's dead.
Oh my God!
Jenny, do you have any idea why
anybody would dig up your sister's grave?
No. Of course not.
Well, I heard that
Vic Lambert was back in town.
Yeah well, Vic's a creep but I
don't think he's a grave robber.
Victor Lambert was
a boozer and a bully.
Always looking for the
easy way, the quick buck.
Ah! I assume these are
what you're here for?
I don't know what
I'm here for, Father.
Well. These are copies of the letters old
Father Nearing wrote to Lambert about the baptism.
What baptism?
- Lambert's son, of course. His baptism.
- He had a son in this town?
Has. Christopher Hatcher, he lives
with his aunt on Broadway Road.
I don't see why you're taking such an interest in this now.
The boy hasn't been in church since his baptism!
He's probably a little hooligan,
just like his father.
Whatever happened, I bet old man
Covey had something to do with it.
Maybe now he's digging up
corpses to chow down on!
Covey, a cannibal? He's gotta have
freezers full with cold ones!
Let's go see.
- What?
- Go to Covey's?
Sound like something
the Sheriff should do, Chris.
Listen, the Sheriff's dating my aunt Jen,
that practically makes me the Deputy.
- Yeah, Deputy Dickless!
- Chickens! I'm going.
Thanks Harvey. Your light should do it.
After what I saw today, not sure I'll ever
wanna go back into my dark room.
Doc? Do you need me for anything else?
No, no... thanks again.
Okay, old son...
let's see what you're made of.
Hi! I need to speak
to the Sheriff, please.
- Sorry Father, but he is--
- It's very important. Is he in the office?
- Why do you wanna see the Sheriff?
- I need his help, trying to find a small boy.
Well, that's against the law here,
isn't it? Yes, sir!
Fuck off.
Where's the Sheriff right now?
He's on his way to Dr. Cole's place,
just down the road on Mechanic.
Thank you.
This is the body of
Lawrence Donald Eggers.
23 year old, caucasian male.
70 inches long, 150 pounds.
The body is in a dessicated condition
and unusually sensitive to light.
I'm beginning with a thoracic incision.
What the hell!?
...identify yourself...
Doc!
Doc, it's Sam!
Doc?
What the fuck is going on?
God help me, but I think I know.
Who the hell are you?
The long bones are gone.
My God! The rib...
Whose skeleton is this, Sheriff?
- Mary Hatcher.
- The boy's mother.
Over here, guys.
He's got the Mayor's tomato lamps!
And he's got the spots from Miss Eggers patio!
He's even got Ginger Kirk's christmas lights!
She'd never take them down.
- He must've ripped off every single light in town!
- What a psycho!
Maybe this is the freezer he
keeps all the dead bodies in.
What's he doing?
God damn it! You son of a bitch!
Vic's not dead, I mean he was just here.
Yes I know. He came to get
something from his son?
No, I drove him to the bus.
He didn't take anything.
Oh yes he did. Think about it.
What? What did he take?
He took a picture.
- A picture. What else?
- What do you mean, what else?
Did he take any hair, did he take any
spit, urine, fingernail clippings?
Father, that's enough.
That's enough, Vassey.
Listen to me! Was he alone with the boy
for any length of time, Miss Hatcher?
Miss Hatcher, the boy is in danger!
What? He's in danger!
Dr. Hatcher, are you leaving?
What about Caesar's operation?
We'll do it tomorrow. My boy is in danger! Those
should have been the first words out of your mouth!
They're out of my mouth now, Miss Hatcher!
Now please, Miss Hatcher!
- Can't see how this happened, just get out of my way.
- Miss Hatcher, please don't go!
Listen to me! I understand that you're angry,
but I need you to stop and listen to me!
- We're not a religious family.
- But the boy was baptized, wasn't he?
What happened at the baptism, Miss Hatcher?
Something happened. What was it?
What?
When the water touched him,
he... Chris bled.
- Blood?
- From the hands and feet.
Stigmata. The mark of our
Lord's passion, may the Lord have mercy.
I don't have time for this shit! I have to go
find Chris! Sam, I'll meet you at the station.
Sheriff, I gotta go take a closer look
at the baptismal records.
Wait! Wait a minute!
- I gotta check something out.
- I'll take you.
He saw us! He's gonna
put us in his freezer!
Paul! He didn't see us. No freezer.
- I wonder why Covey stole those lights?
- Getting ready for tomorrow's eclipse.
- Covery's probably afraid of the dark!
- My sister Kelly says,
if you look at the sun during an eclipse,
you go blind from the sun's radiation.
You do not! I look
at the sun all the time.
Yeah right, Jazz. If you can look at
the sun without going blind, then do it.
Okay fine, I will.
What's the deal with the stigmata thing?
I thought that was just superstitious bullshit.
The church believes that
some souls are born pure.
Free of original sin.
These people have the potential of
becoming great teachers, prophets,
even saints.
Now the marks of the Lord's passion,
when manifested in an infant,
at baptism in particular, they believe
it's a sign that one's been born.
Something's in the
storm drain again, Herb.
Oh my God!
What!?
Hello, son.
Stay back!
- Who are you?
- Oh, shame on you, Father.
After years of warning your congregation
to be on the lookout for my kind,
you don't even recognize me.
Depart from me, evil doers!
For I shall give
the commandment of my God!
I said get back!
The spark of his fire shall not shine!
The lights shall be dark in his tabernacle,
and his candle shall be put out with--
Eventually, the light
always fails you, priest.
Stigmata at baptism is a big deal,
it should have been reported.
In the name of the Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit.
Amen. It would have been a huge investigation.
Hang on, hold!
It was reported.
Quinlan, you son of a bitch!
Sam old son, didn't I tell you
the bodies were helio-reactive?
- Not too bright, destroying evidence like that.
- Doc?
Oh, Father Vassey.
Come to find out just how few hours
your little clique of blood-drinking
bread-eaters has left, Father?
That doesn't hurt as much as it used to.
Tell me, Jacob. In conquering Man's light,
does that mean I'm conquering Man?
You don't exist!
You can't exist!
Why not? By existing,
I confirm all that you believe in.
Don't I, Father?
No!
That stings. I'm getting stronger.
A couple more souls, say yours,
I'll be ready for the boy.
What the fuck was that!?
- Take me back to the station.
- God damn it, Vassey! What was it?
Take me back to the station, please.
You know what it is.
Call it whatever the hell you like.
Death, Darkness, Demon.
I don't give a shit.
Just understand that
it wants the Hatcher boy.
And it'll rip your little
town apart to get him.
Wait a sec guys. I told my aunt Jen that
I'd meet her at the clinic for dinner.
I'll see you guys tomorrow,
for the eclipse.
- Maggie, has Jenny come in yet?
- No.
- God damn! Where's Nestor?
- He's on the north side.
A whole row of sewer covers
blew up on West River.
What... What's going on?
You got a good strong flashlight at home,
Deputy? Extra batteries, candles?
- Yeah, sure.
- Come on, Jenny! Pick up, be home.
Father Morrison? Yeah. This is Vassey.
Get me the bishop, please.
Stay at home. Lock your doors,
turn on your lights, all your lights!
Keep them on all night,
even when you sleep. Okay?
Bishop Gallo? I need you to fax me the pages
of the Dark Texts with the invocation.
- Jenny, call me at the station.
- Sam!
Do it. And call the Ostermans, call the West--
any of the families on your street
- and have them to do the same thing.
- Why?
Because there's a killer still out there, and I
don't want any dark corner left for him to hide in.
- Okay?
- No, it's not okay!
You two are scared shitless, and what's
a priest doing with two 9mm cannons?
Maggie, I don't want anyone else hurt! When
Nestor gets back here, I'm sending him home too.
So please just do me this favor.
Go home. Come back tomorrow at sun up.
Okay. Call if you need me.
Caesar?
What happened here? Caesar?
Hey boy, it's okay.
It's okay boy, don't worry. It's okay.
It's okay.
Settle down, settle down.
Stay.
It's cold!
- Sheriff Logan.
- Sam, it's me.
- You found Chris?
- No, no, but I think I know where he is.
We're supposed to have dinner tonight at
the clinic, that's where he's gonna meet me.
- I'm way across town, you can get there faster, Sam.
- Okay, hold on a sec.
- Base to unit 2. Nestor, are you still out there?
- Come on, break it up!
Nestor, it's Sam damn it, do you read me?
Right now!
- Go ahead.
- You still out on West River road?
Just finishing up.
It's the damndest thing, Sam.
I've had to break up three
fights since I've been here.
Is everyone acting like they got a
blowtorch up their ass? Yes, sir!
It's the Demon.
- Nestor...
- Boys! Get outta here!
Swing by Jenny's clinic,
find Chris and bring him here.
I'm on my way, Sam. Unit 2 out.
Jenny, I got Nestor going to get Chris.
He's gonna bring him here.
Okay, I'll call and make
sure he's there. I love you.
Its presence has begun to
poison your town and its people.
It'll get worse.
Hey Jen!
Hey Jen? Hey Jen?
Hey Jen?
Chris? Oh God!
Chris!
Hatcher? Chris Hatcher?
Nestor, Nestor! Come on!
We gotta go! We gotta go!
- Oh God!
- Time for you to come, Christopher.
- Who the hell are you!?
- I'm part of you.
I'm the one in your dreams.
I'm the one you want to be with.
God is a butcher, boy.
- He divides to conquer.
- I don't understand.
You will. Our alignment is coming.
Sun and moon, darkness at noon.
Come with me. Let me prepare you.
Go Chris!
Get out! Run!
You've made it harder for him, Nestor.
Am I fucked? Yes, sir...
Hell would have come here to you
if you'd been more patient.
Nestor, it's Sam. Come in.
Nestor-- Where the fuck are you!?
Jenny!
- Drive!
- Chris!
Drive!
Just hang on! It's okay.
Please.
Okay Chris, I'm gonna stop
the car and you get in, okay?
Come on honey, get in the car!
Get in the car!
You okay?
Nestor is dead! One of those dogs things
got him, and there was a man with them!
It's okay, it's okay. Honey,
you're okay now, okay you're safe.
Get the fuck off me, you piece of shit!
He is not dead! We need light
to kill him, lots of light!
- Lights? Where?
- I know where!
Damn pirate company feeding me
that defective Canadian electricity!
No no, you don't.
These lights are mine!
Chris, wait!
Over here, ugly!
The lights, the lights!
Turn on the lights!
Fuck me, Old Nick!
Dog gone!
Hello. Jenny, where-- where are you?
You'll never believe me if I told you.
Sam, I got Chris.
Honey, Nestor is dead.
How?
Okay. We'll meet you and Chris there.
And Jenny, just stay put there, all right?
Because we're dealing with much more
than a cult, okay? Okay. See you soon.
She found the boy?
I have to see him.
There's nothing we can do
here, Sheriff. Come on.
Keep an eye out, Vassey.
Vassey!
Yeah.
I like it. Let's go.
I thought you were
supposed to be a priest.
Praise be the Lord, my strength, who teacheth
my hands to war, and my fingers to fight.
- The Book of Psalms.
- Yeah.
Sounds more like the
book of rationalizations.
The Bible, by any other name.
- Okay Chris, I want you to go inside--
- And turn on all the lights, way ahead of you.
Come on.
- Hey.
- Sam.
Hi there Sheriff! We're gonna light this
joint up like a cathouse in Vegas!
I see you recruited the town nut.
- Hey, what the hell happened!?
- It's nothing, you wouldn't believe even if I told you.
Sheriff.
- Harvey?
- Where's the boy?
In the house.
Wait, wait! Let's just get the stuff
out of the back of the truck, okay?
Chris!
Aunt Jen, what are those
people doing outside?
I don't know... but
we're gonna figure it out.
- Could we end up like that?
- Not as long as we stay near you.
How come you are so afraid of Chris?
I can... feel his truth, his light.
It's just a bit unsettling, that's all.
When I held him in my arms
for that first time, I...
felt that light, that thing
you're talking about,
and I knew that he
trusted me completely.
And I think I am the person I am today
because I didn't wanna fail that trust.
I just discovered the opposite.
How? There is nothing evil
or cruel about Chris.
No no! Not him. Me.
The boy makes you face the hidden
part of yourself. For you, strength.
And for you?
- Hey. Is that my coffee?
- Yeah.
Thanks. Listen, I gotta go back in the
kitchen with Jenny and Father Vassey.
You wanna help Mr. Covey
with the generator?
- Okay.
- Good.
Be careful, it's heavy.
It's okay, boy.
I don't bite.
I was with the Christian
relief effort in Somalia.
One sunday, a local warlord objected
to a sermon I was giving against greed.
So he had his men... machine gun
all the people as he left the church.
- Oh my God!
- No, no, God wasn't there.
Oh I... prayed to Him,
and I screamed to Him...
Nothing. I might as well have been
a caveman, howling at the moon.
I understood then and there that...
God couldn't exist.
The next day I woke up, got a gun,
tracked down the warlord and his men...
- and I killed them.
- Good old-fashioned Old Testament justice, huh?
An eye for an eye. Boy, the
traditionalists must have loved you.
They went one better, Sheriff.
They trained me.
You see, the Church needs protection too.
Just like any other political organization.
There really are Devils and Angels.
Yes. And sinners who
really will go to Hell.
Well, maybe we can delay your departure,
Father. Anything here that can help us?
Good evening, Mr. Butterman.
Have... have you come for me?
I killed my wife, you know!
Your soul's all used up.
Hardly worth the effort of taking.
I hit her in the head with the axe...
I don't know why! I love my wife!
Why... why did I kill her?
It was the sound.
The sound of the blade,
burying itself in her skull.
- Wouldn't you like to hear it again?
- Yeah!
Look.
Go ahead.
Again.
According to the Dark Text,
this is our Demon.
A Factor Obscurantis,
maker or builder of shadows.
- Shadowbuilder?
- That's right.
Anyway, they're conjured up
to collect souls.
- Souls give them strength to carry out a task.
- What task?
Oh, it all depends. Quinlan's sect believed
in the perfect beauty of the Void.
Better known as Hell.
They feel that God, in his
arrogance, polluted the Void
with this... us, Creation, all of Creation.
The Shadowbuilder said that God...
separated things so He could control them.
What else did he say, honey?
Well, he said that everything
was coming to align.
The sun and the moon,
and dark at noon.
- It's the eclipse.
- Yes.
It's a chance for the Demon to build
a door between his world and ours.
How?
Here.
Wait a minute!
That's me, isn't it?
No. That is not you, honey.
You said the Shadowbuilder
has to gather enough souls
so he's strong enough to perform
some task. How many souls?
- How old is the boy?
- I'm twelve,
and my name is Chris, not boy! Why?
Half of life is spent in day,
half of life is spent in the dark.
The Demon needs one soul for
each year the boy spent in God's light.
Well, that would be six. So we got...
Doc, Father Finler and Larry Eggers.
- Victor Lambert.
- And Nestor.
No, no.
From what you told me earlier, the Deputy was
killed by one of the Demon's manifestations.
- His soul would have passed way before--
- It was eaten?
Taken.
- All right, that's four. Two left.
- Wait a sec!
- I saw Kelly's car in the clinic
parking lot when I left. - Oh God!
And when he gets six, there will be no amount
of Man-made light that's gonna hurt him.
- The Demon will come for the kid, unless...
- Unless what?
Unless he's... useless to him.
Speak of the Devil.
Move, move! Jenny, start the generator.
Covey, check outside the house, make sure
there's no one out back there.
Chris, you stay with Vassey.
Go! Move, move!
- Vassey! Vassey, no!
- Drop the gun, Vassey! Now!
I kill the boy, all this ends!
No invocation! No more lost souls!
No more Demons to face?
Drop the fucking gun!
You decide, Sheriff!
Your town, this world or the boy?
Killing Chris won't bring
your soul back, Vassey.
The Shadowbuilder is stronger in the
dark, he's getting inside our heads!
Looks like it's gonna be
a long night, kiddies!
Jenny, get Chris upstairs!
Covey, you keep an eye on him.
I'll find out who's trying to get in.
- The whole block is out.
- ...some things are better done in dark...
- Eager?
- ...I've come to say goodbye, Maggie...
You're so cold.
Larry?
- He always felt shy around you.
- He?
He. Me. We.
Jesus asked him, "What is thy name?"
And he said, "Legion."
Larry, wait. I-- I can't.
Of course you can, Maggie.
Maggie, my sweet.
Larry, stop.
Call me... Eager.
Paul!
- We need light!
- I'll go get one!
No, Chris! Chris! Wait!
Chris! Chris!
Chris!
Hello, aunt Jennifer.
How primitive.
Harvey! Drop 'em. Drop 'em.
Drop it. Covey--
Jesus! Are you all right?
I'm all right, I'm all right!
Where's the boy?
Aunt Jen!
Christopher.
It's time, Christopher.
Stop!
I can't stop, Christopher.
In your dreams, you've always known that.
I'll jump, fuckface!
Then you'll have no sacrifice!
Get away from him!
Jacob? You're a positive God-send.
No!
I saw what you did in New York, priest.
I saw you murder those people.
Your soul is forfeit.
- Shall I take it now?
- No!
You want those last precious hours?
Yes! Please, please!
I thought as much.
Let him go!
Come with me Christopher,
and they get to live.
Stop it!
I need you to choose me.
- It's your destiny.
- No!
- Decide!
- I'll come.
- Christopher, how angelic you are.
No! No!
Chris.
Chris?
Where is he? Where is he?
Talk for me, Vassey!
Traded... he traded... himself for us.
Jenny!
- Jenny.
- Give me the keys, Sam!
No, look, I'll drive, okay? We just gotta
figure out which direction they're in.
- I know where he took the boy.
- Where?
It's where Old Nick hides out during the day.
You find the Devil where it's dark!
- Hey, Sam?
- Yeah?
- Thanks for coming. - It's my own damn fault,
I'm the one that wanted us to be discrete!
- What do you mean? - You can't get any more
discrete than sneaking around here, can you?
- Sam, look! It's Chris's shoe!
- Jenny! Wait, wait!
I think it's a trap.
Sam! Sam! Oh God!
Sam!
- Morning, Padre.
- Morning.
The boy?
Sam... the Sheriff and Miss Hatcher,
they went to bring the boy home.
- Where?
- The sewers.
- Uh-uh.
- What? What? Do you know something?
- What?
- Here! What's that look like there?
I'll be God damned! An altar.
No greater act of blasphemy than to
sacrifice the boy in the house of God.
...it sanctified...
...and day seventh the blessed God and...
...made had he which work his all from
day seventh the on rested he and...
...day sixth the morning
the and evening the and...
...good very was it, behold, and made
had he that every thing saw God and...
...heaven the of firmament
the in them set God and...
...the were morning the
and evening the and...
...good was it that saw God and
darkness the from light divide to and...
...night the over and day
the over rule to and...
...them he created female and male,
him he created God of image the in...
Die!
Chris!
Observe, little bitch!
...stars the made he, night the
rule to light lesser the and...
What is that gibberish
Old Nick is spouting?
The Book of Genesis, in reverse.
He's trying to undo Creation.
...appear land dry the let and,
place one unto together...
...gathered be heaven the under
waters the let, said God and...
...day second the were morning
the and evening the and...
...heaven firmament the called God and...
Get her out of here.
The Spirit of God moved
upon the face of the waters.
And God said, "Let there be light!""
And there was light!
And God saw... the light was good!
...day first the were morning
the and evening the and...
...night called he darkness the and...
And God divided the light
from the darkness!
- And God called the light day!
- ...day light the called God and...
- Have you come to beg for your salvation, priest?
- You have none to offer.
Beg me anyway. Beg me!
For the boy's life.
Wake up, Chris.
Look at him, Chris. Look at him!
He is terrified of you.
I know. I was.
He wanted me to believe
you wouldn't come.
People trusted me once,
and I watched them die.
Good practice.
No!
Father!
- Have faith in me, Chris!
- I do, Father!
...darkness and void and
form without was earth...
I'll see you in Hell.
No!
Father! Why have you forsaken me!?
They've abandoned you, Christopher!
I'll have your soul, boy!
- Not today!
- Yes!
Thanks for the loan.
You're welcome!
- I thought you were dead!
- That makes two of us.
The Shadowbuilder was right.
You were a God-send.