(FRENCH SONG PLAYING)
(SONG ENDS)
(DOG BARKING)
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
I smell fish.
You might wanna take
your heels off, my darling.
- Bonjour.
- MAN: Bonjour.
(BOTH SPEAKING FRENCH)
Bonjour.
(CHUCKLES)
- Merci.
What's that sound?
That's the sea.
ROLAND: I don't see a radio.
I'll try to pick
one up tomorrow.
VANESSA: Morning.
I was trying
not to wake you.
You were
sleeping peacefully.
I don't sleep peacefully.
You know that.
Are you off to
find inspiration?
I have
my inspiration.
Then why are we here?
Don't be nasty, darling.
If you want,
I can be back early for dinner.
I need more time.
You go write,
I'll be fine.
All right.
Have a nice day.
VANESSA: I won't.
I know. Love you.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SOFTLY) I know.
(SIGHS)
(LINE RINGING)
Fuck.
(BOTH SPEAKING FRENCH)
(FRENCH MUSIC PLAYING)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
(LAUGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
Ah.
(FRENCH MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey.
- Good day?
- ROLAND: Nope.
Well... I don't know.
I don't know.
Michel's a sweet man.
He's sweet.
Do we have food?
VANESSA: I walked down a ridiculous hill
and went grocery shopping.
Then I read a book.
It was terrible.
I don't know why
you worry so much.
People publish pure garbage all the
time, and nobody seems to mind.
ROLAND: I can write.
I'm a good writer,
remember?
You are.
I love your words,
you know that.
(MAN SPEAKING FRENCH ON RADIO)
(FRENCH MUSIC PLAYING)
(SEAGULLS CAWING)
(SOBS)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
ROLAND: You should
go for a walk or something today.
Might be
good for you.
Don't have a drink today.
Might be good for you.
We could be happy,
you know.
You resist happiness.
Don't quote some book
and try to analyze my life.
You don't resist happiness?
Are you trying to illustrate your point
by making me unhappy?
You're a good woman.
Jesus.
Have I become that dull?
(SIGHS)
Try and write
something today.
Good plan, Batman.
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(MAN SPEAKING FRENCH ON RADIO)
(BOTH WHISPERING IN FRENCH)
(FRENCH MUSIC PLAYING)
(WOMAN MOANING)
(MOANING INTENSIFIES)
(EXHALES)
(WATER RUNNING)
(SPITS)
(TURNS WATER OFF)
ROLAND: You had a tough night?
I don't know.
Ness?
Right.
Are we ever gonna
talk about it?
I suppose it's best
we don't say a word.
(FRENCH MUSIC PLAYING)
(GLASS CLATTERS)
Ah, shit.
Uh... Sorry.
I got it. I got it.
It's okay.
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
What the fuck?
(SCOFFS)
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
Come on.
(BOTH CONTINUE IN FRENCH)
ROLAND: Fucking shit.
Hey, I'm going.
I'm going.
- (SPEAKING FRENCH)
- All right?
This place is
shit anyways.
- (DOOR OPENS)
- (BELL JINGLES)
(ROLAND SPEAKING FRENCH)
(SLAMS DOOR)
(SIGHS)
(MAN SPEAKING FRENCH)
Vanessa.
Hmm.
- New York.
- American?
Hmm.
We talked about having
our honeymoon in New York.
Yeah, my wife and I, we...
We just got married.
That's nice.
Hmm.
Well, have
a nice day.
And you.
(WOMAN LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
(CHUCKLES)
(SCOFFS DISMISSIVELY)
Toast of New York.
(BOTH CONTINUE IN FRENCH)
Hmm.
Ooh-la-la.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(SCOFFS)
(CHUCKLES)
(INAUDIBLE)
(DOOR CLOSES)
You're back early.
I missed you.
Don't be silly.
Drink?
Sure.
Have you seen her?
Who?
The neighbor.
- The couple?
- Hmm.
Yeah.
What?
Nothing.
Anyway,
I was getting bored.
It's not the place.
The place hasn't let me down.
It's moi.
Michel is such
an interesting guy. He's...
He's too kind.
But he's heavy.
Any writer worth his salt
could get a story here.
It's just me.
I'm blowing you a kiss.
I'm blowing you one back.
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
(WOMAN LAUGHING)
(COUPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(CHILDREN SHOUTING PLAYFULLY)
(FRENCH MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(BOTH SPEAKING FRENCH)
(WATER RUNNING)
(SIGHS)
Wake up.
- Wake up!
- What?
- Do you wanna fuck her?
Huh?
The woman next door,
do you want to fuck her?
Honey, what are you doing?
Don't pretend you don't know
what I'm talking about.
I don't know what
the fuck you're talking about. Get off!
And now you just
woke me up.
Where are you going?
I gotta take a piss.
You mind?
(URINATING)
(TOILET FLUSHING)
Do you want to fuck her?
Jesus Christ, no.
Yes, you do.
Honey, why are
you doing this?
Why are you trying
to put that in my head?
Huh? So you can
be the victim?
Being the wife of a failed
writer is not good enough
for pill-popping
and self-pity?
Now you need a better reason
to destroy yourself?
You know my reason.
Plus, you would have to try and fail
to be a failed writer, and you're nothing.
You're a drunk.
(SCOFFS)
Fuck you.
When I return, I hope
you're passed out as usual,
so I don't have to listen
to your silly voice.
(WHIMPERS)
(CRYING)
(GOAT BLEATING)
Bonjour.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(GROANS) God damn it.
(VOMITING)
(COUGHING)
(GROANS)
(TOILET FLUSHING)
(SLURRING)
Come on.
No.
Stop it.
- Stop it.
- Come on.
- No.
(GROANING)
(LAUGHS)
Ugh!
(LAUGHS) Ow!
Stop it.
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
(GROANING PLAYFULLY)
You make me sick.
Disgusting.
I'm not gonna make it.
WOMAN: Good morning.
Morning.
Did you see your
fisherman this morning?
Yes.
François is going to
visit a friend tomorrow.
Do you wanna do anything?
With you?
Yeah.
Like what?
I don't know.
We can play cards,
go for a walk,
get a drink.
I don't know
how to play cards.
I can teach you.
Okay.
5:00?
- 8:00.
Have a nice day. Bye.
(WATER SPLASHING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- Hi.
- Come in.
- Thank you.
- Sit down.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Pretty dress.
Oh, thank you.
You should
put your hair up.
Oh...
It's funny,
my... My husband always say that.
He's right.
(CHUCKLES)
So, do you know
La Belote?
La Belote, the game is to get
the highest number of points.
So let's say
I move everything here.
How many?
- VANESSA: Um, is it?
- LEA: Yeah, yeah, you can do that.
- VANESSA: More wine?
- LEA: Four? Damn.
You won again.
(CHUCKLES) 11.
Okay. 10, king.
VANESSA: I'll take it.
Hi.
- Hi.
- VANESSA: Belote.
- Rebelote.
- LEA: Aw! Come on.
So unfair.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey. We haven't
properly met.
I see you at
the café often.
I'm Lea.
- Nice to meet you. I'm Roland.
- Hi.
Would you like a drink?
Sure.
LEA: So unfair.
Do you wanna join us?
Okay.
And don't tell me
you don't play cards, too.
Your wife told me that,
and then she's won every hand.
Well, she's a natural.
Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
Oh, we can't
play La Belote.
It's not working
if we are three.
We have to
change the game.
Let's play...
- La Bataille?
- Yes.
- Mmm.
- LEA: Easy.
What was
that about?
What do you mean?
Nessa...
Are you trying to
push her on me?
Am I wrong to think
you're trying to destroy us?
I'm gonna take a shower.
(SHOWER RUNNING)
- Jesus! What are you doing?
- Tonight, I'm having a shower
with my wife.
No. No.
- No.
- Enough.
It's gotta stop.
It's all right.
- It's all right.
- No, I can't... It's just...
- Vanessa, enough.
- Please.
- Stop! Stop!
- No.
Stop it! Stop!
- Enough!
- Please.
I'm your husband.
I can't.
At some point
you're gonna stop acting like this.
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
ROLAND: Merci.
ROLAND: Are we
ever gonna talk about it?
(VANESSA LAUGHING)
ROLAND: Nessa?
Do you hate me?
Stop!
Just stop!
You resist happiness.
Nessa?
Ness?
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(EXHALES)
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(DOOR OPENS)
You're smiling.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
Now my outsides
match my insides.
(MOANS SADLY)
Stay.
(DOOR CLOSES)
ROLAND: Good morning.
We were out of coffee.
Why you looking at me
like that?
Just looking.
(FRANÇOIS STRUMMING GUITAR)
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
(FRANÇOIS PLAYING ROCK MUSIC)
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(STOPS PLAYING)
(LEA LAUGHS)
(HEART BEATING)
(LEA MOANS)
(EXHALES)
Hello.
Did you go
on your trip?
Your wife said
you went on a trip.
It was okay.
But I prefer
to stay here.
I grew up in a place
like this,
so I'm happy here.
Mmm.
We might have a big
sailing day next week.
And we don't really have
any friends up here, so...
Would you and your husband
consider coming?
Sailing?
Yes, sailing.
Why not?
It can be fun.
And you can do
the same thing you're doing now,
only on the sea.
(CHUCKLES)
I'll talk to
my husband.
Sure.
Good night.
- VANESSA: Hi.
- Hi.
Thought I'd bring dinner
home tonight.
VANESSA: I'll get some plates.
Nessa?
Yeah?
We okay?
We are the same
as we've been for a long time.
No different.
Okay.
They asked if we
wanted to go sailing.
How wonderful.
And you said?
I said we hate boats
and we hate people.
No, you didn't.
I didn't, but we do.
So we're
not going, right?
Do you wanna go?
Why do I feel like
that's a trick question?
I just thought maybe an adventure
would be good for us.
Maybe, I don't know.
You realize how shocking that is
to hear you say that?
But, yes, I would love
something fun for us.
(POURING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(FRENCH MUSIC PLAYING)
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
(MAN CHATTERING
IN FRENCH ON TV)
(LEA AND FRANÇOIS
CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
(FRANÇOIS LAUGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
ROLAND: Were you
watching them?
What were they doing?
I ask because I was here
the other day
while you were
on a walk,
and I noticed the hole,
and I watched them
fucking.
Does that bother you?
Will you watch with me?
(LEA MOANING)
(LEA SPEAKING FRENCH)
(LEA LAUGHING)
(LEA GIGGLING)
Do you wanna
take a shower?
Yes.
(VANESSA CRYING)
(SHOWER RUNNING)
ROLAND: Good morning.
VANESSA: Morning.
We're out of milk.
Will you get some
when you go to work?
You watch them
in the morning?
Sometimes.
I think I might
stay home today.
Is that all right?
Do you wanna be alone?
No.
Are we perverse?
Would it bother you
if we were?
No.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(FRENCH MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, neighbor.
Morning.
It's our two-months
anniversary.
I was thinking of
berries and cream.
Maybe port?
I don't know.
I guess
it's the thought.
Yeah.
When's yours?
Winter.
Winter?
(CHUCKLES)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Were you with her?
She was at the store.
It's their anniversary.
Ah.
When's ours?
November. Uh...
End of November.
Yeah.
What day?
ROLAND: 27, 20...
Can't remember.
Me neither.
- Ness?
- Mmm?
It doesn't
mean anything.
It doesn't mean anything
that we can't remember.
Okay?
They had fresh pastries.
(VANESSA AND FRANÇOIS
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
What did he want?
VANESSA: Who?
François.
He wanted to know
if we still wanted to go sailing.
You're lying.
He asked me
for a cigarette.
I started smoking
when we got here,
and you were here,
so I said I was out.
I know you
started smoking.
Did you?
Yeah. I know you.
(LEA AND FRANÇOIS
CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
(LEA GASPS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(BOTH CONTINUE
CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
(FRANCOIS CHUCKLING)
(LEA GASPING)
(MOANING)
(BOTH MOANING)
VANESSA: Do you see that fisherman?
He goes out every day,
comes back every night.
Hardly catches any fish.
What keeps him
from going insane?
From being so tired
of it all?
What is it
we don't know?
Let's go to the café
for a drink.
Mmm... No.
How about we invite
our neighbors?
Get them liquored up,
and see what they do when they're plastered.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(ALL CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
What would you like?
- I heard pastis is good.
- Pastis. Pastis.
(CLINK)
- Hey!
- Hello.
ALL: Bonsoir.
Hello.
ROLAND: This is Vanessa's
first encounter with pastis.
- (ALL EXCLAIMING)
- Really?
- And?
- VANESSA: And I've had two.
- Yeah?
- Mmm-hmm.
What did you think?
I think you should
have two.
LEA: (CHUCKLES) Oh.
FRANÇOIS: I'm not so sure.
- ROLAND: Just takes a little practice.
- Yeah?
FRANÇOIS: I have
some memories.
(LAUGHING)
So, Roland,
Vanessa tells us you're a writer.
Uh, some days.
It's great.
- I wish I could write.
- ROLAND: Mmm.
Well, I do, too, lately.
- Hmm.
- WAITER: Voilà.
- LEA: Oh-la-la.
- (ALL LAUGHING)
What do you do, François?
Mmm, I just opened
an art gallery in Paris.
ROLAND: Mmm.
- It's your own gallery?
- FRANÇOIS: Yes.
I was a dealer first.
Art dealer, and then
I opened a gallery.
And hopefully,
I have the help of my nice little wife.
So we work together.
(FRANÇOIS AND LEA LAUGHING)
- Cheers.
- Okay, cheers, everyone.
LEA: Cheers.
Mmm.
- Mmm.
- That's strong.
What do you do,
Vanessa?
Me?
Absolutely nothing.
(BOTH GASP)
LEA: You're a wife, like me.
VANESSA: Mmm...
Technically, yes.
But I'm not very
good at that either.
That's not true.
She's a fantastic wife.
She's the best little
homemaker in the world.
Not funny?
I used to be a dancer.
- LEA: Oh.
- Mmm.
That's great.
Why did you stop?
Because I got old.
FRANÇOIS: But very beautiful.
(LEA CHUCKLES)
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
Yes, yes.
I know this thing
by heart.
VANESSA: New Yorkers
do not eat pigeon.
We eat escargot, too.
FRANÇOIS: I think
I want another drink.
- We are strange.
- VANESSA: You are strange.
All right.
Four more pastis.
(ALL TOASTING)
(GLASSES CLINKING)
ROLAND: Dear Lord, that was painful.
VANESSA: Let's hope it pays off.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(GROANS)
(FRANÇOIS SPEAKING FRENCH)
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
(POURING)
(STRUMS GUITAR)
Well, now we know.
They're miserable drunks.
(SIGHS)
(FRENCH MUSIC PLAYING)
Isn't this
just everything?
My first time.
Really? Well,
you're a natural.
(INDISTINCT)
Can you hold it for me?
(LEA LAUGHING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
You look beautiful
laying there.
Maybe I don't
say that enough.
It's difficult, because it makes me
wanna be with you.
And I know how hard it is
for you to be with me.
Only, don't begin to think
he sees you any differently than I do.
Of course he does.
He doesn't know me.
Is that what you want?
To be unknown by someone?
Maybe.
Do you want him?
Do you want her?
No.
But you like to watch her.
I like to watch
with you, honey.
Makes me wanna
be with you.
I think of you.
I don't think I like
this game anymore.
VANESSA: Roly?
What are they doing?
Nessa...
Please?
ROLAND: They're
laying on the bed.
She's reading a book.
He's watching her.
His hands move down her body.
To her thighs.
Between her legs.
He wants her...
But he's waiting.
Waiting for her to let him
know it's all right.
(GASPS)
He loves the way
she feels.
He wants her to know
how desirable she is.
(MOANING)
And to feel
how she desires him.
How desirable she is.
(BOTH MOANING)
See you later.
Okay.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
(MICHEL SPEAKING FRENCH)
Hey.
Mmm.
Feels strange not to talk.
No, it doesn't.
(CHUCKLES)
Are you working?
No.
- You're writing something?
- Just drinking.
I see.
They told me who you are.
I've read your books.
- Have you?
- Mmm-hmm.
I think I like
the first one best.
I guess everybody did.
Everyone did.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Yes. Everyone
has many opinions.
How do you like
being married?
Yeah, I love it.
Why?
What do you mean, "Why?"
(EXHALES)
I like belonging
to something.
To someone.
I like knowing what
my life is gonna be.
What? (CHUCKLES)
You think I'm naïve?
I think you're a woman.
I think you're lovely,
and I hope your life turns out
just as you imagine.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(FRANÇOIS AND VANESSA
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Wanna go for a drive?
I thought we agreed
we weren't going anywhere until you wrote.
The rate I'm going...
Let's go for a drive.
(FRENCH MUSIC PLAYING)
I'd like to stop
at a church.
Okay.
I prayed
(SNIFFLING)
that God might forgive
me for all the horrible things I said
when we knew.
(SIGHS)
And I prayed for
the strength to mean it.
Because I don't.
I'm angry.
I'm angry, too, baby.
VANESSA: Where are we?
I'm taking you
to dinner.
I'm not dressed
for dinner.
Just do this
for me.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(BOTH SPEAKING FRENCH)
I don't wanna be here.
It's all right,
honey.
Just look at me.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Merci.
(PLAYING SLOW MUSIC)
Dance with me.
(ECHOING) Honey? Ness?
Vanessa?
ROLAND: I think
I wanna write about you.
I'll change the name.
So what?
So what if they know?
Honey, I would
never write about that.
(LEA SPEAKING FRENCH)
VANESSA: I was thinking
maybe I'd get dressed and go for a walk.
I'll go with you.
I was gonna smoke.
I won't stop you.
I'll just go
on the balcony.
(FAINT MOANING)
Going somewhere?
VANESSA: I'm taking Lea shopping.
It's my good deed
for the month.
(CLICKING LIGHTER)
Why the sudden
change of heart?
I needed
a pair of shoes.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
You good?
LEA: Um... Yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
I look, um...
I look different.
You want to see?
VANESSA: Yes.
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
(LAUGHING)
- Hey, Roland.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good.
That's a nice jacket.
Oh, yeah, you like it?
My missus bought it for me.
I guess our girls had
a bit of a spend-up.
Yes.
- And Lea told me about your car.
- Oh, the car is great.
Yeah, that's a great car.
My uncle has the same, actually.
- It's nice. It's a nice car.
- Yeah.
All right.
Have a good evening.
LEA: Bye.
(ICE CUBES CLINKING)
(POURING)
You dressed him like me.
I had that jacket when we met.
Did they look nice?
- Did they look nice?
- You dressed him like me.
What are you doing, honey?
What are you doing?
- (MUTTERS)
- Nessa.
Help me understand.
What are you doing?
What is this?
Would you close the door?
What are you doing?
There's a draft.
What is this?
(VANESSA CRYING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
ROLAND: I think we
should stop watching them.
We don't need them anymore.
We have our life.
We have each other.
Let's let them have theirs.
Honey?
- Ness.
- (DOOR OPENING)
(VANESSA AND FRANÇOIS
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
You're home early.
Mmm-hmm.
Do you want a drink?
I didn't know
you liked cards so much.
That's nice.
Cards are fun.
It's a good game.
I like cards.
Do you want a drink?
No.
No, I don't want
a fucking drink.
I wanna know
what this is.
- Do you wanna hurt me? Hmm?
- No.
- Hurt me.
- No, I don't wanna hurt you.
Just do it. Hurt me.
Get it over with.
- Go ahead.
- No.
- I would never hurt you. Stop, please.
- It's all right.
- Do it.
- Stop it.
- Wanna hurt me? Get it over with.
- Stop!
Go on.
- I don't wanna hurt you.
- It's easy.
- Just do it.
- Stop!
- Come on!
- Please, stop.
- Do it.
- Stop!
Stop! I don't know
what's happening.
- You don't understand?
- Stop! Stop.
- Come on, do it.
- No! Let's just...
Can we get out of here?
Could we just go?
Let's just go.
Let's get out of
this room. Please?
(CRYING)
Please.
(SOFTLY) Okay.
I don't wanna...
I'll get my jacket.
(CONTINUES CRYING)
(GROANS)
(LAUGHTER)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(BOTH SPEAKING FRENCH)
(CHUCKLES)
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
FRANÇOIS: May I?
(DOOR OPENS)
FRANÇOIS: No. Wait!
(FRANÇOIS GROANING)
(GASPS)
Come on.
Why?
(BREATHING HEAVILY) Why?
Say it.
Why?
Look at me.
- No!
- Look at me!
- (WHIMPERS) No.
- Why?
Stop.
You know why. Be honest.
Say it.
Say it. Come on.
Look at me.
Why?
- Because you can't have what they have.
- No.
- (CRYING)
- Say it.
- No.
- Because you can't have what they have.
Because you're jealous.
- No!
- You're sick!
- You're sick.
(SOBBING)
You would ruin them to
make yourself feel better.
- You wanna hurt them.
- No!
- I wanted him!
- Yes.
No! No!
No.
You're jealous
because you're barren.
- No.
- You hate them.
You hate them.
Say it!
(YELLS)
You hate them.
(CRYING)
You're jealous.
You hate them
because you're barren.
And I've loved
you anyways.
You don't want him.
You want me.
You want children with me.
You don't want him.
You love me.
- Say it.
- I'm barren.
I'm barren.
(SOBBING)
(LEA SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
She's home.
(LEA AND FRANÇOIS
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
He's... He's trying
to say something.
Wait.
(LEA AND FRANÇOIS
ARGUING INDISTINCTLY)
He's telling
her the truth.
She won't let
him touch her.
(DOOR SLAMS)
Well done, darling.
It seems you've just
destroyed a happy marriage.
Could I speak with you
for a moment?
I don't wanna
speak to you.
It's not what
you think it is.
(SOBBING)
ROLAND: This is something
that started three years ago,
when we first tried
to have a child.
We lost that child
in the first term,
so we tried again.
We lost that baby, too.
They said they were going
to try and fight past it.
That going through something horrible
could even make them stronger.
She's pregnant.
I assume
you knew that.
I'm not a bad person.
Am I a bad person?
Sometimes.
(SNIFFLES)
We gotta stop
being such assholes.
(CHUCKLES)
(ROLAND TYPING)
ROLAND: I figured out your fisherman.
He goes with the tide.
You let it pull you out to
sea or guide you back in.
Sometimes you have
to move with it.
Sometimes, honey,
that's all we can do.
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
(FRENCH SONG PLAYING)