Subtitles by explosiveskull
♪ We shake like an earthquake ♪
♪ Down here in the city
Where the birds stay ♪
- ♪ Ha, step in And I'm reppin' the A ♪
- ♪ All right ♪
♪ Step in
And I'm reppin' the A ♪
♪ Yeah, we shake
Like an earthquake ♪
♪ Down here in the city
Where the birds stay ♪
♪ Ha, step in
And I'm reppin' the A ♪
♪ Step in
♪ They say New York don't sleep But
we don't do that here Either ♪
♪ I got a crush on a couple
Of Hawks cheerleaders ♪
♪ Fo-oh-fo
Yeah, that's the area I call ♪
Yeah, that's the area I hold ♪
♪ Down in the city here we own
It's my Georgia home ♪
♪ I love my Georgia Dome
Can't leave Georgia alone ♪
Skyler?
Skyler!
I didn't hear you.
Girl, I could bang pots and pans
outside your door
until my blood pressure
got the best of me,
and you still
wouldn't have answered.
Sorry. I was dancing.
Is that what that's called?
Looked more to me like you was possessed
by a chicken havin' a spaz attack.
- What's up, Ma?
- What's up is I'm headin' to work.
Oh! Don't forget to fill out that
application for the program.
Okay?
I haven't
made up my mind yet.
Made up your mind?
Look, now that you're done with
Greenpeace and finding yourself,
you're either getting
a full-time job
or we agreed you'd
sign up for the program.
I don't think takin' blood is what I
wanna do for the rest of my life.
The course is only for three months.
You'll have your certificate.
Maggie makes $17 an hour.
That's good money.
I know, but I just
don't even like blood.
I don't like cleaning
hotel rooms either,
but I do it so that you girls can
have a better life than I had.
Listen, I wouldn't
be pushing you so hard,
but Maggie's pulling a lot of strings
to get you a job at the clinic.
She's not gonna be there
for much longer,
so it's kind of
now or never.
I hear ya, Mom.
Why does Tosha get to do
what she wants?
Baby, you just spent a whole
year abroad doing your thing,
so don't act like now I'm
the Wicked Witch of the West.
Well, it's just not fair.
Skyler, you're better suited
for working with your head.
Now, Tosha,
on the other hand,
she's a natural
at dancing, entertaining.
- That's her gift.
- Right.
Your sister barely graduated.
Thank God for her gift.
Thank God for that.
- Love you.
- Love you too.
What you starin' at, Sis?
- Did you see this?
- What is that?
First prize is a full
college scholarship.
I did see that.
But did you also see the
words, "USA Dance World?"
They are the best
of the best, girl.
But you say Pulsar
is number one.
- In the city.
- Why not the country?
No, you're right.
I mean, why not think big?
Especially if we have a dope
crew this year, Sky. Who knows?
You don't know who's
gonna make the crew?
Miss J makes everybody audition, even
if they were on the team last year.
So, you don't even know if
you're gonna make the crew, huh?
Girl, no, no.
I'll make the crew.
But she gonna make everybody try
out just to keep us humble, girl.
- You know her.
- Hey, Skyler.
- Hey. What's up, y'all?
- What's up?
You thinkin'
of tryin' out?
- Have you seen her dance?
- Wow. Thanks a lot.
No, no, no. I'm just sayin'.
- If she wants to try out, let her try out.
- Yeah. Why not?
'Cause Pulsar is not for beginners.
Thank you, Bryce.
Okay, come on.
Anyway,
I stopped by because
you left your phone on the
kitchen counter, airhead.
- I did?
- Yes.
- Ooh.
- Look, I gotta go. I gotta get to work.
So I'm-a see y'all later.
- All right. Bye.
- Peace. Later, Sky.
- Hey, I won't forget what you said.
- Okay, don't be...
All right, ladies.
Now make it sexy.
Here we go.
Startin' on the left.
Five, six, seven, go.
Other side.
Yes. To the middle.
- ♪ Can you feel the pain? ♪
- ♪ Can you feel it? ♪
♪ Don't ever let it go ♪
Yes. Fellas!
Come on, fellas!
Yes. Yeah.
♪ In the moment
In the music ♪
Okay, good. Everybody keep up with me though.
More energy.
We gonna follow Dante.
Go on from here.
Ready?
And...
Five, six, five,
six, seven, go!
Good. Nice!
♪ In the moment
In the music ♪
Where's your energy?
Give it to me.
Nice.
Givin' up already? Really?
All right. Good job, Nia.
Stay with it. Good job.
Oh!
You all right there?
- ♪ Come on ♪
- ♪ Swaying back and forth ♪
What the hell is that?
I'm tryin' to teach
the whole class a routine.
This is not the Maya Show.
If your head gets any bigger, I'm
gonna have to widen the doors.
- I was just feelin' it.
- Yeah.
I didn't mean for it
to turn into no battle.
Well, that's good, because
if it was a real battle,
I would've stepped in
and crushed you.
I'm sorry, Miss J.
Won't happen again.
Oh, I know it won't.
All right, what's everybody starin' at?
Class is over.
Don't forget, Pulsar tryouts
are right around the corner.
From what I saw today,
some of y'all need some work.
Jada's just mad 'cause you're a
better dancer then she ever was.
- You killed it.
- Thanks, girl.
You're welcome.
Yeah?
- Hey, Miss J.
- Hey.
I was hoping
if we have time next class,
you could take us through
that last combination again.
Maya kind of
took things off track.
Yeah. Maya has a habit
of doin' that.
- You know what I think her problem is?
- What's that, Nia?
She thinks she's better
than everybody else.
Well, to be fair,
she is our best dancer.
Yeah. When she's saying she's a better
dancer than you ever even were,
I think that's
just straight disrespectful.
- She said that?
- I shouldn't have said anything.
Gotta learn to keep my mouth shut.
I'll see you Tuesday.
Yo, I'll take one of those,
one of those,
one of those, and... mm-mm-mm...
definitely one of those.
- You are so not funny.
- I thought you were supposed to be off.
- Nope, I got another ten.
- Yeah?
You tryin' to get me fired?
Come on.
Give me a little one.
You are something else.
All right.
You be like that.
I'm gonna be right over
there, countin' the seconds.
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm-hmm!
Girl, your man is a trip.
Whoo!
I don't know
what I see in him.
Well, I see exactly
what you see in him.
Hey, that ass is mine.
I'm just sayin',
that's all.
But lucky for you, I got my
man over there on the skates.
Hey, baby!
Hey, baby.
You know,
I really don't like you.
You know, I really don't like you.
♪ Hold me
And take me off the ground ♪
♪ Can't take my crown ♪
What happened
to the uniform?
- I can put it back on if that's what you like.
- Nah.
I just got a thing
for women in uniform.
You know your jokes are corny, right?
- So you want me to change now, huh?
- No. I like corny.
What was that?
I don't know.
But that's on the house.
These wings
or that kiss?
Look.
- What's that?
- A dance competition.
And the first prize is a
full four-year scholarship.
They're going
to enter the Pulsar.
- That crew that your sister dances for?
- Yes.
So, why you showin' me?
'Cause I'm thinkin'
'bout joinin' the crew.
The Pulsar? You think you're
just gonna show up and join?
No, but they have
open tryouts in two weeks.
Yeah, babe,
so do the Falcons,
but if I tried to walk on
there, I'd get slaughtered.
You think
I'll get slaughtered?
No, I don't think
you'll get slaughtered.
- I think I'm good enough.
- Okay.
Where's the sudden interest in dancing?
That's all I'm asking.
What are you talking about?
I'm always dancin'.
I rap every morning
in the shower.
- That don't make me Eminem.
- Wow!
Do not compare my dancing
to your rapping.
Okay. Okay.
Bad comparison.
I'm just saying, your sister
goes to school for dance.
You just dance for fun.
Look, this is my chance at
potentially gettin' a scholarship.
And that too. You never even talked
about going to college before.
I didn't even think that was an option.
I don't have the money for that.
That's why you should be happy that
your mom's trying to hook you up.
You make it sound like she's sending
me to Harvard or something.
It is a three-month course
on collectin' blood
and collectin'
urine samples.
Seriously. And I'm supposed
to just thank her for that?
Look, if you have a chance
to make the Pulsar, go for it.
- Are you just sayin' that?
- No.
Now, you slide over to my place
tonight when you get off.
Look, I appreciate
the proposition and all,
but I gotta practice.
I gotta get up on my game if I'm
serious about joining this crew.
The manager said I could stay
back and dance after we close,
so that's even more lit.
I knew I hated
this damn dance thing.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, hey, hey ♪
♪ Stay hungry, stay thirsty ♪
♪ Don't be afraid
To get down and dirty ♪
♪ Stay hungry, stay thirsty ♪
♪ Don't be afraid
To get down and dirty ♪
♪ We came to conquer
We came to win ♪
♪ We came to fight all night
Until the end ♪
♪ So put your flags up
And raise them high ♪
♪ We're goin' for the gold
We'll get the prize ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, hey, hey ♪
♪ Ready, set, go ♪
♪ The fire's burning inside ♪
♪ Just watch us
Fly, fly, fly, fly ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, hey, hey ♪
♪ Stay hungry, stay thirsty ♪
♪ Don't be afraid
To get down and dirty ♪
♪ Stay hungry, stay thirsty ♪
♪ Don't be afraid
To get down and dirty ♪
- ♪ We're breaking records We get it in ♪
- That's right.
♪ We're working harder
Than your reputation ♪
♪ We're undefeated
It's do or die ♪
♪ We're gonna rough it up
And that's no lie ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, hey, hey ♪
♪ Ready, set, go
The fire's burning inside ♪
♪ Burning inside, yeah ♪
- What are you doin' here?
- Excuse me?
You're not tryin' out, are you?
Honey Studio's best dancer?
Girl, you know Jada don't
be playing no favorites.
More like she wants
to put you in your place.
I can't be nobody's bitch. If you're
fine with that, who am I to judge?
- First off, I'm not her bitch.
- So prove it.
Here's your chance.
Okay, people.
Tryouts start in 15.
When I call your name,
you will have one minute-30
to show me what you got,
all right?
- Where you goin'?
- To the mall.
Didn't you just hear me
say tryouts start in 15?
Well, you can text me and let me
know who's gonna be on the crew.
Okay. My office.
- What?
- Now!
What the hell were you tryin'
to prove out there?
You know my rules.
Every season it's a new crew.
Anybody who wants in
tries out,
even if they been on the team
for three years.
Look, it's not fair
to the other dancers
who work hard all year
to improve their skills
only to find
that they didn't have a shot.
I don't know what's gotten
into your head lately,
but you better start
showing me some respect.
Now, if you wanna be
a part of the Pulsar,
you will get back out there
and try out like everybody else.
- Tosha.
- Hmm?
- Check it out.
- Oh, my gosh. She came.
- That girl is my biggest fan.
- Oh, you mean besides your mom?
Ooh, I stand corrected.
That is true.
Sis!
- What's up?
- Look, listen.
I appreciate the support.
I promise you, I do.
But you did not have to come all
this way to watch me audition.
- It is not that serious.
- I know.
- But I didn't come to watch you.
- Okay.
What... Did something
happen to Mom?
No. She's fine.
Oh.
- So, what you doin' here?
- I'm about to try out for Pulsar.
- Yeah.
- What?
You're trying out
for this team?
Yeah.
Okay, that was good.
You got me.
'Cause that was a joke,
right?
No. I'm not playin'.
- Yeah, you go, girl.
- Why are you...
- Jamaica, go back! Go back.
- Sorry.
I mean,
what do I have to lose?
Skyler,
we talked about this.
Pulsar is not
for beginners.
And I don't wanna see you get
up there and embarrass yourself
or hurt yourself
or do anything like that.
- Embarrass myself?
- Yes, Skyler.
I really think you might be nervous
that I might make the team.
- I'm nervous?
- Yeah.
I'm just lookin'
out for you, Sky. That's it.
Well, okay, good, 'cause I'm gonna
need you to be cheering for me.
Cheer for you... Skyler!
All right, everybody. Let's
get this show on the road.
Start with the fellas.
Guys, you're up.
Let's go, Mike.
♪ Hold up,
wicked, wicked Wicked, wicked ♪
♪ Hold up, wicked, wicked
Wicked, wicked ♪
♪ Stand up in the motor
Bust the dashboard ♪
♪ Stand in the motor
♪ Hold up, wicked, wicked
Wicked, wicked ♪
♪ Candles burning, money burning
Graveyard ♪
♪ He's drippin' Cartier
Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Put a gold bird on you
That's what's happening ♪
♪ I fill a one liter up
With Xannies ♪
♪ It's continental
And it's panoramic ♪
♪ It's complimentary
To the savages ♪
♪ I drink lean, lean, lean
It ain't embarrassing ♪
Ooh!
♪ Wicked, wicked, wicked
Wicked, wicked ♪
♪ Hold up, wicked, wicked
♪ Now she going
Now that... going ♪
♪ I purchase Avión
And now she lit, huh ♪
♪ Wedding band
Rings on me lit, huh ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
All right. Next up.
Ladies!
Let's go, ladies.
♪ Now walk it out
Now walk it out ♪
- ♪ DJ's ♪
- ♪ Now walk it out Now walk it out ♪
♪ Now walk it out Now walk
it out Now walk it out ♪
♪ West side, walk it out
South side, walk it out ♪
♪ East side, walk it out
North side, walk it out ♪
♪ Now hit the dance floor
Now bend your back low ♪
♪ She do it wit' no hands
Now stop, pop and roll ♪
♪ Now everybody leanin'
I make the crowd rock ♪
♪ Now go and walk it out
I see they on my jock ♪
♪ It's on once again
Patrón once again ♪
♪ I threw my head back
Then I froze like the wind ♪
♪ West side, walk it out
South side, walk it out ♪
♪ East side, walk it out
North side, walk it out ♪
♪ They walk it on the east
They walk it on the west ♪
♪ The south side just got it
North side snap your necks ♪
♪ In the club, on the goose
Big stacks, no flex ♪
♪ These suckas wanna try me
Tell 'em two long decks ♪
♪ My... on my side Haters
hating Think it's funny ♪
♪ I'm walking on these...
Now I'm getting to the money ♪
♪ Froze on them... I'm not
talking 'Bout dancing ♪
♪ Full count on the charm
Diamond steady Steady hancin' ♪
♪ Now walk it out
You gonna work it out ♪
♪ Now walk it out ♪
♪ Now walk it out Now walk
it out Now walk it out ♪
♪ Now walk it out, walk it out Now
walk it out Now walk it out ♪
♪ West side, walk it out
South side, walk it out ♪
♪ East side, walk it out
North side, walk it out ♪
♪ Now walk it out ♪
♪ Now walk it out, walk it out ♪
♪ Now walk it out Now walk
it out Now walk it out ♪
♪ West side, walk it out
South side, walk it out ♪
♪ East side, walk it out
North side, walk it out ♪
♪ Walk, walk, walk
Now walk it out ♪
♪ Said do it, how you do it
Gone and walk it out ♪
Okay. Thank you all.
I'll be posting the results outside of
my office today at 5:00 p.m. sharp.
Whoo!
Good luck.
Dancers!
Results
are posted inside!
Okay, come on. Let's go.
Okay.
Wait.
Shouldn't we go look?
We just don't wanna
look desperate.
See, that's fine with me. I was the
last name on the list last year.
- Come on. Let's go be desperate together.
- Okay.
Let's go.
I made it.
- How did that happen?
- Yeah, how did that happen, Jamaica?
- Seriously, dude?
- No, I'm just kidding.
Jamaica, you know
we got your back, bro.
- Hey, I made it though.
- Hey, yo!
At least you tried.
I'm sorry, Sky.
You did well.
Come on.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Congratulations.
You are all Pulsar now.
Hey!
All right, all right. For our
dancers who are new to the crew,
I expect you to learn fast and
live up to the crew's reputation.
And for those members
who are returning,
I expect you
to raise your game,
so don't think you can rely
on what you did last year, okay?
- Don't forget about Angelique.
- Ah.
We do have one minor hiccup.
As you may have noticed,
Angelique is not here.
She had to withdraw because her family
is moving back to West Virginia.
So, her spot will be going
to our alternate,
Skyler.
- What?
- Who?
Skyler.
And since she's your sister, I will let you
have the honor of giving her the good news.
Oh, okay. Well, she'll
be surprised for sure.
All right.
Let's spread out and stretch.
- Hello?
- Hey, girl.
- Hey.
- I got some good news.
It actually looks
like you made Pulsar.
What? Nah, you lyin'.
But, listen,
we're rehearsing right now,
and I know you're busy,
so if you can't make it...
No, no.
No, I'm on my way. Bye.
♪ The distance
Between our bodies ♪
♪ Make me feel like I want ya ♪
♪ Yeah, I feel that I want ya ♪
♪ The distance
Between our bodies ♪
Hey.
♪ Yeah, you whine
Like I own ya ♪
♪ Big gun in your holster
Distance between us ♪
Yes! Nice.
Welcome, Skyler.
You're part
of the Pulsar now.
- Are you ready?
- I'm so ready.
Well, come on.
Okay, drop your stuff.
So, everybody, we gonna go
again from here for Skyler.
All right? Here we go.
♪ Whine like I own ya ♪
- ♪ Big gun in your holster ♪
- And five, six, seven, go.
♪ Distance between us Oh, yeah,
oh, yeah Oh, yeah, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Roll tide like crimson ♪
Nice. Do it again.
Here we go.
Five, six, seven, eight.
♪ Oh, yeah, oh, yeah
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Got them gloves that suit me ♪
Not bad.
All right, so we gonna take five.
Work on that.
- Yeah.
- All right?
So, are you ready
to make your debut
on the scene tonight
as a Pulsar?
Wait, tonight?
- Rehearsals just started.
- No, no, no, tonight.
No, girl. She's talkin' about
showin' up at the club
and lettin' 'em know
what we do.
See that? See that?
Now, that... I can do.
Okay.
Come sit your ass down.
So how does it feel
to be one of the crew, Sis?
Oh, my God, it feels good.
Come on, girls. We're not gonna
get any play just sitting here.
- Let's go!
- Finally.
Let's go to town.
Let's go.
♪ Girl, you know
That you break them necks ♪
♪ Break them necks
Make me break a sweat ♪
♪ Damn, baby
When you do that stretch ♪
♪ Make me lose my head
I can't handle it ♪
♪ Working out your business ♪
♪ Checking out your business ♪
♪ It's looking like
It's Christmas ♪
♪ Watch you work
'Cause you're so delicious ♪
♪ Everybody, hands in the air ♪
♪ Wave 'em round like
They just don't care ♪
Sky, I didn't know
you could dance like that.
Neither did I.
Girl, looked more
like possession to me.
- Don't hate, Maya.
- Hey, it was sexy to me.
If you into that hood-vibe
thing, I guess.
Oh, why y'all throwin'
all this shade at our girl?
You looked good
on the floor.
- Maya got her stare on.
- He's been starin' at me since we got up in here.
Can I have him
when you're done?
You want
Maya's leftovers?
I have three older sisters.
I'm used to hand-me-downs.
Wait, wait, wait. Maya, before
you get too excited, dear,
I think you readin' him
all wrong.
How is that, Tosha?
Oh, you didn't see him
lookin' this way?
Girl, good night,
all right?
I saw him first.
Don't try it.
I don't know why you all
are being so possessive.
Men are like buses.
You wait long enough, another
one comes back around.
Nia, open your eyes. That boy is not a bus.
He's a Ferrari. Vroom!
Girl, you know
you want him.
I like the way you move.
You dope.
Oh!
I'm Tyrell.
Skyler.
All of y'all was tight on the floor.
You all a dance crew?
- Yeah, we are. The Pulsar.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- So you've heard of us?
Of course I have. Well, look,
y'all have fun, all right?
- Hey, you wanna dance and show me some more moves?
- Yeah, yeah.
Shut up. I'm just goin'
to the bathroom.
You look thirsty. You want a
little somethin' to drink?
Save some for us
later, girl.
♪ At 16, no, I didn't
Have much though ♪
♪ Knew too many kids
That grew up like us though ♪
♪ I really mean it when I say
I had it rough though ♪
♪ So many things that I wanted
Heard no, no, no ♪
♪ So many times
I wanted them J's ♪
♪ Risin' to the top
Imagining, yeah ♪
♪ I feel like
They just didn't know ♪
♪ So, watch me when I did it ♪
♪ Hate me when I win it ♪
♪ You say I can't get it ♪
♪ Everyone will know ♪
♪ But they shady ♪
♪ No one wants to listen ♪
♪ No one mind they business ♪
♪ Know in time
I gonna make it, make it ♪
You quiet.
I'm just eatin' my cereal
like I always do.
You look like you got
something on your mind.
Tyrell, maybe?
- Why are you pressin' that?
- Why you got a attitude?
You're not jealous that he asked
me to dance and not you, right?
Why I gotta be jealous? I can't
just ask you a question?
I ain't gonna ask you nothin' else.
- Hi.
- Hey, babe.
What are you doing here
so early?
- Just checkin' to see if you're okay.
- Why wouldn't I be?
Oh, I've been callin' you
all night.
Oh, damn.
My battery died yesterday,
and by the time we got home,
I done forgot to put it on
the charger, I was so tired.
Oh, no, babe, that's fine.
I was just on my way to work.
- Wanted to make sure my girl was okay.
- Oh!
That's so sweet.
That's not sweet.
That's stalker-ish.
Yeah, right. So, where
were you last night?
Oh, I meant to tell you.
I made Pulsar.
What? Are you serious?
What, you think
I'm makin' it up?
No, no. Congratulations, babe.
I had no idea.
Everybody who made the dance group,
we all went out to celebrate.
- So, that's what I was doing yesterday.
- You should've called me.
- I'd have met up with you guys.
- It wasn't that kinda scene.
It was just the dancers. Like, literally.
We just went out...
No, it was just us dancers.
She right.
Just us dancers
doin' dancer things.
- You know what we do.
- Okay. Well...
I'll leave you two dancers
to do what dancers do.
I gotta get to work.
I'll see you later, okay, babe?
- All right.
- All right. I'll see you soon.
- See ya, Tosh.
- Bye.
- Oh, you was dancin', all right.
- You so petty.
Listen up.
We got a lot of work to do
between now and Dance World.
Only if we make it
into the finals
do we get
to the one-on-one battles.
As you know, I can only send
one dancer into the battle,
who will represent
for the entire crew.
As our soloist,
I have chosen Maya.
I'm ready. You know I am.
Good, 'cause we
countin' on you.
And five, six, seven, go.
I don't know what you do...
Who's that?
Ah!
- Tyrell?
- So what?
- You gave Tyrell your number?
- He asked for it.
No. Don't you ever call me
easy ever again, Skyler.
- No, no, stop, stop.
- Uh-uh.
No, he wants me to come check
out an underground battle.
Oh. Well,
that sounds dope, Sky.
Exactly.
So you comin' or not?
I would come with you, but I
don't wanna be a third wheel.
I don't mind being third wheel.
I'm into sharing.
No, thanks. I'm not.
Besides, it's not a date.
Okay, if it's not a date, why you
not askin' Luke to go with you?
Because Luke don't even like dance music.
Plus, I wanna check it out.
Okay. You don't need my permission, girl.
Go have fun.
Hey, if you change your mind,
I'm still up for it.
No, thanks, Jamaica.
- Hey, don't knock it till you try it.
- Ooh!
- Did he just say what I think he said?
- We're not gonna address that.
- Okay.
- We gonna move past it like he didn't say it.
♪ No gyal can tell me
'Bout my mother ♪
♪ Sixteen shot
We go longer than a ladder ♪
♪ Them no fi talk
'Bout the real Don dada ♪
♪ Put body in a pot
Them a bun like grabba ♪
♪ No boy can diss me
Or my mother ♪
♪ Round here ain't safe
Everybody need armor ♪
♪ Sixteen shot
We go shotta any brotha ♪
♪ Rah-ta, rah-ta
Ka-ka, ka-kah, ka-kah ♪
♪ Rah-ka-ka-ka-ka-rah ♪
♪ You couldn't be badder
Than a King stony ♪
♪ Diss my mother
Then your skin start bleed ♪
♪ So don't bother mess
With my mommy ♪
♪ With my mommy, with my mommy ♪
♪ Baby, think you bad
Say ya badder than she ♪
♪ I dog a-go bark
Long time them don't eat ♪
♪ Rap on, pop off
Make you move like freak ♪
♪ They say them a gangsta
But so is Mommy ♪
♪ They gon' put hands
On a chick ♪
♪ They gon' put hands on her ♪
♪ Eyes watchin' when I comin'
Through the door ♪
♪ No gyal can tell me
'Bout my mother ♪
♪ Sixteen shot
We go longer than a ladder ♪
♪ Them no fi talk
'Bout the real Don dada ♪
♪ Put body in a pot
Them a bun like grabba ♪
♪ No boy can diss me
Or my mother ♪
♪ Round here ain't safe
Everybody need armor ♪
♪ Sixteen shot
We go shotta any brotha ♪
You should go out there
and do your thing.
What, you want me
to battle her?
♪ Rah-ta, rah-ta ♪
Why not? What's the worst
that could happen?
Well, first,
I can't dance in heels.
Second,
she'll hand me my ass.
Don't think. Just do.
Feel it.
I don't know. I...
You got this.
♪ No gyal can tell me
'Bout my mother ♪
♪ Sixteen shot
We go longer than a ladder ♪
♪ Them no fi talk
'Bout the real Don dada ♪
♪ Put body in a pot
Them a bun like grabba ♪
♪ No boy can diss me
Or my mother ♪
♪ Round here ain't safe
Everybody need armor ♪
♪ Sixteen shot
We go shotta a brotha ♪
♪ Rah-ta, rah-ta
Ka-kah-, ka-kah, ka-kah ♪
♪ Rah-ka-ka-ka-ka-rah ♪
♪ Get one shot
If them think them a man ♪
♪ Get two shot
If them feel them a don ♪
♪ Get three shot
If them take me for idiot ♪
♪ Take four shot This a
couple shot Know that ♪
♪ Get five shot if anybody
What think them hard ♪
♪ Straight, head thump
Ya must drop ♪
♪ If you hit up
The da-da-da-don ♪
♪ Bullets gon' hit you
Wherever you are ♪
♪ No gyal can tell me
'Bout my mother ♪
♪ Sixteen shot
We go longer than a ladder ♪
♪ Round here ain't safe
Everybody need armor ♪
♪ Sixteen shot
We go shotta any brotha ♪
♪ Rah-ta, ta-ta, ta-ta
Ta-ta, ta-ta-ta ♪
- You were sick out there.
- I lost out there.
What do you mean? You battled
the biggest dancer in the city,
and you held your own.
Really?
You think I did okay?
You think I'd lie to you?
You hear the crowd?
They screamin' for you.
See what happens when you
get out your own head?
Told you. Come on.
♪ Oh, it's complicated ♪
♪ Oh, some say it's overrated ♪
Yo, let me get
a blue raspberry, large.
- That's a Slurpee.
- All right. One second.
Skyler,
customer out front.
- Skyler!
- What?
Customer?
Waitin' out front?
Hey, Tyrell.
- Those were some dope moves you were workin' on.
- Who, me?
You don't gotta be humble.
You dope with it.
Thanks.
What time you off?
- We can head to my studio.
- You got your own dance studio?
It's not like Honey, but it's somewhere
where I can work on my moves
and get better.
Well, that sounds cool, but I
just wanna be honest with you.
- I do have a boyfriend.
- I figured.
And that's cool, 'cause I'm
talkin' strictly dancin'.
You a good dancer.
You could be great.
I just wanna
help you with that.
And what do you get
out of all of this?
I'm not gonna lie. Workin' with
you makes me a better dancer.
I could show you
some things.
That's the whole deal.
Well, I get off at 4:00.
I'll see you then.
This is it.
This is...
really different.
Not exactly
what you was expectin'?
No, but not in a bad way.
This is dope.
Yeah, the owner hired me
to manage the compound
and to take the rent
from the artists who use it.
In return, he lets me
use this space to rehearse.
Let me see you freestyle.
I don't know. It's just usually
easier when there's a crowd.
Don't be shy.
It's just me watchin'.
- Nah.
- Nah?
I'll go first.
Follow along
when you're ready.
Yeah.
Start off slow.
Get into the space.
Tease the crowd.
♪ I walk up
Now you mad at me ♪
♪ I took your dope
♪ I told her she done
Now she mad at me ♪
♪ Look at y'all face
Y'all mad at me ♪
♪ Everybody on my side
Mad at me ♪
♪ Everybody on your side
♪ What I'm supposed to do
When you're mad at me? ♪
♪ Let 'em hate, let 'em hate
Let 'em hate, let 'em hate ♪
♪ I walk up
Now you're mad at me ♪
♪ I took your dope
♪ I told her she done
Now she mad at me ♪
♪ Look at y'all face
Y'all mad at me ♪
♪ Everybody on my side
Mad at me ♪
♪ Everybody on your side
♪ What I'm supposed to do
When you're mad at me? ♪
♪ Let 'em hate, let 'em hate
Let 'em hate, let 'em hate ♪
♪ I got stayin' at you mad
I do not have to brag ♪
♪ The look on your face
Make me laugh ♪
♪ Pop-pop-pop
Change the grill ♪
♪ I just might change the world
I jump Tupac for real ♪
Not bad.
But you got a lot more
in you.
Oh, shit. I'm gonna be
late for Pulsar rehearsal.
I'll get you there on time.
We're here.
Thanks a lot. I had fun.
It was a good start, Sky,
but you got
a lot more work to do.
Whatever you say, coach.
I gotta go.
Okay, Skyler, girl.
I see you.
Well done, everyone.
Nice rehearsal.
Oh, my God. That girl in
that video was not all that.
- She don't look better than me though.
- Skyler?
Skyler.
- Can I talk to you for a minute?
- Oh, sure.
Close the door.
I see you've
got some new moves.
I wasn't tryin' to show off, Miss J.
I really wasn't.
Well, where'd you
learn those moves?
Or did they just
come to you?
No, I've been working
with a friend.
He's been showin' me
some of his moves.
Yeah, well, I saw you
on the security cam.
Looked like he was showin'
you more than just moves.
It's not what it looked like.
Honestly.
Look, Skyler, I don't want you
messin' with the likes of that boy.
He's trouble.
I know he look a little rough,
but he's really not like that.
I think I have a pretty good
idea of what he's like.
He's my son.
- What?
- Look, I don't want you to take this wrong
because you are
a beautiful young woman,
but the reason Tyrell is involved
with you is to get back at me.
But I don't...
I don't understand.
We haven't spoken
in the past two years.
Messing with one of my dancers
is another of his games.
So if you don't want to be
played, stay away from him.
But what happened?
I've said more
than I want to.
- But I just...
- I'll see you in rehearsal tomorrow.
Babe, what's goin' on?
Nothin's up. I'm just...
not in the mood.
- What's on your mind?
- Too much.
I'm just, like...
Everything is just
so stressful with work and...
Rehearsals with Pulsar,
and my mom is still on my back
about this medical
assistant's course.
It's just annoying.
I'm over it.
Come here, baby.
Come here.
Just take it
one day at a time,
and everything
will be okay.
- I guess.
- You worry too much. You know that?
As long as everything's okay
with you and me, it's all good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I do think you should listen to your mom
about that medical assistant job though.
It pays more than minimum wage.
It's a great job.
Damn, Luke!
- What, baby?
- It was just gettin' good!
What?
Sk... Sky,
where you goin'?
Hey.
Hey!
- What?
- You don't answer my phone calls.
Why all the shade, Sky?
The shade is that
I spoke to your mother.
- You didn't think I would find out?
- I wasn't hiding anything.
Look, it's gettin' busy in here,
so you want somethin' or not?
How 'bout you just come to
the studio after you're done
and let me explain
everything, please.
Look, I'll come by
to your studio,
but you better not
be wasting my time.
♪ I just wanna
Switch locations ♪
♪ She said to me ♪
♪ Come now, come now, baby ♪
♪ Finish that drink ♪
♪ She don't want
No conversation ♪
♪ Only want one thing ♪
♪ And that's
What's frustrating ♪
♪ Heavy and deep ♪
♪ She said she want to know
She said she want to know ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Oh-oh ♪
Since I can remember, my mom
resented me for a bunch of reasons.
I still don't know why.
Maybe it's because when she
threw my father out the house,
she was forced
to raise me alone.
That didn't help her chances
of becoming a dancer.
We used to always fight.
When I was 16 years old,
I decided to quit school
and get involved into
the underground club scene.
So, she decided
to do tough love
and said if I got kicked outta
school, if I ever quit,
I had to move out.
So I did.
Maybe I'm as stubborn
as she is.
I don't know if any of this
is makin' sense.
Trust me.
I definitely feel
where you coming from.
The only hope in life my mom
sees for me is drawing blood.
And waste all your talent?
That's crazy.
Your mom said that you were
using me to get back at her.
She would say that.
So when I told you
I was with Pulsar,
why didn't you
just tell me then?
I wanted you
to get to know me first.
I would've told you
I was Jada's son,
you would've looked at me
differently.
I guess.
Whatever
my mom tell you,
know I'm not
playin' games with you.
I'm not lyin'.
I'd like more, but as long as we
can dance together, I'm good.
Girl, you made Maya
work for that one.
I was just trying
to keep up with her.
I would not let it
go to your head.
And you know I was bein'
easy on all y'all.
I just don't want Miss J
all up in my face.
Okay. Anyways, some of us are goin'
to the club tonight. You gonna come?
Oh, my God. Y'all always
goin' to the club.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, girl.
All right. I'm in.
- Hey, Tyrell.
- Hey.
Tyrell, this is
my boyfriend Luke.
Luke, Tyrell.
- Nice meetin' you.
- How do you know Skyler?
Tyrell's her private
dance teacher.
I didn't know that you were
taking private dance lessons.
How you think
she got this good?
Obviously, I need to be
over there taking lessons.
Anytime. I just came over to say you
look good on the dance floor tonight.
Those dance lessons
payin' off.
Nice meetin' you.
So, how long you been taking
private lessons with this guy?
- A few weeks.
- Why wouldn't you tell me anything about that?
Do I have to tell you
everything that I'm doing?
No, but if we're
gonna have trust...
You don't even want me dancin', so why do
you care about what lessons I'm takin'?
- Uh, Sis.
- What?
- The competition just got here.
- Who are they?
That's the crew we supposed to be goin'
up against in Ultimate Dance World.
- Wait, I know her.
- You know who?
Remember when I told you I got my
ass whupped in that dance battle?
- Yes, I do.
- That's her.
- You went up against Eva, Sky?
- Yes.
That's Atmasphere's
best dancer.
Well, well, well.
- Hey, Eva.
- Hey, girl.
So, you didn't come
to check out the competition?
I mean, if we were, I guess
we'd have to go home early,
'cause looks like
I don't see any here.
Yo, she funny.
- Super funny.
- I guess you ain't lost your sense of humor
after we beat you
for a... third time in a row.
If you keep living in the past, the future's
gonna sneak up and bite you in your little ass.
Oh, this big ass
right here?
Your little...
I don't see anything.
- No, you see it. Thank you.
- Oh, that little thing?
- We're gonna catch you later.
- Bye.
♪ Cold world
Cold world, cold world ♪
♪ Cold world ♪
♪ It's a cold world
Cold world, cold world ♪
♪ Sometimes it make you wonder
What we doin' here ♪
♪ Real, in the feel ♪
♪ Gotta get it
How you deal ♪
♪ Can't be lookin' for love
Got to get my HQ ♪
♪ It's a cold world
Cold world, cold world ♪
- What's good, girl?
- Just hangin' with my crew.
Ever since you guys showed up
though, the energy's kind of wack.
Why do you have to be
so nasty?
I'm just playing
with you, okay?
I like your crew.
I'm sure you do.
She's the only thing keeping
you from beating Pulsar.
She won't be
at Pulsar forever.
Tell me about it.
The way things are going
between her and Jada,
she's ready
to walk out tomorrow.
Really?
Jada's holding her back.
She wants to be on a crew
that lets her do her own thing.
And why are you
telling me this?
I'm just trying
to be helpful.
With Maya gone,
you'd have a shot
at replacing her.
Is that right?
It's a win-win.
♪ It's a cold world ♪
- ♪ Cold world, cold world ♪
- ♪ Cold world ♪
♪ Sometimes it make you wonder
What we doin' here ♪
♪ Real, in the feel ♪
♪ Gotta get it
How you deal ♪
♪ Can't be lookin' for love
Got to get my HQ ♪
♪ It's a cold world
Cold world, cold world ♪
Hold up. Maya.
Why you insist upon adding your own flavor
when you know that's not what I want?
I'm sorry. I just can't help
it if I'm better than that.
Better than what?
Than the tired moves you
keep throwing at us, Miss J.
- Mike, can you believe her?
- Well, um,
if you're not happy
with my choreography,
feel free to leave,
sweetheart.
- -We're
going from the top.
Maya, get back in line. I don't
have time for your drama today.
I quit.
How's that for drama?
Do you know what? That's gonna be a cut on
rehearsal today. I'll see y'all tomorrow.
♪ Baby, I see you
Doing your thing, yeah ♪
♪ I like the way you
Squeeze and touch me, yeah ♪
♪ Let me take the wheel
You know the deal ♪
♪ Speed it up, slow it down
Make my love come down ♪
♪ Feeling you... ♪
All right, hold up, hold up.
Atmasphere Crew,
please welcome
our newest member.
Hi.
- Hi. How are you?
- Hi.
- Thank you.
- Say hi.
- Hey! All right.
- Hi. What's up?
Hey.
So we dancin' or what?
Does your boyfriend
know you're here?
I'm my own person.
Translation: No.
Look, I'm not about to let his
jealousy get in the way of my dancin'.
Zaytoven.
Let's dance.
'Sup, man
Hey, what up?
♪ Yeah, thumbin' through
The check like "bdtdt" ♪
- ♪ Yeah, oh, God ♪
- ♪ Whoo, whoo ♪
♪ Your ho blow my phone
Like "bdtdt" ♪
- ♪ Oh, God, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ It's your ho, man ♪
♪ I pull up
Like "skrrt, skrrt" ♪
- ♪ I pull up, let's go ♪
- ♪ Diamonds in my "errs" ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Two hundred on my "drrsh" ♪
♪ 'Sup? Ha ha ♪
♪ Gotta ride in "frrs" ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Got your ho like
Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ It's your ho, man ♪
♪ Diamonds in my "errs" ♪
- ♪ I got your ho, man ♪
- ♪ "Bdtdt" ♪
- ♪ She on go, man ♪
♪ I got ice all on my chain
Like a snowman ♪
- ♪ Brrr ♪
- ♪ I'm the boss, man ♪
- ♪ Drink da bottle, man ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Boy, I got it How you want it?
Heard the style, man ♪
♪ I'm the boss, man ♪
♪ Yeah, gotta ride in "frrs" ♪
♪ It's your ho, man ♪
- ♪ Diamonds in my "errs" ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
That was tight.
Yeah. A little too tight.
See you later.
Ooh. Yeah.
- What up, Sha?
- Girl, I didn't even see you come in.
What you doin' here so early? I thought you went to the mall.
I did. But I
finished up early, so.
I would've came earlier, but of course
I had to listen to Mom's lecture.
I think she tryin' to help. I don't
think she's tryin' to hurt you.
Yeah, whatever.
She don't even think we gonna
win now that we lost Maya.
Girl, I hope
she's not right.
- Not you too. Come on.
- I know.
I'm just sayin'. Maya was the
best dancer we had on this crew.
I watched y'all go head-to-head,
toe-to-toe. You can hold your own.
- Hold my own like I could run this crew?
- Yeah.
And you don't have your eye
on being Jada's number one?
Look, I already told you. I'm cool
with just being down with the crew.
Bitch, you lyin'.
All right,
maybe it might've...
it might've ran through
my mind couple times.
But I mean, who wouldn't
want to do a solo?
Shoot, I wanna do
the solo, obviously.
Yeah, obviously. but if
you wanna do that solo,
you gonna need
to get that right.
I'm not even
gonna hold you up.
Your hip was just going
way too far forward.
Okay, so you
giving me tips?
You know, I do what I can.
Man, y'all are
making us look bad,
always showing up early.
Like seriously, stop, okay?
That's how
they make you look bad.
Oh, God.
Man, whatever, Randy.
You better watch your back,
okay, bro?
Ha.
Hey. What's up with your sister?
She's in some kind of mood today.
Yeah, well, with the competition coming and
no Maya, I think we're all a little stressed.
- Right?
- Maya was and is overrated.
We can still win this, okay?
- As long as Jada picks the right person for the solo.
- You mean you?
Why not?
Although I hear somebody's been taking
private lessons with Jada's son.
He's just been showin' me
some dance moves.
Good for you. Men have been
getting some on the side forever.
I'm not getting anything
on the side.
- Seriously, I'm not.
- Okay.
Enough talk. Let's get to work, people.
Let's go. Let's go.
Come on.
We're going again.
Yeah, give me that attitude.
Let me see it in your face. Yes!
Hit this hard. Hit it hard.
Up, down. Yes.
Yeah, that's
what I'm talking about.
Not bad. It's not bad.
Uh, why y'all all sucking wind like
you about to take your last breath?
Dance World
is in two weeks, people.
I don't want to see
any gasping onstage.
Tomorrow I am going to decide on
who gets the solo.
So come in prepared
to show me what you got.
All right, that's it. Get your
lazy bones out of my studio.
Is it just me, or is Miss J
gettin' hard on us?
Girl, it is not just you.
She always gets like this when competition
comes around. Girl, she is tryin' to win.
We all just tryin' to win.
Oh, I meant to tell you.
I'm going to this underground
battle at Lifted with Tyrell.
You want to come?
Is this another one of your,
um, your not-a-date dates?
- Forget I asked, Tosha.
- Wait, I'm just playin'. You know I can't come.
That dude I was telling you about who's
always hooking me up with clothes?
I gotta go Netflix and chill with
him, act like I like his black ass.
- -But first I'm hitting
Zesto's with the crew, so...
Well, have fun.
Thank you. I love you.
Love you too.
Mmm, this shake
is everything!
Yeah, and this is coming from the
guy who literally eats everything.
- So, what's up, Tosh?
- What?
You, uh... You gonna let me get some
clothes from your "friend" tonight?
- From my "friend"?
- Yeah, your friend.
I don't think he will be cool with
me getting another guy clothes,
but if you need a crop
top, sir, I'm your girl.
Hey, Randy, that might
be a good look for you.
- Like for real. No shade.
- I agree.
- Hey, Tosha. What's up, guys?
- Hey, Luke.
- What's up?
- What are y'all up to?
- Chillin'.
- French fries.
- No practice today?
- Eatin'.
We finished practice
about an hour ago.
Oh. Where's Sky? Isn't she
part of the crew now?
That she is.
But she's getting ready to go to
that underground club thing tonight.
Oh. She didn't mention
anything to me.
She said she was gonna
ask you to go,
but that's not really
your scene, she says.
Yeah. Yeah.
I guess that's true.
I think she just decided
to go with Tyrell instead.
So they gonna go and try to see
what's hot, check out some moves.
Just her and Tyrell?
I mean, we were all too tired from
practice to go, but you know Sky.
She gonna take this dance thing
to the next level.
Yeah, I know Sky.
Um, you don't happen to know
where that club's at, do you?
Yeah, actually, I do.
- You know, it's Lifted.
- Mmm.
Yeah, it's 409 Eighth Street.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
Okay, cool. I'll catch up
with you guys later then.
- Yeah, sure. -Later, man.
- Peace, man.
Tell her I said not to come
home too late, please?
- Okay, I will.
- Thank you.
- See you, guys.
- See you, man.
- You threw that?
- Threw what?
- So you don't want the crop top then?
- All right.
♪ Girl, your body movin' Like
this your favorite song Whoo ♪
♪ Know you with your girls
But I can't leave you alone ♪
♪ I don't know
What's in your cup ♪
♪ But you probably
Need some more ♪
♪ The way your body move I
imagine what you do At home ♪
♪ You got the juice, juice ♪
♪ I tell the truth, truth ♪
♪ I'm tryin' to, uh, uh ♪
♪ You got the juice, juice
I tell the truth, truth ♪
♪ You got the juice, juice ♪
♪ I wanna, uh, uh ♪
♪ I can tell you liked it too ♪
♪ Girl, it's not your fault
How you carry it, uh ♪
♪ How you manage that
'Cause the crowd goin' crazy ♪
♪ Uh, lookin' as you like
As want to be my lady ♪
♪ Feel like Brady ♪
♪ Feel like Jay-Z ♪
♪ Stuff is runnin'
Through my mind ♪
♪ I'm goin' crazy ♪
♪ You're the type of girl
That my mama warned me 'bout ♪
♪ But she don't understand ♪
♪ When I bring you
To the house ♪
♪ Girl, your body movin' Like
this your favorite song Whoo ♪
♪ Know you with your girls
But I can't leave you alone ♪
♪ I don't know
What's in your cup ♪
♪ But you probably
Need some more, whoo ♪
♪ The way your body move I
imagine what you do At home ♪
♪ You got the juice, juice ♪
♪ I tell the truth, truth ♪
♪ I wanna, uh, uh ♪
♪ I can tell that you a star ♪
♪ Girl, you're shinin' bright
Yeah ♪
♪ You're the type of girl That
make me hang it up And wait ♪
♪ You and your money, girl ♪
♪ I know you worth it ♪
♪ Juice, Juice
Trippin', trippin' ♪
♪ Zippin', zippin' ♪
♪ Got your own money, money ♪
♪ Girl, you some kisser ♪
♪ You got it, you got it
You know you can dance ♪
♪ Tell me what you think about
This what I dreamed about ♪
♪ Girl, your body movin'
Like this your favorite song ♪
♪ Know you with your girls
But I can't leave you alone ♪
♪ I don't know
What's in your cup ♪
♪ But you probably
Need some more ♪
♪ The way your body move I
imagine what you do At home ♪
- ♪ I can't ♪
- ♪ You got the juice ♪
- Yo, that was so dope!
- Great.
- You're amazing.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Yo, you need to chill out, man.
- Am I talking to you?
Luke, back off.
Nothin' happened.
No, just dancing, right? Isn't
that what you said? Just dancing?
For once she's doing what she likes.
So get to steppin', man.
I'm talking to my girl, dude.
She's her own woman, and from the
looks of it, she don't want you.
- Just get outta here.
- Let me tell ya something, you little broke-ass punk.
I don't dance, but if you wanna step outside,
I'll show you what a real battle is.
All right, that's enough.
- -You know what? That is enough.
Come on. Let's go.
- Are you coming or what?
- You can't come up in here
and drag me out
like you own me.
Know what, Sky?
Enjoy your new life.
Buh-bye!
Look, I'm sorry about what
happened at the club tonight, Sky.
It's not your fault.
So we cool?
Yeah, we cool.
- Damn!
- What?
Skyler, where have you been
hiding these moves?
- I gotta give it up to you. That's just dope.
- What are you guys talking about?
- Yeah.
- You got it, flaunt it.
Damn, you blowin' up
all over the Web.
Come on. 20,000 hits
in two hours, Sky.
- Who does that?
- This is crazy.
- Who posted it though?
- Like, half the kids in the club.
That was ill.
- I was just following Tyrell.
- Come on, girl.
You schooled that boy.
He's got nothing on you.
Looks to me like Jada
has her new soloist.
I wouldn't be so sure.
When she sees this
video, she won't have a choice.
Yeah, she's also gonna see
I'm dancing with Tyrell.
Miss J wants to win just
as much as the rest of us.
She's gonna come around fast enough.
- Oh...
- Did you see this?
Oh, I knew y'all
would be here celebrating.
I'm not celebrating
though.
- I'd be if I were you.
- It was just a dance battle.
Your sister is dope.
We all think
she be dancing the solo.
Y'all think Miss J gonna have
somethin' to say about it?
What are you
gonna major in?
Uh... Shit, I don't know.
Politics, maybe?
Politics? What do you know
about politics?
Hey, down there.
Chill out.
What about you?
What are you gonna study?
Uh, I always wanted to be
an animal doctor.
- "Animal doctor"? You mean, uh, a vet?
- Yeah.
- He means a vet.
- Yes, a vet.
Why not just be a human doctor?
Probably takes just as long.
I like animals better.
That explains a lot. Right?
Okay, whoa, man.
I'm keeping this.
- Hey, guys.
- Good color.
- Hey, what's up?
We were just talking about what we're
gonna do when we win that scholarship.
- 'Sup?
- Okay.
You all feel like we
about to win this, huh?
If you think about it and seen Skyler was goin'
dong stupid in the club the other night.
- I think we got a good chance.
- I hope so.
'Cause I just want to be able to say
that I'm a college graduate, you know?
Okay, so what
we doing here?
We having a slumber party or
dance rehearsal? What's goin'...
We're just talking about
winning that scholarship.
Oh, well, I'm happy to see
everybody's feeling so confident.
Yeah, well, with Skyler
doing the solo, we can't lose.
What makes you think
Skyler's doing the solo?
- Didn't you see the video of her dancing?
- As a matter of fact, I did.
Which is why I am not putting
her in the solo. Sorry, Skyler.
You can't be
serious though, right?
It's my decision to make.
So, yes, I am serious.
I'm not trying to do
the solo for me.
Everybody who's seen the video of me
dancin' says that I could beat Maya.
I also saw the video, which is
why I'm not giving you the solo.
Wait. I'm... I'm confused.
Okay, well, just because you can shake
your booty you think you're a real dancer.
But the kind of dance you do does
not represent the style of dance
that Honey Studio
stands for.
Okay. It's called hip-hop,
and that's what I was doing.
Okay. You can call what
you do whatever you want.
But I call it
cheap exhibitionism,
and your teammates will see that too
once they have time to compare that
to what we do here.
- But I...
- Ah.
Dante, let's warm
everybody up, huh?
All right, guys.
Spread out.
- Sorry, Sky.
- Miss J.
- You just trying to get back at your son.
- What?
You don't want him
to get any credit
for everything he's been teaching
me that you've never seen before.
Let's leave Tyrell
out of this.
Right, 'cause leaving Tyrell out
is easy for you, huh?
What's that
supposed to mean?
It's supposed to mean putting
your son out in the streets
because he dropped out
of school?
- That's cold.
- Whoa, Tyrell didn't drop out of school.
He was kicked out
for fighting and dealing drugs.
And I didn't throw him
on the street.
The judge put him in a group
home, and when he was released,
he chose not to
come back home.
Not that I was
in a hurry to have him back.
You forgot
your water... bottle.
Has everything
you told me been a lie?
I want you
to get to know me, Sky.
Dealin' drugs?
It was stupid. I got caught.
I haven't done it in two years.
You can't build a relationship
based off of lies, Tyrell.
Do you know what it's like
to have nobody believe in you?
That's been me
my whole life.
Do you know how badly I want somebody
in my life to believe in me?
Support my ambition?
I believe in you.
Look. I want somebody
that I can trust.
And right now,
that trust is broken.
♪ Sorry ♪
♪ Rising like the smoke ♪
♪ You linger on me ♪
♪ You got me so high ♪
♪ I can finally breathe ♪
♪ You're walking poetry ♪
♪ It's what you do to me ♪
♪ It's what you do
To me ♪
♪ Touch me with no hands ♪
♪ Hold me with your eyes ♪
♪ Unwind me with your mind
Tonight ♪
♪ Speak with no words ♪
- ♪ Show me and I'm all yours ♪
- Skyler's not here.
- ♪ Show me And I'm all yours ♪
- I came to see you.
Why?
So you could gloat about how you got one of my
girls all twisted with your sad and made-up story?
Me and Skyler
had something real.
- But then you had to mess it up like always?
- No.
You did that to yourself
by lying to her.
- Why you hate me?
- Is that what you really believe?
Tyrell, I brought you
into this world.
I worked hard,
passed on opportunities,
to provide for you.
So why don't you add that you
resent me because of that?
That's not true.
And why you was
never there to be a mom.
Is it because
I look like Pops?
I bet when you wanted to throw him
out, you wanted to throw me out too.
When I met your father,
I thought he was a good man.
He had ambition and dreams.
But when things didn't go his
way, he started using drugs.
When he couldn't afford those
drugs, he started dealing.
So, no, I was not gonna let my son be
put in danger because of his choices.
That's why I tossed him out.
To protect you.
But how was I supposed to know you was gonna
end up in the same patch as your father?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
Nah, you just tellin' me
what I need to hear.
But, Mom, if you're never
gonna forgive me,
don't take it out
on Skyler.
♪ Touch me with no hands ♪
♪ Hold me with your eyes ♪
♪ Unwind me with your mind
Tonight ♪
♪ You're the type of girl
That my mama warned me 'bout ♪
♪ But she don't understand ♪
♪ When I bring you
To the house ♪
♪ Girl, your body movin' Like
this your favorite song Whoo ♪
♪ Know you with your girls
But I can't leave you alone ♪
♪ I don't know
What's in your cup ♪
♪ But you probably
Need some more, whoo ♪
♪ The way your body move I
imagine what you do At home ♪
♪ You got the juice, juice ♪
♪ I tell the truth, truth ♪
♪ I'm trying to, uh, uh ♪
♪ You got the juice... ♪
Oh, hi.
Please come on in.
Thank you. I am sorry
for stopping by unannounced.
Oh, don't be silly.
You're always welcome here.
I'm sorry to say that Tosha's
not here at the moment.
You know, actually,
I was hoping to talk to Skyler.
Oh. Sure. She's in her room.
I'll get her.
- Skyler?
- I heard the doorbell.
Hi.
What's goin' on?
Well...
Tyrell was right. I shouldn't punish
you for what's going on between us.
- He said that?
- Yeah.
He did. That's
actually why I'm here.
I want you to do
the one-on-one battle.
But-But I thought...
Never mind what I said.
I... I was wrong.
So I'm asking you,
will you be our soloist?
I...
The answer
is no.
Skyler's already applied to school so she
could get her medical assistant's certificate
and get
a good-paying job.
Wow, that was fast.
Do you even have an interest
in medicine, or is...
Hey, Miss J.
Hi, Tosha.
Just stopped by
to talk to Skyler.
- What's goin' on?
- She wants Skyler to dance the solo.
Congratulations.
I know I was harsh the other day, but...
I've come to my senses.
And so has Skyler.
Are you sure about this?
I promised her I would do it.
I'm sorry you came
all this way
just to get an answer you weren't
looking for, but I know my Skyler.
And when she's made up her mind,
that's that. Right, honey?
Understood. Well,
then I should be leaving.
We are gonna miss you.
If you change your mind, I have to decide
on who's doing the solo by tomorrow.
Sounds like she's already
made up her mind.
It was nice
seeing you again, April.
You have two
very talented daughters.
Thank you.
Two.
Well, that was
mature of you.
What was, Tosha?
Turning down Miss J so you
could do something practical.
Yeah, that's me,
Miss Practical.
Well, it might've been a good decision,
because I think she was coming over here
because she felt guilty
about what happened with Tyrell.
Or maybe one of the reasons
why she came over here
is she felt like I was
the better person for the solo.
- You have to stop trying to compete with your sister.
- Maybe so. I...
Compete?
Ain't no competition.
You've clearly already picked
the winner from jump.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Look around here. You notice anything?
How many pictures on the wall
does Mom have of you?
- I don't know.
- Twenty.
You wanna know how many of me? Three.
And two of 'em, you're in.
- Why are we doing this?
- That's just nonsense.
Nonsense? Really? Okay.
I'm not here. I'm not here.
I'm not here.
Oh, and this one right here?
I was actually standing
right next to her,
but for some reason,
I didn't make the picture.
Okay, now here we go with the dramatics.
And that chip on your shoulder.
You just really
don't get it.
Sky, Mom has worked hard all this time for
both of us. It hasn't just been for me.
It's always been easy
for you,
because you get the better end
of the deal every single time.
Don't blame me
because I have talent, Sky.
Wow.
You've really got her
brainwashed.
You really got her
And you really think
I don't have talent.
I didn't mean that, but...
I know what you meant.
Why share the limelight with your
sister if you don't have to?
- Okay. You know what? Stop.
- That has...
Stop. I'm not listening
to anymore of this.
You don't have to.
'Cause I made my decision.
You answered Miss J,
not me.
What are you doing?
Don't tear that up.
You are throwing
everything away.
Cool.
And where are you going now?
To let Jada know
that she has a solo dancer.
How can you let that backstreet neophyte
nobody represent us at Dance World?
Girl, you better back it up.
You are shouting in my face.
I'm sorry. I just think
you're making a mistake.
Really?
With Maya gone, we need
our strongest dancer
to go head-to-head with her in the
battle, and that is not Skyler.
So just who do you
think it is, Nia?
I'm not saying this for my
sake, but for the whole team.
It should be me.
There's no doubt
you are one of my best dancers,
but Skyler
brings something fresh,
and we need that going up
against Maya in the battle.
She knows all our moves.
It's your call.
Well, good. I'm glad
we at least agree on that.
- I didn't mean for it to sound like that.
- Uh-huh.
If it's any consolation,
I have added something to the routine
that's gonna feature you and Tosha.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
Huh.
- Atmasphere, bring it in, bring it in. Bring it in.
- Yes!
That was dope.
We are so close
to winning Dance World.
If you all can bring it like
you did today, it's ours.
Eva, the helicopter
was fire.
I want you to rock that
in the solo. Yeah?
- All right. I got you, Coach.
- All right.
Everybody, take five. When we get
back, running the opening piece.
Yeah?
- Hey, Derrick, can I talk to you for a second?
- Cool?
- Yeah, yeah, of course.
- Okay.
So, you told Eva to do the
helicopter in the solo.
Oh, yeah. I think
the helicopter works.
I know it does. I'm the one
who came up with the move.
And you told me I was doin' the solo.
What's up with that?
I didn't mean for it to come out like that, okay?
- I changed my mind, and I was gonna tell you...
- Really? When?
When it was too late for me to change
my mind and go back to Pulsar?
Why would you do that?
We got a winning crew.
The only reason why you have a chance of
beating Pulsar is because I'm not on the team.
Damn. That's the only reason why
you recruited me, isn't it?
What are you talking about?
You never planned on
giving me the solo.
You just didn't want to have Eva
have to go up against me.
I would never do
something like that.
- I'm only doing what I think is best for this crew.
- Really?
I'm gonna do the same.
I'm out of here, Derrick.
Ladies.
Fellas.
Well, what a surprise.
I got played.
Really?
Everybody, take five.
Got played, huh?
I should've never allowed Nia to talk me into
going over to Atmasphere in the first place.
It was her idea.
Nia told me
she begged you to stay.
Begged?
Are you kidding me?
She's been on my case.
On my case about
how you be disrespecting me,
telling me I need to man up
and speak my mind,
how I need
to not hold my tongue.
Well, damn, that sounds like the
exact line she's been feeding me.
It looks like
we both got played.
Clearly. So...
does this mean
that I'm back on the team?
Eh.
Miss J.
- Of course.
- Okay, yay.
- But now, I have given the solo to Skyler.
- No, no, it's totally fine.
I just want to dance.
For Pulsar.
Come here.
- Welcome back.
- Thanks. Feels good to be home.
Everybody,
listen up.
I am happy to announce
that Maya is back on the team.
Thank God. We missed you.
- Does this mean she's doing the solo?
- No.
No, Skyler's still doing the solo,
but I have made a slight change.
I'm going to have Maya and Tosha
do the breakout routine.
- But that's my part.
- Not anymore.
- How can you do that? She wasn't even here...
- Nia, don't.
You have caused enough
trouble for a lifetime,
and if you think I haven't figured
out that you've been playing us,
then you're an even
bigger fool than I was.
Now step back in that line before I change my
mind and give you what you really deserve.
Mmm.
Everybody,
places from the top.
Coming to you live from Atlanta
for the 10th Annual
USA Dance World Competition.
Now, in just a few moments, this place
will be overflowing with thousands of fans
from far and wide for the competition.
I see you ran back
to your little crew.
- More like I came home.
- Mmm.
I really hope I get to go up
against you in that solo battle.
Keep wishing.
I'm not even doing a solo.
Then who is?
She is.
I remember you.
I whupped that ass in the club.
And Jada wants you
to go up against me?
Is she tryin' to lose?
- Bye, Eva.
- Oh.
- Good night.
- Round two? See you later?
- Bye.
- You want it again?
- Isn't camouflage a little last year?
- I think that red isn't in.
Nice outfits.
Can't stand that bitch.
Hey, don't let her get inside your head.
We're good. We're good.
Forget about them.
Seriously.
You know, it's not too late
to back out now.
- What is your problem?
- Nia, go stretch. Seriously?
Okay, people, hundreds of crews
have competed for spots,
but only 20 teams were chosen to compete in
the sickest dance competition in the country.
Y'all ready to battle?
Let's go!
Welcome to the stage Pulsar!
That's my daughter, Tosha.
She's amazing.
One, two...
That was sick.
Ladies and
gentlemen, Atmasphere!
♪ Party plan
Push that system ♪
♪ Bring the heat
So the whole world listen ♪
♪ Party plan ♪
♪ Party plan
Push that system ♪
♪ Bring the heat
So the whole world listen ♪
♪ Party plan
Push that system ♪
♪ Bring the heat
So the whole world listen ♪
♪ Party plan
Push that system ♪
♪ Bring the heat
So the whole world listen ♪
♪ Party plan
Push that system ♪
♪ Bring the heat
So the whole world listen ♪
♪ Party plan ♪
♪ Push that system ♪
♪ Bring the heat
So the whole world listen ♪
♪ Party, party, party, party
Party, party, party, party ♪
♪ Party, party, party, party ♪
♪ Party, party, party
Party, party ♪
♪ Party plan
Push that system ♪
♪ Bring the heat
So the whole world listen ♪
♪ Party ♪
♪ Party plan
Push that system ♪
♪ Bring the heat
So the whole world listen ♪
♪ Party plan
Push that system ♪
♪ Bring the heat
So the whole world ♪
♪ Listen ♪
Our judges
have narrowed down
the competition to four crews,
and they are:
Atmasphere!
Hot Ice!
The Future Kingz!
And...
Pulsar!
Yo, I'm not even gonna lie.
Eva picked up some of my moves
while I was over there.
How am I supposed to beat
those moves?
Go out there and lay
your killer move on her.
- What move is that?
- You know what I'm talkin' about.
- The one Mom calls your chicken spaz attack. That one.
- Yeah.
- Mom hates that.
- You've seen that before, right?
I don't care
if she hates that dance.
You go out there and take it to the
next level and win us this competition.
- Are you sure?
- I am 100-percent positive.
This is your moment.
You got this.
- Okay. Right.
- You got it.
Come on. Come on, come on.
You got it.
Close up, Sis.
- Come on.
- Get it. Come on.
I present to you
the solo battles.
Are we ready?
Let's go!
♪ De-de-de-de-deko ♪
♪ OG Parker ♪
♪ Pop a perky just to start up ♪
♪ Pop two cups of purple
Just to warm up ♪
♪ Two cups, drank ♪
♪ I heard your bitch
She got that water ♪
♪ Splash, drip, drip
Whoo, splash ♪
♪ Slippery
'Scuse me, please me ♪
♪ I'm up, oh, believe me
Believe me ♪
♪ Get beat
'Cause I'm flexin' Raris ♪
♪ You can bet on me ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ I pop two cups of purple
Just to warm up ♪
♪ Two cups, drank ♪
♪ I heard your bitch
She got that water ♪
♪ Splash, drip, drip
Whoo, splash ♪
♪ I pull up Diablo
I pull with models ♪
♪ I give her
Her first Philippe ♪
♪ We goin' full throttle
She swallowed the bottle ♪
♪ I'm all over her ovaries ♪
♪ I gave her some dollars
I Gucci'd her collar ♪
♪ Now she can't get over me ♪
♪ She want a dose of me ♪
♪ Just hop in the Ghost
With me ♪
Go! Go! Go! Go!
♪ Everything I do super huge ♪
♪ I don't do miniature ♪
♪ I'm the hottest thing
Around here ♪
♪ Check your temperature ♪
I've seen that Eva girl compete before.
She's good.
All right! Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
♪ Let me get it like ♪
♪ Hit it ♪
That's right!
Hit it!
♪ Hit it, hit it ♪
♪ Let me get it like ♪
That's my daughter!
We got this!
- That was crazy!
- Amazing!
Whoo!
Oh, man, oh, man!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the judges have spoken.
Your 2018
USA Dance World champions,
from Atlanta, Georgia,
from the Honey Daniels
Dance Studio, it's Pulsar!
- Give it up for Pulsar!
- Yeah!
Yeah! We did it! We did it!
Yeah!
Yeah, girl.
We good. We good.
Mmm.
Congrats, Mom.
This was all you, Sis.
Go find our trophy.
Go find our trophy, Sis.
I'm proud of you.
I'm proud of you too.
Looks like
we're all winning here!
Good job, babe.
Hey, Miss J, they're asking for you.
Come on. Let's go.
Thank you. You really believed in me
even when I didn't believe in myself.
Maybe I should just, like,
not be so hard on you.
You know? Like, I know
just, like...
♪ Sometimes I'm
like A whisper in a riot ♪
♪ But I grow stronger
Keep believing in me ♪
♪ Say you're believing
You're believing in me ♪
♪ You're believing
♪ Say you're believing
You're believing in me ♪
♪ You're believing
Subtitles by explosiveskull
♪ Still holding tight ♪
♪ Through every fright ♪
♪ 'Cause sometimes
I can see through the echo ♪
♪ Oh, every day ♪
♪ Always the same ♪
♪ Until you take a step
And let go ♪
♪ You told me that the shade's
Turning brighter ♪
♪ But I don't know how ♪
♪ You showed me every heart
Is a fighter ♪
♪ Our time is now ♪
♪ I know that we can go higher ♪
♪ If we keep our faith
If we keep our faith ♪
♪ Sometimes I'm like
A whisper in a riot ♪
♪ But I grow stronger
Keep believing in me ♪
♪ Say you're believing
You're believing in me ♪
♪ You're believing
♪ Say you're believing
You're believing in me ♪
♪ You're believing
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I got a couple questions
Though ♪
♪ If it was you and I
How high could we go? ♪
♪ Elevate the stars
That's climate control ♪
♪ 'Cause these BPM's
Got us losin' control, oh ♪
♪ Are you above average? ♪
♪ I could see a picture
With some karats in it ♪
♪ Whenever
I-I-I-I Hear that song ♪
- ♪ The way that beat is bangin' Turns me on ♪
- ♪ Come on ♪
♪ Swayin' back and forth
With nowhere to go ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ Can you feel it, baby? ♪
- ♪ Can you feel it? ♪
♪ Oh, never let me go ♪
♪ The night is young ♪
♪ I'm in your arms ♪
♪ Do you really wanna
Spend tonight alone? ♪
♪ My body's here ♪
♪ Slip me anywhere ♪
♪ Before this song is over ♪
- ♪ Take me away ♪
- ♪ Okay ♪
- ♪ I wanna lose myself ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ In the moment ♪
♪ In the music ♪
♪ I wanna lose myself ♪
♪ In the feelin' ♪
♪ Can't control it ♪
♪ Everybody say ♪
♪ Make it, make it last ♪
♪ Make it, make it last
Make it pure ♪
Make it last ♪
♪ Make it, make it pure ♪
♪ You can feel it
In the air tonight ♪
♪ That spice
I'm 'bout that bounce ♪
♪ That groove
That makes you wanna move ♪
♪ Turn it up now ♪
♪ But you won't get
Enough of this ♪
- ♪ But you won't even Mutt with this ♪
- ♪ Come on ♪
♪ Beam me up
Tell that DJ "Yo, wassup?" ♪
- ♪ Ah, she do it Like a quarterback ♪
- ♪ Huh? ♪
- ♪ I caught it Yeah, real fact ♪
♪ She is on my mind all day ♪
♪ So I'm at the bar chillin'
Singin' kumbay-ay, eh ♪
♪ And she keeps lookin'
This way ♪
♪ Captures my heart
Every move that she makes ♪
♪ She moves to the beats
That's consumin' the place ♪
♪ Let's live for tonight till
They shut down the place ♪
♪ My-My-My heart is jumpin'
Over the line ♪
♪ The way your body's movin'
Close to mine ♪
♪ Swayin' back and forth
It'll slow me down ♪
♪ I can feel it, baby ♪
♪ Don't ever let me down ♪
♪ The night is young ♪
♪ I'm in your arms ♪
♪ Do you really wanna
Spend tonight alone? ♪
♪ My body's here ♪
♪ Slip me anywhere ♪
♪ Before this song is over ♪
♪ Take me away ♪
♪ I wanna lose myself ♪
♪ In the moment ♪
♪ In the music
Make it last ♪
♪ I wanna lose myself ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ In the feelin' ♪
♪ Can't control it ♪
♪ Everybody say it right now ♪
♪ Make it, make it last ♪
♪ Make it, make it last
Make it pure ♪
♪ Make it, make it last ♪
♪ Make it last
Make it, make it pure ♪
♪ My-My-My heart is jumpin'
Over the line ♪
♪ The way your body's
Movin' close to mine ♪
♪ Swayin' back and forth
It'll slow me down ♪
♪ Slow me down ♪
♪ I can feel it, baby ♪
♪ Don't ever let me down ♪
♪ My body's here ♪
♪ Slip me anywhere ♪
♪ Before this song is over ♪
- ♪ Take me away ♪
- ♪ Let's go ♪
♪ I wanna lose myself ♪
♪ In the moment ♪
♪ In the music
Make it last ♪
♪ I wanna lose myself ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ In the feelin' ♪
♪ Can't control it ♪
♪ Everybody say it right now ♪
♪ Make it, make it last ♪
♪ Make it, make it last
Make it pure ♪
♪ Make it last
Make it, make it ♪