We were promised change,
but it didn't come...
not the way they said
it would, at least.
We wore pins and put stickers
on our cars and bikes.
We forwarded emails to our
friends and did everything we
were supposed to do.
But in the end, nothing
much happened.
Here and
now we start something new,
something better.
We forge together and move
ahead, and we never look back.
I guess we'd
all talked and laughed and
maybe even hoped that
someday it would all
come crumbling down.
We envisioned bankers in
expensive suits sobbing and
wandering through a mist of
thick, falling ash, knees torn
and caked with blood, their
bonuses no longer of any
solace or consolation,
politicians suddenly lost
alone without the support of
their corporate masters,
shivering in homemade foxholes,
drinking their own
pee and trying to gel up their
hair with ox blood.
But even if we believed that
this would someday come, we
couldn't really have ever
prepared for the way it was
when it finally did.
For it matters not how small the
beginning may seem to be.
What is once well-done
is done forever.
I guess I should
have known right off
the bat that Daniel would
eventually break under the
stress and go batshit crazy.
But I managed to keep quiet and
put my faith in him like
everybody else.
It felt good to believe in
something bigger than myself,
and I figured at the very least,
it'd make for a killer
blog entry.
When Daniel
first came to my school in the
second grade, he had this little
ponytail and he wore a
big Hawaiian shirt that
used to be his dad's.
Some of the other guys spit on
him and called him a fag and
made fun of him all the time,
but I liked him all right,
even if he did smell like
a fucking hamster cage.
He brought these fireworks that
he'd smuggled from the
state he moved from, and he kept
them in this shoebox at
his dad's house and
hid them from me.
I never knew where it was.
But he'd pull it out, and we'd
go light stuff on fire in a
wheelbarrow behind his house.
Sometimes we'd pour oil in the
wheelbarrow and then light
fireworks into it.
This one time his dad came home
early, and we had to rush
to put it out.
We almost burnt this tree down,
but it just got singed.
He wasn't ever any good
at sports like I was.
I was always kind of cool at
everything, and I got along
with everybody.
And that's why people wouldn't
pick on Daniel so much,
because they knew he
was my friend.
And if they said anything,
I'd probably
punch them in the face.
What
experience and history teach
us is that people and
governments have never learned
anything from history.
We have been saturated with
unbearable facts, assaulted
every morning with headlines
detailing our complicit
involvement in great
global crimes.
We have seen there is
nothing we can do.
And so our only choice is
to create something new,
something of our own.
Here, we can do what we want.
Here, we can create what
we all desire.
We can create real change.
We, a loose
confederation of strangers and
casual acquaintances, forged a
sacred bond and trust that
pushed forward into a limitless
destiny of hope and
possibility.
Like pure sunlight on the wings
of an aged dove, we
hoped and dreamed of
better days and
beautiful things to come.
- I
- feel really good...
really, really good.
I feel like the heart...
the heartbeat of the earth.
And I'm sure it's not mine.
This is not my own.
Um.
Back when my dad
was a kid, a bunch of guys
tried to start their own cities
in the woods and stuff.
Most of them just wanted to get
naked and roll around in
the mud, or wear overalls with
no shirts underneath, or milk
goats and play banjo
music and stuff.
Most of them moved back to the
cities before too long.
They got jobs at banks and
invented new microchips,
started collecting expensive
bottles of wine and carrying
canvas tote bags to the store,
trying to take a one-minute
shower, as if that was
going to do anything.
Their heads were probably in the
wrong places at the time,
or maybe they weren't dedicated.
Poor planning, perhaps.
This year,
according to "The Wall Street
Journal," the top first five
financial firms are...
These are
in no particular order, but,
uh, flag design, uniform
design, c crest,
credo, group name.
We definitely need a
Wikipedia entry.
An insignia, national anthem,
and a Facebook group as well.
So have we done the
Facebook group?
-Yesterday.
And, uh, we're definitely gonna
need some more pictures
on there, guys.
Beach ball thing, uh, was...
was great.
We got some really good
comments on that.
Anybody else?
A little inspiration?
Yes, Tanner?
- I was thinking maybe for the
name, The Resilience Alliance.
And then for the flag I was
thinking a hand with a fuckin'
eyeball on there.
Big block letters say, Revolt.
I didn't know
the rest of them very well,
except that Lucas was
a cheese dick and
Genevieve had a hot ass.
I tried to get to know them and
make up secret handshakes
and stuff, and this was met with
a pretty good response.
I myself feel
despondent, very despondent,
about the situation
into which we...
Make sure
these are online first, then
the numbers.
We set to work
on our assigned tasks while
Daniel asked that Lucas set up
our online bill pay accounts
and focus primarily on
administrative affairs.
-Did you press One?
-Yeah.
- You still gotta press
One first.
We made certain
all our jet skis and
dirt bikes were converted to
biodiesel and agreed to use
only Dr. Bronner's in
laser printers.
Everyone did their part.
Anna Kate tweeted with a rare
strength and diligence, and
Maggie alphabetized the
anarchist literature,
hole-punching all the loose
pages and carefully placing
everything in a highly organized
three-ring binder.
We were in the best of
spirits and had not
a care in the world.
I tried to get
started on the pledge of
allegiance, originally
structuring it like a haiku,
but it was taking a little more
time than I anticipated.
Daniel told me
once when we were in junior
high that he was born with
this feeling like someday
everyone was going to know his
name, like at some point he
would do something, and they
would all know who he was,
like people would look to him,
and he'd be known as the
source of something great.
- I have the people behind
me, and the
people are my strength.
(FORCEFULLY) I have the people
behind me, and the people are
my strength.
He knew not
from where his fame and
fortunes would come, but he
knew they were out there
somewhere, and he never
let this nagging
feeling leave his side.
-Daniel?
Are we putting these
anywhere special?
-Lucas!
Would you show Genevieve where
we're keeping the plastic
bags, please?
Any news on the Wikipedia page?
Actually, that was rejected.
Yeah, those Wikipedian
guys are assholes.
My uncle, who
was more like my cousin
because he was only five years
older than me, loaned me this
book of scary stories
a long time ago.
And one of them was about a kid
whose parents give him a
dog they bought in Mexico,
but it turns out to
be a rat with rabies.
I asked Daniel if he thought
that ever really happened.
He said he wasn't totally sure,
and then read out of a
little red book he started
carrying in his back pocket.
"The people, and the people
alone, are the motive force in
the making of world history.
The masses have boundless
creative power.
They can organize themselves and
concentrate on places and
branches of work where
they can give full
play to their energy.
They can concentrate on
production in breadth and
depth and create more and more
welfare undertakings for
themselves."
-Quick question.
With whom of the following
pioneers of social change do
you mostly clearly identify?
A, Thomas Jefferson.
B, Leon Trotsky.
C, Marcus Garvey or
W.E.B. DuBois.
D, Salvador Allende.
-Ha.
Yeah.
Gotta guard your stomach, chump.
I'm gonna work your
body every time.
Knockout!
A few years ago
I began to feel pretty
apocalyptic.
But I hesitated to use that...
-Whew.
Daniel said the
best kind of government is
that which governs least, so he
took a hands-off approach
and mostly let the people
do their own things.
But before too long, he became
concerned about waning
dedication and lack of focus.
He found Tanner down by the
creek, spray-painting a
diamond design on the back of
a beautiful six-point buck.
And Genevieve filled his desk
drawers with gallons of
strawberry cream cheese in an
act of solidarity with the
Congolese freedom fighters.
You guys OK?
- When liberty is mentioned, we
must always be careful to
observe that it is not truly
the assertion of private
interests which is thereby
designated.
Huh?
All our lives, we've been told
by society that we are free
when in fact we've been trained
by all interests
except our own.
We've been bent to their will.
And they've convinced
us that is what we
ourselves truly desire.
If a plant cannot live
according to
its nature, it dies.
And so a man.
According to
the World Glacier Monitoring
Service, glaciers across the
globe are continuing to melt
so fast that...
Sergio.
-Sergio?
-Luis-Fernando.
Are you gentlemen ready
to change the world?
-Si.
-Yeah.
Si.
- The falsehoods that men believe
are more culturally
significant than the facts
that they ignore.
And if a plant cannot
live according to
its nature, it dies.
And so a man...
huh?
-OK.
Uh, this way.
Back this way.
Let's...
- And this is something that we
see always throughout time.
We can't escape.
-Yeah!
When I first saw
her, I thought she was a
specter, a phantom or something.
She seemed lighter than air,
and sort of seemed to hover
out over the water.
-Hey.
I like your dog.
Is that a wolf?
What's his name?
Looks like a wolf.
Nadia had a
bad haircut and carried
sharpened bones and stuff,
like some kind of
bold fashion statement.
I don't know if we would have
stopped to talk if we met at
the mall or something.
But it was easy to get
distracted, and her eyes felt
like they had some kind of power
when you looked at them,
like some kind of rays,
like magnetic
rays like razor blades.
-Ooh, crawdad.
The
administration is intensifying
their push to expand government
wiretapping of
online communications, including
email, Facebook
postings, and internet
phone calls.
The administration wants
Congress to require immediate
compliance with wiretap
measures, including government
monitoring of encrypted message
methods on the internet.
The White House...
Some nights,
we stayed up for hours,
arguing about internet
browsers and playing
Chatroulette with sad
dog face masks on.
I was a Firefox man, while some
of the others were more
into Google Chrome.
We ended up talking with this
one guy in Korea or something,
but he kept screaming real loud
about fire in the streets
and stuff, so we nexted
him pretty quick.
on Monday
that the White House did have
unreviewable authority to
target and assassinate
Americans anywhere in the world
if they posed a threat
to the United States.
The...
I picked up some
Spanish on a youth group
trip to Rosarito in the eight
grade, so I made small talk
with Sergio and Luis-Fernando.
They knew a lot about nature,
and they told me about how
certain trees needed the heat
of forest fires in order to
reproduce, like a phoenix from
the ashes or something.
They were pretty cool dudes, and
they gave me the nickname
Cabroncito.
Markets around
the globe continued to
plummet despite indications from
the Federal Reserve chair
that he would lower
interest rates.
The chair describes the
financial crisis as a threat
of historic dimensions.
- Ooh, you missed all the stuff.
(SINGING) They don't
love you like that.
-Hey, how's it been going?
Hey, could I get your number
just to chit-chat, maybe go to
a Red Robin or something?
I like your tunic.
You look great.
It's like Fifth Dimension,
real chic.
Fuck.
I think Nadia was into me as
soon as she saw me.
But she didn't want to seem
too eager, so she kind of
played hard to get.
I guess I liked that OK at
first, but after a while it
got kind of boring, and I just
wanted to cut to the chase.
After we took
care of business, had the
Tumblr page up and running, and
put our logo on a bunch of
bumper stickers and stuff, and
had thousands of followers on
our Twitter feed, our hands
began to grow idle, and we
searched for new ways to express
our dissent and passion.
God!
Before too long, Daniel became
frustrated.
Sergio and Luis-Fernando weren't
working out the way
he'd hoped.
And things weren't coming
together the way
he'd seen in his mind.
He started pacing around a lot
and scratching at his head and
balls like some kind
of nervous tic.
I don't know if anyone else
noticed it, but I had thought
it was kind of strange
and telling.
-Whew.
Ah.
Riot police faced a
crowd of at least 1,000.
Riot police...
- Does anybody know how to
program this fucking thing?
Pelosi was on "Charlie Rose."
with rocks
and Molotov cocktails.
-Fuck.
After the fall
of the Roman Empire, everyone
was running around like chickens
with their heads cut
off, pissing and shitting
themselves and
howling like wolves.
Some people went instantly
blind and lost the use of
their limbs.
They should have seen it coming.
It wasn't like one thing at
once, like a magical button
was pressed on high like they
make it out to seem.
It was a convergence of forces,
overlapping waves of
breakdown built up over time.
Anyone else could have seen it
coming from over a mile away.
All the signs were there.
- Lucas is passing out some
handouts on our new
letterhead.
I'd love to get some feedback
from you guys on this.
We went with Arial Black, all
caps, nice and crisp.
So take a look at those
while we get this
PowerPoint juiced up here.
Hey, Dean?
How about no Virtual Boy,
just for the meeting?
Please put it away.
Thanks, man.
Lucas, excuse me.
Can you give me a hand
over here, please?
Uh, am I doing something wrong?
All right, guys?
Actually, those pretzels were
an after-meeting treat.
If we could just round
those back up again.
Bryce, maybe...
thanks.
All right, we seem
to be having some
technical issues up here.
Uh...
we should have this system fully
operational as of 1100 hours.
Is that good for everybody?
Any possible conflicts?
All right, thanks, you
all, for coming.
We still have the pretzels
to look forward
to, so it'll be good.
All the bills were paid
on time and all
the connections secure.
Routers, plugged, unplugged?
Two or three times.
Well then,
you're going to have to go
into town and have a talk with
these people, because this is
not going to fly.
-Sure.
Tanner climbed
this huge tree, and Bryce
helped him hoist the hang
glider up there.
Tanner took a deep breath and
jumped out, and sailed away
into a ravine a few miles down.
He saw some smoke in the
distance, but didn't think
much of it at the time.
- The light doesn't
even come on.
Lucas came
back washed clean, like a
zombie or a mind gone wrong.
He'd seen things that no
man should ever see...
fire and brimstone, complete
chaos, like the End Times come
to pass before his very eyes.
All the Starbucks were up in
flames, and he saw a group of
kids crucify a German Shepherd
after beating it to death with
a "Guitar Hero" controller.
A Penske truck flipped over an
embankment and landed on a
family carrying sniper rifles
and suitcases full of ground
beef and stuff.
He said there was nothing left.
He said he barely got out alive.
This is just
the sort of thing we've
been planning for, right?
Isn't this why we moved out
here in the first place?
To create something new,
something different?
Maybe this is a push in
the right direction.
Maybe this is fate.
Look around us.
Here, we are safe.
In the woods, we are kings.
Just look at this encampment.
This is our place, my friends.
This is our time.
History does nothing.
It does not possess
immense riches.
It does not fight battles.
It is men...
real, living...
who do all this.
We've lost a fond love,
my friends.
But we've inherited the Earth.
Daniel said he
saw it coming off in the
distance, like a giant
vulture or something.
He acted tough in front of
everyone else, but before he
gave his big talk, he came
crying to me, sobbing and
bawling like a homo.
I felt kind of numb, like I
heard what he was saying and
everything, but it wasn't
really getting through.
It was like a complete and total
shift of consciousness
all in one quick second, like
someone ripped off your head
and showed you your soul to you
while your heart was still
pumping good and strong, a
feeling of complete panic and
terror not because of any
immediate threat or danger but
just because of the vast unknown
as suddenly everything
you ever believed or held true
and dear was proved wrong like
a card trick, like you just
got punked, but there's no
Ashton Kutcher to deliver the
good news, just the slightly
sinister smile of eternity
staring back
straight through you.
- Hey, your sink isn't
working either?
Is it safe to drink that?
-River water?
-Yeah.
-You have to boil it.
-Oh, just boil it, huh?
Should have thought of that.
Yeah, we're gonna have
to make Ramen and
stuff, so good to know.
Sergio and
Luis-Fernando told me they
were going to take off, but
I didn't tell Daniel.
I asked how they were going to
survive out there, and they
said they wanted to find their
girlfriends if they were still
alive and maybe try to figure
their own thing out.
-OK, here's the score.
They made off with a half-bag of
trail mix, couple chewies,
and the remainder of our Wild
Cherry Capri Sun stockpile.
Oh, shit.
-I know.
We should have seen this coming.
That Sergio always seemed
slightly uncommitted to me,
kind of shifty-eyed.
But, uh, you know, more
power to him, right?
If they want to play with fire,
I also have to respect a
risk-taker.
On the home front,
compliments...
- We should boil the
river water.
- Tanner, do you mind passing
out some Dews to
whoever wants one?
The loss of
power and connectivity was
something that none of
us could ever have
truly prepared for.
Genevieve held an informal
funeral for her Facebook page,
her status forever immortalized.
Every Thursday night, when
"Project Runway" would
normally have come on, Anna
Kate's eyes would well up
uncontrollably and she'd shiver
softly in the darkness.
- (SINGING SOFTLY) Life
is a highway.
I want to ride it
all night long.
If you're going my way, I want
to drive it all night long.
I want to ride it
all night long.
- We can probably get maple
syrup from these trees.
-Anything?
-Not yet.
Bryce and Anna
Kate said they'd spotted a
bunch of rainbow trout in the
river, and hoped to try and
catch them in a laundry
basket or something.
But upon hearing this, Daniel
struck a somber tone and said
that the wild fish would most
likely be chock full of
dangerous levels of mercury
and other heavy metals and
toxins and stuff.
He said they should be
avoided at all costs.
- So textile fabrication,
linens and leathers.
Seasonal beautification.
Mat-making.
It would be nice to get
a sundial going.
Foraging.
Trapping.
Hunter-gathering.
-We brought gifts.
-Cool.
I have a few things I'd
like to quickly
discuss with you guys.
If we're going to make this work
out here, we're going to
need to assign people
a specific position.
We're going to need a hunter,
a gatherer, a forager.
We're going to need
a cartographer.
We may also have...
need for...
Jesus.
The power was
gone for good, but all the
appliances were still there.
After a while, it all started
to seem spooky or sort of
haunted to me, like electro
ghosts from a distant past,
like the dishwasher had
a mind of its own.
And like Genevieve's iPad was
silently whispering to me,
hinting at its darkest fears and
deepest hopes that, sadly
but surely, would never
come to pass.
The beginning and end
of all things.
The ability to cast out
all doubts and fears.
OK, OK.
So should I call her?
-No!
This is a really critical time.
If you find yourself
reaching for that
phone, go shoe shopping.
Get your butt in a bubble bath.
- She has to know that
you're not ready.
- So do you think that
I'll lose her?
- Oh, honey, you're not
a total loser.
- (EMPHATICALLY) I said, do you
think that I'll lose her?
-Cut.
Tanner, I'm still not seeing
much change on that last line.
Genevieve, where's the conflict?
We're going for another take.
-Do you think that she'll...
-Mmm.
One night,
Genevieve got a fever and
started shaking and writhing
around on the couch.
We covered her with the Tupac
blanket, and she started
blurting out the names of
different Tom Hanks movies,
sometimes reciting the
plots and stuff in
weird bursts and fits.
She spoke the lyrics of a 4 Non
Blondes song and listed
off, like, hundreds of brand
name candies and snack foods.
It freaked the shit out of me,
like some thing that you just
can't un-see.
And I was so disturbed,
I had to take a walk
deep into the woods.
The true
courage of civilized nations
is readiness for sacrifice in
the service of the state.
The important thing here is not
the personal medals but
aligning oneself with
the universal.
This is a dark time, but it
is surely not a Dark Age.
We are a glowing sea, and soon
we will spread our light.
A revolution is not having a
dinner party or writing an
essay or painting a picture
or doing embroidery.
- I don't know if your grandma
ever does this, but Daniel is
always trying to get me
to rake up, do stuff I
don't want to do.
Can I see your staff thing?
Sweet.
The road to
communal actualization is
paved with intention, attention,
invention,
selection, application,
and computization.
Has anybody seen Dean?
Dean?
-It's like a abacus.
Sorry.
So.
Is that a goat hoof?
That's pretty... sorry.
- Bryce, which of the following
personal weaknesses is most
damaging to collective
enterprise?
A, defiance.
B, waning dedication.
C, demagogic
factionalism/partisanship.
D, private indulgence.
I've been sensing some tensions
within the group.
And to be honest with you, Lucas
is not of much help to
me anymore.
You know some of these people
better than I do.
And in particular Bryce has been
making me uncomfortable.
- I don't think you know Bryce
like you think you do.
- Listen, man, I heard him
calling me penis breath.
-Did he say that?
Yeah.
And everybody was laughing
and slapping fives.
Well,
-I mean, it is kind of funny.
-Yeah, it's kind of funny.
It's nice to see people's
spirits high, but not when
it's at somebody's expense.
It's a shame.
Man has forgotten the most
practiced form of
storytelling, the
oral tradition.
One evening an old Cherokee
chief told his grandson a
story about a battle that
goes on inside people.
He said it's a battle
between two wolves.
One is evil.
It is greed, anger, arrogance,
and jealousy.
The other is good.
It is hope, love, generosity,
and faith.
The grandson thought about
this for a minute.
And then he asked his
grandfather, grandfather,
which wolf wins?
The old Cherokee chief simply
replied, the one you feed.
Days turned to
months, weeks, maybe decades.
Who knows?
Provisions wore thin.
Tensions rose.
Tanner told me that he thought
Daniel was a cock suck, and
that he was ready to mutiny.
He said other people were
feeling the same way.
I didn't know how to handle
the situation, so I just
wandered off to see Nadia again.
I told Nadia
about how stuff was getting
pretty rough back at the camp.
And it occurred to me that
I could maybe defuse the
situation by holding a secret
summit where I could introduce
Nadia to the rest of the group.
I figured her positivity and
optimism might be contagious.
Daniel would have to be
excluded, of course, so
everyone agreed that
we'd keep Nadia's
presence secret from him.
Over time, Nadia offered little
tips as to what could
and could not be eaten and
used in the forest.
- This has a Juicy Fruit
kind of taste.
She knew a
lot of interesting stuff.
She taught us how to collect
morning dew from the leaves of
the mighty Madrone and showed us
where we could dig up these
tubers that tasted sort of
like chili cheese Fritos.
-I'd like another.
-What day is it?
-Thursday, I think.
One by one, people started
doing their own things.
Tanner tried to build a
submarine, and Bryce drew up
plans for a rock garden.
I had this idea that we could
collect condensation in a
satellite dish if we covered
it in old Doritos bags and
buried it a few feet
underground.
I found a frog with a beautiful
pattern on his back.
I named him Rascal.
He liked to hang out on
the Apple TV, and
mostly kept to himself.
-Well, seems pretty good.
I think Mossad uses these.
You remember in the early '90s
when everyone was into those,
like, big sleeping shirts with
the Tasmanian Devil on it?
And he would be, like, wearing
clothes like Kris Kross, like
backwards jeans and
Raiders jerseys?
I bet you have to fend off
the guys all the time.
Where...
where'd you go on
your first date?
Oh.
You probably love your grandma
a lot, huh, seeing as how you
guys live together?
Your grandma must
be quite a lady.
I never had a grandma, but if I
did, I bet I'd be as psyched
on my grandma as you
are on yours.
Time moves
differently when a dim fog
settles between the tallest
trees in the forest and
everything's calm and still.
There's no buzzing or humming
to distract your ears or to
pull away from your attention
from even the smallest details
around you.
Everything seems bigger.
Even the small things grow.
And little details that weren't
there before pop out
at you, and you notice mystery
and wonder in places you used
to look straight through.
The moss seems to move a little
on its own, and it's
suddenly a deeper, more radiant
shade of green.
Everything stops, and you can
get lost in the moment without
any idea about how much
time has just gone by.
You can look up at the sky and
try to figure out where the
Sun is situated.
Or you make your own sundial
using an old remote control or
a twig, or maybe a dried-up
Red Vine or something.
-So we were excited.
We were... we were all excited
to go through.
And then you get in there,
and it's just this
really small woman.
She was probably 75.
But she had her arms stuff here,
and her legs were just
steep coming out.
You know those globes where you
put your fingers and then
the... the electricity follows
your fingers?
They were really tall ones.
Instead of trees, everything was
just really tall, sort of
like branching off electricity.
Like, the arms were
electricity instead of branches.
And this woman was leading us,
but somehow she was walking on
just these little feet.
I was
driving in my brother's old
Volvo station wagon.
And I was going on a long
trip by myself.
And I took off my shoes and put
them in the front seat.
And I got off...
um, pulled off at a gas station.
And I had to use the restroom,
so I wanted to put
my shoes back on.
And, um, at that time the car
turned into my... my brown
skirt, and I didn't notice that
it was any different.
I knew it was the same
sort of vehicle.
Uh, and I needed to find the
shoes, so I reached into my
pocket and I pulled
out the sandals.
Then I was able to go
into the restroom.
Sometimes you
get a feeling like something
is a religious experience, even
when it's not, when it's
something simple, like maybe
you're just washing your car
or trying to focus your eyes
on some far-off image.
It's like this spirit overtakes
you, and suddenly
you're lighter and sort of
slowly rising up through the
freshly-cut grass.
Nothing can touch you,
just in that second.
Sometimes I feel like this
when I wander the halls,
calling out in the darkness,
all alone.
I saw Daniel
standing by himself in the
middle of this clearing.
It looked like he was crying,
but when I asked him what he
was doing, he said he saw the
spirit of this creature that
communicated with him.
He saw different shapes and
forms around him in the woods,
looking after him and
his every move.
-Om.
Om.
- Nobody puts anything away
in this fucking place.
It is impossible to predict the
exact time and progress of
revolution.
It is governed by its own more
or less mysterious laws.
Where the fuck is Dean?
Huh?
Yeah!
-Brr.
Yeah.
What do you think was
better, Game Boy
Color or Game Boy Advance?
Your grandma sure is
a great cobbler.
-Oh.
-Hey, man.
What's up?
-Nothing.
Just, uh, making a stick stack
here, chilling out.
-Cute.
Hi.
Nice to meet you, ma'am.
My name is Daniel.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance
-Daniel, this is Nadia.
-Nadia?
That was a really popular name
for a while there, wasn't it?
What you got?
Ooh.
Hip feather necklace.
That's really ethnic.
Huh?
So Dean, what's going on, man?
Everybody's wondering about you.
Genevieve's nearly worried sick.
- I've only been gone for
half an hour, man.
-Oh.
Well, doesn't really negate
their concerns, does it?
So, Nadia, was it?
Why is it that we haven't
met before?
Uh, she
doesn't go out much, man.
She lives with her grandma.
-Oh.
Gosh.
Well, I don't know what, uh,
Dean's been telling you, but
actually at our camp we
have some pretty cool
things going on.
You look like, uh, kind of arty.
You know what?
Are you into live theater?
Because this weekend, we have
the premiere performance.
A lot of our group members
have been working on it.
Big production.
You should come...
both of you.
Huh?
What do you think?
Will you come?
OK, fantastic!
Great.
You hear that?
Dean, see you this
weekend, then.
Well, hey.
Dean, please try to make it to
dinner because Anna Kate has
been slaving away all day on
this improv Mac and Jack fruit
salad kind of thing.
It's going to be kick-ass.
Be safe, though.
Have fun.
For now, you know, hang, though.
Nadia said
that Daniel made her feel
uneasy, but I assured her that
he was just going through a
rough time and that deep down he
really was a good guy, even
if he seemed like an asshole.
I told her about this time we
filled a two-liter bottle with
our pee and threw it out the
window of my cousin's Bronco
at the side of a Carl's Jr. I
also told her about a time a
few days prior when I found
Daniel all dazed down by the
creek, talking to himself
and weeping silently.
Later we went and swung on this
giant rope swing that
hung over a beautiful waterfall.
That episode
of "Law and Order...
Special Victims Unit" you staged
was truly inspired.
I'm going to be straight
with you.
We have a special visitor
coming to the camp this
weekend, and she's expecting
something big.
I need you, Maggie.
I'm really hoping that you can
commit to putting something
together that's more magical
than anything
we've seen thus far.
Can you do that, Maggie?
-Sure.
-OK.
This is a happy time.
Dean has a new love in his life.
Sure, she's had a rough
go at things.
Her eye is like, I don't know.
But that's all the more
reason to show her
a good time, right?
We've had some rough patches and
we've all made sacrifices.
But we can pull this
off together.
Maggie's on board.
We all have special talents
to bring to the table.
What do you guys say?
We can make this something
magical.
-Hey, guys.
Oh, I'm so glad that
you can make it.
This is really exciting, huh?
OK, why don't you come
in and grab a seat
right up front, OK?
Oh, tickets?
No?
-It's fine.
Just go sit down right there.
Get comfortable, though.
It's going to be a great show.
-Yah!
Yah!
I'm in a world that's dead.
- We will not go quietly
into the night.
We will not vanish
without a fight.
Tonight we fight back.
Tonight we celebrate our
independence day.
-I...
I thought that you guys did
really well because, um...
-What's that?
-I'm freaked out, man.
-Oh, it was just great.
-You were great, by the way.
-Yeah.
- The other people didn't
show up, though.
It left a little
something to be desired.
Am I right?
Come on.
I'm trying
to learn about her grandma.
Do your like plays?
Are you... who's your
favorite writer?
-Excuse me.
Nadia, I have a question.
Everybody is curious.
Everybody wants to know.
Are you Greek?
-What the fuck, man?
What kind of thing
is that to say?
Look, everybody wants to...
everybody's made uncomfortable
by her presence, Dean.
- Uh, I think we're all made
uncomfortable by your
presence, Daniel.
You're fucked up.
You should back off.
-You back off!
You...
-Fuck off.
-Fuck!
Fuck you, man.
Fuck!
Fuck this scene, you
boozy shit rags!
Fuck this whole bullshit
anti-revolutionary cock teasing.
You spoiled, whipped bastard.
Just go home to the fucking
suburbs, you rat shit.
In times of
great struggle and strife,
some people shrink and fall and
falter while others gain
momentum and grow and
get stronger.
We are not victims.
We are not innocent bystanders.
I want to become natural again.
I want to be a force to
be reckoned with.
I want to dump a glass of water
on my head and have a
tree grow out where my
hair used to be.
I want to be strong and
free and young.
I want to be breathe fire and
melt shit with the force of my
sheer will.
I want to stay alive forever,
and I want you here with me as
we watch it build back.
I searched for Daniel
for many days.
I found some bones in a cave and
the remnants of some old
clothing that didn't
belong to him.
I stumbled across a serpent in
the brush, and it spoke to me
in a cool and hollow tone.
It whispered in a soft tuxedo
voice, the damned remain
motionless, and slithered away.
-Hey, man.
Pretty deep out here, huh?
What are you working on?
-Several things.
- Hey, we made some
acorn pancakes.
They're pretty tart, but they're
still really good.
- Tell your ching-chong
girlfriend to keep her filthy
fuckin' hands off my
leather jacket!
-What the fuck, man?
-What?
I've seen her eyeing it.
I've seen everybody
eyeing my jacket.
-All right.
-Hey.
Can't you see that
I'm busy here?
Can't you see that I have many
things to attend to, in my
office, as a professor?
Huh?
As a doctor of science?
Some of us are in pursuit
of a higher truth.
I travel only in the shadows.
And I'm not likely to be seen...
whoo!...
pussyfooting around.
I don't
believe that they knew what
they meant when they called
for a city on a hill.
Because I myself have
constructed a shimmering city
upon a hill.
And atop my city, I sent
lightning bolts raining down
to destroy your satellites.
Your satellite television
reception!
I am unstoppable with my
hammer and my blade!
I have held in the
palm of my hand...
-18 towers.
18 towers!
Adorned with gems and sapphires
and rubies and opals
and tigers eyes and diamonds,
cut flare-cut, heart-cut.
Ribbons!
Ribbons of velvet.
I've taken a
suspension bridge and put it
across a vast chasm.
I bring down trees.
I've seen right through the
inside of an ancient tree
older than Christopher Columbus.
Older than Christopher!
I'm on top of the game.
I'm on top of this right now.
I'm capable.
I build things and move
things with my mind.
I don't need assistance.
I'm a one-man marching band.
I have many proclivities
and hobbies.
I'm a collector of
rare artifacts.
If you have a sarcophagus,
I'll outbid you.
I'm not likely to go down
without a fight.
I'm an unstoppable
force of nature!
And I'm bearing down like an
eagle on a herd of sheep!
I'm a raptor in disguise!
I used to have
this dream that I was standing
on the bank of a river with all
my dearest friends in a
kind of halfway morning light.
We heard a sound in the sky,
and I had this feeling like
something big was coming,
something unexpected but
familiar at the same time,
like I'd always secretly
anticipated this moment since
before the very time I was
born, but I never actually
knew it until now.
A bright light shone,
and something large
fell from the sky.
And then in an instant, a bunch
of other flares and
shapes destroyed the towering
cityscape across the water.
In this instant, everything
changed, but we
weren't scared at all.
It was like we were surfing
on this massive wave of
possibility and destruction
pushing us forward into a
beautiful crest of
a future untold.
We knew not what lay before us,
but with arms outstretched
we pushed ahead into the
gaze of a purple dawn.