(Rattling)
Priest:
God, the father of mercies,
Through the death and
resurrection of his son,
Has reconciled the world
to himself
And sent the holy spirit
among us for the forgiveness
of our sins.
May almighty God grant you
pardon and peace.
I absolve you of your sins
in the name of the father,
The son, and the holy spirit.
(Television playing)
Sal!
(Light snoring)
(Rock music blaring)
(Laughing)
It's the truth.
And all I said was...
(Laughs)
"Get that fat little bastard
the heck out of my rectory."
No, father, no.
Francis.
I was just telling
your mother about
Our little renovation
downtown at the church.
Father Gillespie here
Was kind enough to deliver
my bingo winnings personally.
And in return...
Your dear mother
was kind enough
to offer me
Her very gracious
hospitality.
You take care
of that lovely mother
of yours, Francis.
Oh, Francis...
Last week was
the first time
I'd seen you
in confessional for
quite some time.
Guess I haven't had
that mmm-mm
Mm-mm much to confess.
Oh.
Every day is a struggle
to redeem ourselves
In the eyes of God.
The heart is deceitful
above all things
And desperately wicked.
We're all
soldiers, Francis.
We're soldiers
in the battle
to redeem ourselves
From ourselves.
Now, let me suggest
something to you.
We all need
To plumb the depths of
our own imperfection.
We all succumb
to temptation.
But for those of us
Who struggle
to free ourselves
From the guilt
and suffering
of human frailty,
Perhaps we should ask,
"Have I done all I can
To make it worth
his time to listen?"
Have I truly confronted
my darker side?
Have I given myself cause
"To tell God
of my weakness?"
Now, you have got
to go out there...
And you gotta make
a reason for God
to listen.
You've gotta go into
that confessional
And have something
to say.
Otherwise...
Well, what's the point?
You see what
I'm getting at here,
Francis?
Hmm?
Good boy.
(Television plays)
Francis:
Forgive me, father,
for I have sinned.
It's been...
A month since my last
confession.
About a week ago,
I know it's not an excuse,
But it was crowded,
And I got on the bus
without paying.
Several...
Many times I've had
impure thoughts.
Many times I've acted on them.
And sometimes...
Sometimes I question
my faith...
In God.
Sometimes I feel
like I hate him.
I don't hate him,
of course.
No. I mean, I just,
I wonder if he really
does exist,
How he could let
So many bad things happen?
(Hollers)
(Rock music blares)
(Clanking)
Fuck!
Hey there.
You know,
you got a leak
Somewhere?
It's, uh, you know,
Running down into
number two downstairs.
It's probably
the hot water tap,
'Cause that's
what it usually is
in these buildings.
You get a certain kind
of accumulation in, uh,
You know,
in the pipes,
And the pressure
builds up and bam!
The joints,
they just go.
(Television plays)
(Giggling)
(Boisterous laughter)
You've met Vic,
haven't you?
Your mother
is a laugh a minute!
Oh, God,
I almost forgot
I was on the job.
What job?
See what I mean?
I've asked Vic
to stay for dinner.
Would you go in there
And cook up
something nice,
will you, Francis?
(Television playing)
Hey, there.
I guess I'll be
heading out.
Okay.
Thanks for the food.
That was good.
It was real good.
My compliments
to the chef.
You know, your mom...
That's a special lady.
Yeah.
Real special lady.
Okay, well...
Take it easy.
(Rock music blares)
What the hell is this?
Oh, hey, Mr. haroon...
Hey, yourself!
Get your feet
off my counter!
- I didn't expect you...
- of course you didn't
expect me.
I don't want you
to know I'm coming.
That way I see
when you fuck me.
What you think,
I pay you all day
To watch comic books?
Hey!
Fucker!
Are you alright?
(Faint accent)
I know I shouldn't fight,
But I couldn't let
the little shit
get away with it.
It's a sorry comment
on the world,
I'll tell you that.
Thanks, by the way.
Most people
would've kept walking.
I know you.
Yeah, I've seen you before.
You must live
around here.
I live around the corner.
Right. Gloria.
Francis.
Can I offer you
a cup of coffee
or something?
- No, I don't think so.
- Are you sure?
I feel like
it's the least
I can do.
Yeah. No.
Okay.
Well, thanks again.
Fuck.
Is that you, Francis?
Francis?
(Shouts)
Francis!
What?
Why don't you answer me,
for Christ's sakes?
I could be dying of
a heart attack in here.
Jesus.
What's the holdup
in there?
Francis:
No holdup.
You've done it
again, Francis.
Pass the salt, please.
I didn't know
which one was yours.
Looks like
I guessed right.
I wanted to thank you
for last night.
You already did.
I know.
It just seems
Like it calls
for something more.
Anyway, I was hoping
you'd be my guest
for dinner.
I can't.
My mother,
She doesn't like
to be alone.
Why don't you
bring her along?
I don't think so.
Maybe a short dinner,
then.
Tomorrow night?
Around 7:00?
I'll see you then.
You know the building.
I'm in 706.
(Television plays)
(Knocks)
Hi.
Come in.
How about a glass
of wine?
Okay.
Here you are.
To acts of heroism,
large and small.
- (Glass drops)
- It's alright.
- I'm sorry.
- I'd better go.
- No, please.
It's alright.
I'd really like you
to stay.
I hope you aren't
a big meat fan.
I'm a vegetarian.
A vegan, actually.
What's a ve...
Ve... vegan?
It's someone who doesn't
eat animal products.
No meat, cheese,
eggs, butter,
That kind of thing.
Why?
I guess I'm just
not interested
In perpetuating
the cycle of cruelty.
Animals feel pain
just like we do.
If people only knew
what they do to them
So we can have our steak
and cheese and eggs.
Beautiful creatures
cry for mercy
As the butcher's axe
comes down.
But all they know
is a merciless blow,
And a sad farewell
to a life so dear
Before they land
on a table so grand,
And a fat old man
Can raise
his withered sick hand
And swallow
their smoking,
bloody flesh
And get heart disease
and bowel cancer.
- Do you like it?
- What?
The view.
Oh, yeah.
It's the main reason
I took the apartment.
Somehow I can't bring myself
to close the blinds.
Don't you worry that
ppe-pe-people can see in?
The windows
across the street
aren't high enough.
That's the beauty
of it, really.
So, tell me
about yourself.
Like what?
I don't know, like, um,
How long have you
lived here?
We moved here
when I was 10.
Before that
we lived in a house.
It burnt down.
That must have been awful.
Yeah.
How about your family?
Do you have any brothers
or sisters?
I have a brother.
My mother and father
are dead.
I thought you lived
with your mother?
No.
I mean, no...
I live with my
step-m-m-mother.
Oh.
(Sighs)
(Loud rock music plays)
Gloria:
You're an interesting one.
You don't say much.
But there's something
going on in there.
There's definitely
something going on.
Have you ever thought
that you really
knew someone
And then one day
you discovered
You never really
knew them at all?
You might
have been convinced
that you knew them,
Really convinced.
And then they said
something
Or they
did something...
And you discover
it was all such
an illusion.
I guess it works
the other way around,
too.
You meet someone
who seems very different
And though you
barely know them...
You discover
you might just as well
Have known them
all your life.
Somehow I feel that way
about you.
It's funny, I know,
But you seem
so familiar.
- Sorry.
- Francis?
- I have to go.
- What's wrong?
I have to go.
I'm sorry.
Francis?
Francis, would you please
just hear me out?
I'm sorry
if I offended you.
That was the absolute
last thing in the world
I wanted to do.
You've got to know that.
Sometimes you've got
to trust people.
Sometimes
you've got to have
a little faith.
Sal:
Is that you, Francis?
(Shouts)
Francis!
What?
I've never...
Now, if I were to guess,
I'd venture there was
something different
about you, Francis.
Oh, yes, I would.
Wouldn't you, Vic?
Huh?
He looks about
the same to me.
Oh, no, no, no.
There's something
about him.
I just can't quite
put my finger on it.
I know what it is.
Francis has got himself
a little girlie friend.
Isn't that it, Francis?
A real live
little girlie friend.
Coming and going
at all hours,
Hair combed over
like that.
Don't you play dumb
with me, buddy boy.
You can't fool
your mama.
Who would've thought
you could con some
little slut into it?
I gotta give you
credit for that.
Never underestimate
the desperation
Of the truly desperate.
That's what I always say.
Very p-p-profound.
(Mocking)
Very pro-pro-profound.
I bet that goes over
real big with the chicks.
(Laughs)
- What's this?
- What?
This, right here.
A birthmark.
Looks like Spain.
I don't know
what Spain looks like.
It's a profile of a guy
With a pointy nose,
And a pompadour,
Sort of nibbling on
Portugal, right here.
What is it?
You're pretty,
And you're smart
and you're n-nice.
And I guess
I don't know why
Anyone like you
would want to be with
S-someone like me.
I want to be with you
because I like you.
You're a good person.
And I do want
to be with you.
Believe that.
Francis:
Forgive me, father,
for I have sinned.
It's been a month
since my last confession.
On several occasions I've taken
the lord's name in vain.
I found a quarter
on the floor at work
And I didn't tell anyone.
Many times...
I've had impure thoughts,
And acted on them.
Several times
I've fornicated.
On one occasion,
I fed my mm-mother
cat food.
These are my sins
for which I am
truly sorry.
(Muffled praying)
Woman:
The thought of having
kids right now
Couldn't terrify me more.
I thought that was
your intention from
the beginning.
Of course it was,
but, uh,
A few minor technicalities
prevent it.
I really don't think
They want to hear
about that now, dear.
Ken's semen isn't
quite up to snuff.
His little sailors are dead
long before they hit
open water,
So to speak.
They're poorly motile.
More bharat nutloaf,
anyone?
Thanks, no.
It was delicious.
Francis?
No.
Did anyone hear the story
a couple weeks back
About a couple who kept
their 16-year-old
In a broom closet
from the age of three?
When the police found him,
The mother said
she did it because
Jesus Christ told her to
in a vision.
That is awful.
The atrocities
people commit
in that man's name.
It's unbelievable.
I mean, what relevance
does somebody
like Jesus Christ
Have today, you know,
Except as an excuse
or a crutch
For the uneducated,
the downtrodden,
and the insane?
You got that right, honey.
He died for our sins.
He gave his life
so that we could live.
Why would he do
a thing like that?
- Honey.
- No, really.
Why would anyone
walk to their death
To save a bunch
of nonbelievers?
Because he loved them.
I'm sorry if
I embarrassed you.
No, it was priceless.
Do you really believe
all that stuff
About the father
and the son
and the holy ghost?
I guess.
And the virgin Mary?
Yeah.
You're committing a sin
right now, you know.
I know.
Don't you feel guilty?
Yeah.
You really do,
don't you?
We're very d-different.
Not that different.
(Rock music blares)
You like it?
Yeah.
It's g-good.
It's okra.
I'll make a vegetarian
out of you yet.
(Telephone)
Operator 44.
Are you calling to report
a missing child?
Yes. I mean, no.
I want to report
seeing one.
Can you tell me where
you saw this individual?
I saw her in a photo.
I process photos,
and her picture
Was on a roll of film
someone dropped off.
Do you know this person?
Do you know the name?
I think the name started
with a "j,"
Like Jones.
May I have the salt, please?
Oh, sure.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
(Lighter won't flame)
You gonna tell me
what's going on
Between you two?
Between who?
You and Vic.
I haven't
the slightest idea
What you're
talking about.
You nnn-know
What I'm talking
about.
You think
I can't see it?
- He likes you.
- So what?
He lll-likes you.
And?
He's a man.
Can I help that?
A mmm-man, sal.
And what am I supposed
to do about that?
What?
You got a lot of nerve,
You know that?
What gives you the right?
What gives you the right
to judge me? Huh?
He knows.
He knows who
he's dealing with.
Yes siree Bob.
Don't you worry.
He's got a special place
in hell just for you,
Just for a masturbating,
Faithless little pervert
like you.
You don't think
he knows?
He knows
these filthy hands.
He knows this face.
Put a little mark there
just to remind him.
Better believe me.
He's got your number,
buddy boy.
Just like he got
your daddy's.
Maybe yours too, sal.
What are you
thinking about?
Me?
I don't know.
Nn-nothing.
Nobody's ever
thinking of nothing.
How long have you
been a... a...
A vegan?
I don't know.
About 15 years.
Doesn't it ever
bother you...
You know,
that I'm not?
No.
If it did bother you,
would you tell me?
But it doesn't.
Well, if it did?
If it did bother me,
I doubt we'd be
together, don't you?
(Coughing)
(Coughing continues)
What did...
What did you do
last night?
Nothing much.
I went to sleep
pretty early.
Rr-really?
Yeah, I wasn't
feeling well.
How come?
I was a little
nauseous.
- Why?
- I don't know.
I just was.
You must have
some idea.
Not really, no.
Nobody doesn't at least
have a theory
About why they feel
nauseous.
Well, I don't.
Well...
That's just sss-
Stupid.
Are you feeling
alright?
I feel fine.
You seem kind of tense.
What m-m-makes
You th-think
I feel tense?
I guess I've had a lot
on my mind lately.
My mm-mother's
not feeling well.
I'm sorry to hear that.
It's nothing serious,
I hope.
No, it's just a...
Ff-fistula.
Hmm.
Yeah.
I got you
something today.
Ta-da!
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
I really better go.
My mother.
Okay.
Don't be a stranger.
(Door unlocks)
Shit.
Under that can...
Is the meanest,
filthiest, ugliest rat
You ever laid
your eyes on.
Took a year off my life
just trying to catch it.
Sent poor Vic
in for stitches
Trying to get it
with a hammer.
God only knows
how it got in.
What do you want
m-m-me to...
Do what you want!
Just get it the hell
out of here.
I caught it,
for Christ's sakes.
Careful.
Careful,
he's gonna get out.
Do you wanna do this?
He'll take your hand right off
if you give him half a chance.
(Speaking Spanish)
Waiter:
No, senorita.
- Y Los frijoles?
- Completely vegetarian.
Good. I'll have that.
And a Margarita,
no salt.
Gracias.
Can I ask you something?
Of course.
I was just wondering,
Don't you ever feel
like eating meat?
Not really, no.
There isn't any time
when a piece of meat
Just looks
a little appetizing?
No.
You mean there's
n-n-nothing,
Not anything about
a hamburger,
That appeals to you
in any way, at any time?
Never.
Then you must be lying.
What?
Suppose you were
starving.
Is there something wrong?
Suppose you were starving
and there was nothing else
to eat.
Why do you ask me
these questions?
If you were starving
and there was nothing else
to eat,
And you knew you would die
if you didn't eat it.
No.
You mean to tell me
you'd rather give your life
For a cow, a dead cow?
Francis, why don't you
just tell me what's
bothering you?
What makes you think
there's anything bothering me?
Because I feel like
you're striking out at me.
Just because I question
whether or not
You'd really rather die
than eat a hamburger?
I think I know
how I feel.
I'm not so sure
you do.
I'm not so sure anyone
who calls themselves
a vegetarian
Really knows how they feel.
Deep down, I think
they're the most carnivorous
of us all.
They just deny it harder.
They're the ones who feel
like they have to parade
Their smug,
self-righteous,
Sanctimonious,
holier-than-thou attitude
Before the entire world
Every day of the pathetic
miserable shams
They call lives.
Excuse me.
I don't feel well.
I'm sorry I made
such a scene.
It's something
that's happened
all my life.
The seizures come so rarely
I forget all about them.
Sorry if it was
because of me.
Is everything okay
between us?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm so tired.
Can you give me
an order of, uh...
Plah pa muk,
And some of
that spicy, uh,
Nam prik pow.
Yeah, whatever.
And, uh...
Oh, give me
an order
of that...
Yum moo Yang.
(Sal laughs)
And can, uh...
Yeah...
Lick my dong?
(Laughing)
- Yeah, lick my dong.
- (Laughing continues)
Uh, in orange sauce?
Is that right? Yeah?
Why don't you kiss
my ass, fuckface!
Oh, alright.
Well, fuck you, too!
Yeah, fuck you!
(Both laughing hysterically)
Fuck you, fuck you,
fuck you!
Francis,
how about a drink?
No.
Don't be
such a tightass.
I think
you'd better leave.
Come on, just have a little
drink. I'll pour you one.
I said I think you
b-b-better leave.
- Wait a minute
- why don't you have a drink?
Are you deaf?
No.
Oh, for Christ's sake
Then get out!
We're just having
a little party.
I mean, really.
Well, it's over now.
I thought we were,
you know, buddies.
- What?
- I thought we were
friends, you and me.
In that case,
M-m-maybe you can tell me
what you've been doing
In there for
the last six weeks.
Where?
- The bathroom.
- The bathroom?
That's complicated,
you know.
It's a leaky pipe!
How complicated is that?
Well, if you want,
I'll show you.
Get out!
- Wait a minute, I mean...
- I said, get out!
You don't have to show Vic
the writing on the wall.
He can see it.
(Hollers)
Hey!
You don't say much about that
girlie friend of yours, do you?
I'm beginning to wonder
if she really exists.
You gotta be a regular
chip off the old block.
(Telephone rings)
Hello.
Gloria:
Francis?
Hi.
Hi. What are you doing?
Nn-nothing much.
I thought if you weren't
doing anything
Maybe you can come over
for dinner.
- I don't think so.
- Oh.
My mm-mother,
She's not feeling well.
I'm sorry.
Is she okay?
Yeah. Fine.
It's just those, uh...
Those fistulas,
they're pretty tricky.
What exactly is
a fistula?
It's a kind of
ho-hole.
A kind of infected hole.
Can I do anything to help?
No.
Well, call me when you can.
- Okay.
- Goodnight.
Gg-goodnight.
Hi there.
(Shaking doorknob)
I say, hello?
Hi.
Are you a friend
of Gloria's?
Yeah.
She wanted me to pick
something up for her.
Looks like you got
the wrong key, mate.
I've had some trouble
around here lately.
Seems that, uh,
Former tenants,
what they do is come back,
Use their old keys
and help themselves.
Pretty cheeky, eh?
Yeah.
So I've had to change
all the locks.
It's funny she didn't
tell you about that.
I guess she must've forgot.
Yeah.
Yeah, she must have.
Well, thanks.
Here, just a minute!
Hey!
(Coughs)
Must be difficult
going on
When you're not
feeling yourself.
On stage I banish reality
through an act of sheer will.
Marilyn is performing
in her own one person show.
What is it called
again?
"Ich bin Marilyn,"
Based on the writings
of the great Latin
American surrealist,
Dieter ulbricht.
He doesn't sound
Latin American.
But he's Argentine,
of course.
A great artist.
And a tremendous azhole.
A what?
An azhole, an azhole.
What's that?
A shithead.
Oh, asshole.
Of course.
After the violent convergence
of motherhead and fatherwomb,
I emerge naked
Into the stark solitude
of human existence
Only to be
finally devoured
By a swarm of
carnivorous butterflies,
Who spread everywhere
Their message
of eternal light and Booty.
I'm sorry, what?
Booty. Booty.
Oh, beauty.
Of course.
Still hungry?
Have some of that.
It's yellow squash
stuffed with red pepper.
I made it last night.
Want me to warm it up
for you?
I'd better be
getting back.
But it's so early.
I know.
My mm-mother...
How is the fistula?
Better.
Still bad, but better.
(Filing)
(Telephone rings)
Hello.
Gloria:
Hi.
I'd like to see you.
I can't.
My mother is still
pretty sick.
Looks like that
f-f-fistula
Has grown a little.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
So I don't think
it's such a good idea.
Okay.
- Francis?
- Yeah?
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine.
I guess I've...
I've been a little
preoccupied.
(Coughing)
(Rock music blaring)
Yes, sir?
I want to develop these.
Okay.
- The name?
- Jones.
One set or two?
One.
Matte or glossy?
I don't care.
Daytime phone.
Sir? Mr. Jones?
(Festive talking)
(Knocking)
May I help you?
Francis?
- What's the matter?
What's the matter?
I'll show you what!
There's absolutely
no hostility here.
Get back!
No hostility, right?
I said, get back!
You hypocrites!
Just who do think
you're fooling?
Nn-not me,
that's for sure.
Nn-not me!
- Francis.
- Stay back!
I know all about...
I know all about
your little s-s-secret.
You didn't bother
inviting me
To this party, did you?
You won't go anywhere
because of your mother.
Oh, right. Right.
Maybe there's
another reason.
Maybe it's because
you were afraid
I'd discover
Your little secret.
Some vegetarian you are.
- What's this?
- Bamati herb rolls.
- And this?
- Tabouli salad.
And this?
Ummm...
Eggless artichoke
frittata.
(Panting)
Woman:
Oh, my God!
Look at what you've done.
Woman:
Are you happy now?
I hope you're proud
of yourself.
Nice work, pal.
(Startled gasps)
(Telephone rings)
(Continues to ring)
(Knocking)
Keep your shirt on
For the bleeding sake
of sweet Jesus Christ
in heaven!
Do you know that
one of these days...
The sun is gonna
explode?
Gonna go up like a,
A frickin' dime store
firecracker.
It's gonna go supernova.
Fucking gonna fry us
to kingdom come.
Who gives
a tinker's toot?
I'll be long dead.
What if you're
reincarnated?
You know, like as a goat
or something?
Hey...
If I'm reincarnated,
I ain't coming back
as an old goat.
I guess not.
You're about
as far from a goat
as I can imagine.
That's right, ma'am.
I can't imagine
you as a goat.
Not unless
I was a he-goat,
And you were
the prettiest
little goat
In the whole
fucking herd.
(Wheezing laugh)
Hey!
(Hollers)
Ahh! Fuck!
You little fucking
cunt bitch!
(Groaning)
(Grunting)
Who...
Are you...
Calling...
A cunt?
(Telephone rings)
Francis?
Francis, I wish
you'd talk to me.
I wish you would try
and communicate.
I'm not sure
what's happening to you.
But I'm afraid.
I'm afraid for you.
I want to help you.
If you'd only let me.
I love you.
(Hangs up)
(Knocking)
Listen, Francis,
Something stinks to high heaven
in this place.
I can't smell anything.
You can't smell that?
(Sniffs)
That stink?
Like something died.
Jesus Christ,
I think I'm gonna vomit.
It kind of smells like
it's coming from up here.
Well, I'll look around.
(Gagging)
Sal:
Smells like a hog farm.
What are we gonna do,
Francis?
What are we gonna do?
I don't know.
Well, we gotta do something.
Maybe we should call
the police.
No, no, no, no!
Then what?
Francis...
I didn't kill him.
What?
What did you say?
It was God's will.
God's will?
Is that what it was?
And just what do you think
God's will is, sal?
I'll tell you what it is.
He wants to make us pay,
just like he made daddy pay.
That's God's will.
No, no, no.
Whom he would destroy,
he first makes mad.
No!
Do you think it matters
how much we pray?
Do you think
it matters how much
We get down
on our knees and beg?
No!
God loves us.
- No, he doesn't!
- Yes, he does!
He's
a spiteful, mean,
Vengeful f-f-fucker!
And he never,
ever, ever forgets!
Oh, boy.
Oh, boy, will you ever
pay for this!
I'm ashamed
to call you my son!
I'm not your son!
You can deny it
all you want.
Mama's dead, sal.
She's dead!
No! No, no!
You loved mama, sal.
You loved mama more
than anything.
But God took her,
didn't he?
- Didn't he?
- Daddy took her!
He made daddy take her!
Daddy was bad.
No, he was sick!
God made him sick!
- Because daddy was bad!
- He wasn't bad!
Then why did God
make him sick?
Why?
Who knows why?
Who knows why he decided
to ruin our lives?
But you know what
I say to that, sal?
You know what I say?
I say God damn him.
God damn God.
Damn the father,
damn the son.
No!
God damn the holy
fucking ghost!
Fuck God, sal!
Fuck him!
Something's lost
that can't be found.
Please, Saint Anthony,
look around.
Saint Anthony.
Something's lost
that can't be found.
Oh, please, Saint Anthony,
look around.
(Coughing)
(Bell sounds)
(Clicking through channels)
Sal:
Hey, buddy boy!
Who ever thought
it would come to this?
Huh?
Who would've guessed it?
Would you tell me that?
Huh?
What did we do
to deserve this?
We aren't bad.
Are we?
We didn't do anything
to anybody.
Did we?
(Shouts)
Something's lost
that can't be found.
Please, Saint Anthony...
Look around.
Something's lost
that can't be found.
Please, Saint Anthony,
look around.
Something's lost
that can't be found.
Please, Saint Anthony,
look around.
(Sobbing)
Something's lost
that can't be found.
Please, Saint Anthony,
look around.
Something's lost
that can't be found.
Oh, please, Saint Anthony,
look around.
(Sobbing hysterically)
We've looked up high,
we've looked way down.
I've looked all over
this lousy town.
Excuse me.
(Rock music playing)
(Faint chatting)
Guests:
Ooh! Wow!
- That's nice!
- That's just gorgeous!
(Silence)
Noooo!
Hi.
Where is he?
- What are you talking about?
- Get inside.
Nn-now!
- Where is he?
- Who?
You must've
finished him off
P-p-pretty fast.
What are you
talking about?
- Where did you put him?
- Who?
Him!
Francis, I really don't know
what you're talking about.
In the kitchen.
Nn-now!
Francis, you're sick.
You need help.
Oh, I'm sick.
I'm the sick one.
That's good.
At least I don't
eat people.
Where have you gotten
these ideas?
I've ss-seen it!
There, in the window!
- You've been watching me?
- Yes!
You didn't bet on that,
did you?
No.
You must think I'm
P-p-pretty stupid
to actually believe
You could've
cared about me.
(Panting)
I love you, Francis.
I know you don't
believe that.
I know you never have.
But I do,
and I always will.
I've tried to be
as honest with you
as I can.
It's been hard,
you know, because,
I care what
you think of me.
But I've tried.
And I just hope,
I just hope you
can believe that.
It's so hard
to see you like this.
He wants to make me crazy.
Who does?
God.
(Sniffs)
It's true.
I've watched you.
But what I saw
wasn't real...
Because he hates me.
He shows me things.
Things that aren't real.
Bad things.
But I don't care.
Because if God
doesn't love me...
At least I know
that y-y...
You do.