[Music playing]
[Phone ringing]
Shit.
Hello?
Wade?
Yeah, hold on.
Wade, you got a phone call.
WADE: OK, I'll be
out in a minute.
Who is it?
Didn't ask.
Hello?
Oh, hi!
Hey.
Hey, man, where have you been?
Anne's gonna be here any minute.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I was talking to
preacher man, Bob.
And I just kinda
lost track of time.
So did you get it?
Yeah, yeah, here it is.
Wow.
Anne is gonna be knocked
out when she sees this.
Yeah, the best one my
uncle had in the store
In your price range.
Great.
Here's what I owe you.
Oh, thanks
So you think she'll say yes?
I have a feeling she will.
Yeah, you know what
preacher man, Bob, says.
Never sign the way of
love or the work of God.
Here she comes.
You better go.
Oh, yeah.
Hi, Annie.
Hey, Ken.
Hi, Brian.
I got that movie you wanted.
Cool.
[Music playing]
(ON TV): Wanna
eat dinner, Jason?
I'm real hungry.
You're hungry?
I'm starved.
Oh god, I'm starved.
I could eat anything right now.
Well here.
Try a piece of this candy.
(SINGING) Gonna
have a good time!
You know it!
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, guess what?
My sister's coming to
town next Saturday.
That's only a week away.
She'll be staying with my mom.
Uh huh.
Wade, remember how
earlier we were talking,
And how Annie was coming
over this evening,
And we're going to spend
some time alone together?
Oh, hey man, that's cool.
I'll be in my room
playing Atari.
You won't even know I'm here.
I swear.
Good.
(ON TV): You hungry?
I just got a little [inaudible].
(SINGING) Na, na, na!
How about some wine?
OK.
(SINGING) Gonna
have a good time!
Hey, hey, hey!
(ON TV): [inaudible].
Well that's OK.
[Inaudible]
Annie.
Yes, Brian?
I love you.
I love you too, Brian.
(SINGING) It's called survival!
Oh, hey.
Sorry to bother you guys.
I just remembered I
have to do some laundry.
I don't have anything to wear.
I mean nothing.
I have been wearing this
same shirt for three days.
Hey, I love this movie.
This movie is great.
It doesn't have any
violence in it or anything.
Well it does have
some violence in it.
But it's crucial to the plot.
It's just a good
movie, you know.
Wade?
It's OK.
I won't bother you anymore.
I promise.
[Singing] Only the strong
will survive, sweet mama!
I am so sorry.
He promised he would
leave us alone.
I don't think he'll
bother us anymore.
Do you?
I really can't stand the way
he never pulls his pants up.
I swear to god, I get
physically ill looking at that.
He won't bother us.
(ON TV): [inaudible].
(SINGING) It's called survival!
Only the strong will
survive, sweet mama!
You know what I'm talking about!
It's called survival!
Sorry, I dropped some underwear.
[Singing] Na, na, na.
Gonna have a good time.
Hey, hey, hey.
I should be in the mood
again in a few seconds.
I think I will be, too.
I think.
(ON TV): OK.
So the master plan
would be [inaudible].
OK.
OK, I'll do it.
Well go do it.
I'll be watching.
OK, Ill go do it.
I'll do it.
[Inaudible]
(SINGING) Come on in.
Baby, take your clothes off.
Come on in, baby.
Hey, uh, Brian?
What, Wade?
You want me to throw any of
your laundry in with mine?
No need for us to do any
more loads then we have to.
Gotta protect the ozone
layer and all that.
No, Wade.
I can do my own laundry.
Are you sure?
It's no problem.
No, I'm sure, Wade.
What about you, Annie?
All righty.
Oh, my back.
I need to get a new chair
to play Atari in. (SINGING)
Na, na, na.
Gonna have a good time.
Uh, Brian, I'm really
not in the mood right now.
Oh, Annie, please.
I had this special
evening all planed for us.
Well you should have
planned for your roommate
Not to be here.
I tried to get him out.
But he never goes anywhere.
He doesn't have many friends.
I know.
It's just that I'm really not
feeling so good right now.
I think I'm going to
be sick to my stomach.
I think I should go home.
I might throw up.
No, Annie, please, no.
You want to go out?
We can go out and
eat at a nice place.
I wanna spend this
evening with you.
There's something
I wanna ask you.
I don't know.
I think it was the
sight of his buttcrack
That many times in one evening.
I'm feeling really sick.
Annie, please.
I really have something
I wanted to ask you.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Can you ask me then?
I love you, Brian.
I love you, too.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
(ON TV): You feeling OK?
Totally fine.
Never better.
Have fun.
Enjoy.
[Inaudible]
(SINGING) Only the strong
will survive, sweet mama!
Hey Annie, are you
sure you don't want me
To wash your underwear for ya?
Hey, where did Annie go?
She had to go home, Wade.
Oh.
(ON TV): Get out of my room!
What are you doing?
What have you done!
OK, master Jason.
I love this part.
Watch this.
(ON TV): And people eat these
[inaudible] bacteria in it.
So the master plan
will be perceived.
[Inaudible]
[Laughing]
(SINGING) This
is it, this is it.
This is life the one I got.
So just... just eh.
Morning, Brian.
Boy, do I feel great.
There is nothing,
and I mean nothing,
Like a beautiful, bright,
sunny Sunday morning.
I'm going to go take a shower
and enjoy this awesome day.
Really?
You have plans for today?
No, not really.
Probably just play
Atari all day.
Maybe open up the window.
Enjoy the fresh air.
Ah.
What a great day!
Yeah.
(SINGING) This is it.
This is it.
Ba ba loo!
If you have it!
[Music playing]
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
Brian.
Hey, Ken, what's up?
Hey, how'd things
go last night?
She say yes?
Y'all set a date yet?
No, things did not go as
smoothly as I had hoped.
What?
She turned you down?
Nah, it's not that.
I never got the
chance to ask her.
Things were going great.
And then guess who
happened to ruin it?
Buttcrack.
Yeah, Wade.
I swear, I am really
starting to hate him.
I am counting the days
till the semester is over.
And then, he is out of here.
I'm gonna get myself
a decent roommate.
Hell, Annie can move in.
So what did he do?
Wouldn't he shut up?
Shit.
Him and his damn butt.
Let me ask you something.
Is it so hard for a guy to
keep his pants pulled up?
I mean, the least he
could do is wear a belt.
Yeah, well, it
could be he doesn't
Realize he has a problem.
You know, preacher
man, Bob, always
Says he with the
problem is usually
The last to know about it.
Yeah, I suppose I
could talk to him.
Tell him he has to do
something about that.
Oh, yeah.
That wouldn't hurt.
I would like to have Annie
come over once in a while
Without being grossed out.
I mean, what's the
point in having
A house if you can't have
your lady over once in awhile.
I suppose I could visit
her at the dorm room.
But how much privacy
can we get there?
Yeah, tell me about it.
So you gonna pop the
question tonight?
If I can get her
over here I will.
I want everything
to be just right.
Nice wine.
Nice dinner.
Everything, you know?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I don't know if she'd
take another night of buttcrack
In my way, though.
Listen, don't worry about that.
Invite Annie over.
And I promise, I'll
get Wade out of there.
I'll take him to a
movie or something.
Really?
Cool.
Tell buttcrack I'll be
over there about 6 o'clock
To pick him up.
Cool.
All right.
See ya.
Bye.
Boy, do I feel all
fresh and clean.
Hey, Wade.
I was just talking
to Ken on the phone.
He said tonight he's going
to take you to a movie.
Ken?
What movie?
And why?
I don't know.
Any movie you want, I guess.
Sounds, kind of, weird to me.
Look, he ain't gay or nothing.
He just wants to go to movie.
You know, male
bonding and stuff.
Just go.
Well, OK.
But I get to choose the movie.
Yeah, sure.
Whatever.
(SINGING)There's a
rock n roll demon.
And he's coming for your soul.
I'm a rock n roll demon and
I'm coming for your soul.
God.
(SINGING) Coming for your soul.
I'm a rock n roll demon.
Hey, Brian.
I just thought of something.
What?
My sister's coming
into town next week.
Do you want anything from her?
I'm sure I don't, Wade.
Are you sure?
You know she did
me up real good.
I really don't need to
know these things, Wade.
No, I'm talking about voodoo,
witchcraft, that kind of thing.
She studies it.
You see and she cast
this spell on me.
And now I get really good
grades in school the time
And never have to crack a book.
And it's great because it leaves
more time for Atari that way.
Could she put a spell on you
to make your pants stay up?
That's all I really need.
No, seriously.
She could cast a spell
on Annie that would
Make her fall in love with you.
And then, she wouldn't
be running out on you
All the time.
Come on, you'd like that.
Wouldn't you?
I really don't think I
need anything like that.
Well it don't cost nothing.
She cast the same spell
on our cousin, Vernon.
And now he's married to this
girl with really big tits.
I mean, they're freaking huge!
And all it takes are some tears
from a pregnant with pink eye
And some vanilla extract.
But you can get that anywhere.
Wade, no!
OK.
All right.
But if you change your
mind, just let me know.
I'm going to go play more Atari.
OK.
(SINGING) Na, na, na,
gonna have a good time!
Jesus, Atari.
Get with the times.
What?
Nothing.
[Atari sounds]
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
Wade?
Yeah, hold on.
Wade, it's for you.
Who is it?
I don't know.
Probably your sister.
OK.
Hello?
Oh, hey, sis.
Oh no, everything's great.
Yeah, that was Brian.
Oh no, we're great friends.
We're just like brothers.
Yeah, I asked him.
No, he said he didn't want it.
Well yeah, I can ask him again.
Yeah, hold on.
Hey, hey, Brian.
No.
Uh, no.
He say's he's OK.
Yeah, so you're still
coming up on Saturday?
Oh, you're driving.
Oh, OK.
Well hey, I guess
I'll see you then.
OK, bye.
She says she's driving.
How long do you think
something like that would take?
Where's she coming from?
Louisiana.
Louisiana to Virginia?
That'll take a while.
She says she'll be
here on Saturday.
I'll probably go spend the
weekend at my mom's next week.
Hey Wade, you go
ahead and do that.
It won't be the same
around here without you.
But you do what you gotta so.
I think you and my
sister should meet.
I think you'd really
like each other.
I really do.
It's almost 6 o'clock.
Ken will be here soon.
You ready to go?
I'm ready.
I know exactly what
movie I want to see, too.
I still get to pick
the movie, don't I?
I mean, Ken wont
give me a hard time
About it will he because Hackman
Four just came out on Friday.
And I really want to see it.
And I was reading about it.
And in the first three, he
killed guys with a shovel.
In this one he kills
guys with a rake.
And I really want to see it.
I'm sure he won't mind.
[Knocking]
That's him.
Come in!
Hey.
Hey, Ken, are you ready?
I want to go see Hackman Four.
Is that OK?
It just came out on Friday.
Yeah, I been waiting a
long time to see that one.
Yeah, me too.
And you know, in
this one, he kills
Guys with a rake, not a shovel.
Oh, really.
Boy are the really developing
his character, aren't they?
Yeah, come on.
Let's go.
I don't want to
miss the previews.
All right.
[Music playing]
He's gone.
Now if Annie would just hurry.
Are we alone?
I promise you the
evening is all ours.
Good.
Sorry about last night.
I didn't mean to run out on you.
It's just that I was
feeling really sick.
Last night was last night.
Tonight is tonight.
Would you care for some wine?
Sure.
So what was this question you
wanted to ask me last night?
All in due time, Annie.
All in due time.
Cheers.
(SINGING) In a shanny shack
down by the railroad track.
That's where I met you baby.
You looked so sweet.
Wade, you want
to go get a drink
Or something after the movie?
Yeah, sure.
Hey, you moving
back to Louisiana
There with your sister?
I don't know.
It all depends on whether
Brian's willing to extend
My lease or not.
I really like it here.
Well you know, man.
That's the thing.
Brian is, kind of,
wanting Annie to move in.
That's OK, too.
I can always find a
new place to live.
Hey, I got to ask you question,
you know, just as a friend.
I hope you're not
offended or anything.
Man, you're not coming on
to me or anything, are ya?
This isn't going to
turn weird, is it?
Oh man, I always
knew you were gay.
What?
Gay?
I'm not gay.
Jeez, I just wanted
to know something.
Are you sure you're not gay?
I mean, the way
you talk and all.
What's wrong with
the way I talk?
I just wanted to know, you
know, why don't you wear a belt.
Well what do you mean?
You know, your pants.
They never stay up.
Your butt's always sticking out.
What do you mean?
You look at my butt?
You are gay, aren't you?
What?
No!
Yeah you are.
That's why you're always
looking at my butt!
Man, you shouldn't be
looking at my butt.
You should be looking
at girls butts.
You're a sicko!
Maybe if you keep
your damn pants up
I wouldn't be seeing
your butt all the time.
You know, you have
a problem, Wade.
And as a friend, I just thought
you should know about it.
Man, just stop the car.
I'll walk home.
You're a pervo!
Forget I said anything.
Let's just go see the movie.
No, man.
Stop the car.
Find yourself
another boy toy, man.
I'm going home.
Wade.
Look, I just can't give
you things that you want.
Goodbye!
Wade!
Shit.
Sorry, Brian.
You know, I think
I know what this
Question you want to ask me is.
So you may as well
go ahead and ask.
I already know what the
answers going to be.
I'll ask soon.
After dinner.
After we dance.
Dancing huh?
Mm hm.
What kind of dancing?
We'll be standing up.
It'll be the kind I like.
Well we'll start in
the vertical position
But we don't have
to stay that way.
Mm, I get goosebumps
just thinking about it.
To your bumps.
(SINGING) Honky tonk loving.
Let my love burn you up.
Gonna set you on fire.
Burn you up with desire.
Hey, boy!
Pull your pants up you
dumb son of a bitch!
Wow, Brian.
You're a great cook.
That was really fantastic.
This can wait.
I love you, Brian.
I love you too, Annie.
(SINGING) Let my
love warm you up.
Let my love warm you up.
Gonna set you on fire.
Burning up with desire.
Le my love warm you up.
Let my love warm you up.
Will you marry me?
Oh, Brian.
Yes!
(SINGING) Burning
up with desire.
Gonna set you on fire.
Hey, I love this song!
Can I dance with you guys?
Churn the milk and
make it butter!
Wade, what are doing?
You're supposed to
be at the movies.
Churn the milk
and make it butter.
Churn the milk and
make it butter.
Damn it, Wade!
Can't I have any
moment without you?
Churn the milk and
make it butter.
Annie, are you OK?
Churn the milk
and make it butter.
Churn the milk and
make it butter.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm dancing here.
I'm in the groove.
And when the music
calls, you got to answer.
Ewe, that's vomit!
Your girlfriend's gross.
Don't worry about
it, Annie, OK?
What'd you do that for?
I was in the groove.
The music just took me away.
Fuck you, Wade!
Annie and I were
having a great evening.
You're supposed to
be out with, Ken!
That's another thing.
I don't appreciate being pimped
out to your pervo friends!
That guys a flamer, I tell ya!
And I'm just not that way!
What?
Ken?
He is not!
Yeah, right.
That's why he went on and
on all night about my butt!
I'm just not comfortable with
guys looking at me like that!
I'd rather have girls like
Annie looking at my butt.
Uh!
What'd you cook.
Jesus, Wade.
Oh, I really have to go.
I'm sorry, Annie.
I planned for this
evening to be so special.
It's not your fault!
Boy, she really vomited good.
Must have gotten sick
from Brian's cooking.
He's a nice guy but
not much of a cook.
Uh, and all over my nice pants.
I need to take a bath.
Yeah, a bath.
(SINGING) I got a love handle!
Got a love handle!
Chicka boom, boom, boom.
Got a handle... on my love.
Let me wear you like
a glove, oh yeah.
Got a love handle.
Somebody help me.
(SINGING)Got a love handle.
Chicka boom, boom, boom.
Hey, Brian, I took one of
your t-shirts cause mine
Had puke all over it.
Are you happy, Wade?
Do you like screwing up my life?
I never screwed up your life.
You screwed up your life.
I ain't do nothing!
No.
I'm not going to say anything.
The semesters almost over.
And I can have my life back.
Have your life back?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm going to go take a bath.
(SINGING) Put your beer
goggles on and make love to me.
Through those hazy shades,
I'm not so bad a fella.
My belly ain't so big.
My teeth ain't so yellow.
I can't believe he
actually shut up.
[Music playing]
Damn it!
I can't take it anymore!
[Music playing]
God damn it!
Would you shut the hell up!
Ah!
You pervo!
What are you doing in here!
Go get your jollies
somewhere else!
I don't like guys
watching me in the tub!
Hell, I might let a girl watch
me in the tub, but not a guy.
[Knocking]
Huh.
Man, sorry about that.
Hope Wade didn't mess
anything up for you.
I did everything I
could to stop him.
And he just jumped
out of the car.
And tried turning
the car around.
It just died.
What's wrong?
What did Wade do?
What's that smell?
I didn't mean for it
to happen, I swear.
The radio just fell
out of my hand.
Something happen?
Bathroom.
So, like, what happened?
It slipped out of my hand.
The radio.
I was trying to
get it to shut off.
And it slipped out of my hand.
That's OK You didn't
do it on purpose.
Hi, Mrs. Jenkins?
Ken here.
Yeah, Wade's friend.
Afraid I kind of
have some bad news.
I really don't quite
know how to put this.
Evidently, Wade
was taking a bath.
Yeah, yeah, he's taking a bath
and listening to the radio.
What?
No, I don't know what
station he's listening to.
Anyway, the radio kind
of fell in the tub.
My boy, oh God, oh
God, my baby boy!
Yeah, I'm terribly sorry.
Yeah.
No, that won't be a problem.
Yeah, I fully understand.
Yeah, the coroners are
taking him away right now.
All right.
OK.
Bye-bye.
So I was here in the kitchen.
I was cleaning up some
vomit for my fiance who
Has been ill a little earlier.
And suddenly, I didn't
hear the radio anymore.
And I heard a splash and the
sound of electricity buzzing.
And I knew right away
what had happened.
I always thought Wade
had more sense then
To put an electrical appliance
on the edge of a tub.
But I don't know anything
about his upbringing.
I ran and unplugged the
extension cord immediately.
But when I went into the
bathroom, well, he was dead.
Yes, I see.
People should really
be more careful.
You know, they should
make public service
Announcements about that.
And during ballgames.
You know, really get the message
out there about being careful
With electricity when you're
taking a bath because it
Could have saved a life.
The life of your friend.
Well, Brian, I think
I have all I need.
If I need any more
questions, I'll be in touch.
That's, pretty
much, what happened.
Yeah, that was Wade's
mom on the phone.
She's, kind of, taking it hard.
God, what a day.
Yeah, she was wanting to come
up and get some of his stuff
But really didn't feel
up to it right now.
She thought maybe
after the funeral.
That's OK.
Isn't it?
That's fine.
Those cops, they weren't
accusing you of anything,
Were they?
No, no, she believed
what I told her.
It wasn't my fault. It
slipped out of my hand.
You believe me, don't you?
Yeah, of course.
It really was an accident.
Hey, you don't need
to explain it to me.
Want me to call Annie for you?
That's all right.
I'll talk to her tomorrow.
I want to tell her myself.
Yeah.
Knowing Annie,
she's probably going
To want to run out and get a
marriage license right away,
And move in after Wade's gone.
That's a safe bet.
Thanks for calling his parents.
I couldn't handle that.
Yeah, it's no problem.
Better they heard
from us than the cops.
You know, preacher
man, Bob, always
Says better to
hear from a friend
Then some guy in a uniform.
(SOBBING) My boy,
oh God, my baby boy.
Why did you have to
take him, oh Lord?
Why him and not his father?
Brothers and
sisters, our friend,
Our comrade, our brother
Wade, he did not have to die!
Amen.
He did not have to die!
Brother Wade did
not have to die!
Except, God has a plan for him.
God, in his infinite wisdom
and glory said, Wade,
This is your time.
Now is the time, brother Wade.
Brother Wade, get your
butt up here to heaven.
I know brother Wade is happy.
Oh Lord, he's happy that
his friends, and family,
And comrades, and
spiritual arms,
Have gathered here today to
send him on to the promise land.
I know you feel
good because brother
Wade's in a better place.
I know you're happy
for Brother Wade.
I know you're pleased that he's
gone to the kingdom of heaven!
Can I have an amen?
Amen.
Let me hear you say amen
brothers and sisters!
Amen.
I can't hear you!
Say amen!
- Amen.
- Loud!
Loud!
Say amen, brothers and sisters!
Amen.
I don't know why God chose
to electrocute Wade the way
He did.
Brother Wade was taking a bath.
He was in a tub washing
off the impurities.
The dirt!
The filth!
The scum!
The vermin that each one of
us have in our earthly bodies.
He was taking a bath.
And the radio just
happened to jump.
Radio jumped!
It just... the radio jumped
into the tub with brother Wade!
And it electrocuted him.
It shriveled him all up.
I don't know why God chose
that path for brother Wade.
I can't understand it.
But God understands.
And Wade us with God.
Brother Wade is with God.
They're up in heaven.
And one day we're
going to go to heaven.
We're going to get on that
freight train of love.
That freight train of happiness!
We're going to go to heaven!
And we're going to
see Brother Wade!
Do you want to see brother Wade
in heaven brothers and sisters?
Let me here you say amen!
Amen.
Let me here you say it loud!
Say it proud!
Amen!
Say amen brother Wade!
Amen.
God!
God bless this ground
that contains the shed
Off body of brother Wade.
Bless this whole area.
Bless this hole that
his body will lay into.
When we come to pay our
respects to brother Wade,
We will feel his
presence here among us.
And we loved him so.
Yes we did, God.
We loved brother Wade
so but now he is gone.
You gotta help me God.
Let us all now bow our heads in
silent prayer for brother Wade.
Amen.
You guys go back to the car.
I'll be with you in a minute.
I saw what you did.
What?
He didn't deserve
what you did to him.
I have no idea what you're...
You may be able
to fool the police.
But you can't fool me.
I saw you throw the radio in
the tub and kill my brother.
It slipped out of my hand.
It slipped out of your hand?
What were you doing
in the bathroom
When he was taking
a bath anyway?
I... he was-
He was taking a bath.
Look.
I'm sorry.
Wade was never very good
at standing up for himself.
But I'm going to see
that he does this time.
But I...
[Chanting] Buttcrack,
buttcrack, buttcrack,
Buttcrack, buttcrack,
buttcrack, buttcrack, buttcrack.
Stop it!
Isn't that what you called him.
Isn't that what you called Wade?
Buttcrack?
Say it 12 times in one breath
and then just see what happens.
Look, this witchcraft mambo
jumbo voodoo doesn't scare me!
Just get out of my face with it!
[Chanting]
Brian.
Yo, Brian.
Huh?
Hey, man.
Where'd you go?
Paris?
What [inaudible]?
Hey, come on.
Annie's in a hurry to get back.
Some girl thing.
I don't know.
Yeah, let's get the
hell out of here.
You know that there were
a lot more people there
Than I thought there would be?
Really?
Hey, you want to watch some TV?
Sure.
I got dibs on the floor
next to the window.
Last year, over nine people
in the greater Arcola,
Virginia area alone died
as result of electrocution
In their own bathtub.
Don't be a statistic.
Keep your radio and all
other electrical appliances
Away from your tub and
any other areas of water.
Remember, bathing is important
but nothing to die for.
Didn't take long.
Hey, you mind if I put
it on the biker channel?
I don't care.
Biker channel?
You're no biker.
Yeah, but they have
really good shows.
(ON TV): [inaudible] will return
right after these messages.
Used to be that when my old
lady got her monthly visitor,
I'd swear she used
to drive me crazy.
[Knocking]
(ON TV): [inaudible]
Nagging and shit.
I swear to god, I thought
I was going to kill her.
Preacher man Bob, hi.
This is a pleasant surprise.
That was a beautiful
sermon you gave earlier.
Some of things you said, they
just touched me right here.
Brother Brian, that lifts
my spirits to hear that.
Can I come in?
Oh, sure.
Thanks.
So uh, what brings you by
here today preacher man Bob?
I just come by to
make sure that you
Kids are doing all right.
You know, the loss of a
friend is a very trying time.
I want y'all to know
brother Wade is gone
To a far better place
then this ratchet
Earth we find our self on.
I know y'all are
in a lot of pain.
I know y'all have a lot
of loss in your heart.
I know you wish you could have
his round mounds of God loving
Pounds right here with you!
But you can't!
But you will see
brother Wade again.
You'll see him
again in paradise.
That's where you will see.
I know.
Can I get you something
preacher man Bob?
I have some apple juice.
No, no.
I don't want to impose.
I just came by to make sure
y'all are doing all right.
You know, I want to make sure
that your souls are at piece.
That you've been able to accept
the passing of your friend.
I'm here to offer guidance.
Spiritual counseling.
Do y'all need any?
Well I could use some guidance.
Brother Ken, I see
the pain in your eyes.
I know that it's hurting you.
But preacher man Bob, I
am going to help you son.
I'm going to help ya!
Thank you preacher man Bob.
You know what we ought to do?
Let's go to the
kitchen, get a beer,
And get it on with the Lord!
Come on, boy!
You know, I don't
mean this bad.
But I'm on a hard
time missing Wade.
It's just that it's so nice
here without his buttcrack
Getting in our way.
Yeah, you're right.
I feel, kind of, bad though.
He might've could've
been somebody if he just
Learned to keep his pants up.
You never know.
I don't know.
Once a buttcrack,
always a buttcrack,
Their are buttcracks in
this world like he was.
People who don't have enough
sense to keep their pants
Pulled up to cover their private
parts like their buttcracks.
And then, there
are non-buttcracks.
People like us who have
enough sense not to show
Our buttcracks to the world.
I mean, after all,
who wants to look
At another persons buttcrack?
I know I don't want to
look at peoples buttcrack.
I think buttcrack
is a state of mind.
You either have enough sense
to hide your buttcrack.
Or you're too stupid to
realize that everyone
Can see your buttcrack.
When I think of Wade, all that
comes to mind is his buttcrack.
Ooh, I go to remember to
breath when I go on like that.
My mom always said I
could be long winded.
(SOBBING) Oh, my boy.
My, boy.
That's all right, mama.
We'll just make us
another baby boy.
(SOBBING).
I'm gonna go for a drive.
I need some fresh air.
(SINGING) [inaudible].
Man, people like
that ought to be shot.
Hey, buttcrack!
Pull your damn pants up!
Man, what if I was
driving here with my mama?
She don't want to look
at that kind of stuff.
That's just disgusting!
Country folk like me don't
like that kind of stuff.
I'm gonna teach that
asshole a lesson.
(SINGING) I love my
crazy little [inaudible].
Hey, buttcrack!
Buttcrack!
I'm talking to you!
I'm talking to you,
you piece of shit!
Oh, so that's how
its going to be, huh?
What are trying to do?
Gross the whole
fucking world off?
Pull your god damn pants up
you retarded son of a dick wad!
Come on, buttcrack!
Come on, boy.
Oh, yeah.
Come on now!
(SINGING) Follow
that drinking gourd.
I just had about
enough of you, boy!
Oh, god, the humanity!
What the... mama!
Mama!
Mama, my face is melting!
(SOBBING) My face is melting!
It's melting!
It's melting, mama!
My face!
It's melting!
My face is melting!
(SINGING) Drinking gourd.
God is in the flowers!
God is in the trees!
God is in Troy Aikman's knee!
God is in Chevy Nova's!
God is in the little tiny hairs
hanging off your [inaudible],
Ken!
God is everywhere, young man!
Is he in urine?
God is in Pepsi Cola!
God is in everything!
God is in the Trident
Sugarless Gum.
God is in... he's in my shoes!
He's in my pants!
He's making me do a
little tiny dance!
God's everywhere!
He's in the sand at the beach!
He's in the sky
He's on the floor!
He's everywhere!
He's underground!
Overground!
He's over the top,
battle royale.
God is your friend!
You know, Brian, we've got
our marriage license, right?
Yeah.
Well I why don't if you
wanted a big fancy ceremony
Or anything.
But if you just want
to keep it simple,
Preacher man Bob is here.
Maybe we can ask him if
he'd do it right now.
What do you think?
Yeah, you know,
that's not a bad idea.
Let's do it.
Brian, I'm so excited.
I love you.
Satan is after your
soul, young man.
Satan wants to get you I'm
a Satan hating preacher!
I am preacher man Bob!
And you got to avoid him!
You got to keep away from his
dastardly ways, young man!
Do you here me?
Is Satan everywhere
too preacher man Bob?
Oh, he thinks he is!
Satan thinks he's a bad man!
He's walking through the
forest of life right now going,
I'm bad.
I'm Satan.
Satan is not doo doo.
Satan is not the crap.
He's in chainsaws that are
tearing up the rain forest.
Satan in it acid rain.
What?
Speak, son.
Is he in urine?
You got to keep Satan
out of your life.
You, brother ken, has got to
keep Satan out of your life.
The only way Satan can
get in is you ask him in.
Satan will come to your door.
He will knock upon your door.
He said, Ken, can I come in?
You say, no!
Satan, stay away from me!
You say get thee behind
me old master of evil.
Ge thee behind me
old master of evil.
Do not, do not, do not
let Satan into your life!
Can you hear me brother, Ken?
Excuse me, um, we're not
interrupting anything here,
Are we?
Oh, no.
You're not interrupting.
I'm just putting
brother Ken back
On the correct spiritual path.
Yeah.
Preacher man Bob,
Annie and I were
Wondering if you'd marry us.
Marry ya?
Marry you two?
Why nothing would fill
my heart with more joy.
How better to get over
the lost of a loved
One than for two people
who love each other so
To be united in holy matrimony.
Cool.
God.
God, will you
sanction this event?
Will you bless this holy wedding
that I am about to perform?
Amen.
Say it brother, Ken
Amen!
Say it loud and say it proud!
Brian, you take this
woman, this woman Annie,
To be your wife, to love her,
to cherish her forever, forever,
And ever?
I do.
And Annie, do you take
this man, this man Brian,
To be your man forever,
forever, till death do you part?
I do.
By the power vested in
me by the God almighty,
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
Amen.
Well hey, let's celebrate.
Alrighty.
To the happy couple.
Here, here.
Cheers.
Well let's get
this party going.
[Music playing]
(SINGING) [inaudible].
Woo!
I'm jumping for Jesus, baby!
Jumping for Jesus!
Yeah, baby!
Woo!
I'm jumping for Jesus!
Jumping for Jesus!
Yes!
Woo!
Excuse me.
I have to pee.
[Toilet flushing]
God, you scared me.
Sorry, I have to pee, too.
I love you, Brian.
I love you to, Annie.
What do you say we
make this party short
So we can have our honeymoon?
Oh, yeah.
Good.
Churn the milk
and make it butter.
[Screams]
Churn the milk
and make it butter.
Get thee behind
me master of evil.
What?
Uh, nothing.
What's going on?
I feel kind of weird like I
missed something or something.
Uh, nothing's happening.
You know, just stuff.
Wait a... you feel OK, son?
Uh, yeah.
I feel kind of weird.
Go ahead and keep
dancing there, boy.
It's good for the spirit.
Dance on!
Come on dance.
Dance on, um.
Churn the milk
and make it butter.
Churn the milk and
make it butter.
Is it Satan preacher man Bob?
Is Wade possessed by Satan?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
What's going on?
This can't be happening.
Can it?
Annie, there's a
reason for everything.
And I'm going to
figure this out.
I promise!
Wow, I wonder.
Wonder what, Brian?
Do you know something we don't?
You know?
Now is the time to
talk, young man.
I didn't take her
seriously at the time.
I never believe in
that witchcraft stuff.
Didn't take who
seriously at what time?
What are you talking about?
At the funeral.
Wade's sister.
She told me some mambo
jumbo about a curse.
She said if anybody said the
word buttcrack in one breath,
Wade would the chance to come
back and stand up for himself.
Buttcrack 12 times
in one breath?
Oh, God!
Me and my stupid big mouth.
What do you mean he'd have a
chance to stand up for himself?
Um.
So he really is possessed
by Satan, isn't he?
No, Ken.
Wade is the victim here.
He's been robbed of his
chance for natural afterlife.
There's some kind of
dark magic going on here.
Something evil is at work.
Something is wrong.
Wade's not the source of it.
Oh, yeah.
Wade was a true friend to you.
And you're going to help him
back to his resting place.
You're going to help him regain
his dignity down in the ground.
This darkness that
has befallen him,
You must help him overcome.
Well I mean, how do we do that?
Look at him.
He's alive.
He's not alive!
That's not alive!
He's being made a
mockery of by his sister!
Some kind of evil
at work here, I say.
Evil, dark magic!
What we got to do is help
him get back into that earth!
That's what we gotta
do, brothers and sister.
You mean hell.
No Ken, not hell.
Wade is the victim here.
He was a faithful
member of my church
For many, many, many years.
He's being deprived of
his spiritual rights.
Someone is denying him of
what he belongs to be doing.
What we need to
do is help return
To the proper resting place!
Do you understand?
Oh, yeah.
OK, I guess we should make
doubly sure that he's dead
And take him back to his grave.
That's right.
Let's go it him!
Ow!
What are you doing?
Huh?
What did you do that for, Brian?
He's already dead.
You can't hurt him!
Whack him good!
Give it to him!
Ah!
My nose
[Interposing voices]
Keep going!
Hit him!
I sure hope we did
the right thing.
Trust me, Brian.
If it was you, you'd want
us to do the same thing.
Aw, man.
You got to kill the evil beast!
Come on!
Whack him!
Whack a doo!
Get him!
Let me see.
I think we got him here.
Now what?
Let's take him back
to his resting place.
(SINGING) Got a love handle.
Chika boom boom boom.
Chicka boom boom boom.
Aw, shit.
He's alive again.
Ah!
[Music playing]
Well I know I already
said everything
I could possibly say at the
first funeral for brother Wade.
But I feel that anytime a
young man is to be buried,
Words should be
said over his body.
Whoa, hey, hey, hey, now.
Whoa.
Oh, shit.
God, this is not
the first time we've
Laid poor brother Wade to rest.
But I sure hope it's
gonna be the last.
Please don't blame brother
Wade for the actions
Of his evil sister.
And please, God, except
the wretched soul
Back into your Heavenly kingdom.
Amen!
Amen.
I said amen, Ken!
Amen!
Give me a loud amen!
Say it again like you mean it!
Amen!
Please God, amen this man and
keep him down in the ground.
Thank you.
Amen.
There.
Fools.
Uh.
What's going on?
Don't let them get
away with it, Wade.
What do you mean?
I was, I was, I was
going towards this light.
It was this beautiful light.
And I knew that when
I got there that...
I know, I know but
he tried to kill you.
He threw the radio
in the tub with you.
No.
No!
Ow!
If you weren't already dead,
that would've killed you.
You've got to get your revenge.
You've got to do
something if you
Want to go back to the light.
What?
You have to kill him, Wade.
Oh.
If you don't, you're doomed
to walk the earth forever.
You'll never get
back to the light.
Why did you do this to me?
Why couldn't you
just leave me alone?
Others will try
to kill him, too.
You have got to be the
one to kill him, Wade.
Why couldn't you
just leave me alone?
A spell this powerful comes
with certain side effects.
Well I've never killed anybody.
Do what you must.
Strangle him.
Electrocute him.
Shoot him.
I don't even have a gun.
What are you going to do?
I guess I'll get my revenge.
Good.
I'm only doing this
because I want to get
Back to where it's peaceful.
I'm not really mad
at Brian or anything.
Wade?
Huh?
Pull your pants up.
Well preacher man Bob,
thanks for marrying us.
And thanks for your
help with Wade.
No problem at all, son.
I'm just glad I can help.
So you're sure
Wade won't be back.
I mean, you don't think so.
Little lady, I'm 98% sure
you'll be seeing no more Wade.
Well what if he does come back?
Are there any special
prayers we should say?
You know, the bible doesn't
cover zombie resurrections.
I wish it did, but it doesn't.
What you should do.
What you should do is just
chop his arms and his legs off.
I mean, just hack him up.
That way, he won't be able to go
anywhere if he does come back.
And let me tell
you one more thing.
He's already dead.
You can't hurt him.
He's dead.
Just make sure he
stays in the ground.
OK.
Should we burn
all of his stuff?
Would that rid the
house of all evil?
Brother Ken, I'm getting sick
and tired of explaining to you
That Wade's not the problem.
He's not evil.
It's his sister.
Holy!
Oh, yeah.
But shouldn't we burn
all of his stuff anyway?
Brother Ken, me
and you are going
To have to have a special
spiritual counseling session.
You come down by the church
about 1 o'clock tomorrow.
You hear me, son?
And we'll have a
little talk then.
OK.
So I guess you want
to be alone, huh?
Well, yeah.
I understand.
Mind if I use your
bathroom first?
I got to piss like a racehorse.
No, go right ahead.
You don't think Wade
will be back, do you?
I don't know really.
I don't know how powerful that
spell Wade's sister put on him.
She blames me for Wade's death.
You didn't have anything
to do with Wade's death.
Everybody knows that.
Even the police know that.
I know.
She just thinks she knows
something the rest of you,
The rest of us, don't.
Well I guess that's
all behind us now.
We're together.
And no one will ever come
between us again the way he
Did with his buttcrack and all.
Yeah, once Ken leaves, we can
get this marriage underway.
Brian, um, there's
something I have to do first.
My mom's going to be so excited.
I can't believe I
haven't called her yet.
Hello, mom?
Hi, it's me.
Guess what.
Yeah!
Guess what else.
Well we, kind of, eloped.
Preacher man Bob was here,
and he did the ceremony.
And it was really nice.
I hope you're not mad at me.
Good.
Oh, I will.
OK.
I love you too, mom.
I'll see you at Thanksgiving.
OK?
Bye, mom.
[Inaudible] baby.
[Screaming]
So where are you and Annie
going on your honeymoon?
[Inaudible].
Annie!
[Music playing]
Get away, buttcrack boy.
[Screaming]
Brian, whatever you do,
don't look at his buttcrack.
You're out of your
mind, butt boy!
[Screaming]
Get out of my way [inaudible]!
Ah!
Oh, grandma!
Get the biscuits ready!
I'm coming!
Preacher man Bob.
I just came back
to get my bible.
I left it in your living.
Nice shooting.
If I can't defend
myself, I can't
Do the Lord's work, young man.
What happened?
Annie.
Wade's sister is
interfering in areas where
She does not belong at all!
Annie.
Son, it's time for you to lay
down and take that big rest.
Oh, God, except this young man
into your heavenly kingdom!
No, please, no!
Brian, no!
You can't be dead!
Wade, brother
Wade, Brian's gone.
He's gone.
You can't bring him back.
No!
I know it's hard to except
the loss of a friend.
But Brian is gone, Wade.
Brian, no!
No!
Wade, what's happening?
I was heading
towards this light.
Brian, you're not dead!
Brian?
Meet your maker, boy!
[Chanting] So long, Wade.
Lady, you done really
made a mess of things.
You done really screwed
a lot of people up.
Excuse me?
When you mess with God, who
mess with me, honey bunny!
[Gunshots]
And I will not tolerate
you messing with me!
[Music playing]
Hey, dad.
I found it.
Wade Jenkins, right here.
Wade Jenkins.
Outstanding.
Have you got your
picture now, Stan?
Can we go?
My feet are hurting.
Hold on.
Wait, I know.
Go stand next to the grave.
Trevor go stand
next to your mother.
Oh, Stan.
Honestly, what is
this all about?
It's cool, mom.
This is Wade Jenkins.
You know, the buttcrack guy.
Well why do you need a
picture of this guy's grave?
He's part of the local history.
That's right.
He died in his bathtub.
He got electrocuted.
But what is weird is
that after his funeral,
His roommate was
found dead, too.
Somebody beat the
tar out of him.
And his face was all melted.
Melted.
Couple other people
were there, too.
And they were just as dead.
You ever heard of such a thing?
Well that doesn't sound right.
It was in the paper, mom.
And now it's going
to be in my book.
You're not still working
on that silly book, are you?
I absolutely am.
I've got pictures of Nigel
the psychopaths grave.
And now I'm getting pictures
of this buttcrack guys grave.
I think it'll make a
great coffee table book.
Just think about it.
A picture book featuring all
the famous and infamous graves
Of Northern Virginia.
All I got to do is keep
my eyes in the paper.
And whenever somebody important
dies or anybody at all dies
With some mystery around
them, like this guy,
I'll get a picture of the grave.
I have a vision here, Harriet.
Work with me on it.
It's going to be cool, mom.
Oh, it's going to
be more than cool,
Especially when I go into all
the rumors about this guy.
All the stuff the
papers didn't even talk.
Oh, yeah, definitely.
All that stuff about
saying buttcrack 12 times
In one breath.
Yeah.
12 times in one breath.
Come on.
Well that's what
folks are saying.
They all say that he came
back to life to get revenge
Because somebody said
the word buttcrack 12
Times in one breath.
There was a curse on him.
And that's why everybody's
face was melted.
He came back to life, they
looked at his buttcrack,
And then they died.
His sister died, too,
right here in the parking
Lot of this very cemetery.
The same parking lot
where our very own car
Is parked at this exact moment.
Six bullets.
Six of them all
lodged in her brain
Shot there by an
unknown assailant.
Who shot her?
Why did she die?
Nobody knows.
To this very day, it's
remained a mystery.
Oh, my.
Oh, my indeed.
That's why I wanted a
picture of this grave.
Hey, dad.
Why don't you get a picture
of the sisters grave, too.
It'd be good for
the book, you know,
Especially that she's the
one who put the curse on him.
Can't.
Cremated.
Religion demanded it.
Ah.
Well I don't understand
why anyone would even say
That 12 times in one breath.
It's ludicrous to think
anyone could actually
Fit that into a conversation.
It could happen.
Buttcrack, buttcrack,
buttcrack, buttcrack, buttcrack,
Buttcrack, buttcrack.
It's kind of stupid.
But it can be done.
Yeah, well that's just
what folks were saying.
I didn't make it up.
[Music playing]
Where's my puke?
Brother Wade did not have
to die, brothers and sisters.
[Chanting].
Cut.
[Laughing]
The loss of a loved one's a
very trying time, young lady.
Oh, there's a whole
bunch of y'all here.
I didn't even notice.
Buttcrack.
You're a preacher man Bob.
You need help?
I don't know.
(WHISPERING) I'm sorry.
I saw him fixing that.
We'll have a little talk then.
Door's locked.
It's total mayhem!
Oh, my god!
Still rolling, and
lets do it again.
And ready, set?
I'm eating bugs.
I'm afraid I, kind
of, have some bad news.
Yeah.
No.
[Bleep]
God!
God, I'm speaking to you!
Could you please sanction
this holy wedding
I'm about to perform?
Can you help me unite these
two people in holy macrimony?
[Laughing]
[Music playing]