[MUSIC PLAYING]
MAN: Tell me why you
like horror movies.
-My name is Anakin, and
I like horror movies
because the amount of
people that get murdered.
- --to metal one week,
then goth, or, like,
glam-rock, but I'm
still into horror.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
- --a culture surrounding
it that is very enjoyable
and, you know, oddly positive.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
- --bloody, it's kind of
sexy in this weird way.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Watching a good
horror movie will
give you a-- a brain orgasm.
-I just like watching
people die pretty much.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-A horror fan?
Hell yeah.
I'm a monster a kid.
Aren't you a monster a kid?
-From the outside
looking in, they
think they're all a
bunch of, you know,
slobering, crazed idiots.
Um, some of them are.
-A lot of improv was encouraged.
And that produced things
like, you know, e-x-i-t, exit.
You know, which
was basically a tip
of the hat to "Sesame Street."
-Pretend, like for
instance in reality,
that 99.9% of the human
population never heard of me,
or thinks I'm a dead French guy.
-Sid Haig is the only
man on the planet that
can say that he worked with
Lon Chaney, Jr. And Rob Zombie.
And I am.
-My favorite type
of horror film--
it's usually
psychological actually,
the horror that's implied
rather than shown.
-I like to do a
trash with a Linda
Hamilton Terminator Twist.
Something like that I think
would be, like, my dream role.
-You know, I think
I'm a good screamer.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
- --horror stuff, but you also
like, I don't know, rainbows.
- --kicked out of here if
I answer that honestly.
I'm really not a horror fan.
I never have been.
-They not only remember
anything I did,
they remembered shit I
didn't even remember doing.
-Horror films are my life,
um, because I make them.
[SCREAMING]
-What am I looking at?
I felt like I'd
been shown much more
than I was supposed to see.
-(SINGING) One, two,
Freddy's coming for you.
Three, four, better
lock her door.
-The scariest horror
movie I've ever seen
would have to be Twilight.
-(SINGING) Five, six,
better get your crucifix.
Seven, eight, stay up late.
-I always wanted to watch
them just to be scared,
to see how scared I could
really get and stay that way.
-(SINGING) Nine, ten,
never sleep again.
-We had gone way beyond
The Three Little Pigs,
and way beyond, some of
the other fairy tales.
-You can kind of
escape your daily life,
and-- and, you know, scare
yourself a little bit.
I think if you're
always on edge,
a little bit fear
is good in life.
-People see it, and they're
like oh, do you like to cook?
I'm like, no, I like
axe-murdering maniacs.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-I heart monster movies.
MAN: Alright, and got it.
-So my first horror movie was
"Nightmare on Elm Street,"
and that scared the crap out of
me, because Freddy Krueger is
really scary, and he's
really gross looking.
-Johnny Depp's eaten
by the bed, I just
have, like, vivid
memories from childhood
of having these horrible
nightmares of getting eaten
by the bed and blood
squirting all over my room.
-It's kinda cool how,
like, when you fall asleep,
and then Freddy
kinda comes for you.
-I'm really picky when
it comes to my horror.
Like, it has to be good, or
I will not sit through it.
- --anything that's
scary and creepy,
possibly sexy in
there somewhere.
- --things like "It."
I don't like clowns.
- --and the clown
were, like, awful,
and I would not watch a horror
movie for years after that.
- --going out in the
rain, seeing, like,
storm drains and just
thinking of clowns.
-My mother came into the
shower when I was a kid
and would throw balloons up,
and start making the sounds
that the clowns did
on the movie "It."
Scared the hell out of me.
Yeah.
-They come in-- in--
in all walks of life.
I have teachers, and soccer
moms, and lawyers, and--
-So I'm pretty much just
a-- a-- a mild fan, I guess,
when it comes to horror movies.
I like to go and watch them.
It doesn't really
influence my life.
- --not a uber fan, like, I
have many friends who are.
-Basically grew up
watching horror,
I think, like a lot of kids do.
-Well, I wouldn't
consider myself
to be a fan of horror movies.
-I'm a definite horror fan.
I went to the drive-ins.
-I hate horror movies.
-People actually say
they think, like,
my house looks like
a Halloween house,
because I have skulls
hanging in cages
outside of-- all year round.
-I've always been into the
macabre, anything that's
really spooky, and scary,
and stuff like that.
-I like horror films
because-- a real horror
film, not a slasher film.
-Oddly enough, even though
I love horror films,
I don't handle gore that well.
- --the American stuff, which
is more just straight blood
and guts-- which, I mean
I can appreciate, too.
-Gotta have blood.
Lots of blood.
-As long as it's horror,
I'm pretty happy person.
Yes.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Hi, mom.
-My name is Annie
Violet, and I am
here at the Seattle Zombie Con.
So, I'm from
southern California.
So, drove all the way up
here just to see everyone,
and, like, hang out
and see all the panels.
Very excited about the panels.
-I'm at Zombie
Con because I have
been a lifelong zombie fan.
-The thing about conventions
is there's always,
like, tattoos buzzing, and
flourescent lights, and a lot
of people you need to talk to,
and you gotta stay charming,
and you probably sleep all
of three hours a night.
So, they're definitely
draining, but they're super fun.
And you, you know,
you get to hang out
with people you don't
normally get to see.
-I'm here because
I'm a horror freak.
I adore movies, adore the
genre, video games, comic books,
you name it.
I love it.
-There's a lot of fun to be had.
You can meet a lot
of people who've
created these
works of art, be it
films, or books, or paintings,
or, you know, whatever.
You need a lot of
people behind that.
-I just like the vendors, and I
love, like-- I can find things.
It's like, oh, I freak out.
I'm like-- I nerdgasm.
-Yeah, you get to be with other
people who like to be weird
and put blood on their face
and dress like characters, too.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
-One of the great things about
doing The Twisted Geeks podcast
is we get to go to
conventions, like
Zombie Con, like Crypticon,
and other ones that I love,
like StarFest, where
we get to meet,
not only just the
fans of all this
and see the great
fan outpouring,
but we also get a
great opportunity
to meet the-- the minds behind
all the stuff that we've
enjoyed, some of the
writers, directors,
especially the actors.
And we get to spend
time interviewing
and talking with them.
And it's been a fantastic time.
-Yeah, I look up, Malcom
McDowell is ahead of me
getting coffee.
Chuck Palahniuk and
Max Brooks are trading
notes for their talk that night.
And George Romero is just
kicking it in the lobby,
and I just look around, and
I'm like, I'm surrounded.
There's so much
genius in this room.
It was very hard for
me to contain myself,
and not just run up to
everyone and be like --
oh my God, I love you.
I'm such a fan!
-If this seems a awkward
for people at home,
it's because the people that
are interviewing me right now
have no idea what I've done.
So I'm feeling like --
I'm sitting here like,
what do I do.
I have to like feed
them into this stuff.
-Going to shows like this, and
you see the way people dress,
and the way that
they get into it --
and they express themselves,
and something that they like.
I've always -- as an outsider,
someone who's not really
into the genre myself, I can
still appreciate the fact that
they are enjoying it,
and enjoying themselves.
-These people had seen
everything, a lot of them,
and they would probably --
I don't mean to be mean,
but they'd probably be more
equipped to interview me than
this stuff -- don't
even know [INAUDIBLE]
-I'm telling you because
they are the best.
Our film fans are absolutely
the best there is on the planet,
OK?
They buy all the tickets, they
buy the DVDs, the posters,
the T-shirts , the
pictures, the --
whatever the hell and
the crap we come up with,
because they're there supporting
us all the way down the line,
and without them I got nothing.
[INAUDIBLE] you what's
your favorite line in this,
and my mind's going, oh God
-- I don't know [INAUDIBLE],
what's your favorite line?
And then they would
tell it to me,
and I would say, coincidence!
That was my favorite line too.
And I'd write it on the thing.
-I don't talk to
the celebrities,
only because I'm always scared
it's going to change the way I
see the movies, or anything
I'm interested in them in.
I like to see them in
like every day life.
You know, you see like -- like
we saw like Boondock Saints
just walking around
casually like last night,
and Sid Haig just
walking around.
And like that alone
is awesome to me --
just to see them in real life
when they're not in a film.
So I usually don't
talk to them much.
[SWING MUSIC]
-I have mixed feelings
about autographs.
I really love get, you know,
my picture taken with someone ,
and get, you know, my book, or
my poster, or my movie signed,
but I'm also very poor
and don't want to pay $20,
$20, $20, $20, down the line.
-I don't do this for the money.
I have my school, I'm --
you know -- Independent.
I come here because of hanging
out with Mosley or Sid Haig,
you know?
How hard is it to
sit here and have
people throw money at
you all day, you know?
If you complain about
that you're a moron.
-Finished signing
an autograph here
and there's a guy that comes to
the table over here who said,
would you sign my dick?
I said, no I wouldn't.
Not even if you
washed it recently.
Besides which, I'm not sure I
could fit my signature on it.
-Lovecraft has kind of enjoyed
this resurgence in popularity.
People are taking an
appreciation of sort
of their -- the
literature aspect of it.
In fact, in Portland
we have a bar,
the whole theme of
which is Lovecraft.
The guy's kind of
painted on the ceiling,
and painted on the floor, and
posters, and all kinds of crazy
stuff on the wall.
-Hello, I'm John Horrid.
I'm the owner of the Lovecraft
bar in Portland, Oregon.
The Lovecraft bar
is not a Gothic bar.
It's a horror-themed bar
embracing all horror culture.
Be it literature,
music fashion or art.
That way it's a broader
spectrum for everyone
who loves anything
dark or spooky
that goes bump in the night.
It's sort of like Tim
Burton designed a lounge,
you know, it's goofy horror.
It's not so serious,
But it's definitely --
we have children's
coffins on the walls.
There's bones
everywhere, and chains,
but it's also kind
of fun feeling.
[MUSIC]
JOHN HORRID: H.P. Lovecraft
is probably one of the biggest
names in horror, but has
never got credit for it.
It's always Poe, and
Stephen King, and Anne Rice,
and whatnot.
But Lovecraft's impact on the
world of horror is immense.
They've inspired
Metallica, Iron Maiden,
mentioned in "Ghostbusters"
"Hellboy" -- he's everywhere.
He's dark, he's gloomy, he's a
total freak, and he's awesome.
I didn't want to be
specifically Lovecraft themed
because there's so
much more to offer,
and I'm a huge fan of
black-and-white horror movies
honestly, so it's
just basically,
I wanted to capture
that sort of feel.
With the broader spectrum of
horror, it attracts all sorts.
I love that we've attracted
authors, for example,
like young, punky,
splatter horror authors
are hanging out here.
Apparently the road
manager to Metallica
has been hanging out here.
One of my favorite nights
ever, we first opened --
you got your
sulking metal heads,
and your gloom-and-doom
goths over here,
and there's a girls
dressed all in white --
she's bouncing around, and
I'm like, fuck, here we go,
there goes the end
of the bar, you know?
But I'm not a dick, I
want to, like, be polite.
She came up, she's
like, you're the owner?
And I was like,
yeah, I'm the owner.
And she's like, I love your bar.
And I'm like, thank
you, you know?
She's like I'm gonna tell
all my friends about it,
and I'm like, cool.
And she's like, I'm a librarian.
And I'm like, please tell all
your freaky library friends,
'cause librarians are freaks yo.
Bottom line.
And we're slowly attracting
across the country
a buzz with little
to no advertising.
I don't Twitter.
I fucking hate that shit.
Word of mouth has
been strong enough
that horror fans
are coming to us.
And ultimately my
goal is to get, like ,
Bruce Cambell or [INAUDIBLE]
in here, just to hang out.
And they drink for
free, of course.
So I was in a huge sort
of renovated furniture,
recycled materials place.
And I gave the
question, I was like,
what do you have that's
uncomfortable for you
guys here?
And they mentioned, their
1890s children's coffins,
and I was like, oh
I got to see those.
And they're mahogany, and they
came in the original packaging.
I fell in love with them
the second I saw them.
And the price is right.
I can't say I've spent more on
sushi , but I've come close.
And they had a matching pair.
And even the guys who delivered
didn't want to touch the boxes
-- they were so superstitious.
The Lovecraft Bar is an art
project always in motion.
Whenever I'm out, antique
stores or whatever, I always
ask whoever is
working there, what's
the most messed up
thing you have here?
What makes you uncomfortable?
And then I usually guy it.
Animal traps, old surgical
instruments, coffin handles,
weird taxidermy art, stuff like
that has always appealed to me.
LINNEA QUIGLEY:
Chainsaw Manicure.
It was actually pretty easy to
break into movies when I first
started, because I
was at a young age.
I actually looked a
lot younger than I was.
I was 18 when I started, and I
looked probably, oh 15 or 16.
So it was actually a pretty
easy step for me to get into it.
And they were doing a lot
of the '80s horror films,
and I fit right in, at that
time, as being a victim.
After "Return of
the Living Dead"
and "Night of the
Demons," all of a sudden,
like People Magazine,
Entertainment Tonight,
all these, you know, press
people started coming to me --
Premiere Magazine.
And they start calling me, you
know, Queen of the Screams,
which is like, I
love it, you know?
I like that title.
I want it.
And so I embraced it, where a
lot of the actresses back then
-- like nudity
wasn't, you know, you
just didn't do nudity back then.
I was doing some nudity.
You didn't do,
like, these B-films
that would hurt your career.
And I just, like I said,
embraced it instead of just
shrugged it off, and said, I'm
not doing one of those films.
It's blood, breasts,
and they did say bimbos,
but it's not bimbos anymore.
It's more strong women.
But you've got to
have some blood,
and you've got to
have some breasts,
I think, to have a
good horror film.
I mean, I make the
perfect scream queen,
it's shown at theaters --
it's been shown at theaters.
I've done like 100
films, I love horror.
I think you have
to love horror too.
And you have to
scream very well.
This is a crazy fan is
coming after you: Ahhh!
-There's a lot of really
good horror bands out there,
but I think the one that did
-- has the greatest influence
over things would
be White Zombie.
They're one of the
few that started off
doing horror for the very start.
And even the name, White
Zombie comes from the movie
White Zombie, which
some people think
is the first zombie
movie ever made.
-I joined White Zombie be back
in 1980 -- like late '85/86.
Joining a band before
White Zombie with Shauna.
It was a band called LIFE.
And so that's how I met her.
We did a few shows,
band broke up.
They got -- she was going
out with Rob Zombie,
and basically they called me
up right after they had this
drummer Peter do a couple songs.
I jumped on board and we
started, just immediately
writing and recording,
and touring.
We just picked up right away.
Rob had that band named before
the band was even formed.
So White Zombie already
existed before the band
was even in existence.
He just said, I want a band to
be called White Zombie one day,
and then he put the band
together with Shauna.
Rob and I both had that
background of horror movies.
He brought that
flavor into the band,
and I was all about
that because, you know,
I came from the
horror stuff myself.
And I was all into Iron Maiden
with the Eddie monster thing,
so I thought that was
perfect, you know,
for something I wanted to do.
You know?
IVAN DE PRUME: Toxic Zombie,
man, these guys are awesome.
Bryan Bennett worked
with me on "Metalopolis."
That's when I first -- when
he first joined Toxic Zombie,
and they did a Halloween show
where they had me come up,
play "Thunder Kiss" with them.
We hung out and
talked about doing
the some songs
here in the studio.
[MUSIC]
-If you were to describe
what kind of music we play,
if you would imagine that --
and you have to have a good
imagination for this --
imagine if Kiss, Motley Crew,
and the Misfits had a gang
bang with Joan Jett, Lita Ford,
and Wendy O. Williams, we would
be their bastard children.
It didn't actually start
out as a zombie band,
even though we were called
Toxic Zombie at first.
We actually started out more
as just a regular hard rock
band with a little influence.
And then we had the dancing
girls, of course and stuff.
But it didn't actually
start out as a zombie band
until probably a couple months
into doing our first shows.
We just kind of embraced
it a little bit more.
And I actually
think Sam, actually,
is the one who kind of embraced
the concept a little bit more.
SAM: Yeah, I was the first
one to put on the make up,
and I looked rather
weird without everybody
else putting the make up on.
-It's a very unconventional
type of thing.
There is a zombie culture,
there's a horror culture,
but there are -- in Portland
and I'm sure they're out there,
but I'm not aware
of them, there's not
too many horror bands.
-We've played a
lot of gigs with --
we've played with the
Misfits, Wednesday 13,
Gunfire 76, is also connected.
And we opened up for Creature
Feature was one of our first,
bigger shows that
we played with,
which kind of led to all
those other shows, Wednesday
13 and the Misfits and what not.
And we also played a local event
called Zombie Prom a few years
ago, and having 600
people scream out
"we will eat your
brains" with us
was probably one
of the best moments
ever to have at a show, you now?
-Especially when they're
all dressed like zombies.
Got a mass of zombies
in front of us chanting,
"we will eat your brains."
Like, how can it be better?
MAN 1: We're here
at Zombie Prom 2011.
-We are in fabulous
Portland, where
there is nothing but
zombie awesomeness.
[MUSIC]
HEATHER ERICKSON:
[INAUDIBLE] is Zombie Prom 4.
My inspiration for
doing it, really
was, there's not enough events
downtown that were inexpensive,
fun to go to.
My idea for this was
someone could roll around
in the dirt, the mud, come
in, you know, with clothes
from Goodwill, something like
that, and come to a prom.
[MUSIC]
-My name is Blake.
This is -- who the hell are you?
-Janellle.
Nice to meet you.
-Oh, OK.
I found her.
She's a random zombie.
We like her though.
JANELLE: My impression
is really fun.
Just a group of people dressing
up and going to a dance.
I don't care for horror movies,
but I'm here to have fun,
so this seemed like a
really fun thing to do
and I'm all dressed up.
[MUSIC]
MAN 2: This is my
first big zombie event.
The first I've actually
gotten dressed up
to show up outside of
Halloween, other than being
cast for a play or a movie.
Actually I set the
Guinness World Record
for fastest straitjacket
escape in 2007
when I was stationed
over in Japan,
and it works great as a costume.
everyone seems to
recognize it wherever I go.
It's kind have been a
staple for Halloween,
any other type of
dress up event,
or anything for fancy dress.
-We are foreign exchange
students at this zombie prom.
WOMAN 1: This is our 4th
year, and I was just looking
for something
different to do so --
I always wondered if
the vampires did exist,
what would they do when
everybody turned into zombies.
What are they gonna eat?
-Maybe they would just
come out and have some fun.
-Yeah.
HEATHER ERICKSON: The first year
we didn't have a theme with it,
it was just Zombie Prom 1,
and we expected about 200-300
people and ended
up with almost 700.
So we weren't
expecting that at all.
So we had to move to
move to a bigger venue,
and we've been at the
Bosanova ever since.
The first one we had here
was Under the Dead Sea.
And then we had a Pretty
in Pieces last year,
and then this year
is Tiki Terror.
AUDREY ANGEL: My
name is Audrey Angel.
I'm one of the merch girls this
year, selling the art up there.
I do colored pencil work
that's pretty photo realistic,
but I do it of a fantasy nature,
so I turn people into zombies,
or mermaids.
You know, I've done lots of
zombie events in the past.
I did Zombie Prom here a couple
years ago as a merch girl.
I do the Zombie
Walks every year.
I had a random zombie wedding
with a girl a few years back.
I like making horror
things, I don't --
I don't really like being --
I don't like watching horror
movies, but as soon you give me
the project of making something
explode, or into a gory
mess, I live for that.
-There are little
ones everywhere.
We're one of the biggest in
this side of the United States.
There are a lot of individual
parties, children's parties,
I get asked all the time how
to do a zombie kid's party.
Things like that.
-My name is Robyn Winn
and this is Sofia.
I would consider myself
a hardcore horror fan.
It's not all I live and breath,
but I am a really big fan,
and I like them a
lot, which is weird
'cause when I was little I
was kind of scared. of them.
-I wasn't allowed to watch a
lot of horror movies growing up.
My parents took the R
rating very seriously,
so I was restricted from
watching a lot of these films.
-My family's really --
anything scary, horror, blood,
it's, you know,
the devil's work.
-My mother-in-law, Joe's mom,
she's not very supportive of us
like letting her
watch horror stuff.
There's nothing that's going
to warp her, and like I said,
there's nothing overly
sexual or super, super gory,
and not a lot of
realistic violence.
-My son's 11 and
he's been watching
horror movies since he was four.
And it's nothing -- I
mean, I I'm not concerned.
He doesn't talk about it to
a point where it scares me.
He doesn't do anything
that would scare me.
-The first horror movie I
ever saw was "Ghost Ship,"
and I was four.
I was a smiling the
entire way through it.
I just loved it.
-The first movie I
ever saw in the theater
was "Beauty and the
Beast," the Disney.
And I actually was so,
I was really young,
and I was so frightened of
the beast on the big screen
when he was all angry, that I
actually ran out of the theater
and had to like stay out
in the lobby and calm down.
-What I know is every
Disney movie has
a really bad scary guy in it,
and psychologists will tell you
that kids gravitate towards
that part of the movie
because they get to practice
handling their fear.
-It was "King
Kong" or "Godzilla"
or whatever, and it was really
funny because my mother would
watch them with me for
the first couple of years,
to make sure they didn't
tweak me out for some reason.
-My name is Sally
Skelding, and I'm
an early childhood specialists.
And throughout my career
in early childhood,
I've been very interested
in the impact of violence
on television and movies,
and how that influences
the behavior of young children.
-With Kiara we watch like
Addams Family movies,
and Army of Darkness,
'cause it's super campy.
Nothing too gory,
nothing sexual.
-Being a parent, I have
a six old daughter,
so my horror community
has veered back
towards the Munsters,
and the Addams
Family, and Universal Monsters.
-In the very early
years they do not
think the way that we think.
They do not construct a
reality the way that we do,
and a lot of people
simply cannot accept that.
They'll say, oh my
child understands this,
I explained that to them.
And the child will sit
there and go, oh yes,
I know this is pretend,
but they really
don't because until they're
about eight or nine years old
they do not even begin to
think the way that we do.
JOE: Hey, so when we
watch horror movies,
you know it's not real, huh?
-I know it's just fake.
-Is it costumes?
Some times they
use puppets, right?
Remember you were asking
about Army of Darkness
and if the skeletons
were on strings.
And I told you they
were puppets, remember?
-That's like "Pee
Wee's Play House."
-She does understand that
it's costumes and props.
-A very young children,
like a preschool child,
will go to see one of
these horrible movies,
and they think this is real.
Even though they
bought the ticket,
they've gone in
with their parents,
everybody says this is pretend.
What they see on
the screen is real
because it resembles
their reality.
-My first exposure
happened at age six,
and this was back
in the 1970s when
PG movies could get
away with a lot more.
So I saw full-frontal naked
Brooke Adams, and Donald
Sutherland smashing in the
head of his alien doppelgangers
here with a shovel, and kinda
going, what am I looking at?
I felt like I'd
been shown much more
than I was supposed to see.
-Children have to see it
over, and over, and over,
and over again in order to
try to make sense out of it.
So they see it, it
comes into their mind,
they have to make an adaptation
between what they've seen
and their reality.
If they're young, up to like
seven or eight years of age,
that can be almost impossible
sometimes for them.
-Just as long as you talk
to your kids about it,
and you're like, it's not real.
But you can't really keep
them from having nightmares,
but I mean, you know, watching
"Poltergeist" at eight
didn't hurt me.
-Part of the problem
is that, in this age,
we think the child is
anything from zero to 18,
and so what we would allow our
18-year-old child to watch,
then we go ahead
and let our baby
go to the movies with this.
Or we take our three-year-old
or our four-year-old.
We no longer make those
very clear distinctions
about what is appropriate
for children who
are in the early childhood
years and early primary years,
and what would be
appropriate for an adult
or for an older teenager.
-As a mother, I don't have a
problem with horror movies.
We don't, like we don't
shy away from her right
now with her around 'cause she's
too little to really notice,
but I do have a stepson
and he is seven.
He will not watch
anything with blood in it.
He's like, no I won't
watch that, it's scary,
and if it's got blood
in it I won't watch it.
And I mean it's
really like up to him.
-You will find absolutely no
child guidance book, no book
on child development, no
expert on early childhood that
will say, oh yes, the
thing you need to do
is to fill your child's
head with horror.
-I think that horror
movies themselves
don't affect anybody.
I think it's how -- I think
it's the person that decides how
the movie's going
to affect them.
Because I do work with children,
and there are children who do
watch horror movies,
and they come to school
and they are perfectly behaved,
and they don't perseverate
on the violence, or the horror.
And then I have other kids who
come and that's all they do,
is to perseverate on the
violence and the horror.
-Bottom line is, the kids take
everything off of the parents'
vibration about it, so if
the parents think it's OK
and it's just another
movie, the the kids grow up
thinking it's OK and
its just another movie.
-I kinda grew up as a gentle
creature in a somewhat hostile
environment, and I do
believe that horror films
helped me process
my environment.
-I don't think anybody ever
landed on a therapist's couch
and said, I'm hear because
I watched horror films.
-I just think that this
horror stuff, if it goes in,
it's going to come out and
we don't know how it's going
to come out, and we do
know from the research
that it does indeed create some
insensitivity to other people's
feelings of fear, or
terror, or if we see people
on the street that
need help, we can't
sympathize with them anymore.
We don't have the
empathy that apparently,
as a society, that
we used to have.
-Even now it's kind
of like old hat.
I look down and
go, OK, whatever,
she's getting tortured.
Yeah, OK.
Chainsaw to the head,
yeah, OK, whatever.
So I'm desensitized by it,
but I love watching it,
and I love making it.
-The horror's all
around us at all times,
whether you want to
believe it or not.
Just turn on the news.
You know, people
are being abducted,
and raped, and
killed, and beheaded,
and dumped by the side of
the road every single day.
None of this is
from the imagination
of a horror film director.
WOMAN 1: Texas
Chainsaw Manicure.
[MUSIC]
-I Had seen the original
"Texas Chainsaw Massacre."
It really freaked me out, so
what I ended up doing was --
my best thinking was, if I
see it about a dozen times
it's going to become so familiar
that it won't freak me out
anymore, and really all that
happened was it just drove that
wedge deeper and deeper
each time I saw that movie.
And I penned about a
five minute scenario
about a woman who goes
to a beauty parlor,
gets her hair done, wants to get
a manicure, Leather Face comes
out with a chain saw and
gives her the manicure.
And she comes out of
the beauty parlor,
and I'm her husband waiting in
a pickup truck, and she comes
and she goes, look honey, I
got the best manicure ever.
And I had a friend
from high school
who was now a screenwriter in
Hollywood, and I showed him
and his wife my five minute
video of the Texas Chainsaw
Manicure, and he said, you know
what a coincidence, my writing
partner and I have an office
right across the hall from Toby
Hooper, the director of the
original Chainsaw Massacre.
And Toby, was working on
"Poltergeist" at the time,
and he said if you leave
me a copy of the Manicure,
I can maybe walk it into Toby.
I said, well that'd be cool.
I mean that'd be kinda
cool for him to watch it.
So I did, and he did,
and Toby watched it,
and Toby loved the Manicure.
And Toby loved my
performance in the Manicure.
And Toby be called in his
producing partner, Steven
Spielberg, who also watched
the Manicure and loved it.
And two years later,
that was 1984,
two years later when they were
casting "Texas Chainsaw II,"
I got the job based
on my little cameo
the "Texas Chainsaw Manicure".
I never auditioned for it.
I Never met Toby until
I got to Austin, Texas
to get my head shaved and
start going undergoing
the transformation
from me to Chop Top.
And that really, kind of,
was how I got my big start.
[MUSIC]
-Yeah, some of them bug
the shit outta you, yeah.
But you know, it
ranges from little kids
to doctors and lawyers.
You know?
I mean the fans are a
pretty eclectic group.
You know?
-I've really been lucky.
I've never had
anybody at a horror
convention bother me intensely.
-With traveling around
in different cities,
and meeting different people for
these conventions, I've met --
yeah -- I've met
all kinds of people.
For the most part,
the fans that I meet
are relatively normal,
appreciative people.
-It was our first convention
ever, and a fan comes in.
And it was packed.
-"Grindhouse" had just
come out a month before.
So there was just a
lot of people waiting
to get signatures from us,
and it was our first time
so we were just, you
know, overwhelmed,
and this guy comes up,
and he's very excited,
and he gives me a gun.
And it's heavy, and
he's like, I want
you to shoot anybody
in the audience.
And I was just like, I'm OK.
I was like, oh cool.
-And so she points the gun,
and he's like, you shoot it.
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
-And this person goes, it
doesn't have a red cap on it.
And we're like --
-The tip.
And now she's like, what is it?
And I was like, is
this a real gun?
-And he says, yeah.
It's loaded
-It's my gun.
And I was like, it's loaded?
-And then Geoff Bayhi had
heard all of it, and so he --
-He grabs the gun,
and he opens the gun
and notices it has
real bullet in it.
-And in 2 seconds security
was around the guy,
like had him down, and I had to
explain to him that it was just
all make believe.
You know?
Like he thought that
we had killed people.
He was like, oh yeah,
shoot somebody --
-And she was gonna
shoot the gun.
She could have
killed someone there.
It was crazy.
-It was a crazy signing.
-Yeah.
-Well I've never had
really any crazy ones.
No one's ever, you know,
threatened us or anything.
You know?
But there are some
pretty eccentric ones.
One guy will come over
and he'll spend $400,
you know, and you'll sign some
photos, then he takes them
and he folds them, sticks them
in his pocket and walks away.
-It was -- somebody had spilled
some stage blood on the name
Otis on the floor
plate, and I thought,
that's weird, you know?
Then I went down and I had
breakfast, and then I came up
and I was in the other
elevator, and the door opened
and there was more blood on
the other Otis [INAUDIBLE].
And it turned out
it was a stalker
that had done that
intentionally.
In fact, she called
up the room --
I remember I was already
asleep or something,
and the phone rang and this
female voice said, hello --
this female voice said, I'm
your stalker, and I said,
I'm sleeping now,
stalk me tomorrow.
And I hung up the
phone and that was it.
-Mine were both
female, and there
was a kind of a psycho
sexual thing going on.
But they both melted
away into the darkness.
-You know, some
fans will stand here
and spider webs
will form on them.
You know, they
stand there all day
and they're interviewing
you all day,
but normally we have a
signal with security.
You know, we do that,
it's time to get this --
ask them to go for a walk
or something, you know.
-Last one I did,
I lost my wallet,
and I lost my bag out of
this stupid [INAUDIBLE] --
oh shit, I lost it again!
It's like 1992,
like lap sack thing.
Like [INAUDIBLE] --
I left it somewhere.
Both of them, in the middle
of thousands of people
were brought back to the
concierge, and put in the lost
and found.
No offense to LA, but shit
you lost that stuff in LA
and it'd be gone.
You know, I had my wallet in
it, nobody even opened it,
they just brought it back, and
it was like, I just came up,
nobody opened anything.
It was just, basically, saying
a lot about the kind of people.
-My name's Tunisia and I'm
doing the Monster Shoot Pinup
Calendar, and I am the werewolf.
[HOWL]
[MUSIC]
-My name's Ren Murry.
My company is Golden Era Pinups.
It's kind of our art that we do.
You know, really a lot of
re-creation of classic pinup --
you know, whether it be classic
[INAUDIBLE] photography,
or Bettie Page Photography.
Gil Elvgren is, you know,
a legend in the industry.
Elvgren's paintings
are, you know,
what we call today cheesecake,
which is the whole,
you know, cutesy kind of
thing, with the big oopsy face,
and the, you know,
skirt being blown up
by the wind, or the dog's
got a hold of the dress.
Or you know, those
kind of crazy, almost
unbelievable situations.
The Monster Pinup Calendar
was sort of a collaboration
of ideas where, you know,
we kind of had this idea --
well they had the
idea originally to do,
you know, monster pinups.
You know, there's a number of
different ways we could shoot
it, and a number
of different loos
that we could give the calendar.
We sort of all
agreed that we wanted
to keep it more
Elvgren-painting inspired.
Obviously there are liberties
being taken with the way
that they're dressed
and their overall look.
Elvgren didn't do a lot
of Halloween themed,
or monster themed kind of stuff.
There was a little bit
of that in his work,
but we sort of took
that and ran with it.
You know, I had done like
zombie pinups before.
I've done a couple of zombie
calendars -- things like that.
But they were always
shot on location,
it was very zombie specific.
The freedom of this
calendar allowed
us to sort of go
and try new things.
When it was first proposed to
me that we were have a werewolf
in the calendar, I thought,
OK, why not make zombies sexy
and get that concept.
You know?
And a lot of these other
things are going on here,
and get how we're
gonna make them .
Sexy I just could
not imagine how
we were gonna take
a beautiful girl,
cover her in hair and tattered
clothes, and make that sexy.
But In the end, you know
with the way everything came
together, she wasn't overly
hairy but it still translated,
you know, in the look that
it was definitely a werewolf.
Just that whole
composite background,
we gave it a nice creepy
sort of background,
but with her, sort of,
knee-up on the rock,
and was doing this very
provocative type of pose.
[INAUDIBLE] women I've
ever seen, I have to say.
The ghost shot was one that
we had to use our heads up
front while doing
the actual shoot.
You know, how are we
gonna create the illusion
of her floating
through the air, you
know, and actually
being a ghost?
We went ahead and decided
to actually just have
her standing, doing
her poems and then
I did separate shots of
her from the knee down,
just sitting on a
stool with her feet
sort of dangling out in a few
different angles and whatnot.
And then from there, it was
just sort of making sure
that those angles matched up
with the way she was standing
and everything,
you know, looking
as seamless as possible.
With the demon shot -- that's
the one where the young lady is
sitting on the chair,
she's got [INAUDIBLE].
That's directly inspired
by a Gil Elvgren painting.
The pose.
The whole, you know, holding
the pumpkin out and everything.
I kind of enjoy, in
that particular photo,
is having her face
on that pumpkin.
You know, creating the
jack-o-lantern with her face.
So for me, that was one of the
things I was most proud of.
Making it have that, sort
of, inner glow with her own
face on the jack-o-lantern.
This was a tough [INAUDIBLE]
for me to do because of,
you know, kind of
exploring new territories.
They wanted me to put my style
into it, but at the same time,
I sort of wanted to make
sure that the calendar was
a little bit distinct
from my normal, you know,
kind of everyday pinup style.
I think we were hugely
successful in doing that.
You know, the calendar's got,
sort of, my signature style,
but at the same
time, is of at least
a small departure from
what I normally do.
A lot of what I actually
learned in doing this calendar
has started to, sort of
filter into my daily work
with my clients, and
models that I work with.
[MUSIC]
-So there's a long
history of hearses.
They have motorcycle
hearses, they started out
with the horse-drawn
carriage hearses.
It's a very, very long history.
-Paired up with death, but
they're a beautiful car.
Each hearse is
totally custom built.
-Everbody likes to call
them a hearst with a t.
Pretty much 90%
of the population
tend to get that
wrong, and it just
digs into the bottom
my soul, but I'm
done correcting people in it.
If they can't read my
shirt then that's alright.
-You get a lot of funny
looks from people, you know?
Especially driving
through downtown Portland.
You know, people look to
see a hearse, and a hearse,
and a hearse, and you
can just watch heads turn
and people are always trying
to figure out what's going on.
-We are as Coffin Cruisers
-- we're in our ninth year.
There was another club
prior to that, and just
like any type of club you're
going to have differences
of opinions and that's kind of
what happened with the old club
that morphed into the new club.
-People start
hearse clubs so you
can be around people that
have the same interest.
There's lots of other
car clubs -- you know,
corvette clubs, mustang clubs.
-So we've had a pretty good
membership over the last
several years of, you know,
anywhere between 9-13/14
people, and just like other
cars, they come and go.
They break down and go
away, and typically that's
how we lose most of our members.
-My dad, he wanted
one ever since he
was in the third grade,
and my mom wanted one
since she was in high
school, and they came to me
and said, how would you
feel about having a hearse?
And I said as long
as it's white.
-For me it was the horror stuff.
For some reason, ever
since I was a little kid
I remember seeing like a hearse
going by, and it's like, oh
that's sweet.
What is that?
It just had -- it was a
slow funeral procession with
motorcycle police escorts, and
it was just amazing to see all
the traffic at a
dead stop, and let
this nice long procession go.
-Right there in
your face with it.
You got all that Detroit
steel right there.
I wanted one and I refused to
drive a minivan by all means,
you soccer moms are out.
-What makes a
hearse different is
they have a purpose, a very
specific purpose, which
is to take those
that have passed
to their final resting spot.
You're talking about
a 7,000-9,000 lb.
vehicle that hold two
people and a dead person,
and is typically
about 20-22 feet long.
They're hard to miss,
so they're fun to drive.
-When we have different car
shows -- things coming up,
or different events
for Halloween,
people will contact the
website, and then I try to get
in contact with them, see
how many cars they want,
if they want to
be all tricked out
for Halloween type
things or whatnot.
I remember we actually did
a wedding at the [INAUDIBLE]
cemetery that they wanted
the bride and the groom
to come up with the bridesmaids
and groomsmen, all in hearses.
That turned out really well.
My hearse is a 1970
Cadillac Miller Meteor.
It's -- I'm the fourth owner.
It's been owned
by two mortuaries.
It's specific purpose,
it appears to have
been mostly a
children's hearse .
It's painted very light
color, it's beige,
so that's a little unusual.
It's usually a
children's-related hearse.
And it shows a lot
of evidence of having
hauled a lot of small coffins.
-Well, my mom's not
too fond of the hearse.
I run a foster home for
medically-fragile, disabled
children, and I used my hearse
as a wheelchair vehicle.
She kind of cringes a
little bit when we show up
at Dorenbecher's
Children's Hospital
and I'm rolling out
looking like this,
with my tattoos pulling
wheelchairs out of the back.
And Kids have a seat that rides
in the back there as well.
That kind of freaks people out.
My daughter's doing
this out the window
as we're driving down the road.
-My friends and family, you
know, my dad helped me buy it,
and he's an eight-year-old
conservative Republican.
Maybe my neighbors
across street that
are trying to sell their house,
they don't necessarily like it
so much, but they're
about the only ones.
-I think you're probably
a hearse fan first,
if you own a hearse,
before you want to buy one.
Just 'cause you
like horror stuff,
if you like horror things
and go buy horror effects,
you know, a hearse
[INAUDIBLE] first,
and then probably have
an interest in, you know,
the dark side of things,
or the macabre stuff.
-I don't have like, it all deck
out with skeletons and things
like that.
I have it very classic,
with the white-wall tires,
and just want to keep
it as professional
looking as possible.
So that's my goal.
Just to have,like
a collector's car
that's a little more
on the macabre side.
-My cars' all are custom.
They've got skeletons hanging
from the ceiling in there.
You know, big fan
white walls was
kind of in your face vehicles.
DAD: Those look like
the Halloween props,
when we put the
Halloween props in.
-Especially Zilch.
-Yeah, especially Zilch.
Zilch is a little zombie
baby that we put in the car.
BOY: He creeps me out.
DAD: He doesn't like to ride
in the same seat as Zilch.
[MUSIC]
-My name's Voltaire, and I
have a little bit of trouble
explaining exactly
what it is that I do,
because I do a lot
of different things.
I started out as a
stop-motion animator.
I animated and directed some
of the early MTV and Sci-Fi
channel station IDs --
all of the spookier ones,
I like to think.
And I got into
making comic book,
so I made some comic
books -- sci-fi, horror,
usually with a touch of comedy.
And then at some point in the
'90s I learned to play guitar,
and I, on a dare,
played a live show which
got me signed to a
record label, and I've
been a recording
artists ever since.
[MUSIC]
-Everything I do
tends to be macabre.
So there's always,
sort of an appreciation
or a love for monsters
and the macabre,
and there's also,
usually, a sense of humor.
I don't choose to put
the macabre in my music.
The macabre is just in my
music, because I'm macabre.
And that may sound really,
I don't know, pretentious
or corny, but it's
just the truth.
Everything around
me, I inevitably
find some cynical or
sarcastic way of looking at.
I have been a fan of
monsters since as far back
as I can remember.
My earliest memories were
memories of, you know,
getting excited because
"King Kong Vs Godzilla"
was going to be
on the 4:30 movie.
As a child, if it had a monster
in it, that was all I needed.
So "King Kong" is
probably my favorite film,
and as far as I'm concerned
it's a monster movie.
I was on tour a few years ago,
and I was in Portland Oregon,
and I was in a bookstore
-- no record store,
and I saw a gentleman
signing a Bauhaus poster,
and that gentleman was
apparently the bass player --
David J. And at some point,
when I least expected it,
the man came up to
me and said, excuse
me is your name Voltaire?
And I said, yes.
He said, did you write a
book called "What is Goth?"
And I said, yes.
And he goes, I loved that book.
Would you autograph it for me?
And I like, wow -- the
bass player of Bauhaus
is asking me for my autograph.
This is pretty epic.
[MUSIC]
-Yes, I'm a founding father,
if not the godfather, of goth.
It is said that I wrote the
song, "Bela Lugosi's Dead,"
but actually I
made a contribution
to the song, in that I wrote
the lyrics and the bass line.
And then Peter saying it as if
he'd been singing it for years.
And then we recorded the
thing, like the next week.
So it was all very quick.
And then it was made into
a record very quickly,
and it took off.
[MUSIC]
-Director -- Mr. Scott.
He saw a performance of ours on
a TV show called "Riverside,"
and we were doing
"Bela Lugosi's Dead,"
and he ran it Bowie and
Bowie gave it the thumbs up.
As far as my favorite
type of horror film,
it's usually
psychological actually.
And the more subtle,
and the horror
that's implied rather
than shown, I think,
is much more potent.
IVAN DE PRUME:
Unleash with no fear.
People don't like it
when we hold back.
When you're -- we you
watch someone on stage
and they're holding back,
then we're going to hold back.
We're not gonna go crazy.
We notice when the
band is going crazy,
the audience is going crazy.
Right?
[MUSIC]
-We are Dead Animal
Assembly Plant.
We're a horror industrial band.
The story goes back to the
Sweet Meat's slaughterhouse.
It was found in the late
1800s by someone named Wilhelm
Schroder, who industrialized
butchery with the machines.
And after he was fed to the
machines by the townspeople,
the Sweet Meat's
Slaughter remained
empty until we came along.
-Be who you are -- 100%.
Kick ass, and then you're
gonna be proud of yourself,
because no one else is
gonna give a shit except you
in the end.
-The whole theme is
cannibalistic, murderous,
you know, slaughterhouse,
kind of dirty south --
more the embrace of
raw industrial sound.
It's not clean, it's not
perfect, but it is sincere.
-So If you want to do
a horror kind of thing,
do a horror kind of thing.
But do it 100% present!
Don't just do a
little dibble dabble.
Don't just get one monster,
get all the monster.
You know, make them
as ugly as you can.
Like, big teeth, you know?
With fire.
Saw blades.
-Virtually every
creative outlet I have,
horror films have wormed
their way into it.
-Started working on
independent feature films.
Did everything
from being a blood
guy to dealing with
the body parts.
-To which I'm really,
really grateful,
because it's made my work a
lot better and more interesting
than it use be, I think.
-To washing off the
naked women when
they were done doing
their blood scenes.
-I wrote a book
called "Shadow Play:
Philosophy and Psychology
of the Modern Horror Film,"
to explore aspects of the psyche
that we're trying to leave
behind as we reach
for civilization.
And horror films are
a perfect fantasy
arena to process all that stuff.
-Started developing a
distribution company
to distribute my own
movies, and then that
was the creation of "Iron
Virgin" and "Stripper Land,"
of writing and directing and
co-producing horror movies
with our own company,
to open the doors
to bigger and better things.
DANIELLE ANATHEMA: I
always love photography
because I can't paint.
Basically I like to capture an
image that looks like a movie
still.
When I was a child I had
horrific nightmares a lot,
and I was just
constantly terrified.
Kind of in my
junior high years I
just started to just try
and find the beauty in it,
and just watching horror
movie after horror movie,
and just got into the
makeup, and just realized
that it could be a
very beautiful thing
with such deep emotion, and
just kind of went from there.
-Horroregon.net -- which
is a website for news,
reviews, and interviews.
But really it's just me
finding a reason to get online
and trying to collect up stuff.
We will touch on national things
if it's something that we find
interesting or it comes
to us, but absolutely,
100%, specifically
Portland, and Oregon horror.
If you really wear your passions
outwardly and pursue them,
there's a large swath of the --
what you consider the average
pedestrian, Oregeonian
and Portlander,
that will follow you,
and will be enthused.
-Scream is for horror lovers.
If you are a fan of horror,
you want to read our magazine.
We cover classic horror
from the early 1920s,
right up to the present day.
Measuring up to Fangoria is
obviously a huge deal for us.
They have got a long
history -- even just
the name itself
carries such a cache.
-What makes me Moviecynics.com
unique is that, you know,
we're kind of assholes.
We tell it like it is, but
we try and be constructive
at least, especially when
working with indy filmmakers.
When it comes to
Hollywood horror movies
we'll terror those things apart.
Especially if they're garbage,
which a lot of them are.
-I usually don't go into
interviews unless I'm pretty
convinced A) That I"m going to
get something that the readers
are gonna want, and B) It's
kind of a personal thing,
where it's like, I
want to be enriched.
I've turned down interviews
with major horror stars
because I didn't feel like I
could learn anything from them.
-Since launching
MailOrderZOMBIE.com,
I've had an opportunity to
attend like the the Cripticon
Horror Convention, Horror
Hound Weekend in Indianapolis
or Cincinnati as a
fan, but also then
as a podcaster covering
it for my podcast.
And then sitting in
on panels as well.
And it's been a lot of
fun being able to flash
my MailOrderZOMBIE.com
business card
and say, hey I'm with
MailOrderZOMBIE.com,
can I interview you?
And then talk to people like
Tom Savini, Ken Foree, you know,
people that I looked up to
growing up when I finally
discovered horror
movies full on.
And be able to
connect with them,
and just thank them
for their work.
-I always look at
interviews like first dates.
You know, where on a first
date you're with someone,
you're going, tell
me about your job.
That's kinda what we're doing.
And as long as you are
interested and listen --
so often interviewers, I think,
they're slaves to their notes
and they're so busy preparing
for the next prepared question
that they're missing
all this gold.
-And they asked me,
would I go and cover it,
and speak to people,
and get a feel
for what horror conventions
in the US Are like.
In the UK, they tend to be
a lot lower key than this.
We don't have the
same kind of madness.
We don't have the same
people in costumes.
So it's been a crazy experience
for me to be here this weekend,
and just see the
level of fandom,
and just how much the bar
has been raised in America.
-I [INAUDIBLE] pretty hard
recently with Kate Beckinsale,
I'll say that.
Just because it's Kate
Beckinsale, come on,
and she smells amazing.
I think I've got
Elvira coming up,
which is another
one that you go --
do you want to talk to Elvira?
Fuck yeah, I want to talk
to Elvira, but after a while
you go, oh I get it.
There's this
infrastructure in place.
We're here to pimp your film.
We're here to pimp your book.
We're here to find
some stuff about --
the reason that brought
you to the table.
-Nine times out of
ten, I'm probably
going to have way more fun
with an independent horror
film than a Hollywood
horror film.
The Hollywood horror film
is catered to teenagers.
-I don't care if you
don't have a lot of money.
Spend some time on your script
developing your characters,
and make them somebody
that, you know,
I want to be invested with.
I want to spend time with
these guys for, you know,
90 minutes, whatever long
your movie's gonna be.
-It doesn't quite resonate
with people that grew up
in the '80s, and early '90s,
and '70s, watching just
brutal horror movies
that were entertaining,
well done and well
put together, but not
designed to get as many
people into the theater
seats as possible.
-If your characters
aren't somebody
that I'm going to
care about, I'm
not going to care
about your movie, man.
I don't care how big
your special effects are,
how bloody your
special effects are.
Give me some characters
that I care about.
-So you find this current
run of PG-13 horror films
that are just disposable,
uninteresting, cookie cutter,
formulaic.
-And don't take advantage of me.
Don't treat me like an idiot.
I've watched a lot of
horror movies, man.
You know, I have
certain expectations
to be treated as an equal
here, as a horror fan.
You know, if you're
making a horror movie,
I assume you like
horror movies as well,
so let's go on this
journey together.
Don't talk down to me, and
don't give me something
that you think I need to
see because every horror
movie has it.
You know, I like
nudity, whatever.
I like the special effects,
whatever, but give me
a solid story and give me
characters that I care about.
-You gotta have the violence.
I mean, tension goes a
long way, but in the end
you want that tension to lead
up to some actual violence.
You want to see the red
stuff on the screen.
I can probably count on my hand
the amount of successful horror
movies that, you know,
had all that tension
but didn't really
have the violence,
and within the
last 20 years, you
don't really see that very much.
-I've always said that
being a horror fan
is kind of like panning for
gold in a river of shit,
because you go
through a lot of crap.
-My name is Nowal, and
I love horror films
because when I was
about three years old,
my family was watching "Hell
Raiser 2" in the basement.
-I really enjoy the blood,
guts, and gore aspect of it.
The fact that it
always made my mom
scream whenever certain
things happened,
and I kind of got a sick
little thrill out of that.
-I remember watching "Hell
Raiser" when I was far too
young to be watching
"Hell Raiser."
-And I love the hooks
impaling the man's
flesh towards the end.
-I went downstairs and
hid behind the couch
and watched "Hell Rasier 2."
Nobody noticed I was there
until the movie was over,
and at one point I just
imagined something happened
and was like, oh shit!
And then my family's
like, oh OK.
Number one, you're
three, don't swear.
Number two, you're three and
it's like 11:00 at night,
why aren't you in bed, but
I remember seeing pinhead
for the first time at three, and
instead of being afraid of him,
I was like in awe of
just this character.
It was the first horror
icon, as pinhead, that I saw,
and I fell in love
with horror movies
at three years old
from his performance.
So I think if I
ever got the chance
to meet Doug Bradley I
would probably pass out.
Just that excited.
[MUSIC]
-I mean, I've been told I'm the
greatest actor who ever lived,
which I've been told.
So take a backseat, James Mason,
Marlon Brando, the rest of you.
Numero uno.
I mean, that's nuts.
My name is Doug Bradley.
I am best known, particularly
at horror conventions
for having played Pinhead
in the "Hellraiser" series.
I've also done a ton of other
movies, TV work, stage work.
I wrote a book even.
I was a fan of horror
movies as a teenager,
before I knew I was
going to be an actor.
And when I became
an actor I didn't
have any particular ambition
to work in the genre,
so the two have come
together quite happily.
When I first started
doing the conventions,
I was slightly freaked
out by mom dad,
and the kids coming to my table.
And the parents will be saying,
oh he loves your movies,
and I'm looking at him and
he's like seven years old,
and I, you know, not really
comfortable with that.
But I now have so many
people come to my table who
are clearly entirely together
and, you know, rational, calm
human beings who
encountered these movies
when there were
6, 7, 8 year olds.
The evidence of 20 years
of coming to conventions
is telling me that
it doesn't really,
you know, OK people will
have nightmares fora couple
of months, a couple of weeks,
a few nights, whatever.
But nobody seems, to me, to be
permanently scarred or damaged.
-I'm really excited
-- I got two VIP
tickets to Crypticon
for my birthday.
I get to meet Doug
Bradley -- Pinhead ,
in all of the most important
"Hellraiser" films.
When I meet Doug
Bradley, I'm pretty
sure I'll have the
most enormous nerdgasm
in the history of ever.
I'm gonna be nervous -- I
already am nervous to meet him.
I honestly don't know
what I'm going to do.
It's one of those moments
where like, don't be a freak.
Just do not be a freak.
[MUSIC]
-I walked around a little bit,
saw some awesome movie posters.
Then I turned a corner and
there was Doug Bradley,
and I freaked out.
I had to walk away.
I couldn't handle myself.
So I turned the corner,
and there was Dee Wallace.
And again I had to keep walking.
I'm still freaking out.
Like honestly, freaking out.
And it's gonna be
even more when I
go back to actually
meet Doug Bradley.
It was awesome.
I'm really proud
that I didn't vomit,
because I though that
was gonna happen.
And I showed him my tattoo,
and he translated it himself.
[SPEAKING LATIN] Wow.
-He didn't ask what it meant.
He's like, wait
-- do I look like
someone who cares
what God thinks?
In Latin.
That's amazing.
I was like -- and then I told
him that I've been a fan since
I was three, and so we shared
stories about things like,
you remember
watching it at three?
And I was like, yeah.
How could I not?
It was "Hellraiser." my friend
Brinn, that does my tattoes
can photocopy the signature
and tattoo it on me
when I get home. 'Cause I'm
definitely planning some kind
of Hellraiser-themed tattoo now.
I have been for a while,
but now it's official.
It's gonna happen.
My experience at Criptocon
has been great so far.
I'm gonna try and make
it back next year.
See who else is here.
It's really fun.
I had a lot of -- I'm gonna
have so many stories to tell.
I didn't vomit!
-Hold on one second,
I'm going out of frame,
but I'll be right back.
I still say it's the
standard that CGI effects,
though helpful,
though cost effective,
will never replace
good, crafted,
animatronics and makeup effects.
-Hello!
So it was a six-piece
application.
There was like one
piece that was here,
then cheeks, including
around the ears.
Neck .
From the eyes, up here,
and then another piece
over the back of the head.
It did get simplified to a
two-piece application later.
The nails, preset in the latex.
So as the pieces get glued on
to my head, the nails go on.
So when people ask
me, did it hurt?
Did you really have nails
banged in your head?
I say, yes I did.
I have very good healing flesh.
And I'm sponsored by Tylenol.
-I started modifying
masks when I was little.
I would take masks that
I had around the house,
or that I got really cheap,
and paint them, and cut them
up so they would
fit my face better.
And try and hot glue them,
and random things like that.
-I also just had a
fascination with monsters,
as a young boy, who wouldn't?
It kind me to mask
making when I got older,
and get into some
special effects hobbies ,
I guess you could say.
Nothing too professional,
but a lot of fun.
I have, the Wolfman, and
Frankenstein, and Dracula.
And on my back I have the
Bride of Frankenstein.
-My name is Dutch, and I'm
a professional face and body
artist.
The piece I'm working on right
now is gonna be, sort of,
a corset made out of human body
parts all stitched together.
It's a step by step process
where you have kinda layer
things on, and detail
it out as you go,
and then the finishing touches
kind of all comes together,
and you get your
finished product.
-I started out as a
makeup artist back
in, I guess about 1989/1990
in Victoria, British Columbia,
Canada.
I started doing
make up for the film
school that was
there at the time.
And the very first
"Final Destination,"
I was the effects designer.
And I've also done a slew
of Sci-fi Channel Network,
you know, creature of
the week type movies.
Many of those.
The last say, 3 or 4 years, I've
been teaching makeup effects,
as well as writing and
directing my own feature films.
-I'm just going for
patches of skin,
and eventually I'll paint
the Lisa's on there --
do some others texturing with
the skin, and stuff like that.
And it will look really
sharp when it's all done.
-I think what makes it
New Image College of Fine
Arts different than any other
school in North America,
basically is the fact that we
actually make feature films
at the school that end
up being distributed.
So we specialize in horror
movies, monster movies,
and the acting department --
the acting students get to act
in the feature
film, and the makeup
department does the make up.
My favorite special
effect that I've done
would be working on David
Cronenberg's "Existence."
I was in Toronto for
about six months.
Cronenberg is my, you
know, my filmmaking idol.
I mean, being fellow Canadian,
Cronenberg is God to me.
So to work on that, and
have him coming around
while I'm sculpting one of the
little amphibious creatures,
and he'd come by and
say, oh that's cool,
you know, I love
what you're doing.
I'm just like, oh!
I'm in heaven, you know?
-Our school is handing
out a crap ton of money
and scholarships, so
we sponsored this.
And it was just a
chance to kind of,
you know, see some of the
talent south of the border,
and you know, find some people
that might be interested.
You know, 'cause a lot of people
don't really know where to get
started in this industry,
or how to get started.
So, you know, it's
just education really,
is why we put this on, and it
gives ever body else a chance
that loves this sort of stuff
to try their hand at it.
-They typically give
everybody an identical kit,
and then they usually have some
sort of mystery ingredient.
So they want you to
do different stuff.
With this one, it
was more theme based.
They wanted beauty, as
well as, you know, a beast.
So it was the beauty and
the beast was the theme,
and I just wanted to personally
deviate from the zombie stuff.
You know, I mean everyone
can slap blood on people,
and make them all gory,
and make a zombie,
but I wanted to go in
a different direction.
What I'm hoping
to get from this,
I want a little bit
more in-depth knowledge
about what I'm working
with, so that I can
take my skill set
to the next level.
-I love Tom Savini.
He will always be Sex
Machine in my heart.
I'm sorry, I've always
wanted those pants.
-I did stumble across
a documentary called
"Scream Greats Volume
One," from Fangoria.
It's about Ton Savini,
and that became my entry
into a lot of modern
zombie effects, makeup
effects, and things like that.
-When people think
horror, that's
one of the main names that
comes to people's minds.
[MUSIC]
-I got so scared watching
movies when I was a kid,
that I decided I wanted to
-- I wanted to scare people.
I still have that.
I still have to scare people.
I scare my daughter at
home, you know, constantly.
My grandson, who's 9 years old.
It's a thrill.
It's the same thrill.
I mean why do you go
to the amusement park
and have somebody strap
you into a machine
and shoot you up into the sky.
You pay for that.
Just like you pay to
go see a horror movie.
The movie "A Man Of
A Thousand Faces."
I saw that movie when I was
11 years old, and that was it.
From that day on I
wanted to be the guy
that creates the monsters.
Before that, I thought
they were real.
You know, and they were real.
And that magic is
gone forever, you
know, once you get
behind the camera,
you know, behind the scenes.
That's the sad thing.
That's the irony that
most kids don't realize.
They want to be involved in
movies for the magic that some
-- the saw, but it kills the
magic forever, as you know.
Yeah.
The only two movies that have
scared me were "The Exorcist"
and "Alien," you know.
'Cause so many times you
go to see a movie and you're
thinking about camera angles,
and you know, what the
directors choices for making.
You didn't have to
time in those movies.
You were just getting
too scared, you know?
Plus I was raised a Catholic,
and it hit a nerve, you know?
[MUSIC]
-I'm into tattoos.
But yeah, I have
a lot of friends
who get a whole series
from a horror movie.
Like a full sleeve.
-Halloween's my
favorite holiday,
so a lot of the tattoos
are based on that.
Like this whole sleeve
is like Halloween- based,
but there's like a
little kid right here,
and he's got like dream
clouds around him,
so it's basically all supposed
to be like a nightmare.
On this arm, I've got a couple
of Vincent Price portraits
holding a portrait of me as a
kid zombie with my brains out.
-I like to refer to my
look as horror punk.
A lot of people call me goth.
My tattoos -- my favorite
one being my Elvira.
And then I have
my interpretation
of Gage and Church
from "Pet Cemetary."
And then, this is just my own
design of just a Halloween.
-I m on my neck I'm gonna
have two zombie hands
eventually, like
tearing my throat open.
-People get horror tattoos
because it's something
that's easily relateable They
can relates to the monsters
themselves, and they
have -- it's great art.
Depending on whether you're
doing a realistic tattoo
or not, it's pretty much -- you
take the portrait of the actual
tattoo, and you take a picture
and then you make a stencil
from that, and lay
it on the person
so it's directly the same thing.
Unless you're doing a custom
drawing of the tattoo, and then
you're making a
stencil for that.
[MUSIC]
DOUG BRADLEY: The loyalty of
horror fans is staggering.
-Attracts a highly
intelligent fan base
who are willing to
do the research work.
You know, drama fans are
or even action fans are.
They're willing to do it.
They're fiercely loyal.
Underestimate them
at your peril.
-People treat you
differently 'cause,
you know, you can kind
of sense that you're
like a die hard horror fan,
and then that scares them.
-People like to be scared
because, I mean, they know
their lives aren't in danger
when they're in a theater,
when they're in a
haunted house, you know?
They freak, but
then they kind of
laugh about it at the same time.
-It reflects a whole lot of
what happens to us in real life,
but it's also a huge
bit of escapism.
It's more or less the
mystery that scares me.
If it's something that's
gory and right in my face,
I can already see it.
I know what it is.
I know what I'm dealing with.
When I don't know with --
-Our idea of horror itself is
deeply based psychological.
We all have a fight
or flight response.
-But I think it's
almost therapeutic.
I really do.
I mean, I look at
myself and think back --
even in my youth, why
did I watch horror?
I think I had certain
fears of inhibitions,
and some how, on the screen,
it all played out for me.
-I think the true
horror for any of us
is the fear we have
within ourselves.
-The blood and guts stuff,
it's like that's nice,
but it's not really so
much what is frightening.
What's frightening is not really
understanding what's going on.
-It became very
tangible and doable.
I could watch it unfold.
Problems being solved,
monsters being resolved.
You know?
I think it's very, very healthy.
I really do.
-And I like good
versus evil, and that's
what they're all about.