I'm better now.
I think it helped.
That's good.
Things been busy?
Things are always busy, James.
I was thinking,
I could just [???] you how land
and drive myself to Boston.
That way you wouldn't
have to leave the farm.
What do you think?
We need to talk about
you going to college.
FAIR HAVEN ORCHAND
James.
That was my money, you
had no right to use it!
Sometimes life is unfair,
we both know that.
There were hospital bills, and the funeral had to
be paid for. Not to mention your treatment
Look, I've been putting some money
away while you were gone so,
If you could just help with the harvest next Fall
then maybe you could go to college in a year.
I already deferred my enrollment once
and give my spot to somebody else.
I'm doing my best, James. Jesus.
When was the last time you
fantasized sexually about a man?
About four months ago, I guess.
- Nothing since then?
- No.
- Dreams?
- Gay dreams?
- No.
- What about women?
- I think about women often.
- And what do you think about when you masturbate?
- I don't masturbate.
- You looking forward to go home?
- No, I've had a very nice time here.
I'm not trying to trick you.
I'm sure it would be very nice.
- Have you spoken with your father?
- He called on my birthday.
How's he doing?
Seems fine.
James did your father ever seek counciling
after your mother passed away?
- He may not dealt with his grief.
- My father' is a very strong man, I don't think he'll need therapy for anything.
Sometimes even strong people
need someone to talk to.
I'm sure he'll be glad to have you
around before you head off to ...
Berklee College of Music. You
must be looking forward to that.
Yes, very much.
When you came here you said your greatest
desire was to become a concert pianist.
Is that still the case?
I'd still like to but... it's not the most
important thing in life anymore.
What is now?
God,
I'd like to settle down,
meet a girl have a family.
I am sure you can still fit
music in there somewhere.
Being away from home
you're going to find yourself
in a lot of new situations
It'll be a lot of temptations
out there for you.
I know.
I'll be good.
I'm sure you will.
Well, I think that's badassery.
Once more  before taking the road?
Our Father who hart in heaven .
We ask you to bless James as
he goes forth from here today.
To watch over him as he
walks through temptation.
Guide him, help him,
deliver him from evil.
Lead him on your path to salvation.
Help him to avoid the
sins of the flesh
And to embrace the
glory of your light.
We ask these things in
your name, oh Lord
And pray.
- Amen.
Goddamit!
- You okay?
- Yeah, just stupid.
Watch out the handle
is really hot.
I've been thinking.
Maybe taking a course at the Community College
would be a better idea. Give you a leg up.
I don't know the courses they have I don't
know if Berklee would accept them.
If I were you I wouldn't go to
Boston I'd stay closer to home.
Vermont Tech is a good school.
Dad, I'm studying music.
- What to be a teacher?
- Maybe. Or play.
Okay.
That's what I wanna do.
But less.
Look, if I'm paying for this I want you to major in
either agricultural business or something like that.
- Maybe I will pay for it.
- And how you gonna do that?
I'll find a job.
Doing what?
Whatever I have to.
A minimum wage is not gonna
pay the bills and school both.
Dammit! I'll figure it out.
Why do you have to make things so
difficult? I want what's best for you.
You know, one day you gonna inherit this place.
You gonna have this place all to yourself.
Not any time soon.
We can hope not.
But when you do, I want
you to be able to run it.
That's mine so
I'll have to sell it.
No, you will not sell this farm.
This farm was your grandfather's,
this farm is my grandfather's!
This place is home, this place is a roof over your
head it's money in the bank when you needed.
You don't understand that
now, you have no idea.
But one day you'll appreciate it.
Why can't you see I'm just trying
to do what's best for you?
I'll take a look at those classes.
The Community College.
- I appreciate it.
- Yeah.
You can just drive around back to load
in the dock. Someone can give you a hand.
Make sure you get a receipt.
Can you handle that?
Yeah.
James?!
When did you get back?
A few days ago.
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
- What are you doing here?
- I work here.
We can't be friends
anymore, okay?
Friends?
I can't be around you.
I see.
Things are different now.
I'm different.
So you..?
I got to go.
How are you feeling right now?
Sad.
Can you expand on that?
Sad? How? Describe it.
Alone. I feel alone.
Lonely.
Do you miss your mother?
Yes.
Your father?
What about your friends?
Were you close to them?
Did you have any
special friends?
You mean like best friends?
More special than that.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
What about a boyfriend?
It's okay. You can tell me.
Yes.
How many?
One.
What is his name?
Charlie.
Were you intimate?
It's okay, you can tell me.
Sometimes.
How that make you feel?
I don't know. Good I guess.
Sins makes us feel good while we're commiting
it, James but that doesn't mean it's good for us.
It can really mess us up inside.
And when we're done,
we feel bad about it.
Does that make sense?
Yes.
Charlie is like a drug.
It's hard being away from him right now I
know but being with him would be worse.
Once he's out of your system I promise
you, you're going to feel so much better.
And then you gonna wonder why
you ever had him in your life.
Did you get that receipt?
Well?
Dad can you take care
of this from now on?
Why?
I give you one simple job you can't even do that?
- Forget it.
I need the receipts.
- What?
- I need the receipts for the apples!
Dammit.
Hurry up please.
What did they do to you?
Don't worry about it.
Are you happier?
You seem happier.
Maybe I should be send -
I wanna go to church.
- What now?
- On Sunday.
- Alright?
- Yeah I guess.
When you were slaves of sin, you were
free in regard to righteousness
So what fruit did you then get from the
things which you are now ashamed?
The end of those
things is death.
But now that you've been freed
from sin and enslaved to God,
The fruit that you
get is eternal life.
For the wages of sin is death and
the gift of God, is eternal life.
In Jesus Christ
Our Lord.
- Thank you.
Richard.
James. So great to have
you back with us.
How have you holding up?
- He's doing alright.
- That's good to hear.
- How old are you now?
- I'm 19.
- My Suzi just turned 19. She's going to UVM in the Fall.
- That's a good school.
James is saying good bye for Vermont Tech.
Maybe Suzi could give him some advise.
I'm sure she would love that.
Hang on, Suzi, could you
come here honey?
- Suzi, you remember James?
- Yeah, not well, we were a year apart in school.
He's going to college in the Fall. Maybe
you could help him with his application.
Yeah I would love to. Let
me give you my number.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
ONLINE REGISTRATION SELECTED COURSES
AGRICULTURE 9:00-10:00 MUSIC THEORY 9:00 - 10:30
musical theory: 9:00 to 10:30
It looks good.
- How many can I take?
- One should be enough now.
Okay.
Have you called Suzi yet?
- No.
- She seems like a nice girl.
Pretty too.
Yeah.
James, come on in!
- How are you?
- Okay.
Great.
Suzi!
She'll be right down.
- Hi.
So do you want to
come to my room?
Here's my application.
Take a look at it.
Thank you.
I get the feeling you're not really
looking for help with this.
I'm sorry, I don't
mean to be rude.
Why the lack of interest?
My dad wants me to apply
to a state school, but I was...
I'd like to go somewhere else.
Where do you wanna go?
I was accepted at Berklee
College of Music in Boston.
Wow congratulations!
Thank you.
Dad says it's not
practical though.
I see.
He's probably just trying to do
what he thinks is best for you.
You are engaged.
No, it's a promise ring.
What is that?
It means I've promised to stay
a virgin until I'm married.
- It's silly, it's okay.
- No, I don't think so.
Well, you know... I should...
I have some stuff
to do I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry I wasn't of much help.
- Don't worry about it I'll figure out.
And if you have any more
questions you have my number.
Or, we could just hang out, you
know it could be funny too.
- Hang out?
- Yeah.
We could grab some dinner, watch
a movie have something fun.
Sure.
You don't have to
if you don't want to.
Yeah...
I need to check my schedule.
I'll give you a call.
- Alright.
- Okay.
Bye.
I'll be back with your receipts.
I'm sorry about how
I acted the other day.
You should be.
I don't agree with this.
But If we can't be lovers
we could at least be civil.
Yeah.
Did your father ever hit you?
No.
Why are we doing this?
I'm trying to estabilish if there's been
any emotional trauma in your life.
Something that happened a long time
ago that you may have forgotten about.
I don't think so I think
I would remember it.
No, not necessarily. We often repress
difficult or painful memories.
If something like that
did happened if...
You were abused or mistreated, for instance
it would help explain your situation now.
And if that's the case working
on that might help you to
Transition back to healthy
heterosexual desires.
Like I'd be interested in girls?
I believe you already are. Deep down.
That's what nature intended you to be.
Something just knocked you
off course along the way.
I mean I wasn't abused or molested
or anything like that.
Okay, that's great.
We'll look for another explanation then. You
and I can work on finding that together.
I want to help you, James.
But you have to want it too.
- I do.
- Good.
It won't be easy. You have to work at it, you
have to push yourself toward healthy behavior.
Try to avoid temptation.
Everyone is different. You may have tremendous success
walk out of here a total heterosexual young man,
Or you may struggle
with your feelings.
Hello, hi, it's James. How are you?
Good. I'm good.
Listen, I was thinking
about what you said,
And I was wondering if maybe you
want to grab dinner tonight?
Yeah, sure.
Sure, six o'clock.
Yeah I agree. See you there.
Bye.
I was heading into town. I just wondered
if you needed some supplies?
No, I'm fine.
You gotta buy
books, don't you?
Yeah but I don't know
until classes start.
If you need more let me know.
Are you going somewhere?
Yeah, I was going to
grab dinner with Suzi.
Where you going?
I don't know.
Go to the Rubi's. I know they don't look
like much, but the food is good, honestly.
Here my treat.
- Have a big time.
- Thanks.
- We can go somewhere else.
- No, this is fine.
- There's lots of personality.
- You sure?
- Absolutely.
- You guys want an appetizer?
- What do you have?
- Chips, pretzels, peanuts.
- I think we're okay for now.
- Let me know when you're ready to order.
- I'm sorry.
-Don't be.
My dad is always saying this place is a den
of sins. I've been dying to see why.
I'm kidding. It's fine.
In fact, I wish you
would have sinner.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I wish we had known each
other in High school.
We were in different
grounds I guess.
You were always with Brad
Miler and Charlie Greene.
Is it true what they
say about Charlie?
- What did they say?
- That he is gay.
I don't think I should reveal
the details of his life.
That's crazy!
Does it bother you?
I think that people should
live as they like.
- Thanks again.
- Yeah sure thing.
Guess we see around.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
- I'm sorry.
- No, I'm sorry, I...
- I should get off.
- No, no, listen...
I'd like to take things slowly.
- I think slowly is better for me.
- Okay.
Look, I'd like for us to be...
How you want.
Sure. You do.
Yeah...
I should go then.
- Bye.
You still dreaming about
girls? Sexually?
Does anyone know why
we have dreams?
Dreams are our brains way of making sense
of the things we experience during the day.
So if for instance, we see
a dog when we are awake,
And we think about that dog.
We may dream about it at night.
When our brain is sorting out those
memories. Does that makes sense?
So if you're having sexual
dreams about women at night,
It's probably because you're thinking
about them sexually during the day.
- But I wasn't.
- It's okay.
Everyone slips up from time to time.
You just have to focus and try your best
To stay away from thoughts and situations
that will lead you down the wrong path.
Remember your body wants you to
be attracted to the opposite sex.
Why is that?
Because that's what
god intended.
I'm not sure
I believe in God.
That's okay, James.
He believes in you.
God made Adam and Eve.
One man and one woman. Because
that's what's required to have a baby.
Not two men, not two women not
three people of different genders.
One and one.
And that's not just to us people
but also in the animal kingdom.
One male lion and one female
lion can make a baby lion.
One male zebra and one female
zebra can make a baby zebra.
Right. I get it.
It's in your genes. Your body
wants you to be with a woman
So that you can make babies
and carry on the species.
- I don't think I want babies.
- Well...
Maybe not right now, but one
day you will when you're ready.
And you won't be able to have
them with another woman.
I appreciate your interest,
it is a fine offer,
You know it is not for sale. It's been
in the family for generations.
Okay. I'm new here. And interested in
take the orchand in a different direction.
A lot of people in the area
think about more organic.
Sure. A lot of the grocery stores
they really get a lot of interest
I think they would pay extra
for organic apples and-
Good luck with that.
The place ain't for sale.
That's a shame you've got
a beautiful property here.
There's nothing we can
do to change your mind?
I don't think so.
Okay then.
Let me give you my card.
- And if you change your mind.
- You don't need to waste your cards.
Please keep it.
- Alright, good luck.
- Thank you.
- Who were those people?
- A couple of weirdoes.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What did they want?
They wanted to buy the farm.
Incredible. What
did you tell them?
What do I think I told them?
Not thinking about it?
They want to modernize
it. Go organic.
I told them the apples are already organic,
they come right out of the ground.
It think they meant the ones
they use less pesticides dad.
They're not very good
farmers then are they?
A lot of people are starting to think like them.
- It is a phase, it will pass.
I'm just saying we gotta
look into it that's all.
James I appreciate
you want to help
But trust me when I say I know
what the hell I'm doing okay?
When you run the show, you can
grow apples anyway you want.
Maybe then you'll find out your old
man knows what he's talking about.
You still in your pajamas?
- I'm sorry, but I'm one handed.
- What happened to you?
- I knocked a door...
- Charlie...
A couple of guys after work.
- Here?
- No.
Down in the road.
I go walking home.
You can't walk home
on foot from here!
It won't happen again,
okay? I'll be careful.
No, you won't walk
home, I'll drive you.
- James I don't need an escort.
- I don't care.
What time is your shift over?
- James...
- What time is your shift over?
- Nine.
- Okay.
See you at nine.
Here it is!
Hi.
- What it's going on?
- I dropped by to surprise you.
I hope that's okay.
Yeah. Sure.
- It was nice sit with you.
- You too.
So my parents wanted me to
invite you to dinner tonight.
You know my dad actually is gonna
be cooking dinner tonight.
I just told him I was gonna invite you to dinner
with us and he said he didn't mind eating alone.
- If you don't wanna come it's
- No, no, I do.
- What time?
- Seven thirty.
- Okay.
- I'll see you then. Bye.
Steak...
Getting pretty handy
with the oven.
- You look nice.
- Thanks.
Tell your girlfriend that tomorrow
we'll have her for dinner over here.
We have to keep practicing
not to poison her.
Your mom would be
proud of you.
Have a good time.
How are things on
the farm James?
We drive by there almost
every day, don't we ?
- All the time.
- It's gorgeous.
- It is.
- It's nice.
And so what is it like working
on a apple farm?
It's fine. I guess.
- A lot of work.
- I bet.
How long is it been
in your family now?
A long time.
- Well, well...
- It's incredible.
It's only fair having apples from
Fair Haven from now on.
- And Suzi told us that you play music.
- Yes, I do piano.
That's lovely! You'll have to play
something for us some time.
I'd gladly do. Do
you have a piano?
No. We don't.
James is gonna take over
the farm someday.
That's great. That's very admirable.
Keeping the family business going.
A lot of kids these days they want
nothing to do with tradition.
As soon as they graduate
school, they're gone.
So true.
It's good to hear you'll be staying
in the area the long term. I mean,
We wouldn't want you to whisk our
daughter to God knows where!
- Dad!
- Stop it, you gonna scare him.
Come on he knows I'm
joking, right James?
Yes, sir.
I mean, come on, it's not like
I've mentioned their children.
What do you feel about children?
You want some some day?
It's nine o' clock right?
Yes.
I'm sorry I have to run. The
dinner was really wonderful.
Thank you so much.
James.
James
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah, everything is fine.
Are you sure?
I just forgot I had a
thing to do at nine.
My dad was just joking around.
- It's fine. I got to run.
How bad is it?
Not bad.
You should start carrying pepper spray.
- I should get out of this town.
Still thinking in
joining the Circus?
- That was a good idea.
- Not it wasn't.
I could be the most famous sword
swallower of America at this point.
Why aren't you then?
Because you wouldn't
come with me.
Hold on.
Thanks.
Sure.
See you tomorrow?
What you felt for your boyfriend,
wasn't love. It was lust.
- You don't know that.
- Love is different.
Think about your parents right now.
Your mothers and your fathers.
Think about how
they make you feel.
That is love.
Now think about someone of
the same sex you're attracted to.
It's the same feeling?
Sometimes we remember things the way we prefer
them to be not the way they actually were.
The way you describe your relationship,
when you and your boyfriend were together
You could hardly keep
your clothes on.
That's not true love.
There's nothing pure or
beautiful about that it's lust.
Pleasures of the flesh.
If you would run into your
boyfriend again right now,
You would probably
yearn to be with him.
You would want him to touch you, hug you,
kiss you. But that's the devil's influence.
Sin is very attractive. You
have to fight against it.
It's different with girls?
Sometimes.
Sure, you can lust after girls but
you can also fall in love with one,
And believe me, that's
worth waiting for.
You can't fall in love with
a man, it is impossible.
How do you know?
My father told me.
Right here.
You follow this and you'll
know the difference.
Fuck! Goddammit!
- Having trouble?
- What the hell it looks like?
What is it?
Those yankees came back
again this morning.
- Who?
- The ones trying to buy the farm.
- I thought you told them no.
- I did.
They thought maybe I'd changed my
mind they gave me a better offer.
- How much?
- It doesn't matter.
- I'm just curious.
- Not enough.
- This place worths more than money.
- Yeah, but how much money?
Seven-fifty.
$ 750,000?
- Dad why did you say no?
- I told you.
No with that kind of money you
could do whatever you want I -
I told you I'm not selling it!
I could go to school for godsake!
James I'm not gonna discuss
it anymore, alright?
You got chores to
do. Go do them.
Now!
Jesus.
Come on you son of a bitch.
Play the one your
mom used to play.
You would like to
hear that one again.
Please.
He don't even consider
what I want.
All he cares is about is a
stupid family tradition.
- It's your family's.
- I don't care about.
With that kind of money
I could do anything.
I guess there's one
thing left to do.
We have to kill him.
- That's not funny.
- It was a little funny.
No. It wasn't.
Seriously though. I don't think
your dad should run your life.
What other choice do I have?
Tons. You have
nothing but choices.
So he won't make it easier for you?
Big deal. We've do it on your own.
- It's too hard.
- Poor of you it's too hard.
So life is rough for a few
years. Then it'll be great.
Or you can just sit here, do what you're
told stay here and be miserable.
- Thanks for the ride.
- You're welcome.
- If you want something for it?
- No, don't worry about it.
Why don't we grab something
to eat some time? As friends.
Nothing more. I promise.
When?
I'm free Saturday night.
Alright.
Okay.
Pick me at six?
See you.
SUZI
Good?
Yeah.
My dad has been teaching
himself how to cook.
He's huh...
Sort of bad now actually.
See? Doesn't need you.
He needs my help on the farm.
My mom would have
wanted me to stay.
Your mom would want
you to live your life.
How was it like there?
My dad found a place online.
I don't think it was what
he was looking for, but...
I think he knew that they
were Christian therapists...
It was always a big part
of my mother's life.
It seemed so bad at first.
I had a lot of grief and anger.
I was mad at god
and my mother...
It helped me to get pass that.
And they said if I wanted someone to
blame I really had to blame myself.
They said that sometimes ...
If our lives aren't according
to god's plan,
He send us a sign to
get us back on track.
How can you believe that?
I started to.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
You're still as fast
as you used to be?
What?
What the hell!
Hey, hey.
This way.
James, will you sleep all day?
James!
- Not yet.
- I'm sorry.
- What time is it?
- I don't know.
- We should get up.
- No. - Yes.
- Before my dad wakes up.
- No.
- And kill us.
No.
- Hi.
- I really missed you.
- I missed you too.
- Who the hell is that?
- Suzi!
Suzi! Suzi, wait!
Suzi!
- Wait, I'm sorry.
- You bastard!
- You're a bastard!
- Wait!
- Don't touch me!
- You listen to me?
You know what you are? You're
disgusting. You're pathetic.
Burn in hell!
- You're okay?
- Yeah.
I'm fine.
James.
- Wait in the truck.
- Yeah.
Listen, it did look pretty bad.
I had to break up with Suzi just
now and Charlie is a friend from-
Just stop!
I honestly have no
idea what to do.
Maybe if your mother was here
she would know but I have no idea.
- About what?
- About you.
About how to help you.
Help me with what?
To help you grow up,
help you to be a man.
- I am a man.
- Yeah, you're one hell of a man.
Go ahead.
Say it.
Go ahead and say it.
No come on I want you to.
That's okay.
You were never the kind of man
I wanted for a father either.
Mom saw you now she'd be
ashamed you know that?
That makes two of us I guess.
I guess.
Well, look who
the cat dragged in?
I haven't seen you
a while Ricky.
- Awfully early to be pissed drunk.
- You want my money or not?
I saw your boy in here a while
back with a pretty girl.
He isn't my boy.
I didn't know him.
I'm sure every father said that about
their boy some point or another.
Bulshit!
I minded my old man.
Didn't you tell me one time about when
you were 17 you wanted to run away?
Cause your old man wouldn't
let you join in the army?
You don't remember as
well as you think you do.
- Oh no?
- No.
I was eighteen and
it was the Marines.
And I would made
a damn fine one too.
Of course you would.
- You ever think about that?
- What the Mariners?
Seeing the world, never know
where you have ended up.
You don't always get
what you wanted.
So I heard there's this
really nice couple
Looking around town lately.
Looking to buy some land.
Have they up to see you?
They have.
How was their offer?
Insufficient.
That is a shame.
If it was more you might be
able to get their apple business.
Live a little.
I'm not a young man anymore.
But you're not worn out either.
See you around.
Take care, Ricky.
Don't be a stranger.
What about your dad?
I don't know.
- I don't think I can go home.
- You think he'll hurt you?
No... no.
I just don't think he wants
me there anymore.
You can stay with me.
It's not a permanent solution.
So we leave.
Yeah?
Where would we go?
I don't know.
The circus?
I'll just go in.
Pack my clothes,
what else I need.
Then leave.
And then the circus.
Okay?
Right. Here it go.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome. Have a great day.
- Hey, Rich.
- Hey.
- How's the apple business?
- It's fine, it's fine.
- Listen, I'm sorry I'm so late.
- Don't worry about it. I'll get your receipt.
Thanks.
100% Organic
- Excuse me.
- Sure.
Here it go.
- So a lot of folks go for the organic?
- Yeah, actually they're very popular.
Let's see Winston Clark switched
to organic. You know Winston?
Yeah.
The Shelley's also went
to the organic.
- See you later.
- Hmm.
Hi. How can I help you?
That's all?
Good.
It's all $ 11.
You play better than she did.
- I was... - James...
- I was just leaving.
- I don't really want to talk about it.
- Just wait. Just wait.
Sit down. Please.
For a minute.
Where you're going?
- I was thinking of going to Boston.
- Alone?
No.
Is he... What's his name again?
- Charlie.
Is he the one from before?
Yeah.
Your mother and I were pretty
concerned about that.
So you ended up at that place.
I'm sorry about that.
You care about each other?
Yeah.
We do. Very much.
That's good.
I want to apologize for what I
said yesterday. That wasn't right.
I don't know If I'll ever
understand it but.
I think I can do a better
job of accepting it.
Thank you.
I decided to sell the farm.
- What?
- I took the offer.
Why? Why would you...?
You know I've been running this place
for the last 20 years for my dad
When I should have been
running it for you.
I'll give you some of the money you can
go to school, move away, whatever you want.
I guess, I guess I'll retire.
Anyway.
The farm isn't family we are.
Dad I'm sorry that things
didn't really work out.
Don't.
That's life.
We just do the best
we can, okay?
Okay.
COMING SOON ST. JOHN'S ORGANICS
- We didn't miss it?
- No I still got about 10 minutes.
Okay.
- I should, we should...
- Yeah.
I...
- Call if you need anything.
- I will.
Your mother would
be proud of you.
I am too.
Well ...
- You better get going.
- Yeah.
English Subtitles:
Pinky and the Brain