[♪♪♪]
[DOOR BELL JINGLES]
LOVELY.
VERY NICE.
PERFECT.
OKAY, JUST BE CAREFUL
LOADING IT IN THE VAN.
THANK YOU.
BETTY, THE CENTERPIECES
ARE PERFECT, JUST BEAUTIFUL.
AND THE BOUQUET?
ALREADY AT THE
CHURCH WITH EMILY.
OF COURSE IT IS.
SHE'S A GOOD GIRL.
OH, YES!
COME ON OUT.
PUT THEM IN THE VAN.
THOSE ARE LOVELY.
HEY!
THIS ISN'T A RACE TRACK,
YOU KNOW!
AND, ROSEANNE,
I'M THINKING,
INSTEAD OF STARTING
WITH THE FIRST DANCE,
WE HAVE THE GROOM
SAY A FEW WORDS.
I'M REALLY THINK
IT'LL BE LOVELY.
IT'S OBVIOUS THIS COUPLE
IS MEANT FOR EACH ANOTHER...
YEAH, UH,
PUT A PIN ON THAT.
UM, WE MIGHT HAVE
A LITTLE PROBLEM.
OKAY, SEE THESE?
THEY DON'T MATCH.
THESE FLOWERS ARE WHITER
THAN MY DRESS.
OKAY, NO,
IT'S NO PROBLEM.
UM, EMILY,
SWEETHEART?
IT APPEARS THAT THE
FLOWERS ARE CLASHING
WITH THE BRIDE'S DRESS.
CAN YOU FIX IT?
NOT A PROBLEM.
VANESSA, COME WITH ME.
LOOK AT THAT EMILY.
SO TOGETHER, SO
GROUNDED, SO PERFECT.
I STILL CAN'T
FIGURE OUT
WHY SHE AND COLLIN
NEVER WORKED OUT.
OKAY, NOW IS NOT THE TIME
TO DISCUSS YOUR SON'S LOVE LIFE,
OKAY?
ESPECIALLY WHEN THE GROOM
SEEMS TO BE MISSING.
I'M ON IT.
YOU KNOW, THAT DRESS REALLY
MAKES THE GREEN IN YOUR EYES,
LIKE, POP.
[GIGGLES]
OH, THERE YOU ARE.
DO YOU WANNA GET MARRIED?
[PASTOR]: DO YOU, ROBERT GRANT,
TAKE VANESSA FRASER TO BE
YOUR LAWFULLY WEDDED WIFE?
I DO.
AND DO YOU, VANESSA FRASER,
TAKE ROBERT GRANT TO BE
YOUR LAWFULLY WEDDED HUSBAND?
I DO.
ROBERT AND VANESSA...
SEE? PERFECT.
[PASTOR] MARRIAGE OFFERS YOU
THE PROMISE OF LOVE,
WHICH IS TRUE
AND MATURE.
I NOW PRONOUNCE YOU...
HUSBAND AND WIFE.
YOU MAY KISS THE BRIDE.
[APPLAUSE]
[♪♪♪]
AW!
OKAY, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
JUST ONE FOR ME
BEFORE YOU GO.
[FRIENDS]: BYE!
I NEED YOU TO TAKE
A LOOK AT SOMETHING.
I HEARD HE WAS MOVING
NEXT TO OUR SHOP.
[MARCO SPEAKS ITALIAN]
ON THE RIGHT SIDE,
A LITTLE HIGHER.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON.
THEY DIDN'T SEND A NOTE
ABOUT IT OR ANYTHING.
JUST BRING IT UP.
IT'S A LITTLE TOO LOW
ON THE RIGHT-HAND SIDE.
MAKE IT... YEAH.
YES, PERFECT, LIKE THAT.
[SPEAKS ITALIAN]
OKAY, EXCUSE ME?
EXCUSE ME!
YOU JUST PLACED YOUR SIGN
IN FRONT OF OUR WEDDING CHAPEL.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
OH, YOU LIKE THAT?
PERSONALLY,
I THINK THEY WENT A LITTLE
TOO HEAVY ON THE AIRBRUSHING.
I'M MARCO, MARCO AMORINI.
ROSEANNE.
YOUR NEW NEIGHBOR.
FROM THE WEDDING PLACE
NEXT DOOR!
WELL, IT'S A PLEASURE
TO FINALLY MEET YOU.
WELL, THAT'S MY LITTLE
WEDDING PLACE NEXT DOOR....
WEDDING PLANNING,
TO BE EXACT.
NOW, WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO
ABOUT YOUR SIGNAGE?
I'M SO SORRY.
I'VE GOT A 12:00
ANY MINUTE.
CIAO, BELLE!
UNBELIEVABLE.
YOU'RE TELLING ME.
WHOO...
WELL, I'M OFF TO MAKE DINNER
AND TO HELP GARY NEGOTIATE
OUR CURFEW FOR OUR DAUGHTER.
WELL, THANK YOU FOR
EVERYTHING, ROSEANNE.
I COULD NOT HAVE PULLED
IT OFF WITHOUT YOU.
WE CANNOT HAVE A DIVORCE
ATTORNEY NEXT DOOR!
WELL, YOU FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO GET RID OF CAPTAIN GORGEOUS,
AND I'M GOING HOME.
NIGHT-NIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT.
OH, I GOT THAT FOR YA.
THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK
WE WERE FORMALLY INTRODUCED.
I'M MARCO AMORINI.
AH, WENDY.
WENDY HAMPTON.
WELL, NICE TO MEET
YOU, WENDY HAMPTON.
GOOD NIGHT.
WELL, DENNIS...
LOOKS LIKE WE PULLED OFF
ANOTHER ONE TODAY.
EXCEPT FOR MY NEW NEIGHBOR.
[FRIENDLY KNOCKING]
LOGAN!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
DATE NIGHT, REMEMBER?
OH...
RIGHT, YEAH, OF COURSE.
I'M SO SORRY.
YOU WILL NOT BELIEVE
THE DAY I HAD.
A DIVORCE ATTORNEY HAS MOVED IN
RIGHT NEXT DOOR TO MY SHOP!
OH...
WELL, IT IS MOVIE NIGHT,
BUT IF YOU'D RATHER,
WE COULD STAY IN
AND PLAY "WORDORAMA".
OH, RIGHT, YEAH.
WOW, I HAVEN'T PLAYED
WORDORAMA IN YEARS.
GOTTA WARN YA,
I'M PRETTY GOOD.
OKAY, THEN.
OKAY...
MITOCHONDRIA.
THAT IS A TRIPLE-WORD SCORE,
AND THAT IS...
60 POINTS FOR ME.
MITOCHONDRIA?
IT'S A MEMBRANE-BOUND ORGANELLE
FOUND IN MOST EUKARYOTIC CELLS.
YOUR TURN.
OKAY!
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S SEE.
[BLOWS AIR OUT
IN RASPBERRY]
UH, THE TIMER IS...
MYEH!
[PHONE RINGS]
[SIGHS]
DOESN'T COUNT.
HELLO?
[COLLIN]:
HEY, MOM.
COLLIN! SWEETHEART, I WAS
JUST THINKING ABOUT YOU.
I JUST WANTED
TO LET YOU KNOW
THAT I'M COMING HOME
TOMORROW MORNING.
YOU ARE?
TOMORROW MORNING?
IT'S THE MIDDLE
OF THE SEMESTER.
IS-- IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH, I'LL EXPLAIN
WHEN I SEE YOU.
I LOVE YOU.
OKAY... OKAY,
I LOVE YOU, TOO, BABY.
THAT WAS COLLIN.
HE'S COMING HOME
TOMORROW MORNING.
HMM.
UH, SHOULD I RESET THE TIMER?
[DOORBELL RINGS]
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WOULD IT BE OKAY
IF WE JUST, UH...
FINISH THIS NEXT WEEK?
I PROMISE,
I WON'T TOUCH A THING.
OKAY, I'LL JUST MAKE NOTES.
DAD!
HEY, KID, CAN I COME IN?
IT'S COLD OUT THERE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
COLLIN CALLED ME
THIS MORNING...
SAID HE WAS COMING HOME.
HE ASKED ME TO BE HERE.
OH, I DIDN'T MEAN
TO INTERRUPT YOUR DATE.
COLLIN CALLED YOU THIS MORNING?
WONDER WHY HE DIDN'T
CALL ME EARLIER.
EVENING, RAY.
LOGAN, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
DAD, DID COLLIN TELL YOU
WHY HE WAS COMING HOME?
HE HAS SOME NEWS.
OH, HEY, THEN
WE CAN FINISH OUR GAME.
UH, NO, I'M SORRY, LOGAN.
I'VE GOT TO GET
TO THE STORE.
I HAVE NOTHING TO FIX COLLIN
FOR BREAKFAST,
AND I KNOW HE'LL BE HUNGRY.
[DOOR CLOSES]
DO YOU LOVE WORDORAMA?
COME ON!
SURE.
AH, ALMOST.
[RAY]: WELL, I MISS YOU,
TOO, MY SUGAR BEAR,
BUT I PROMISE I'LL
MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
BYE.
SO WHAT'S HER NAME?
DIXIE ROSE...
AND ONE FINE LADY,
I MIGHT ADD.
AREN'T THEY ALL?
HONEY, IT'S ALL
PART OF THE JOURNEY.
[CAR HORN HONKS OUTSIDE]
HE'S HERE!
MOM?
COLLIN!
OH, SWEETIE!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I'M FINE.
OH! UH, AND...
WHO'S THIS?
MOM, GRANDPA...
THIS IS SOPHIA.
NICE TO MEET YOU, SOPHIA.
AND YOU.
SO...
I GUESS THIS IS THE SURPRISE.
[LAUGHS]
OH, WELL...
COME ON IN.
I MADE BREAKFAST.
COLLIN, ALL YOUR FAVORITES.
SOPHIA, PLEASE JOIN US.
SOPHIA...
YOU CAN SIT
RIGHT HERE...
ACTUALLY, MOM...
I'M SORRY, I NEVER GOT
A CHANCE TO TELL YOU,
BUT I DON'T EAT MEAT.
I'M VEGAN.
YOU'RE WHAT?
WE'RE VEGAN.
WHAT'S THAT?
SOME KIND OF RELIGION?
NO, WE JUST BELIEVE
THAT IT'S HEALTHIER
AND MORE HUMANE.
WE DON'T EAT ANIMALS
OR ANIMAL PRODUCTS.
AS SOPHIA SAYS, NOTHING TASTES
AS GOOD AS BEING VEGAN FEELS.
[LAUGHS]
RIGHT.
WE GOTTA GO.
WE HAVE SOME BUSINESS IN TOWN
THAT WE GOTTA TAKE CARE OF.
I WAS HOPING
THAT WE COULD DO
FAMILY DINNER
HERE TONIGHT, THOUGH.
WELL, OF COURSE,
BUT... I'M CONFUSED.
I'LL EXPLAIN IT ALL
TO YOU TONIGHT.
IS IT OKAY
IF SOPHIA'S FATHER JOINS US?
SURE.
'KAY, BYE.
LOVE YOU.
IT'S GREAT TO FINALLY MEET YOU,
MRS. HAMPTON.
COLLIN HAS TOLD ME
SO MUCH ABOUT YOU.
SEE YOU BOTH TONIGHT!
SEE YOU TONIGHT.
[ROSEANNE]:
DINNER WITH HER FATHER?
THAT SOUNDS SERIOUS.
I DON'T KNOW.
THIS IS
ALL SO SUDDEN.
AND COLLIN NEVER SHOWED
ANY INTEREST
IN THIS "HEALTHIER,
MORE HUMANE" STUFF,
AND NOW HE'S VEGAN?
WHAT IS THAT ABOUT?
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I'M NOT BUYING IT.
[LAUGHS]
OOH...
I KNOW HE'S THE MORTAL ENEMY,
I KNOW,
BUT WHOO!
HE IS GORGEOUS.
AND YOU ARE
HAPPILY MARRIED.
MM-HMM,
BUT NO HARM IN DREAMING.
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHY COLLIN
WOULDN'T HAVE SIMPLY CALLED ME
AND TOLD ME ABOUT
A NEW GIRLFRIEND
RATHER THAN JUST SHOW UP
WITH THIS... THIS SOPHIA...
AND WHAT DO WE KNOW
ABOUT THIS SOPHIA?
NOTHING.
THAT'S THE POINT.
[WOMAN]: IF HE WANTS A FIGHT,
I'LL GIVE HIM A FIGHT!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU-- YOU WILL GIVE HIM A FIGHT.
HEY, THE McDOUGALS,
THEY BOOKED THEIR APPOINTMENT.
WHO?
THE McDOUGALS!
WHAT IS GOING ON OVER THERE?
[CLIENT]: YOU KNOW HOW
HARD I HAVE TO WORK?
THEY CAN'T BE YELLING
LIKE THAT.
I CAN'T EVEN HEAR MYSELF THINK!
MAYBE THIS DIVORCE
ISN'T SO AMICABLE?
I WORKED AND WORKED AND WORKED!
ALL OF THE THINGS I DID
FOR HIM,
AND ALL THE STUPID PARTIES
I THREW FOR HIM...
COULD THIS DAY
GET ANY WORSE?
[CLIENT, SCREAMING]:
IT'S NOT FINE! IT'S NOT FINE!
[DOORBELL RINGS]
HEY, BABY.
HI!
WHERE'S YOUR DAD?
HE'S COMING
RIGHT BEHIND ME.
HI, MRS. HAMPTON.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE DESSERT
I MADE.
[COLLIN]: YOUR VEGAN
PROFITEROLES!
THAT'S MY FAVORITE.
OH, WELL, THANK YOU,
BUT IT WASN'T REALLY NECESSARY.
EXCUSE ME,
JUST A CALL WITH A CLIENT.
DAD, THIS IS MY
BOYFRIEND, COLLIN.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
THIS IS HIS GRANDFATHER, RAY.
RAY.
AND HIS MOTHER, WENDY.
UH, RIGHT... I...
THINK WE'VE...
ALREADY MET.
WE HAVE?
UH, HOPE YOU LIKE RED.
YOU'RE SOPHIA'S FATHER?
[QUIETLY] IT
JUST GOT WORSE.
[BRIGHTLY] DAD, WILL
YOU SHOW THEM INSIDE?
[RAY]: FOLLOW ME.
LET ME GET
THE DOOR FOR YOU.
COLLIN, LET ME SPEAK TO YOU.
LOOK, I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY AREN'T YOU IN SCHOOL?
AND WHAT IS WITH THIS SOPHIA
AND HER DAD?
MOM, TRUST ME,
IT'S ALL GOING TO BE OKAY.
[MARCO]: SOPHIA.
THANKS, DAD.
-THANK YOU.
-OH!
OKAY.
TA-DAH!
VEAL PARMIGIANA!
COLLIN, YOUR FAVORITE!
WONDERFUL!
YOU COOK ITALIAN?
I TRY.
MOM, I ALREADY TOLD YOU...
WE'RE VEGANS.
REMEMBER?
OH, DON'T BE SILLY.
THIS HAS ALWAYS BEEN
YOUR FAVORITE.
NO, REALLY, MOM.
SOPHIA AND I,
WE CAN'T EAT THIS.
IT'S NOT WHAT
WE BELIEVE IN.
BUT THE SALAD
LOOKS DELICIOUS.
ARE THOSE
HEIRLOOM TOMATOES?
SOPHIA, DARLING,
WE'RE GUESTS.
JUST PLEASE EAT
WHATEVER'S SERVED.
PLUS, A LITTLE MEAT
IS HEALTHY FOR YOU.
ACTUALLY, DAD,
IT'S MUCH HEALTHIER THIS WAY.
AND I FEEL GREAT.
IN FACT, I'VE NEVER BEEN BETTER.
WELL, WENDY'S VEAL PARMIGIANA'S
ALWAYS BEEN MY FAVORITE.
[COLLIN LAUGHS]
SO, MOM,
HOW DO YOU AND MR. AMORINI
KNOW EACH ANOTHER?
WELL, APPARENTLY, MR. AMORINI
IS MY NEW NEIGHBOR AT WORK.
[RAY]: OH YEAH?
WHAT KIND OF BUSINESS
DO YOU RUN?
UH...
I'M A DIVORCE ATTORNEY.
[LAUGHS]
REALLY?
WHAT A HOOT!
A DIVORCE ATTORNEY
AND A WEDDING PLANNER,
SIDE BY SIDE.
ONE-STOP SHOPPING.
OR THE UNIVERSE
WORKING AGAINST ME.
OR MAYBE YOU COULD LOOK AT IT
AS THE UNIVERSE OPENING UP
FOR YOU.
MAYBE WE COULD OPEN UP THE WINE?
YES.
ALLOW ME.
OH, NO, I'VE GOT IT.
SO...
SOPHIA AND I, WE HAVE
SOME EXCITING NEWS.
[SOPHIA]: GO AHEAD,
SWEETHEART.
YOU TELL THEM.
SOPHIA AND I...
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED!
[COUGHS]
[SOPHIA]:
AND THERE'S MORE.
WE'RE GOING TO BE
ORGANIC FARMERS.
ISN'T IT GREAT?
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
DAD, DON'T START.
YOU ARE 22 YEARS OLD.
YOU ARE TOO YOUNG
TO GET MARRIED.
WHAT, YOU EXPECT ME
TO SIT HERE
AND JUST BE HAPPY
THAT YOU'RE DROPPING OUT
OF LAW SCHOOL?
COLLIN, YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS!
AND WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"ORGANIC FARMING?"
DOES THIS HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THAT VEGAN THING?
NO, MOM.
SOPHIA AND I
HAVE BEEN PLANNING THIS
FOR A WHILE.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU EVEN
KNOWN EACH OTHER?
TWO MONTHS.
WELL...
SOPHIA...
IT APPEARS THAT THIS BOY
HAS MADE YOU LOSE YOUR SENSES.
HOLD ON A SECOND.
THIS BOY DIDN'T HAVE
ANY OF THESE CRAZY IDEAS
UNTIL HE MET YOUR GIRL.
MOM, I KNOW
THAT THIS IS A LOT TO PROCESS,
BUT WE KNOW WHAT WE'RE DOING.
MY DAUGHTER'S NOT GOING
TO BECOME A FARMER.
I RAISED YOU
TO BE MY LAW PARTNER.
THIS IS SO TYPICAL
OF YOU, DAD.
MR. AMORINI, PLEASE.
I'M NOT TALKING TO YOU.
WE HAVE THOUGHT THIS THROUGH.
YOU ARE DESTROYING
MY DAUGHTER'S FUTURE.
[WENDY]: EXCUSE ME!
HE WAS JUST FINE
AND ON TRACK
FOR A GREAT LAW CAREER.
AND I'M QUITE CERTAIN
THIS WHOLE FARMING IDEA
WASN'T EVEN HIS!
OH, REALLY?
AND YOU THINK THAT SOPHIA
WOULD GIVE UP HER DREAM
OF PARTNERING UP WITH ME
AT THE FIRM
TO, WHAT, MILK COWS?
THAT'S RIDICULOUS!
UNLESS YOUR SON
TALKED HER INTO IT.
THIS MIGHT BE A GOOD
TIME TO LEAVE.
MY SON WAS EATING MEAT
BEFORE HE MET YOUR DAUGHTER.
MEAT?
WHO CARES ABOUT MEAT?
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT HER CAREER!
MY BUSINESS!
OH, OF COURSE,
YOUR BUSINESS.
AND WHAT KIND OF PERSON
OPENS A DIVORCE OFFICE
RIGHT NEXT TO A WEDDING PLANNER?
YOU'RE SELLING FAIRY TALES.
MARRIAGE IS NOT A FAIRY TALE.
THIS HAS BEEN
AN ENLIGHTENING EVENING.
CIAO.
CAN I HAVE SOME WINE?
[GROANS]
MORNING!
I SAVED YOU SOME MUFFINS.
GOOD MORNING.
COLLIN,
ABOUT LAST NIGHT...
IT'S OKAY, MOM.
I UNDERSTAND.
YOU DO?
OH, THANK GOODNESS,
BECAUSE YOU CAN SEE
WHY DROPPING OUT OF SCHOOL
AND RUSHING INTO
THIS MARRIAGE
IS A BAD IDEA.
I MEAN, IT'S OBVIOUS
YOU'RE HEAD OVER HEELS
FOR SOPHIA...
MOM, WHAT ARE YOU
SO AFRAID OF?
COLLIN, YOU'RE SO YOUNG.
YOU'RE 22.
YOU AND DAD WERE 21
WHEN YOU HAD ME.
THAT WAS DIFFERENT.
AND I NEVER WANTED YOU TO REPEAT
WHAT YOUR FATHER AND I DID.
YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO FINISH COLLEGE.
BESIDES, YOUR FATHER AND I
HAD A SOLID PLAN, WE...
SO DO WE.
MOM, I GOTTA GO.
I HAVE A MEETING AT THE BANK.
THANK YOU FOR THE MUFFINS.
THE BANK?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING AT THE BANK?
[SIGHS]
HEAVEN HELP ME.
[SINISTER MUSIC]
JOSH, COME ON.
YOU KNOW AS WELL AS I DO
THAT IF MY CLIENT WANTED TO,
SHE COULD GO AFTER
ALL YOUR CLIENT'S ASSETS.
EVEN THE ONES
STASHED OVERSEAS.
EXCUSE ME, YOUR CAR IS
IN MY PARKING SPOT.
JUST ADVISE YOUR CLIENT...
ADVISE YOUR CLIENT
TO PLAY FAIR,
AND SO WILL WE.
IT'S THE LEAST HE CAN DO
AFTER 10 YEARS OF MARRIAGE.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU THERE.
I WILL.
[CAR REMOTE BEEPS]
[CAR ALARM BLARES]
[TURNS IT OFF]
WHO DOES HE THINK I AM?
SOME KIND OF VALET?
[LOUD SCRAPING SOUND]
NO, NO, NO, NO!
OH MY G... WHAT'D YOU DO?
HOW DID YOU...
YOUR FAMILY IS A DISASTER!
LIKEWISE.
WHAT... WHAT IS
WRONG WITH YOU?
WHY DID YOU EVEN NEED
TO MOVE MY CAR?
THERE ARE PLENTY
OF SPOTS.
DO YOU NOT SEE THE SIGN?
"PERFECT WEDDINGS
BY HAMPTON?"
I'VE BEEN PARKING
IN THIS SPOT
SINCE MY HUSBAND AND I
OPENED THIS BUSINESS.
RIGHT.
YOUR HUSBAND.
SOPHIA TOLD ME
HE PASSED AWAY.
I'M SORRY.
LOOK, JUST...
FORGET ABOUT THE SCRATCH.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
I'M JUST GONNA PARK
IN THE STREET
UNTIL WE CAN GET THIS WHOLE
PARKING THING FIGURED OUT.
IT'LL BE SAFER THAT WAY.
THANK YOU.
YOU SCRATCHED HIS CAR?
OH, THAT'S RICH.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO.
HIS DAUGHTER
IS BRAINWASHING MY SON.
MAYBE HE IS NOT BRAINWASHED.
MAYBE HE'S IN LOVE.
YOU KNOW...
I SEEM TO RECALL
A YOUNG COUPLE
THAT WAS SO IN LOVE,
THEY ACTUALLY STARTED
THEIR OWN WEDDING BUSINESS.
DENNIS AND I WERE DIFFERENT.
WE WERE HIGH SCHOOL SWEETHEARTS
WHO GREW UP TOGETHER.
COLLIN HAS JUST
MET SOPHIA.
A YEAR AGO,
HE WAS IN LOVE WITH EMILY.
AND NOW, OVERNIGHT,
HE IS DROPPING OUT
OF LAW SCHOOL,
BECOME A VEGAN,
IS GETTING MARRIED,
AND STARTING HIS OWN
ORGANIC FARMING BUSINESS.
[LAUGHS]
YOU DON'T THINK
THAT'S CRAZY?
AH, YOU KNOW,
WE CAN RAISE THEM,
BUT, HOO, WE CANNOT LIVE
THEIR LIVES FOR THEM.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO GET MORE COFFEE.
HEY, McDOUGALS. 10:00.
LARGE COFFEE, DOUBLE SUGAR,
NO CREAM, PLEASE.
SO, WHAT ARE WE
GOING TO DO
ABOUT THIS RIDICULOUS PLAN
OF SOPHIA AND, UM...
UH...
COLLIN?
-MY SON?
-YES.
THE ONE WHO WAS
ON THE RIGHT PATH
BEFORE HE WAS BLINDED
BY THE AMORINI CHARM?
AMORINI CHARM?
[LAUGHS]
HANG ON A SEC,
I GOT THIS.
NO, I GOT IT.
NO, REALLY, I INSIST.
NO, I INSIST.
[CLATTERING]
I GOT IT.
[THWACK]
OW!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M FINE.
OKAY. I'M SORRY.
[WOMAN]:
YOO-HOO! MARCO!
WHAT?
HI.
BEVERLY! CIAO.
NICE TO SEE YOU.
GOOD TO SEE YOU, TOO.
YEAH, UM...
I WOULD LOVE A MOCHA.
UH, ONE MOCHA,
ONE ESPRESSO.
UH...
[CLATTERS]
UH... I GOT THIS.
HANG ON, I GOT THIS.
[WENDY]: OUR WEDDING
PACKAGE INCLUDES
THE CEREMONY AND
THE RECEPTION,
BOTH OF WHICH
ROSEANNE AND I WILL PLAN DOWN
TO EVERY LAST DETAIL.
FLOWERS, FOOD, CAKE...
NOW, WE HAVE DOWN
THE MAID OF HONOR,
BUT WHO WILL BE
THE BEST MAN?
THAT WILL BE
MY BROTHER, STAN.
UNFORTUNATELY.
[SEAN]: HONEY,
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH THIS.
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH
THAT MEANS TO ME.
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
NO, JUST...
EVERYTHING ABOUT HIM
IS BAD LUCK.
[DOOR OPENS]
HEY, SORRY.
YOU LEFT THIS BEHIND.
SEAN?
SEAN McDOUGAL?
CONGRATULATIONS!
TAKING THE PLUNGE AGAIN, HUH?
WOW!
THAT LAST ONE SURE PUT UP
QUITE A FIGHT, DIDN'T SHE?
BUT I'M SURE THIS TIME,
YOU'LL GET A PRENUP.
THAT IS MY SPECIALITY.
[LAUGHS]
WAIT A MINUTE, WAIT...
YOU WERE MARRIED BEFORE?
WELL, I, I... WANTED TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT THAT, YEAH.
[WOMAN]: OH, YOU WANTED
TO TALK TO ME ABOUT THAT?
I'M SO, SO SORRY.
WILL YOU EXCUSE US?
YOU KNOW WHAT? I THINK
I MIGHT HAVE TO GO.
WAIT, WAIT,
PLEASE, WAIT...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
I'M IN THERE TRYING
TO PLAN A COUPLE'S WEDDING,
AND YOU'RE BRINGING UP
HIS DIVORCE AND PRENUPS?
I'M JUST TRYING
TO PROTECT HIM.
YOU GIVE A MARRIAGE
TWO WEEKS,
AND I WILL GIVE YOU
GROUNDS FOR DIVORCE,
AND BY THE SOUNDS OF IT,
THEY DON'T EVEN NEED TWO WEEKS.
WHEN DID YOU BECOME SO CYNICAL?
MOST MARRIAGES END
WITH BOTH PEOPLE
TRYING TO INFLICT
AS MUCH PAIN ON ONE ANOTHER
AS HUMANLY POSSIBLE,
WHICH IS EXACTLY WHY
SOPHIA WILL NEVER MARRY
YOUR SON,
NOT IF I CAN HELP IT.
GREAT, AT LEAST
WE AGREE ON ONE THING.
GREAT.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
ABOUT IT?
ME?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
WELL, I'VE ALWAYS
BEEN ABLE TO TALK TO COLLIN.
REALLY?
[LAUGHS]
OH, NO, NO,
I COULD TELL BY THE WAY
HE SHARED HIS ENGAGEMENT
WITH YOU.
I WILL HANDLE MY SON.
YOU HANDLE SOPHIA
HOWEVER YOU WISH.
FINE.
OH, DON'T, NO!
COME ON, I WAS INSIDE
FOR TWO SECONDS!
WHERE DID YOU
COME FROM, ANYWAY?
I HAD TO MAKE CHANGE!
LOOK... AGH...
WONDERFUL MEAL.
IS THERE DESSERT?
YES.
COLLIN, WILL YOU HELP ME CLEAR?
SO, RAY, UM...
YOU'RE A HUNTER?
OH, YEAH. YOU?
NO, NO, NO.
YOU SHOULD TRY IT!
MAYBE!
THANKS FOR DINNER, MOM,
BUT I HAVE TO GO.
OH, WAIT, NO...
BEFORE YOU GO,
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
YOUR TRIP TO THE BANK
THIS MORNING,
DID IT HAVE SOMETHING TO DO WITH
THIS WHOLE FARMING BUSINESS?
YEAH, WE'RE APPLYING
FOR A SMALL BUSINESS LOAN,
BUT IT'S KINDA COMPLICATED.
I MIGHT NEED TO CASH IN
ON MY EDUCATION FUND.
COLLIN!
OKAY, WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"CASH IN" YOUR EDUCATION FUND?
MOM, I HAVE IT HANDLED.
OKAY, BUT THIS IS ALL
MOVING SO QUICKLY,
AND YOU'RE COMMITTING SO MUCH,
I'M AFRAID YOU'RE GETTING IN
OVER YOUR HEAD.
MOM, DIDN'T YOU AND DAD
USED TO TELL ME
TO GO FOR MY DREAMS?
THIS IS ME GOING FOR IT.
OKAY, BUT WHAT ABOUT YOUR DREAM
OF BECOMING A LAWYER?
I THINK THAT WAS MORE
YOUR DREAM, NOT MINE.
OKAY,
BUT THIS IS JUST SO DRASTIC,
AND I THINK
YOU'RE BEING IMPULSIVE.
MOM, I LOVE YOU,
BUT THIS IS MY LIFE.
I HAVE TO GO.
OF COURSE YOU DO.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HE NEVER BEHAVED
LIKE THIS WITH EMILY.
I MEAN,
THEY WERE SO GROUNDED.
THEY MADE SENSE--
LIKE YOU AND I, LOGAN.
QUESTION, IS THIS LACTOSE FREE?
I DON'T TOLERATE DAIRY
THAT WELL.
GIVE THE KID A BREAK.
HE'S HAVING FUN.
WHAT, LIKE YOU, DAD?
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT FOR HIM?
A WHOLE STRING OF GIRLFRIENDS
AND FAILED RELATIONSHIPS?
EASY NOW.
I'M STILL YOUR FATHER.
AND I'M STILL COLLIN'S MOTHER.
YOU KNOW, STATISTICS INDICATE
MOST KIDS DON'T LISTEN
TO THEIR PARENTS.
NOW, THAT'S A PROVEN FACT.
YOU'RE RIGHT!
YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
WE NEED A HIGHER POWER.
WHERE YOU GOING?
TO CALL A HIGHER POWER.
[SPEED DIALS]
PASTOR MACY?
IT'S WENDY.
[SPEAKS ITALIAN]
I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU.
READY?
HUH? WHAT DO
YOU THINK?
DAD, I ALREADY TOLD YOU.
I'M NOT GOING INTO PRACTICE
WITH YOU.
COLLIN AND I
ARE GOING TO BE
ORGANIC FARMERS.
[MUTTERS IN ITALIAN]
DARLING...
YOU AND I BOTH KNOW HOW
DIFFICULT MARRIAGE CAN BE.
AFTER YOUR MOTHER LEFT,
IT BROKE OUR HEARTS.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU
GO THROUGH THAT AGAIN.
DAD, THAT WAS YOUR MARRIAGE.
IT'S DIFFERENT
WITH COLLIN AND ME.
THAT'S WHAT THEY ALL SAY.
BUT TRUST ME, THINGS CHANGE.
I MEAN, FOR GOODNESS SAKE,
DIVORCE PAID
FOR YOUR LAW SCHOOL,
NOT MARRIAGE.
[SPEAKS ITALIAN]
[WENDY]: SORRY!
I DON'T MEAN
TO INTERRUPT, BUT...
I WONDER IF YOU AND COLLIN
MIGHT DO SOMETHING FOR ME.
MEET WITH MY PRE-MARITAL
COUNSELOR, PASTOR MACY.
MOM...
NO, HONEY, IT'S FINE.
WE'D LOVE TO, MRS. HAMPTON.
OH, THAT'S GREAT...
BECAUSE I ALREADY CALLED,
AND HE CAN SEE YOU RIGHT NOW.
PASTOR MACY CAN HELP THEM
"EXAMINE" THEIR CHOICES.
RIGHT.
WELL,
PASTOR MACY'S A GREAT GUY...
SO I THINK WE CAN DO THAT.
LET'S GO.
I TAKE IT YOUR TALK
DIDN'T WORK SO WELL?
PASTOR MACY IS TOUGH.
DON'T WORRY. HE'LL
SET THEM STRAIGHT.
[PASTOR]: THE QUESTIONS
I'M ABOUT TO ASK YOU
ARE DIFFICULT.
THEY NEED TO BE DIFFICULT.
BUT DON'T BE AFRAID OF THEM.
MARRIAGE SHOULD NOT BE
ENTERED INTO LIGHTLY.
THERE ARE MANY THINGS
TO CONSIDER.
YOU REALLY THINK
THIS IS GONNA WORK?
IT'S GOT TO.
YOU KNOW,
I WOULD HAVE NEVER THOUGHT
SOPHIA WOULD HAVE DONE
SOMETHING LIKE THIS,
ESPECIALLY AFTER HER MOTHER
LEFT US THE WAY SHE DID.
I'M SORRY.
I HADN'T REALIZED.
HOW OLD WAS SOPHIA?
SHE WAS FIVE.
OH... THAT'S HEARTBREAKING.
HOW OLD WAS COLLIN
WHEN HIS FATHER DIED?
EIGHT.
IT'S HARD FOR A BOY TO GROW UP
WITHOUT A FATHER.
NOT ANY HARDER THAN FOR A GIRL
TO GROW UP WITHOUT HER MOTHER.
YOU KNOW, SOPHIA'S MOM
WILL NEVER BE
WHO SOPHIA WANTS
HER TO BE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MANY MORE TIMES
SHE'S GOTTA BE LET DOWN
BEFORE SHE REALIZES IT.
WHAT ABOUT COLLIN?
WAS HE CLOSE
WITH HIS FATHER?
OH, VERY.
THEY DID EVERYTHING TOGETHER.
CAMPING, BIKING...
THEY WENT FISHING
ALMOST EVERY WEEKEND.
[DOOR OPENS]
BE PREPARED.
THERE MAY BE TEARS.
[PASTOR]: WENDY!
I HAVE TO SAY,
I'M SURPRISED.
YOUTH CAN, INDEED,
BE PROBLEMATIC
WHEN MAKING SUCH
SERIOUS LIFE DECISIONS,
AND I ALWAYS
RECOMMEND
THAT YOUNG COUPLES
TAKE THEIR TIME,
SPREAD THEIR WINGS.
BUT I CAN CLEARLY SEE
THAT THESE TWO
HAVE THEIR FEET ON THE GROUND
AND A GOOD HEAD
ON THEIR SHOULDERS,
AND I HAVE NO DOUBT
THAT THEY ARE ENTERING
INTO THIS MARRIAGE
WITH LOVE AND REASON.
CONGRATULATIONS, COLLIN.
THANK YOU.
-SOPHIA.
-THANK YOU, PASTOR.
I KNEW THAT
WOULDN'T WORK.
OH, DID YOU?
WELL, IF YOU WERE SO SURE,
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY SOMETHING?
AT LEAST I'M TRYING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
OTHER THAN POINTING OUT
WHAT I'M DOING WRONG?
AT LEAST I'LL THINK
OF A BETTER PLAN
THEN MARRIAGE COUNSELING.
FINE, THEN DO IT.
FINE, I WILL.
WELL, AS FUTURE IN-LAWS,
YOU GUYS ARE GETTING ALONG
JUST GREAT.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
-MARCO!
-HI.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
MR. AMORINI!
YOU READY TO GO?
YOU BET.
WE'RE GOING FISHING.
THAT'S RIGHT...
A LITTLE FATHER-IN-LAW,
SON-IN-LAW BONDING,
JUST THE TWO OF US,
SO WE CAN GET TO KNOW
EACH OTHER BETTER.
SEE YOU IN THE CAR.
EXCUSE ME...
HOW IS FISHING BONDING
GOING TO HELP?
I GOT THIS, ALL RIGHT?
PERSUASION
IS MY SPECIALTY.
WHERE'D YOU GO?
THERE YOU ARE.
HERE, USE...
YEAH, USE ONE OF THESE.
IT'S EASIER.
[MARCO]: SO, COLLIN... IT'S A PITY
THAT, WITH ALL THE...
RESPONSIBILITIES OF RUNNING A FARM,
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO SPEND
MORE FREE DAYS FISHING.
IT'S A LOT TO TAKE ON AT 22.
SOPHIA AND I BOTH THINK
THAT LIVING LIFE TO THE FULLEST
MEANS PURSUING YOUR GOALS.
WELL...
SOPHIA CERTAINLY HAS GROWN UP,
BUT SHE'LL ALWAYS BE
MY LITTLE GIRL.
I MEAN, YOU'VE ONLY BEEN
TOGETHER FOR TWO MONTHS.
MARRIAGE IS FOREVER.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE READY
TO DEDICATE
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE
TO MY SOPHIA?
YOU'RE BOTH SO YOUNG.
AND IN MY LINE OF WORK,
I CAN TELL YOU...
WHAT YOU'RE FEELING TODAY
WILL PROBABLY VANISH
AT THE FIRST SIGN OF PROBLEMS.
MR. AMORINI...
I KNOW YOU THINK
I'M TOO YOUNG
AND THAT WE'RE LIVING
IN THIS WORLD OF DREAMS,
BUT I DO KNOW THAT MARRIAGE
IS A LIFETIME COMMITMENT,
AND WHEN THINGS AREN'T EASY,
YOU JUST DON'T QUIT.
MAYBE THAT'S WHAT
YOUR CLIENTS DON'T GET.
SIR...
I LOVE YOUR DAUGHTER.
SHE INSPIRES ME
TO BE THE BEST MAN
THAT I CAN POSSIBLY BE.
I KNOW, WITH HER AT MY SIDE,
THAT I CAN ACHIEVE ANYTHING.
I WON'T STAND FOR HER
BEING HURT.
NEITHER WILL I.
HOW DO YOU CAST
THIS DARN THING?
OH, HERE.
NO...
WELL, UH, HERE...
SEE?
OOF!
I'M OKAY.
YEAH, PURPLE'S
MUCH BETTER.
YEAH.
[DOOR OPENS]
[LAUGHS]
OKAY, SO...
DID YOU CATCH ANY FISH?
FUNNY.
I KNEW IT.
OH, REALLY?
YEAH, REALLY.
WELL...
I DON'T THINK ANY OF OUR IDEAS
ARE WORKING.
OH, AND COLLIN TOLD ME
THEY'RE GONNA SEE
A FARM TOMORROW.
WHAT?
YOU KNOW, YOU GUYS
COULD THINK OF IT THIS WAY.
THE KIDS SEEM REALLY TENACIOUS.
I MEAN, THINK ABOUT IT.
FARM LIFE?
THAT'S A TOUGH LIFE.
-ARE YOU DONE?
-WE NEED TO GO WITH THEM!
WELL...
ABSOLUTELY.
ON THIS,
I THINK WE CAN AGREE.
HEY, DAD, IT'S ME.
I'M LOOKING FOR COLLIN.
HAVE YOU SEEN HIM?
MARCO JUST GOT BACK
FROM THEIR FISHING TRIP,
AND HE SAID SOMETHING ABOUT
HE AND SOPHIA
GOING TO LOOK FOR A FARM
TOMORROW?
I DON'T KNOW.
A LOT OF GOOD
THIS FISHING TRIP WAS.
THANK YOU.
OH, WAIT, NEVER MIND.
I SEE HIM. OKAY.
HEY, BABY!
HEY!
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
UH... REFILL.
BUT, UM,
NOW THAT YOU'RE HERE,
HOW WAS YOUR FISHING TRIP
WITH MARCO?
LOOK WHO'S DOING
THE FISHING NOW.
OKAY, SO YOU CAUGHT ME.
SERIOUSLY, HOW'D IT GO?
IT WAS GREAT.
-IT WAS?
-YEAH.
MR. AMORINI'S A GREAT GUY.
HE IS?
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, I MEAN,
OBVIOUSLY,
HE'S NOT A FISHERMAN...
I MEAN, NOT LIKE YOUR DAD.
YEAH. IT'S OKAY.
AND HE GOT BETTER AFTER A WHILE,
AND BESIDES...
I THINK IT'LL BE A GOOD WAY
FOR US TO BOND.
AND I CAN TEACH HIM
HOW TO FISH, AND HE...
SO HE DIDN'T TRY TO TALK YOU
OUT OF YOUR PLAN WITH SOPHIA?
MOM, MR. AMORINI WANTS
WHAT'S BEST FOR HIS DAUGHTER,
AND SO DO I.
AND THAT IS...?
LOOK, MOM, I BETTER GO.
SOPHIA'S WAITING AT THE PARK,
AND I PROMISED I'D MEET
HER WITH SOY LATTES.
OKAY, OKAY. BUT WHAT IS THIS
ABOUT SEEING A FARM?
YEAH,
THERE'S A FARM THAT WE FOUND
THAT WE'RE INTERESTED
IN LEASING.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
I THINK MARCO AND I WOULD LIKE
TO SEE THAT WITH YOU.
YEAH! THAT WOULD BE GREAT!
OKAY!
YOU CAN COME
WITH US.
GREAT!
-YES!
-OKAY! MWAH!
[SPLAT]
OH...
I TOLD HIM TO WEAR BOOTS.
WHAT IS IT WITH YOU AND MUD?
[MAN]: HEY, OVER HERE!
WELCOME!
[COLLIN]: HEY!
OH, THAT'S
A GOOD QUESTION.
ON THE FARM,
WE KEEP LIVESTOCK.
THEY'RE ALL USED
TO BEING HANDLED,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
THEY STILL WON'T
GIVE YOU A HARD TIME.
LET ME SHOW YOU
THE BARN.
THAT SOUNDS
LIKE A HANDFUL.
COLLIN, YOU NEVER
EVEN HAD A DOG.
AND REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED
TO THAT GOLDFISH YOU HAD?
NOT TO WORRY.
YOU'LL GET A FEEL
FOR THE ANIMALS.
OH, BUT YOU TWO
PROBABLY CAME FROM FARMING,
UNLIKE THESE TWO.
ACTUALLY, I WAS
AN ECONOMICS MAJOR,
AND MARIANNE HERE HAS GOT
HER Ph.D. IN PSYCHOLOGY.
COME ON.
I'LL INTRODUCE YOU TO BELLA.
[GOAT BLEATS]
THIS IS BELLA,
OUR NUMBER ONE
MILK PRODUCER.
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO GIVE IT A TRY?
SURE.
[WENDY]: YOU MUST HAVE TO GET UP
AT THE CRACK OF DAWN
TO GET EVERYTHING DONE.
BUT IT'S WORTH IT
WHEN YOU SEE
THE SUNRISE OUT HERE.
YOU'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
MORE BEAUTIFUL.
WELL, MAYBE THE SUNSET.
BE HONEST.
THE PAYOFF
FOR ALL THE HARD WORK...
I MEAN, IT CAN'T BE
THAT MUCH.
WELL, IT WASN'T FOR US,
BUT THE OTHER FARMS
THAT HAVE GONE ORGANIC
AREN'T DOING BAD AT ALL.
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT?
HE'S A NATURAL.
[MILK SPATTERS IN BUCKET]
MR. AMORINI?
YOU WANT TO GIVE IT A TRY?
NO... NO, I'M NOT...
OH, COME ON.
I'M NOT GOOD AT...
NO, SHOW SOPHIA THAT
IT'S NOT THAT EASY.
[MILK SPLATTERS IN BUCKET]
I DON'T SEE HOW TURNING
THIS PLACE INTO AN ORGANIC FARM
COULD BE EASY OR CHEAP.
BASED ON MY RESEARCH,
THE LAND NEEDS TO BE
PESTICIDE FREE
FOR AT LEAST 36 MONTHS,
AND YOU NEED
AN ORGANIC SYSTEM PLAN,
YOU HAVE TO BE CERTIFIED...
DAD, WE'VE ALREADY
BEEN IN CONTACT
WITH THE LOCAL CERTIFICATION
AGENCIES.
AND OUR FIELDS HAVE BEEN FALLOW
FOR THE PAST THREE YEARS.
HA HA...
WOW, MR. AMORINI.
YOU'RE A REAL NATURAL AT THAT.
[COW BELLOWS]
[EVERYONE LAUGHS]
[COW MOOS]
[ROOSTER CROWS]
LOOKS LIKE IT'S GOING TO NEED
A LOT OF MAINTENANCE.
COLLIN, LOOK!
THIS IS WHERE WE SHOULD
HAVE THE WEDDING!
YEAH, SOPHIA,
THAT'S BRILLIANT!
THIS IS WHERE WE'RE GONNA
BUILD OUR LIVES.
YEAH, THE SMELL OF COWS,
THAT'S REALLY ROMANTIC.
WHERE WOULD YOU EVEN HAVE
A RECEPTION?
NO, WE'D WANT IT
TO BE CASUAL,
BE MORE ABOUT OUR FRIENDS
BEING PART OF THE CELEBRATION.
LET'S NOT HAVE
A FORMAL RECEPTION.
OKAY, WAIT A MINUTE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
[SOPHIA]: WE WANT A SIMPLE
REFLECTION OF OUR LIFESTYLE,
RIGHT DOWN TO THE CAKE.
DEFINITELY VEGAN.
YES.
AGAIN WITH THE VEGAN.
DO THEY EVEN MAKE
A VEGAN CAKE?
CARROT CAKE?
I KNOW.
I DON'T EVEN
RECOGNIZE COLLIN.
IT MAKES ME WONDER
WHAT KIND OF A JOB I DID.
NO MATTER HOW GOOD
OF A FATHER I WAS OR NOT,
I'LL TAKE CARE OF HER NOW.
DAD, ISN'T THIS
PLACE PERFECT?
WELL, I'D HARDLY
CALL IT PERFECT.
JUST LISTEN.
[WIND CHIMES]
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S LIKE THE WIND CHIMES WE HAD
ON OUR BACK PORCH, REMEMBER?
WHAT'S THIS?
YOUR PRENUP.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I DON'T NEED A PRENUP.
THAT'S JUST EVEN MORE FOOLISH
THAN THIS WHOLE FARM BUSINESS.
MR. AMORINI, I APPRECIATE
YOUR CONCERN, BUT...
YOU'RE IMPOSSIBLE.
THAT'S IT?
THAT'S YOU
TAKING CARE OF HER?
WELL, IF SHE INSISTS
ON GOING THROUGH
WITH THIS WHOLE FARMING DEAL,
AT LEAST I WANT HER PROTECTED.
LOOK, I DON'T WANT TO SEE
COLLIN HURT EITHER,
BUT A PRENUP
IS NOT THE SOLUTION.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU
SUGGEST, WENDY?
I DON'T KNOW.
HOW ABOUT THIS?
HOW ABOUT WE STOP FIGHTING
EACH OTHER,
AND WE START
WORKING TOGETHER.
I CAN DO THAT.
[CAR DRIVES AWAY]
LOOKS LIKE I'LL BE
NEEDING A RIDE.
I GOT SOME ROOM IN MY TRUNK.
[COLLIN]: DON'T WORRY,
WE'LL FIND A WAY TO GET IT.
I MEAN, IT WAS JUST PERFECT.
THE HOUSE, THE BARN, YOU...
[LAUGHS]
YEAH.
22 YEARS
I'VE KNOWN THAT BOY,
I'VE NEVER SEEN HIM
SO HAPPY.
[COLLIN]: SOPHIA,
WE WILL MAKE IT WORK.
WE CAN DO
ANYTHING, RIGHT?
'KAY.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
OKAY, YOU'RE ALL SET.
OH, YOU LOOK AMAZING!
WHY, WHAT'S
THE OCCASION?
NO OCCASION.
JUST COFFEE.
MARCO AND I NEED TO DISCUSS
THE KIDS.
OH, MARCO? MM-HMM.
WELL, THAT'S AN AWFULLY
FANCY DRESS
FOR A LATTE.
LOGAN!
WHAT A SURPRISE!
YEAH, JUST THOUGHT I'D COME BY
AND SEE IF YOU HAD ANY IDEAS
FOR MOVIES TONIGHT.
IT'S MOVIE FRIDAY, REMEMBER?
OF COURSE.
NOPE, I CAN'T THINK OF ANYTHING.
MM, DON'T WORRY, I'LL BRING
A DVD FROM MY PLACE.
SO... OH, THIS IS FOR YOU.
TWO CREAMS, NO SUGAR,
JUST THE WAY YOU LIKE IT.
ACTUALLY, LOGAN,
IT'S NO CREAM, TWO SUGARS.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL, REALLY.
IT'S THE THOUGHT THAT COUNTS.
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
UH...
WELL, SEE YOU TONIGHT.
OKAY! I'LL
SEE YOU TONIGHT.
SO, IF YOU'LL AGREE,
WE'LL GO AHEAD AND FILE
THE ANNULMENT REQUEST.
[KNOCKS GENTLY]
GREAT.
WELL, I LOOK FORWARD
TO WORKING WITH YOU.
SHALL WE?
LARGE COFFEE, DOUBLE SUGAR,
NO CREAM.
RIGHT. THANK YOU.
THAT WOMAN
IN YOUR OFFICE EARLIER...
OH, RIGHT, YES. UM....
WELL, IT TURNS OUT HER HUSBAND
HAS A BIT OF A WANDERING EYE.
REALLY?
YEAH.
HEY, YOU KNOW, IT'S BETTER
TO FIND OUT THESE THINGS
SOONER THAN LATER.
THAT WAY, WE CAN ASK
FOR AN ANNULMENT.
IF NOT, WE GO TO BATTLE...
WHICH IS EXACTLY WHY WE NEED
TO GET ON TOP OF THIS.
[SIGHS]
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
IT'S JUST...
WELL, COLLIN AND SOPHIA SEEM
REALLY HAPPY, DON'T THEY?
YEAH, ABOUT AS HAPPY
AS THAT WOMAN IN MY OFFICE WAS
EARLIER ON HER WEDDING DAY.
PEOPLE IN UNHAPPY
RELATIONSHIPS AND MARRIAGES
SHOULD JUST... MOVE ON.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT. OKAY.
SO WHAT DO WE DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
SOPHIA'S NOT TALKING TO ME.
DO YOU BLAME HER?
COLLIN...
I DON'T EVEN RECOGNIZE COLLIN.
WHEN HE WAS WITH EMILY,
HE WAS...
HE WAS STEADY,
HE WAS ON THE RIGHT PATH,
HE WAS...
WHOA... EMILY?
WHO'S EMILY?
HIS EX-GIRLFRIEND.
HOW LONG AGO?
WHAT DOES IT MATTER?
NO, BECAUSE IF WE CAN GET
COLLIN AND EMILY TOGETHER...
NO.
NO, NO, NO. I DO NOT WANT
TO BRING EMILY INTO THIS. NO.
WENDY, THIS MAY BE
OUR ONLY HOPE.
SOPHIA, THIS WEEKEND, IS GOING
TO GO TO HER MOTHER'S.
LET'S PUT THEM TOGETHER
AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
MARCO... I DON'T...
I DON'T KNOW. THAT'S...
WENDY...
WE DON'T WANT OUR CHILDREN
TO GET HURT HERE.
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER.
[DOOR OPENS]
YOO-HOO!
MARCO!
THERE YOU ARE,
MY DANCE PARTNER.
HI...
I HAVE BEEN LOOKING
EVERYWHERE FOR YOU.
NOW, I NEED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT
THE DANCE CLASSES AT THE HALL.
BEVERLY, I...
I HAVE BEEN PENCILING
YOU IN FOR TONIGHT,
AND THEN NEXT FRIDAY
AND SUNDAY...
BEVERLY, CAN WE JUST TALK
ABOUT THIS LATER, PLEASE?
NO, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S...
NO, NO, NO...
YOU WORK IT OUT WITH
YOUR DANCE PARTNER.
I HAVE TO GET GOING.
DO YOU KNOW THE TANGO?
TA-DAH!
SO, IN HONOR
OF NATIONAL BIOLOGY WEEK,
WE HAVE A RIVETING DRAMA
ABOUT LIFE IN THE TAIGA.
TAIGA?
OH, YEAH.
IT'S THE WORLD'S LARGEST
TERRESTRIAL BIOMES
OF CONIFEROUS FORESTS,
PINES, SPRUCES, LARCHES...
LET'S GO DANCING.
DANCING?
OH, NO, BUT IT'S DVD NIGHT.
COME ON. IT'LL BE FUN.
BUT... THE TAIGA...
YOU KNOW, WENDY...
IT'S BEEN SOME TIME...
ACTUALLY, A REALLY LONG TIME
SINCE I'VE DANCED,
AND EVEN THEN, IN COTILLION,
YOU KNOW, I HAVE TO SAY,
I NEVER REALLY MASTERED...
COME ON, LOGAN,
IT WON'T BE THAT BAD.
RIGHT, BUT IF I HAD KNOWN
YOU'D WANTED TO GO DANCING,
I COULD'VE PRACTICED A LITTLE.
I'M SURE THERE ARE SOME
VERY GOOD INSTRUCTIONAL VIDEOS
ON THE RHYTHMIC PATTERN
OF THE WALTZ AND, UH...
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
A LOT OF FUN.
COME ON.
ARE YOU SURE YOU WOULDN'T WANT
TO TRY BOWLING INSTEAD?
BOWLING IS...
DON'T WORRY.
I'M SURE WE'LL AMAZE
THEM WITH OUR MOVES.
♪ HERE COMES LOVE
♪ AND ALL OF THE JOY IT BRINGS
♪ AND ALL OF THOSE
CRAZY THINGS I DO ♪
♪ FOR FALLING IN LOVE
WITH YOU ♪
HI. NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN!
I'M BEVERLY.
HAVE YOU BOTH COME
TO SIGN UP AS DANCE PARTNERS?
UH, I'M...
I'M WENDY,
AND THIS IS LOGAN,
MY, UM...
BOYFRIEND.
HI, BEVERLY.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
IS THIS A DANCE CLASS?
YES, IT IS A DANCE CLASS...
FOR THE RETIREMENT RESIDENTS.
WE'VE BEEN DOING IT FOR
YEARS. THEY JUST LOVE IT.
ESPECIALLY
WHEN THEY GET TO DANCE
WITH SOME OF THE YOUNGER FOLKS,
LIKE THAT MR. AMORINI.
[♪♪♪]
THE WOMEN JUST ADORE HIM.
OH, "NATIONAL BIOLOGY WEEK!"
WILL YOU BE ATTENDING?
PERSONALLY,
I WOULDN'T MISS IT.
I HEAR THEY'RE GOING TO SET
A RECORD
FOR THE MOST TREES PLANTED
IN LESS THAN A MINUTE.
YOU DON'T SAY!
SHOULD BE EXCITING.
YEAH!
EXCUSE ME.
LOGAN, THIS WAS
A BAD IDEA.
LET'S LEAVE.
WENDY!
YOU HERE TO DANCE?
YES... YES, WE ARE.
GREAT.
UH... MARCO, LOGAN.
LOGAN, MARCO.
AH, THE DIVORCE ATTORNEY/
FUTURE FATHER-IN-LAW.
WELL, YOU GOT
ONE OF THOSE PEGGED.
AND YOU ARE...?
BOYFRIEND.
AH.
-LOGAN, LET'S DANCE.
-OKAY.
[BEVERLY]:
MARCO, MARCO...
YES?
YOUR NEXT DANCE PARTNER
IS WAITING.
OH, OF COURSE.
IT WAS NICE TO MEET YOU,
LOGAN...
WENDY...
ONE, TWO,
THREE, FOUR...
[GRUNT IN PAIN]
SORRY. I'M RUSTY.
IT'S OKAY. NO,
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, WENDY,
I'VE BEEN THINKING.
UM, YOU AND I HAVE BEEN DATING
FOR A WHILE NOW...
AND TO ME, IT JUST
MAKES PERFECT SENSE
THAT WE SHOULD
TAKE THIS... THIS "US"...
YOU KNOW, TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
AND, YOU KNOW, I JUST... OH!
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M GOOD.
IT'S ALL RIGHT. REALLY.
YEAH. NO, IT'S FINE.
-I REALLY GOTCHA THERE.
-NO, IT'S OKAY. IT'S OKAY.
[MUSIC FINISHES WITH FLOURISH]
OH...
UH, LOGAN...
WOULD YOU GET ME
SOMETHING TO DRINK?
SURE.
OKAY.
[ROMANTIC JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS]
POSSO AVERE
QUESTO BALLO?
YOU KNOW I CAN'T SPEAK ITALIAN.
AH...
IT'S THE LANGUAGE
OF LOVE.
IT MEANS,
"MAY I HAVE THIS DANCE?"
♪ A DAY WITHOUT YOU
IS A DAY WITHOUT SUNSHINE ♪
♪ A NIGHT WITHOUT YOU
JUST A LITTLE BIT BLUE ♪
♪ YOU LIGHT UP MY LIFE
LIKE THE SUN IN THE SKY ♪
♪ HEAVEN KNOWS WHY
I FEEL LIKE I DO ♪
♪ IT MAY BE YOUR EYES
MAY BE YOUR KISSES ♪
YOU KNOW...
UM... WHEN YOU MENTIONED
THE THING ABOUT EMILY
THE OTHER DAY,
I DON'T KNOW
THAT I FEEL COMFORTABLE...
SHH.
JUST DANCE.
♪ SOMETHING IS MISSING
WHEN YOU'RE NOT WITH ME ♪
♪ HEAVEN KNOWS WHY
I FEEL LIKE I DO ♪
♪ BUT HEAVEN KNOWS I'M CRAZY
I'M CRAZY ABOUT YOU ♪
♪ HEAVEN KNOWS
♪ WALKING DOWN THE AVENUE
♪ DREAMING
♪ WISHING I COULD BE WITH YOU
♪ HOPING AND SCHEMING
♪ BUT LOVE IS HARD TO EXPLAIN
♪ IT CAN SLIP
THROUGH YOUR FINGERS ♪
♪ SOME MEMORIES FADE
SOME MEMORIES LINGER ♪
♪ MY LOVER, MY FRIEND
I STILL CAN RECALL ♪
♪ THE NIGHT THAT WE MET
THE THRILL OF IT ALL ♪
♪ HEAVEN KNOWS WHY
I FEEL LIKE I DO ♪
♪ BUT HEAVEN KNOWS I'M CRAZY
I'M CRAZY ABOUT YOU ♪
♪ HEAVEN KNOWS
♪ WISHING I COULD BE WITH YOU
♪ HOPING AND SCHEMING
♪ BUT LOVE IS HARD TO EXPLAIN
♪ IT CAN SLIP
THROUGH YOUR FINGERS ♪
♪ SOME MEMORIES FADE
SOME MEMORIES LINGER ♪
♪ MY LOVER, MY FRIEND
I STILL CAN RECALL ♪
♪ THE NIGHT THAT WE MET
THE THRILL OF IT ALL ♪
♪ HEAVEN KNOWS WHY
I FEEL LIKE I DO ♪
♪ BUT HEAVEN KNOWS I'M CRAZY
I'M CRAZY ABOUT YOU ♪
♪ HEAVEN KNOWS
WE SHOULD GO.
I'VE GOT AN EARLY CLASS
TOMORROW.
OH, OF COURSE, RIGHT.
WENDY, I AM SO SORRY.
I MEAN, I DID TRY
TO WARN YOU,
BUT EVEN THAT MUST'VE
BEEN A RECORD FOR ME.
IT'S OKAY. I'M FINE.
MY TOES ARE FINE.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL, REALLY.
THAT MARCO, HE HAD
SOME MOVES, HUH?
YEAH, UH, GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
HE'S A VERY GOOD DANCER.
YOU KNOW, I SAW HOW MUCH FUN
YOU WERE HAVING IN THERE.
I NEVER KNEW HOW MUCH
YOU ENJOYED DANCING.
I THINK I FORGOT.
DENNIS AND I USED TO LOVE
TO GO DANCING.
HE WAS A VERY GOOD DANCER, TOO.
UH, DON'T YOU HAVE
SCHOOL IN THE MORNING?
I DO.
YEAH, IT'S JUST...
YOU KNOW, IF COLLIN
MARRIES THIS SOPHIA,
DOES THAT MEAN THAT
MARCO IS GONNA BE...
YOU KNOW...
AROUND?
YOU KNOW, LIKE, FAMILY
GATHERINGS, DINNER...
YOUR HOUSE...
OH, YEAH, UM...
I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS I HADN'T EVEN
THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
HE'S AROUND ENOUGH ALREADY,
ISN'T HE?
HE IS?
WELL, HIS BUSINESS
IS RIGHT NEXT DOOR TO MINE.
RIGHT, OF COURSE. YEAH.
LOGAN, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
OF COURSE. SURE.
WE SHOULD GET GOING.
DANCING? REALLY?
OH, I DIDN'T THINK LOGAN
KNEW HOW TO DANCE.
OH, WELL...
HE DOESN'T.
HE TRIED. IT'S OKAY.
AH, AND THAT SUMS IT UP.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
NOTHING.
ROSEANNE...
LOGAN IS... SOLID.
HE'S PREDICTABLE.
HE'S SAFE.
SAFE IS A GOOD THING.
I HAVE ALREADY BEEN
THROUGH HEARTBREAK.
I DON'T NEED
TO GO THROUGH THAT AGAIN.
SO YOU DON'T LOVE HIM?
LOGAN IS A GOOD MAN.
[GROANS]
OKAY, SO, UH...
WHAT ABOUT MARCO?
YOU LIGHT UP
WHENEVER HE'S IN THE ROOM.
THAT'S "WHAT
ABOUT MARCO?"
WE WERE SIMPLY
DISCUSSING THE KIDS.
I HAVE SEEN THE WAY
YOU LOOK AT HI--
GO ON, TELLING ME IT'S
ABOUT SOME DARN KIDS!
DON'T YOU HAVE SOME WORK
YOU NEED TO BE DOING?
AND I HAVE SOME WORK
I NEED TO BE DOING AT HOME.
I GUESS YOU DO.
GO ON AND RUN AWAY FROM DENIAL.
[LAUGHS]
[RAY]: SHE WAS.
KIND, GENEROUS...
THE MOST LOVING SPIRIT
YOU COULD EVER FIND.
I'M REALLY SORRY
YOU LOST HER.
SO AM I.
IT'S HARD TO OPEN
YOUR HEART UP AGAIN
AFTER LOSING
SOMEONE LIKE THAT.
I TRIED.
LORD, I TRIED,
BUT I GOT SCARED
EACH TIME.
WENDY KNOWS.
SHE LOST THAT KIND OF LOVE
WHEN DENNIS DIED.
AND NOW...
SHE'S JUST SCARED, TOO.
HEY!
SO WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING HERE?
HI, MRS. HAMPTON.
RAY HERE WAS JUST TELLING ME
ABOUT YOUR MOTHER.
OH?
UM...
I'LL JUST LEAVE YOU
TWO LADIES TO IT,
SEEING AS I GOTTA SEND
SOME ROSES OFF
TO MY OWN DIXIE ROSE.
NICE CHATTING
WITH YOU, SOPHIA.
YOU, TOO, RAY.
SOPHIA!
WHAT BRINGS YOU BY?
I WAS ACTUALLY HOPING
TO SPEAK TO YOU, MRS. HAMPTON.
OF COURSE, BUT PLEASE,
CALL ME WENDY.
LOOK, I UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU'RE WORRIED.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
TALKING TO YOUR DAD,
I REALIZED THAT WE ALL HAVE
TO DEAL WITH LOSS,
AND I ACTUALLY THINK
THAT BRINGS PEOPLE
CLOSER TOGETHER.
BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I WOULD DO
IF SOMETHING EVER HAPPENED
TO COLLIN.
OH, MY GOSH...
YOU WERE SO YOUNG!
WERE YOUR MOM AND DAD
AT THE WEDDING?
YES.
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL
IN YOUR DRESS.
DID YOUR MOTHER HELP YOU
PICK IT OUT?
YES, SHE DID.
I'M SUPPOSED TO SEE
MY MOTHER TOMORROW.
[PHONE RINGS]
HELLO?
OH, HI, EMILY...
YES, YES, THAT'S TWO DOZEN.
NO, PLEASE.
THANKS FOR CHECKING, EMILY.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
THAT WASN'T COLLIN'S EMILY,
WAS IT?
YES... IT WAS.
SHE'S A WONDERFUL FLORIST.
I LOVE WORKING WITH HER.
THEY WERE-- THEY WERE
REALLY SERIOUS, WEREN'T THEY?
YES... THEY WERE.
WELL, I'VE TAKEN UP
ENOUGH OF YOUR TIME, WENDY.
I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
'KAY, BYE.
BYE.
SEAN AND CANDACE...
YOUR MARRIAGE OFFERS YOU
THE PROMISE OF LOVE,
WHICH IS TRUE AND MATURE.
[FRANTIC "WEDDING MARCH" MUSIC]
TO TAKE THIS LOVE,
YOU HAVE TO COMMIT YOURSELVES
TO EACH OTHER GLADLY...
[WOMAN]: THERE YOU ARE!
MY LAWYER SAID
THAT YOU CHANGED THE SETTLEMENT.
IF YOU THINK THAT I AM GONNA BE
HAPPY WITH THAT DUMP OF A HOUSE,
THEN YOU HAVE GOT
ANOTHER THING COMING!
[STAN]: LANA! THIS IS
MY BROTHER'S WEDDING!
[SEAN]:
WILL YOU GET HER OUT OF HERE?
SEE? YOUR FAMILY
IS A NIGHTMARE.
[GUESTS MURMUR]
I... I CAN'T DO THIS.
I'M NOT MARRYING YOU!
[SEAN]: BUT MY FAMILY...
HEY, WAIT!
[YELLING]
SHOULD I JUST
START DISMANTLING?
UH, HONEY, I GOTTA GO.
GARY JUST SENT ME A TEXT.
BABY ROSIE'S GOT A FEVER.
OH, OKAY... IT'S
OKAY, ROSEANNE.
DON'T WORRY, EMILY.
I'LL CALL COLLIN
TO COME HELP YOU.
[DIALS]
[DOOR OPENS]
HEY, MOM.
I GOT YOUR MESSAGE.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
COLLIN?
EMILY!
HEY.
COLLIN, SWEETHEART,
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
WE HAD A RATHER SUDDEN
WEDDING CANCELLATION,
ROSEANNE HAD TO LEAVE,
AND I REALLY NEED YOUR HELP
TAKING EVERYTHING DOWN.
SURE.
START THERE.
YEAH.
YEAH, THERE WE...
[LAUGHS]
[COLLIN AND EMILY LAUGH]
MOM, I THINK WE'RE DONE,
UNLESS YOU CAN THINK
OF SOMETHING ELSE
WE CAN HELP YOU WITH.
NO, IT LOOKS GREAT.
THANK YOU!
WHY DON'T YOU KIDS
GO GET SOMETHING TO EAT?
GREAT, BECAUSE
I AM STARVING.
ME TOO.
AND YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M THINKING OF?
ZENO'S!
YES! LET'S DO IT.
BYE, MOM!
I'M SO SORRY...
BUT YOU'RE VERY FORTUNATE
TO HAVE SUCH A GREAT FATHER.
SOPHIA!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT
YOU WERE WITH YOUR MOTHER.
SHE NEVER SHOWED UP.
OH, SOPHIA...
[RAY]: YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
THANKS, RAY.
I'M SO SORRY.
NO, IT'S MY OWN FAULT.
I SHOULD HAVE EXPECTED IT.
BUT I'LL BE OKAY BECAUSE...
I KNOW THAT I'M GETTING
THE BEST MOTHER-IN-LAW
A BRIDE COULD HOPE FOR.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY LUCKY ONE.
GOSH, I WAS REALLY HOPING
TO SEE COLLIN.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE HE IS?
YEAH, HE'S OVER AT ZENO'S.
GREAT.
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING, WENDY.
SOPHIA!
SOPHIA, WAIT!
NO, SOPHIA! SOPHIA!
WENDY?
WHERE'S THE FIRE?
ZENO'S, IF I CAN'T REACH COLLIN.
[PHONE RINGS]
OH, NO.
HE LEFT HIS PHONE.
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
DAD, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
AH, PRENUPS!
P... R... E...
N... U... P... S.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
DAD, I GOT IT.
[PHONE RINGS]
HELLO?
MARCO, IT'S WENDY.
I NEED YOU
TO CALL SOPHIA AND STOP HER.
STOP HER? I THOUGHT SHE WAS
WITH HER MOTHER.
SHE'S NOT. YOU NEED TO STOP HER
FROM GETTING TO ZENO'S.
NON ANCORA...
WHAT HAPPENED?
JUST CALL HER!
I'LL MEET YOU THERE.
[COLLIN AND EMILY LAUGH]
SO WHAT ABOUT YOU?
HAVE YOU FOUND ANYONE?
ACTUALLY, I HAVE.
HER NAME'S SOPHIA.
IN FACT...
WE'RE ENGAGED.
WOW...
THAT'S REALLY...
THAT'S REALLY GREAT, COLLIN.
I KNOW
IT DIDN'T WORK OUT FOR US,
BUT I KNOW NOW
IT WAS FOR THE BEST.
HOW DOES YOUR MOM FEEL?
SHE'S NOT TAKING IT TOO WELL.
[LAUGHING]
YOU KNOW, COLLIN,
I HOPE
THIS SOPHIA'S GOOD TO YOU...
BECAUSE YOU DESERVE THE BEST.
THANK YOU.
SO DO YOU.
[PHONE RINGS]
THANK YOU.
SOPHIA!
[WENDY]: SOPHIA, WAIT.
I PROMISE,
THIS IS NOT WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
SOPHIA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING
TO SEE YOUR MOTHER.
YEAH, I'M SURE YOU DID.
EXCUSE ME?
NO, THIS IS ALL
MY FAULT.
I SHOULD NEVER
HAVE LET THIS HAPPEN.
LET WHAT HAPPEN?
ARE YOU EVEN READY
FOR THIS COMMITMENT?
ARE YOU, COLLIN?
BECAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAYBE MY FATHER IS RIGHT.
WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
SOPHIA, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY AREN'T YOU
AT YOUR MOTHER'S?
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE, DAD!
I THINK I'M
JUST GONNA GO.
MOM, WHAT DID YOU DO?
COLLIN, I...
HEY, LISTEN TO ME.
WOULD YOU JUST LISTEN TO ME?
LEAVE ME ALONE, DAD.
SOPHIA!
DO SOMETHING!
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON!
THIS WHOLE THING
IS A MESS.
[MUTTERS IN ITALIAN]
I FEEL TERRIBLE.
THEY'RE MAKING
BAD DECISIONS...
DECISIONS THEY'LL
LATER REGRET.
WHAT, LIKE...
OPENING A DIVORCE PRACTICE
RIGHT NEXT TO A WEDDING PLANNER?
LOOK...
EVERYTHING'S
GONNA BE OKAY.
WE'RE ALL
WE ARE?
BECAUSE I REALLY DON'T FEEL
THAT WAY RIGHT NOW.
LOOK, UM...
JUST DON'T WORRY.
I'LL START LOOKING
FOR A NEW OFFICE TO LEASE,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT.
YEAH.
IT'S PROBABLY BETTER THAT WAY.
I SHOULD GO TALK TO COLLIN.
COLLIN, I AM SO, SO SORRY.
WHAT HAPPENED AT ZENO'S
WAS A MISTAKE.
I NEVER MEANT FOR...
MOM...
YOU'VE BEEN AGAINST US
GETTING MARRIED
FROM THE START.
OH, HONEY...
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO PROTECT YOU.
PROTECT ME FROM WHAT?
LOVE? HAPPINESS?
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT
SOPHIA WAS FOR ME...
IS FOR ME.
I JUST GOT SCARED.
SEEING YOU SO, SO CHANGED,
AND EVERYTHING WAS HAPPENING
SO FAST.
I...
I JUST DIDN'T WANT TO SEE YOU
GETTING HURT.
EVER SINCE DAD DIED,
YOU'VE LIVED YOUR LIFE
LIKE YOU'RE TRYING TO PROTECT
YOURSELF FROM LOVE.
I KNOW IT HURTS.
I WAS THERE.
IT HURT ME, TOO.
BUT I'M NOT GONNA LIVE
MY LIFE LIKE THAT.
I CAN'T.
HE'S RIGHT, YOU KNOW.
BECAUSE FOR THE LAST 30 YEARS,
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO
DO THE SAME THING.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
AFTER YOUR MOM DIED,
I DIDN'T THINK I COULD EVER
OPEN UP MY HEART AGAIN.
AND EVERY TIME
I FELT I MIGHT,
I RAN AWAY...
MORE TIMES
THAN YOU OR I COULD COUNT.
I KNOW YOU JUST THOUGHT I WAS
BEING FOOTLOOSE AND FANCY FREE,
BUT... I WAS SCARED.
JUST LIKE YOU.
SO THAT'S WHY THERE WERE
SO MANY GIRLFRIENDS.
YEAH.
WENDY...
I'D BEEN LIVING MY LIFE
AFRAID TO GET HURT ALSO...
BUT A LIFE WITHOUT LOVE
IS NO LIFE AT ALL,
AND IT SURE ISN'T
THE LIFE I WANT FOR YOU.
DON'T BE AFRAID.
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
AW...
NOTHING THAT CAN'T BE FIXED.
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
LOGAN.
OF COURSE.
GAME NIGHT, RIGHT?
IT IS,
BUT, ACTUALLY, I HAVE
SOMETHING BETTER PLANNED.
REALLY?
OKAY!
WHAT'S THAT?
THIS.
OH, LOGAN, I...
NOW, I HAVE THE RECEIPT
IN CASE YOU DON'T LIKE IT.
I KNOW IT MAY SEEM IMPULSIVE,
BUT IF YOU THINK
ABOUT IT,
WE HAVE BEEN DATING
FOR A WHILE,
AND IT MAKES
PERFECT SENSE TO ME
THAT YOU AND I SHOULD TAKE THIS,
"US," TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
NOW, I AM GONNA BE
COLLECTING
A REALLY GREAT PENSION
IN A FEW YEARS...
LOGAN...
WE NEED TO TALK.
LOOKS LIKE NEITHER ONE OF US
GOT MUCH SLEEP LAST NIGHT.
I MEAN...
HOW COULD I?
WHAT WITH SOPHIA CRYING
ALL NIGHT?
LOOK, I KNOW WE THOUGHT
WE WERE DOING THE RIGHT THING,
BUT WE WERE WRONG.
I MEAN, SO WHAT
IF THEY PICK A ROAD
WE THINK
IS GONNA BE TOO HARD?
IT'S NOT LIKE
THEY DON'T BELONG TOGETHER.
IF THEY WANT TO MILK COWS,
LET THEM MILK COWS.
THEY'RE IN LOVE...
AND MAYBE LOVE MAKES YOU
DO CRAZY THINGS,
BUT THEY KNOW WHAT THEY'RE DOING
AND WHAT THEY WANT.
WHEN DENNIS AND I GOT MARRIED,
WE DIDN'T KNOW!
WENDY, WENDY...
I AGREE.
WE NEED TO FIX THIS.
OKAY.
WELL, GOOD!
THEN LET'S TALK TO SOPHIA
AND FIX THIS.
SHE SAID SHE WAS GOING
FOR A WALK IN THE PARK.
THEN LET'S GO.
ALLOW ME.
THANK YOU.
WHAT ARE THEY SAYING?
I DON'T KNOW.
OH...
THANK GOD.
WHAT A RELIEF!
OW!
[SOCCER PLAYER]:
OOPS! SORRY!
MOM?
DAD?
HI.
WE JUST WANTED
TO MAKE THINGS RIGHT
AND SAY HOW SORRY
WE ARE FOR EVERYTHING.
UM, YEAH,
WE WERE JUST DOING
WHAT WE THOUGHT
WAS BEST FOR YOU.
DAD, I'M NOT ONE
OF YOUR CLIENTS
YOU CAN JUST "MANAGE."
I GET IT, YOU THINK
THIS WHOLE THING IS A MISTAKE,
BUT IT'S OUR LIFE,
AND WE'RE GOING TO GET MARRIED,
WITH OR WITHOUT YOUR BLESSING.
SOPHIA, I WAS JUST
TRYING TO PROTECT YOU.
DAD, DON'T, OKAY?
YOU CAN'T KEEP PROTECTING ME
JUST BECAUSE MOM LEFT US.
IF YOU WANT TO KEEP
TELLING YOURSELF
THAT IT'S BETTER TO BE ALONE,
THEN GO AHEAD.
BUT THAT'S NOT
THE LIFE I WANT...
IT'S NOT THE LIFE
WE WANT.
[COLLIN]: NOW WE'RE GOING
TO GET OUR MARRIAGE LICENSE
AND WE'RE PUTTING A DOWN PAYMENT
ON THE FARM
AND THAT'S IT.
THERE'S NO MORE INTERFERING
OR TRYING TO STOP US.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
WELL, WE CERTAINLY
MESSED THAT UP.
YOU'RE NOT KIDDING.
WE'LL BE LUCKY
IF WE EVEN GET
INVITED TO THE WEDDING.
THAT'S IT!
THAT'S HOW WE MAKE
THINGS RIGHT!
WHAT BETTER WAY
TO SHOW OUR SUPPORT
THAN THROW THEM
THE WEDDING OF THEIR DREAMS?
YOU WANNA THROW
THEM A WEDDING?
I MEAN, IT'S NOT EXACTLY
MY FIELD OF EXPERTISE.
DON'T WORRY, IT'S MINE.
ARE YOU IN?
YOU BET I'M IN.
[PHONE RINGS]
HELLO?
[WENDY]: MARIANNE?
WOULD YOU AND CLIFF BE OKAY
IF WE USED THE FARM
AS A LOCATION
FOR THE KIDS' WEDDING?
AND IT'S TOMORROW.
WOULD THAT BE OKAY?
AH...
HAVE THE WEDDING HERE?
OF COURSE.
WE'D LOVE THAT!
OH, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[DIALS]
OH, ROSEANNE,
I'M SO GLAD I CAUGHT YOU.
OKAY, I DON'T HAVE A LOT OF TIME
TO EXPLAIN,
BUT COLLIN AND SOPHIA
ARE GETTING MARRIED TOMORROW.
[ROSEANNE]: WHAT?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
THEY'RE GETTING MARRIED
TOMORROW?
WHAT ARE THEY THINKING?
ARE THEY GOING TO LAS VEGAS?
NO. NO, NO, NO,
BUT MARCO AND I
ARE SURPRISING THEM
WITH THEIR DREAM WEDDING
AT THE FARM.
HMM, SINCE WHEN DID
YOU AND MR. GORGEOUS MAKE UP
AND BECOME CUPID-IN-LAWS?
OKAY, LOOK, I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO EXPLAIN EVERYTHING.
JUST GO WITH ME ON THIS.
WE'RE GONNA NEED
AT LEAST 20 CHAIRS,
A COUPLE OF FOLD-OUT TABLES,
AND LET'S JUST GO
WITH THE DECORATIONS
FROM THE McDOUGAL WEDDING.
YOU MEAN THE WEDDING
THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN?
WHAT ABOUT CAKE AND FLOWERS?
MARCO AND I HAVE THE CAKE
AND FLOWERS COVERED.
THANKS, ROSEANNE.
I'LL SEE YOU IN THE MORNING
AT THE FARM.
I LOVE COLLIN,
BUT YOU KNOW YOU'RE GIVING ME
A RAISE FOR ALL OF THIS.
I KNOW.
OKAY. SEE YOU IN THE MORNING.
LOGAN! HI!
HI.
HOW ARE YOU?
I'M... GOOD.
I'M GOOD, WENDY.
MAY I?
YES, OF COURSE! PLEASE!
YOU KNOW, I'M JUST SO GLAD
THAT WE REALIZED
THAT US... YOU... WE...
JUST WEREN'T RIGHT
FOR EACH OTHER.
NOT IN THAT WAY.
RIGHT, 'CAUSE EVEN THOSE THINGS
THAT SEEM LIKE A GOOD MATCH
AREN'T.
LIKE WATER AND LIPIDS.
I MEAN, THEY DON'T MIX.
HOW'S COLLIN?
DID HE AND SOPHIA
FIGURE THINGS OUT?
OH, MY GOSH, YES!
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
WE'RE SURPRISING THEM
WITH A WEDDING TOMORROW.
I HAVE SO MUCH TO DO!
THAT IS SO GREAT FOR THEM.
YOU KNOW,
I THINK COLLIN AND SOPHIA
ARE A REALLY GOOD MATCH.
LOOK, CAN I LEND AN EXTRA HAND
TOMORROW?
I'D BE HAPPY TO HELP.
REALLY?
OH, WE COULD DEFINITELY
USE A LITTLE HELP.
THANK YOU.
BUT YOU MUST STAY
FOR THE WEDDING.
SOUNDS GREAT!
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
OH, HI! UM...
CAN I PLEASE GET
TWO REGULAR COFFEES,
ONE BLACK,
AND ONE WITH LOW-FAT MILK
AND ONE SUGAR.
THANKS.
NO, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOOD.
THANKS, LOGAN.
OH, THE...
IT'S FOR BEVERLY.
I'M MEETING BEVERLY HERE.
THE COFFEE'S FOR BEVERLY.
WELL, SHE WAS CURIOUS
ABOUT BIOLOGY WEEK,
AND SINCE SHE COULDN'T ATTEND...
NO, IT'S OKAY!
I THINK IT'S GREAT!
THE COFFEE,
BEVERLY...
IT'S ALL GOOD!
WHY DON'T YOU INVITE BEVERLY
TO THE WEDDING TOMORROW?
WELL, THAT WOULD BE NICE.
THANKS.
I'VE REALLY GOTTA GO,
BUT THANK YOU SO MUCH,
AND I WILL SEE YOU TOMORROW!
OKAY, SO THIS ONE...
BUT VEGAN.
SO NO MILK, NO EGGS,
NO BUTTER.
THANK YOU!
NOTHING TOO FORMAL.
NO ROSES, NO ORCHIDS...
WHAT ABOUT WILDFLOWERS?
PERFECT!
[EMILY]: GREAT.
[DOOR OPENS]
FOR YOU.
JUST CONSIDER IT
A PEACE OFFERING
AND A...
WELL, A CONGRATULATIONS
ON A JOB WELL DONE.
THANK YOU.
WELL...
IF ALL GOES AS PLANNED,
I GUESS I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
MARCO...
MAYBE YOU DON'T NEED
TO TERMINATE YOUR LEASE.
I MEAN...
MAYBE IT COULD WORK.
AND, UM...
HOW WOULD LOGAN FEEL?
WE'VE MOVED ON...
JUST FRIENDS.
NICE FLOWERS.
AREN'T THEY?
MARCO GAVE THEM TO ME.
THERE'S A SMILE
I HAVEN'T SEEN FOR A WHILE...
NOT SINCE DENNIS WAS ALIVE.
HEY, GRANDPA.
HEY, COLLIN.
DON'T WORRY.
HE'LL COME AROUND.
OKAY, DAD, I NEED YOUR HELP.
YOU KNOW THE WEDDING
IS TOMORROW AT 1:00.
CAN YOU GET SOPHIA
AND COLLIN TO THE FARM?
GOT IT.
I'LL ASK FOR A TOUR
OF THE PROPERTY.
PERFECT!
[LOGAN]: DID YOU KNOW THAT
THE FIRST USE OF WEDDING FLOWERS
CAN BE ATTRIBUTED TO THE GREEKS?
THE GARLAND BOUQUET WOULD OFTEN
HAVE BULBS OF GARLIC IN IT
TO WARD OFF ANY EVIL SPIRITS
THAT COULD, YOU KNOW,
HARM THE COUPLE'S FUTURE.
-SORRY.
-IT'S OKAY.
WHY DON'T I TAKE THIS ONE
RIGHT TO THE BARN?
GREAT IDEA.
-OKAY.
WELL... HOW DO I LOOK?
SI BELLISSIMA.
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
[DISTANT SOUND OF CAR ENGINE]
THEY'RE HERE!
WHA...
MOM, WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S YOUR
DREAM WEDDING...
JUST LIKE
YOU DESCRIBED!
AND DON'T WORRY--
EVERYTHING IS VEGAN,
INCLUDING THE CAKE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THIS IS...
AMAZING, GUYS.
I LOVE IT!
IT'S PERFECT.
THANK YOU.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
IT'S ITALIAN.
THANK YOU.
AND THIS IS
FOR YOU...
IF YOU WANT IT, OF COURSE.
OH, MY GOD,
THIS IS YOUR DRESS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH,
WENDY, IT'S PERFECT.
WELL, YOU TWO,
BETTER GET DRESSED!
YOU HAVE A WEDDING
TO CATCH.
[LAUGHS]
ARE YOU READY, DAD?
READY AS I'LL EVER BE.
[WEDDING MARCH BEGINS]
YOU TAKE CARE OF HER.
I WILL.
I PROMISE.
[PASTOR]: LET US ALL REMEMBER
THAT THE PATH OF LOVE
IS MEANT TO BE WALKED TOGETHER,
WITH ALL THE HUMAN FAMILY.
ALL LOVE IS NURTURED AND GUIDED
BY THE LOVE OF OTHERS.
EACH OF US COUNTS ON RELATIVES,
FRIENDS, AND NEIGHBORS
FOR THE CARING AND CONCERN
THAT REPLENISHES
THEIR OWN ABILITY TO LOVE.
MARRY THIS DAY IN THE MIDST
OF AFFECTION AND LOVE...
FROM YOUR FRIENDS
AND ESPECIALLY YOUR PARENTS.
I ASK THEM NOW
FOR THEIR BLESSING
ON THE MARRIAGE
OF THEIR CHILDREN.
DO YOU,
THE PARENTS OF THIS COUPLE,
GIVE YOUR BLESSING AND PROMISE
THE SUPPORT OF YOUR LOVE
TO THIS MARRIAGE?
YES, WE DO.
FOR BETTER, FOR WORSE,
FOR RICHER, FOR POORER,
IN SICKNESS AND IN HEALTH,
'TIL DEATH DO YOU PART.
[PLAYING JAZZ MUSIC]
WELL DONE, HONEY.
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING,
ROSEANNE.
EXCUSE ME, BEVERLY,
WOULD YOU LIKE TO DANCE?
OH, THAT WOULD BE
WONDERFUL!
POSSO AVERE QUESTO BALLO?
YOU SPEAK ITALIAN?
THINKING ABOUT LEARNING.
AFTER ALL,
IT IS THE LANGUAGE OF LOVE.
♪ WALKING DOWN THE AVENUE
♪ DREAMING
♪ WISHING I COULD BE WITH YOU
♪ HOPING AND SCHEMING
♪ BUT LOVE IS HARD TO EXPLAIN
♪ IT CAN SLIP
THROUGH YOUR FINGERS ♪
♪ SOME MEMORIES FADE
SOME MEMORIES LINGER ♪
♪ MY LOVER, MY FRIEND
I STILL CAN RECALL ♪
♪ THE NIGHT THAT WE MET
THE THRILL OF IT ALL ♪
♪ HEAVEN KNOWS WHY
I FEEL LIKE I DO ♪
♪ BUT HEAVEN KNOWS I'M CRAZY
I'M CRAZY ABOUT YOU ♪
♪ HEAVEN KNOWS
[♪♪♪]