At what point shall we expect
the approach of danger?
By what means
shall we fortify against it?
You are out.
You know what I like?
The ancient Greeks.
Egyptians and Romans.
Alexander the Great'
Julius Caesar, Cleopatra,
the Trojan Horse,
gladiators, chariot races,
spectacular murders and suicides,
the eruption of Vesuvius,
temples, amphitheaters, arenas,
mosaics' frescoes' baths.
I remember those things
as if I learned them yesterday.
But then the Middles Ages...
-And...
-Is this over the summer?
It was over the...
It was over the, like...
into the beginning of August.
So you ditched school
for the first couple of weeks?
I did do that, yeah. I did.
But I told my parents
that what I was doing was...
But then the Middle Ages?
Fuck that.
A blip of a disgusting mess.
The Renaissance,
the beginning of the end,
the modern age, just look at us.
And American history,
what is that?
I remember studying
in high school
and praying for the British to win.
Praying for the Native Americans
to slaughter the Pilgrims'
for the whole kit and caboodle
to go up in smoke'
both sides in the Civil War.
And then both World Wars
and, and Korea and Vietnam
and Kuwait, Iraq, Afghanistan.
Who needs that?
They don't. They don't care.
Neither do I, neither do you.
I'm not going.
Paul, it takes three months
to get a reservation to this place.
And Stan got it overnight.
Congratulations.
Well, so, you don't want them here,
you refuse to go to their place.
-You don't want to go anywhere.
-I'd rather stay home with you.
That restaurant's a joke.
Anyway, it's ridiculous.
It sounds super-exclusive
and sexy and food art.
Like going to France.
During the German occupation, maybe.
Look, I'm sure
we're gonna get a great table...
-Great table at a great restaurant...
-For God's sake.
-Great dinner in great company...
-You can't do this.
It comes at great expense.
Stan'll pay. I need help.
For that kind of expense,
you know, you pay a bigger price
for not picking up the check.
Okay.
-In there.
-I know how.
That goes in there.
-It's just...
-Here.
Okay.
Thank you.
-How are you feeling?
-Great.
-You?
-Punished.
Just don't want to be
with these people.
-What's so funny?
-It's you.
You. You.
This routine
we have to go through
every time we wanna
leave the house.
"These people."
You're right. These leeches,
these maggots, these apes.
Let's cancel.
I want you think about tonight
as a date with me.
The two of us out on the town.
We're gonna ditch them
at some point,
and we'll go have a nightcap
somewhere.
It will be fun.
You know Michael has a girl over.
Is that a bad thing?
-She looks 25.
-She's 20
and she's very nice.
Jesus, he moves fast.
What is she, a college student?
A barista.
-So he's drinking coffee now.
-Not drinking coffee.
He's drinking caramel, salted,
hot chocolate with whipped cream.
What? What's bothering you?
-He tells you too much.
-No, he doesn't.
-He just tells me everything.
-Not everything.
Look, it's too much.
You treat him like a daughter.
Come on, let's go.
Get ready. I don't want to be late.
No, I thought you didn't want to go.
If we're late, it's just
another victory for the apes.
Okay, you know we're gonna be
too early now.
We can get a drink in the bar.
It's, you know,
they have like a lounge thing.
At least, you know, online.
Love you.
Love you, too.
I mean, I really do.
It's pretty much unbearable.
No.
I have the spreadsheet, yes.
I know what he said.
I was there.
-Thank you.
-Congressman.
What?
No.
-Is this really happening?
-It was so fucking tense.
Dad.
-Dad?
-Hey. What's going on?
What are you doing with my phone?
I just... nothing.
Just looking for you.
-Why?
-You know...
-What's going on?
-I don't know. Just looking for you.
Just... Where's the girl?
The girl has a name, Dad.
Okay, where's, Jennifer, Michelle...
-Zoe...
-Anna.
Anna.
Yeah, Anna. It's not like that.
We're just friends.
Well, tell Anna to come up.
We don't bite.
Do you know
where the bike pump is?
-It's...
-It's not in the garage.
It's... I don't know where...
Have you tried the bushes
in the backyard?
Why would they be in the bushes?
-You okay, Dad?
-Sure. Yeah.
We have to go out to dinner,
with the hominids.
-Who's that?
-Great apes.
They don't teach you anything
at school these days?
See? You do bite.
-Hey, I found your...
-Hello...
-pump.
-Anna.
-We'll be out of your way real soon.
-Okay.
-Are you a smoker, Anna?
-What? No.
Good for you. That's...
Keep away from cigarettes.
If you kids are hungry,
there's, plenty of food in the fridge.
Not that you're a kid,
you know.
You're a young person.
I mean, we have a coffee machine,
-if you want a coffee.
-Cool.
Understand you're
in the hospitality business.
-Yeah.
-That's it.
Here it is. For four?
-Mr. and Mrs. Lohman have not arrived.
-Yes, we have.
You want to see our driving license?
-No, I mean...
-I know what you meant.
-I'm his brother.
-Of course. I apologize.
I accept your apology.
But he wouldn't
if it was the other way around.
Of course. Right this way.
Mr. and Mrs. Lohman, welcome.
So glad you could join us this evening.
Mrs. Lohman, can we take
your coat, please?
Hello.
-Watch your step.
-Stay where you are, guys.
Thank you.
That's it for tonight.
Good job. Good job, everybody.
Thank you.
All right, go home.
I'll see you tomorrow.
-No, I'm coming in.
-There's really no need.
-Give us a call in...
-I'm not leaving you alone tonight.
Not with everything that's going on.
-I mean, seriously, boss.
-Okay.
But I don't want to be disturbed
during dinner.
That's fine.
Wait, hold on, Congressman.
It's a DC number.
-Who is it?
-I think... Yes, it's the Speaker.
Great, great, great, great.
Thank you. Great.
Mr. Speaker, before you say anything,
I want you to know
I'm working on Parity votes.
And we are close.
Here we have a garden of young
vegetables for you while you wait.
Chantenay carrots,
breakfast radishes,
wild fennel
and a Tokyo turnip.
Simply served with olive oil
from the Peloponnese,
-infused with rosemary from Oregon.
-Tarragon?
Oregon the state.
Oregonian rosemary.
-Yes.
-I know it's a state.
I, I thought they grew oregano
in Oregon.
-Funny.
-Yeah. Timing.
Also, there is a light dusting...
I mean, we don't have "time"
for rosemary so take it away.
-My God.
-There is a light dusting
-of Himalayan pink salt.
-That is delicious.
Can you taste the wars and plagues
and the fire bombings,
lightly doused with a drizzle
of famine and. polished off
-with some volcanic eruption.
-He's showing off now.
He used to teach.
Here's the wine menu
for your selection.
No. No, the campaign
is not slowing me down at all.
In fact, I'm more determined
than ever.
Yeah, I just need tonight
to tally everything up.
Yeah.
Come on, Stan, we have to go.
Yeah, sorry. Sir, sir?
I'm sorry, got to go.
Got to go. Yeah.
I'll have those votes by the morning.
Okay, and Kate,
Kate sends her best,
her love...
to you and Sabina.
Thanks.
Talk to you tomorrow.
Bye.
-Jesus Christ.
-What?
Do you know how much this bottle
of pink shit we just ordered costs?
Don't worry about it.
I'm sure Stan won't mind.
That's immoral.
That's an act of war.
-That's, that's...
-It's not.
-Come on.
-It's champagne.
-It's a fancy drink.
-I'm not drinking something that expensive.
-Okay, you don't have to drink it.
-It's fucking wrong.
Here we go.
No, no, you can go.
You can go, thank you.
Hello, Congressman.
Good to see you again.
-Welcome back.
-Thank you so much. Thank you, thank you.
-I don't think you were here last time.
-I was in France.
Yeah, yeah.
-Hi.
-I'm so sorry that we're late.
Paul insisted. We were early.
-Really.
-Actually, I insisted. We were on time.
Aw, Paul.
It's been a hell of a day.
-Nice to see you.
-Here, too.
Can we just go out and get pizza?
-Why? What's wrong with this place?
-Nothing.
-Everything.
-You look good, Paul.
-Thanks.
Not as good as my brother,
but then I don't spend quite as
much time in makeup as he does.
Why don't you just take
the compliment and move on?
Sorry.
You look good, too, Kate.
Thank you.
And you are your usual gorgeous self,
Claire, it goes without saying.
Thanks.
Very nice to see you.
Please, please.
Sometimes it's very hard
to avoid people.
Claire, Claire. Look at you.
-Hello.
-You look great.
It's been too long.
It's fabulous.
-Thank you.
-Brother.
Worried about you there, Stan,
if you were gonna make it
across the room.
I got my posse here with me.
Highly trained bodyguards.
You can stop smiling now, Stan,
it's just us.
Give it a rest, will you, Paul.
This is long overdue.
What were you talking about?
-We...
-We were just...
We were just enjoying one of those
awkward pauses, as they say.
Not talking about anything.
Well, we're gonna talk tonight.
We're gonna put it all on the table...
Something wrong?
This is about...
-Stan, would you... stop.
-Are you okay?
No, no, don't.
-He doesn't like the table.
-See if there's a better table.
No, it's really, it's all right.
We're fine here.
-We just got settled.
-You know, actually, actually the other room...
-I think I'll see...
-But this room is private enough.
-There's no need.
-Private as a fish tank.
There's another room over there.
Just a second. Let me check it out.
-I actually agree.
-I'm not moving.
I'm not.
Thank you, Antonio.
You're a real jewel.
Thank you very much,
and for the table, too.
It's my pleasure.
All right, a toast.
To our beautiful wives.
How about to the children?
To health.
To getting through this dinner
in one piece.
Cheers.
For the gentlemen, we have a potage
of butternut squash,
that's with some candied
seasoned acorns,
two shoots roasted garlic
and a pecorino sardo tuile.
Yeah, it's quite delicious.
The ladies are having
our young winter roots.
Those are chioggia beets,
thumbelina carrots and purple radish,
that's served with a goat cheese
and smoked herring vinaigrette.
There's also a few charred leeks,
radicchio, blood orange,
and it's sprinkled
with a burnt pumpernickel soil on it.
-That's the one.
-That's what you ordered?
Really, it's beautiful.
Please feel free to start in
on those appetizers.
This is gorgeous.
These winter roots were grown
right here in our garden.
Terribly sorry.
The cork doesn't seem to want to be
cooperating with me on this one,
so let me run to the back
and get another bottle.
-My apologies.
-No, no, that's fine.
Always good for the nurse
to draw your blood,
not the specialist, right, Stan?
I don't know what you mean.
I felt bad for him.
He was very embarrassed.
Shouldn't be waiting on us.
That's what the waitresses are for.
Well, he knows me.
-We're friends.
-So what?
We're just people, eating food.
Eating very good food.
It is delicious, isn't it?
Excuse me.
Just a second.
I'll be right back.
You okay?
Okay, how's it looking?
We're 15 shy
and you need to flip them.
Grant's switched,
Murphy's back to wavering.
So that was a good call.
-Great. Great.
-The insurance lobbyists
are fighting on your Parity language
versus ACA.
-Yeah, of course. I expected.
-And we're here.
Why are we here?
Okay. Just, just dial.
You're not yourself,
but what's up with Katelyn?
Well, you've met my brother.
Okay, yeah, that's the thing.
You leave a fund-raiser in the middle
on the night you should be going to DC
to invite your
psycho brother to dinner?
All the time that I've known you,
you've never canceled anything
without consulting me.
-What is going on?
-It's a family matter. It's private.
That's all you need to know.
Are you fucking kidding me?
You are running for governor.
Your bill is going down in flames.
-Nothing is private.
-This is private
and it will stay private.
For now.
After tonight, it...
it'll all be over.
You are freaking me out.
Tell me what is going on.
I'd take a bullet for you,
you know that.
Don't take a bullet for me, ever.
Don't ever... Don't even talk like
that. I don't know why you just...
This is my bullet.
Dial.
Please just dial.
-Thank you very much.
-You're welcome.
-Can you just put all this on my tab?
-You got it.
-Stan Lohman.
-I know.
-How are you doing tonight?
-Hey. Very well. Thank you.
Can I get you anything else?
Look, can someone just call
a cab or something.
God. I mean, I don't have enough
for all the way home.
What about you, Beau?
I got three dollars.
Wait, don't you have
your mom's credit card?
No. I mean,
it maxed out last month so...
-And the month before.
-It was for emergency but...
-And the month before...
-I mean, listen,
I mean, the cabbies,
they want cash from kids, anyway.
-Yo, what about your dad's driver?
-Yeah, no, he's out of town.
Anyway, Dad doesn't want us kids
being chauffeured around anyway.
-Doesn't look good.
-He's a man of the people.
That's why,
that's why Uncle Stanley
and Aunt Barb adopted you?
-For the people?
-Okay, look, that's not funny.
I'm sorry, Jesus.
I'm just kidding.
I mean, everybody knows
your dad has the African-American
vote in the bag, anyway.
It's still not funny.
-Stop messing with him, Michael.
-What the fuck.
-Seriously.
-Jeez, I take it back, okay?
God, you guys.
Come on, Beau, lighten up.
Yo, that's pretty funny?
Telling him to lighten up.
-Get it?
-You're an idiot.
Jesus, I'm just drunk, okay?
Listen, I love you, cousin.
That's what's most important.
Even if you can't handle your beer.
That beer was bad.
How can anybody fucking
live in this town?
-It's a shithole.
-Everything sucks tonight.
It's just a small health club
but, you know,
I mind my own business.
It's really nice there.
Yeah, I just don't really like
how the club,
they work you hard
and how the instructor...
How is it looking?
We'll get there.
We'll get there. Yeah.
-I'm so sorry to interrupt.
-Yeah.
-This was in hallway.
-What is it?
-It's you, no?
-God, it is mine.
It's your pin.
-Here, let me.
-Where did you find it?
Just there the foyer.
-Enjoy now.
-Thank you.
That could have cost you
a few votes there, Stan.
Now you're back to loving America.
Thank you.
So, how's Beau?
What do you mean?
How's he doing?
You know... Don't you mean
how are the kids?
No.
I mean, how's Beau?
And then, how's Val
and then how's Rick and...
We don't...
Not necessarily go in that order.
I didn't mean... I didn't mean
anything by it. I just...
You speak so seldom
about the kids.
Sorry, I just thought
it was odd that you were...
That's okay. It's okay.
So, how is Beau, you know?
Same as always.
I, I think that he's starting
to open up with me
and then something triggers him
and then he goes back to...
But,
I have hope so...
I mean, he's always been
Barbara's boy.
He loves ya.
Is Val still going
to that special school?
Before and during the war,
there were dozens
of breech-loading rifles and carbines.
Both single... and multiple-shot.
Stan never objected.
I couldn't leave the kids there
in that filthy orphanage.
God, his smile
just warmed my heart.
You should've seen
the looks we got in the airport.
I felt so complete.
Yup, yup.
It's okay, baby.
Honestly, I think
our marriage needed that.
You know, with the move and all,
it's the best thing.
-Mommy.
-Okay, Val, it's okay, calm down, honey.
Come on. You want to take her
in the other room?
-Okay, now.
-All right.
She can be a bit much,
sometimes.
You know how kids are.
-She's done really well today.
-She's a good girl.
Handguns'
both single and multiple shot,
generally were carried by officers,
and possibly artillerymen.
While the type of handguns used
by both sides were...
-What are you reading, Paul?
-Two of the most common were...
It's a book.
Two of the most common were...
-He's researching Gettysburg.
-Shot-and-ball by Colt and Remington.
You know, for the book
he says he's writing.
Right.
You should think about adopting,
Claire. You know, Michael's alone.
I don't... I don't think
I could ever love another child.
-Seriously.
-No, no.
I mean, not with everything
we went through with Michael, no.
I mean, just trying to get pregnant
and then almost losing him, no.
I don't want to love another child.
I wish I had your clarity.
-Does that make me a horrible person?
-No.
No, not at all.
That's not what I'm saying. I just...
It adds a lot of pressure,
you know.
I can handle it.
Pressure on Michael.
Can't be healthy for him.
Beau?
Hey. Hey.
Hey, buddy, what is it?
It's all right.
It's okay. You're safe here, all right?
No one's gonna harm you.
Rick! Michael!
Get down here.
-What did you guys do to Beau?
-Nothing, Mom.
-Really nothing.
-I'm not gonna ask you again.
I just looked at him,
that's all, honestly.
You have to stop
picking on him.
How am I racist?
Do I really need to spell
this out for you?
I just think he instinctively
exploits his position in the family.
You know, it's fascinating.
She was never like this
with Rick or Val or Stanley.
Are you listening to yourself?
You do realize you're accusing a child
of playing the race card.
Exactly, it's just, it's...
It makes sense, he's a kid.
It's survival, it's Darwinian.
I get it, but I don't have to like it.
I'd be a racist
if I liked the little hypocrite
just because of
the color of his skin.
-That's racism.
-My God.
Or if my not liking the little shit
affected my opinion
of Africa in general or Kenya.
But it doesn't.
I just have a bad feeling about him.
-I'm not a racist.
-You don't know him.
-I'm not...
-You don't even know him.
Well, I'm not a racist.
At best, I'm...
Okay, okay, okay, okay,
you're not a racist. You're not.
-Orthodox thinking.
-All right. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry I brought it up.
-There's nothing malicious.
-Hey, hey.
-What?
Do you think we should have given
Michael a brother or sister?
What?
No, God, no, no, no, no.
Thank you, no, no.
Our family is perfect.
Perfect-ish. Okay?
And you can work on yourself.
It's not a doomed marriage.
No, watch.
They're gonna have
a fresh start in DC.
Who is the blind guy that said,
"Washington DC
would make for beautiful ruins"?
No, "wonderful," yeah.
"Wonderful ruins."
Senator from Oklahoma.
He was Gore Vidal's grandfather.
-Man, now I'm gonna be up all night.
-Google it.
That's cheating.
It's got to be hard on Barb.
-A needy, self-centered, little shit.
-Well, he's hardly ever home.
I don't mean Stan.
I mean, Beau, the kid.
Okay, shut up, "the kid."
You realize you still sound
like a racist.
Hey, half my students
are black, okay?
At least. More.
I'm the only person in my family
that cares about real people.
You know, running for public office.
Bullshit, Stan.
Elitist, self-serving,
just like mother raised him.
Stan is for Stanley.
I teach public school.
I go to those kids' homes,
I speak with their parents.
I help with their problems,
decently, idealistically.
I give them money sometimes,
for, you know, whatever.
And I don't have corporate sponsors
or lobbyists or fund-raisers.
And I'm... I'm not racist.
I'm a warrior for the underclass,
and I know how to ID
an asshole in the making.
Wow.
I'm voting for you.
My mother and Stan. Jesus.
Ever told you about the time
she slapped me so hard,
-I lost consciousness.
-No.
Well, it was,
she was always touching him,
hugging him and...
like some trophy.
Right there on the staircase.
I was, like, 11 years old, and I...
I said, "Get a room, you two."
And she lost it. She just...
What was his name?
Press called him the "blind cowboy."
-Hey, hey, hey.
-What was his name?
Hey, stop.
Stop.
That was kind of outrageous
what you said to her.
It was worth it, though.
It got her attention.
But you weren't really unconscious,
were you?
Just shut my eyes for a while.
I could hear Stan crying.
He thought she killed me.
It was a beautiful moment.
Thomas Gore.
The blind senator.
Fuck Google.
Mr. Lohman. Are we okay?
Are we okay?
I don't know, Heinz.
I don't know.
Do you have kids?
-No, I don't.
-Why not?
I have pure selfishness.
I haven't stopped
being a kid yet myself.
I think it's more selfish to have kids
than to not have them.
Yeah.
And talking about them is worse.
-Right?
-Yeah. Sure.
We were duped into having kids
by our genes
who need to create hosts
to propagate themselves
to ensure their survival
and to create future generations.
-That's what I think.
-Kinda dark.
-Yeah, it's kinda bleak.
-Yeah.
You chose well, Heinz.
Don't let the fuckers
get you down.
Who are the fuckers?
The... the kids?
People who want you
to have kids?
The genes, Heinz, the genes.
Of course. The genes.
Yeah.
Would your genes like a cocktail
while you're here?
I think they would.
-Good.
-That's the feeling I get.
What would you like?
A whiskey soda.
Absolutely, no problem.
Coming right up.
Yo, let's get some beer
before we get the cab.
I'm tired.
So what? So am I.
-The door's busted.
-I mean, you only had, like, three.
What happened?
That was fucking quick.
-What's going on?
-There's somebody in there.
Smells like shit.
It's disgusting.
Shit.
-Is he dead?
-I think so.
-Paul...
-Turns out, hitting the head
was really an excellent idea.
Should've thought of it myself.
You're such a filthy little asshole.
All right.
I guess it's just the three of us.
I can talk to her later about this.
-I think she wants someone to follow her.
-Really?
Yeah, I think that's normally how
it works in the kingdom of the apes.
I'll go.
That's probably better.
Thank you. Thanks.
I can't be a father again.
I can't do it.
She keeps talking about this,
but I can't do it.
You know, she's young.
She deserves to have her own kids.
I can't go there.
And she brings this up.
She uses it as a distraction,
so I... change the subject at hand.
That's why I think it's good she's
talking to another woman about it.
She doesn't have many women friends.
-So sorry.
-Yeah.
-Another change happened.
-What have we got?
Okay.
All right. Well, just check
and make sure these dates work.
Okay? And I will help him
on Appropriations,
but he's got to bring
Goren and Hazelton with him
-to my bill, okay?
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-Parity needs them.
Okay, thanks.
She's terrific.
There's someone with a sense of
commitment, dedication. I'm serious.
Yeah, I'm there sure is, Stan.
So what's the subject at hand,
why you invited us
out for dinner and all?
You know what it is.
We're way past that point.
We're all very good
at pretending.
But we have to do something.
Something has to be done here.
And for the record,
I didn't even know those boys
were going to the party that night.
-Does Katelyn know?
-Yes, she knows.
She knows now.
That's why, that's why...
And I'm assuming that Claire
knows everything?
Don't, don't assume.
For God's sake, man,
come on.
We don't talk about painful things.
She's been through a lot.
I don't want her to get sick again.
I don't, I don't get you,
I don't get your life. I...
Who asked you
to get anything?
Nobody.
My. Well, my bad.
Would you like to wait
until the ladies return to the table?
No. No. Just put them down.
It's fine.
-Okay. Very well, Congressman.
-They'll be back, sorry.
Thank you.
Here we have
guinea-hen and yolk
in a nest of foraged mushrooms
on a bed of mustard...
That's okay.
We don't need the summary.
-No, I want to hear more.
-Really delicious.
-Easy.
-It was fun.
Heinz, I thought we were friends.
-May I, Congressman, for your brother?
-Sure, go for it.
He's having line-caught
steelhead trout...
Paul, please.
-I'm so sorry.
-Yeah, that's okay.
He'll be back.
Most women
get sick of Stan
three, maybe four weeks
after they start fucking.
His first wife Barbara left him
to go live in an ashram in India.
She lost it.
You'd think it would make him
more humble' but no.
Yeah, well, anyway, we haven't
heard from her in a while.
The only reason I'm telling you this
is, as a warning,
in case you're falling for him.
Everyone falls for Stan.
Once you fall for him,
I can't protect you.
He's not my friend.
Not even voting for him.
In fact, I'm not voting at all.
Ever.
See, history is either a lie or a bore.
I tried to make the subject interesting
when I was teaching.
Now I have no one to talk to.
Kids needs to be entertained
in order to learn'
that's what I thought.
I was wrong.
History can't compete
with video games, YouTube,
Twitter, Facebook, Instagram,
Tumblr, Snapchat, Vine,
Kik, Burn Note, Whisper,
Yik Yak' Skype'
Tinder, Grinder, texting, sexting,
porn,
and that shitty, shitty, shitty orgy
of mind-numbness
they call Hollywood.
You see' kids'
history can't compete.
History is over.
Everything is happening
in this second.
-Hello.
-Dad?
-Yeah, Michael, where are you?
-Home. I've just been looking...
Sorry, I thought
I was calling my phone.
You were, you are.
-You have my phone?
-Sure looks like it.
-Why do you have it?
-I have no idea.
I must have thought it was mine.
One of those senior moments,
I guess.
I've been looking for it
for, like, forever.
Well, we'll be home
in an hour or so, so...
No, no, I need it now.
I, I just need some numbers.
You can ask me and I'll...
I can look them up for you.
I mean, what's... Is the passcode,
the same as always?
It's okay.
I'll just come and get it.
Don't worry about it.
-How?
-I don't know.
-I'll ride my bike.
-What? No.
Don't come up here.
It's too far.
Hey, do you mind giving me
a ride someplace?
It will take five minutes.
But you know, sometimes I think
I'm actually going to lose my mind.
Claire?
Paul.
Dear sweet Paul.
I am a monster for keeping
your wife away.
Yes, you are, Kate.
Yes, you are.
Far from it.
She's been patiently listening
to my complaints about work.
Sometimes,
it's just nice to connect.
You never complain, do you, Kate?
I mean, honestly,
I've never seen anything like it.
Really? Well,
never complain, never explain.
That's how my father raised me,
for better or worse.
I don't have anything
to complain about.
I mean, we all don't.
We're blessed.
Go inside. It's cold,
and the Congressman
is getting very lonely.
I just... just, I just want everyone
to be happy.
Is that so outrageous?
Of course not.
I'll be in in a second.
Hey, Beau here.
Tonight's okay.
Let's get it done tonight.
Get it over with.
I'll see you there, wuss.
Hi, love, it's Mom.
I'm on my way home.
Dad and I are going out
to a restaurant
and I'll make sure
that we stay out late.
Your father doesn't know
about tonight
and I'd like to keep it that way.
I'll check in with you around 10:00.
Please don't stress.
Take your bike.
It's all gonna be fine.
Nobody will ever find out
if we just keep cool.
Dad?
Hey. Hey-hey.
I thought I'd meet you outside.
I really feel guilty about the phone.
Here you go.
Were you just on my phone?
Who were you talking to?
-You.
-What?
I just was trying to call you.
I was worried about where you were.
This is my phone.
How were you trying to call me
on my own phone?
You know, I guess
I'm losing my mind.
Again.
You really think he's dead.
I guess...
It's just fucked up
this whole thing.
I think he's still breathing.
The fucker probably died...
He probably died in his sleep.
-I don't know, that's really horrible.
-It's not horrible. Don't be scared.
-Calm down.
-Are you getting the money or not?
-Let's go.
-Tell me about...
Come on.
Who cares? Just go!
Just do what Michael tells you.
God. Jesus!
Let's get out of here.
Well, don't be a pussy.
Come on,
he's a fucking homeless bum.
I think he's still alive.
Just find another ATM.
Come on,
don't be a pussy.
Jesus.
Come on.
Hey, yo, get up.
Get the fuck up.
The guy's probably deranged.
Well, I'm outta here.
-You're such a fuck...
-Beau, come on.
-Fuck you.
-Come on. Get back here.
-You're a little bitch.
-How are you gonna get home?
Look.
We still need the cab, jeez.
Look at this, really a piece of shit.
Hey! Why don't you get up?
Hey, stink-o!
Why don't you get the fuck up?
Smells like rotten eggs.
Probably got some
fucking food in there.
Hey, mister. Get up!
There's one of you
and there's two of us.
You better get the fuck up.
Come on, get up.
Leave me alone.
-Shit.
-What do you want?
What are you waiting for?
Get out of here.
Get out. Just fuck off.
Go find some place else to sleep.
Get a fucking job.
You shut your face, you little shit.
Hey, why don't you
shut your face, witch?
Shut up, you little fucker.
I said get out of here.
My God, get the fuck out.
You spoiled piece of shit.
You fucking treat me like a lady or...
Shit.
What are you doing?
-Get out of here.
-No, don't. Come on.
You don't know what the fuck...
Let's find out.
Stop it. You get out of here.
-You leave me alone.
-Fuck you!
-My God.
-Don't. Leave me alone.
Get out of here.
Get out...
-My God.
-You get out.
-Wait, wait, wait. I got an idea.
-Like what?
-Leave me. You go and leave me alone.
-Holy shit.
Just leave me.
-Garbage to garbage.
-You fucking shit.
No. Shit!
Dude, come on. Move, let's go.
We're outta here.
-Look.
-Fuck.
You threw it all in her face.
Filthy piece of shit.
-You looked, didn't you?
-I did. I know. I saw.
This is getting weird
talking about this right now.
Weird?
That's... That's
a weird choice of word.
It was just supposed to be a joke.
You threw a burning match
at her as a joke?
She shouldn't have been there.
I mean...
The whole place stunk, Dad.
She yelled at us.
She cursed us.
I mean, she threatened us, Dad.
We just needed the money
to get home, that's all. Okay?
But she was like a fucking animal.
She was like a raccoon
or something.
And we just couldn't get her out.
That's all. We couldn't do it.
I mean, you would've done
the same exact thing.
My God. Really?
What did she do?
I...
She's got to go. Get home and...
Okay, look, I get it.
-Okay?
-Okay.
-Can we talk about it later?
-There's no need.
As long as nothing happens,
nothing happens.
-Are you being serious?
-Hey, Michael Lohman,
you've known me 16 years,
am I serious? Come on.
I can't tell.
Time is what we need.
Time is on our side.
Time is our friend.
You know?
That's how news cycle works.
It's old news already.
It's...
You know, you got lucky.
We got lucky.
You know I remember
when I was a teacher,
time was, it was not...
It was not like this.
-Okay.
-Time was... It was different.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Okay. Okay.
You're gonna spin out, okay?
You just need to stop talking.
Okay.
-Okay?
-Okay.
All I am saying is,
we'll get through this.
-Yup.
-We always do.
-You and me, right?
-Yeah.
You and that basketball,
you know.
-Yeah.
-I got this under control.
Yeah, I always do.
I always do.
You remember
when you threw that ball, and I...
But I went in there, I said,
-"The rap," so I took the rap.
-Dad, seriously, shut up.
That's what...
That's what fathers do.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I didn't throw that ball.
I got this.
I'll pay for the damages.
He did it on purpose.
Just give him his ball back.
It was an accident.
What do you think I am?
A kid can't throw that strong.
Why would I want
to break your window?
How the fuck would I know?
Dude. You mind?
Just tell me the truth.
I came here to pay
for your lame-ass window,
not to hear you talk.
You have no idea what we're going
through right now, okay?
He's sorry. He said as much.
That ball is like
his best friend.
Shit happens.
Things gets broken.
I asked you to name your price.
-Be civilized.
-I'm being more than civilized.
I'm being fucking magnanimous.
-You fucking kidding me?
-Goddamn it!
-How much for the goddamn window?
-It is not about the money.
I have money.
I could buy this store if I wanted to.
Burn it to the ground.
Save a few lives.
I remember you.
Your wife, she used
to come here all the time,
to buy cigarettes.
Well, she won't any longer,
because you killed her.
I don't want to be with sick people.
No, listen.
Good morning, Claire.
Good morning, doctor.
You're looking pretty today.
Are you expecting guests?
Any minute.
-Is she going to die?
-What? No, no, I'm just saying...
Okay.
You seem like an old man.
Look at you.
Let's go home.
All right, let's just,
let's just go once around
and get outta here.
I like doing this.
Let's go around again.
See how fast we can go.
Okay, give me the phone.
You got to get rid of that footage.
Deleting it won't be enough.
-Dad, stop it.
-You just gotta break the card out.
-Come on.
-Maybe she just... Give me the phone.
-No. I...
-This is not a game, Michael!
-Hey, you mind?
-You got to give me that goddamn phone.
-Hey, Mike.
-I'll be right there.
She smokes?
You told me she didn't smoke.
You know how your mom and I
feel about smoke.
You fucking scared her, okay?
God. You're being
such a fucking weirdo.
-She's an adult, you know.
-Just keep your voice down.
Does she know about this?
-What? About Mom's cancer?
-No, about the ATM.
No, of course, she doesn't know
about that, come on.
Why the hell did you and Rick have to
post that goddamn stuff online?
-Do you think it was funny?
-It wasn't us, okay?
-Are you listening to me?
-Jesus Christ. Yes. I am.
I am listening.
You're the one
who is not fucking listening.
I listened to you.
I listened to you too much.
Where are you going?
What are you doing?
-Who posted it online?
-Stop it.
Who posted it if it wasn't you?
You can't walk away from this.
That video will haunt you
-for the rest of your life.
-Dad, for the last time,
shut the fuck up, okay?
God!
Anna is gonna take me home
and then I've got some stuff to do.
But you stay the fuck
out of my business, okay?
You're a big talker.
Goddamn it.
You're such a fucking child.
-Okay, I'll just shut up.
-Yeah.
I'll just shut up.
I'll keep quiet.
When are you gonna act normal?
-For once.
-Boy.
-I do my best.
-Yeah?
Well, your best
is pretty fucking lame.
Sweetheart,
what are you doing here?
I thought you had a meeting.
Dad stole my phone.
-No, I didn't.
-And he watched it.
There was a mixup.
I thought it was mine.
How much do you know?
Paul, maybe you should go inside.
You've been out here a long time
and they're wondering if you left.
I'm not hungry and don't talk to me
like I'm a retard.
Mike, come on, this is crazy.
I'm outta here.
Go.
I thought you were on my side.
You have to know
that first and foremost,
I was thinking about you
and your well-being.
I was afraid you wouldn't
be able to handle this.
Since... Since when?
-How long have you known about this?
-Honey.
You know, Michael said he and Rick
didn't put that hideous video online.
-They didn't.
-Who did?
-Honey, it really doesn't...
-Who? Stop calling me honey.
-You know, you better tell me...
-Beau!
Beau did it.
He found it on Rick's computer,
the footage that they shot...
Where's Michael going?
He's not...
He's gonna go pay Beau the money
that he wants to keep quiet.
-Are you fucking kidding me?
-Calm down. He'll keep quiet.
-What are you...
-It's under control. He's just, he's angry.
He's angry at Michael
for calling him a wuss.
Where's the money coming from?
It's coming from our account.
What do you think?
It's only a few thousand.
-A few?
-No, then, everything's gonna be fine.
How long have you known
that it's Rick and Michael?
-Honey.
-Since when exactly. You tell me.
Michael called me
after it happened.
They needed a ride home.
Jesus, you liar!
-Just stop it.
-You thief.
Calm down.
Do they know about
Beau and tonight?
No, no, I have it under control.
Do you? You keep saying that
which means you don't.
What, what are you,
are you in charge?
What's my role in this family?
Who am I? Who...
The village idiot?
This whole time, it's...
I've been the odd man out.
It's been you and Michael.
And I'm just, you know,
I'm just, it's, it's, I'm alone.
-No.
-I'm alone.
You are his father.
No, I'm... I'm the lunatic.
It's... It's Gettysburg.
You're going back to Gettysburg.
No, its not.
It's not Gettysburg.
Okay?
Let's go in.
It's cold.
That wars are won or lost
on the basis of irrational
considerations.
Like Hitler and Stalingrad.
Remember that?
As it happened,
for General Lee
and the Confederate Army,
Gettysburg was the beginning
of the end.
May I please
have your fucking attention?
There you are.
Good.
Well, now that
I have your attention,
I'd like you to think
about something
when you go home
to your miserable lives tonight.
I want you to think about this.
How many people
do you think there would be
in this country
without wars?
I'm not saying
that the Civil War
wasn't fought
for legitimate reasons
but, if everyone had been
able to go on fucking
instead of going to war, any war,
anywhere in the world,
how many people would that leave
on our dying planet?
Do the arithmetic for me,
for the next time we meet.
I'm gonna go outside
and get a breath of fresh air.
Do whatever you want.
Just,
clean up after yourselves,
you sad, pathetic, doomed shitheads.
Sit down, Klein.
Thank you.
Okay, let's do some math.
In a group of, say,
a hundred people,
how many assholes
do you think there are?
In an average group, say.
I'm serious,
how many parents
who humiliate
or deny their children?
How many morons
with stinking breath
who refuse to do anything about it?
How many...
How many constant whiners,
complainers,
rapists, embezzlers,
liars, thieves,
dirty politicians, cheaters?
It could be your mother,
could be your brother.
Could be your mother,
You, for example.
How many of you
would be happy
if some of your friends
were gone tomorrow?
You, for example,
how many of you would be happy
not to see some of
your classmates tomorrow?
Gone. Dead. Buried.
Their desks empty.
Show of hands.
Come on, you don't
have to name names.
Show of hands.
Klein.
Exactly.
Now a little closer to home.
Members of your family.
The uncle with shitty stories.
The, the molester.
Boy, you know about those.
The, the ugly cousin
who mistreats her dogs.
The verbally abusive mother.
Now think how happy
you and your loved ones would be
if that uncle or adopted cousin
were to step on a land mine
or get hit by a military strike.
Just like that.
Wiped off the face of the earth.
Yeah, that's good.
Just like that.
Wiped out.
You'd be happy, right?
You'd, you'd be pleased.
You'd support the idea of war.
Because families are oppressive
and unloving and cruel.
Okay now, stay with me.
Now imagine...
Because families are oppressive
and unloving and cruel.
Okay, stay with me.
Now think of all the victims
of all the wars
that have ever been in the past
and,
and now think of the tens
of thousands of assholes,
hundreds of thousands,
maybe more, millions,
that we need around
like a hole in the head.
Now from a purely
statistical standpoint,
it's mathematically impossible
that all the victims of wars were
good people, whatever that means.
The true injustice of history
is that the assholes
appear on the lists
of innocent victims.
Their names are carved
into the memorials
with the noble and the virtuous
and the good.
Nausea, constipation,
somnolence, dry mouth,
dizziness, sweating,
nervousness,
fast heartbeat, hypertension.
Sexual dysfunction.
B-But she said, she said
that she wasn't expecting
any of these problems at this dosage,
remember?
Is that all?
Impaired coordination,
memory impairment,
short-term memory loss,
which I guess, memory slips, right?
Or something,
What... I don't think we should
need to look at this anymore.
What about personality changes?
That's not a side effect.
That's the effect.
Is that good?
I guess we're here.
Glad we're doing this.
I wouldn't have suggested it
if I didn't want to do it, Paul.
I thought the shrink suggested it.
-Shit.
-Take it.
No, its okay.
I'm gonna turn it off.
There's no shame
in getting help, Paul.
There's help in getting shame?
-Am I causing you shame?
-You're shaming my cause.
Are you just gonna flip
every sentence I say. Is that it?
I'm just gonna say
every sentence you flip.
Jesus.
Susej.
You're good. You're good.
You're good.
You're a knucklehead, but you're good.
Pennsylvania Avenue
at the Walnut Street Bridge
in downtown Gettysburg.
The event is open to the public.
It will be held rain or shine.
Preservation Pennsylvania
will be back on Sunday...
Come on.
Have you seen these?
You sure you want to go in?
Yeah.
You are on hallowed ground.
The exact place where events changed
the course of American history.
Though it is the bloodiest place
in America'
there is a deep peace to be found
here at Gettysburg.
If you let it,
this land will speak to you.
Now, let's go.
Please pay attention for this sound.
Well, I wish I was in
the land of cotton...
As the sun rises
behind the clouds of July 1st,
wisps of mist partially obscure
the figures of Confederate soldiers
as they make their way
across Marsh Creek.
At 7:30 a.m., Union Lieutenant
Marcellus Jones of Illinois
borrows a soldier's carbine rifle
and says,
"Let me have the honor
of opening the ball."
He rests the rifle
across a fence rail,
a column of rebel infantry
crosses Marsh Creek.
He fires...
the first shot
of the greatest battle ever fought
in the Western Hemisphere.
Gettysburg begins.
From mid-morning
until mid-afternoon on July 1st,
these woods would see some of
the most intense fighting of the battle.
For both armies, it is now
a race to the battlefield.
Rebel reinforcements arrive
along the Harrisburg Road
and smash the Union right flank
at Barlow's Knoll.
In less than 20 minutes' these
Yankees are retreating in disorder.
And soon, the entire Federal position
is forced to retreat.
In about a mile,
you will pass the site
of General Lee's headquarters.
As the Union forces retreat
through the fields of Gettysburg,
towns and streets turn into a chaotic
and vicious, bloody battlefield.
From Seminary Ridge
located to our west,
The Black Hats Brigade
explodes from the woods
with the general riding 50 yards
in front of his 1,400 men.
The Mississippi was crashing
through the right side...
The Union flank explodes
like ripe fruit.
There is little protection
of this exposed flank.
Men take cover
as best as they can.
Please pause the audio
until you reach
"stop gate" further left.
From the heights
of Little Round Top and...
Paul!
Come on, let's keep going.
From the heights
of Little Round Top
and Cemetery Hill,
units fire
into the sides of the Rebel lines,
tearing through scores of men.
No, the Union troops surge back
pushing against the Rebels'
dwindling their numbers
as they fall.
New reinforcements
swarm over the ridge.
The few men who break the Union line
are killed, wounded or captured.
It is known as the high-water mark
of the Confederacy.
Never again will Confederacy come
so close to winning the Civil War
as they do here at this moment
on this day, July 3rd, 1803,
Gettysburg.
This is too much,
I don't know. Sorry.
Almost as many here
as the whole Vietnam war.
You realize that? 50,000?
What are you talking about?
Millions of people died in Vietnam.
I'm talking about Americans.
You know what I'm talking about.
Give me a break.
I don't see you crying.
People express emotions
in different ways, Paul.
You know that.
Doesn't mean I don't have any.
You're saying I'm weak?
I'm not saying you're weak.
I'm saying...
I'm saying that you are who you are
and I accept that.
I accept you.
I always accept you.
We're different people,
so what? Big deal.
I will always accept you.
Come on.
What are you trying to say?
What are you saying?
We have had a history of mental illness
in this family for generations
so maybe it's...
it's time for us to actually
do something about it.
We need to deal with it.
-What are you saying?
-I'm saying Mom was a wacko.
That's what I'm saying.!
And Dad, where was he?
The guy checked out. It was...
We had each other.
It was you and me.
You remember?
And I always looked out for you.
-I still don't see you crying.
-Come on.
You always thought
that I had it easier than you,
that I had the run of the house,
Mom liked me better. All of that.
This is all bullshit.
Someone had to be the adult in the
house and it wasn't going to be Mom.
I didn't ask for the job, okay?
Yeah, I can see
you're all broken up about it.
Come on. Paul, stay here.
I wanna talk.
We're talking. Please.
Fuck you.
Don't be a baby.
Fuck you!
Ay-yi-yi-yi.
It doesn't matter what we teach,
we learn nothing.
I've done nothing with my life.
He destroyed me.
Bullshit.
He took time off to be with you.
Paul, he's a busy man.
He cares about you.
Yeah, well,
only one side wins in a war.
No' no' no.
Listen, come on, Paul.
He's your brother.
You got to tell me
what's going on.
I'm okay.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
I'm just...
I've been thinking
I'm not gonna write the book.
There's, you know, we know
too much about the Civil War.
It's time to un-know it.
Did you take your pills?
Yes.
Okay' thank you.
Did you have dinner last night?
I wasn't hungry.
Stan ordered something to his room.
Paul, you ready?
How's Mike?
' he's good. He's good.
Do you want to talk to him?
-Paul.
-I'll get Michael. Feel better.
Okay? So hang on
one second. I'll get him.
No, no. No, no.
Paul?
Come on. I know you're there.
Hey, Paul?
-Let's go.
-Hey, Paul?
Paul, are you there?
-Come on. Come on.
-Hey, Paul?
Let's go' Paul.
We gotta go now. Come on.
Paul, please pick up the phone.
Paul?
-Open the door. Now!
-All right.
All right, I'm coming, I'm coming.
-Hey.
-God.
-I'm sorry.
-What did you do?
-What... Do you have a key?
-I'm gonna go get some ice.
-What did you do?
-Punched the mirror.
Paul. Paul.
Please stop me if you've
heard this one before
but I am a cheese fanatic.
Seriously, I can talk
about this for hours.
Literally, I could tell you
the names of the cows.
You seem like very nice people
so I don't want to bombard you.
Unless you ask me to.
So, very quickly starting by region,
from Vermont, this
is a Harbison cheese.
This is a very gooey cheese.
If you cut it in half,
it will spill out.
So you need to make
an incision on the top rind
and eat it with a spoon
or with a fork.
Also from Vermont,
we have the Bayley Hazen Blue cheese.
It's a very flavorful blue cheese.
Personal favorite of mine.
From New York state,
the Hudson Flower.
The Hudson Flower
is a riff, if you will,
on the Corsican classic,
Fleur du Maquis.
Hudson Flower.
In the middle, the centerpiece is,
the Mimolette from France.
The infamous Mimolette,
the controversial Mimolette.
You may have heard of this cheese.
The FDA tried to ban it.
We have it here for you today.
Mimolette.
And finally, this is a tricky one.
It's a German name
but it comes from Italy.
So, insert joke about fascism here.
Weinkase Lagrein.
Weinkase translates literally
into "wine cheese"
and Lagrein is the red gr...
The red wine grape variety
that is found in the valleys
of Northern Italy.
So there you go.
Any questions.
Don't move.
Let's just stay put from now on.
Nobody leaves the table.
Not even to go to the bathroom?
-Yes, Paul.
-What is this? EST? Scientology?
You know what I mean.
We really need to talk
and th-there's no reason why
we can't talk about anything here
discreetly, pointedly.
-I think that window has closed.
-No, Paul.
-Paul, let him.
-I don't want to talk.
Please, dear.
We're gonna put the truth
right here in front of us,
and we're gonna do
something about it. Okay?
And, Paul, if you could
just get out of your head for a minute.
Me? What about you, Scarf ace?
-Please don't go there.
-You should have closed that door.
-Enough of that.
-Wait, wait.
What happened to "we should
be able to talk about anything"?
I don't think we need
to turn this into...
-Unbelievable I thought...
-No, no, no...
You're just trying to protect yourself.
I have been...
Forgiving you is all I've been doing.
Keep your voices down
and, Stan, come on.
You think that forgiveness
is the same as absolution.
You should have closed
that door, you ape.
Stan, just go on. Go on.
Stan wants to talk about the truth.
It's not about the truth,
it's about the boys.
Let Stan say what he has to say.
We don't have to agree with him,
-but we can have a civil discussion.
-I want to...
-Please, just give him a chance.
-Give him a chance.
Okay, I want to know what
the truth is to a politician.
I want to know what the truth
is to a child
-who made his parents ignore his brother.
-Don't do it.
You don't know half of it, Kate.
You're late to this party.
Okay, Paul, stop. Enough.
You're being incredibly
disrespectful to everyone.
-Now you're turning against me?
-I think everyone should just calm down.
Claire, is that...
Now, of all the rotten times, is...
You've always been against me?
Why don't you just say what is inside
that small head of yours?
-What is this Parity bill?
-I don't know what you're talking about.
This bill you've been working on.
What is it?
What does it have to do
with anything, this bill?
-Tell me.
-Last year you told me it was boring.
-No. No, no.
-You felt it was boring.
Last year I told you,
you were boring.
You want me to tell you about it?
Are you really interested in it?
You want to know?
-Sure.
-Jesus fucking Christ.
The Mental Health Parity Act,
MHPAA.
It's about closing loopholes
in the Affordable Care Act.
It requires that medical insurers
offer mental health options,
insuring that mental health
treatment is reimbursed
at levels exactly the same
as physical.
Ultimately, all this is about
is destigmatizing mental illness.
So, it's about... it's about me.
What is it about you?
-What does it have to do with you?
-Come on, Paul, really.
"Fuck you, Paul" bill.
"Fuck you, Paul" as federal law.
Look, this is about getting
real treatment for people who need it.
This was... It was Kate's issue,
long before me.
Every, every family, has someone
who suffers from mental illness.
"Every family has someone
who suffers from mental illness."
-Yes, exactly.
-"It's time to break the silence"...
I've heard these speeches before, Kate.
You know, it's...
Do you enjoy doing this to me
every single time
when you expose me?
Is that your intention?
I'm not gonna sit here
and take this from you, Paul.
-You're acting like a child.
-You're just like him.
-Barbara cared about me.
-And I would appreciate it if you...
-Barbara tried to make amends.
-Acted like an adult
-and showed some class.
-You don't have to defend or protect
your husband every time
I say something.
-It's true.
-I am trying to protect you, dear.
So shut the fuck up and don't you
dare talk to me like that.
I don't know why you think
that attacking me
is going to stall this conversation
because it's not.
Want to turn me into your hall monitor
for tonight? Fine.
Pipe down and listen...
you ape.
Wow.
Sorry, Congressman,
I need you for a minute.
-It's really urgent.
-Are you sure?
Five minutes. No more.
Five minutes.
Nobody else moves, okay?
What the fuck?
Makes no fucking sense.
-' no' no.
-No, no, no...
Let's go. Come on, Rick.
Let's go.
-Hey.
-Porn in the kitchen?
Just listening to music.
-How are you?
-Good. Great. Fine.
That's three different answers.
Pick one. Any one.
You would not believe the day I've had.
Would you come
back to the table?
I think we should leave.
No.
Everything's fine.
-Everything's going to be okay.
-Hey, hey.
-Just don't overreact. Okay?
-How is it fine?
We can't talk about the truth.
The truth is their son's gonna rat out
our son and his own brother.
He's getting his money.
He's gonna get his money tonight.
I've taken care of everything.
Now, please do not overreact.
It's my job to take care of things.
-My job. I'm the father.
-I'm sorry.
-It's my job to take care.
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You know, a house
divided against itself
-cannot stand.
-Do not quote at me right now.
Do not quote at me right now.
Don't. Take a deep breath.
-What the fuck were those
fucking kids thinking?
I don't know. I wish I knew.
But that doesn't matter now.
They are good kids
and they took a wrong turn.
And we're gonna get them
back on track
and they're gonna move on
with their lives.
Can we go home now?
We need to hear them out.
Your brother,
he can be very practical.
He's a deal-maker.
Okay? So, don't antagonize him.
And lay off Kate.
Because we need them both.
I don't want you to get sick again.
But I'm... I'm perfectly fine.
Don't leave me ever again.
-Please don't die.
-Stop talking like that.
-Stop. Stop talking like I'm not here.
-I...
-I'm right here.
-Should've closed that door.
I-I-I asked him, very calmly,
-I told him to close the door.
-I know. I know. I know.
-And Michael was just standing there.
-I know. I know.
I know.
Boy.
Shit.
Hey.
-Hey, brother.
-Hey.
What are you doing here?
We just went by to see Claire
and wish her luck tomorrow.
-Right. Thank you.
-You're gonna invite us in?
-How are you doing, Paul?
-You should really have called first.
I'm sorry. We didn't think
that it was necessary.
-Yeah.
-All right just to come over?
How're you doing?
Yeah, I was about to call
Mike for his lunch.
I try to make every meal
a celebration.
-Take his mind off things.
-Yeah.
Mikey, we have guests!
Is he okay?
-How's he doing?
-He's doing okay. I'll go find him.
Mikey!
Mikey, your uncle is here.
And his aunt.
And your aunt.
-Hey, bud.
-There he is.
-Hey, kiddo.
-Hey, beautiful boy.
Look at you. Look at you. Man.
We just came by to say hello.
Still in your PJs?
Daddy gave me
ice cream before lunch.
-He did?
-Did he?
Yeah.
Sometimes ice cream makes
everything better, a lot better.
Come by tomorrow,
you can eat it off the floor.
-What's going on?
-Michael,
why don't you go upstairs
for a minute...
Exactly. More important things
to think about than...
We just want to talk to your dad
for a second. Okay, babe?
Hey, but just a minute, okay, partner?
I just... We really should eat
and then we were gonna start
cleaning your room like you said.
-Okay. See you in a little bit.
-I'll see you in a minute.
Okay? All righty?
Okay. Listen here, Paul.
We've been thinking.
We have an idea.
Well, I can't take credit for it,
but I fully endorse it.
-We would like...
-Paul, we know hard it's been for you.
-With Claire in the hospital...
Will you let me talk, please?
Will you just let me talk?
-Go ahead.
-Thank you. You're an angel.
Barbara and I think
it might be best for Michael
if he comes to stay with us
for a while.
Paul, let's get a maid in here,
and get you back on your feet.
Michael needs to start
going back to school.
And you need to start
visiting Claire again.
We understand
what you're going through.
I mean, look, we're just here to help.
-Okay?
-Maybe... yeah.
It could give you a little space,
you could relax, take care of yourself.
You know, I think it makes perfect sense.
We've got that extra room.
I think, really, Paul, I think
it would be the best thing for us.
For Michael.
It might be a break for Michael.
He puts on a brave face,
but children need a stable home.
Hey, listen.
Listen, Paul.
My son and I were about
to sit down to eat.
There's not enough food
to ask you to stay, but...
-We had lunch already.
-We didn't come here to eat.
Listen, we just thought
with the operation tomorrow and all,
it would be best for Michael to come
and stay with us for a while.
-Work with us. Come on.
-I think you should leave.
We can't leave you here like this.
Come on, man.
This is... This is insane.
-Look at the place. Look around.
-Stan. Stan.
-Look at this place.
-Stan, calm...
Come on!
-Take it easy.
-Wake up. Look at me.
Be quiet!
Look at me. Come on.
Come on. For Michael.
And for Claire.
Please, Paul.
I'll help you. I'll help you.
We'll all help you.
We'll help you clean up the place.
Seriously, Paul.
I'm sure even you realize
this is not a good situation for a kid.
He should be talking to someone,
dealing with his feelings,
-and so should you.
-Excuse me?
Stan is only trying to say that this
can all be a bit too much for you, Paul.
-Yes.
-We know you're trying
to keep things as normal
as possible for Mike,
but this is anything but normal.
I really think you should leave.
His mother is ill.
He needs strength.
He shouldn't feel that his father
can't deal with life anymore.
-You need to find your center.
-Yes.
Do you know anything
about meditation?
Okay, okay, all right.
Claire and I agreed to keep things
as normal as possible for Michael.
-We agreed.
-Yes.
Well, you should be with her
right now, okay?
Yes. Claire's alone
in a hospital bed right now.
She needs you there.
Paul, Paul, listen to me.
Stop it, stop it, stop it,
stop it. Look.
This is the thing.
We already spoke to Claire.
She agreed. It's all good.
Whose idea was it?
-It really doesn't matter.
-It does.
-It comes from a place of love...
-It does, it does matter.
-It does matter. It does.
-No. Why?
Because if it was your idea
then it's just the usual pathology.
You know, he took my mom
and dad from me
and now my son
for his collection.
Don't tell me that I got the larger part
of the inheritance as proof of something.
-Like I got that house and you didn't.
-You know, Paul, at some point,
you're gonna have to stop blaming
other people for who you are.
If it Claire's idea then, well,
that's between Claire and me.
But I will not let you steal my son.
-Steal?
-Paul. I'm not, we're not stealing...
-Stop saying my name.
-You've said it 11 times.
Paul. That's your name.
What am I supposed to call you?
Since Michael...
Whatever, I'm tired of counting.
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
-How about we just...
-Look at this. Look what you've done?
-We can take him for two...
-Look at it!
Don't worry about the food. Okay?
We can get him something else.
Close the door, Stan.
-Paul.
-Michael, go back upstairs.
Close the door, Stan.
-Go back upstairs.
-Michael, go back upstairs.
Close the fucking door!
Here we have our dessert course.
Our melting chocolate egg
with parsnip cake and grapefruit
on Brazil nuts,
edible flowers and mint,
topped with a salted whiskey
caramel sauce.
And of course, our Bananas Foster
with a cocoa...
I don't want anything.
Thank you.
-But you must have it. It's beyond...
-I must?
No, I don't want it.
I've had enough. Thank you.
You've never tasted anything like it,
I assure you.
I said I don't want it.
Can you take it away now?
-Kate?
-This is not up for debate.
-I'll take it.
-Thank you.
-All right.
-All right. Where were we?
How is everything?
Having a great time.
Yeah, absolutely.
I hear there was a problem
with the dessert. I'm horrified.
-I'm sure it's fine.
-No, everything's fine.
-Dessert is on us.
-You don't have to do that.
No, no, I insist.
Anyway, the night...
You know, the cork, the pin,
the dessert.
The horror.
It's all good.
Really, it's all good.
What else can I get for you?
You can fucking get lost already.
Of course, we can leave you alone.
You know,
I hope you understand that...
my tolerance from your rudeness,
it come from the respect
I got for your brother,
not from any tendency to back away
from throwing a man like you out.
Believe me, he understands.
I understand but I don't
necessarily respect you for it.
I'm sorry.
He's so obsequiously effete
and sycophantic.
Come on, let's go.
What kind of a name is Antonio?
He's probably not even French.
-Follow me, please.
-He's probably from Cincinnati.
Nina, could we have
some privacy, please?
Thank you.
Why don't we sit over here?
Katelyn, sit over there, please.
You two on the other side.
Could you that for me, please?
Thank you.
-Dirty rotten shithole...
-Wanna do this?
Yeah.
Hey, come on,
let's fucking do this. Let's do it.
Are we gonna fucking do this?
-You get in.
-Get in.
Here, bitch.
Shit.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
-Shit.
-Get something big.
I got her right
in the fucking head, dude.
Excuse me, could you please
kindly open the door?
Holy fuck.
You got, you got it.
-Look what I found.
-There you go.
-Go, go, go.
-Get the fuck out.
Don't scream all night, lady.
Fucking stink-o.
-Hey, get out of here.
-Hey, come on, let's get out of here.
We give you get two minutes
to get the fuck out.
Get out of here.
Let's go.
Shit. Shit.
-Bullshit political spin on the wrong audience.
-Paul, Paul, Paul.
I need you to be quiet now.
Thank you.
All right, I'm gonna try to explain.
I spoke to Rick. He's a mess.
We had a call from his school.
He spent the entire morning
in the nurse's... crying.
He's not eating,
he's not sleeping.
-He's not functional...
-I want to be clear,
we've not had a chance
to discuss this between us.
Please, honey.
Well, that's right, that's right.
I'm speaking for myself, okay?
Just speaking for myself.
Now...
I've been trying to see this separately
from my own political future,
not that that's even possible.
The most important thing for me
is my son, my son's future.
I think it's possible
that they won't be found out.
Maybe...
this case will never be solved.
But is that really what...
What we want?
For the kids?
For us?
I don't think so.
I don't see it. I don't...
I don't see myself
living my life thinking that...
that my son was involved in a murder.
Wait, wait, wait a minute.
Where did you pick up a word like that?
-You don't mean that. He didn't mean murder.
-No, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
That's going too far, that word.
-She died with third-degree burns.
-No, no, no. You...
You're blowing things
way out of proportions, Stan.
-I mean, this was an accident.
-It was, it was.
It was an unfortunate
series of events.
Absolutely.
-That poor woman was savaged.
-Poor woman? Come on, Stan.
What was that "poor woman" doing
camping out there
in the first place.
I mean, there are many places
for deranged people like that to go.
-I mean, there are shelters.
-Homeless people...
Shelters that we pay for
with our own tax dollars.
-You know, hospital, prison...
-That's not the point. Please.
That's not the point.
She was in their way, Stan.
She was dangerous
and she was threatening them.
Michael said things
just got out of hand.
Just imagine
how scared they were.
They were shaking
when I picked them up.
These are good boys.
Not that night, they weren't.
You weren't there
and I choose to believe my son.
All right, all right.
Let's not argue anymore. This...
We have to stick to the point
and when we...
Okay, this is the point, sweetheart.
Imagine this,
you open your door,
and you have to step over
a violent, disgusting bum.
Someone who's totally out of control.
What do you do?
-Claire, please.
-What do you do?
-Do you turn around and go back?
-Claire, it's a human being.
-You pack up when you're spooked?
-It's a human being.
I'm not talking about the homeless.
I am talking about one bad person.
One problem. They were just
trying to get her to leave.
I mean, it was an accident.
We have to protect the boys now,
for what's done is done.
Of course it was an accident.
That is not in dispute.
It was an accident. But the end
result is the end result, so...
-We have to work out what to do next.
-Yes, yes. Exactly. Thank you.
This is Rick and Michael's future
we're talking about.
That's exactly what I wanted
to talk about. The future.
I don't think our boys can live
with this poison inside them.
It's gonna rip them apart.
It's already happening with Rick.
I...
I spoke to Kate earlier, briefly,
this afternoon.
-There are other ways...
-She doesn't agree with me...
-to deal with this, Stan. We don't have to...
-But I've made up my mind.
-There are other ways that will help...
-For my son, for his future...
-that don't involve you...
-the only way I can see surviving...
-throwing away your entire...
-any of this...
political career and everything
you've ever worked for.
For him to be able to go on
with his life.
Doesn't make any sense.
-I don't know where... I can't find...
-May I? May I?
Sure. Go ahead, go ahead.
You're on your own.
Good luck with your speech.
See you backstage.
I'm going to withdraw my candidacy.
For the good of my son, my family,
Michael, you, all of us.
My bill will pass tomorrow
or it won't. Either way...
After that,
we're dealing with this.
-You can't do that.
-Of course he can't.
You see? It's insane. It's...
After all that we've gone through.
No, no, that's not what I mean.
You can't make this
decision alone, Stan.
I mean, we all have a stake in this.
Yes. So that's why I wanted to meet.
That's why I wanted to talk about this.
Figure out how we're
gonna actually do it.
-Do what?
-Go public.
As a family,
to save our children.
Don't be a fool, Stan.
You make a decision like this,
you also decide the future of my son.
You have no right.
I won't let you.
-He is my son.
-Ours.
And don't play
the noble politician.
I hate to break it to you
but it's not very noble.
It's not very modern,
and it's not very you.
You'll get elected.
You're ahead in polls.
No, I don't...
How do you explain to your only son
that you're willing to have
their prospects ruined.
Their prospects are ruined anyhow,
and not by me.
Be realistic.
They got away with it.
It's awful.
It's unthinkable,
it's... it's terrible.
But we have a responsibility as parents
to help them cope.
You don't want to live with this, fine.
Fine. Drop out.
But don't expose them.
-Well, you can't drop out.
-It's not your decision.
No, fuck, yeah, it is.
Fuck, yeah.
You feel bad?
Well, then do something about it.
Make homelessness
your number one priority.
Give a donation
in this woman's name.
You can make it right.
Her name?
They don't even know her name!
She has no name!
No amount of money
is going to fix this...
-in any way.
-What, so you're gonna fix it?
You're gonna fix it by putting
our boys behind bars?
Do you have any idea what they do to
a beautiful child like that in prison?
-Do you?
-They're minors. They're minors.
No, they'll be tried as adults.
-They are two white boys.
-Don't pretend that you don't know the law.
They're gonna have a field day.
Another case of affluenza, right,
of rich, privileged kids.
Maybe they should make
an example of them.
Are you fucking...
That is a child you're talking about.
Maybe they deserve
whatever comes now.
-Are you out of your fucking mind?
-You think I want this?
They...
They will serve their sentences.
They will pick up the pieces,
and we will be with them
every step of the way.
We will get them the best lawyers.
Thank God, we can do that.
We will love them,
we will care for them,
we'll care about them.
Believe me, I have looked at this
from every possible angle.
-There's no other choice.
-Yes, there is.
You do nothing.
Yeah, I hate to tell you I don't think
this is a police priority.
And people will forget about it.
It will just blow over.
Rick will not forget.
He will come around.
I won't forget.
It's not about you.
The system will fail them.
We won't.
We can help them.
We can really help them
find the right kind of care,
the right kind of counseling,
medication.
No. I know it won't help.
It's all about second chances.
-Won't be enough!
-Why don't you give your son
-a second chance?
-It won't be enough.
-It's exactly what's needed.
Believe me.
I'm going to set
a press conference in DC
first thing tomorrow morning
after the vote.
I'm announcing
I'm suspending my campaign
and Kate and I will sit down with Rick,
and we're gonna explain
everything to him.
And then together,
we're gonna drive to the police
and make a full confession.
We'll throw ourselves
on the mercy of the court.
These boys have committed
a horrific crime.
They'll have to pay for it.
It's the only way for them.
I suggest you do the same
with Michael.
I'm gonna pay for this, and we'll...
get out of here.
Are you just gonna sit there?
Say something.
Our son.
Not your son.
Holy fuck.
Is this really happening?
-Dude, this is so fucking intense!
-Why doesn't she just get up?
Holy shit.
Come on, come on, dude, let's go.
No, no, no, hold on.
We got to get something funny, come on.
We got to have something funny.
It's not cool, I mean,
dude, come on.
Here, look.
Come on, dude, let's go.
Let's go, come on.
We're out.
I need to call Michael.
-What time is it?
-A little after 10:00.
Poor kid.
He's been alone all night.
What do you think, Paul?
Me? What does it matter?
-Claire's in charge.
-Stop it.
No, seriously. You haven't said
anything for a while. I want to know.
I don't think there was anyone
innocent in this story.
Not even that woman.
Not even Beau.
Certainly not Barbara. Not even you.
What do you mean, "Beau"?
Beau wasn't there.
He doesn't know what he's saying.
-Hello.
-Hi, sweetheart.
How are you doing?
Not too bored, I hope.
Beau wouldn't take the money.
He says we need to pay for it.
-How much?
-Not money pay for it.
To society or some shit.
-Okay.
-He said I'm the real wuss.
I'm here with Dad, Stan and Kate,
and we're going to be
coming home soon.
So you have time to clean up.
-What did you have for dinner?
-He's gonna turn us in.
He's gonna turn us in, Mom.
He's gonna turn us in.
I know. I mean...
Okay, listen, don't worry.
It's just homework.
Everything always seems
more complicated than this.
So sit tight.
-God.
-I'm gonna send Dad home. He'll help.
-Fuck.
-I love you. I'll see you soon.
Okay, bye.
He's fine.
He's absolutely fine.
I don't know
what's taking him so long.
I'll go find out.
Listen, we need to finish this
conversation because it's not over.
-No, I know. I'm coming back.
-Not by a long shot and it's urgent.
I understand, Claire.
You're hurting my arm.
Beau changed his mind.
-What the fuck? You kidding me?
-He chickened out.
-He's gonna expose them.
-Jesus. That dirty, rotten...
Christ.
Where are Mr. and Mrs. Lohman?
We're right here for fuck's sake.
Of course you are.
But I mean, the other Lohmans.
-I want this to be our decision.
-Our decision?
Well, it's not our decision
because you've already made it.
Stan.
What do you think, Nina?
-Hey, don't bring her into this.
-Well, what do you mean?
She's right here.
She's always right here.
You brought her into it.
I think he's right.
There's no choice.
Really? How is this hitting you?
-I think...
-I told her what she needs to know. That's all.
I'm really, I'm trying
to keep my mind open.
Listen, listen, you never
listened to me the whole night.
I've listened to you.
I've listened to you
when you made me feel like shit
in there for not agreeing with you.
And now you're making me feel like shit
in here for not agreeing with you.
I'm done. I'm done fighting.
Yeah, sure you are.
Sure you are,
because either way you win.
Either way I'm fucked.
-What the fuck are you talking about?
-I have given your family everything, Stan.
Everything.
I've sobbed for days
when you weren't around
and Val was impossible.
I slept on the floor by Beau's bed
for nine months
when he had those nightmares.
I've nursed you every time
that you were down.
I did my best with Rick.
I'm not their mother.
And you weren't there to defend me
but I fucking tried.
Because I love those kids.
And I love you.
So I didn't care.
I didn't care every time
that you got a hard-on
for some adoring little slut
because I knew that you were shattered
when Barbara left you like that.
And I picked you up,
so either way, you would
always come back to me
and either way,
you needed me.
Well, either way...
Either way, Kate is great.
The eternal intern.
Sweet,
tolerant, tolerant Kate.
She won't mind,
she's fine.
Well, no. Not anymore, Stan.
Do you hear me?
Because if you walk away
from this fight,
I walk away from you.
Call the press conference
in the morning after...
Don't you fucking dare.
Stan, listen to me.
Rick won't be able to handle this.
He won't.
You don't know him like I do.
I'm sorry. But he won't.
You're making someone else's
tragedy ours.
It's our tragedy.
Either way, it's ours,
it's everybody's.
-Call the press conference.
-Okay, boss.
"Okay, boss." You do realize
that this is everyone's life.
-Stop, please. Just do your job.
-No, no, hey, hey, wait up.
What's in it for you exactly?
Because it's not your job
because you will lose that. Understand?
You know, there's a lot of things
you don't know about me.
Lot of things you never
even bothered to ask.
You're right. I'm sorry. I'm selfish.
Right? I'm the trophy wife.
I'm the gold-digger
and everything else that you've
ever said about me behind my back.
Did you ever bother to think that I'm
a human being that has feelings?
No, probably not. But I don't care
because I don't need your pity.
And I don't need your support.
Stop it, honey.
Stop, both of you. Just stop.
I don't think you have
any other move left, Stan.
No. Of course he does.
Stan, listen to me.
You will do more good as a governor
than you ever will
as a father or a husband.
You're nothing without politics.
And that's not all
you're nothing about.
You need me
more than I need you.
And those kids
need a parent.
And that's a stone-cold fact.
No. No. We're talking about
something here that is so extreme
and so awful.
What we're talking about
is you're dead to the woman
who is raising your children
for you.
It's the right thing to do, Kate.
You know it is.
You know, sometimes,
sometimes the healing thing to do
is to leave the wound alone.
Come on.
Give it a week.
We'll talk about it. You and me.
Look, not here. Not like this.
We'll go home.
We'll go to the beach house.
We'll talk and we will discuss things
and we'll make a decision, together.
As we've always done.
Together.
What will he become
if he gets away with this?
He'll just be our son.
Honey, I can't wait a week.
Can't do it.
Okay, well, give it a few days.
Five? Give me five days.
Come on.
I'll give you three days.
Give you three days.
-Okay, three days.
-Three days.
-Yeah.
Thank you.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
I told you I didn't want
to bring you into this.
I know how upsetting it is
but we can't go back.
He doesn't listen to reason.
She has no power over him.
So we have to take matters
into our own hands.
I'll take care of Stan.
I can take care of him.
Okay?
You have to take care of Beau.
Can you do that?
You know what...
I don't feel so good.
I haven't, taken my medication.
I mean, not for a long time.
Not for months.
I wanted to feel myself again.
I know.
When I do the laundry,
I find the pills you hide
and forget to throw away.
That's why your
pants' pockets are pink.
Why didn't you say anything?
Because I wanted my Paul back.
Because you were numb
for a really long time.
Because I was very lonely.
Listen.
I know that I let you down.
I know that Michael doesn't think
I'm much of anything.
That you're close.
That you...
It's just you two.
That you keep things from me.
-But I can still do things.
-Yes, I know. Good.
And you could prove it.
So I need you.
I need you to be strong.
-I need you to be focused.
-Yeah.
I need you to go take care of Beau.
Okay. Take care how?
Talk to him.
Okay, check's paid.
It's gonna be all right.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
-Let's blow this Popsicle stand.
-I'm going.
Where are you...
Where are you going?
You don't know?
Sometimes you just have
to let Paul go be Paul.
But, listen, I want to talk
about this press conference.
There won't be one.
For now.
For now. For now, no.
What do you mean?
As far as everyone's concerned,
you all just had a nice, long dinner.
Let's all go home?
You need a ride.
We can call you a car.
What do you mean,
"for now"?
-Heinz.
-Mr. Lohman.
Well, it's been a pleasure
serving you and yours,
volcanic eruptions and all.
Yeah. Thank you.
-Good night.
-Thank you.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
-All right.
-Good night.
-All right?
-Yup.
You're gonna give it three days?
Yeah, I owe her that much.
I owe my son...
much more than that.
Family isn't politics, Stan.
It's all politics.
Don't be so naive.
It's all strategic.
There's never a path
that's been just right or wrong.
Just a lot of shitty choices.
Someone always gets hurt.
Like in politics, right?
And every family that ever was.
Okay, so what happens now?
Some impossible happy ending?
I know.
Weird fucking fairy-tales, Stan.
All right.
Good night.
Yeah, good night.
Thanks.
War is always motivated
by a profound act of love.
Much more than hate.
To fight a war, you have to
deeply love the cause
and transcend sacrifice.
You fight for who
and what you love.
Freedom, power,
land, treasure...
Open the door, Beau!
Religion, dominance,
mother, country, leader.
I love my family.
Open the goddamn door.
I will go to war for my son.
I know you're in there!
I will go to war
as an act of love.
I just want to talk!
You would do the same.
Come on, Beau!
Hey, open the door.
I'm his uncle. I just want to
speak to him. Open the door.
Hey! Hey, stop.
You don't have to hide
from me, Beau.
You know, we never really
got to know one another.
You're kinda unknowable.
I mean, I'm not a bad person.
If anything, I feel too much.
You know?
I just... You know, I see things
from a father's perspective, though.
You know, what you're trying
to do, Beau, it's...
it's not right.
It's not what families do.
Families work together.
Families work together
to bury the ugly stuff.
They don't...
Come on out, Beau.
You... Just want to talk,
you can trust me.
Come out.
I'm sorry, Uncle Paul.
Families will do anything
to protect each other
and I don't want to hurt you, Beau,
but what choice do I have?
You didn't give me a choice.
Claire didn't.
It's our job to give Michael a future.
You know, I used
to teach kids your age.
I thought they loved me,
but they just didn't want
to listen anymore.
Scaring you straight
wouldn't work.
I'm sorry, Beau.
Beau!
Hey, Stanley, I was just thinking.
-Reason's what's separating...
-Is Beau up there?
Reason is what's
missing from our lives.
Just be quiet a second, all right?
-Is Beau up there with you?
-You can't Google reason.
Quit talking.
-Did you do something with him?
-No.
-What did you do?
-Nothing.
What did you do?
-What did you do to him?
What did you do with him?
I was just talking to him!
You don't talk to my son.
Do you hear me?
You are nothing to me.
-Stan! Stan!
-I am done with you!
-What did he do?
-Boy.
-Where's Beau?
-I don't know.
Why don't you call him?
Call him on your phone,
see if you can get him.
-Stan, over here.
-What is going on?
He's out there somewhere.
-Beau!
-Paul.
It's okay, honey, come here.
Hey, honey.
Beau!
I think he cracked a rib.
I was just...
I was just talking to Beau.
I was just talking to him.
Like you said,
I just took care of everything.
-And instead he lost his marbles.
-I'll call you back, okay?
Those are the right numbers?
We should call Michael, okay?
-Shit.
-We need to call Michael.
Say it again.
Tell me again.
-That many?
-What? What's going on?
Just hang on. You're sure?
I got Michael.
I got the votes.
It's gonna pass, it's gonna pass,
it's gonna pass.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Get me the...
-Michael.
-Yes, yes.
No, honey, how are you?
How are you doing?
Shut up.
-Everything's gonna be fine.
-No, no. Not you.
No, I was talking to somebody.
Daddy took care of everything.
Okay, call me. Now.
Mental health for all.
-You got him?
-No, it's voice-mail. I'll keep trying.
You did good.
You did real good.
Beau?
You were very, very smart.
This is funny, apes with phones.
Fucking apes with phones.
Beau? Thank God.
We were worried sick. Where are you?
I love you.