I'm, sorry?
I said don't you wish you could
paint like your husband?
Really, you must be so proud of him
Yes they're all fine now, they grew up
Now I don't say that my client
is the best landscape
Denmark,
but he is in the top one.
Yes.
It's going very well.
Thought that would be impossible.
Oh God!
My God!
Thank you.
- And Rasmussen...
- Oh, come on, be kind.
- At least he agreed to see your work.
- It's only because he was drunk.
I know.
- Yes you were loving it.
- I was not.
'I'm not saying that my client is the
best landscape artist in Denmark... '
But...
He's in the top one! '
Quiet! People are sleeping!
Sorry.
Do you know what time it is?
Time you came back to bed.
No.
I'm ready
to start work.
- Gerda.
- What?
Your face.
You think
I can't resist you?
Do you want to resist me?
No.
But I'd like you to ask nicely,
so that I'm not such a pushover...
Gerda Wegener,
my life,
my wife.
- Logged in?
- Mr. Wegener.
Perfect.
Yes, more?
Einar Wegener!
Oh, don't worry about him,
He's only ever had eyes for one woman.
My guilty secret's out.
So...
when are you going to breed
me a godchild?
Ulla, you're an atheist.
Have you tried to drink
raw eggs?
- No.
- Do it.
For my sake.
- We're trying.
- Try harder.
Anyway,
What are you doing in today? I thought
you had finished last week.
I wanted to check on the painting of the backdrop
for the storm scene.
And give Gerda
some space.
Ah.. she's got a shy one.
You know I'm next?
Oh so I heard.
I won't be shy.
I imagine not.
She'll need all
her colours for me!
Head up!
I wanted to tell you
I appreciate our being alone
I hope that your husband
does not mind.
Not at all.
I could see his being here made you..
uncomfortable.
It wasn't
personal.
It's not uncommon.
It's hard for a man to be looked at
by a woman.
Women are used to it,
of course,
but for a man... to...
submit...
to a woman's gaze,
it's unsettling.
Although I believe there is some pleasure
to be had from it,
once...
you um, yield.
Sit!
Good girl.
Good morning!
Well?
Perfect.
Almost.
Come here.
- Good luck!
- Toodle oo!
All portraits.
That bad?
Not per se.
This kind of work
is not really my...
Gerda...
I don't think it will benefit
either of us to show these
It's not a judgement on your abilities
I agree with Einar,
you could be
a first-class painter,
if you found the right subject matter.
How was it?
Fine.
I finally managed to get the colour for the snow.
A bog in violet.
I don't know how you can paint the same thing
over and over
I suppose I just haven't finished with it yet
- Gerda?
- Could you please not speak to
Rasmussen about me again?
My work is my business.
- Stay out of it.
- Gerda...
I had my period.
Sorry.
- Really?
- Of course I am.
You know I am.
Could you help me with something?
Anything.
Ulla has another rehearsal.
She cancelled again.
Would you try on her stockings and shoes?
I'm just so behind. I do not know how
I'll be finished in time for her opening.
I'll.
I'll do it.
It's fine I'll do it.
Stop it! Not now
He almost snagged it.
Oh dear.
No.
That's backwards.
I saw those in the window
at Fonnesbech.
Smart, aren't they?
- I don't think they'll fit.
- Well...
you'll do the best you can.
- No I need the dress.
- No.
- I need to see how the hem goes.
- No, Gerda.
I'm not going to put it on.
Just relax.
The sooner I start,
they sooner I'll finish.
Well, hello there!
Don't worry, my darling.
We're going to call you...
Lili.
Such concentration.
Sometimes I think you're going to
slip through the surface of the painting
and vanish
into the bog.
Like your friend's kite when you were a boy.
Hans.
Yes. Hans.
I bet he still sits on that rock
- Sobbing his heart out.
- Don't.
He's actually an
art dealer in Paris
peddling old masters to rich
Americans.
No we don't need to
worry about Hans.
No, we shouldn't worry.
- I didn't mean to disturb you.
- No it's ok. I'm finished.
And don't worry,
I won't disappear into the bog.
The bog's in me, silly.
- What?
- Can't a man watch his wife get undressed.
It's new.
That's very observant.
No no leave it on.
It's pretty.
I might let you borrow it.
I might enjoy that.
Is there something
you'd like to tell me?
you'd like to know?
No.
I'm your wife.
I know everything.
Those two, over there.
Both of them.
At the same time.
Oh, people are married
so delightfully easy to shock!
Oh can't we just pretend to be shocked
because it encourages you?
I know.
That is why you're the only married couple
- in my party for the Artists.
- No.
Out of the question.
She can go without me.
Gerda, without an escort?
Why, a scandal!
Gerda loves scandals.
Look at the way she dresses,
flaunting her ankles.
I don't think anyone is likely to be corrupted by
seeing my ankles.
I was.
The first time we met,
I was leaving the Academy
and she was sitting on the steps,
flaunting said ankles.
And she propositioned me.
Is that true?
When I said hello to him,
he actually blushed!
He was so shy, so I asked him out.
- And you said yes.
- Well she made me.
- She seemed so sure.
- I was sure.
- I still am.
- Oh, please, enough.
No!
What was it about him?
I don't know.
But we went.. coffee,
and after...
I kissed him.
And it was the strangest thing,
it was like kissing myself.
Well, these two won't be staying long...
Unmarried people are
so delightfully easy to shock..
Leave it.
Were you really
corrupted by my ankles?
You were shameless.
I still am.
Beautiful...
shameless... Gerda
Wait.
Did I wake you?
Sorry,
I couldn't sleep.
Why?
Wondering about things.
What things?
Wondering if we made a baby last night.
What do you think?
Wondering when got so pretty.
I was always pretty.
You... just never noticed.
- Hello?
- In here.
These are good, Gerda.
You think?
Well thanksyou.
I had a coffee with Ulla.
She asked me
about the Artists' Ball.
I'm not going.
Don't worry,
I told her no.
You should go,
- You enjoy it.
- With you, I enjoy it.
It's good to be seen
at those things, I do understand that.
- and that is why you hate them.
- I feel like I'm performing myself.
Giving them your... Einar Wegener.
Why not give them
something different,
go as someone else?
You have someone particular in mind?
No.
You'd be very convincing.
- That is outrageous!
- You might even enjoy it.
No.
You'll have to shave closer,
next time.
Close your eyes.
It  is hard on someone else..
Here let me try.
What d'you think?
Better than
I ever did.
Lili!
I want to sketch you.
Sit!
Come on, Hvap!
- Come on, you.
- On the other side.
Knee over,
Head up!
Oh, those hands...
Relax!
- Don't maker her a slut!
- It's your fault.
You excite here.
Why, Miss Lilly?
You are forward...
You have no idea.
Maybe bring out the hand.
Morning.
- Morning, Thorbjorn.
- Good morning.
Forward.
Hello?
I was wondering where you were.
It's getting late.
We have plenty of time.
Bought you these.
Oh, perfect.
Are you sure about tonight?
What is it?
Am I pretty enough?
Of course you are.
I'll never be as pretty as you.
You are so beautiful.
My darling!
Ulla,
let me introduce...
It's Lili!
You're right.
Einar's cousin from Vejle.
My dear,
exquisite!
In let's go in, come on!
You won't leave me..
No. Never.
People are looking.
Well you're a pretty girl,
you'll get used to it.
It's fine.
You're just feeling self-conscious.
Gerda?
Go talk to her.
No, I'll stay with you.
Go.
Go before they come over.
Alright.
Are you a reporter?
No.
A poetette?
Do you know the story of
this oak tree?
No.
They say that
if you eat its acorns,
you can make a wish
and become
anyone you want for a day.
Why would they say that?
Henrik Sandahl.
At your disposal.
Lili.
Are you here with someone, Lili?
Yes with...
my cousin's wife.
Who's your cousin?
Einar Wegener.
Painter.
Yes,
He's.
Rather a good one.
- Is that right?
- He's better than most people think.
Most people our age adulate him
Don't go back in. It's... cooler out here
Besides, I'm a romantic.
Really?
I prefer the shadows.
I don't mean to presume,
but I've been watching you,
and I think
you might be the same.
Come on.
Have you seen Einar?
I can't find him.
Of course not, he isn't here.
You're different from most girls.
That's not a very original line.
It's true.
You're old-fashioned.
Provincial.
I'm new to the city.
No, it's more than that.
I feel I'd need to...
ask your permission
before I kissed you.
I should go and find Gerda.
Why don't you tell her... I'll walk you home?
No, she wouldn't like that.
- Lili.
- I know...
He might be waiting for us, and he wouldn't like... this.
No?
No.
Lili.
You didn't ask permission.
I couldn't risk you saying no.
What's the matter?
I'm sorry,
I don't know what happened...
How are you?
You were late home last night,
so I thought I'd let you sleep.
How was it?
Did Lili have fun?
I think it would be better
if Lili didn't come here again.
Fine.
Exactly what happened
between you and Sandahl last night?
Nothing.
- It was nothing.
- Did he know it was you?
It wasn't as simple as that.
I watched him kiss you, Einar, so
could you please make an effort?
He may have known who I was.
But I wasn't always m-me.
There was a m-moment when I was just Lili,
and I think that he could see that..
- Do you see?
- But Lili doesn't exist.
- We made her up.
- I know.
- We were playing a game!
- I know we were.
But then...
- Something changed.
- This is absurd. We need to stop.
You need to stop, Einar.
I am going to try.
Another headache?
It's nothing.
Can I get you anything?
I'm fine.
Maybe you should
see a doctor.
Gerda,
I'm fine.
I didn't think you'd come.
No.
Nor did I.
I thought you might not come back.
That's absurd.
Is it?
The model...
Einar's cousin.
The resemblance is...
- Are there others?
- A series back at the studio.
These are different...
For these...
I don't know... there may be a market.
- You're taking them?
- Well... yes.
Come in.
I haven't got long.
Gerda's seeing Rasmussen.
I don't like all these lies.
- She's very protective.
- Why don't you tell her about us?
I couldn't do that.
Sorry.
I don't want to upset you.
Come here.
- No.
- Yes.
Einar...
- What?
- Come on... it's all right.
I don't understand.
Lili, please!
I don't know what you want.
- I...
- I don't know what you mean.
- I want you!
- No.
Lili. Lili! Lili, wait!
Are you alright?
No.
I've been seeing Henrik Sandahl.
I thought perhaps you knew.
No, not this.
So...
Are you in love with Sandahl?
No.
No, I love you, Gerda,
only you. It's Lili she...
- Be honest.
- I need you to believe me.
You of all people to understand.
Alright, you need to tell me when...
Henrik and Lili...
Are together,
They what, they...
kiss?
- Has it gone beyond that?
- No.
No, Lili has never gone further than that
with other men. He would not...
There have been other men?
There was another,
but it's was a long time ago.
It was that boy, Hans...
She fell for him, and...
he kissed her. Just once.
But then my father
came in and he caught them,
and he smacked Hans down.
He was so angry.
I do not know what to say.
What?
- I'm so sorry...
- Einar?
I'm so sorry...
- I'm sorry, I'm not feeling well.
- Einar, what is it? Einar?
Einar Einar......... Einar?
What's happened?
What's happening?
So you saw Dr. Andersen
after a bout
of severe nosebleeds,
which you have come to believe
coincide with
the stomach cramps,
and on a monthly basis.
So.
How long have you been married?
- 6 years.
- Children?
No.
Is there regular copulation?
Yes.
Perhaps less...
less than before you started
to dress as a woman?
I am a specialist, Mr. Wegener.
You may be embarrassed,
I'm not.
Tell me about... Lili.
Where does she come from?
inside me.
You know the most likely explanation
for all of this,
is a chemical imbalance?
Really?
On the bed.
That would explain the pain,
the confused state of masculinity
and infertility.
Let's hope it is that because that at least we can cure.
I don't need to do this. There's nothing wrong with me.
- That's not true.
- Gerda this can't be right.
Radiation is
a miracle, Mr. Wegener:
It destroyst the bad
and saves the good.
I'm sure it'll be over quickly.
Lie still, Mr. Wegener.
Mr. Wegener!
How are you feeling this morning?
You hurt Lili.
I'm afraid your husband's aberrant thinking persists.
- Do you keep a lock on your wardrobe?
- Of course not.
Mrs. Wegener, you're not
encouraging this delusion?
- You do understand that your husband is insane?
- No.
That's not true.
We trusted you.
We came
to you for help.
Gerda!
Where have you been?
Away.
Why, what's wrong?
I sold the Lili portraits!
I have enough interest now to mount a whole show.
That's wonderful!
And there's more...
The Gallery Etienne Dufour
in Paris, wants to represent you.
- In Paris?
- Yes, you must go.
I can't travel just now.
Gerda, this is
your moment.
You've waited long enough...
These art dealers can be difficult.
What are you doing?
I've been asked to exhibit in Paris.
- That's wonderful.
- Yes.
We have to go!
Rasmussen said
it will make all the difference.
I'm not sure I can.
I'll take care of you.
- Surely there's no.
- Can't you just do this one thing for me?
What's happening?
I had
a letter from Hexler.
He wants to lock me up.
Everything will work out for us
Really,
I know it.
You just have to trust me.
I do.
Einar's a painter too.
Do you exhibit in Paris?
I think my work's a little
introspective for French taste.
Excuse me...
- Is the model her?
- No.
She stayed behind in Denmark.
Oh, I was hoping so much
to meet her.
Really?
Madame Gerda Wegener,
Madame de la Roche.
They say it's so feminine.
And the passion...
No...
I'm sorry.
Will you sit for me?
Just as you are.
We haven't done that since art school.
The teacher...
suddenly at the mercy of the
student.
He found it exciting.
I can't just now.
I'm sorry.
I miss you.
I miss you working beside me.
I can't remember the landscape anymore.
I can't remember Vejle.
Well, you can help me
with this background.
What does it need?
A lake?
A farmhouse?
Gerda...
Oh, he is playing with us!
He knows the price.
Look, I have to go. I have Danish girl
waiting to see me.
- Alright.
- Madame?
Hans Axgil.
Thank you for seeing me.
Don't thank me yet,
I can't represent you.
I don't handle any contemporary art.
Of course, I know that.
The reviews of your show
they were terrific, but...
Perhaps if you would let me speak, perhaps
things would be clearer.
So when did you arrive?
Six months, almost
I do not know why Rasmussen
gave you my number,
but I'm glad he did.
I asked him.
I wanted to meet you,
to put a face to the name.
I believe you were a childhood friend
of my husband.
You have a husband?
I'm married to Einar Wegener.
- Einar?
- You remember him?
Of course I remember him.
We were such friends. How is he?
- He told me that you kissed him once.
- I what?
Oh right...
You're right, I remember.
We were fooling in the kitchen
and he was wearing his grandmother's apron
You know, little boys playing around?
He was looked so pretty in that,
I had to kiss him!
So yes,
I kissed Einar.
Next think I know, his father's chasing me out.
Einar... my God...
Why didn't he come today?
He doesn't know I'm here.
I don't think he'd like me asking for help.
We don't really know people here,
and Einar he's...
He's lost his way.
He's not working.
He needs
someone to represent him.
Someone who knows him.
He needs a friend.
I have a new dealer coming over later.
I'd like you to meet him.
I, I don't want a new dealer.
Doesn't make sense to me. I'm hardly working.
That might change.
I don't think so.
I'm happy, helping you.
It's Hans Axgil.
Dinner at La Delphine at 8,
then ack here to see the paintings.
He remembers you
with great fondness.
It was handmade and
and I've had it since I was 4!
Einar's still stricken with guilt about your kite.
My kite. I'll tease him about that.
No,
it's too cruel.
If he ever gets here.
- Perhaps he doesn't want to see me?
- No.
No, it's not that.
Maybe we should order without him.
Does he abandon you often?
Of course not.
I was joking.
I can come back another time
if you think Einar would prefer it.
Really,
He's expecting you,
and it will do him good.
I know this.
The Vejle Fjord,
not far from our houses.
Yes, he painted it just before we left.
Lili?
Hans?
May I introduce
Lili Wegener.
Einar's cousin from home.
You cannot imagine how happy I am...
We actually met once before, in Vejle,
but you probably don't remember.
Can I take your coat?
Of course.
A digestif, Hans?
It's so chilly all of a sudden.
Yes I feel the cold these days,
I don't know why.
Here.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry
that Einar couldn't be here.
He told me that back in Vejle,
you were his great friend.
Always plotting to get away!
- That's true.
- Such a hideous place!
He said that you wouldd sit,
and you would look out together,
beyond the fjord to the sea,
to the future.
We had big dreams, yes.
Yes.
And you were the only one that would let him
paint in peace.
You told him that it was alright to be a painter.
He used to sketch my portrait.
Take a stone and draw me on the rocks, at the side of the road.
- I didn't know that.
- Yes.
- Would you like to see more of Einar's work?
- Do we have any?
- Of course, Lili.
Can we not do it another time?
I want to hear more about you, Hans.
- Are you married?
- Er, no.
Well why not?
You don't mind, do you?
I've been on my own a long time now, I'm...
too set in my ways.
Yes I think that marriage is the single thing that
we should all hope for in life.
Really?
Yes you see it creates someone else,
More than just the two of you.
It would be terrible not to
It could be terrible not to...
I'm so.. will you excuse me?
Lili?
You ought to go.
Let me help.
Please.
Sorry.
Good night, Lili.
Good night.
I don't think he noticed, did you?
I don't know.
I think I got out
just in time.
Sleep now.
We'll talk more tomorrow.
Can I borrow a night dress?
No. We've never done that.
Lili's never spent the night.
It does not matter what I wear.
When I dream,
they're Lili's dreams.
- A new dress?
- And this is for you.
Do you like it?
Yes.
It's perfect for you.
- We're a little short of money at the moment.
- I know.
But now that I'm back,
I can sit for you.
Well it worked
well before,
didn't it work?
Come on.
That's good.
Head up.
Now.
- No, back!
- Yes.
That ring.
Thank you.
Oh, I meant that I do not think...
There are.
How are you, ma'am?
- Mrs. Venort, and magnificent.
- I didn't know you were coming.
It's a good crowd.
She's a popular girl.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for inviting me.
I thought you had forgotten all about me.
We've been busy.
Is Einar here?
- He hates this kind of thing.
- That's a shame.
For you, I mean.
- I don't mind.
- Is he well?
He's excited
A friend, is coming to town, Ulla Fonsmarck
the dancer. Maybe you know her.
I don't think so.
Can I take you to dinner?
To celebrate?
I think someone ought to.
No,
thank you.
Gerda,
have I offended you?
No.
Gerda.
I am still Einar's wife.
Hans!
Oh, Henri, how are you?
What a nice evening!
Absolutely!
At least take an umbrella.
No, I'm fine, honestly.
Well, if you just wait a minute, someone
will drive you.
No, I'm fine.
Oh Gerda, you're soaked.
Did it go well?
Tell me, how was it?
You'd know if you'd been there.
I... I made us a little supper.
- You should have come.
- A little.. sort of celebration.
This is not how it goes.
We do these things together.
That was you and Einar.
Stop with that
stupid, stupid game!
Please, Gerda.
Don't you think this is a game.
You should have been there.
How could I?
- Look at me.
- Not everything is about you!
- I need to see Einar.
- Let me help you, please.
I need my husband.
Go get him.
I can't.
I need to talk to my husband.
I need to hold my husband.
I need him.
Can't you just get him?
Can you at least try?
I'm sorry.
Gerda.
What is it?
Are you alright?
Gerda, wait,
wait!
I don't think I can...
give you what you want.
I don't know how long we can go on like this.
No.
- He needs to see someone.
- You know what happened with Hexler.
He's so thin.
Something's
wrong with him.
Can you work yourself bigger?
Look,
There's a doctor,
He runs the women's clinic in Dresden.
He'ss interested in men
like Einar,
who are
confused.
And who are different.
He's often in Paris.
Just talk to him.
You're awake?
How do you feel?
Come.
I've got somewhere to go.
Where?
S-sorry, I...
I don't know how to hold on to you any longer.
I know.
I love you.
And I'm going
to find an answer.
...
Victor?
- Look.
- Love.
It's a lesbian.
No, not a woman.
Come, come, come!
- Good morning.
- !
What's your name, sir?
- English?
- English.
Do you speak English?
Are you a boy or a girl?
Do you have a...
What are you? Huh?
- Don't be afraid.
- Kids.
Joking.
Stand up.
Hold him up.
I can't hold the buyer's much longer, I'm sorry.
Einar.
You're good at this.
I boxed for a while.
Shame you weren't with me earlier.
I'm sorry I've not been to see you before.
It's alright.
You're here now.
I couldn't let Gerda see me like this.
She's had enough to put up with.
What's happened to you?
I don't understand.
Nor do I.
But I don't think it's anything new.
Even back in Vejle.
Sorry.
What?
I was different.
It didn't take much to be
different in Vejle.
Surely that's why
we became friends.
Every morning
I promise myself that I will spend
the entire day as Einar.
But there's so little
of Einar left.
You only think these things
because you're exhausted.
Sometimes I think about
killing Einar.
But it's only the thought that
I'd be killing Lili too, that stops me.
You need to see someone.
- A doctor.
- No.
- Yes.
- No doctors.
I'll help you find someone.
You have to try.
A confused state
of identity.
I drill small holes...
here and here.
I listened to you very carefully
and I'm afraid it's not good news.
You are an homosexual.
I don't really know
what kind of help I need,
but I can't go on living without knowing who I am.
Please excuse me for a moment.
Schizophrenic
Do you think I'm insane?
Did a doctor say that?
I'm sorry, I know that we agreed
no more but...
- Look at me.
- You are not insane.
Did I do this to you?
What?
Sometimes I wonder
if it hadn't been for the paintings...
Oh, Gerda, no...
You helped bring Lili to life,
but she was always there...
- She was always waiting...
- Now she's making you ill.
I don't know what to do.
The doctors
can't help.
Do you want to try one more?
- Warnekros... Einar.
- Pleasure.
Good to see you.
So what do you think would explain
what you've been experiencing, Mr. Wegener?
Professor Warnekros,
the fact is...
I believe that I'm
a woman...
Inside.
And I believe it too.
You probably think that I'm insane.
That we both are.
Well,
there are some people that think that I'm insane.
But I think you're
probably right.
I've met
another... man like you.
I pursued his case...
against the wishes of my colleagues of course.
I told him I could operate.
To make him fully a woman.
That was what he really wanted.
- Is it really possible?
- What happened to the man?
- Was the operation successful?
- On the morning of the first operation, he ran away.
- He was too frightened.
- I wouldn't do that. I...
Perhaps he was the smart one.
The surgery... it's never been attempted before... Never.
Professor Warnekros,
What is the surgery?
Two operations...
The first to remove
the male parts entirely.
The second, once you're
strong enough again,
to construct a vagina.
An irreversible change
and a high risk of failure,
infections,
- Complications.
- It's too dangerous.
It's my only hope.
I leave for Dresden
lunchtime tomorrow.
Mrs. Wegener,
I do believe I can help
your husband.
But, he won't be your husband, when I've finished.
It feels strange, going dressed like this.
It's important.
Hans says that the Germans won't check your papers.
You're nearly there.
I won't be seeing you again.
I've only really liked a handful of people in my life
and you've been two of them.
Take care.
I wish you'd let me come with you.
I can't.
You love Einar.
And I have to let him go.
Here...
Take this.
Hello.
My name's Lili and I'm here to see...
Professor Warnekros.
Lili what?
Elbe...
Lili Elbe, like the river.
Of course
Please take a seat over there.
Must I really wait?
It's only a week.
I need you to rest. Gain some weight.
We can't risk an infection.
For what we are attempting,
I need you to be strong.
This is not my body, professor.
Please, take it away.
You're having a baby.
And you?
Oh, no, no.
I'm ill inside.
But Professor
Warnekros will help me get better
And will you be able to have children after?
D'you know, I don't know.
I hope so.
Gerda, why don't you go?
- He asked me not to.
- He wanted to protect you.
- You should be there. I'll go with you.
- If I go, it will be alone.
- Now you're sounding like Einar.
- I am like Einar.
- What do you want me to do?
- I want you to go away.
Really?
No... I... sorry...
He regained consciousness
very briefly.
We had to give her a great deal of morphine of course,
so that's to be expected.
You mustn't move Lili,
it only makes it worse.
Oh God.
Breathe.
I'm here.
It's alright,
I'm here now.
Lili.
I can feel myself getting better
when I listen to your pencil.
You've always sketched
me better than I was.
But what you draw, I become.
You made me beautiful,
Now you're making me strong.
Such a power in you.
Shall we go back to Denmark then, Gerda?
Shall we go home?
Lili...
You're late.
Your pills...
Every 2 hours. And I need to eat something first.
I have some macaroons
in my bag already.
And these,
only if you need them.
Good luck.
And remember, making a purchase from Fonnesbech,
is not merely shopping,
it's an experience.
You lived in Paris, yes?
Yes.
Let everyone know!
The store is a stage,
we're here to perform!
In Paris, you see a lady
would never dream of
spraying scent
directly onto herself.
No, she's spray it in the air,
and then she would walk
through it. Voila
You try.
Voila!
- Thanks
- That's so unfair, you've got the sweetest tooth,
and the narrowest hips in the whole store.
Really, how do you do manage it,
eating so much sugar?
Oh the trick is not to
eat anything else.
- See you tomorrow!
- Goodbye, Lili.
- Bye.
Lili, you coming?
You know one night last week, I
had the strangest dream.
- What was it?
- I dreamed that you were getting married.
- Do you think I ever will?
- Who knows?
So many strange things have happened
I do want to, Gerda.
It's not so long ago
... that you and I were married.
You... and Einar.
I know it was Einar.
But really...
it was you... and me.
Lili!
Is it really you?
I believe so.
So, what
you're suggesting...
is that a... a doctor...
intervened...
to correct
a mistake of nature.
- He made you a woman?
- No, God made me woman.
The doctors... the doctor
He is curing the sickness that is my disguise.
A real woman?
You're going to need a new notebook
if you carry on like that.
When Warnekros
suggested I keep a diary,
I thought I wouldn't have
anythin to write.
It does help...
- To make sense of things.
- Maybe I should try it.
So?
Do you enjoy working at Fonnesbech?
For now at least...
I do sort of enjoy being part of it..
You never think of painting?
- You might be good at it.
- Gerda, I want to be a woman,
not a painter.
Well, people have been known
to do both.
I'm curious to see what you
would paint, that's all.
Sometimes it's hard to know what's
in your...
Didn't you just take one of those
Some minutes ago?
Gerda, I know what I'm doing.
I'm going to get some fresh air.
You know, sometimes I do wonder why
You let me go through all of this,
if you thought that everything
would be the same afterwards.
I didn't.
But I promised Einar
That I would take care of you.
For goodness sake,
Gerda, Einar is dead.
We both have to accept that.
You took care of me,
but now I have to take care of myself.
I have to have a life of my own.
And you need to do the same.
Come on, HVAP.
Yes.
In London?
- Is it urgent?
- No, everything's fine.
Just tell him...
Tell him it's a beautiful day
in Copenhagen
- Good morning.
It's not what you think.
Henrik's homosexual,
so there's nothing between us.
But I should have told you
that I'd seen him.
No, you shouldn't.
It's a friend, Gerda.
Someone to talk to.
Because you can't talk
to me.
I've made a decision.
I'm going back to Dresden
for the second operation.
- That's too soon.
- No, it's time.
- I have to finish what I started.
- You're not strong enough.
Professor Warnekros
thinks that I am.
Warnekros? Warnekros
hasn't seen you.
I've made up my mind, Gerda.
- It could kill you.
- I'm going on Friday. Will you come with me?
I won't help you to hurt
yourself.
Gerda, will you come?
This will be harder than the first operation.
You understand that?
Yes I do.
It's a complex surgery.
And I will sleep
all the way through it.
- Yes, you will.
- And you will be there when I wake up?
Of course.
I want a husband
that looks just like you.
Maybe
a child one day.
Like a real woman.
One step at a time.
Get some rest. Good night.
Are you still angry at me?
I'm not angry at you,
I'm worried about you.
You heard my wish, Gerda.
When no one else could hear me,
you did.
Come...
We both our rest.
I'll sleep on the chair, there.
- No, off to your little hotel.
- I don't mind.
Here, take this,
there's a chill in the air.
- No.
- Please.
You have it.
For now.
I'm going to be fine.
Yes.
- Sleep well.
- Good night.
Good evening.
- Room 9, please.
- Number 9, yes of course.
Thank you.
Hans?
It's alright.
Everything will be all right.
Miss Elbe?
It's time.
Good luck everybody.
Professor Warnekros
would like a word...
He lost a lot of blood. Now we are
struggling to keep the fever down.
There's a chance it might burn itself out, but...
I have to be honest.
The prognosis is not...
Here, just lie still.
It's alright.
Lili.
How are you Lili?
I am...
entirely myself.
You had us worried there you know?
Can I go outside...
Gerda?
Into the garden?
You should rest.
Please.
You mustn't worry
about me anymore, Gerda.
It's an old habit.
I am are slow to change.
How have I ever
deserved such love?
There's nothing to be afraid of anymore.
No.
Last night...
I had the most beautiful dream
I dreamed that I was a baby
in my mother's arms.
She looked down at me
and she called me Lili.
Lili.
Lili!
No, leave it!
Let her fly.
Lili Elbe's diaries became
the basis of the groundbreaking memoir
'Man into Woman',
published in 1933.
Her bravery and pioneering spirit
remain an inspiration
for today's transgender movement.
Gerda continued to paint
portraits of Lili for the rest of her life.