Subtitles by explosiveskull
(ticking)
(gavel bangs)
Order in the court.
Foreman, has the jury
reached a verdict?
Yes, your honor, we have.
The defendant and his counsel
will stand for the verdict.
Read on.
In the case of the state
of North Carolina versus Garcia,
the first charge of indecent
liberties with a minor...
not guilty.
Man: What?!
(crowd shouting angrily)
Order in the court!
The second charge of murder
in the first degree...
not guilty.
- That is bullshit!
- (all shouting angrily)
Order in the court!
Were the facts and the evidence
in this trial irrelevant,
or has the jury been asleep
for the entire deliberation
of this trial?
The defendant shall be released
from custody.
This court is adjourned.
I hear she has a sister.
Jim, Jim, stop!
- How do you defend this trash?!
- Jim, sit down.
Get yourself together, man.
He's not worth it.
I'm okay. I'm free.
(screams)
(all shouting and screaming)
Get that processed right away.
So, what now?
You know that stuff's
gonna kill you, right?
- Low dose.
- I was talking about the soda.
You put way, way, way too much
pressure on yourself, man.
You and the family
should just get in the car
and get out of town
for a while.
- Take a long vacay.
- (telephone rings)
I don't understand.
You gonna get that?
All right,
I'll get the phone.
D.A.'s office.
Uh, yes, ma'am.
Um, he's here.
Hold on for a second.
I need you to take this.
Hold on, please.
- This is James.
- Woman: Hi, honey.
Someone called
from the Cedar Falls
County Sheriff's Department.
Yeah? What's wrong?
They found her this morning.
I'm sorry. She's gone.
Oh.
We're gonna have to plan
the funeral right away.
So... it's about
a five-hour drive up there.
Why don't you get
the car packed,
and we'll leave
first thing in the morning?
We'll be up there
for a couple of weeks.
Gotta get the house sold.
Faith can watch Danny
while we're gone.
James: No, actually,
I want them to come with us.
Are you sure?
Yeah, yeah, positive.
- Okay.
- I love you.
I love you.
Okay, bye.
Mother's dead.
Oh...
Woman: I'm sorry about
your mother-in-law.
I know you didn't
know her very well, and...
Yeah, this whole thing
just seems so weird, you know?
Yeah.
Like, I just never...
I never got to know her.
And... I don't know.
I don't even know
how to read James on this,
you know what I mean?
Like, when's somebody's
so private
about their information,
about their family.
How is he holding up?
He's seems like he's okay.
It's just, you know, his dad
passed when he was young,
and he's alone in that respect.
His family is gone.
It's definitely gonna
be interesting going there.
Wow.
Look at this town!
Oh, I feel like
we stepped back in time.
It's very Americana.
I don't think much has changed
since I left.
Looks about the same.
Some things don't change.
That school is very old.
Woman: Yikes.
James: They stopped using it
a long time ago.
- Anybody hungry?
- James: Hey, kiddo, you hungry?
I bet you I know somebody
who's very hungry.
- This is the best behaved you've ever been.
- Honestly.
James:
So, what do you want?
You relax, kiddo.
Why don't you finish
those fries?
If you're hungry later,
I don't want to hear about it.
Are you sure you're all done?
Boy: I'm sure.
You're not gonna finish?
James: No? You sure?
What's wrong?
Did you see the way
that she was staring at Danny?
No.
No, uh, I didn't.
Just this place, you know,
I don't know.
It just feels kinda... stale.
- Yeah, like the coffee.
- (laughs)
No, honey,
I just think you're tired.
You need to relax.
Actually, we should get going
'cause we've got to stop
by the florist
before we get to the funeral
home, so.
Okay, let's go.
(doorbell jingles)
You all right?
You think grandma would like
these flowers right here?
Those are funeral flowers, bud.
Hey, what do you think
of these flowers?
You like those there?
Hi, there.
Can we get a card
for him to fill out?
Here, buddy. You can fill
that out for grandma, okay?
This place is giving me
the creeps.
There's nothing
but funeral arrangements.
"Oh, it's so nice
in the country."
It's so nice and all,
but this is what you get...
a lot of old people dying.
- Daddy?
- Hmm?
Are we home?
No, Danny.
This is not our home.
This is gonna be a tough sell.
Is this ours?
I mean,
are we going to live here?
No, Danny, it was grandma's.
We're gonna fix it up,
and we're gonna sell it
'cause it's way too big
for the three of us.
- James: Let's go.
- Okay.
All right.
(sighs)
We have our work
cut out for us.
Oy, you haven't seen
anything yet.
Hey.
I need you to help me get
some things out of the car
'cause we have to get ready
for the funeral, okay?
Okay.
Where did you find this?
It came down the stairs.
James: Hey, honey,
come here a second.
All these toys?
- Yeah, what about 'em?
- They're mine.
Woman: Well,
maybe your mom put 'em out
for the neighborhood kids
to play with.
James:
No, honey, look at them.
They've been out here
for years.
I don't know.
I know that we've got to get
ready for the funeral, okay?
Yeah.
(soft music playing
over speaker)
It's over.
Come on.
Whatever we see
or then seen
is but a dream
within a dream.
I pray God wraps his wings
around you
and gives you peace,
Nadine.
James: Hey, what do you want
to do with the other boxes?
Um...
just, uh...
just put them on the table,
and I'll get to them later.
(thump)
Be careful.
James: I'm fine.
There's so much crap.
Woman: I know. That's what
I've been trying to tell you.
Where's a donation
center nearby?
(both speaking indistinctly)
Gosh, look at all
of these pictures.
Your mom, like,
had such a cool collection.
Yeah, I doubt
she remembers the names
of everybody on the wall.
Danny?
- James?!
- What?
What? What happened?
I don't know, your son...
I don't even know.
"Your son,"
which means he's in trouble.
- Look!
- Whoa, what happened?
Is he down there
in the basement right now?
I don't know.
Danny?! Danny!
Why is that walled up?
It doesn't make any sense.
Mom probably had this walled up
after pop passed away
because his workshop
was down in the basement.
- Go!
- Danny! I can't...
Danny! I'm not gonna
be able to see shit.
Danny?
Danny, answer us
if you're down there!
I need a flashlight
or something.
Here.
Thank you, honey.
Perfect.
Well, be careful.
Jesus.
Son, you in here?
- (roars)
- Ah, shit!
Gotcha.
Yeah. (chuckles)
Yeah, you did, bud.
You scared the poop
right out of me.
- I did, didn't I?
- Uh-huh.
Yeah, so, uh, don't you think
it's a little dangerous
crawling around down here
in the dark, you know?
And it kind of stinks,
doesn't it?
- Yes, it does.
- Yeah. Yeah.
So, is there a good reason
why we're down here right now?
No.
So what do you say
we go back upstairs?
You know? All right.
Come on. Let's go.
James: This one
is called "The Raven."
"Once upon
a midnight dreary
while I pondered,
weak and weary,
over many a quaint
and curious volume
of forgotten lore,
while..."
Are you trying to scare me?
Why, no, I'm just trying
to entertain you.
Trying to entertain yourself.
(chuckles) Yeah, well,
that might also be true.
Are you tired?
You just wanna go to bed?
Yeah?
Thy will be done.
Let me tuck you in.
I'll see you in the morning,
okay?
Okay.
Woman: Hey, don't forget
to put away all those old toys
- in the yard tomorrow.
- All right, yeah, I will.
Okay.
And my soul
from out the shadows
floating on the floor
shall be lifted nevermore.
(both chuckle)
- Are you trying to scare me?
- Maybe.
Yeah, well, it's not working
on me either.
Damn.
(laughs)
Good night.
Yeah, good night.
Danny: What's wrong?
You look very sick.
Are you okay?
Are you a sleepy boy?
Yes.
Did your daddy's stories
keep you awake?
No, we were playing.
(laughs) What?
Who's we?
- He was...
- (knock on door)
All right, okay,
chew your food.
Hi, how may I help you?
Good morning. How are you?
I'm fine, thank you.
My name is
Father Donovan O'Malley.
And I'm sorry
for the intrusion,
but I knew the lady
that lived here.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I, uh...
I took it off this morning.
I'm a little bit clumsy
with my dress,
but my soul is tidy.
- (chuckles)
- Are you moving in here?
Oh, actually no, we're not.
This belonged
to my mother-in-law,
and we're just
putting it up for sale.
- Please, come in.
- Oh.
So, Nadine
was your mother-in-law.
Uh, yes, she was.
And James is your husband.
Yes. Unfortunately,
he's not here right now.
He'll be back
in a little while.
Look, I just put on
a pot of coffee.
Would you like some?
- I don't want to impose.
- Oh, my pleasure.
Thank you.
Oh, oh...
forgive me
for being so inquisitive,
but I remember that picture.
I knew Nadine and James
when he was just a little boy.
It's a wonderful family,
full of faith and integrity.
She was giving to a fault.
Really.
I never really knew her.
Really?
How do you take your coffee,
Father?
Pure. Unadulterated
and pure, thank you.
Black it is.
Hello.
What's your name?
Danny.
Okay, Danny,
not with your mouth full.
Hope I didn't get you
into trouble.
It's okay. I'm used to it.
Here you go, Father.
Thank you. Thank you.
Oh.
- Please have a seat.
- Thank you, thank you.
At our messy breakfast table.
I'm really happy to be here,
thank you.
- Thank you for this.
- Excuse the table.
It looks like we're having
crayons for breakfast.
So, is the parish nearby?
Yes and no.
How's that?
Well, the building's still
there, but most of the people
have a rough time
getting out of the cold.
Winter's come so fast.
Sundays in Cedar Rock Falls
is mostly about TV
and housekeeping,
not so much about worship.
Mm.
You are the youngest couple
in town.
I had noticed that.
It's mostly older people
and no children.
Um... old age
is not contagious,
but it will happen
to everyone.
Most of the young folks,
including your husband,
left town as soon
as they were old enough,
and the rest are merely
forgotten parents.
That's terrible.
Not really.
They treasure the solitude,
and, um, the quiet
is to die for.
(thump)
- Holy shit!
Holy shit is right.
Danny, don't say that.
Did I say that out loud?
I'm going down to the basement
and play with my friends.
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
You're not going downstairs.
You can go upstairs
to your room, okay?
Sorry. He has a new
imaginary friend.
Not surprising.
It's age-appropriate.
Look at this.
Oh, and his father
reads him Poe stories at night.
Oh, really?
He likes the classics, huh?
- Yeah.
- (door opens)
- James: Jennifer?
- Donovan: I should go.
Oh, no, no, no, please stay.
It'll be a nice surprise.
We have a guest!
Huh? Who is it? Oh.
Wow, it's...
it's been a while.
Wow, I haven't seen you since...
easy, buddy.
You were 13.
Yeah, yeah. Come on in.
It's really been
that long, huh?
Yeah. I was there when you went
off to boarding school.
I'm very sorry
about your mother, my son.
Well, knowing her
as well as I do,
I'm certain that she'd be very
happy that you're all here.
James: I think so.
I think so.
I just wish Danny
had the opportunity
to get to know her.
How old is he?
Oh, Danny? He's six.
Oh, just about ready
for school.
That's unfortunate.
Well, why is that?
Our school's been closed
for decades.
Damn it, honey. I thought
you had this door locked.
There must be something wrong
with the lock.
Okay, all right, I'll...
I'll fix it later.
Well, I think
I've overstayed my welcome.
Oh.
Well, Father, no,
we're happy that you stopped by.
- It's great to see you again.
- My pleasure.
And please,
come back any time.
With your special blend
of hospitality and good coffee,
I'd find it impossible not to.
(door opens)
Jennifer:
He seems like a nice guy.
Kind of open-minded, though,
for a priest, don't you think?
Yeah, I don't know.
I barely know the guy.
Well, he knows you.
Yeah, it sure seems
that way, right?
Jennifer: He knew your mom
really well, too.
James: Well, he and dad
were old fishing buddies.
Actually, I can recall that now
quite well.
He was around here
quite a bit.
You don't think that he
and your mom had a little...
Oh.
No.
No. Dad would have killed him.
(indistinct whispering)
- Danny?
- (whispering stops)
What are you doing
in here in the dark?
Playing.
But you're
supposed to be in bed.
What... what the hell
are my toys doing out?
I didn't do it.
You scared them away.
Scared who away?
Okay, you know what?
That is enough play time
for tonight.
All right, back to bed.
And you play
with your friend tomorrow.
- That's right.
- Okay.
Yeah, he has
an imaginary friend.
(sarcastically) Great.
Now you need to go to sleep.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Night night.
- You listen to your mother.
Okay.
- Good night. Night, buddy.
- Good night.
(whispering continues)
(low gurgling)
Go home.
I have to go to sleep.
Come back tomorrow.
Shoot.
Danny: Mom!
Hey, Danny?
What happened?
Oh, honey. Honey.
Oh...
Okay, you know what?
We'll keep this
our little secret.
We'll get you
all cleaned up, all right?
I'm gonna go start the tub.
- Okay.
(bath water running)
(screaming)
What is wrong with you?!
Why did you do that?!
- I didn't.
- You think it's funny?!
No.
Then why did you do it?!
I didn't.
You get in this tub,
and you don't get out
until I tell you.
- (laughs)
- Oh, my God!
Whoa, whoa, hey, hey!
Easy, whoa.
You scared the shit out of me!
All right, all right,
I noticed, jeez.
- (laughs)
- Jesus.
What took you so long?
Well... actually, honey,
I have some very good news.
We have a prospective buyer.
Oh, my God,
that's such good news.
Yeah.
Yeah, it really is.
They're gonna stop by
sometime next week, so...
I need your help.
Yeah, sure, what can I do?
Hanging sheets?
I'm good at that.
Not really.
I need you to talk
to your son.
Again, why does he always
become my son
when he's in trouble?
James, I'm serious.
What did he do?
Nothing.
Really.
Come on, tell me,
Clearly, he did something.
He's blaming his mistakes
on his imaginary friends.
James: What kind of mistakes
are we talking about?
Jennifer: Nothing.
I just don't think
that having imaginary friends
is good for him.
James: Really? Didn't you have
some when you were a kid?
Jennifer: Yes, yes, I had one.
Everyone has one.
He has several.
Don't you think
that that's strange?
(indistinct whispering)
(whispering stops)
Hey.
What are you doing there?
Coloring.
So, your mother tells me
that you have some friends
that are running around here.
Is that true?
Yes.
Yeah?
Who are they?
I don't know. Just friends.
Now, Danny...
I don't want you hanging
around with these friends.
- Why?
- Because I say so.
But I remember
when I was growing up
all the way out here
in this big house,
in the middle of nowhere,
it got kind of lonely.
So I made up
these imaginary friends.
I don't want you hanging out
with the same friends.
They're not good for you.
What are you guys
talking about?
We're just discussing
his new friends.
Bud, what do you say
we get to bed, huh?
Come gimme a hug.
Come here.
Hey, you.
Hey.
Jennifer:
Everything okay?
James:
Just one of those headaches.
- Another sinus headache?
- Mm, yeah.
Yeah, I can feel it
coming on.
Is there anything I can do?
No, honey.
No, I got my medication.
I just gotta pick up
some more tomorrow, so...
You've already done enough.
(ticking)
Oh, God! I overslept!
I knew it was gonna happen.
I'm supposed to meet the buyers
in, like, 10 minutes.
Didn't I set the alarm?
Didn't you see me set it?
Yeah.
It didn't go off?
Yeah, no, it didn't.
All right, I love you.
I'll see you later.
Love you, too. Mm.
Wish us luck.
Okay. Good luck.
(door unlatches,
creaks open)
- (gasps)
- (roars)
(gasps)
Oh, my God.
I thought I'd stop by
and check on you folks.
The front door was wide open.
Is everything all right?
Is it?
Is... is what?
Everything all right.
Sure.
I-I suppose.
Can I make you some coffee?
That's nice, thank you.
Where's the little one?
He's upstairs.
Damn it.
Was that door open again?
No problem.
It's closed now.
It keeps doing that.
Yeah, probably explains
why they had it sealed up.
How did you know
that it was sealed up?
You mentioned it.
Did I?
(loud crashing)
Danny!
Oh, my God.
Danny.
Danny... what happened?
Are you okay?
We were playing.
Jennifer:
Who is "we"?
They're gone now.
Danny, enough.
Should I close the window?
Yes, please.
Oh, God.
What?
(bird cawing)
Nothing.
There was a raven
on the windowsill.
You know, I think I should...
I think I should take
a rain check
on that coffee, okay?
Yeah. We need
to clean up this mess.
Yeah.
Oh, my gosh.
(birds cawing)
James:
So, just warn me now.
Is that kitchen a mess
with this fried chicken?
- Jennifer: It's a mess. I know.
- Dad?
Yes, buddy?
Can I bring a friend
to dinner?
Sure, would this be
your imaginary friend?
Yes.
Does he have a name?
Charlie.
Oh.
Yeah, I think it'd be great
if Charlie joined us.
He could sit right next to you.
He has a name now.
Yes.
I'm gonna get Charlie a plate.
I think that would be awesome.
Look what I found.
For Charlie.
What do you say to your mother?
Thank you, mommy.
That is very sweet of her,
isn't it?
Well, maybe Charlie
will do the dishes.
What do you think?
Right?
James: I'd be
his number-one fan.
(whispers) He said
he'd be your number-one fan.
What are you doing there?
He said he knows you.
Hmm. Is that right?
That's interesting.
I don't know if we've met yet.
Yeah, you know, I don't know
if I know him, buddy.
He said he heard you.
Yeah, yeah, I'm sure he did.
I also hope he can hear me
when I say
that I don't believe
in imaginary people.
(whispers) He said he doesn't
believe in imaginary people.
He lost his appetite.
He's not hungry anymore.
Well, that just means
that there's gonna be more food
for the rest of us,
so that's just fine.
What the hell?
(clock ticking)
(Danny screams)
- Danny?
Danny, are you okay?
What is going on
in that little head?
James: You all right?
(indistinct whispering)
Oh, my God! Danny!
Danny! Are you okay?!
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- What the hell happened?!
- What happened?!
- Oh, my God, are you okay?!
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Are you okay?
What happened?!
Tell me what happened!
I don't know! I don't know!
I don't know! I just...
What the hell
are you doing with that?!
I was just standing there
holding it!
Oh, my God, are you okay?
Jennifer, back up.
Back up.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Oh, my God.
Come here.
Here, here's teddy.
You okay?
No. I don't...
I don't want any.
I don't know
what's wrong with me.
- I could have killed him!
- I know.
- I know. It was an accident.
Jennifer: And... and I'm
sleepwalking and shooting?
I want you to get rid
of that gun.
I don't even know
why my mom had it anyway.
(children laughing)
Danny!
- Where are you?!
- (children giggle)
There she is.
Oh, God.
You okay, honey?
You all right?
What happened?
Danny said you took
a pretty nasty fall.
I remember running and, and...
I saw him.
Easy. Easy. You saw who?
The little boy.
Okay, hon, I think maybe
you sat up a little too quickly,
and you're not
thinking straight.
No, no, no, no, no.
I am thinking straight.
That was him, wasn't it?
Mommy, don't make them
mad again.
Whoa, you two.
Honey, Jennifer...
I saw Charlie.
Right.
Don't patronize me.
Are you listening
to yourself right now?
Son, tell me,
did you see an imaginary boy
that mom's talking about?
Yeah? You saw him?
Hon, do you hear
what that sounds like right now?
But I did. I saw him.
That's fine. That's fine.
So, what did he look like?
Jennifer: He's...
He was... he was small,
and he had dark hair.
- He has a...
- He had a scar.
He has a scar.
Yeah, no, okay, I got it.
It's crystal clear.
You think that I'm crazy,
don't you?
Honey...
- No, hon?
- I sound crazy.
Hon, no,
you don't sound crazy.
Listen. Hey, you know
what I think?
I think maybe you need
to get out of the house
for a little while, okay?
Just take Danny with you.
Maybe you guys go get
some ice cream or something.
Does that sound good?
Yeah?
You feel up for that?
I'm sorry, mommy.
For what, honey?
For everything.
It's okay.
Why is he staring at me?
Let's ignore him.
Good day to you, madam.
He's a handsome lad.
Thank you.
What's your name, son?
Danny.
Old man:
You look just like my boy.
I had a boy
just like him one time.
About your age.
But he's not here anymore.
Old woman: What a lovely boy
you have there.
He's so cute.
Old man: Wonder if I could
take him home with me.
Jennifer: No,
that would be inappropriate.
Old woman:
Do you need a babysitter?
No, we're good on babysitters.
He is so handsome.
My son was seven.
My son's
not coming home anymore.
Danny:
Can we go now, mommy?
Yeah. Sorry, excuse me.
I'd sure like to...
sure like to know him better.
You're scaring my son!
Old man: Did I offend you?
I'm sorry.
All I was trying to do
was say hello.
Excuse us, please.
Please excuse us.
- I beg your pardon.
- Come on, Danny.
Good morning.
Morning, Father.
How are you?
Good, thank you.
- Why don't you come on in?
- Thank you.
What did they want?
You know what?
Your dad can hire
a real-estate agent,
and he can sell the house
that way.
I'm done with this town.
I need to just forget
about this house.
You saw him.
You saw him, didn't you,
mommy?
Is he in your imagination, too?
I don't know.
But I know
one way to find out.
Sure I can't
get you something?
No.
I just stopped by
to see how things were going.
Yeah, yeah, well,
aside from a few bumps
in the night,
I'd say all is good.
Bumps?
Understandable.
Okay, come on in, buddy.
Come here, come here.
All right.
Hello?
Donovan: You know, people say
that organized religion
is for people that
are afraid to go to hell
and that spirituality
is for people
that have already
been there.
Did you mother ever talk to you
about your adolescence?
My adolescence.
Yeah.
A time when you were too young
to remember anything specific.
Where are you going
with this?
I have to know...
do you remember the details
of your car accident?
Well... of course, I do.
I was 13 years old.
They say that I nearly died.
Oh, my God.
Oh, your life was definitely
hanging by a thread.
So I heard.
Yeah. What about
before the accident?
- Anything?
- No.
Why?
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to be odd.
It's the mind of a theologian.
You know, the two most useless
things to a pilot
is the runway behind him
and the sky above him.
I'm just happy that you're home,
and you have a beautiful family
and you're thriving.
Yeah, thank you.
Thank you.
It's, uh...
it's good to be home.
It's just strange
with all this...
sinking in.
There's a lot of memories here.
All these objects.
That must bring back
some pretty strong emotions.
It does.
Um...
please give my regards
to the children, will you?
I most certainly will.
Good, thank you.
Come on, honey.
(air horn blaring)
(no voice)
James?
Are you down there?
James, what were you doing
down there?
Just putting away
my old toys.
Are you okay?
Oh, I'm fantastic.
(curtly)
How are you, honey?
Go upstairs, okay?
All right?
Mommy's got to talk
to daddy.
Danny, mind your mother.
He's a good kid.
You have no idea
what we just saw.
There, there was
this horrible accident,
and everybody...
everybody was dead.
There was blood everywhere,
and then these people
were following us
at the mall, James.
These older people
wouldn't leave us alone...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Where is this going?
What are you talking about?
- Where'd you get that?
- At the newspaper office.
- I thought you went to the mall.
- We did.
Do you recognize this boy?
Not really.
It's Charlie.
And who is that?
Danny's imaginary friend.
Oh, his imaginary friend.
Don't you mean ghost?
Is that what we're
believing in now, is ghosts?
No, damn it, James,
he's not imaginary.
It's true. It's true.
The ghosts, honey?
The ghosts are true?
Does my wife
believe in ghosts now?
Is that what you're trying
to tell me?
'Cause that's bullshit.
It's bullshit.
I was just downstairs,
and I didn't see a thing.
Look, somehow,
he is connected to this house!
Tell you what.
Giving myself a little bit
of a headache.
I'm gonna go lay down
for a little bit.
Try not to stir up any spooks
until I get back.
James, no,
there's something wrong!
Somehow this house is connected
to the disappearances!
Something is wrong!
Something is very wrong!
- I'll tell you what's wrong!
- And I wanna leave!
It's my crazy fucking wife
who is having psychosis
set in right now
when I'm trying to
have buyers come over!
What is wrong with you?!
Oh, my God.
What is... (yelps)
Get your fucking shit together.
(sobs)
Get off of me!
Why?!
(cell phone dials)
God, come on,
pick up the phone.
Hello, this is
Father Donovan O'Malley.
- Hello?
- I'm not available at the moment.
So please leave a message,
and I will get back to you
as soon as I can. Bye.
Father O'Malley, uh...
this is Jennifer.
And I really need
to talk to you.
Oh, my God.
Danny, are you okay?
(cell phone dials)
(cell phone rings)
Hey, girl.
Faith, it's so good
to hear your voice.
Listen, um, I need you
to come here to Cedar Rock Falls
and take Danny
for a couple of days, okay?
What's wrong? Are you okay?
I just, uh...
I need to sort some things out.
I'll explain everything
when you get here, all right?
Yeah, of course.
Whatever you need.
I'll be there
as fast as I can, okay?
I'll see you soon.
Okay.
What about daddy?
He's on his own.
(train whistle blows)
Come on, Danny.
Father? Excuse me.
James and I
have been fighting.
And, uh...
he hit me.
And nothing...
nothing makes sense anymore!
I feel like
I'm losing my mind!
It's like I'm seeing things
that aren't there!
They're not real!
I don't know
what's real anymore.
I just...
I have so many questions.
Did you know
about the missing children?
Yes, I did.
I've got something
for you to play with.
They taste good, too.
Have one.
And you can build things
with them.
Here, right there.
Look at that.
Are you a religious woman,
Jennifer?
Not really.
No?
If you don't believe in God,
wait till you see
your first ghost.
You already have,
haven't you?
Look at this.
Oh.
(sighs)
There were nine of them
in total,
the most innocent children
in the purest sense of the word.
Well, what does this
have to do with James?
James's mother
was a very sick woman.
James's mother?
Yes.
Yeah.
Listen, I can't.
Here, please.
Why not?
I've been
in purgatory too long.
Its guilt rolls downhill
like an avalanche.
The truth shouts,
no matter how long it takes.
We see with our hearts
things that we want to shut out.
We go deaf
rather than listen
to things
we don't want to hear.
As a priest, I made a vow
that the spoken sins of others
would never leave
the confessional.
You understand?
For the sake of my family,
I need you tell me
what's going on.
It's all about
your husband James.
All of it.
James was an angry child.
As a preteen,
James became adept at killing.
First insects,
then small animals.
And then more.
He had a good home,
the church, good family.
It was very hard
to diagnose anything
in those days.
Henry got him the best doctors
he could afford,
but money can't buy you
everything.
And they insisted
on institutionalizing him
to study him.
Nadine wouldn't allow that.
There was an unborn
little brother.
He was the first.
She told Henry that she had
fallen in the kitchen.
Until one day, he finally
witnessed it himself.
It caused him to retreat
into his own hell.
You see, he knew what
little Jimmy had become
and what he had done.
From there on,
life just took a wrong turn.
(gurgles)
(crying)
♪ Hush, little baby,
don't say a word ♪
♪ Mama's gonna buy you
a mockingbird ♪
♪ If that mockingbird
don't sing ♪
♪ Mama's gonna buy you
a diamond ring ♪
♪ If that diamond ring
don't shine ♪
♪ Mama's gonna buy you ♪
♪ A looking glass ♪
They buried the body,
cleaned up the evidence...
and kept him away
from the other children
as best they could.
It's okay, baby.
I'll take care of it.
They went about their lives
as if nothing ever happened.
That was the flame
that lit the fire.
(shovel digging)
Nadine just kept
washing the blood
out of little Jimmy's clothes.
(crying)
And Henry just drank away
his conscience.
Come here.
You come here.
You wanna kill something?
Kill me.
(crying)
When James was 13,
he got hit
by a hit-and-run driver.
It almost killed him.
He was in a coma for months.
When he came
out of the coma,
it was a blessing.
He was a different boy.
He didn't remember
the things he had done.
It was redemption.
It was a divine intervention.
I can't.
I can't anymore.
Gave us the opportunity.
We sent him
to boarding school.
You need to take Danny and find
a safe place for a while.
Danny!
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
We gotta go
We gotta go.
(train whistle blows)
(baby crying)
(crying stops)
Woman: Do you remember
last summer?
Man: Up at the lake? I do.
Woman: And the summer
right after that?
Man: That was nice.
Woman: Yeah.
Woman:
I think about that
almost every single day.
Man: I do, too.
It was great.
You were an angel.
(cell phone beeps)
- Shit!
- (tires screeching)
(gurgles)
(door opens)
Jennifer?
Jennifer, is that you?
No.
Oh, it's you.
Your timing is impeccable.
Seeing you the other day
brought back some fond memories.
Some not so fond.
Amnesia.
It's a double-edged sword.
Your memories must be
flooding back like waves...
some of them frightening.
Some?
All of them.
You...
you were born...
without empathy,
and I am really sorry
for that. So sorry.
Yeah, really?
(mockingly)
You're so sorry.
You think sorry
is gonna fix any of this?
You really think sorry
is enough?
You've caused so much pain...
so much misery.
There will be
no forgiveness for you,
not in this world.
Well, for once,
we actually agree.
(sighs)
So, where do we go
from here?
Because the problem is
you knew.
All along,
you knew what I was doing.
And you knew what I had done.
(sniffles)
You told her, didn't you?
Did you tell her?
Yes.
Wh...
what am I supposed to do now?
James...
Mother should have
had me committed.
She could have done something.
Fucking something!
You all
are just as guilty as I am
because you knew!
You fucking knew!
And you didn't even do
a God damn thing!
I made a vow.
A promise.
Well, you can't
let a bad thing get in the way
of a good thing, right?
Right, Father?
You're picking it up right
where you left off, aren't you?
Make me the last one.
(grunting)
You're just a worthless
piece of shit, just like me.
Just like me.
(groans)
- You still with me, Father?
- (groans)
You still with me?
Yeah, attaboy.
Attaboy,
we're almost done now.
We're almost done now.
Don't you leave me yet.
Don't worry.
The end is nigh.
(shovel digging)
Stay in the car.
Jennifer: James?
(crying)
(purrs, meows)
(meows, purrs)
(mewing)
(yowls, bones crack)
Stop your whining, bitch.
(gunshot)
Subtitles by explosiveskull