(PIGEONS COOING)
(PANTING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
Come on. This way.
(GRUNTS)
(ENGINES REVVING)
Go, go!
(SCREAMS)
Fuck!
(GRUNTING)
Got you! There's nowhere to run!
(LAUGHS)
(GRUNTING)
ANNOUNCER: Welcome, everybody,
to tonight's weighing in!
(CROWD CHEERING)
First up onto the scales,
we have Wes "The Jailor" Baylor!
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
- (CROWD CHEERING)
(CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING)
170! Whoo!
And his opponent, of course,
we cannot forget his opponent.
For he cannot fight this fight
alone in the ring.
Here we go, baby.
- We have Jonny "Solid Gold" Sutherland!
- I'm proud of you.
(CROWD CHEERING)
168.
I'll see you in the ring, motherfucker.
Get ready, 'cause I'm not playing.
I will see you tomorrow night!
Mmm.
ANNOUNCER: What a night.
I've been waiting for this night.
Tension is so high.
You know, Baylor is out to get Sutherland,
and Sutherland is out to get Baylor.
- (BELL DINGING)
- It's just a matter of who wants it more,
Baylor or Sutherland. That's it.
(CROWD CHEERING)
MAN: Come on, use that jab!
ANNOUNCER: Oh, Sutherland gives
a good first kick. Couple of kicks.
Baylor comes back.
He punches, he kicks... Knees!
This is crazy. Yeah. This is starting
faster than I thought it would.
To the legs, to the legs,
and Baylor's on the floor!
Baylor's on the floor.
MAN: Sink it, sink it!
ANNOUNCER: Oh, Baylor...
- (BELL DINGING)
- Baylor's got Sutherland in a headlock.
And the first round is over.
Go back to your corners.
(CROWD CHEERING)
ANNOUNCER: That was charged
with energy, folks.
That was insane. That was crazy.
Here's some water. Come on.
ANNOUNCER: All right, folks, here we go.
Round two, round two.
(BELL DINGING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
COACH 1: Move!
Get in his head.
- Move!
- COACH 2: Come on, Jonny!
COACH 1: Come on, move!
(CROWD CHEERING)
Move!
ANNOUNCER:
He'll try to struggle out of it.
Oh, and Baylor frees himself,
clenches, just missed Sutherland.
Look at these longtime
sparring partners go at each other.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
COACH 1: Stay on him!
ANNOUNCER: Oh, my God!
A roundhouse to Baylor's face!
(BELL DINGING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
REFEREE: Come on.
Back it up. Give him some room.
Get up.
In your corner.
MAN: Yeah, baby!
Don't know about the first,
but you definitely lost the second.
You can't leave it up to the judges, okay?
Remember out there, keep the jab.
Keep the jab always.
Get out there and do your bloody business!
Tell me what I gotta do, man.
Just tell me what I gotta do!
You gotta knock him out.
You gotta take his head off.
Now, get in there!
Come on! Pull it together!
Go!
(BELL DINGING)
MAN: Come on, Wes!
MAN: Hey, hands up! Hands up!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
COACH 1: Finish him, Wes! Finish him!
(GRUNTING)
COACH 1: Put him away, Wes. Put him away!
ANNOUNCER: And Sutherland is down!
COACH 1: Yes, yes!
Come on, Wes!
(CHEERING)
ANNOUNCER: Oh, my God!
And Sutherland is down!
(CROWD CHEERING AND WHISTLING)
Oh, my God. He's still down.
Sutherland is still down.
And he's not even moving.
Oh, my God. Somebody help Sutherland!
Somebody go up...
Wes, help him!
(EXHALES)
Jonny!
(SHOUTING)
JONNY: I just want you to know,
no matter how this turns out,
win or lose, you're family, all right?
You're always gonna be welcome
out at the beach house.
WES: What beach house?
The one I'm gonna buy with the money
I get from kicking your ass.
What if I kick your ass?
Well, then you can buy me the beach house.
This is to remind you of all the time
we spent training for this,
and how it paid off. Jonny.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
KAY: I really don't know how best friends
can do this to each other.
WES: Kay, don't worry about it.
We kick the shit out of each other
in the gym on a daily basis.
The only difference here?
We're gonna get paid for it.
KAY: Wes, Jonny didn't make it. He's dead.
(DOVES COOING)
(COUGHING)
(SNIFFS)
(CROWD CHEERING)
ANNOUNCER: Are you guys ready?
(CROWD CHEERS)
I said, are you guys ready?
(CROWD CHEERS LOUDER)
Fight!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
- Hey. Good to see you.
- You, too.
You having a good night?
Hey, good to see you. Welcome.
I should put you in that fight.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
(SCREAMING)
(LAUGHING)
(PANTING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
You just won me 3,000 bucks.
Already got paid.
(LAUGHS)
Not enough for this shit.
I'm Jonah Aldrich.
I come from a family of fight promoters.
Never heard of you.
I'm not on the MMA circuit,
and neither are you these days.
Look. (CLEARS THROAT)
For what it's worth,
I think it sucks how they treated you.
After Sutherland,
you deserved a title shot.
Wasn't your fault what happened,
yet here you are,
risking your neck for chump change.
It's just not right.
Listen, uh, Mister...
- Aldrich.
I didn't just get the shit kicked out
of me by Bruce Lee over there,
so that you could bullshit me to death.
Want to tell me what it is you want?
I want to give you a second chance.
You want to give me a second chance?
Yeah, I do. (LAUGHING)
I'm putting together something special.
A one-off fight in Myanmar.
Winner takes home half a million.
(CHUCKLES)
- Not interested.
- (LAUGHS)
Really?
And how long is it before
some lunatic comes along
and just caves your head in, huh?
And for what?
A hundred bucks and a shot of tequila.
Actually, it's 400
and two shots of tequila.
One fight.
One last payday, and you're set for life.
Madden, give Mr. Baylor our particulars.
JONNY: You're always gonna be
welcome out at the beach house.
WES: What beach house?
JONNY: The one I'm gonna buy with
the money I get from kicking your ass.
WES: What if I kick your ass?
JONNY:
Well, then you can buy me the beach house.
Best view in Bangkok. Have a seat.
You hungry?
So, are you a fight promoter or a chef?
Sushi requires precision.
It helps me to focus.
Which helps me to relax.
Are you calm and focused, Mr. Baylor?
Because, given your history,
killing your best friend
would destroy most men.
Bury them in guilt and regret.
Man might even try to
get himself killed in the ring
as some sort of sad, pathetic penance.
Are you that kind of a man, Mr. Baylor?
I want one million.
No bullshit gate percentages,
no win-bonuses,
and I want the cash up front.
You like to win, Mr. Baylor?
WES: Sure. Don't you?
Abso-fucking-lutely.
Welcome to the Republic of the Union
of Myanmar, Mr. Baylor.
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
(CHILDREN SCREAMING)
(CAR DOOR SHUTS)
General.
(LAUGHING)
Good to see you.
The Republic of the Union of Myanmar
gratefully accepts your donations.
No worries.
We're just here to help the people.
(CHUCKLING)
Come and meet the gang.
Señor Esparto,
Spain's most celebrated bullfighter.
Killed as much meat as a slaughterhouse.
It will be an honor to see you
in the arena, Mr. Baylor.
The Zimlings from Texas.
Jacob and his son, Tobias.
Here for some father-son bonding.
You're lucky, kid. My dad only
took me to Chuck E. Cheese.
(LAUGHING) Holy shit.
You're Wes Baylor. The Executioner.
Sorry, my ring name was The Jailor.
(LAUGHS) Not after that last fight.
My boy and I were there.
Fuckin' A, let me shake your hand.
(LAUGHS)
We're big fans.
Like I promised, Mr. Zimling.
Only the best.
Miss Sofia, heir to the third-richest
oil baron in the world.
Taking Daddy's lifelong hobby
of big game hunting to the next level.
Bit of a sore subject.
They tell me you like punishment.
Sorry, ma'am. You're not my type.
That's bullshit.
I'm everyone's type.
Landon Marshall.
You probably recognize
the face from Wired magazine.
They called me the Mark Zuckerberg
of the first-person shooter.
I've never heard of you.
Never heard of you either, bro.
- ALDRICH: Where's Maduka?
- Probably sleeping off last night.
Very well. Let's begin.
Begin what?
What exactly is going on here?
Where's the ring?
Where's... Where's the opponent?
Your opponents you've met, and the ring,
well, you're standing in it.
A hundred square miles of jungle.
The purse?
A million dollars' worth of rubies.
You get across the border, they're yours.
Thailand's that way. Due east.
(CHUCKLES)
What is this? Some sort of a joke?
Is there a hidden camera
around here, or...
You signed up for
a no-holds-barred contest,
and that's exactly
what you're going to get.
That's what you're all going to get.
Time to find out where
you are on the food chain.
Choose your weapon!
Hey.
(LAUGHING)
I recommend the crossbow
for the real hunter.
- ALDRICH: And don't worry.
- Hey.
Change your mind later,
there'll be plenty of time.
They'll be following us.
It's all yours.
(SNIFFS)
MADDEN: Yes, sir.
(MADDEN SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
A little demonstration of what lies ahead.
(SPEAKS OTHER LANGUAGE)
(CROSSBOW FIRES)
(GROANS)
That is just a start.
You're facing the ultimate challenge.
Hunting your equal
on the evolutionary scale.
You rise to this challenge,
you'll reach the pinnacle
of satisfaction as a hunter.
Can I get a "Fuck, yeah"?
- ALL: Fuck, yeah!
- (LAUGHS)
(ALDRICH CLICKING TONGUE)
No weapon for you.
Oh, I'm sorry, Mr. Baylor. Madden's right.
But I will give you this.
- A two-minute head start.
- (WATCH BEEPS)
And a water bottle.
Fill it when you can.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
What the hell is wrong with you people?
This isn't a fight. That's murder.
No, it's a hunt.
It's fucking insane.
Ninety seconds.
This is bullshit, Aldrich.
I didn't sign up for this shit.
Find yourself another piece of meat.
I'm out of here.
ALDRICH: You're right about that.
One way or the other, you are out of here.
It's up to you to choose.
Not a lot of choice here.
ALDRICH: Course there is.
You can win, or you can lose.
Oh.
Seventy seconds.
What's the matter?
You need me to ring the bell? Ding-ding.
This will be a good hunt.
Mr. Maduka. So glad you could make it.
Chief Lord Maduka.
My apologies. Chief Lord.
But cameras, cell phones,
any recording devices.
You know the rules.
(GROANS) No calls, just a few snaps?
Take a mental picture, Mr. Marshall.
You're about to join
a very exclusive club.
We don't just share this with anyone.
Besides, what you're about to experience
can't be captured on camera.
You're gonna let it live in here forever.
(LAUGHING)
SOFIA: Jesus, ladies.
You want to fuck or hunt?
Let's go! (LAUGHS)
ALDRICH: Get him!
(PANTING)
Damn, you are in great shape.
You CrossFit? Spinning?
Krav Maga? That's my jam.
Excuse me while I get my heart rate up.
The pressure getting to you, kid?
Why don't you shut the fuck up, old man?
A hundred miles due east, huh?
Fuck you, Aldrich.
North border's only 40.
He's run flat out for a mile,
knows we're right behind him.
Probably doesn't like
his chances out in the open.
Try to get in his head.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Clever lad.
(GUNSHOT)
Who's missing?
Maduka.
Shit.
(PANTING)
Fuck!
(GRUNTING)
Please, please! Please stop!
Seriously?
You like my little toy, huh?
I make it special for monkeys like you.
(PANTING)
ESPARTO: When we step into the arena,
we don't always step out.
Not so noble now, Chief Lord.
ALDRICH: They're called
hard targets for a reason.
Jesus.
For the first time you're hunting
something as smart as you are.
(SCOFFS) Doubt that.
ALDRICH: Baylor won't be an easy kill.
As it should be.
Lady and gentlemen, all bets are off.
From now on, watch your backs.
And I guarantee one of you will be wearing
his balls for breakfast by sundown.
(COUGHING)
Wipe your goddamn mouth.
(PANTING)
(WHISTLING)
This way!
Stay alert. He's close.
Shit.
(CROSSBOW CLICKS)
ALDRICH: Target's in sight!
We have the high ground!
(GRUNTING)
Man has hunted every
species on the planet.
What makes you better than him, huh?
It is time to find out!
(GRUNTS)
JACOB: Fuck this bow-and-arrow shit.
Like shootin' fish in a barrel, Baylor!
(GRUNTING)
Try this!
(LAUGHS)
Now you're talking.
It's Christmas!
Come on, let's go. Let's go. Fuck!
(GRUNTS)
(ELEPHANTS TRUMPETING)
(GASPING)
You want to fight these elephants?
He threw the first punch.
You fell in their bath and scared them.
I saw the whole thing.
You working for Aldrich?
Who's Aldrich?
(PANTING)
Forget about it.
Shit!
Hey, you see a watch around here anywhere?
(THA SPEAKS OTHER LANGUAGE)
Here you go.
Thanks.
What are you doing out here?
Some people are hunting me.
My brother was being hunted, too.
Win.
Have you seen him?
WES: No.
I'm sorry.
I have to get to the border.
The border's not that way.
Just follow me.
(ELEPHANTS TRUMPETING)
Baylor is good. I'll give him that.
Yeah. Maybe too good.
Hey, perhaps we could
take a short break, huh?
Fuck that. I'll kill him myself.
I realize you didn't pay
good money to run a jungle 5K.
You're here to hunt.
But even good hunters
need their trusted steeds!
(LAUGHING) Hey! Now you're talking.
Come on.
How do you know where we're going?
Everything looks the same to me.
My brother and I grew up here.
That's how we got involved in all of this.
Got involved in what?
They told him he was doing a drug run.
Then he disappeared.
When someone in our village disappears,
we know they're being used in a game.
So how are you here?
WES: I'm a fighter.
They told me there was gonna be a fight.
Fight turned out to be a hunt.
My brother's a good fighter, too.
He fights for me and our village.
Well, the best fighters always
have something to fight for.
What is your something?
(WHIRRING)
I love it when they take the temple route.
MADDEN: Where did he pick up the girl?
I don't know.
Let's see if we can charge extra for her.
(LAUGHS)
Tell the gang there's another target.
Which way now?
Through the old
temple grounds, over there.
Then we follow the train tracks
and the river for a long time
before we get to the border.
Okay.
Train tracks, river, all the way to
the border. Thank you. Sorry, I...
I didn't get your name.
Tha.
Tha? I'm Wes.
All right, cool. Thank you.
Thank you very much for your help,
and good luck finding your brother.
I'm gonna make my own way now.
Tha, listen.
Your life is going to be a lot safer
without me in it. Trust me.
(ENGINES REVVING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
I'll lead them away. Hide!
(PANTING)
I saw the girl.
We'll have to go on foot to get her.
Hey. I love this.
(LAUGHS)
You think it's a good idea
to leave the bike?
Shit. Dad.
I can smell her.
(LAUGHS)
What are you doing?
I saw someone.
There's no one there.
- (PANTING) Yeah.
- You fuckin' clown.
Ow. You think I'm crazy?
JACOB: She's up ahead.
I hate the fucking jungle!
(GRUNTING)
Little bitch.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Won't be needing that anymore.
You like the rough stuff, do you? So do I.
Trouble is, you can
never get enough of it.
I don't want anything to do with this.
Tobias. Tobias!
Where the hell are you going?
Get back here, you pussy! Tobias!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
JACOB: Tobias! Tobias!
(THA SCREAMING)
What the hell is wrong with you, lady?
There are infinite
privileges and side effects
to being the only child
of one of the greatest assholes
in the history of big game hunting.
(YELLING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
All the time and resources to train
your mind and body for combat.
I just hoped that the day might come
that I get to hunt the hunter.
Oh, so, that's what this is about.
Daddy issues, huh?
Why don't you just get yourself
a sparring partner?
(CHUCKLES)
Because it doesn't count
unless the hunt is real.
That real enough for you?
(MOTORCYCLE APPROACHING)
Not good, fuck! Not good.
Not good. Not good. (GRUNTS)
(THA SCREAMING)
Tha!
He's dead.
Come on, let's go.
Come on.
Karma's a bitch.
Cover him. This is not good for business.
ESPARTO: He's awake.
- He's awake.
- No.
(GRUNTING)
What happened?
I don't know.
SOFIA: The woman.
She did this.
You let a girl do this to your father?
How could you, huh?
(GRUNTS)
Your father spent a small fortune
so you could grow some balls,
and that's exactly what you're
gonna do, right here, right now.
You want to kill these people?
No, no. I don't want to kill anyone.
Say it.
- I want to kill them.
- Louder.
- I want to kill...
- Louder!
I want to kill them!
- Like you mean it!
- (SCREAMS)
I want to kill them.
That's good.
Hey, maybe...
Maybe we should head back, huh?
SOFIA: Yeah, that's right.
Why don't you run home to Mommy?
We came here chasing death.
We should not be surprised if we find it.
You're wrong, sir.
We did not come here to chase death.
We came to deal it.
(BOTH PANTING)
Come on, we gotta keep moving.
I didn't want to kill him.
WES: You didn't have a choice.
No. We always have a choice.
Look, you got two choices, all right?
Either you fight,
or you stay here and you die.
What's it gonna be?
Good choice.
(GRUNTS)
You're hurt.
- That needs to be treated.
- Yeah, with what?
Let's go.
I know a place.
Ah, shit.
Show me your wound.
What are you going to do with your money?
I'm gonna buy a big house by the sea.
I'm trying to buy a whole village.
Yeah?
Did everybody leave?
The soldiers told us they needed the land.
But one of the soldiers
was from a nearby village.
Told us that hunters had paid the General
to clear out this entire area.
So, they moved us to a border town.
It's awful there.
No way to make offerings
to the forest spirit.
So, she's become very hungry.
And very angry.
Now that Y'wa is fed,
we will suffer no more.
She'll return my brother
and village to me.
Come.
Show some respect.
ALDRICH: You got a position, yet?
Two klicks over that ridge.
Good. Get the kids.
Team!
(PANTS)
Okay, great.
So, what, we follow the road now?
No, we go through this field. See?
Down the river and further down
is the bridge to the border.
Come on, let's go.
What's that smell?
THA: What?
WES: Smells like gasoline.
(FLIES BUZZING)
Land mines.
- What?
- Don't move!
WES: Shit.
(VEHICLES APPROACHING)
Grab a drink if you need one!
Get down.
They're here already?
Get back there.
Come on.
That's right.
Come on in, you bastards.
(GRUNTING)
There!
Here we go.
Stop! Everybody freeze!
You've cornered your prey.
He's in the minefield, stuck, nowhere to go.
Checkmate.
All that remains is target practice.
Break out the M16s.
(CLATTERING)
- Hey, no, no, no! Tobias, wait!
- Die, motherfucker!
ALDRICH: Wait!
(GUNSHOT)
(GROANING)
Fuck!
God damn it! Somebody kill this prick!
(BOTH PANTING)
You want to die?
Get out of here.
Leave me alone. Run!
Pretty soon, they're
gonna find me, all right?
And when they do, you shouldn't be here.
Now, go!
I'm not leaving.
I know a good hiding place.
- (COUGHING)
- THA: Wait, did you hear that?
- Someone else is here.
- (GROANING)
(GROANING)
THA: Win?
(EXHALES) Win.
Tha! Tha.
(GROANING)
WIN: (PANTING) Who are you?
- What are you doing with him?
- No, it's okay.
He's one of them!
Take it easy, man. Take it easy.
I'm not one of them, all right?
I'm in the same position you are.
It's okay, trust me.
We can trust him. Okay?
Those guys are hunting me as well.
THA: Just trust me. It's okay.
Okay.
It's okay.
MADDEN: This way.
Tracks lead down here.
What's wrong?
(SIGHS) I've lost the tracks.
I lost the signal.
Fuck.
I'll handle this.
Let's make camp here, everyone.
Why do you care so much about that watch?
A friend gave it to me.
Reminds me of something.
Something good?
Not really.
Here. Let me take a look.
Tomorrow, we cross the border.
Then what?
Then I'll leave you.
That's what you want, right?
You should get some sleep.
Good night, Tha.
LANDON: Kind of burnt.
What is this? Fucking summer camp?
(EXHALES)
So, Aldrich, how'd you get into this
business, if you don't mind me asking?
CIA didn't have much appreciation
for my talents.
Said I was too theatrical.
- Can you believe that?
- (CHUCKLES)
So, I came up with my own business.
Hunting with a twist.
Turned into international success.
The General was escorting rebels
in the Yangon prison.
I suggest he help us hunt.
He bites.
I mean, prisoners
are gonna die anyway, right?
So, why not have some fun?
They let them loose in the jungle,
we acted as trackers,
grew the business from there.
So, the money's good?
MADDEN: Yeah.
Killing's better.
Didn't get your fill in the military, huh?
I was never in the service.
Didn't make the psych evaluation.
Pussies thought I was too crazy.
Well, they weren't wrong.
No. No, no. No.
Jonny.
(PANTING) Jonny! No!
Wes!
(ECHOING) Jonny!
- (GRUNTS)
- THA: Be quiet!
Who's Jonny?
Jonny was my best friend.
We were both in line
for a shot at the title.
They wanted us to fight each other.
Offered us more money
than we'd ever known,
so we did.
I wanted to win.
And I didn't want to leave it
in the hands of the judges,
so I went for the knockout.
I hit him so hard, he never woke up.
It was an accident.
You didn't mean for it to happen.
(EXHALES)
But it still happened.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Tha?
Oh, shit.
ALDRICH: Nice to see you again, Win.
How appropriate we caught you both
at this particular place.
The Japanese killed nearly
100,000 workers building this railroad.
Starvation,
exhaustion, dysentery.
Plenty of them got beaten to death.
Where's Wes Baylor?
I killed him.
For the rubies.
ALDRICH: You killed him?
(CHUCKLES)
- (GRUNTS)
- No, he was asleep.
I don't buy it.
(GRUNTS)
THA: Please!
Please.
Please!
Help!
(THA SCREAMING)
- (MUFFLED SCREAMING)
- (SHUSHING)
Shut up. Shut up.
I didn't kill anybody.
I'm just a shitty video game designer.
Please don't kill me.
ALDRICH: The Japanese killed nearly
100,000 workers building this railroad.
Starvation. Exhaustion.
- Move.
- Yeah.
I saw a Burmese soldier do this.
Just a length of bamboo.
Took him only four shots
to get clean through the neck.
I don't think you'll last two.
THA: Don't! Stop!
Don't do it!
Stop it.
Where's Baylor?
THA: Please! Stop it!
No! Please!
WES: Aldrich!
(PANTING)
Let 'em go.
What do you care about them?
They took your payday.
Yeah, I'm taking it back.
Cut 'em loose.
(GUN COCKS)
Cut 'em loose and back up,
or I'll blow his fuckin' head off!
Let me take him.
ALDRICH: No. You'll only kill Marshall.
So what?
It's bad enough for business
losing clients to Baylor.
It'd be a fucking catastrophe
if we start shooting them ourselves.
Cut 'em loose.
Give her the rubies.
(PANTING)
Wes.
Save it. Get behind me.
ALDRICH: Now what, Baylor?
Got you backed into a corner.
You got nowhere to go.
Come on, dude. Game over.
Please, just let me go.
You and Win, go on, go.
No.
I'll hold 'em off, and then...
Then I'll jump.
Go!
- Move!
- (GRUNTS)
SOFIA: Where's Baylor?
I got this.
Sorry.
(GRUNTING)
Meet me at the river.
I will never tell you.
Oh, I think you will.
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (GUNSHOT)
WIN: Wes, come here!
Win!
(GASPING)
Ay.
Not good.
(ALDRICH EXHALES)
(CHUCKLING) This guy is...
THA: Sorry about before.
Don't do that again. It's crazy.
(PANTING)
The rubies.
(PANTING) Found Sofia.
(SPEAKS OTHER LANGUAGE)
Fuck.
At least we know where they're going.
They're called hard targets for a reason.
First time you're hunting
something as smart as you are.
Baylor won't be a...
I don't blame you for being angry.
When I save your ass, you rob me blind?
We had no choice.
We always have a choice.
The rubies aren't for me.
They're for my village.
If I pay the General, he'll let us
return home. They'll stop hunting us.
That's why I took the rubies.
How am I supposed to know
you're telling the truth?
You can't.
But you can choose to.
You get me to the border,
we'll call it quits.
LANDON: Look, man.
I'm not even a hunter. I'm a gamer.
Just give me back my phone.
I'll call my assistant,
have someone pick me up.
(CLEARS THROAT) The memory card's missing.
Where did this come from?
I have no idea.
It must be that woman, or someone.
Really?
A poor villager in bamboo flip-flops
can afford a $1,000 minicam?
I told you, Mr. Marshall,
no phones, no cameras.
No recording devices.
Yeah, we cleared that up, remember?
Like you said, I'm gonna carry it here,
in my heart,
and my heart is full of the...
- What did you film?
- I didn't film anything!
No, stop! Okay, look.
It was a few POV shots,
first-person-shooter stuff.
Of us?
You filmed us?
I was stuck on my new game.
- The pressure to deliver is fucking insane.
- (LAUGHS)
And the critics, man,
thirteen-year-olds are harsh.
I just... I needed some new inspiration.
Look, I know I screwed up,
I'm really sorry.
Do you understand the concept
of a verbal contract?
We can get that card back.
You guys are badasses.
It's binding.
And actionable.
- (GRUNTS)
- (GAGGING)
Congratulations, Señor Esparto.
You're our last hunter.
Let's bag that target. Signal's back.
- Let's see where they are.
- (DEVICE BEEPING)
He's almost at the border.
Wait. You had this all along?
You're tracking with this?
(SWEARING IN SPANISH) You have no honor.
- Ah, give me a break.
- Ah.
Trying to contain a situation,
you dumb, spic bastard.
(GRUNTS)
Easy, amigo. Back off.
Did something get lost in translation?
Mr. Marshall brought in a recording device.
Baylor's got the footage.
Footage that might not sit too well
with your fans back home, or Interpol.
So, do you want honor,
or do you want Baylor?
Nobody calls me a spic. I'm a dago.
(SPEAKING IN SPANISH)
We can't let Baylor get to the border.
Call in the cleanup crew.
- You think we need them?
- Call them!
(GRUNTS)
Shit, we can't pass here.
Follow me. Ready? Come on.
Stay low.
(VEHICLES APPROACHING)
(BEEPING)
How the hell did they find us again?
Wait a minute.
They lost us when we went
in that cave, right?
And they found you two when you
went outside with the rubies.
We never even had a chance, then.
We don't.
But you do.
I'm gonna hang on to this.
ALDRICH:
GPS says he's around here somewhere.
You two get to the border.
(PANTING)
You make him pay.
Why would you do this for us?
I guess I finally found
what I'm fighting for.
Go.
Go on.
They've got to be here.
(ENGINE STARTS)
What the fuck? Get him!
ALDRICH: Stop him!
He cannot reach the border!
No, no, no. I got you.
Take him out, right now.
You hear what I'm saying?
General wants to talk to you.
(SHOUTS)
Guess you want me to call for a boat.
No. Something better.
I see you, yes. I'm coming for you.
I can see the look in your eyes.
You remind me of a famous
Navarra bull. Murcielago.
He survived 24 strikes of my lance.
Come on.
Come on!
(YELLING)
Win!
Still on the move.
Keep on your right.
Bring it around again!
He fought with such spirit
that the crowd called
for his life to be spared.
But sadly for you,
there is no crowd here today.
(GROANING)
- (SPEAKING IN SPANISH)
- THA: No!
(GRUNTING)
(WIN GAGGING)
He's almost at the border.
I don't think we can get him in time.
ALDRICH: Ah, it's a long walk to
the other side. Anything can happen.
Let the troops know.
Tell them to stop them
from getting to the Thai side.
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
(GUNFIRE)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
I ain't no bull.
(GRUNTS)
You son of a bitch.
(GAGGING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BOTH PANTING)
Wes.
- Keep him on the right.
- (GUNFIRE)
On the right. Don't lose his ass!
(SOLDIER YELLS)
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
Get us on that bridge!
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
Fuck you, Aldrich. I win. (GRUNTS)
Baylor!
Wrong side of the bridge. Tough break.
Guess you'll have to come through me.
We'd like to invite you to join us
for a party in your honor!
No regrets, please.
Shit.
This was meant for you.
Come on.
Aldrich! Let him go!
And if I don't?
They're called hard targets for a reason.
You know what?
You look great in HD, Aldrich.
Really captures what a prick you are.
(ALDRICH WHISTLES)
You have something that belongs to me.
False sense of superiority?
Memory card. Where is it?
Ah, that.
Yeah, it's safe.
It's up my ass.
Well, let me help you extract it.
(GRUNTING)
You know, I know you're not
that bright, Madden,
but you do realize that wasn't my ass.
I'm not the man you insult.
I just can't tell what kind
of man you are, Baylor.
(CHUCKLES)
So, I've been crawling,
rattling around in my brain,
and then I suddenly realized,
you are just a nobody.
- You're just some savage animal.
- (CHUCKLES)
I mean, what you did to your best friend.
Leaving a son without his father,
his wife a widow.
I mean, if it was up to me,
I'd go out of my mind.
Hell, I would just die.
I wouldn't be able to...
(GRUNTING)
Stop it. That's what he wants.
That's exactly what he wants.
Death's just not enough for you, is it?
You want to go out like your friend,
like a warrior.
Just give me what I want,
and I'll be happy to oblige.
No more shame, no more guilt.
Unless, of course,
you don't have the card.
You gave it to the girl.
Then I'll hunt her down.
But first, you know what?
I think I deserve a little entertainment.
Did you bring the beer?
You know, Baylor, I am going to enjoy
watching you get your ass kicked.
Thanks.
So, I brought five friends.
Let's see how they rip you apart
with their bare hands.
One, two, three, four guys
and a little girl? (CHUCKLES)
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHING)
Not you. Not yet.
You know, you were
right about me, Aldrich.
I was a nobody.
No shot at redemption.
Not until you came along.
Hell, son, you're welcome.
Praise Jesus, you're saved.
Fighting spirit's back, huh?
You gave me something to fight for.
Now.
What do you say, Baylor?
Don't pussy out on me now.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Not bad, Baylor.
I thought you wouldn't have anything left.
God damn, Baylor. You're the man.
(MADDEN GRUNTING)
It's a shame to have to put you down.
- (GRUNTING)
- (GUN FIRES)
Wes!
Don't do it!
You know how this works, Aldrich.
You get a two-minute head start.
Get up.
Get up!
(GRUNTS)
Ninety seconds.
Sixty seconds!
(LAUGHING)
You're gonna have to kill me, Baylor.
'Cause I have friends.
Rich, powerful friends.
You think you can hunt me?
Who the hell do you think you are?
You lose.
General. Kill that asshole.
THA: Wait!
Wait! Wait!
General. I have the money.
(BAG UNZIPPING)
Lower your weapons.
(PANTING)
- What did you just say?
- It's okay.
ALDRICH: General.
General, you dirty motherfucker!
Shoot him!
(BOTH PANTING)
Thank you.
So, you paid the General?
Yes.
Thanks to you,
he's letting us get back our lives.
Return to our village.
As long as we help him
look for the missing rubies.
What missing rubies?
The ones you lost in the jungle.
Oh, you only gave him half?
(CHUCKLES)
You're a good man, Wes.
Get that house by the sea.
(CHILDREN SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
KAY: I hope you don't blame yourself
for what happened.
Fighters fight.
What's important is finding
something to fight for.
You asked for my forgiveness,
but I'm afraid I can't give it to you,
because there is nothing to forgive.
Thank you for what you've done for us.
Love, Kay.
P. S. We're still gonna keep
the beach house, though.
WES: As I said before,
pushing off the back leg,
twisting, kicking with the shin.
Twist all the way around.
So, remember to twist that hip
all the way to the front.
Twist the hip.
I guess it's break time, guys.
The boss says it's break time.
Twist. See the hip? All the way around.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)