[Theme music]
NARRATOR: My name is Aaron,
and the study of man's past
Has always fascinated me.
So much so that I made
it my life's work.
You see, I've always had this
desire to shape the way we look
At our past because our lives
seem so short... like we're just
So many points of
light, fighting it out
Within some vast
and utter darkness.
It all started
peacefully enough.
I'd earned a postgraduate
scholarship in history,
And was working as a
general teaching assistant
For the summer schedule.
Earlier that morning,
I was informed
That one of our faculty
had suffered a stroke.
At the time, I was
really excited.
All my hopes and dreams,
once far off and frustrated,
Now seemed possible,
provable, within reach.
My main goal in life
was to solve the mystery
Surrounding America's
first documented,
Tried and convicted cannibal.
The man I had based my
entire master's thesis
And professional career around.
In life, his name
was Alferd Packer.
In death, as in life,
great controversy
Always surrounded Packer.
Even on his headstone, a
misguided mason's sense
For proper English
misspelled his name
As Alfred for all eternity.
But many skeptics,
including myself,
Questioned if it
really was Packer dead
And buried there in that grave.
Packer journeyed into
Colorado at the height
Of the Gold Rush ear.
As a kid growing up
back there, I'd heard
Many ghost stories about him.
In the winter of 1874, he
led an ill-fated expedition
Of gold miners into
Slumgullion Pass, where
He killed and ate all
of them, before stealing
Away with their gold.
Packer was caught, trying
to cash in his stolen
Gold at an Indian trading
post, but he claimed
He knew the whereabouts of a
huge motherload for the West,
And vowed that no jail
could keep him from it.
One night, he vanished.
The story was, they
brought back the wrong man
Who took the blame for
Packer, but was eventually
Even pardoned by the governor.
I thought if there was
any truth to these tales,
I'd be able to chart the
ancient path of his travelings
By researching the archivals
of various county coronorers,
Due west of Colorado.
You see, Packer
allegedly murdered
My great-great grandfather
on his way west,
And I eventually
was able to track
Down old gramps' gravesite.
I figured I'd like to
do the same for Packer.
No one knew exactly
where he had ended up,
But I was determined
to find out the truth.
I did my research mostly
by facts, and a modem
To my computer.
Finally, I found a nearly
complete ring of locations
About five miles
in circumference
Near a place called Miller's
Pass in Southern California.
With a little more
documentation,
I could ensure myself academic
fame and tenure for life.
But some of the tales I heard
seemed more than far-fetched.
They were on a scale that was
almost biblical in proportion,
And they really made me laugh.
Especially the one about
Packer meeting the devil down
In those deep, dark mine shafts
where they made a blood pact...
A pact that allowed
Packer keep his soul,
Live forever, and own more
gold than he could have spend.
Well, like many deals, it wasn't
all that it seemed at first,
And it went badly for Packer.
Being so close to
the gates of hell,
The devil took him
there for a short visit,
Where he crucified him.
After that, according
to the legend,
He put what was left of Packer
back on Earth, doomed to hunger
Only for human flesh,
and the gold in the earth
Forever... or at least
until judgment day.
After all, a deal's a deal.
Since I knew the professor
wouldn't be coming back
That semester, I figured
I'd surprise the class
With a new assignment,
and be on the trail
Before anyone could object.
This is Miller's
Pass, and this was
Alferd Packer, just before his
infamous mining extradition.
Many claim they
caught the wrong man.
And then, in 1890...
Along a 20-mile stretch
Of canyons and
deserts, a new darkness
Spread across the land.
The land was turned
into a graveyard.
[Ominous music]
A killing ground for
a savage murderer,
Who dispatched his victims with
one powerful blow of a pick.
Described as a monster,
a pure force of evil,
The likes of which have never
been seen again to this day.
Alfred E. Packer slaughtered
over 40 men and women
During his reign of terror.
The deranged miner's
insatiable appetite for blood
Was surpassed only by his
lust for gold, vowing he
We would never let his body
be laid to rest till he
Had struck the mother load.
Any questions?
Yeah, I got a question.
Who the hell are you?
Me?
I'm your worst nightmare.
I'm a teacher's
assistant, with the power
To flunk you boneheads.
When your professor
had a stroke,
I was assigned to give
you a final project
To help you pass this course.
So I've taken it upon
myself to organize
A little anthropological
expedition
To search for this legendary
corpse of Alferd Packer.
And you all are coming with me.
We're going to have so much fun.
Oh, it is too late
to drop this course.
[Flies buzzing]
[Eerie music]
AARON (SINGING):
Who's crying now?
Are you crying now?
Are you?
Hi.
Hi, have a seat.
That was nice.
Did you write it yourself?
Yeah, a long time ago.
So, why are you
out here, Aaron?
Aren't you tired?
I think I should be
asking you the same thing.
Why aren't you up there,
cold, back there with all
The rest of your classmates?
What, with those light-weights?
Are you kidding?
They were asleep before
we even got to camp.
Maybe we should slow
down just a tad, huh?
Maybe a tad bit.
Tara, wake up.
Tara!
What?
Laura and Aaron are missing.
Who?
Geez, go to sleep.
We've got to find them.
Oh, oh, OK.
I'll catch up to you.
Tara, come on, this is serious.
What do you want
me to do about it?
We've got to find them.
You don't seem like
a night person to me.
Are you kidding?
I love the night.
I love everything
about the night.
You know, when I was in school
and I was having a hard time
Doing a term paper, I used
to set my alarm for 3 o'clock
In the morning.
I'd get up, go out on the porch
at my dorm, and just sit there,
Staring off into the night.
I found myself
doing the same thing
When school was out at home.
Getting up at 3
o'clock in the morning,
Going out, lounging
out on the chair
On my parents' front lawn...
Just staring out into the night.
Parents didn't know
what to think of me.
Got to be pretty good friends
with the milk man, though.
HOLLY: Where did she go?
What?
Is their stuff still there?
HOLLY: Yeah.
Well, maybe they
just went for a walk.
HOLLY: In the
middle of the night?
Come on, you guys.
[Booming]
What the hell is that sound?
This trip isn't about books or
graphs, or about taking notes.
It's about getting
out of the classroom,
Getting away from the computer.
Getting out here.
You know?
Experiencing things first-hand.
Sharing things with others,
sharing your observations.
HOLLY: Well, looks like I'm
going to have to do it myself.
Weasels.
No one talks anymore.
How's this?
VOICE: Help!
I'm down here!
Help!
Please, help me, please,
somebody, I'm down here!
Please help me!
I'm down here, please!
I'm down here, somebody
help me, I'm trapped!
Down here!
Someone help me, please!
Help me, please!
Please help me!
He's coming, help me!
Please, please, he's coming!
[Screaming]
Goose behind you!
You little creep.
Mom gets harder.
Move that.
Cut it out, I'll smack you.
Cut it out.
Hey, stop screwing around.
What?
Yeah, right.
She started it.
Big puss.
You got crap on your back.
Cut it out.
Wow.
Hey, you guys.
Look at this bone?
Yeah, Laura, remind
you of anything?
Howdy.
You're trespassing, boy.
Yeah, we were just on
our way to Miller's Pass,
Do a little prospecting.
You look more like
city folk, to me.
Lost your way.
We thought we could
spend the night here.
Warm weather brings your kind.
Mostly undesirables.
You're not much better
than the trash you leave.
Well, you won't have
any... any sort of problem
Like that with us, sir.
I know I won't.
Ah, look, if you're
going to spend the night,
There's one thing I
want to warn you about.
A long time ago, there
was a field hospital here,
And they took every precaution
to fix people up and send
Them back to work in the mine.
At one time there was this
guy, he had gallstone problem,
So they figured they take out
the gallstones right here.
So just before
they put him under,
They figured, they just tell
him, you know, reassure him,
OK, he's going to be all right.
OK, he was fine.
He went under.
And after the
surgery, guy came to.
And they told him he had a very
successful liver operation.
Well, he was so upset,
he went instantly crazy.
He was supposed to have
his gallstones out.
And this guy, got up
off the operating table.
He just looked around, he
killed everybody in the room.
And he just ran out of room.
Nobody saw him again.
But after that, the patients
in some of the other tents,
They could swear the flap of
the tent would just open up,
And they'd see an image
of somebody coming in,
Come over and start to peel
back the sheets a little bit.
And all they could hear is
somebody saying, my liver!
I want my liver!
Where's my liver!
[Laughing]
They fell for it!
Oh, god, you fell for it.
Everyone one of you fell for it.
Hey, you know what?
I had a lot of fun.
You know what?
Let me see if I can work up
a good puss pocket for you.
No, listen, listen...
Have you ever heard
Of the legend of Alferd Packer?
Alferd Packer?
What do you want to
know about him for?
Hey... what's with you anyway?
You're not prospectors.
You came up here looking for
something else, didn't you?
No, no, no... I just heard
that he was buried up here.
Uh-uh... no, uh-uh.
You go messing with the dead,
you go messing with Packer,
You're in trouble.
I mean it.
Something bad's going to happen.
No, it's not that at all.
It's just that one of us last
night, traveling in our party,
Said she saw a
light, or something.
And we can't find her now.
[Inaudible]
No, uh-uh.
Forget it.
She's as good as dead.
She's probably dead by now.
The same thing's going to
happen to you... or worse.
Just get out of here.
Get off my land.
I mean, get all your stuff.
Come on, come on, here.
Get this thing.
You, too.
Come on.
Get out of here.
There's something wrong.
Just get out of here, I mean it.
Something... oh, you
have no idea the trouble
You've made for yourself!
You have no idea!
Aaron, I thought you said
there was someplace out here
We could get help.
I did.
This is it.
What is it?
This.
I think the answer's here.
Are you joking?
This is not happening.
Holly is gone.
This whole field trip is over.
Don't you think I know that?
Aaron, we have to get to
the police to get some help.
The police are three days back.
Well then, we'd
better start now.
You know, sometimes when
you're out here like this,
You have to rely
on other sources.
What are you trying to say?
This path is sacred ground.
With all your help,
a little luck,
We might be able to
find out some answers
About what happened to Holly.
Well, what are you getting at?
I'm talking about
speaking with the dead.
I'll just wait for
you guys out here.
This is it.
All right guys, take your stuff
off, don't bring it in here.
Ooh.
Aaron, what are you doing?
I think he's been out
in the sun too long.
Tara, Tara come here.
It's due west, the color black.
I like black, black's cool.
Like we care.
Rebirthing,
transformation, death.
The sign of the east,
stand right here.
Illumination, the rising sun...
I got your rising
sun right here.
Sacred cloud.
Right here, here, right there.
That's it.
It's the sign of the...
Sign of the south.
That will be the north.
Strong noises right here.
OK, all right.
I think we're ready.
Everybody sit down.
In the dirt?
Yes, in the dirt.
Put your legs out in the center.
Connect hands, form a circle.
Get comfortable.
Right, under, over.
Relax.
Take a deep breath.
Feel the energy from
one hand to another.
[Thunder]
Keep your arms on the rock.
Think of where you
last saw Holly.
[Wind blowing]
[Howling]
[Whispering]
[Distant screaming]
Wake up.
Come on you guys, wake up.
[Ominous music]
Wake up, you guys!
[Eerie piano music]
Come on, you guys.
Hey, where's Tara?
I don't know.
Aaron?
Hey, Aaron.
I'm just going to
go find her, OK?
Wait, wait, wait...
I'll go with you.
HOLLY: Come on.
Tara.
Holly?
Hello?
Come on, Tara.
[Eerie piano music]
[Drumming]
Tara!
Hey... wow, look at this mine.
You don't think she...
Wussy.
Tara!
Tara?
Are you coming?
Come on.
Forget it.
Nuh-huh.
No way.
Hey!
Laura, Laura, come back!
[Flies buzzing]
Ah, damn.
Stupid.
Laura!
[Buzzing]
HOLLY: Tara, come on.
Holly?
Oh... Laura?
Oh, god.
Tara!
Hey you guys!
Laura!
Curtis!
Whew... god, it smells.
[Grunting] Damn!
Stupid class.
Oh, something died in here.
That's it... when I see
Aaron... this stuff is way
Beyond the course description.
Aaron's girlfriend... she
never liked me, anyway.
Should've took that
dance elective.
[Flies buzzing]
[Gagging]
LAURA: What is this?
[Flies buzzing]
Somebody lives here?
[Music grows louder]
HOLLY: Come on.
Laura?
HOLLY: Tara?
It looks like s...
[Gasps]
[Gasp]
Wait till Aaron sees this.
[Roaring]
HOLLY: Tara, this is serious.
[Moaning]
[Screaming]
Tara?
Is that you?
[Gasping]
[Coughing]
[Growling]
Laura, is that you?
Tara?
What the...
[Screaming]
[Panting]
Oh, god!
Help!
How do I get out of here?
It's a rat trap!
[Choking]
[Crashing]
[Whimpering]
[Screaming]
[Crying]
[Boiling water]
[Roaring]
[Clanging]
[Screaming]
Hey, hey, hey!
It's me, it's all right.
Laura, it's me, it's Aaron.
It's all right.
What is happening?
I don't know.
[Whimpering]
It's OK.
He hurt me, so bad.
We've got to get out of here.
Can you walk?
Oh, I think so.
OK, hang on to me.
OK, ready?
This way.
You're going to be OK.
I hope there's a way out.
Oh, god.
Don't worry about it.
Don't think about it.
God, oh, god.
[Rumbling]
Come on, this way.
I think I hear something.
[Panting]
LAURA: I tried to
pray... [echo] Couldn't
Think of any prayer [echo].
Mother used to always
say if I needed
Something, to ask our Lady.
Christ couldn't
refuse his mother.
I don't even know how
to ask her. [Echo]
[Drums]
Oh, Aaron!
What is it?
Shh.
[Gong]
[Drums]
Ssh, now calm down.
Do me a favor, you
just stay here.
I'm going to go down there
and search out what that is.
I will be right back.
No!
- It's all right.
- No!
Stay here.
[Crying]
[Gong]
Listen, I won't let
anything happen to you.
I will be right back, I promise.
OK?
Oh, be careful.
Be careful.
Shh.
[Animal noises]
[Grunting]
[Crackling]
[Gong]
Oh, my god!
Cindy!
Cindy, come on, it's OK!
It's all right!
[Screaming]
What is happening?
He's coming!
[Screaming]
Let's go!
Come on!
[Gong]
Aaron, what is it?
[Screams]
It's OK.
No, Curtis.
[Drums]
[Crying]
[Screaming]
Aaron!
[Whimpering]
[Screaming]
[Roaring]
[Chewing]
[Music]
[Coughing]
[Tapping]
What's this?
Watch your head.
Cover your head.
[Panting]
A nugget of gold.
Stop it.
You're doing it all wrong.
You gotta time it
with the picking.
The picking, the picking, OK?
Come on.
Pick, pick, pick.
OK, on three.
One, two, three.
Come on, listen, listen.
Pick, pick, pick, OK on
three... one, two, three.
One more, one more, shh, shh...
Listen.
One, two, three.
Come on, come on, wait, come on.
We can't fit through there.
Laura, you have to go.
Yes, you do.
No, no, no!
Look, do you want
to die in this cave?
No.
Well, you have to go out.
I can't do it, no.
You'll be all right.
You go, you get help for us.
Go.
At's a girl.
Come on, that's it.
Come on.
All right, all right,
come on, Cindy, come on.
Come here, come here.
I love you.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Duck, duck your head.
Come on.
Twist around.
Laura, help her.
[Screaming]
I can't get her.
Help her, Laura.
Help!
Wait a minute... shh, shh, shh.
I don't hear a pick.
[Screaming]
Get her in!
Laura!
Go!
Go get help!
Come on!
[Screaming]
No!
Not my Cindy!
[Screaming]
Are you going to
help me, or not?
Or do you want to
wait in here to die?
Huh?
Is that what you want?
To die?
Your girlfriend would be real
proud of you, wouldn't she?
[Panting]
I'm not going to die
in this hell hole.
[Whimpering]
Help.
[Coughing]
Hey, let's get out of here.
My name is Aaron.
Jeff.
Shall we?
[Drumming]
[Gong]
[Whimpering]
[Drumming]
Fourth of July.
[Gong]
Aaron!
Ah!
Help!
Come on, let's go home.
What was that thing?
It's all right, calm down.
I'm going to get us out of here.
No, it's probably
going to get us!
But first, I'm going
to rock his world.
[Bell ringing]
[Growling]
Don't worry about
it, just keep moving.
Keep moving.
[Animal sounds]
Are they coming?
They...
[Bell ringing]
Hurry, Aaron... hurry, hurry!
Come on, hurry!
Aaron!
Come on, Aaron!
[Roaring]
HOLLY: Looks like I'm going
to have to do it myself.
- Wait, wait...
- What?
Did you hear that?
No, Aaron, come on.
No, I think that
was Holly's voice.
No!
Yeah!
Come on, Aaron, just forget it.
Leave it alone!
Come on, please!
I need your help.
[Roaring]
Aaron!
[Screaming]
Hurry!
[Explosion]
This way.
Just a little bit further.
Can you hear that?
Is that a road?
Could be, come on.
Come on.
Can we get a lift?
Thanks a lot.
I better get an A out of this.
[Theme music]