Settle. You said, "settle." Settle
for anything, and you're doomed.
My biggest fear is being mediocre.
We can't settle for anything,
especially for less than we deserve.
We watch other people live their dreams...
...instead of investing in our own.
We should strive for greatness.
Life is short.
We must make it extraordinary.
Never settle for anything
less than extraordinary...
...or else life will suck.
It might suck anyway, but it's better
to suck with integrity, right?
Trent?
Are you listening to me?
May we have the check, please?
I know, Mom. I know.
Never trust a man who doesn't
have eyes like Sinatra.
You know, it's all fun and games
until somebody loses an eye.
"There is no chance at all.
We are all trapped
by a singular fate.
No one ever finds the one."
- Oscar Wilde?
- Charles Bukowski.
Can't we ever start
the day with a positive vibe?
My dear cousin, what is the point
of getting our hopes up?
God forbid..
- Hi.
- Can't I have him for a while longer?
- I'm sorry, B.J.
Someone's gotta open the cafe,
and it ain't gonna be me.
I can already hear your father downstairs.
I'm on my way.
Has anybody been in about the job?
With Frankie leaving in a few days,
we have to hire someone soon.
Somebody come in yesterday.
EntrevisteI interview him. You know what?
He ask me, "You gotta play
this garbage music all day?"
I say, "Yes."
He say, "Goodbye."
I say, "Va fangool".
So nobody comes. So what?
Got you, got me. Father, son.
We run the joint, right?
Someday you get yourself a nice wife.
I retire.
You need a good wife.
You know that, right?
- I'm too young to get married.
- What do you mean, "too young"?
I was half your age
when I marry your mama.
I was your age
when your mama left me.
Maybe you're right.
No, I don't think you're right.
I think you need a girl.
When you gonna get yourself a girl?
I...
-  Well...
- Come on, Roberto.
I'm your papa. You can't
talk to me, who you talk to?
All right.
I...
I have a girlfriend, Pop.
I wanted to keep it to myself,
but you got it out of me.
That's wonderful,
wonderful, wonderful!
Who is she?
It's...
It's Allison, but don't say
anything because she's shy.
Okay, so just... Look, what do you
see? See, she's here to see me.
I just can't keep her away from me.
God, you're looking sexier
than ever, you know?
I've missed you, sweetcakes.
-  Are you all right?
-  Bear with me.
No, I'm never all right
without you, baby.
Okay.
Well... So has Miss Personality
emerged yet this morning?
She's still upstairs, honey.
Come here.
Oh, God.
Enter.
-  Hello, baby.
- Oh, hi. It's you.
Who were you expecting,
Jean-Claude Van Damme?
I'll be ready in a sec.
Baby, what is wrong
with Rob today?
He is acting semi-strange.
I know he's different,
but we love him just the same.
So how did it go last night?
Alli, I refuse to speak to you...
...unless you talk
in your God-given voice.
All right. I said,
how did it go last night?
How did what go?
The date. The straight brother.
Play or pass?
Oh, that. Pass.
I can't believe you
thought I'd like that guy.
He's so not my type.
Here, play with me.
- No, hate the game.
- Play!!
All right. What do you mean,
he's not your type?
He's smart. He's attractive.
He's a successful lawyer,
and he likes you.
What is your type?
Poor, ugly and stupid?
My type is indescribable,
but not him is a good start.
Frankie, you haven't had
a second date in over a year.
I think you should maybe
give this guy a chance.
Please, I'm not that desperate.
He's sleazy, and he's arrogant.
And most importantly,
he has brown eyes.
Nobody told me
he had brown eyes.
- Prepare to be alone.
- What do I always say?
"Anything less than extraordinary
is a waste of my time."
If you know this,
why do you set me up, ex-frat guys...
...with these six-figure,
..who could never know what I'm about?
You know what, honey? I just want you
to have a little fun. Is that a crime?
Fun is fleeting. It's pain that endures
and gives life its meaning.
All right. Very good.
Come on, Gretzky. Audition.
- I'm dreading this.
- Really?
It's strange that you'd
be dreading something.
- You sleep well?
- Of course not.
- I have an audition this morning..
- That's good.
And I have some errands that I have to run...
..so I'll be back around 3.
You take your time, bambina.
Don't take too much time, bambina...
...because I have plans
tonight, okay?
Okay, wish us luck
on our auditions
Okay, you break you legs,bambina.
I don't know why we're going
on this audition. The script sucks.
What on earth else are you gonna do?
Just try, please, and make
a good impression, okay?
You know, smile, look happy.
You just lost your button.
And be nice. There's the pretty.
Sweetheart, let me walk you out.
- Juice, see you later.
- Hey, Juice.
I'll be here.
- Okay, what is wrong with you?
- I need your help.
I kind of told my father
that we were... We were...
...well, seeing each other.
You what?
Isn't it getting a little stuffy
in that closet?
I'm not ready.
Please, can you go along with me?
He was questioning me.
He put me on the spot.
Are you crazy? No, I cannot lie.
No. You say that it got too serious
and that we broke up.
Come on, this is not funny.
- I'm begging.
- It is funny.
You're gonna leave in a week.
Just think of this
as an acting exercise. Please.
For me.
Well, it would be a challenge
to see if I can pull it off, yeah?
I will be your slave for life.
Is it just me or are we having
a Brady Bunch moment here?
- All right.
- It might be you.
Thank you.
- Hi, what can I get for you?
- Actually, I'm here about the job.
- Is that still available?
- No, we...
I'm kidding. One second.
Hey, Papa. Papa,
someone's here about the job.
My father will talk to you.
He runs the place.
- Sir. Can I help you?
- Yes, sir. I hope so.
I'm just new here in town,
and I'm looking for a job.
- What do you know about coffee?
- Well, I know how to make coffee.
- I mean, to be honest with you...
- How many years are you?
- 24. I just graduated....
- Are you Italian?
No. Is that required?
Grazie, Angelica. It's about time.
- Excuse me?
- Nothing.
It's me and my sister.
We have a conversation.
- What did you say your name was?
- Sir, David Shrader, sir.
Tell you what I'm gonna do,
Sir David Shrader.
I'll give you the job,
but don't let me down.
No, sir.
All right. Listen, why don't I
show you around today?
We'll get you acquainted
with everything.
And you can start tomorrow.
Yeah, that'd be great.
- I'm Rob.
- David.
- Nice to meet you.
- So where'd you say you were from?
- Michigan.
What brings you to San Francisco?
Writing, hopefully.
Lots of writers seem to like it here.
All right, here I go.
Well?
Not bad for your first one.
At least I'll finally get a day off now.
So you pretty much run
this place yourself?
Yeah, pretty much.
It's...
My cousin, Frankie, works here too,
when it's convenient for her.
She's an actress and she's moving
to L.A. next week.
- Is that her?
- Yeah, that's her.
And that's her too,
when she was a kid.
Oh, okay.
- This...
- What?
Are you guys related to Sinatra
or something?
No, Frankie's father was a musician...
...and they played together
for a long time, so...
Top of the day to you, my darling.
- Hi.
I'm Allison.
I'm the love of Rob's life.
- How am I doing so far?
- Great, but Leo left.
This is David. We just hired him
so don't scare him away.
She's pretending to be my girlfriend.
My father doesn't know I'm gay, so....
Oh. Well, that's...
I mean, bravo.
I didn't know you were gay.
See? Now who's scaring him away?
Nobody's scaring me away.
Hi, Allison. Are you from Ireland?
No. Pacific Heights actually,
but thank you very much.
- Another actress, this one.
- Okay.
You don't have to hang out.
Come back tomorrow at 10...
...and we'll start you up.
- Yeah, okay. That works.
Actually, I don't know
many people here yet.
I appreciate the job.
- Don't worry about it.
- Thank you.
- Nice meeting you.
- Nice to meet you.
Oh, he seems nice.
Don't you think?
I'm certainly not gonna mind
looking at him every day.
Cookie moment.
Thank you.
You're relatively talented. The
audition couldn't have gone that bad.
Forget the audition.
The audition was fine.
But?
But they wanted more copies
of my resume.
Do you know what that means?
Twenty-four hour copy shop from hell.
Know how disgruntled workers
shoot people in the post office?
This place is next.
It's out of control.
The lines are three miles long.
The manager doesn't know what a
laser printer is. Broken machines!
"Oh, I'm sorry. We're out
of recycled paper, ma'am.
Can you pick it up tomorrow?
Bathroom?
The bathroom's broken, but there's
a 7-Eleven down the street.
And haven't I seen you
somewhere before?"
"No, never."
"I'm sure I have."
"Trust me. You haven't. Your eyes are
green, and you smell like Jovan musk!"
Caffeine is a drug!
I got one word for you:
NyQuil. Maybe?
I just remembered something.
Last night I had this dream
that we were on our way to L.A
I was tired and wanted to sleep.
You wouldn't let me...
...so you put toothpicks in my eyes
to keep them open.
You know, like Bugs Bunny.
My eyes were all watery
and bloodshot when I woke up.
Scared of that.
I dreamt last night that Friedrich
Nietzsche was whispering in my ear.
He kept saying, "All men
are inherently evil.
- All men are inherently evil."
- Oh, you are so dark.
- What do you mean you dreamed that?
- I'm not dark. I'm realistic.
How do you dream
if you don't sleep?
Well, I was napping then, okay?
I'm not sleep-deprived.
I'm just sleep-deficient.
You are not realistic. You are cynical.
I have high standards.
VYou're a realistic idealist.
No, but dreams happen in REM.
REM is deep sleep.
You don't sleep long enough
to reach that stage.
You must hallucinate.
See, your problem is, you will
not compromise what you want.
What I want...
It doesn't exist.
I read that sleep deprivation causes
hallucinations. I read that.
Acid causes hallucination.
Oh, my God. I'm not on acid,
and I'm not hallucinating.
I am not sleep-deprived.
Insomnia is not a total lack of sleep.
It's poor sleep.
You're not even looking
for Mr. Right.
You won't give any poor guy
a chance.
Well, a watched pot never boils.
You've got to at least turn
the stove on.
Then you get burned.
Dreams, as we know them,
they don't exist for you, Frankie.
- And you care because...?
- Because I'm writing a book, maybe?
Does anyone wanna know how
my audition went today? Anyone?
I've got ice-cream headache.
Coffee, anyone?
I'll take some if you're getting up.
It was fine. It was really great.
I did really well.
- I might have a career.
- Where are you going?
- My mother needs the car.
- Wait until Leo gets back...
...because I want him to see
us leave together.
You're kidding.
- How about a kiss?
- Yeah, with tongue.
Do it.
You know, you're sickos, all of you.
You're all just...
- Is everyone deserting me?
- Everyone but me.
Oh, thank God.
Rob, what time do I have
to work tomorrow?
10. I forgot to tell you.
We hired a new guy today.
Leo wants you to break him in.
Why do I have to break in the rookie?
He's harmless. I told him you guys
would get along great.
Don't hold your breath.
There, see? Cynical.
What?
What is he like? Is he cute?
Yeah. Probably not your type.
Great. And I'm stuck with him all day.
I already showed him how
to do everything.
He just moved here
and doesn't know anybody.
So would you try to just
be nice, okay?
Why is everyone always telling me
to be nice?
Why? Let's see...
This better be useful
and pertinent to my life.
Always.
"In order to win, you must expect
to win." Dan Fouts.
Francesca, is that idealism I hear?
Of course not.
Dan Fouts was a good quarterback
who never won a Super Bowl.
Point being?
Point being, a positive attitude does
not always guarantee success.
Just when I thought you were
beginning to lighten up.
Cheerio! Speaking of lightening up,
Francesca...
...did I mention I was having
my rib removed?
I'll be at supermodel status before
you can even think about it.
Step aside, Cindy, because there is
a new sheriff in town.
He goes by the name of B.J.
All right. All right.
I'll see you guys later.
Juice, you scared me.
Where's the new dude?
He's got 10 minutes to get here,
or he's out of a job.
Scared of that. I'll point him out
when he gets here.
Your cappuccinos.
Frankie, right?
Hi. David Shrader.
Sir David Shrader? The rookie?
That's what you call me
behind my back?
How did you know who I was?
I recognized you from your picture.
You don't look quite as ethnic
as this place implies.
Oh, well, my father wasn't even Italian.
Sinatra just kind of went to his head.
I know. Rob told me
all about you yesterday.
Don't believe anything he said.
No, don't worry.
He's a fan, you know?
He said you were a little
on the dark side...
...but that you always aim at the good.
"Every action and pursuit is thought
to aim at some good...
The good has rightly been declared
to be...
...that at which all things aim."
Not so easy to quote Aristotle off
the top of your head. I'm impressed.
It's not so easy to recognize Aristotle
off the top of your head.
"Knowledge comes,
but wisdom lingers."
Tennyson.
Have I met my match?
No one's been able to stump me yet.
Well, me neither.
Is that a challenge?
For you.
"I am now a central part
of your mind's landscape...
...whether you care or do not."
Morrissey, Steven.
"I am troubled immeasurably
by your eyes.
I am struck by the feather
of your soft reply.
The sound of glass speaks
quick disdain...
...and conceals what your eyes
fight to explain."
Morrison, Jim.
"The lady will have the linguini
with clam sauce and a Coke, no ice.
Remember, wherever you are,
that's the place to be.
Isn't this great?"
Damone, Fast times.
"I'll be taking these Huggies and
whatever cash you got in the register."
Raising Arizona.
Hey, Frankie!
That's him. That's the new guy.
Thanks, Juice.
Way to be on the ball there.
He's the resident slacker of the cafe.
He never pays for anything,
just so you know.
Juice, say hi to David.
Hey, David.
Did she tell you not to charge me?
Yes, I told him.
It's because I'm a unique
and talented individual.
- He's a musician.
- An artist!
How do you like it here so far?
I'm immensely entertained.
Good, because we like everybody
to feel like part of the family.
- Welcome to Cafe Blue Eyes.
- Thank you.
Frankie, are we still playing
Scrabble tonight?
Yeah, Rob's place. 11:30.
Is he a relative too?
No. You know how Italians are.
Anyone whose last name ends
in a vowel is indirectly related.
That's a great line!
That's really...
Can I borrow that? I'd start
a chapter with it or something.
Are you a writer?
I'm working on it.
You're an actress, I hear.
Yeah, I'm working on that.
- I'd love to read some of your stuff.
- Really?
Yeah, if you have some.
Yeah. Sure.
Great.
Hey, do you play Scrabble?
Do I play...?
C-A-Z-l-Q-U-E. Cazique. That's the
highest-scoring word known to man.
Good, because Rob's having
a game later.
He lives next door,
if you wanna come.
And bring some of your work
for me to read.
Yeah. Okay, yeah, that sounds
great actually.
Great.
You have to allow an artist to express
themselves as they choose to.
As long as the honesty is there,
and they both do that.
Well, that's where I tend
to disagree with you.
Well, that's where your reasoning
ability is broken down.
- Would somebody back me up here?
- I will.
She's right, Juice.
Eddie Vedder is very much
like Bono was a decade ago.
It's the passion.
But Eddie Vedder will never
turn into the spectacle...
...that Bono has become.
Who's Eddie Vetter?
Vedder. D, sweetheart. Two of them.
All right. Easy, Crusher.
Please don't talk like that about Bono.
You wanna talk voice of a generation,
let's talk Michael Stipe.
They all belong in the same category.
It's a hierarchy.
What do you mean by "hierarchy"?
It's like a trinity. If Bono is God,
then Eddie would be Jesus.
But why is Bono God?
Why can't Eddie be God?
Bono's older.
Right. God came first.
Right.
Well, so if it's the trinity,
then who's the Holy Spirit?
The man, Sinatra. Who else?
Scared of that.
Excuse me.
Yes B.J.?
I'm sorry, but that just
does not work for me.
Well, Benny, in this family
Sinatra is God, so...
I don't know why you stick up
for that...
...whiskey-drinking old geezer
all the time.
Because he happens to have
the eyes of an angel.
And he gave my father a job,
when no one else would.
David, you better hide your letters.
I tend to glance.
I think we're getting
off the point. Frankie.
What is the point?
The point is, if A and B,
then C.
Bono's lost his integrity.
Vedder hasn't and won't.
Thus, Vedder is God. Period.
"Worship the music, not
the musicians." Vedder said that.
- I read that interview.
- You did?
- It was really good.
- It was great.
Oh, God, I am so, so over
this conversation.
I have lost the will to spell, and I have
no idea what just transpired.
- I'm quitting.
- I gotta go too.
Oh, here.
- I know, I'm so sick of Chinese food.
- Lf you get a chance. Enjoy.
Hold it. Who's gonna
take home that dip?
Fuck!
One coffee for you.
- Can I get one of those?
- Yeah.
With the PowerBar,
we're looking at $2.99.
You said Frankie was working.
She is. She's still upstairs,
taking her time, no doubt.
She'll be here pretty much
all day then?
I imagine you'll be seeing quite a bit
of her before she leaves.
- When does she leave again?
- In three fun-filled days.
Sorry I'm late.
Hey, stinko.
Hi.
You slept in today. Are you sick
or something?
Sick? Do I look sick?
No, I'm... I'm not sick.
I'm... What's the word?
- Horny?
- Roberto!
You watch your tongue.
What kind of language is that?
Yeah.
I hope you no talk like that
around your girlfriend.
- Yeah.
- I no teach you that.
Trust me, I'm as polite as they come.
Are you ready to go?
Francesca.
Sir David.
You take care, okay?
We'll be gone a couple hours.
What is this? Father-and-son day?
Miniature golf.
Oh, how cute.
Roberto!
First, I'm gonna wash your mouth out
good this time. Get over here!
Good morning.
Well, well, well. Aren't we
the little Renaissance man?
Pardon me?
I read your stuff. It's very brilliant.
All of it? You read all of this last night?
Yeah. I don't sleep much.
I kind of have insomnia.
It gave me something to do.
Well, thanks.
What?
- Nothing.
- What?
- No, tell me. What?
It's... It's just, that's it.
- What's it?
- That.
It.
The stuff you read. That's old.
I haven't finished anything in a year.
And I'm starting to think
that I have nothing left.
And she's amused
by my lack of inspiration.
- Mr. Shrader.
- Yes?
"Inspiration is a treasure chest buried
at the bottom of the sea of your soul."
Well, I must have lost my map.
And you're a man, so God forbid
you stop and ask for directions.
Never.
Well, it's a good thing
you met me then.
Oh, it is?
This town is filled with precious jewels
of inspiration.
You have to know where to look.
And what are you? My compass?
Is that so unreasonable?
"The reasonable man adapts himself
to the world.
The unreasonable man persists
in trying to adapt the world to himself.
Therefore, all progress depends
on the unreasonable man."
- You think you got me on that one.
- Yes, I do.
For an intelligent guy, it's very foolish
to quote a great writer...
...being that you're
a great writer yourself.
- Who is George Bernard Shaw.
- Oh, she's so smart.
- I study the Trivial Pursuit cards.
- And so clever.
I lie awake at night thinking
of clever things to say.
And always has to have
the last word.
Thank God for caffeine.
You really don't sleep much, do you?
No, I really don't.
You're serious? Is it...?
Is it, like, a chronic thing?
Kind of.
I doze off for short periods
of time during the night...
...but I haven't slept a full eight hours
since I was 6 years old.
Why 6?
Because that's when my parents died.
I'm sorry.
They were killed in a car accident.
Leo and I were there too.
And what? You still have nightmares?
No, not really.
When I was little, my parents used to
put me to sleep singing lullabies.
You know, Sinatra songs, of course.
They used to just sit at the edge
of my bed...
...and sing till their heart's content.
I remember them looking down at me
for what seemed like forever.
They would smile at each other, then
back at me, then at each other.
There was just a lot of love
in the room, you know?
And after they died,
I used to dream that scene.
That they were singing me to sleep,
that they were alive.
And I'd wake up, and I'd remember
that they were gone.
And it was so hard for me
to lose them again...
...that I trained myself to stay awake.
And I haven't had
a good night's sleep since.
After all this time...
...do you ever think that maybe
it's in your head, the insomnia?
Well, isn't your writer's block
all in your head?
Indirectly, I guess.
Of course it is. You can't
force either one of them.
Inevitably you try, but it's like
a surfer waiting for a wave.
You just have
to let it come to you.
Well, since you're
the self-proclaimed map...
...to my destination,
I guess I have to be yours.
You think you can
put me to sleep?
You think you could
inspire me to write?
I know I can.
Okay, then.
Starting now,
we're both on a quest.
- You're gonna do that for me?
- That's what friends are for, right?
I haven't made a friend since Juice
stole Alli's lunch box in 4th grade.
- To friends.
- To friends. And I'll take that. Thanks.
- Excuse me?
- I'm cutting off the supply.
All you drink is coffee.
You got a gang of coffee over there.
You drink an awful lot of coffee.
You put coffee in your coffee.
- So?
- So coffee has caffeine.
Has it ever occurred to you
that might be part of your problem?
I didn't drink coffee when I was 6.
Okay, okay.
Bear with me here.
We're gonna detox you.
I want you to have a glass
of warm milk before you go to bed.
No, no. That's a fallacy.
I've tried that.
- Humor me, okay?
- Okay.
I don't wanna hear complaining
when I keep you out till dawn.
This is 50-50, remember?
- Of course.
Okay, I'm ready.
- Hop in.
- Okay.
You're not gonna make me drink any
more warm, white liquids, are you?
No.
You tired?
David, do you have
any brothers or sisters?
Yeah. One sister.
- Older or younger?
- Older.
- Are you close to her?
- Yeah, we're pretty close.
What are your parents like?
They're just your basic
generic mom and dad.
Are you close to them?
Probably not as close
as I should be.
Did you have a dog
when you were growing up?
- A sandbox?
- No sandbox. I had a basketball hoop.
Were you on the Little League?
Is this The Barbara Walters Special?
I just want to know...
where you came from.
Your parents must be
really proud of you.
You think so?
Yeah, I think so.
You think too much.
That's why you can't sleep.
Stop thinking.
Okay.
- Now what?
- Now lay back.
Shut your eyes.
Everywhere
Creatures are falling asleep...
The collapsible frink
Just collapsed in a heap
And by adding the frink
To the others before
I am able to give you
The who's-asleep score
Right now, 40, 40 4
Creatures are happily
Deeply in slumber.
I think you'll agree
That's a whopping fine number...
Go to sleep!
Come on. Help me out.
Counting up sleepers
Just how do we do it?
It's really quite simple
There's nothing much to it
By an audio...
Telio Tallyho count.
On a mountain halfway
Between Reno and Rome
We have a machine
In a Plexiglas dome...
Which listens and looks
Into everyone's home
And whenever it sees
A new sleeper go flop...
It jiggles and lets
A new biggle-ball drop
Our chap counts these balls
As they plop in a cup
And that's how we know
Who is down and who's up.
Good morning, sunshine.
Morning.
Shit! I gotta go.
What's the matter?
Do you have a date?
No. We'll talk tomorrow.
I'm working, remember?
Well, what about me?
I'm wide awake.
I know. I'm sorry.
I fell asleep.
The book put me out.
All right. Go home
and get some rest.
I will. Okay,
I'll see you tomorrow.
David, wait!
It is tomorrow.
Well, then, I'll see you later.
Good. That makes it seem sooner.
- Penny for your thoughts, Francesca?
- Is that all they're worth?
With all the money he charges me
on bagels, I know he can afford more.
- Did you pay for those, ass?
- Tab.
- I feel like he's holding out on me.
- Who, David?
Who else?
You've known each other
a couple days. You want a ring?
He probably doesn't
want to get too attached.
- I mean, you are leaving.
- Thank you, Scarlett.
But he could be a writer anywhere.
He could come with me.
What? And then just sort of
pack up and move again?
People have done
crazier things for love.
- Honey, you are such a romantic.
- Right.
- Maybe he's gay.
- He's not gay, Juice.
My, my,
I do not think he's gay.
No. All I'm saying is,
maybe he's gay.
- He's not gay!
- I really don't think he's gay.
Rob will know.
Rob, do you think
David could be gay?
- No, he is not gay.
- How do you know?
Because he wears running shoes
with jeans. And I asked him.
What? What did you do?
- You just asked him?
- Scared of that.
What did you say?
I said, "Do you play polo?"
What do you think I said?
I said, "Are you a gay?"
I mean, what?
He's a cute guy, I guess.
- You are such a little flirt.
- What did he say?
He said,
"Straight as an arrow."
He said that?
He is so witty.
- Don't worry. He likes you.
- Wait! How do you know?
Because he talks about you
all the time...
...brings you up in conversation,
asks questions, from day one.
Well, then, what's the problem?
Honey, maybe he's shy.
You don't know.
Maybe he's nervous.
- Maybe he's impotent.
- Maybe he's a Republican.
Maybe he's an escaped convict.
Maybe we should stop,
because here he comes.
Oh, my, my, my.
Hi, David!
Hi, gang. Hi.
Hi.
- So how'd you sleep last night?
- Pretty well. I didn't get... Sorry.
- I didn't, really.
- No?
Try this.
That'll help, hopefully.
- You working today?
- Eventually.
Molly!
Hi. I hope I'm not
disturbing you.
You forgot your keys.
No. Come on in.
Guys.
This...
This is my girlfriend.
Hi. Molly Munday.
Nice to meet you.
Molly, this is...
Juice and Allison, Rob...
...and this is Frankie.
I've heard a lot about all of you.
I wish we could
say the same about you.
So, Molly, darling,
what an interesting name.
Where are you from?
Oakland, actually.
Yeah, I'm a local girl.
I went to school in Michigan.
That's where David and I met.
Molly's in law school here in town.
Really? Well, great.
That's just great.
Yeah, how about that? A lawyer
and a writer in one house.
That's very, very
impressive, isn't it?
Anyone?
Bueller?
You have a very talented
boyfriend, Molly.
Don't tell him that.
He'll never get a real job.
Well, I didn't mean to interrupt.
- I just came by to drop these off.
- Thanks, I'm...
I'll be in the library all night.
I've got an exam tomorrow...
...so don't be alarmed
if you don't see me till then.
- Okay. Good luck.
- Thanks. I love you. Bye.
I'm gonna go...
I'm gonna go pack.
So...
...how about those Niners, huh?
- How about those Niners?
- Delivery.
- I'm gonna go see how she is.
- Me too.
Do you mind?
We just wanted to see
if you're okay.
I'm fine.
I just want to be alone.
Who do you think you are,
Greta Garbo?
I mean it!
It's no big deal, okay?
Now go!
Frankie, there's other fish
in the sea.
Alli, I don't want any other fish.
I want that fish.
The little blue-eyed,
angel-faced fish.
The David Shrader fish.
Fucking bastard!
What? What are you looking at?
This is all your fault.
First you leave me alone
like a dog for 17 years...
...and then you tease me
with this?
You two have each other.
What do I have?
Nothing. Nothing!
Hey, everything happens
for a reason.
Really, Einstein? Well,
explain the Holocaust to me then...
...because I've been trying
to figure that out for a while.
Frankie, come on,
he's just trying to help.
I know, and I appreciate it,
but would you guys just excuse me?
What a dickhead.
- Come on, he's not a dickhead.
- Not him. Me.
Okay. You wanna go shopping?
Listen, I gotta get back downstairs.
I'll let you know when David leaves.
Rob, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Hey, we've all had
broken hearts before.
I'll never break your heart.
Promise.
- Alli, would you stay a little while?
- Sure.
Oh, come here.
There you go.
I saw no chemistry.
Did you see chemistry?
No. I saw no chemistry.
I saw... I saw physics.
I saw a negative and I saw a positive.
I saw opposites attract, is what I saw.
I saw incest. I mean,
they looked like brother and sister.
- Didn't they?
- Yes. They look like brother and sister.
And you know who got
the looks in that family.
Honey, you're gonna find
somebody else.
Alli, I don't want to be
60 years old some day...
...seemingly happily married to some
man I know is my second choice...
...and wondering whatever happened
to David Shrader, that beautiful angel...
...who came in and out of my life
and who never gave me a chance.
I don't want to have to settle for that.
Looks aren't everything,
but I don't get it.
I know. I mean, you know, she's not
ugly, but he could do better.
- Like, how much better?
- Like, way better.
- Like, "me" better?
- With the talk, "way better." Of course!
- You know what else?
- What?
A name is directly related to
someone's sexual attractiveness.
No, it's true.
It's a big medical breakthrough.
Scientists all over the world
discovered this.
I read it in the New England Journal.
- So, what are you saying?
- What I'm saying is...
...with a name like Molly Munday,
a Little House on the Prairie name...
...you can bet that he's been dying
to shoot a good load.
- Frankie, with the talk! What's this...?
- What?
Would you do it with someone whose
last name's the worst day of the week?
With the name "Molly"? That's not even
the cute blind one from Little House.
- That's Nellie Oleson.
- Nellie was the mean one.
- So?
- So I don't think she's mean.
I think she's just, you know,
she's just ordinary.
All right.
Laura Ingalls.
Definitely Laura.
You know, bella...
...not a day's gone by in 17 years
that we haven't been together.
And now I look at you,
such a beautiful young woman.
Just like your mama, Angelica.
She was beautiful too, you know.
I know. I'll never forget the day
se told me her name meant "angel."
I thought she said she was an angel.
- Until today l... I still believed it.
- Come on. Sit.
Please, sit down.
Uncle Leo sees something wrong
and I know what it is.
Sometimes things happen
are not so good.
But you find good in them, capisci?
Maybe not today.
Maybe not next week.
But one day things will all work out.
You trust me?
I know you.
Just remember what you got to have:
perseverance.
Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- Don't we have plans tonight?
Not until 10, if you still wanna go.
I'd like to talk to you, though.
Maybe we could take a walk
or something?
I really can't leave right now.
Hey, Francesca, what am l,
an invalid?
- Go on, get out of here.
- Okay. All right. I'll see you later.
So, what do you want to talk about?
Nothing, I guess.
Even nothing is something.
I think I wanted to say I'm sorry.
- There's nothing to be sorry about.
- I was gonna tell you.
I mean, it's not your fault. I assumed
you were single. I assumed wrong.
You know what they say:
Never assume.
It'll only make an ass
out of you and me.
- Thank you, Felix Unger.
- I quote the truth wherever I find it.
What? She's at a loss for words?
Come on, cheer up.
It's not the end of the world.
I know, I know. It's...
It's just bad timing.
"Life can only be understood
backwards."
Kierkegaard.
Oh! "I wish I was like you,
easily amused."
Ouch. Kurt Cobain.
You know, before I even met you,
the day I was hired at the cafe...
...I saw your picture
and I couldn't stop staring at it.
It was... It was like I knew you
or something.
I mean, the funny thing is, I was right.
You're exactly the way
I imagined you'd be.
And how's that?
Honest...
...vibrant, different. I don't know.
People who've know me for years
can't see in me...
...what you saw out of that picture.
- Don't you think it means something?
- Frankie, I have a commitment.
- I don't see a ring on this finger.
- You know what I mean.
Do you love her?
We've been together for so long.
You... You don't just throw away
three years on a chance.
- Are you gonna answer me?
- About what?
Love, David, love! Do you love her?
I mean, does the thought of her,
the smell of her, the touch of her...
...make you quiver? When she's away
from you, do you think about her...
...and wish she were in your arms
making love to you?
When you see her
after not seeing her for a whole day...
...does she make everything okay?
It's getting late. Leo's waiting.
We should go.
Okay, I get it. I get it. Just...
Just remember one thing:
"Anything less than mad, passionate,
extraordinary love is a waste of time.
There are too many mediocre things
in life to deal with...
...and love shouldn't be one of them."
You live in a dream world.
Don't I wish.
Roberto. You don't look so sad.
Your Allison, she leave you tomorrow.
Oh, I mean, I'm...
You know, I'm gonna miss her.
I mean, she's my girlfriend, right?
But you know...
...when you've been single
as long as I have...
- Bello, come here. Sit down.
- Sit down?
Sit down, bello.
I want to ask you something.
You love this girl?
- Well...
- What, I pressure you too much?
Let me tell you something!
- If you love this girl and let her go...
- Papa, I...
I think that this separation
might do us some good.
You know, strengthen
our bond a little. Yes.
What? He has writer's block.
I'm helping unplug him.
That's great, but my shift was over
hours ago...
No, no, no, no, no!
Tonight's a very important night.
- Please, cover for me!
- Don't worry. He'll be deleted.
- "Delighted."
- Thank you. Thank you. I adore you.
Did I ever tell you
you're my favorite cousin?
I'm your only cousin.
You know what John Lennon said.
"One is all you need."
No, he said "love."
"Love is all you need."
He was right.
- Smile. God loves you.
- Yeah, right. At least you're leaving.
- What's not eating you?
- Nothing.
The last thing I want to discuss
right now is my lack of character.
Come on. You only have me
for one more day. Talk.
It's something I have to work out
for myself, you know?
Did something happen
between you and B.J.?
No. It's... It's me. It's me.
Can I tell you something?
You don't steal. You don't murder.
You don't deal drugs and
your father loves you very much.
I promise you, as soon as you
realize this, your life will change.
Hi.
What is it with you hoser family, eh?
Manic depression?
Really, we cheer up occasionally,
but we get over it.
Love. What's it all about? Bout.
Bout.
Alli, you're never going
to have to play a Canadian.
Vancouver and Toronto happen to be
the biggest film communities going.
So are we still waiting
for Mr. Shrader?
- Haven't quite given up?
- I never give up.
I either get what I want,
or I change my mind.
See, I know you.
I have until sunrise to make him
fall in love with me.
- How do I look?
- Natural beauty. It works for you.
Thanks, I think.
Stealing a man from a live-in, that
ain't easy. Unless he's married.
Knock on wood.
God, I think that's Leo. Let me...
Allison, can l...? We'll do one of these.
- All right.
- This is getting so tired, Roberto.
- Does somebody need a nap?
- Yeah. You, Groucho.
- What the hell did I do?
- Nothing. Nothing.
I'm just sick of people hiding the truth.
You're gay. Big fucking deal!
- Stop being such a pussy!
- Why do you say that word?
- You know that I hate that word.
- Not nearly as much as I do.
Pussy, pussy, pussy, pussy.
We're all pussies.
It's what we have to overcome
in our life, our pussiness.
It's gonna be so nice and quiet
around here when you're gone.
Can't you just say "vagina,"
if you have to say anything?
Please, just not the P word.
Who will you hide behind
when we're gone?
Fuck you, Frankie!
You got no idea what this is like.
My grandmother used to call it
a "fee-fee." Isn't that nice? A "fee-fee"?
- See? There. Make love, not war.
- You crazy people.
- B.J. calls it a "ravioli."
- Hey, B.J. has a ravioli?
- Oh, God, no.
- Wouldn't have known.
Where are you going?
- I've got some nuts to crack.
- Sorry. It's been a long day, cugino.
I know. What am I doing?
I'm gonna miss the hell out of you.
I didn't mean what I said.
It's none of my business.
Of course it isn't, but you know what?
I think you're right.
- So I will see you pussies later.
- You know what? Get out.
- I'm not related to him.
- Oh, but you are.
So, honey, you haven't
told me your plan to woo Mr. Shrader.
- Care to share?
- I don't think you're ready for it.
I am never ready. Go.
I'm going to circumnavigate his soul
until he's anchored on all sides...
...by my love.
- There's a good omen.
- Hi.
Okay, bye.
Okay, honey. I'll be back
in the morning and we will load up.
- And then we are out of here.
- Otay, Panky.
Otay. We're really gonna do this,
aren't we?
We're gonna do it.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye, Allison.
- The night is young. Shall we?
- Yes.
- We're not gonna rob banks, are we?
- No.
I don't think so.
Here, so you don't forget
where you came from.
Are you inspired yet?
- Now what?
- I can't believe I'm doing this.
- Here. Open this.
- Excuse me?
Look at the bright side.
This is better than warm milk.
- Let's live a little.
- I...
What? You said you wanted
to leave your mark. Look, "Juice."
You're not gonna spray paint
this wall, are you?
"Spray paint"?
No, we're gonna decorate the wall.
This is an industrial art form.
- Do you do this often?
- I've never done it before.
But Juice does it all the time.
How hard can it be?
- What am I supposed to do?
- I don't know, do anything. Be creative.
Most graffiti artists have a tag.
Watch.
All right, your turn.
All right.
That's beautiful, but this isn't
the Sistine Chapel.
You might want to speed it up
a little bit.
I'm only gonna do this once in my life.
I want to do it right.
I think I'm gonna add a little color...
Wow. I've never been in jail before.
Have you?
No, Frankie, as a matter of fact,
I haven't.
- Is Molly gonna be upset?
- Frankie, we gotta talk.
- Good. Me first.
- No, no, no. This is serious.
So is this.
I'm moving to L.A.,
and I want you to come with me.
- What?
- I'm in love with you.
What? Frankie, things aren't the same
in real life as they are in your dreams.
- They could be if you let them.
- I don't agree. It's not that simple.
Then you've never been in love before.
- You don't know what you're missing.
- Maybe later.
- Go ahead. Call me stupid.
- Stupid?
I would never call you stupid, David.
A stupid man wouldn't succeed
in fooling himself as you do.
Molly's a good person, really.
She's smart, she's kind,
she knows all my bad habits.
- I'm happy with her.
- You're safe with her.
I love her. I do.
Well, I love a good cappuccino, but I
wouldn't drink it if I didn't get it for free.
What is that supposed to mean?
I don't know.
Something to do with passion.
You seem to think I have a lot
of choices here. I don't see it that way.
Choices are like connecting highways.
They all take you to the same place.
Some just take longer to get there.
Frank Poncherello. I don't know.
Who said that?
I just made it up.
- It was good.
- See?
We can be best friends but we'd still
have lust in our eyes.
You need to learn the difference
between dreams and reality.
It's night and day.
I know more than you give me
credit for.
What is it that you know
that I don't know?
I know life can be taken away from you
at any random moment, David.
I know if you don't make an effort
to be happy, you won't be happy.
And I know there's a point when your
"maybe later" becomes too late.
If you only dream when you're asleep,
when you wake up, nothing's there.
I'm really gonna miss you.
I guess that means
you're not coming with me.
- You tired?
- No.
Should probably try and get some rest.
Okay, you two. You're out of here.
Here, you keep this.
So you remember
where I left my heart.
- Bye.
Bye, Uncle Leo.
Roberto.
You're a good boy. We're gonna
be fine, you and me. Don't worry.
- I have to talk to you. This is important.
- You hear what I said?
Well, you might hold off on this
pride stuff until you hear what I say.
What? What it is?
Promise to hear me out before
you make any judgments.
- All right?
- No, no, Roberto.
You know me. I don't make
no promises. I don't know why.
Tell me why, and maybe I make
the promise.
All right.
- You see, this isn't easy for me.
- Roberto, I teach you to be a man.
- Tell me. Talk to me. Be a man.
- Papa, l... I'm a...
Roberto, I got a tee time soon,
you know? Talk. What?
All right.
Papa, I am...
Come on, Frankie. You know what?
I cannot take five hours of this. I can't.
- I put the top down. It's freezing!
- I need the air.
Oh, great. Five hours,
me and Norma Desmond.
Great. Just great, great, great, great.
I so worried I think
you're gonna tell me:
"Papa, I murdered someone."
But no, instead you
tell me something...
...l've already known
for a long, long time now.
- What? You knew?
- Come on. Francesca, you know.
I love her. She's a woman.
She's wonderful. She says:
She told you? What about that stuff,
the girlfriends and the wives? What?
I figure I'll wait until you're ready.
So I wait. I wait, I wait and I wait.
Finally, I think maybe I give him
a push and he spill the peas.
I'm right.
You're not ashamed of me
or anything?
Roberto, I love you. You're my son.
We're the same blood.
I love you so much,
I just want you to be happy.
Whatever makes you happy,
me happy.
I just don't want to know the details,
capisci?
Hello, gorgeous.
Looks like we're running out of room?
Here you go.
- We got another one.
- Hello?
Couldn't you pretend you're excited
to see me?
I've got the self-esteem of a cover girl.
- Coffee, two sugars.
- Sure.
Can I have a cup? Wow.
- You gotta love him, though, David.
- Yeah.
- Hi.
- Hi. What's up?
You forgot your keys.
I didn't want you to be locked out.
Thank you.
I'm off in 10 minutes.
Wanna stick around?
We'll go out for sushi or something?
Sushi? Since when did you eat sushi?
Since I decided to go
out on a limb for my art.
I don't eat anything with a heartbeat.
- That's right.
- Besides, I can't. I don't have time.
- I got too much work to do.
- Well, what about later?
You'll need a break.
We could catch a late movie.
David, please.
We can't live off our love alone.
- I have to go.
- All right.
- Bye.
Molly!
Molly.
David.
What's the matter?
"Anything less than mad, passionate,
extraordinary love...
...is a waste of your time."
- What?
- She's pregnant. I swear.
- I can see what she's saying.
- No!
- She can't be pregnant, please.
- No, honey, please.
- She's not happy.
- Oh, no!
- Freak-out. Look at her!
Throw it back.
- Honey, she's going at it.
- That's cold.
No, this isn't funny.
- No, no, no.
- Oh, she's off.
- She's bolting.
- She's whaling on him.
- Oh, shit.
- Fuck.
Sorry about the short notice.
Don't worry about my paycheck.
- What? What the hell are you doing?
- I quit.
You...
Is it me, or are they
dropping like flies?
Don't even think about it.
That's your man.
Hello. Hi. How are you?
And you said my accents
would never come in handy.
- Well, I did it.
- Did what?
The commercial! I got the commercial.
I shoot tomorrow.
It's two months' rent in one day.
I didn't get it?
You cannot demand proof
that the product works...
...and expect to get hired.
I mean, what's wrong with you?
I have a tortured soul.
Okay, I have a feeling this has nothing
to do with the commercial, young lady.
Not one word. You think he'd at least
call or write or something.
I mean, for all he knows,
I could be in a gutter somewhere.
He doesn't care.
Frankie, he's got a girlfriend.
You wouldn't want him calling
a girl if he was going out with you.
Come on, you understand that.
You've really got to get over him.
You've got to move on.
- Think I should call him?
- Yeah, let's call him at work.
- No, wait! I'm scared.
- Too late.
I'll just be honest.
I'll tell him how much I miss him...
...and that I can't live...
- David! Hi.
Frankie wants to talk to you.
Hi.
Uncle Leo.
Fine. Yeah.
No, Alli got it.
How are you?
You miss me?
Does anyone else miss me?
Does David miss me?
Is he there?
Because I need to talk to him.
Well, when will he be back?
He what?
Did he leave a number?
Anything?
No, I'm okay. I'm...
I gotta go.
I'll call you later.
- What, what, what?
- He quit about an hour ago.
Apparently, he just ran off.
No word, no nothing.
Alli, he's gone.
I don't have his number.
I don't even know where he lives.
I'm doomed.
No, I'm doomed.
Hello, I am Deepa.
With Sheik condom,
you can go...
- Sorry. Am I in your way?
- Yes.
- More.
- Okay. With Sheik...
The belly. Show the belly.
Right. Good.
Oh, God.
- Dolly. Watch the dolly.
- Ready? Okay.
Hello, I am Deepa.
And with Sheik condom,
they are thinner...
...they are...
I'm sorry. What's the line?
I forgot the line.
- Stronger.
- Okay, thank you. Sorry.
I knew this one. Okay.
Hello, I am Deepa.
And with Sheik condom,
they are stronger, they are thinner...
...and you can go deeper
with Sheik.
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
Oh, my God, I cannot believe
I just did that.
Oh, dear. Okay.
So cut, I guess?
Is this Michigan information?
Do you have a number
for a Shrader residence?
S-H-R-A-D-E-R.
I don't know the first name.
I don't have an address.
How many do you have?
Can I have all of them, please?
Is this the Shrader residence?
Do you know a David Shrader?
Are you related to a David Shrader?
Have you ever met a David Shrader?
Have you ever heard
of a David Shrader?
No? No Shrader?
Okay. Okay. Thank you.
Who is it?
All right. I'm coming.
David!
This is your room, right?
What about Molly?
"There are too many mediocre
things in life to deal with...
...and love shouldn't be
one of them."
Have I ever told you
how beautiful you are?
No. Go ahead.
You are so beautiful,
I can't even describe how beautiful.
That makes you beautiful squared.
That makes you beautiful infinity.
That makes you beautiful
infinity times infinity.
You always have to
one-up me, don't you?
I have an idea.
Let's take turns
one-upping each other.
- I love you, Frankie.
- You do?
Yeah, I do.
- I loved you first.
- Well, I love you more.
Only because you're bigger.
Sweet dreams.
Subtitles by NMK.