- Christina?
Is that you, baby?
- We want to play again.
- Give me my daughter back.
- No.
- I want her back.
- You invited us,
we want to play.
- I just wanted my
baby to get well.
- Her heart doesn't
work anymore.
- Just let me talk to her
and we'll play, please.
- Promise?
- I promise, just let
me, let me talk to her.
- Okay.
Mommy!
- Baby.
- Mommy, it hurts so much.
- Come here, baby.
- Why'd you do it to me?
- I just, I wanted
you to get well.
- You killed me, mommy,
they told me you killed me.
- No, no.
- She is dead, now we play.
This is not going to work.
- I love you, baby.
- You are no fun.
- Em.
Emily, Emily, wake up.
- How long was I asleep?
- Zach's acting a little weird.
- Is he okay?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, he's
fine, but I think he...
- What's that smell?
- Shut up, woodrow.
- Jesse, how much longer?
- A couple miles,
we're almost there.
- You okay, Zach,
it's gonna be okay.
- Yeah, it's okay, buddy.
You know, sometimes i
wish I could just relax
and let it all go,
you know, right now,
I feel like I could
probably exploded.
- That's not fucking
funny, woodrow.
Stop being such a dick.
- Oh, come on, don't
be so tense, woman,
I'm just trying to make
it a little less awkward.
- No one finds it awkward.
- Okay, fine.
- Sorry.
- Don't be sorry, em, it's
okay, we're almost there.
- I'll be right back.
- My whole body is numb.
- Can you please help
me out with Zach?
- Hey, you don't need
to hesitate to ask me.
Come on, I'm here with you.
I love you.
We're gonna get
through this together.
- You promise?
- I'll get the wheelchair.
- Hello?
Hello?
What the fuck?
Hey, man.
Are you okay?
Whoa!
- Restroom's for customers
only, customers only.
- Dude, it's 10 in the morning.
- Happiness knows no time, son.
- Oh, no, I got it, i
got it, don't worry.
- Okay.
- Here we go, come on, buddy.
Come on.
There you are.
Do you need any help?
- No, I think I'm good.
- Good.
- Let's go get you cleaned up.
- What do you want?
- I was just wondering
if I could gas up.
- You got cash,
i just take cash.
- Okay, you got an atm?
- Sure, right in the back
next to the teleport.
- Yeah, come in.
- Hi, could we use
your bathroom, please?
- No, it's customers only.
- Just go, he's
drunk, it's fine.
- So, where you kids heading?
- Just a house up here
that my friends bought.
- Must be Dolores's old place.
Why do you wanna come here?
- It's a good question.
Listen, I just came
here to help my friends
fix their house,
but we gotta go,
so, yeah, if I could buy some
gas and beer, that be great.
- Oh, beer?
Yeah.
I got just what
the doctor ordered.
This is the best
homebrew in the state.
Billy's beer, boy.
- Hey, Jess, check it out.
So, this is apparently the
best beer in the state.
- Oh, sweet.
- And more great news,
weird guy in there does
this home delivery service
of his beer every Saturday,
today is Friday,
guess who signed up?
- You did.
- I did.
- Cool, man.
- All right, what's up?
- What?
- Come on, how is she?
- What, she's good.
- And you?
- I'm good.
Yeah, you know, ever
since we got Zach,
I'm watching a hell of a
lot more Internet porn.
No, she just has no idea
how to take care of him,
you know, so she really
hasn't been herself lately.
- I can't even imagine
what that must feel like.
- Yeah, it must
be awful waking up
in the middle of the night just
to check if he's all right.
- Yeah, there's that,
but I was talking about
not having sex for months.
- Fuck you, asshole.
- Oh, what, come on.
- No, it's all gonna
be over soon, so.
- How is she with the
whole institution thing?
- You know, she's
good, we're good.
By the way, guys, thanks for
coming all the way out here
and helping us move in,
we really appreciate it.
- Yeah, of course, man,
look, we got some fresh air,
we got some cold beer, we got
the birds squawking and shit,
you know, I feel like we're
gonna like this place.
- Welcome, welcome,
ladies and gentlemen.
- Hey, man.
- Hey, name's Richard,
here on behalf of the city
to bring you the key to
this wonderful house,
that's yours, well, from now on.
- Okay, that's what I call
some small town hospitality.
- Yeah, now is it safe to
say that you are in charge?
- Oh, no, no, no, I can
barely take care of myself,
it's this lady right here.
- Hi.
- Come here, we're going in.
Good to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
- Yeah, now just a
few little formalities
we have to go over here
before I give you the key
to this stunning palace.
Now, just need an
autograph right there.
- Okay.
- And now by signing that,
that states that you've
been met here by me,
Richard Alonso Jr. III, okay,
and flip it over, we
got part two here.
Okay, now one more
signature there,
and now by signing here,
also states that you've
been given the key
to this wonderful house.
Guys, guys.
- Thanks, Richard.
- Alonso Jr. III
- yeah, he knows it.
- Yeah.
- He already knows it.
And you know what, oh,
and let me be the first
to congratulate you folks
on this marvelous house.
Okay, and I'm not gonna
hold you any longer.
It has been a real
treat, it really has.
It's funny 'cause normally, i
take like one Adderall a day,
I took two today.
- Wow.
- I just, I'm so excited
for you kids, it's great.
- Just take care, bro.
- Yeah, oh, oh, and
guys, before I forget,
the previous owner left in a
hurry for personal reasons,
I don't know, I don't care.
I don't ask those questions,
but I just gotta
put it out there,
when the key was handed to us,
we didn't really have a budge
to hire a cleaning company,
so it's just pretty much left
as is which is even better
'cause you might find something
nice and valuable in there,
you never know, you never
know guys, this is awesome.
You guys enjoy, guys, okay?
- See ya.
- Wow, he's something.
- It's beautiful.
- Yeah, it is.
Yeah, everything's
gonna be great.
There you go, bud.
- Can someone check
the circuit breaker?
- Yeah, I'm on it.
- Wait, there's
someone over there.
- What the fuck is that?
- Oh my god, it's so freaky.
- Hey, I love this stuff.
- Stop acting like a kid,
can you go hide that thing?
- Let there be light.
Oh, wow, it's
actually not that bad.
- Not that bad, dude,
this is freaking awesome.
- You go get rid of that thing,
I'm gonna pick us a room out.
- Okay.
It's time to go,
i know, come on.
It's just that she's a
little hormonal at the moment
and I think it's gonna be best
if you two just don't spend
too much time together, okay?
Come on, why the sad face?
Okay.
You gonna like it down here.
You're not gonna needle these.
Fuck you, bubbles.
- Oh, wow.
Zach, it's your new room.
- Check it out, bud.
- So cool.
- Let's see here.
- What is this?
Oh my god.
She had a heart defect.
- Who you talking about?
- The little girl who
must've lived here.
- Hey, is everything
okay with you, bud?
- Oh, he's okay, i
think he's just tired.
- Okay.
- Let's put him to bed.
- Hey, baby, check it out.
I'm gonna knit us the
finest everlasting condom.
- Oh, Jesus, shut
up, come to momma.
- Oh, that's what's happening.
- I so want you right now.
- Okay, oh, yeah, I see.
- You want this right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, okay.
Of course, you want this.
You know you're not the
only one who wants this.
- I want it.
- You're the only who gets it.
- Oh, good.
- Are you sure
it's okay to do it?
- What?
Of course, we need to do it.
- No, it's just, I don't
wanna damage anything.
- Don't worry, it's too small.
- Yeah, I know it's only small,
but what if it...
You know, what if it
feels me when I'm...
- I wasn't talking
about the baby.
- Oh, I see, you were
talking about my...
That's funny, you need
to watch your mouth.
- You need to watch your mouth.
- One, two, three.
There you go, can you move that?
There you go, buddy.
- Oh my god, they're so dirty.
- You know, I wanna be
a little dirty, too.
- I know, Jesse, I'm sorry,
it's just really
not a good time,
I need to give him
his medication.
- Yeah, it's never been
a good fucking time
since we got Zach.
- Jesse.
- What, look at him,
he doesn't mind,
he doesn't fucking mind at all.
- He might not make it
through another seizure, okay?
I don't know why you
think a little sex
is more important than
my brother's health.
You don't need to be here.
- We bought the fucking
house because of him.
Look, I'm sorry, okay.
Fuck, it's just, it's
been a long time.
- I know, I'm just not sure
I'm doing the right thing.
- Hey, of course, you are.
Okay, let's just
stick to the plan.
We'll go see the
doctor on Monday
and he'll show us that he'll
take much better care of him
than we ever could.
- I know, but he's
my responsibility
and he's my brother,
he's my only family.
- I know that, I know,
and that's why we
bought this house,
so we can be close to him
and still get on with our lives.
Oh, fuck!
Come on, you dirty, dirty dogs.
- It is time for a toast
to this house,
to old Billy,
and to you guys, my friends.
- Aww!
- Cheers.
- Come on, em, chill
out a little bit.
- I have to give Zach his
medication, I really can't.
I'm sorry.
- Em, he's right, you know,
you need to relax a little bit.
- Yeah, drink with us.
- Come on.
- Do it.
- All right, just
a little party.
- Yeah, that's the spirit.
- I always wanted to ask you,
you know, how in high school,
girls always have a
crush on the hot teacher,
did you ever have any
students hit on you?
- No, no, no, no, no,
they were always too busy
with cool guys from their
class like that dude.
- Ah, yeah.
- I think you were the
biggest bully in high school.
- Fuck high school,
let's just drink.
- Cheers.
- I feel really good right now.
- Really?
- This is hot.
- Yeah, shit.
- It is, look at these two.
- Oh my god.
- Well, speaking of being hot,
you gonna keep that
fire going or what?
Well, they don't call me
Woody for nothing, I got it.
There you go, baby.
We're out.
We can use that.
What the fuck is this?
- Duer, buer, what's that?
- It looks like some
kind of religious symbol.
- We can heal.
- What religion, though?
- It's hard to say, I mean,
we don't know who lived here
or what they believed in.
- I believe in this.
- We can save you.
You are Zach, you're
body is useless.
We will.
No need to resist.
- Oh, shit.
Hey, guys, we have another
symbol on this board, and...
It says
sabnock.
- Okay, Wikipedia says
that buer is a spirit
that appears in the
16th century book goetia
where he is described as
the great president of hell.
- Oh.
- And that he's capable
of healing all infirmities
and then there's a list
of 72 different demons.
Yeah, what d'you say
the other name was?
- Sabnock.
And this one, this
one says gamory on it.
- Sabnock and gamory, yeah,
they're all listed here.
- All of this is
freaking me out.
- Guys, it's bullshit.
I can heal all
infirmities, with this.
- Man, we got a lot of
stuff to do tomorrow.
- We need to get rid of
all the creepy stuff.
- We'll do it, first thing
in the morning, okay?
- Oh my god, Zach's medication.
- Zach?
Hey, Zach.
Remember that prayer
mom taught us?
Now I lay me down to sleep,
I pray the lord my soul to keep,
if I should die before I wake,
I pray the lord my soul to take.
I just wish mom was here.
- How is he?
- He's really calm.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Well, that's good.
- You know what else?
Maybe some fresh air.
Maybe he'll actually get better.
- Jesse, he's not gonna better.
- Oh, I don't
know, you know why?
- Why?
- Love makes miracles happen.
Seriously.
- That's so cheesy.
- Oh, yeah, you know what
else makes miracles happen?
- What?
- Making love.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Fuck, fuck you, woodrow,
fuck, I'll kick
your fucking ass.
Baby, baby, don't
worry about it,
no, no, no, it's just woodrow
being asshole, please?
- Okay, no, I'm sorry,
goodnight, Jesse.
- Goodnight, baby.
- You were right about Zach.
- What?
- I need to take a lot
better care of him.
Jesse?
Jesse.
Jesse, wake up.
Jesse!
- Oh, oh my god.
- You're okay, baby,
you're okay, you're okay.
- Zach?
- I'll be damned.
Hey, buddy, how
are you doing this?
Hey, hey, come on,
let's sit down.
Let's sit down.
- Fuck me.
- Emily, Emily, what
the fuck do we do?
Emily?
- What's going on?
- Go with her.
- Em, what happened?
- He...
He walked.
- He's freaking me out.
- Oh, that's the doctor.
Hey, how's it going?
- Good.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi, Dr. waisenberg, I'm
Emily, very nice to meet you.
Sorry we had to
bother you today.
- No, this is no bother.
- This is Zach.
- I'm sorry I didn't get a
chance to pull Zach's file.
If I remember correctly,
he's suffering from spastic
quadriplegia, am I right?
- Yes.
- And you said that he
stood up this morning.
- Yeah.
- Let's have a
look at you, Zach.
Did you notice anything
unusual about his behavior
over the last day or
two, anything at all?
- He slept really
calmly last night,
but I forgot to give
him his medicine,
so I don't know if that...
- You forgot to give medication
to a patient with
spastic quadriplegia?
- Doc, come on, give
her a break, okay?
- Zach.
My name is Dr. waisenberg,
can you hear me?
I'm just going to listen
to your heartbeat.
There we go.
- Is everything okay?
- Did you hear that?
- Hear what?
- I've never seen
anything like this before.
- Well, what do we do about it?
- I'm gonna ask your permission
to take Zach with me
to the institution
and run a few test right now.
- Okay, I'll come with you.
- No, no, you can stay here,
you might just get in the way.
We'll keep our Monday
appointment as we discussed
and I promise I'll
keep you updated
and you can contact me anytime.
- No.
- Emily.
- What?
- Emily, come on, we've
talked about this.
We don't need to get
in the way, okay?
They're gonna take better
care of him, right?
- That's right.
We should get going.
- Everything's gonna
be all right, okay?
We're gonna go see him soon.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah, let's get to work.
Last one, man.
Looks good, bro.
- Yeah, at least I'll be
getting me some of this.
Hey, so where are the girls?
- What are you talking about?
They're doing what
they were made for.
- I wasn't made for this.
Em, it's gonna be okay.
- I know, I'm sorry,
I just have a really
bad feeling about this.
I just don't know if I'm
doing the right thing.
- I thought you hated
taking care of Zach.
- I don't hate
taking care of Zach,
I'm not very good at it.
I just feel like
Jesse's been talking me
into doing this stuff
i don't wanna do.
- What are you talking about?
Jesse's here for you,
he quit his job for you.
- Michelle, Jesse didn't
quit his job for me.
- What do you mean?
- He's taking an extended leave.
- What?
- One of his students,
her boyfriend taught
she was cheating on him
with someone from class,
and he brought a gun to school.
- And he shot her?
- And then himself.
- How did I never
hear about this?
- It's a private school,
they shut down the media.
- Oh my god.
- He doesn't like to
talk about, so don't.
- Okay, enough of the bad news,
why don't I finish up here?
- Yeah, I'll just go
start on the basement.
- Yeah.
- What do you think
about all that?
About Zach.
- I don't know, man.
I mean, I guess it's
a good thing, right?
- Right yeah.
- Yeah.
- You know I never
talked about this,
what happened to Emily's mom?
- Well, we think that she
fell asleep behind the wheel,
hit the center
divider with her car.
- And Zach was in the car?
- Yeah, yeah.
- How did he even survive?
- Well, when she
crashed, the car lit up,
this couple pulled over
in time to get Zach out,
but they didn't
make it to his mom.
The shitty thing is I think Zach
saw everything that
happened to her.
- Oh.
That's fucked.
I guess it's a good thing
that he doesn't understand
anything, you know?
- What are you talking about?
He has cp, he's not a vegetable.
Dude, you know nothing about
cerebral palsy, do you?
- No.
- All right, he understands
everything he sees and hears,
he just can't respond,
like his brain can't
control his muscles.
- God, you scared
the shit out of me.
- Sorry.
Wow, look at all
this creepy stuff.
I wonder what kinda
freaks lived here.
- Don't open that.
- Why not?
- I don't know, it's not ours.
- I wonder how much
more weird stuff
we're gonna find in this place.
What's that?
Fuck.
- Me.
- There you go.
- Oh my god, I feel
like such a dick.
- Oh, that would be
a first, wouldn't it?
- Hey, there's something
you guys should see.
- Look, this is extraordinary,
I've never seen
anything like it before.
This boy is going to
change everything.
- What the...
- I wanna go home.
- Baby, don't
freak out about it,
it's just some kids
playing Harry Potter.
- No, no, these are too
detailed for just some kids,
whosever doing this knew
what they were doing.
- Well, what about the
lady who used to live here?
- I don't know.
I think...
I think she was obsessed
with demonology.
- Demono,
is that a real word?
Did...
- shut up, man.
What are you talking
about, Emily?
- I mean, look around the house,
look at all these
signs that we found
and then...
I found this book downstairs
that kinda looked
like a spell book.
- Wait.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- A spell book?
- Yeah.
- For what?
- I don't know, she
had a sick daughter,
maybe she thought it
could help with that.
- Okay, well, do we know
what happened to them?
Why did they leave?
- Maybe the doctor,
maybe he knows.
- Yeah, you know what,
that's a good idea.
I'll give him a call.
- It's okay, I'll call him,
i wanna check on Zach anyway.
There's still no answer.
What if something
happened to them?
- Emily, you gotta
relax, he's fine.
Okay, the doctor's probably
just a responsible driver
and doesn't wanna
pick up the phone.
- I don't get it, your brother
is finally getting better
and all you do is
complain about it.
- Wow, Michelle,
you don't get it?
- Yeah.
- That's weird
because you've never taken
care of anyone, but yourself.
- Okay, come on.
- Oh, really?
- Come on, girls, stop.
- Jesse, I wanna go
see Zach, please.
- There's no need to go.
- Oh my god.
What happened?
Are you all right?
There's blood on his shirt.
- Shit, hey, let's
get you inside.
- Come on, Zach,
well clean you up.
- Hey
- they're almost here.
- What's wrong with his eyes?
- I don't know.
Michelle, can you
get him some water?
- Yeah.
- Zach, you said
someone was coming,
who were you talking about?
- What, wait a minute, did
you say he said something?
- He said that
somebody was coming.
I don't know what...
- Hey, hey.
- What is it?
- It moves.
So little.
Smaller than the
first one you killed.
- Shut up.
- Hey, you stay away from
her, you fucking freak.
- Zach?
What are you talking about?
- I'm so sorry.
- Hey, you need to
call the doctor again.
- Em, my phone's dead,
where'd you put yours?
- I don't know, it's over there.
- Guys, it goes
straight to voicemail.
- Man, there is some
really weird shit
going on with this guy and we
need to do something about it.
Hello, what are you doing?
- There's somebody out
there, look in the woods.
- They're here.
- Zach, who's here?
- Who's that?
- There's more.
- Is this a joke?
I'm calling the cops.
- Jesse, I'm scared.
- Don't worry, honey,
everything's gonna be fine.
- Let's play.
Don't be afraid.
You can trust us.
Get rid of it.
Kill it
kill it.
- Who is that?
- It's the dude from
the gas station.
- Billy, what the...
- Old Billy's homebrew delivery.
Got your beer here.
- Oh my god, he brought
my fucking beer.
I'm gonna find out if he knows
about those assholes out...
- woodrow, wait.
- What?
- Look.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey behind
you, look behind you.
Holy shit!
- This can't be happening.
- What are those things?
- Go to the back, all right,
we need to get the
fuck outta here.
- Come on.
- What is that, why
is this happening?
- They're everywhere,
they surrounded the house.
- What are you doing, man?
- What do you think I'm doing?
I'm gonna break into
the fucking house.
- The pets will not come in.
- What did you say?
- They obey us, now we play.
- What the fuck is
wrong with you, man?
- Your bitch kills babies.
- What?
- She's dying,
better go get her.
- Zach.
- Zach's not here.
- Who are you?
- We're Zach's friends.
- Oh, god.
- Help, help.
Help, help, help.
- Holy shit.
- - Oh my god.
- What happened?
- Call the fucking
ambulance now, go.
- I'll go get towels.
- Oh my god, baby,
what have you done?
Oh, fuck, it's okay, it's okay.
- Where are the phones?
Zach?
- They hate fire.
They didn't want
anyone else to come.
- Okay, did she call, did
she call the ambulance,
did she call 'em?
- Calm down, she's on it.
- Okay, fuck, oh, fuck.
She was pregnant, she was
fucking pregnant, man.
She's gonna be fine, okay?
No, look at me, man,
look at me, man,
she's gonna be fucking fine.
- Those things outside
and what the fuck
is happening, man?
Fuck.
- I don't know, man, all
right, just calm down.
- I...
It's that freak's fault.
I'm gonna make him
fix all of this shit,
stay in here with her.
- You need to fucking
stay in here, man,
I can't fucking do this.
- Oh, shit, oh, shit.
Did you call the ambulance?
- No.
I'm sorry, woodrow.
- What are you
talking about, why?
Oh, no, no, no, my
Michelle, she's dying.
Oh, fuck, I need a first,
where's the first aid kit?
- We don't have one.
- Yeah, yeah, we gotta have
something, come on, where is it?
- You're okay, it's
okay, you're okay.
Woodrow?
- Please, don't scream.
- Oh, fuck, fuck, oh, shit.
I'm gonna take the car.
- No, please, woodrow,
don't go out there.
- No, I gotta do something.
- If you go out there,
you're gonna die.
- If she stays in
here, she's gonna die.
Your fucking brother,
your fucking brother
has to make them leave.
- No, no, no, no, please,
please, please don't hurt him.
- Make 'em leave,
you son of a bitch.
- Get off him.
- She told us your secret.
- Michelle, what the
fuck is wrong with you?
- She told us your cock was
so hard when you were dancing.
- Michelle, shut the fuck up.
- Dirty Jesse.
Do you still want me?
You can have me, I'm all yours.
We will chop your
cock off, Jessie.
- Stay away from me.
- You have no guts, you cunt.
- Oh, fuck.
- You broke my heart.
- What the fuck
is wrong with you?
- We think you're fun.
- Hey, hey, open
the door, Jesse.
- Get the fuck in here, man.
- Jesse, come on.
- Get the fuck in here, man,
just get the fuck in here.
- Kiss me hard before you go.
- Oh, fuck.
- Holy what, what did you do?
- She tried to fucking kill
me, man, she tried to fucking...
- Oh, no.
- Oh my god.
- She tried to fucking kill me.
I can't fucking see.
I can't fucking see,
man, I can't fucking see,
why the fuck can't I see?
Why can't I see, why, what's
wrong with my fucking eye?
What's wrong with
my fucking eye?
- Baby?
Okay, baby, we need to
take that out of your eye.
- Oh, fuck, it hurts so much.
- I know, I know.
But you still have to do it.
- Oh, fuck.
All right, let's just fucking
do it, let's fucking do this.
- You know everything,
don't you, you freak?
You made her kill our baby.
You should've died in
that car with your mother.
You're gonna pay for
what you've done.
- Just do it, just
do it, just do it.
- Okay.
- Stop, stop, stop!
- You're not gonna
hurt anyone else.
- I'm waiting for you, woodrow.
- What d'you say?
- I'm here, woodrow.
- Gonna take you to the hospital
and they're gonna take
care of you, okay?
- Okay.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- I think my fucking
brain's damaged.
- Okay, okay,
- no, it's fucking damaged.
- You're gonna be okay.
- No, I'm not gonna
be okay, okay?
I just lost my fucking eye.
- Jesse, just tell me
what happened in there.
- I don't know, you know, I...
I was trying to stop
the blood, but...
You know, she suddenly
stabbed me in the face.
It wasn't her, though, you know,
she was all messed up,
she was talking different,
I didn't understand it.
- Well, what did she say?
- I don't know, it doesn't
make any sense, you know,
she kept talking like
Zach, she kept saying we.
- Okay, did she say why
she did what she did?
- Fuck, I don't fucking
know, all right,
I don't have answers to every
fucking question you have.
God damn it.
- Why are you acting like this?
Michelle is dead.
Woodrow thinks
it's Zach's fault.
I just need your support, okay,
please don't push me away.
- I'm sorry, okay, you know,
I'm just scared,
too, okay, you know?
- Yeah.
- Hey, look at me, okay,
we're gonna be okay.
- You made me do this?
- No, no, no, no, fuck this.
No, I'm...
- I was just a little kid.
Why did you bully me?
- I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I've changed.
I'm different now.
- Do you know where suicides go?
- Oh, please, no.
- That's where I'm
waiting for you.
- No, please, stop,
man, I can't, I can't,
I can't take it anymore.
- Today will be the day you
pay for your consequences.
You condemned me to
burn in hell forever.
- No, no, no, no, Dennis.
Dennis, I'm sorry, please.
I, I didn't...
It wasn't my fault.
- Will pay.
- What the hell was that?
- Woodrow!
- Holy shit, what have you done?
Oh, fuck.
Hold his head.
I gotta get this outta you, man,
I gotta get this outta you.
Oh, geez.
- Oh my god.
- Hey, no, no, no, no,
don't, don't touch it,
stop, stop that, look
at me, look at me,
you're gonna make it worse,
okay, don't touch that.
- Let's put him in here.
- Move, I'll get him.
Fuck.
Oh, shit, no, no,
no, I can't move him,
look, look, I think
he broke his leg.
- Okay.
- Hey, hey, we gotta
get him to the hospital,
he's losing too much blood.
- Jesse, we can't go to the
hospital, we can't go outside.
Someone's out there.
Okay, Zach said they're
not gonna come in here,
so we just need to stay in here.
- Where the fuck is Zach?
- Oh my god.
Zach, what happened?
- I need them, Emily, they heal.
- They heal.
- What did he say?
- He said they heal.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- All the things on the
windows and the witchcraft
and the basement, it
has to do with the book.
- What book, Emily?
- The goetia, it talks about
being able to summon demons
straight from hell and...
People think they can help.
- Help how?
- Take over the
body and heal it.
- Come on, that's
fucking bullshit, Emily.
- Well, Jesse, that's what i
thought, too, but look around.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
there has to be a logical
explanation for this,
everything has a
reasonable explanation.
- Okay, there's a
logical explanation
for Michelle ripping her body
open and trying to kill you,
and there's a logical explanation
for those things outside?
- I don't know, maybe it's a
fucking virus or something.
- Oh, it's a virus
that's making Zach talk.
Look at woodrow for god sakes.
- What about god?
- What?
- Well, where is he?
If all these demons
and hell exists,
that means god's out there
somewhere watching us,
well, where the fuck is he?
What d'you say?
- Your god is dead.
- Hit his head.
- Do you think he's...
- I don't know, em,
all I do know is that
if you're right about
this book and stuff,
it's just a matter of time
until one of us becomes that.
- No, just.
- They've all been hurt pretty
badly when turned and...
Fuck, em, look at me.
- No, Jesse, I won't
let them take you.
- No, no, look.
If they get inside me,
don't hesitate.
- Jesse, get the pills.
- Emily, come on, i
don't wanna go alone.
- Jesse, please.
Okay, you're gonna be okay.
- Fuck!
Oh, shit.
Sarah?
- I was in love with you.
- No, don't say that,
that's not true.
- I trusted you,
you didn't stop him.
- No, that's not true, there
was nothing I could do,
it wasn't my fault.
- You let him kill me.
- I know, I froze,
I didn't know what to do.
I didn't know what
to do, I'm sorry.
- You were a coward.
You broke my heart, now
I'm gonna break yours.
- Zach, please stop, i
can't take it anymore.
Oh, Zach, I'm here with you.
- Jesse.
Jesse.
- I'm sorry, Sarah, I'm sorry.
- Jesse, no.
- Oh, what, she was just here.
- Who?
- Sarah, my student,
the girl that got shot,
sh was just here,
she was just here.
- No, Jesse, nobody was here.
- Yes, she was.
- No, that's just the demons
playing with your mind.
Jesse, none of this is real.
- I almost did it.
I couldn't control myself.
- Okay, come on, I think
i know how to stop this.
- How?
- The woman who
used to live here,
her spell book's
in the basement.
- All right, if this
lady summoned them,
there has to be some way
of sending them back.
- Yeah, must be something here.
- What a useless body.
- You promised me.
- You will be healed, but
the game's not over yet.
- Wait a minute,
what does it say?
- It says that these
things that are outside
they're called the guardians,
and then...
They're descriptions
of all the demons,
there's seven of them.
- Seven, does it say
how to defeat them?
- No, I don't think so.
- Let me see these.
- What is it?
- It says they can
only use your body
if you let them heal it.
- That's why they make
you hurt yourself.
- Keep the house sealed.
- Sealed with what?
- I don't know,
there's nothing else.
- These symbols, Emily,
you've read about them,
what do they mean?
- These are from the goetia,
and each and every demon
has one of these symbols.
They call 'em sigils.
Oh my god.
The house was sealed
when we came here.
- The boards.
They're outside.
- Okay, well, we have to
make our own seals then.
- Okay, how?
- We need to figure out
which of these symbols
goes with the
demons she summoned.
- I remember the
symbols of the board
and the windows I pulled off.
It was sabnock,
yeah, it was sabnock.
- Did you just call us?
- Jesse!
Sabnock.
Please let us go.
- Oh, we can't stop the game.
- But I don't
wanna play anymore.
- You people are so much fun.
There is no premise,
your filthy nature is the game.
I'll play, please don't tell me.
- Each and every one
of you is a sinner.
Each and every one of you
will do anything to live.
We've played this
game so many times
and every time, we see people
killing their loved ones,
mothers slaughtering
their children
and brothers betraying
their sisters
just like Zach.
And you?
Well, you're not different,
you selfish bitch.
- Jesse, he's gone.
- I won't let them take me.
- Oh, I'm so sorry, baby.
- Zach, he knows.
- I love you, baby,
I'll fix everything,
just hang in there, okay?
- Hurry.
- You made the seals.
- They told me
they would heal me
- you knew what to do
all along, didn't you?
- I had to watch our mom burn
and I couldn't do anything.
- I'm so sorry, Zach.
I'm so sorry.
- I just wanted to be normal,
i didn't want any of this.
- And these signs, they'll
make the nightmare end?
And what happens to
you when they're gone?
- I don't care.
- Okay, okay.
- We told you everything
about us, Zach.
Been trapped in his own body.
You didn't know what
it's like to be loved.
I thought you
understood what we feel.
- I know
what it's like to be loved.
- Do you really?
Emily.
Now, we know your
filthy lover's secrets.
Sarah, what a lovely
young cunt she had.
- You liars.
- Oh, are we?
Think about it.
He hated taking care
of your brother.
He despised hearing you
whine every fucking day.
Oh, Jesse, I can't right now,
I have to give Zach
his medication.
We're gonna get inside you
and rip your fucking soul.
You whore.
We are the bornless
ones, we are...
- I'm so sorry, Jesse.
- Now I lay me down to sleep,
I pray the lord my soul to keep,
and if I die before I wake,
I pray the lord my soul to take.
You remember that
one, don't you?
- Mom?
- We were so alone
after you left us,
just me and my baby boy.
- I wish I was there with you.
- Oh, I wanted that so
badly, too, but you won't.
- I'm so sorry, mom.
- It's all fine,
baby, it's all fine.
That day I wanted me and
my boy to go together
to a place where
everyone was happy,
I wanted him to be happy.
I couldn't watch
him suffer anymore.
- I was so selfish,
i was so stupid,
I just wanted a normal life.
- I don't blame you,
i love you, baby.
We can fix everything right now.
We can all be together again.
- What do you want me to do?
- You know what to do, darling.
You can end his
suffering right now.
Be a good sister, just once.
Good girl.
We love you so much.
- Mom, do you remember
what you said to me
the last time we were together?
- Of course, I remember.
I told you how much I love you.
You and Zach were the best
things that ever happened to me.
- You told me never
to give up on him.
And I did.
And I'm not gonna do that again.
You're not my mom,
my mom's dead.
- Don't say that, baby,
you're hurting me.
- Fuck you.
- You made me kill myself
and now I burn in hell,
you ungrateful bitch.
- My mom didn't kill
herself, it was an accident.
- You want him to have
this miserable life,
you can't take care of
him, you selfish whore.
You think you're smart,
you stupid bitch,
you're not going anywhere
because we won't let you.
- Try and stop me,
you motherfuckers.
- We can heal your
brother, he needs us.
- He has me.
- You are fun.
- Zach?
Zach, it's all over.
They're gone now.
- Emily.
Emily, please help.
Help me.
Emily.
Emily, please help, help, help.
- Jesse.
- Oh, oh, baby, it hurts so bad.
Oh, oh.
Oh, why'd you do this to me?
- I'm sorry, I had no choice.
- Oh, are they gone?
Emily, please, please,
please stay here,
stay here, take it out of me.
Please, baby, do it,
take it out of me.
Please.
- Oh!
Oh, baby, everything's gonna
be all right, I'm here for you.
- We need to play.
- What?
- We play!
Such a pleasure watching you
creatures killing one another.
So fun giving you the pain.
No, don't be so selfish,
the game is not over.
- Zach, I don't feel my legs.
- Come back.
Don't leave us.
You need us.
We can heal.