[Electricity crackling]
[***]
[Screaming]
No! Ahh! No! No!
[Screams]
[Screaming]
No! Ah!
[***]
[Crickets chirping]
Vodka...
Scotch...
Gin.
Mmm.
[Crickets chirping]
Woman:
I cannot wait
to roll a fat blunt.
I'm gonna get even more drunk
than I did last weekend
when I went to see
"steel panther."
Ugh, I hope Jenna
doesn't puke this time.
Oh! Last time
we had to hold her hair.
[Knocking on door]
[***]
Woman 1 [Laughing]:
Yeah.
She's always such a mess.
She fell asleep with her face,
like, on the toilet.
Woman 2:
Oh, hey. There she is.
Our hostess.
Hi!
Hi, guys!
Come on in.
Hey, what's up?
What up, chica?
Come on in.
[Gasps]
Oh!
Woman 3:
You guys like it?
Oh, my gosh.
Whoa!
This is nuts.
[Laughing]
Oh, my God.
Talk about
goin' all out.
Right?
What's the deal?
Put your stuff anywhere. Make
yourself comfortable, girls.
Oh, I will,
and I am.
Wow. You don't fuck around,
do you?
It's not a party
till Ms. catalina arrives.
You know that.
I feel you on that.
Hey.
I practically
had to twist her nipple
to get her
to make a store run.
Well, I'm glad
someone thought of food.
I'm on an herbal diet.
Oh, well, when you're getting
your little munchies later,
you're gonna be kissing
rocky's feet.
When are the boys
coming?
Oh, right. The boys.
Um...
Please tell me
there are boys coming.
Actually, I thought
we'd have a girls' night.
You know how my mom and I
make the haunted house
every year?
The house that dripped
horrors, right?
Yeah, that's us.
Cool.
Tonight is the house
of dripping hoes.
Nice.
Jen:
Yeah, well, anyway,
it's pretty much how we pay
our bills every year,
but there was an emergency
so my mom had to go
out of town for the week,
so there's no way I could
put all these decorations up
by myself for Halloween.
So you recruited us
to do your dirty work?
Yeah. Kind of. Yes.
That's some bullshit, girl.
I think it'll be awesome.
[***]
Come on, you guys.
This can be fun.
Hmm. Yeah, but I did wear
these fuck-me heels for nothing.
We can still put them
to good use.
By doing what?
Shoving them up your butt?
I don't swing that way,
and I won't swing that way.
You can make cat's kitty
purr anytime you want.
Meow.
Ugh.
Come on, you guys.
This is gonna be great.
We can watch movies, we can...
We can put all this stuff up
and we can,
you know...
And what?
Get really messed up.
I've got a whole stock
of booze in the kitchen.
Sweet. Thanks.
Hm. Okay.
So you guys are gonna help?
Hell, yeah.
I'm in.
Okay, whatever. I'm in.
Wait a minute.
Where's Giselle?
Oh, right. Um, well,
I kinda sorta
didn't invite her, you know?
I mean, I love her to death,
but she doesn't exactly
like to get her hands dirty,
so I figured we'd get
more done without her.
You know she's gonna
go bat shit on your ass
when she finds out.
Yeah, she'll go spaz
on all our asses.
Just so our stories
are straight,
I was never here.
Okay, well,
if we get it done,
then I won't say a peep,
but if we don't, who knows?
Okay, little miss blackmail!
We already said
we'd help.
Sweet. Okay,
and just one last thing.
Just to get
in the spirit of things,
check these out.
Woman:
What?
[Laughing]
Aren't they cool?
Whoa. These are rad.
Wow, thanks, Jen.
Yeah, thank you.
These are so cool.
They're not for the haunted
house, though, okay?
I just found them
in my mom's stuff
and I knew they'd
look better on you guys.
Oh, I like
the beads on yours.
Yeah?
Sexy. Yeah.
I wish I could see it.
You guys look
really awesome.
I think mine's
the scary one.
Oh, thanks.
Yours is kinda scary,
but it's like a scary queen.
Can you move the mouth?
Hang on. Rawr.
[Laughing]
That's...
Boo!
Yeah, you're
kind of crooked, Jen.
Oh.
[Laughing]
Yeah.
Let's get sloppy.
Yeah!
Yeah, why don't you guys
make yourselves comfy
and I'll go get the booze.
Sounds good.
Let's get this party
started.
[Rap music playing]
* come on *
* fired up, fired up, come on *
* fired up, fired up,
come on *
she said get comfy,
right?
* fired up, fired up *
* fired up, fired up, come on *
* fired up, fired up,
come on *
* fired up, fired up, come on *
* freshly showered,
smell couture *
* took about an hour
to get dressed and get gone *
* there's a whole lot of power
in this excursion *
* we roll *
[muted sound]
* just to make
their jaws drop *
yeah! Whoo!
I love this song.
I love this party.
[Laughing]
* bottles of grey goose *
* and the grand marnier's
flowing continually *
[***]
[Muted sound]
Thanks for having us over,
Jen.
Are you kidding?
I love having
you guys over.
It's kind of hard
when my mom's around.
Why do you say that?
Well,
i love her to death,
but since my dad's
been gone,
some people might think
she's a little weird.
In what way?
Well, most of the stuff
outside
is for the haunted house,
but my mom is
one of these people
who celebrates Halloween
all year long.
That's not so weird,
i guess.
I mean, I know a lot
of people like that.
Tattoos, black lipstick.
Sunset boulevard is full
of vampire-looking creeps.
Yeah,
but it's more than that.
Like, my mom's into
palm reading, tarot cards,
séances, riding brooms
and eating children.
Okay, I'm kidding
about the brooms
and children part of it.
[Laughs]
Seriously, she's,
like, really into it.
Kind of creeps me out.
To each her own, I guess.
Come on.
Those bitches are starting
the party without us.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
[***]
[Woman inhaling, coughing]
And things got pretty heated
between me and the slut.
I mean, she was
all up in my face
arguing with me big time,
like she was ready
to throw down on my ass.
Finally, I just had to
sit her down and say,
"look, dude,
the cotangent is x over y
if the corners of the right
triangle are bac. You dig?"
Imagine.
Girl trying to
school me on trig.
I would've slapped her
if I didn't think
I'd break a nail.
Shit. Girl didn't know she was
messin' with a math whiz.
Oh, hell.
[Coughing]
I can't even figure out
a tip at a restaurant.
Like you ever have to
pay for your own dinner.
Truth.
Somebody say, "hey!"
All:
Hey!
Diets are to be
ignored tonight, ladies.
Diet? Who diets?
A body like that
and she doesn't diet?
I hate you.
Come on, guys.
Let's get started.
Oh, yes. Gin.
[***]
Ew!
It's not gross
from where I'm standing.
Ew!
[Laughing]
Hey, you guys.
Come check this out.
What is it?
Jen:
I don't know.
It might not even work.
What?
One moment.
[All screaming]
Oh, my God!
Bitch!
You suck.
[Laughing]
I guess it still works.
Holy shit.
I guess so.
That is awesome.
Oh, my God.
[Laughing]
That was not cool.
It wasn't that scary.
Come on.
Okay.
Woman:
I just shat myself.
[***]
Ooh, check this one out. Wicked.
Oh, new additions
to the haunted house.
I haven't even
seen these yet.
Ooh, these are
gonna scare the crap
out of the little kids.
Not just the kids. Barf.
What's the matter,
honey?
Too scary for you?
More like too silly.
Who would be afraid
of this stuff?
Ah!
[Gasps]
[Laughing]
That's not funny.
Silly, huh?
You seemed pretty scared to me.
Okay, I admit it.
I was a little scared.
Good one, kianna.
[Laughing]
Whoa! Okay! Okay!
[Snarling]
Thank you.
Scary, right?
Oh, my God.
[Laughing]
That's awesome.
That's enough.
That one's good too.
Pretty scary, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Twice in one day.
All right, you guys,
let's get back to work.
By the way, Jen,
don't you think
this crystal ball
would look perfect
in the center
of the room?
Whoa, whoa! That's my mom's
crystal ball. Be careful.
Well, don't you think
it's hidden here?
Honestly, I think we should
just leave it where it is,
because it's not even
part of the haunted house
and she'd freak out
if she knew we were touching it.
Catalina:
What do you mean?
It's perfect for
the centerpiece of the room.
It's beautiful.
Cat, you wouldn't
know beautiful balls
if they slapped you
on the ass.
You're right.
I gave up balls
a long time ago.
But I do love huge,
heaving orbs.
[***]
Seriously, guys?
She loves that thing
more than anything.
Like, she talks to it
all day long.
Full-on conversations.
To be honest, it kind of
freaks me out.
Like, I feel like it's
watching my every move.
[Phone rings]
Oh, my God! You guys,
it's my mom.
Ugh.
[Phone beeps]
Hi, mom.
Mother: Hi, honey.
How's everything
going there?
Fine, but the question is, "how
are things there?"
Oh, you know.
It's coming along.
They need to be.
We open a week from tonight.
I know, mom.
Everything will be ready.
It better. And I don't want
any boys there while I'm away.
It'll just distract you
from your duties.
Okay, got it. No boys.
And that goes double
for your girlfriends.
They're worse. Especially that
catatonia.
Mom, it's catalina,
not catatonia.
What was that?
What was what?
I heard laughter.
Is somebody there with you?
No, mom. Not... nobody's here.
You listen to me, missy.
Nobody better be.
I'll find out, you know.
I have eyes and ears
in that house.
Jen:
I know, mom.
Nothing escapes the wicked,
wondrous gaze
of the crystal ball.
You've got that right,
young lady.
The crystal ball
tells it all.
You didn't touch it,
did you?
No, of course not.
It's probably lonely
without me.
I'll take good care of it,
mom, I promise.
You just stay away from it.
I have to get going.
Your aunt will be out
of the hospital today.
Okay, well, stop fussing.
I promise everything
will be ready, okay?
It better be.
And remember, I'll find out.
Okay. Love you too. Bye.
See, you guys?
I told you.
She loves that thing
way too much.
I don't know.
I think it's kinda cute.
Maybe you just gotta
get to know it better.
[Deep laughter]
Hey, if you break that,
i am in deep crap.
Catalina:
Yeah, boobs!
Whatever, you guys.
Hey, what is this?
Open it.
Ugh.
You have such
beautiful eye.
That thing
is really gross.
Hey, we could put it
right here on the pedestal.
Catalina: Yeah.
Keep watch over us.
Uh-huh. Oh, hang on.
Oh, it's a DVD
of the movie.
What movie?
The killer eye, durr.
They made a movie
out of that thing?
They make movies
out of everything.
I saw one once
where this evil bong
sucked people inside of it when
you smoked out of it.
What was inside?
Naked bitches.
So hot.
That's my kind of
horror movie.
I love those movies.
Hey, I think we can
call it a night, right?
Maybe we should just stop
decorating for a while
and watch it.
It's not exactly
a chick flick.
It's more like
a dick flick.
Come on.
Don't be bitches, bitches.
It's probably like,
really cool
with lots of blood
and brains and...
Boobies?
Well, we can only hope.
Come on, you guys.
Rocky:
Come on.
Jen's under a lot of stress.
It's probably
gonna be great.
Everyone in favor,
raise your hand and say "aye."
Aye!
Okay, but I'm not saying it.
Come on!
Does somebody think
she's too cool for school?
[Sighs]
Whatever. Aye.
[Crickets chirping]
Tonight's feature presentation
is the killer eye.
It's about
a gigantic eyeball
that lives
in the eighth dimension.
Eighth dimension? Don't we have
enough trouble
with the three
we're living in?
Don't forget the fourth. Time.
So, what's the fifth?
The twilight zone,
of course.
My bad.
Don't ask me what six
and seven are. I have no idea.
Okay, so the eyeball's
from the eighth dimension.
Why are we watching
this again?
'Cause it's fun.
The eyeball lives off
some kind of electrical power,
sends people into a trance,
kills some of them,
and impregnates the women
so that killer eyes
can invade our world.
Like a sexy version
of "the body snatchers."
Hell, in our
current mental state,
it's bound to be
a fucking classic.
Oh, wait.
We can't watch it yet.
Killer eye wants
to watch too.
He loves to watch.
He's a peeping peeper.
The shit that turns you on,
girl... unreal.
Never thought
I'd have a nympho nerd
for one of my homegirls.
Um, geek, please.
Geeks are hot,
nerds are not.
Mmm-hmm.
I think he's kind of cute,
in a round sort of way.
[***]
Okay, now we are ready
for our main attraction.
Here we go.
[Scary music playing over TV]
Rocky:
Oooh. Da-daa!
Jen:
You guys, shhh!
The killer eye.
Shhh! You guys!
Oh, my God,
jacqueline lovell
or something.
[Laughing]
Jonathan Norman!
Jen:
Are you gonna talk
through the whole thing?
Maybe.
Richard chasen!
Shh!
I think he's gay.
Man 1 [Over tv]:
I'm on with this guy with this
killer band down by this beach.
Man 2:
Man, this sounds
like blackford, man.
[Indistinct chatter over TV]
[***]
Jen:
Oh, my gosh, is she dead?
Kianna:
Is that a siberian husky?
Catalina:
What?
Rocky:
She's dead or roofied,
one of the two.
Kianna:
It's roofied.
Rocky:
Does he know
that giant eyeball's there?
Catalina:
Boobies! Whoa!
Jen:
I thought this was rated pg.
[***]
Rocky:
And see? Siberian husky.
What did I say?
Oh, God.
Oh, my God, there's lightning
shooting from her nipples.
Jen: Shh!
What is that?
That's the grossest penis
I've ever seen.
Catalina:
He is not hot.
He's got crisco like
all up in his hair.
Yeah, is he sweaty,
or...? I don't get it.
Looks like
he rubbed crisco...
What is going on?
This is the least scary...
Kianna:
You put this movie in.
Rocky:
I think it's frickin' amazing.
Jenna, you have such
a huge boner for this movie.
Jen:
Shut up!
Rocky:
You can't deny
this is cinema genius.
[Laughing]
Yeah.
Kianna: Eww!
What is that
doing to her?
Woman [Over tv]:
Yeah, but the thing
we couldn't figure out is,
what are we gonna
use for bait?
You.
What?
We'll find somewhere dark,
like the attic,
where we know the eye
is sure to show up.
We know it's obviously
attracted to you.
Yeah, I'm real flattered,
but, you know...
And, when
it does show up,
we exit, trap the eye,
lock the door,
set off the bolt.
Man 2:
And run like hell, I hope.
Man 1:
We'll have five minutes
before the bomb goes off,
should give us enough time
to be out of the blast radius.
And what if it isn't?
Quite frankly,
the explosion will be so huge,
you wouldn't even feel
or see a thing.
So Peter and I are going
to go up to the attic.
I want the rest of you
to stay right here
and don't move until
we have trapped the eye.
You got that?
What if i
gotta take a pee?
You hold it.
Well, what about when it was in
the street kid's head?
Didn't that,
like, recharge it?
No. No, the kid
was already dead.
There's no active brain cells,
so...
It needs active brain cells
in order to energize it.
And how does it
pull that off?
Catalina:
Oh, I just wear
my socks in bed. What?
Kianna:
I hate it when guys do that.
Catalina:
Ooh, I know
how he got this part.
Casting couch.
Rocky: Richard.
Richard chasen.
He's about to
whack off to this eye.
I'm riveted.
Kianna: I'm scared.
Rocky: No homo.
Or homa,
you know what I'm saying?
Kianna: Who's that?
Catalina: Eww!
Rocky:
Ugh!
Oh, my God.
Zoom into your face.
Hi!
[Speaking indistinctly]
Jen: Now he's really big.
Rocky: Yeah.
[Electricity crackling]
Man, why haven't I seen
somebody...
Jen:
Whoa! I didn't
see that coming.
Rocky:
Jersey shore's goin' down. Whoa.
[***]
Sucks.
What are you talking about?
I'm loving it.
Are you serious,
girlfriend?
This movie is about as fun
as going down on 80s bush.
Well, from my perspective.
It isn't fun.
[***]
[Electricity crackling]
Hey, did you hear that?
I didn't hear anything
but a pervert eyeball
squishing around.
Maybe what we need is
a different soundtrack.
That's what
I'm talking about.
[Dance music playing]
* all right, all right *
* want a piece? *
* I can give you,
feel the freeze *
hey, turn that down.
* take a picture
if you sell it *
[***]
[Muted sound]
[Groaning]
Teach me how to Dougie.
Oh, I can teach you
more than that, girl.
You guys,
be careful around that.
If we break it, we don't have to
worry about Giselle finding out.
My mom's gonna kill us.
That's for you, Jenna.
[Laughing]
You tease!
Holy shit!
Oh, my God.
I am so sorry.
It's...
* I know the flow and hustle *
okay...
* catching fame
and watch my haters *
[***]
[Electricity crackling]
Hey. Hey, look.
Did you guys see that?
Um...
I don't...
I guess it was nothing.
I told you that weed
was good, girl.
Yeah, that must be it.
Let's get this
in the wash, okay?
No, it's okay. It's
just...
No, I've got stuff
for you. You can borrow.
I don't need to wear
your clothes.
It's fine.
I don't care.
You can have them
if you want.
Well, I definitely need
to take a shower.
This stuff is
really sticky.
Okay, it's not a problem.
Let's go.
You might
want to pause that.
Otherwise the plot
might get us all confused.
Cock!
[***]
I gotta go make a drink.
Double cock. I'm out.
Now what am i
supposed to suck on?
Just give those things up.
They're gonna rot
your teeth anyways.
I have a wicked
oral fixation.
Besides, I like to
think of it as practice.
Okay, well, why don't
we go make me a drink
and find something
for you to practice on?
[***]
[Electricity crackling]
[Gasps]
Stupid thing.
[Baby crying]
[***]
I can't believe they didn't
invite me to this party.
[Groaning]
Jesus.
Freaky.
[Water running]
[Electricity crackling]
Hey!
Oh, shit!
Girl, you nearly freaked me
out of my skin.
Knock next time.
What are you doing? Peeping on
me, perv?
No,
i was just telling you
that your clothes
are laid out for you.
That couldn't have waited?
Well, maybe I was peeping,
just a little.
Man [Over tv]:
Did you find that wallet?
[Suspenseful music playing
over TV]
[Electricity crackling]
[Heart beating]
[Screams]
[Groans]
What the hell are
you screaming about?
[Rustling]
Hey, hey.
Quit... quit that.
Seen anything peculiar
around here?
Yeah.
Right, dumb question.
Man:
What... what are you
looking for, anyway?
Woman:
The killer eye.
Man:
The killer what?
Killer eye.
This big eyeball floating
around diddling everybody.
[Laughing]
I don't know anything
about killer eye,
but right now,
I've got a killer buzz.
Woman:
You're pathetic.
Man:
Hey, you can't
just come in here
and call me names
like that.
I'm tellin' Joe.
Where is he, anyway?
He's next door
keeping an eye on Jane.
[Suspenseful music playing]
Thank you.
Oh! What are you doing?
Massage.
[Thunder crashes]
There's something
awfully familiar about this.
Martin would wring your neck
if he caught you.
Mine too.
Roll over.
Listen, Joe,
you're a really nice guy,
but I love my husband.
Understand?
[Screams]
Somebody help me! Help me!
You killed my best friend,
you stupid bitch!
It doesn't seem to be
growing very weak to me.
Jean?
I'm okay.
It's not any weaker
'cause he got a recharge
from Joe's brain matter.
Man:
What's that mean?
It means your friend's brain
has been sucked dry.
Is he gonna be okay?
He's dead, you moron.
This is serious. It's killing
people, attacking the women.
We can't afford to play around
with this thing.
We've gotta call somebody,
dead body in the attic or not.
Woman:
What the hell is
going on around here?
What the hell?
[***]
Doctor:
No, no.
We'll stick together,
keep the lights on.
We definitely have the
advantage.
Ugh! Gross.
Woman:
My God.
Man:
Very difficult.
Doctor:
No, we just relax.
Man:
Your lights!
Hit it with your lights!
Hey! Kianna.
What?
Did you do something
with the eye?
Your eye? What the fuck's
wrong with your eye?
Not my eye,
the killer eye replica.
I don't know
nothin' about it.
Well, okay, fine.
Get your ass in here
and get your booze.
Trip's trippin'.
That thing isn't even hers.
Your lights.
Hit it with your lights.
[Screeching]
Don't let it get away.
Ooh, come to mama.
Did you find
your suckers?
I haven't found
shit up in here.
happy hunting.
This totally sucks.
[***]
Kianna:
Shit.
I see you.
Get your ass in here.
I saw cars out front. Looked
like a party.
Nobody parties
without the gis.
Eww, that sounds
so gross.
What up, kianna?
Hop off me, skank,
I'm busy.
Look, I just came to party.
It isn't really a party.
Could've fooled me.
Well, Jenna just asked us
to come over
and help her set up
the haunted house,
and she knew
you weren't into that shit.
What shit?
Anything that resembles work.
Ha. She got that right.
So if you wanna go
upstairs and talk to her,
I'm sure she won't mind
if you stay.
She better not.
Come on. Let's go.
Okay, so be prepared
to be really creeped out.
Giselle:
I'm so afraid.
Ta-da!
A lot of work went into this,
just so you know.
Seriously.
Kinda dramatic.
Speaking of dramatic,
let's not make this dramatic.
Just go talk to Jen
and everything'll be cool.
[Sighs]
All right.
Make me a drink, kay?
Make it neat.
Slut.
[Eerie music playing over TV]
[Electricity crackling]
Damn. I'm hit.
Dear lolly-gods,
please bestow upon me
your sweet, bountiful nectar.
I know this may sound
silly to ask for,
but I really need something hard
in my mouth right now.
You know what I mean.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit, lolly-gods.
You guys
don't fuck around.
[Electricity crackling]
[Screaming]
[Screams]
We have to bring
all this stuff downstairs.
I told you that would fit.
My ass looks so
totally delish in this.
I know. It looks perfect.
You're welcome to try a piece.
I told you
i don't swing that way.
It's one thing
to admire from afar,
but I don't need to know it
up close and personal.
Not even bi-curious?
Not even.
But let me know when we're the
last two survivors on earth.
Thanks, tramp.
[***]
[Electricity crackling]
I'm sorry if I hurt
your feelings, cat.
No, man, it's my bad.
You're right.
I shouldn't come on
to you like that.
No, it's okay.
I like it.
You really shouldn't
be such a tease.
You know how bad
i want you.
I'm not teasing.
But what about
all that stuff
you just said about
last two bitches
on earth
and all that bullshit,
like...?
Bitch can
change her mind.
Right.
[***]
[Laughs]
Seriously? What the hell?
Gis!
What's going on here,
you guys?
I... it just happened.
Three's company.
Unless you grow
a monster dick,
I'm not interested.
I-i-i...
No, you don't have to explain
to me, hot crotch.
What happened?
Hey, I wasn't that bad.
[Giselle laughs]
Um, what's going on here,
and why wasn't I invited?
Honestly, I have no idea.
We were trying to put
the haunted house together
and I guess
things got out of hand.
I guess so.
[Slurping noises]
Did you guys
just hear something?
Come on, let's get a drink.
Are you coming, cat?
I... I'll be down in a minute.
I'm gonna relax here
for a second.
[***]
[Baby crying]
[Electricity crackling]
[Screams]
[Coughing]
[Spits]
I have better things to do.
[Sighs]
[Electricity crackling]
[Screams]
[***]
What in the blazes
are you doing?
Where are your clothes,
slut?
Hello?
Anybody in there?
Hey, Jen.
Get in here.
Whoa. What's wrong with her?
I don't know.
One minute she was
her normal, annoying self,
and the next minute,
she's whoring it up.
She looks like she's
in some kind of trance.
[***]
Shit.
Tramp is just high
or something.
You're looking
good tonight,
bitch known as "rocky."
Are you insane?
Okay, you two
are punking me, right?
Me and gis? You know she doesn't
have a sense of humor.
Rocky:
Okay, so then, you tell me
what's wrong with her, then.
Nothing's wrong, sexy.
You're too stressed out,
bitch known as "rocky."
I could help you calm down.
Oh,
shut your whore hole.
I'm gonna punch you
in the cooter,
I swear to God.
Unbe-fucking-lieveable.
The eye doesn't
understand our world.
It's still young.
What the fuck?
Wait, what do you mean
"it's still young"?
It's still learning.
Learning about what?
Learning about us.
About itself.
About what it can do.
And if we don't do
what it wants,
it will kill us.
Whoa.
The bitch known as "Jenna"
knows how serious this is,
and you will too
once you look over there.
There's your
goddamn toy.
[Speaking indistinctly]
Wait, wait, don't
stare right into it.
Staring at it?
I'm going to shove this
up the ugly thing's butt.
No, rocky, don't.
[Grunts]
[Screams]
Oh, my God. Ah.
Oh, oh!
[Panting]
Oh!
Hey, Jenna.
What's up?
Where's rocky?
I'm filled with desire.
Come on, let's bang.
Jesus h.
Snap out of it.
Wha... what'd you do that for?
It's the eye.
The replica I got.
Somehow it's come to life.
I don't know how,
but it has,
and it put you under a trance,
and it killed rocky.
Don't look at the TV!
Giselle!
[Electricity crackling]
Let's rub donuts.
Would you knock it off?
Man, you're a real downer.
I'm sorry, but this
worked the last time.
[Gasps]
We have to leave.
I'm gonna go upstairs
and get catalina,
and there's something of my
dad's I think might help us.
Hurry up.
Be careful.
[***]
Cat, come on,
we've gotta go.
[Screams]
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
Got you!
I know you're there,
you little bastard.
[Screaming]
Fuck you!
Rocky?
But you...
But I'm fine.
Nothing happened to me
in the next room.
Don't you wanna fuck me?
Just a little.
Weird ass hoe.
[***]
Hmm...
I think I look hot.
The eye wants something.
Jesus Christ, here we go.
It wants something from you,
bitch known as "Giselle."
It wants something
from all of us.
Oh yeah, and what's that?
It wants to
procreate with us.
Procreate?
You still don't get it.
This is going to happen.
My ass it will.
Ooh. Your ass.
Hey!
Don't fight it, Giselle.
Hey, let me go. Fuck you!
[Thud]
[Wind howling]
George, I'm scared.
Oh, don't be afraid.
I wouldn't let anything
happen to you.
You know, I have
a confession to make.
I mean, since we might be
getting blown to bits and all.
I haven't been the most
faithful wife in the world.
I know.
And, you know, you haven't been
the most loving husband.
I know that too.
And I was... I was thinking
maybe we should get a divorce.
Wow!
That good for you?
Real good!
[***]
[Moaning]
Oh, it's never
been like this.
Mmm.
Oh, God!
Don't be afraid, Rita.
It's not an evil being.
It let me look
into its mind.
What'd it just do to me?
It had certain needs,
and it asked me to help it,
and in exchange,
it's gonna help me.
And so I did it.
I did it, Rita.
It's gonna show me
how to open up a real portal
to the eighth dimension.
I mean, isn't this great?
A whole world full of these
little guys everywhere you look?
What are you
talking about?
This eye.
It's not here by accident.
Rocky?
We're leaving.
It doesn't want us
to leave, Jenna.
Put that down.
Not on your life.
I said, "put it down."
Hey!
Get off of me! Stop it.
Don't fight it, Jenna.
Do what it says.
No!
Listen to it, Jenna.
Open your eyes.
[***]
Get off of me!
Open your eyes.
Cat?
Wakey, wakey.
[In deep voice]
Time to get nakey.
Jenna just went
upstairs to get you.
I'm not there.
Obviously.
We have to get Jenna
and get out of here.
Jenna can wait.
This can't.
[***]
[Moans]
[Growls]
[Bones snap]
[Screams]
Stop it.
No!
Look at it, Jenna.
[Screams, grunts]
Ugh!
[Electricity crackling]
Help! We have to...
[Screams]
No! No!
[Electricity crackling]
[Groaning]
[Grunts]
[Screams]
[Panting]
I think it's over.
Guess I turned that
freaky-deaky pervert into jelly.
Oh.
I thought
you took off on me.
Never. Oh.
[***]
[Indistinct groaning]
* let's go, it's party time *
* mount up, fellas *
* what up? *
* it's taxation
without representation *
* let's scream *
* fired up, fired up, come on *
* fired up, fired up,
come on *
* fired up, fired up, come on *
* fired up, fired up *
* call me *
* fired up, fired up, come on *
* fired up, fired up,
come on *
* fired up, fired up, come on *
* call me *
* freshly showered,
smell couture *
* took about an hour
to get dressed and get gone *
* there's a whole lot of power
in this excursion *
* we roll *
* it's on *
* Hollywood bound
hit the town, it's hot *
* you can tell from the line
wrapped around us *
* valet parked just to make
their jaws drop *
* oh *
* straight to the ball
from preliminaries *
* and the bmc's headed
to the vip *
* bottles of grey goose *
* and the grand marnier's
flowing continually *
* that goose
best way to get it started *
* from the boom box
invade a room *
* let's see, you got it
yeah, you, grab your girl *
* come on, let's party
with ohh, that body *
* this for all my peoples
who've been living for me *
* tell my man what you drinking
'cause it's rounds on me *
* got my hands
on this Lincoln, come on *
* ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba *
* this for all my peoples
who've been living for me *
* tell my man what you drinking
'cause it's rounds on me *
* got my hands
on this Lincoln, come on *
* ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba *
* after party,
back to the hut *
* truckload of hotties
hot for me *
* it's however many bodies
we can fit up in the truck *
* 'cause they're all... *
* Roscoe's to go,
i can't go wrong *
* ordered about an hour ago
it takes so long *
* it's the late night place
that's worth the wait *
* ohh *
* it's so bomb, eh, okay *
* with chicks
that go both ways *
* don't play your hood
if you out to get paid *
* might get mad cover
most likely blazed *
* but ohh *
* no change, don't break that
i think we'll be cool *
* I hit you
whenever I'm in your city *
* keep it crew *
* bring your girls
let them do what they do *
* got my whole crew
acting fools *
* this for all my peoples
who've been living for me *
* tell my man what you drinking
'cause it's rounds on me *
* got my hands
on this Lincoln, come on *
* ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba *
* this for all my peoples
who've been living for me *
* tell my man what you drinking
'cause it's rounds on me *
* got my hands
on this Lincoln, come on *
* ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba *
* this for all my peoples
who've been living for me *