GIRL: So here's
the crazy thing.
Invisibility is everywhere.
I mean, sure, people tend to
focus on the things we can see.
Like matter, living things.
But there's also all this stuff
that we can't see.
Like sound waves or gasses.
And a few things we miss
because they're hidden
in plain sight.
Like I said,
invisibility is all around us.
Even in the most obvious
and familiar places.
These opposites exist
side by side.
The seen...
Hey, Molly!
...and the unseen.
( indistinct chatter )
♪ This is the time ♪
And the same pattern
repeats itself.
Over and over.
♪ Your life is waiting ♪
Those bright, shiny objects,
they soak up all the attention.
While at the same time,
the invisible objects
right under our noses don't.
♪ Your life is waiting ♪
♪ And as you fall ♪
That's just the way
things are.
( bell rings )
We can't change it.
No matter how much
we might want to.
At least,
that's what I thought.
( bell rings )
( indistinct chatter )
( muffled rock music plays )
- ( music stops )
- Mr. Perkins.
Fancy seeing you here.
Well, I really hope
you were meditating
on the marvels of science
and not rocking out
to Fitz and the Tantrums again.
Oh, well, actually
it is The Hives today,
in honor
of those skinny jeans
you are only slightly too old
to pull off.
GIRL: Ah, look at that.
Not so fast.
Yeah, I got your pitch
for the semester project.
Really? Turning a papaya
into a battery?
I've already got seven other
kids turning vegetables
into batteries.
In my defense,
papaya's a fruit.
Mm. Well, your proposal
is officially rejected.
( scoffs )
George gets all A's
and you're letting him study
how a guinea pig reacts
to an all-ice cream diet.
- It gives them terrible gas.
- Yeah, thanks, George.
Make sure you put that
in your report, okay?
(guinea pig passes gas )
That's it, Mr. Whiskers,
no more Rocky Road for you.
I want to see you challenge
yourself. Do something relevant.
Maybe something to do
with transformation.
This is the same matter
in two distinct forms.
One state is dense, dull--
Much like this conversation.
The other is transparent.
Brilliant. I'm assigning you
a new experiment.
Figure out what that
substance is,
then transform it
into its crystal state.
And how am I supposed
to do that?
Build a homemade
spectrometer.
Yeah. You're gonna have
to do this little thing
we in the science community
like call science.
You think The Hives
became The Hives
by shutting out the world
and listening to their
headphones all day?
No. They got out there.
All right, my point is you never
know what you can accomplish
unless you engage the world
a little bit.
And as an added incentive,
I've decided as of right now,
this is worth
half your class grade.
- What?
- Mm-hmm. Check out
whatever gear you need.
You've got till Monday.
( scoffs )
He wants me to make mystery gunk
into a crystal.
That's impossible.
It's not technically impossible.
It's not like
"time-travel impossible,"
or "speed-of-light
impossible".
It's just... hard.
George, why are you
wearing clown pants?
These are
vintage lounge slacks.
They're all the rage
in Budapest,
which is the new Paris,
by the way.
Girls dig these pants.
At least six girls
have noticed them.
Okay. One girl noticed them.
And that girl was you.
Just now.
( indistinct chatter )
Whoa!
Nice vampire outfit, freakshow.
But Halloween's
not till tomorrow.
Really? "Vampire outfit?"
Is that all you got?
Is it because of my cape
and my pointy teeth?
Code red, code red!
C-Dog approaching.
11 o'clock. Be cool!
- What?
- Hey, Cleo!
Carter, my man.
What's the ups?
Lay the good news on me.
- How's it going?
- Good.
I was just wondering if maybe
you wanted to study together
- for Perkins' next quiz?
- BOY: Who is that?
- ALL: ( laugh )
- No idea.
Yeah! Yeah, totally.
We could be a cliché, how fun.
I'm sorry, cliché?
The sports guy, asking the nerdy
girl for help with his homework.
No. I just thought we could,
you know, join forces.
Uh... okay. I'm going to be in
the lab for study hall tomorrow.
If you have a change of heart,
stop by.
Your epic crush
just asked you out on a date,
and you shut him down.
That wasn't a date, George.
That was just a crafty jock
trying to weasel his way
out of doing any actual
thinking. No thanks.
I'll leave the mindless flirting
to my sister.
"Awesome city! So the bomb!"
MOLLY: Cleo!
Speak of the devil.
Hello, car full
of beautiful women.
School's done.
You know what that means.
Fro-yo. YOLO.
Oh, no. Let's go! Yeah!
ALL: ( whooping )
- You wanna come with?
- Yes!
No, thanks. I'll pass.
Darn.
Come on.
It'll be awesome city,
totally the bomb.
( scoffs )
Thanks, I'll pass.
It's Thursday! They're gonna
have salted caramel!
Come on! Yeah.
Your buddy can come too.
This is George, Coug.
You've met him 400 times.
Sorry, small dude. My bad!
Still a pass.
Catch you later then, sis.
- GIRL: All right, let's go!
- ALL: ( whooping )
Come on.
I'll give you a ride home.
I've got
the big scooter today.
I made a few modifications
to it.
Really souped it up.
All right! Give The Coug a paw!
( chuckles )
Aw, yes!
( trolley bell dings )
( scooter engine sputters )
( backfiring )
( engine dies )
( engine grinding )
- MAN: Honey!
- WOMAN: Yes?
MAN: Did you pack my charger?!
It's in your dopp kit.
And I printed
the boarding passes.
MAN: ( laughs )
There it is!
- It was in my dopp kit!
- WOMAN: Yeah.
( pulls zipper )
Do they even know you're
here yet?
Give them a second.
Oh. Hi. We were afraid we were
going to miss you.
- Hey, George.
- Hey, Cleo's Dad.
I'm gonna get Whiskers
all settled in.
I'll see you inside.
Okay, remember,
set the alarm on at night.
Don't touch the thermostats.
And there are protein shakes
if you run out of food.
Honey, I am so sorry we're gonna
miss the big lacrosse game.
No worries, Dad.
There'll be others.
But the first game always
sets the tone for the season.
- The college scouts
will be there.
- Ohh!
- Just remember,
keep that stick up.
- Stay loose.
Keep that middle line open and
cross if they double team you.
- ( playful growl )
- BOTH: ( chuckle )
And you...
Stay loose, you know,
with your studies and stuff.
I'll be sure to do
some rigorous stretching
before I tackle my homework.
- MOM: Okay.
- Okay. Bring it in, team.
- One, two, three, family!
- ALL: Family!
MOM: ( whoops ) Bye, girls.
- Bye.
- Bye, Mom.
- CLEO: Bye!
- MOLLY: Bye, guys!
Oh, I forgot to mention,
I'm having some people
over for dinner tonight.
Molly, you can't. I have to
focus on my science project.
Who's coming over?
Just a few girls from
the lacrosse team.
The whole team.
And their boyfriends.
And anybody else
who wanted to come.
( sighs )
- ( loud music )
- ( excited chatter )
ALL: ( chanting)
Hoo! Hoo! Sad but true!
The Fightin' Owls
are hunting for you!
Does anyone know
what goes in meatballs?
- Meat, babe.
- Huh.
( playful screams )
( squeaks )
( muffled music thumping )
( computer beeps )
( scoffs ) This is hopeless.
I can't even get light
to pass through it.
Did you try diluting it?
- Yes.
- ( splashing in pool )
I can't believe I've been exiled
out of my own house.
I don't think you were exiled
so much as "gently displaced."
You know what I suggest?
A break. We head inside,
sample some meatballs,
see if maybe one
of your sister's teammates
has a penchant for shorter,
less athletic,
but very intelligent, men.
You should go, George.
Go get some food.
I'll still be working.
You're a good person.
( passes gas )
( up-temp pop song plays )
♪ Trick or treat
Feeling kinda creepy ♪
I don't mean to brag, but I'm
a bit of an athlete myself.
I was one of the top
lawn bowlers at math camp
last summer.
You know they call lawn bowling
the "gentleman's polo".
- I like horses.
- Me too!
I love horses!
Love them!
What are your thoughts
on guinea pigs?
CLEO: Let's see what happens
if I turn up the heat.
( typing on keyboard )
( computer beeps )
Now we're getting somewhere.
Sucrose.
How sweet of  Señor  Perkins.
He gave me sugar.
( chuckles )
Shoo! Get out of here.
Ahh!
Ahh! Oh!
( grunts )
Uh...
Move!
Damn! ( panting )
( grunts )
( alarm beeping )
Had a little oven-temperature
misfire, but all good now!
CLEO: Coming through!
Excuse me
for just one second.
Hey, what's going on?
George, I made a moth disappear!
Ooh! Ooh!
- What?!
- I know this sounds impossible,
but it's true.
I don't see it!
Where is it?
- Do you see that?
- Uh... not really.
Thanks for coming, guys.
Get some rest.
We have a big day
tomorrow.
No!
No, no, no!
( panting )
Bye, guys.
On the bright side,
the lacrosse girls dug me.
I got a bunch of digits.
You got no digits.
I got no digits.
But I did enter my number
into Nikki's phone
while she wasn't looking.
That's something.
BOTH: ( chuckle )
I made a moth invisible.
You believe me, right?
I believe... you probably
should get to sleep.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Ugh.
( alarm beeping )
Ahhhh!
Molly?
Molly, are you okay?
MOLLY: Where am I?!
Uh, you're in the bathroom.
MOLLY: No, I'm not. I'm gone.
What do you mean, you're gone?
Um... Molly?
- Molly, where did you go--
- MOLLY: Exactly!
- ( startled gasp )
- MOLLY: Where did I go?
I don't know!
I don't know where I went!
- Cleo!
- Ahh!
I'm not in the toilet!
( whimpering )
MOLLY: This is just a bad dream.
Wake up, Molly! Wake up!
Okay. There.
Now, I'm going to
remove this towel
and be awake and everything
will be totally normal.
MOLLY: Ahhhh!
Ahhh!
- What are you doing?
- Calling for help!
And what are you
going to tell them, Molly?
I don't know!
That I've disappeared?
I'm invisible?
I can't see myself?
( sighs ) You're right.
They're gonna think
I'm a crazy person.
Okay. This is going
to sound insane,
but I think my experiment
spread to you.
What are you talking about?!
I made a moth invisible
last night.
- You what?!
- I was working
on a sugar solution
and then I just spilled a bunch
of chemicals into the mixture
and then a moth flew
through steam and it
became invisible.
Did it land on you or touch
or did you swallow it?
You're asking me if I swallowed
an invisible moth?
Actually, there was something.
Something in the bathroom
in my water.
It was really weird.
It was sorta bug-like. Gross.
The bathroom window was open?
Yeah. I think so.
Okay, so what if the moth was
attracted to the light
and then it flew into the room
and then fell into your water?
Where I accidentally drank it?
Are you kidding me?!
I accidentally drank your
invisible science project moth
- and now I'm invisible too?!
- ( knocking )
THE COUG: Hello?
Happy Halloween, everyone!
- ( stomach growls )
- Oh, man!
Yo, next time The Coug says he's
gonna eat 26 meatballs,
you tell him
that's too many meatballs.
Oh, no. Your boyfriend's here.
Oh. Hey, Cleo.
Hi, Coug.
You're... a bear.
Sure am. Didn't Molly tell you?
We're all going as a big
Wizard of Oz team costume.
I'm the Cowardly Bear.
- It's a lion.
- What's a lion?
The Cowardly...? Never mind.
Uh, is Molly ready to roll?
Um, no, she is sick.
And she's in the bathroom.
And you can't see her.
Oh, no. Was it the meatballs?
Molls? Babe?
Are you okay?
MOLLY: ( muffled )
Oh, not really.
Cleo's right.
I'm really sick.
You're our Dorothy!
Let me take a look at you--
No! I'm very contagious!
Nobody can see me.
Literally.
Go, Coug.
Save yourself.
Quick! Go!
- Quick!
- ( gasps )
- Bye!
- Bye.
- I guess.
( exhales )
Wow, Molly,
your boyfriend.
Two words:
"Cowardly Bear."
MOLLY: ( sighs ) Can we maybe
not mock my boyfriend right now
and instead focus
on the crisis at hand?
Okay. You're invisible.
How and why are you invisible?
- You tell me.
- I don't know.
If it spread
through your body this fast,
it's extremely soluble.
It should only take a few hours.
A few hours?!
I think. I hope.
Okay, listen, Molly,
I have to get to school
and figure this whole thing out.
And what am I supposed to do?
Just lay low. Call in sick.
I can't!
I can't miss school today!
Wait. It's Halloween.
Really, Molly? I think your
friends can survive Halloween
without Dorothy.
You don't understand. Today is
the first game of the season.
If I don't go to all my classes,
I can't play.
This is what you're
concerned about, lacrosse?
College scouts
will be at that game.
This is my only chance
for them to see me.
And my teammates
are counting on me.
I can't let them down.
I can work with this.
Maybe with a little make-up
and some gloves.
Cleo!
The invisibility must... spread.
So I anything that I touch will
gradually become invisible too?!
I don't know, Molly.
Yes?
So there's absolutely no way
I can un-invisible myself?
- I have an idea.
- What?
Yup. We're the same height,
we sound the same,
we'd have the same skin tone
if you ever learn to moisturize.
This could totally work.
This is insane.
There is no way I'm going to
pull off pretending to be you.
I'll be there coaching you.
( scoffs ) Come on, Molly. Even
with the hair and the makeup,
I'm still me.
A mask, really?
Dorothy didn't wear a mask.
We're in New Orleans. Just say
you're Mardi Gras Dorothy.
Mardi Gras Dorothy?
Yeah. From a big
Munchkin Town parade float,
with Munchkins
giving beads and stuff.
Look, I've gotta
go to school today.
So you've gotta get me
through this.
Get your science gear
and do whatever it is you
need to do to figure this out.
Just please help me
get through my day
until I can
be seen again, okay?
Besides, you look totally cute.
- Fine. Give me your car keys.
- What?
Molly, you're invisible.
You can't drive.
Well, you can't drive either.
You don't have a license!
( car engine starts )
This is crazy.
What if we get pulled over?
How do we explain this?
MOLLY: Relax.
It's going to be fine.
Sorry. Just talking
to my invisible sister.
She's a really amazing driver.
MOLLY: See? She probably thought
this was one of those
self-driving cars.
( boat blows horn )
( up-tempo pop song )
♪ If you could see
inside of me ♪
♪ Everything that I could be ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
This is never going to work.
Dorothy should've made
better life choices.
"Oh, there's a tornado coming.
I'm gonna go
put on my party clothes."
Come on, you'll be fine.
( grunts )
Don't walk like you.
Walk like me. Stand up straight.
Look more cheerful. Wave.
- GIRL 1: Hi, molly.
- GIRL 2: Hey, Molly.
- GIRL 3: Hey, Molly.
- MOLLY: See?
- This is totally working.
- GROUP: Hi, Molly!
Okay, here's the real test. If
Nikki buys this, everyone will.
Okay, act natural.
But... act like me.
Act like natural me.
Molly?
Yes.
Oh, Molls! I'm so glad you're
here! I thought you were sick.
Uh, yeah,
- I am still very sick.
- Oh.
But I'm a bit better
and I'm still quite pale
and my voice is a bit different.
But, you know, Nikki,
it's okay.
Awesome city, right?
I love the mask.
The mask. Uh, right.
Well, I am
Mardi Gras Dorothy.
Hmm, cute.
Molls, I'm totally freaking out.
Arianna Burmeister is
also out sick,
so that means
I'm totally in charge
of Romp the Swamp tonight.
And I don't know what to do or
if we have enough decorations.
Please, just tell me
everything's gonna be okay.
That actually
sounds awful Nikki,
but I would just cancel.
- ( gasps )
- Are you okay?
Uh, I am fine. I just have a
little neck twitch this morning,
- but it is okay.
- (laughs softly )
Molls, you're here.
But I thought you were sick.
- She got better.
- Hey, that's great!
- Give the Coug some sugar.
- No. No, that is eww.
Um, I am very contagious.
So I will see you around. Bye.
Molls?
Did I do something wrong?
Um, no, no.
It's-It's my disease.
( cell phone rings )
Hey, George.
GEORGE: You're not at school?
No. I'm-I'm really sick.
Your sister's here.
She's like some freaky carnival
milkmaid Zorro.
Hey, Molly!
Uh, yeah. Yep.
She is Mardi Gras Dorothy.
She looks totally smokin'.
What? Eww. ( scoffs )
George, can you please
just cover for me today
in Perkins' class?
You got it.
CLEO: All right, Molly, we have
to go get to the lab.
No. First period is starting.
I can't be late.
And what class is it, Molly?
Intro to Conformity?
Intro to Geometry, room 42.
Come on.
C-minus?
Molly, if you needed help
with line segments,
you could've just asked.
Right, because
you're always so...
warm and supportive.
Okay. I have to go
get to study hall
so I can get a big
compound microscope
so I can figure
this whole thing out.
Actually,
I'll grab it for you.
You have to get
to Pep Circle.
Pep what?
( awkward laugh )
BOTH: (laugh softly)
That was weird.
A thing we do on game days.
Just bonding and trust-building.
It's a pre-game ritual...
that you are leading.
- ( applause )
- (cheers )
ALL: ( chanting ) Trust!
Teamwork! Fellowship! Pride!
A team united can't be denied!
Whoo!
Who puts the pep
in Pep Circle?
ALL: We do!
Please don't make me do this.
Molly! You made it!
ALL: Molly!
I've warmed us up. We're totally
ready for you to take over.
Oh, well, that's just great.
Um, so let's just go straight
into the first thing then
- which is the...
- Group hug!
Or we can skip the first thing!
Okay...
Oh. Oh. ( grunts )
Next thing on the agenda.
The circle of trust.
Right.
So let's circle up
and do some trust.
NIKKI: You can have the bunny.
The bunny?
The bunny of truth.
Well, the bunny of truth.
Um, Nikki, could you
please remind us all
what the rules are
of truth bunnying?
Whoever holds the bunny
gets to safely say
something true and meaningful to
clear the air before the game.
( soft laugh )
Well, then Nikki
should start us off.
Oh, okay.
Um...
Okay, I'm so grateful
to be on a team with all of you.
If I am strong, it's only
because I'm surrounded
by such strong women.
And I'm especially grateful
for Molls.
She's always there. No matter
how crazy my life gets,
she gives me the friendship
and support I need.
She's an amazing friend
and captain.
- ALL: Yeah!
- Thank you.
I also want to say one more
quick bunny truth,
and that is that
I'm really mad at the people
who invented weather apps
because don't you wanna wake up
every morning
and be surprised
at what the weather is?!
ALL: ( laugh ) Yeah.
Your turn.
Well, my truth is
that I am so grateful
to be sitting down
because this dress
is a serious chaffing hazard.
ALL: ( murmur )
Okay. Now for your...
emotional truth.
My emotional truth. That would
probably have to be that
I am fine. I am great.
Thank you, Nikki.
Molly, this is your safe place.
You can trust us.
We love you.
ALL: ( agreeing )
My truth would be...
I'm not the girl that
everybody thinks I am.
I'm not
the beautiful shining star
that everybody suspects.
I'm actually more of the person
that nobody notices,
or nobody pays attention to.
But...
this is probably why
I'm so uncomfortable here.
( uncomfortable laugh )
But, guys,
this is- this is all in my head.
Right?
Because I'm awesome city Molly.
I mean, the bomb.
Anyway, that's my truth,
which is actually,
weirdly, true.
( indistinct chatter )
( door opens )
I think that deserves
another group hug!
Um, okay.
All right. Yep, yep.
Love you too, okay.
( squeaks, then passes gas )
GEORGE: Carter. My hombre.
- How's the guinea pig?
- Still farting like a chainsaw.
I can't figure out why.
Because there's talmitic acid
in the ice cream.
It's reacting with ascorbic acid
and turning it into a fat.
Ascorbyl palmitate. They can't
metabolize the fat,
- so you end up
with the flatulence.
- How'd you know that?
I was a Governor's Scholar
in Chemistry last year.
GEORGE: Really? A Governor's
Scholar in Chemistry?
- That's, like, crazy amazing.
- How about
we keep it between us?
You know, it's not
really something
I like to advertise.
Hey. Do you know if Cleo was
planning on showing up?
I'm sorry, man.
She's actually sick today.
But I know she might've
maybe wanted to be here, maybe.
Can I ask you something?
What's Cleo's deal?
Whenever I talk to her,
it's like,
you know...
and she's kind of...
Never mind. It's cool. Uh,
good luck with the guinea pig.
( indistinct chatter and sighs )
This is actually amazing.
Oh! Okay!
- Gotta go, guys. Bye.
- GIRL: Molly?
ALL: ( murmuring )
What are you doing?
Did you get the microscope?
Forget about that!
Some really cute guy
in the science lab
was asking for you!
Oh, that's just Carter.
"Just Carter?" He's super cute
and totally into you!
No, Molly.
I'm not the kind of girl that...
guys like Carter
are ever actually into.
Come on.
There's only one way
to find out.
No. Don't you think
we have bigger things
to worry about right now?
I'm not going
to go meet Carter, okay?
That's final.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have
a massage circle to lead.
Aah! Meatballs! Meatballs!
- ( stomach gurgles loudly )
- Ohh, coming through!
Coming through!
Coming through! Mayday!
Meatballs!
- ( gurgling continues )
- Lots of meatballs!
( grunting ) Why did I eat
so many meatballs?!
Watch my fur, dudes.
( stall door shuts )
( exhales )
Here goes nothing.
You can do this, Molly.
Just hold your breath,
get in and get out.
Gross.
Uh... is there a chick in here?
MOLLY: ( deep voice ) No.
It's me, a dude.
In the stall.
Doing my dude things.
- Mmm.
- ( door closes )
- MOLLY: Carter!
- Uh, yes?
It's me! Cleo!
- Sorry, who? You're--
- I'm Cleo!
- Cleo! You showed?
- Yep! Sure did!
- I thought you were---
- MOLLY: Sick? Yes. I was.
But now I'm
feeling much better.
And you're in costume.
You hate costumes.
Yeah, I know,
but I'm working
on this thing
where I'm trying to relax more
and be less judgmental
and uptight.
GEORGE: Are you sure
you're okay?
You don't really
seem like yourself.
Those pants
look ridiculous on you.
There's the Cleo
I know and love.
So, hi. We're hanging out.
Yeah, I guess we are.
This is great.
I'm really psyched.
- You are?
- I know.
I've probably been
confusing in the past.
A little grouchy, right?
Mean, even.
But let's just
put all that behind us.
Focus on the now.
Maybe get to know each other.
Tell me about yourself.
What kind of stuff
does Carter groove to?
( gasps ) Oh, no.
Oh. Uh...
Actually, I have to run.
But maybe we could
go out sometime,
like in a non-study setting.
Like a real date.
Wait a second, I--
I'm not sure I'm hearing you
correctly in that suit.
Are you asking me out?
Yeah. I am.
What? Is that weird?
Honestly, coming from you,
a little.
- A lot, actually.
- What are you doing tonight?
Tonight? Um, I'm volunteering
at the school fundraiser.
Romp the Swamp? That's
my favorite event of the year!
I'll see you there tonight.
It's a date.
- BOTH: ( grunt )
- Coug!
Watch where you're going!
It's not The Coug!
Molly? What are you doing?
So, you didn't miss your study
date with Carter after all.
- What?
- I figured out a way
to pretend to be you.
- You what?!
- Yeah.
The bear costume
was thick enough,
so it didn't turn invisible.
Well, at least,
not right away.
Anyways,
I got you a real date.
He's working
at Romp the Swamp tonight.
At least,
I think it's a date.
Honestly, it was
a little hard to communicate,
being in the bear suit.
Oh my!
Bear. With no head.
- Headless bear.
- Oh, no.
Molly? What's happening?
I'm Cleo.
No. You're Molly.
No. That's Molly.
No. That's a headless bear.
Or an armless bear?
Torso-less bear?
Okay, I'm kind of
losing my mind right now.
George, calm down.
Remember how I made a moth
invisible last night?
- Yeah.
- CLEO: Well, it flew
into Molly's drink
and now she's invisible.
- Say something.
- MOLLY: Hi, George.
How are you?
Fine. Are you okay, Molly?
MOLLY: I'm good.
This is amazing.
And very scary.
THE COUG: Who stole
my bear costume?
MOLLY: Oh, gotta hide!
Molly! Wow, you are
a sight for sore eyes.
- Oh, hey, little guy.
- George.
Of course.
Someone stole my bear costume.
Just right out of the bathroom.
Any of you guys seen it?
Um, no. Nope, Coug.
I haven't seen a thing.
But it was so great
talking to you. Awesome city.
Um, I have to leave.
( stammers )
So do you think, in exchange for
me being cool and keeping all
this a secret,
you might put in a good word
for me with your friend Nikki?
MOLLY: You like Nikki?!
That's so adorable!
Nikki's a sweetheart.
She likes nice guys.
Just be yourself around her.
Yeah, I find the whole
"being myself" approach
never really works out for me.
Just give her a chance.
She might surprise you.
Molly Eastman?
- Yep, that's me.
- Yeah, I'm Mr. Perkins.
Your sister's
in my science class.
Oh. Well, I have
heard a lot about you.
Uh, can I talk to you
for a minute?
Sure.
Yeah, uh, listen, I know your
sister stayed home sick today.
Yeah, she's really,
really sick, Mr. Perkins.
- She has to stay home.
- Yeah. The, uh, thing is,
I went all angry teacher
on her yesterday
and I told her, well,
she'd fail my class
if she didn't deliver
on her science project.
I just want to make sure
that she's okay.
That the science project isn't
the reason she's staying home.
She's okay. Yeah.
She is actually doing a lot more
than you expected.
A lot more.
I'm pretty sure she's gonna
blow you mind.
Okay, that is great to hear.
See, I knew she had it in her.
- Thanks.
- Your sister is one of
the brightest kids
that's ever sat in my class.
She's got this potential
inside her.
You know, I think she could do
great things in this world
if she wanted to.
If she would just get out
of her own way.
Yeah.
Um, if she were here,
she would want me
to tell you that
She really doesn't want
to disappoint you.
Well,
tell her to feel better.
It was good
talking to you.
Come on.
- ( gasps ) Yes!
- ( bell rings )
- ( up-tempo pop song plays )
- ( excited chatter )
MOLLY: Cleo, shouldn't I
have at least started
turning visible by now?
CLEO: ( sighs ) Yes.
Which is exactly why
we need to go home
so we can figure
this whole thing out.
MOLLY: Wait.
We're not going home now.
But school's over.
MOLLY: And the most important
part of the day is starting.
- Which is?
- MOLLY: Lacrosse.
Making me visible
is gonna have to wait.
I... ( groans )
- ALL: ( cheering )
- MALE ANNOUNCER:
All right, everyone.
Five minutes until game time.
Don't forget to buy your
Go Fighting Owls T-shirts.
I think I'm gonna
sit this one out.
- I don't think so.
- Molly, I cannot do this.
I am going
to get creamed out there.
You'll be fine.
That's easy
for you to say.
What? You think
this is easy for me?
I'm terrified every game.
I can hardly sleep
the night before.
I have to drink ginger fizz
just to untie the knots
in my stomach.
Well, then why do you do it?
Well...
I like being on a team.
When everyone's around me,
my nerves settle.
I don't feel alone.
It's like, when I'm part of
something bigger than myself,
- it makes me better.
- Hmm.
Hey. You can do this.
I'll be there with you,
telling you exactly what to do.
( panting ) You ready to rumble,
Molls?
We've gotta rock it,
today.
Uh, yeah, rock it!
Totally.
Okay, bring it in! Bring it in!
WOMAN: Bring it in, ladies!
All right, everyone.
Go Fighting Owls!
ALL: ( cheer )
( whistle blows )
Okay, high school sports fans.
It's the moment
you've all been waiting for.
It's game time!
ALL: ( chanting ) Owls!
Owls! Owls! Owls!
MOLLY: Your stick's upside down.
Duly noted.
Molly, move up!
You're running the wrong way!
- Come on, come on, come on!
- Come on!
Yes!
( groans )
ALL: ( groan )
Wow, slow and painful start
for the Fighting Owls.
- Let's see
if they can recover.
- It's okay, it's okay.
Should somebody
call an ambulance?
( panting ) You okay?
That hurt more than anything
in my entire life has hurt.
- All right, come on. Get up.
- Sure, just let me try
and start breathing first.
Molly, what's wrong
with you? It's like you've never
held a stick before!
Uh, it must just be my cold.
( coughs )
Hey, listen to me.
This is my whole life, here.
Those college scouts are
my future. I can't lose today.
( up-tempo pop song plays )
I've got an idea.
- ( crowd cheers )
- You got this, guys!
( whistles blows )
MALE ANNOUNCER: And the
visitors win another draw.
- ( music continues )
- ( blow lands )
( groans )
- Great attack by the... wind?
- Go! Come on, come on!
- Power forward Molly Eastman.
- Whoo!
We're seeing some of her
trademark wizardry out there
with that ball.
- GIRL: Pass it!
- ( uhh )
- ( whistle blows )
- Just like that,
Owls are right back
in this one, folks!
- COUG: Yeah!
- Way to go, Molly!
The Fighting Owls
have really picked up steam.
Come on, Molly!
( music continues )
They've got the visitors
totally off-balance.
Literally.
( groans )
- ( grunts )
- Go! Go!
( whistle blows )
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
( whistle blows )
- ( whistle blows )
-  This has been a very
strong push by the visitors.
They've clearly got
their sea legs back.
( whistle blows )
- Wh--
- Come on! Come on!
( whistle blows )
- We're all tied up! Time out!
- ( whistle blows )
Refreshment?
Thanks.
You know, there's some
really complicated physics
in lacrosse.
I'm available for
a one-on-one consultation
anytime.
What makes this drink
so blue?
Huh, you got me there.
( panting )
How you doing?
I can't play.
I just can't.
I can't even feel
my legs.
Please, Cleo, this is it--
all or nothing.
MOLLY:
See over there?
This is my future, Cleo.
I need this.
All right, guys,
everybody bring it in.
Uh, good luck.
Thanks, thanks.
Okay, bye.
Okay, guys, I know
you are exhausted.
I'm exhausted
and in pain.
A lot of pain.
And I mean a  lot
of pain.
( laughter )
But there is this thing
I always say,
which is when you're part
of something
bigger than yourself,
it makes you better.
That's what
a team means.
So let's get out there
and have each others'
backs, okay?
ALL: Yeah!
You guys,
we can do this.
- Right?
- ALL: Yeah!
All right, all in.
- One, two, three...
- ALL: Owls!
Nice job.
I don't know how
you do this every week.
ANNOUNCER (over P.A.):
What an absolute classic.
We're all tied up,
30 seconds left.
Time for one more play.
CROWD: Owls! Owls! Owls...
ANNOUNCER:
What a pass by the Owls!
I can't get to the goal, Cleo.
It's all you, you got this.
Go, Molly!
CROWD: Molly! Molly! Molly...
ANNOUNCER:
Molly Eastman is now
one on one with the keeper.
( whistle blows )
ANNOUNCER:
Goal!
-  Molly Eastwood scores!
-  She did it!
ANNOUNCER:
And the Fighting Owls win 8-7!
You did it!
( all cheering )
CROWD:
Molly! Molly! Molly...
CLEO:
Hold the slide steady
so I can figure out
what's going on
with your cells.
Okay, getting focused here.
There's a nuclear membrane.
- Wait.
- MOLLY: Wait what?
Is that a good wait
or a bad wait?
Your body, your cells,
they aren't metabolizing
the compound.
That sounds like
a bad wait.
Why is this even happening?
The original sugar
solution
must be turning
into a fat
and getting stuck
in her cells.
So what does that mean?
We have to figure out how
to neutralize the solution
before her body could
fully absorb it, or--
Or the invisibility will
become permanent.
What?
I thought you said
this was temporary.
It takes the human body
24 hours to fully digest
something.
Right.
Okay, so when did you
swallow the moth?
Last night at midnight.
GEORGE: That means we have
until midnight to find
an antidote.
Or she becomes
invisible forever.
But where do we start?
I don't even remember
what I spilled
into the last solution.
So that's what
we do first.
We redo your experiment.
Someplace where we can
fully analyze it.
A real lab.
Like the one at school.
Okay, we'll start with
a basic sugar solution
and keep adding chemicals
until we get the right
combination.
Exactly. We'll know
we got it right
when the moth vanishes.
We'll catch a moth.
You head to school
and start setting up
the lab.
Go, Fighting Owls!
Yeah, this probably wasn't
the right context for that.
MOLLY:
Where are we going
to find a moth before midnight?
CLEO:
Come on.
I know the perfect place.
Cool. A cemetery
on Halloween!
Great.
The key to catching
a moth
is to be
in the darkest place...
( strikes match )
...with the brightest light.
Moth...
CLEO:
This is crazy.
Where are all the moths?
MOLLY:
Here, mothy.
Here, mothy mothy mothy.
CLEO:
They're not cats, Molly.
MOLLY:
Whatever.
Cleo?
It's no big deal, moths.
Must have just been
the wind.
I can get this back on
in no time.
Cleo!
Can you see me?
Yeah. It's nice to
almost see your face again.
Am I getting better?
No, you're not.
It's just the night mist
glistening in the moonlight.
I'm scared, Cleo.
Me too.
But it's gonna be okay.
MOLLY: Look!
MOLLY: I got this.
Molly, I don't think
this is a good idea.
We don't have a choice,
Cleo.
This moth may be
my only hope.
Please be careful, Molly.
I'm getting closer.
Come on, moth!
Almost got it. Almost there.
- Hold on!
- Come on, moth!
Ohh! I lost it!
( both scream )
( coughs )
Molly, are you okay?
( Molly grunting )
No! I am  not  okay!
I am very much not okay.
I am in a cemetery,
at night, soaking wet,
covered in swamp ooze,
and now I'm gonna
be invisible forever.
- We still have time.
- Just forget about it.
We can't.
We can't forget about it.
We can't give up.
Maybe we should just go home,
leave all the lights on,
- and try to draw a moth in.
- And then what?
You can reverse
the invisibility?
For sure? Because
as far as I can tell,
you really have no idea what's
actually happening to me.
I'm done.
I'm done with your science
and your judgments
and your sarcasm.
I'm done with all of it.
Come on, Molly.
This isn't you.
You're supposed to be
the positive one.
Just leave me alone.
If I'm gonna be
invisible forever
and have my life
completely ruined,
I want to face it alone.
You of all people
can relate to that.
Come on, Molly.
Molly?
Molly! Come on!
Come back! Molly!
Molly?
I don't know if you can hear me
or not, but if you can...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry
about the sarcasm.
I'm sorry about everything.
It's just not easy...
being your sister.
You've got this thing...
this light.
Everyone is drawn to you.
And it's hard sometimes...
because...
the truth is...
that I've always
wanted to have that.
And when...I didn't...
it was much easier...
to blame you...for feeling...
...invisible.
So...
I pushed you away...
and...everything...
everything away.
I should have come for froyo.
MOLLY:
You can come for froyo
next time.
Molly, you're here.
I'm here, sis.
He never saw me comin'.
It's almost nine.
We only have a few hours
until midnight.
Hopefully George has gotten
everything set up in the lab.
MOLLY:
That would be great.
Oh. Oh! Ohh. Ohh.
( streetcar bell dings )
Did you mean
what you said back there?
About always
feeling invisible?
I'm sorry.
I had no idea.
I get now how rough
that would have been.
he funny thing is,
've always been envious of  you.
- Me?
- Because you're a genius.
You get straight A's
with your eyes closed.
I kill myself
and barely pass.
You have other things
going for you.
Like what?
Lacrosse?
Popularity?
Both are pretty useless
after high school.
Molly...
that light I was talking about,
it isn't because you're friendly
or pretty or a good athlete,
it's because...
you make those around you happy.
You see what they need,
and you make them better.
It's like
the best kind of smart.
You really think so?
I know so.
I've been you all day.
Okay, there's just enough time
to go home and get changed
before we meet George at school.
Finally! Where have
you guys been?
The building's locked.
I don't know how we're
gonna get inside.
Leave it to me.
I have an idea.
That is why I do kung fu.
I'm a black belt.
Well, a brown belt.
Oh, okay,
I'm a yellow belt.
But I am a very advanced
yellow belt.
( knock on door )
Let me call you back.
Hello?
Anybody out here?
( whoosh )
Huh?
MOLLY:
Boo!
Aah...
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Let's add a little
more sodium...
Okay, we got it.
Good.
Let's analyze it
so we can figure out
how to make an antidote.
I don't understand.
The solution's complex.
This is heavy
organic chemistry.
So now what?
We have to find someone
who can sort through this.
Someone who knows
what all that means.
Who?
A governor scholar
at chemistry.
Believe it or not,
it's Carter.
- What?
- It's true.
I heard him talk about
a bunch of crazy science stuff
with George.
Trust me, if anyone
can help us, it's him.
And I know just where
to find him.
( dance music playing )
♪ Shake that body
show me that la la ♪
♪ Shake that body... ♪
♪♪
MOLLY: Carter said
he's volunteering tonight.
He's gotta be
in there somewhere.
What's wrong.
If I go in there,
then Carter's going to know
I like him.
And I do.
And he likes you too.
We don't know that,
Molly.
If a girl like me lets on
she likes a guy like him,
then he usually ends up
laughing in her face.
If he did that,
he'd miss out
on the best thing
that ever happened to him.
♪ Together we can dance ♪
♪ Whoa we gotta do it
do it do it baby ♪
♪ Shake that body
show me that la la ♪
♪ Shake that body... ♪
No outside food or drinks
School rules still apply.
What are you thinking?
COUG: Cleo?
Oh, no.
Um, hi, Coug.
- Is your sister around?
- No, she's not,
but we really have to go.
Wait, wait.
I just really need to know.
Is Molly dumping me?
No, no, she's just
really busy.
You don't have to
protect me, Cleo.
She's avoiding me.
I mean, she loves
Romp the Swamp.
She'd never miss it.
Would you just tell her
one thing?
Tell her I just want her
to be happy.
That's all I've
ever wanted.
And if she's happier
without me,
then I can learn
to live with that.
Somehow.
( sobbing )
The Coug's okay.
He's not crying.
( Coug sobbing )
Coug...
I've never been
the biggest fan of yours,
but I was wrong.
Hmm?
Molly's really lucky
to have you.
And if you'll just
give me a second,
she'll be back.
I just miss her
so badly.
MOLLY:
I miss you too, Coug.
Molly?
I'm not breaking up
with you.
I'm right here.
I'm just invisible.
Like you can't be hurt?
No, that's "invincible",
babe.
I'm "invisible".
I can't be seen.
This is very confusing.
Oh... Oh!
Molly, it is you!
Oh, I missed you too.
Thank you for not
dumping me.
Whoa, whoa, wait.
You're invisible?
Wait, what?
How?
This is completely crazy!
Coug, I'll explain later,
but if we don't
find Carter now
and make Molly visible
in less than an hour,
you're going to go to prom
with an invisible girlfriend.
Which won't make for
great couples pictures.
Right?
Right.
Okay, let's split up.
I'm gonna go to the yard,
and you go into the house,
and we'll meet in the barn
at the end, okay?
Okay, yeah.
Let's go.
( thunder, screams playing )
Have you seen Carter
anywhere?
Have you seen a guy
named Carter?
Uh-uh.
You go in there.
I'm gonna go this way.
Oh, uh, excuse me,
do you know where
Carter is?
Soccer player,
about this tall,
luscious curls?
George, have you seen Molly?
Uh, "seeing" is really
the tricky word there.
We're out of snacks,
the bowl of fake eyeballs
turned mushy,
the smoke machine
ran out of whatever
makes it make smoke.
Molly is supposed
to be here.
This is a complete
disaster.
Nikki?
Yeah?
It's not a disaster.
This is the greatest
haunted house fundraiser ever.
Really?
Definitely.
Oh, are you having
a good time?
See? She's happy,
and she doesn't even
have a head.
You're doing a great job.
Thanks.
You're a really...
really nice guy,
George.
Thanks.
You're nice too.
Maybe we could
hang out sometime?
I'd like that.
Uh, great.
To be continued.
See you soon.
Carter!
( sighs )
Can you guys
give us a sec?
Hey... you're here.
You're late, but here.
And you're not
in costume.
Um, no.
Costume?
Your bear costume?
Um... No.
Can I ask you something?
What's up with you?
I mean, generally,
you're kind of standoffish.
Today you're actually
nice to me,
and now you barely even
bother to show up.
Carter, I'm so sorry
about the weirdness.
The truth is...
I have always wanted
to hang out with you.
And I never thought
that you would want
to ever hang out
with me.
What are you wearing?
Uh, I'm--
I'm honey.
Honey?
Yeah, you know,
I thought, 'cause, you know,
with your bear costume,
I'd-- I'd be honey.
'Cause, you know,
bears and honey are--
they're kind of a...
thing.
I-- I literally spent
all afternoon gluing felt.
But, you know, since
you're not in costume,
I-- I may have
overthought this
a little bit.
I really want to talk
to you about this,
and I want to talk to you
about a lot of things.
But right now,
I really need your help.
What is it?
You should just not
see for yourself.
It's just over here
in the barn.
Isn't the barn
off-limits?
Carter.
Hey. Hello.
What's going on?
Okay, here we go.
Hey, Carter.
Whoa, Carter,
Carter, Carter...
Wow, this is
a sophisticated solution.
But I think I can
work out an antidote.
The problem is we only
have 45 minutes.
'Cause at midnight,
we're toast.
The tricky part is
after we create the antidote,
we need to distill
its steam.
Of course.
The steam is what
turned the moth invisible,
so that's what Molly needs
to drink.
But how? We don't have time
to get to the lab.
We can make a homemade still.
All we need are a few
simple components.
Hey, sorry, fire code
violation, gotta take this.
CLEO:
A heat source...
some tubing...
Sounds better
without these notes.
CLEO:
... and a funnel
of some kind.
CARTER:
Ok, so now that we've
created the antidote,
all we need to do
is boil it...
then distill its steam...
so that Molly can drink it
before midnight.
Okay, here we go.
It's almost midnight.
We've got 40 seconds.
MOLLY:
Is it working?
Just one drop...
and another one.
This is gonna take forever.
30 seconds.
Oh, come on, boil faster!
PERKINS (banging on door):
Hey! Open the door, people.
- It's Perkins.
- Ignore him.
PERKINS:
Whoever's in there
better come out,
or you're gonna meet
my good friend,
Mr. Detention!
Less than 20 seconds.
Come on, work,
you stupid machine.
PERKINS:
Come on.
What's going on in there?
( clock chiming )
Okay, Molly,
this should be enough.
Drink it.
PERKINS:
Seriously, open up!
People, your actions
have consequences.
MOLLY:
I have to do something
for you first.
What are you doing?
MOLLY:
It'll just take a second.
You kids are in
some serious trouble!
Mr. Perkins, it's Molly.
Cleo turned me invisible
for her science project.
You have to know
how special she is.
( clock chiming )
Oh, no.
Molly, what did you do?
MOLLY:
I had to make sure
Mr. Perkins knew, Cleo.
You did something amazing
the world had to see.
We missed the deadline.
MOLLY:
It was a risk I was
willing to take for you.
Molly, I'll never see
your beautiful face again?
That's okay, we can still
have a life together.
Maybe even with little
half-invisible kids someday.
So you actually did this?
You really turned
your sister invisible.
I-- I-- Okay,
I can't get my mind
around-- around this.
Uh...
No, no, we can't give up.
There has to be something else
that we can do.
Your calculations were
conservative.
There should have been
enough time, it should
have worked.
Well, then, there's
something we're missing.
Molly, did you eat
anything weird last night?
Meatballs.
Huh? The meatballs.
Wait, you had a game
the next day.
You were nervous.
Ginger fizz.
MOLLY:
I drank some
with the moth.
Then that's what
we're missing.
Its acidity must have
impacted the solution
somehow.
Do you have any on you?
MOLLY:
I never leave the house
without it.
( liquid hissing )
Drink it.
MOLLY:
Hey, no matter
what happens,
I really liked spending
the day with you.
Me too.
ALL: ( cheering )
( "Brand New Day"
by Joshua Radin playing )
It's nice to see
your face again.
It's good to see you, too.
♪ Some kind of magic ♪
I think The Coug needs
to blow off some steam.
Molly! Finally!
Hey!
NIKKI: Where's your costume?
Hi, Nikki!
Wow. You finally took
your headphones off, Cleo.
You did some real science.
Maybe a little too real.
Listen, I chaired
the New Orleans Association
of Applied Scientists.
Would you please come
and present your findings
with us next month?
- Yeah!
- Yeah?
All right.
Thank you.
Hey. Look, I know
it's been a crazy night.
But-- And I'm dressed as honey.
But do you want to dance?
Yes.
♪ The sun is shining ♪
♪ It's a brand new day ♪
Cleo: So as I was saying,
invisibility is everywhere.
But as it turns out,
the line between visible
and invisible,
it isn't that wide.
♪ I'll be okay ♪
( applause and cheers )
Cleo: Transformation
from one state to another
is indeed possible.
I know now that visible things
can disappear...
...and invisible things
can finally be seen.
♪ Most stories
have a hero who finds ♪
♪ You make your past
your past ♪
♪ Yeah, you make your past
CLEO: Crossing this line
between invisible and visible
is easier than you think.
♪ The sun is shining ♪
CLEO: What people see...
...what they really see...
( no audio )
...visible or invisible...
...comes from inside us.
And we become visible
when we are not afraid
to show the world
who we really are.