[Music playing]
[Scratching sound]
[Fast forward sound]
DIANA: You've never
modeled before?
Am I doing a poor job?
DIANA: I didn't say that.
Mmm, no.
I always wanted to.
I just never really had
the chance, you know?
[Camera flash]
Is something wrong?
DIANA: What makes you say that?
I don't know know.
I just feel like
there's something wrong.
Why?
I don't know.
I mean, I'm nervous, I guess.
Do I make you nervous?
No.
Do you feel uncomfortable
being naked in front of me?
No, not really.
Then what do you have
to be nervous about?
I don't know.
I just want you to
think I'm pretty.
I mean, your assistant said
if you found me pretty,
Everything would be OK.
Don't you think you're pretty?
I'm all right, I guess.
Do you think I'm pretty?
Well, yeah, beautiful.
Let's try another pose.
Lie down.
My assistant said he
found you on the street.
Yeah, I met him in the street.
He said you don't have a home.
I have a home.
I just ran away
from it, that's all.
Why?
Why does anybody run away?
Don' t move your head, please.
[Scratching sound]
What are you doing?
Relax.
Your assistant said you were
going to paint a picture.
[Screaming]
[Rustling sounds]
[Creaking wood]
[Crying]
[Dripping sound]
[Scraping sound]
[Music playing]
[Projector sound]
[Beeping]
[Dog barking]
[Footsteps]
[Music playing]
Don't call me, dude.
Let's go fuck a
prostitute, man.
Look, I got things
to to, all right?
Ah, man, listen, would
you talk to her for me?
You know, maybe if you
told her that I was cool,
Then I could go over there.
Conner, look, I'll see
what I can do, all right?
CONNER: You know,
maybe she could
Paint my picture or something.
EDMOND: Diana only paints women.
CONNER: All right, fine.
Look, you want to get
together later this week,
Maybe go get a
beer or something?
Yeah, sure.
Hey, guys, I'll fuck
you both for $20.
CONNER: How old are you?
I'm legal.
All right, $20 each?
Or $20 for both of
us at the same time.
You live out here
on the streets?
Yeah, this is my home.
Come on, look how
young and sexy I am.
$20.
What about your parents?
I live with my daddy.
Who do you think my pimp is?
You make me sad.
Well give me $20,
and I'll cheer you up.
Maybe some other
time, tootsie pop.
CONNER: Whoa, whoa, Edmond,
where are you going, man?
Didn't you hear what
she fucking said?
- Yeah, I heard what she said.
- Fucking $20, man.
I got $10 right here.
Let's do it.
Dude, she doesn't
looks very clean to me.
CONNER: Fuck, I got six bars
of Zest at the house, OK.
Dirt ain't no problem.
Wonder how old she is.
Man, who cares fucking
cares about her age?
$20?
I don't any place
where you could
Get laid that cheap except
maybe like fucking Cambodia.
You got to pay a shitload
of money to get there,
So it ain't even worth the trip.
You know what I'm saying?
Let's fuck this girl.
Dude, man, I got something
to take care of, all right?
Do it.
All right?
Go for it.
Hey, Edmond, I'm going to meet
that artist some day, right?
Yeah, sure.
You're the man, Edmond,
I'll catch you later.
[Dog barking]
[Gunshots]
[Squealing]
[Music playing]
[Door opening]
You're late.
EDMOND: Sorry.
DIANA: I wanted you
here half an hour ago.
EDMOND: I know, Diana.
What kept you?
Pretty.
I asked you a question.
I was out.
Doing what?
What I always do.
Hanging with that boy, Conner?
Yes.
I don't know why you
choose to surround yourself
With such normal people, Edmond.
They are so maudlin.
You're above them.
You should be one of us.
How many more paintings
do we have left, Diana?
Two.
And my show goes up in two days.
So that doesn't leave much time.
EDMOND: Fine.
DIANA: And find
me someone older.
EDMOND: Older.
I don't know where you find
these waifish little girls,
But they are
exasperating to paint.
Their blood is so thin, it
doesn't, uh, what's the word?
Coagulate very rapidly.
And it tastes like
absolute piss.
So find me someone older.
You know, that may
take a little time.
I may have to go out
of time for that.
Don't be silly, Edmond,
there's a homeless whore
For every tree in this town,
and clean up this mess.
It smells like death in here.
It always smells
this way, Diana.
[Bed creaking]
[Moaning]
[Scream]
Stop!
What are you doing?
Cut it out!
You're hurting me.
What the fuck do you
think you're doing?
Lay back down.
Fuck you, psycho.
You're wacko, man.
CONNER: Come over here.
You need help.
Jesus, man, you
ripped my neck open.
Oh.
You're a freak, dude.
Fuck you!
Shove it up your asshole.
[Music playing]
[Heavy breathing]
[Laughing]
[Music playing]
[Digging]
Where you heading?
Anderson.
Yeah?
Well, you've got
a long way to go.
Ha, yeah, well, you
don't know the half of it.
I've come a long way.
Well, uh, where
you staying tonight?
Been sleeping in a tent
for the past few months.
EDMOND: Well, listen,
I'm... I'm going
To Anderson tomorrow morning.
You can ride with me there.
I got a friend you
could stay with tonight.
[Electronic sound]
Wow!
Would you check this place out?
What the fuck?
What does your friend do?
She's an artist.
She's a painter.
Oh, my god.
Nice paint.
What kind of things
does your friend paint?
I paint live drawings.
Oh, hi, you must be Diana.
Mhm.
Great place.
[Electronic sounds]
And who are you?
EDMUND: This is Deborah.
I picked her up on
the road hitchhiking.
She's on her way to Anderson.
I am going to drive her
there in the morning.
If it's not a problem.
Don't be silly.
I love company.
Thanks.
Do you mind if I
use your bathroom?
It's down the hallway.
Take a shower.
Thanks.
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
Why don't you just
stay here tonight?
No way.
What's wrong, Edmond?
[giggling] You've been acting
So strange lately. [Giggling]
Goodnight.
I want you to
stay here tonight.
I want you to stay here tonight.
I don't want to
stay here tonight.
I got to go home.
You could be so powerful,
Edmond, so powerful.
EDMOND: That's it, Diana.
I can't do this shit anymore.
Don't underestimate me, Edmond.
Daddy can't live forever.
You stay the fuck
away from my father.
Come sit down.
Sit the fuck down.
[Music playing]
[Babies crying]
Oh, man, that was
the best shower ever.
Ah, I really needed that.
[Roar]
[Screaming]
[Ripping sound]
[Ripping sounds]
[Crunching]
[Music playing]
I'm going to bed.
I want her out of her
before I wake up tomorrow.
I thought you said you
were going to paint her.
She's not pretty enough.
Walt Whitman is the best.
No, no... it's wrong.
It's wrong.
WOMAN: Out of your book.
MAN: No, he don't.
WOMAN: Walt Whitman
tell you everything
That's supposedly going on.
And see, your book
says bullshit, OK?
MAN: What is it going
to take to chill out?
[Inaudible]
WOMAN: I want you to understand.
I want you to understand that
book is just as dumb as mine.
Your book is just
as dumb as is mine.
[Music playing]
[Remote click]
[Loud sound]
[Music playing]
MOTHER: I'm dying, baby.
I know, mama, that's OK.
Promise me that you'll
take care of your father
Because without you
he'll die from the grief.
Do you understand
what I'm telling you?
I do, mama, I do.
Don't let that happen.
I won't.
I promise.
Mom?
[Music playing]
[Roar]
[Screaming]
[Heavy breathing]
[Music playing]
I got it now.
[Mad laughter]
Hey, man, you got $5?
Man, give me $5.
Man, fuck you.
Man, give me some of that ass.
It's my daughter.
She's been missing three weeks.
Have you seen her?
No.
Please, ask around.
If you find out anything
at all, call me.
I can't live without her.
[Kids playing]
Have you seen my granddaughter?
She's been missing since April.
Have you seen her.
Please, help me.
Her grandmother is
getting sick over this.
And so am I. Please,
have you seen her?
Have you seen my daughter?
Her name is Kelly.
- Have you seen my daughter?
- She's 110.
She's got brown hair.
Have you seen her?
Have you seen my daughter?
[Interposing voices]
Listen to me.
Have you seen her?
You've got to help me.
Have you seen my daughter.
Help me.
No!
Have you seen my...
[Interposing voices]
Help me find her!
[Crying]
[Interposing voices]
MAN: Have you seen my daughter?
Come back here!
[Heavy breathing]
[Music playing]
What the hell are
you staring at?
Help me up, would you?
I ain't got nothing on my hands.
You're the guy from
the other night.
Yeah, I remember you.
Yeah.
Look what your buddy
did to my neck.
The son of a bitch
tried to kill me.
What?
He bit you?
Yeah, he bit me.
He fucked me.
He bit me.
I didn't even get my money, man.
Look you got to help me.
Please.
I can't take this shit anymore.
I don't have any money.
I don't have any place to stay.
Let me suck you off.
It'll only cost you $5.
No.
I'm begging you.
Come on, man.
I'm losing my mind out here.
Hey, look, come with me, OK?
All right, come on.
I just... I just [inaudible].
[Music playing]
This is your place?
Yeah.
Here, come on.
[Music playing]
Take off your clothes.
Here's fresh clothes
for you to change into
And get yourself cleaned up.
I'll be in the other room
if you need anything.
Can I use hot water?
Yeah, of course.
[Music playing]
Wake up.
Hello.
Do you want to fuck me now?
No
Then what am I doing here?
You're resting.
Here.
Sit closer to me.
Ah!
That isn't so bad.
Your friend is a psychopath.
I don't know why Conner
would do something like this.
Well, he's deranged.
Was he good?
What do you mean?
Was he good in bed?
He was too rough.
What?
You don't like it rough?
I get it rough all the time.
For once I'd just like someone
to be gentle, you know?
I'd just like to
be held for once.
Yeah, but your
friend's got problems.
He thinks he's a
vampire or something.
Conner is weird like that.
Conner did this to you?
Diana.
[Screeching sound]
EDMOND: How long have
you been standing there?
Long enough.
The door was wide open... an
open innovation for anyone
To just come on in.
You really should
be more careful.
Who is this?
Just a minute, Edmond,
I just want to look.
What's your name?
Dee.
Well, you're very
beautiful, Dee.
Thank you.
Who did this to
your precious neck?
I heard the name Conner.
Is that your friend, Edmond?
Yep.
Conner did this to you?
Yes.
He bit your neck?
Why?
I don't know.
We were fucking,
and he attacked me.
How odd.
EDMOND: Diana, what
are you doing here?
My show goes up in
two days, Edmond.
You hadn't forgotten, I hope.
I painted the woman you
brought by last evening.
I don't have time to be picky.
But I need one more model.
Fine, I'll find
you someone today.
No, Edmond, I think
you already have.
You don't have a home?
No.
And you were having sex with
this Conner fellow for money,
I assume?
How would you like to
make some money modeling?
DEE: Modeling?
DIANA: Mhm.
I'm an artist.
I paint women.
Really?
I think you have a
very interesting face.
I think you'd be perfect.
I always wanted to be a model.
Then you shall be.
EDMOND: No.
Yes, of course you shall.
EDMOND: No, not her.
You like this one, Edmond?
I'll find you somebody else.
She is beautiful.
I'll find you someone today.
No, I want her, Edmond.
I thought you said you
wanted someone older.
Well, that was then.
This is now.
What do you want
from me, Diana?
Good question, well,
I simply want you.
I'll never be with you.
Then I will take
everything you have.
Why me?
Find someone else.
You know why, Edmond.
You're torturing me.
If you loved me,
you'd let me go.
I can't let you go, Edmond.
Now bring her by tonight.
I want to paint her.
No.
[Sighs] Saving her soul
isn't going to erase all
Of the sins you've committed.
Your soul is as damned as mine.
You're going to be a model.
Would you like that?
DEE: Fuck yeah.
Have Edmond bring you
by my place in an hour.
And bring Conner with you.
I'd like to meet him.
His methods of
seduction intrigue me.
DEE: Hey, was that
your girlfriend?
No.
I'm not like getting
into trouble, am I?
Look, where do you live?
I don't have a home,
man, I told you that.
But do you have any relatives?
I've been on the
street since I was 13.
My parents don't
give a shit about me.
Where do they live?
Why do you want to know that?
Because I've taken you home.
I'm not going home.
What?
You'd rather live
on the streets?
You'd rather fuck people
that you don't even know.
What type of life is that?
It's a way better life than
I got waiting back home.
Look, I don't know
why you're trying
To be Mr. Good Samaritan Eagle
Scout, and I don't give a shit.
All I wanted was
$5 to suck you off.
Calm down, OK?
Listen, just take me to
your artist friend's house,
And you don't have to
worry about me anymore, OK?
I can't do that, all right?
Why not?
Look, I'll take you
anywhere but there.
Listen, you heard
what she said.
She wants to paint my picture.
I'm going to be a model.
Why do you have a
problem with that?
I just do, all right?
Well, tough shit.
Tell me where she lives,
and I'll fucking walk there.
No, you're not going anywhere.
What?
You heard what I said.
Oh, you give me
some clean clothes,
And you bandage my wounds.
And I'm supposed to do
what tell you tell me?
Is that it?
Well, I'm out of here.
(ANGRILY) No, you're
not going anywhere.
[Drums]
I said you're staying here.
You're a fucking crazy
man just like your friend.
No, I'm crazier than he is.
If you don't let me out
of here, I'll scream.
If you scream, I'm going
to tape your mouth shut.
And I'm going to
tie you to the bed.
No you won't.
Oh, yeah?
Try it.
Now, I don't like doing this.
I had a tough time
tying up my dog.
But one day I decided
not to tie him up.
And he ran out in the street.
And he got hit by a car.
I don't want the same
thing to happen to you.
I mean, I'd hope that you
don't run down the street
And get hit by a car.
I like you, Dee.
And I don't want to
see you get hurt.
[Mumbling]
You want to say something?
You're not going to scream.
[Mumbling]
Now, got a feeling
you're going to scream.
You're going to scream.
[Mumbling]
OK.
I'll fuck you if you let me go.
Dee, we're not going
to have sex, OK?
Why not?
Don't you think I'm pretty.
I think you're beautiful.
But you'd be only
having sex with me.
So I'd let you go.
I don't want that.
Why not?
Dee, look, I gotta go
take care of something
That I should have taken
care of a long time ago.
I promise to let you
go when I get back.
What are you going to do?
All right, all right,
you know the artist,
The woman... the women
who was just here
And wanted to
paint your picture.
Yeah.
I'm going to kill her.
You're going to kill her?
Yes.
Why?
She's a vampire.
Yes.
She takes homeless
girls like yourself,
And she paints still-life
renderings of their bodies
With their blood.
You're insane.
No, I'm not insane.
To be completely
honest with you,
I just never told
anybody before.
And you're a vampire too.
No.
No, I'm her assistant.
I find her models, and then
once she's painted them,
I take their bodies,
and I bury them.
Why do you do that?
Because if don't,
she's threatened
To turn me into a vampire.
You don't want to be a vampire?
No.
No, I want to be an artist.
I don't understand.
It's simple.
Look, about six months ago,
I went to an art museum.
[Music playing]
Now, this would look
good on our wall.
That's tacky, Bill.
Tacky?
Well, I'm not the one who
ladens the wall with Mapletons.
It's Maplethorpe.
And he's a genius.
Maplethorpe is a genius?
You think everyone's a genius.
I don't think you're a genius.
Oh, well, screw you.
I'm just kidding.
Don't talk to me.
I'm mad at you.
It is tacky.
[Music playing]
You like this one?
Yeah, yeah, very much.
How does it make you feel?
I'm not quite sure,
but alive, you know?
But it seems to be about death.
It's not about death at all.
It's about rebirth.
It's interesting
you see it that way.
It is that way.
How can you be so sure?
I mean, the artist
may have intended
Something entirely different.
Because I envy artists.
And you painted this?
Yes.
Well, it's really amazing.
Thank you.
Are you also an artist?
I'm an aspiring artist.
I paint.
But I haven't quite
found my style yet.
Well, the search
isn't that difficult.
You just paint from the heart.
Is that what you do?
Yes.
Do you have any other
paintings here in the gallery.
I'd love to see
more of your work.
No.
I'm working on a collection
for a gallery across town.
Wow!
When's it... when's it open?
Four months.
That's great.
[Music playing]
Would you like to
be my apprentice?
Excuse me?
I need an apprentice, someone
to assist me while I work.
I'd like for you
to be that person.
Why me?
I mean, you don't even know me.
I know enough about you.
Besides, it may help
you find that style
You've been searching for.
Yeah.
Possibly.
What's your name?
Edmond.
Do I excite you, Edmond?
Yes.
Yes, you do.
You want to fuck me, Edmond?
Yes.
Yes, I do.
Ah.
Do you want to
fuck me now, Edmond?
Yes.
[Music playing]
Hey, Earth to psycho.
I'm not a psycho, all right?
Look, everything I
told you is the truth.
All right, so... so
then what did she do?
Did she bite your neck?
You know, Dee, this isn't
a fucking joke, all right?
Well, I'm not
laughing over here.
Jesus, just untie me, would you?
So I can get the
hell out of here.
EDMOND: Would you
just calm down.
You're just like your friend.
You're both
completely fucked up.
Dee, I'm going to let you go
in a couple of hours, all right?
I'm not going to hurt you.
Fuck.
I feel something for you.
I mean, I don't know what it
is, but it's something strong.
I can't explain it.
What are you talking about?
EDMOND: I don't know.
I mean, I'm not quite sure.
I've never felt this way before.
I mean, I feel some strong
connection with you.
I know it sounds stupid, but...
And it's... it's how I feel.
I mean, you think I'm insane.
And that's totally
understandable.
But I'm telling you the truth.
That woman who wants to
paint your picture... she
Is a vampire.
She wants to paint your
picture with the blood
That flows through your body.
How can you be so sure?
Because I know.
Well, if she's a vampire.
How come... how come she can
walk around during the day?
Well, she's not a vampire
in the traditional sense.
I mean, she bites
people on the neck,
And she feeds off their blood.
But other than that,
she's pretty normal.
What about crosses?
Don't they hurt her?
I don't know.
Oh, Jesus, man,
stop fucking with me.
Wait a minute.
What's going on
here with this lady?
Dad, you scared me.
Oh, you scared me too, son.
Why do you have this
girl tied to the bed?
Hey, I ain't
fucking no old man.
Hey, watch your language.
This is my father.
Your son is out of his mind.
He's keeping me prisoner here.
What in the world is
going with this lady.
This is crazy.
Jesus, man, let me go
you fucking faggot... you
Piece of shit... you cocksucker.
Oh.
What the... get the fuck...
Get that fucking... ohh.
Mmm.
Come on, pop.
Come on, let's go.
[Muffled scream]
There's a perfectly good
reason for all of this, OK?
And I'll explain
everything to you later.
But right now, I
need you to watch her
For me for a couple
of hours while I
Go take care of something.
MARVIN: What are
you talking about?
You know what this is?
This is kidnapping.
- Dad, look...
- No.
- Listen.
- I can't.
I can't.
Listen.
Just make sure she doesn't
get out of those robes, OK?
What's going on?
Are you in some kind of trouble?
EDMOND: No, I'm not.
Everything is fine.
This is crazy.
I mean, you got a girl tied up.
What's going on?
Dad, look, what's the big deal?
You used to tie mom to
the bed all the time.
Well, how did you know?
Do you know about that?
EDMOND: Dad, look,
you don't have to have
A conversation with her.
Just entertain her.
All right?
Do one of those old
vaudeville routines for her.
Do... do the Durante
impersonation.
MARVIN: Want me to to do it?
You'd like me to do it for you?
I'll do it for you, all right?
How's that?
Like that?
That's great, dead.
(DURANTE VOICE) Everybody's
trying to get into the act.
Hello, Edmond.
Who tied that girl in there?
- That's great.
- How did you like that?
That's phenomenal.
Look, dad, do it for her.
OK?
OK.
- I got to go.
- Where you going?
Come here Edmond.
You got me worried.
Please, don't go.
Dad, look, there's
nothing to worry about.
Everything's OK.
All right, before you go,
will you give your dad a hug?
Yeah.
All right.
OK.
I love you.
I love you too, Pop.
Take care, take care.
All right.
CONNER: Oh, no, no, wait,
whoa, whoa, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to
call you a bitch.
No.
You're not a bitch.
No, what you are is
a fine-looking woman.
You deserve to be treated
better like that, baby.
You deserve respect.
You taste good.
Mmm.
You like that?
Yeah.
Oh, oh.
So hard.
I'm sorry sweetie.
Oh, oh, god.
Oh, too hard.
[Crunching]
Hey, that hurts.
[Screaming]
Ah!
What are you doing?
You crazy.
God.
Oh [screaming] Oh,
god, get away from me.
[Crying]
Nobody loves me.
[Screaming]
Oh, my god.
Oh, oh.
[Crunching]
[Screaming]
[Music playing]
Hello, sweetie pie.
[Muffled talking]
You know, I'm not supposed
to take off your tape.
My son, Edmond's afraid
that you'll scream.
[Muffled talking]
Hey, what's going on, anyway?
DEE: [muffled talking]
Oh, I see, you can't talk
because you got the tape on.
I understand.
Listen, are you hungry?
Can I make you something
in the kitchen?
Something nice?
Mhm.
How about if I make
you some nice meatballs?
Hmm.
I make the good, Italian,
delicious meatballs, all right?
- [muffled talking]
- OK.
How does that sound?
Good?
Mhm.
Now, you be nice and relax,
and I'll be right back.
I am going to make it up.
All right, sweetheart?
- Mhm.
- OK, be a good girl, all right?
[Door knock]
Hey, Conner.
Edmond.
You're bleeding.
Yeah, I may have punched myself
in the face shadow boxing.
You're naked.
Yeah, ah, well, what are
you fucking doing here, Evan?
Listen, man, I was
wondering if you wanted
To go meet my artist friend?
Right now.
Now?
Right now?
Now.
Fuck yeah.
Wait here while I get some
clothes on, all right?
[Dog barking]
EDMOND (VOICEOVER): Man,
it smells funny in here.
And Conner had a little dick.
Dude, your house smells funny.
CONNER: Yeah.
I, uh, I think there's a
dead rat under the sink.
It smells familiar.
Hey, so you said you were
banging this artist, right?
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah, you know,
I saw the picture
In the paper the
other day that said
She's got a show going up at
the art gallery in a few days.
Yeah, tomorrow.
Tomorrow, huh?
Yeah.
You told her about me, right?
Actually, man, she asked
me to tell you to stop by.
No shit?
Yeah.
How did you say you
cut your lip again?
I told you.
I cut myself in the
face shadowboxing.
Can I... can I
ask you something?
Sure.
You believe in vampires?
Why do you ask that?
Well, you know, I mean, you
and I are pretty good friends,
You know?
I'd like to think that
I can ask you anything.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can, Edmond.
All right, so I'm asking.
Do you believe in vampires?
What if I said that I do?
Then I'm going to tell you that
the artist that I'm taking you
To meet right now is a vampire.
And I need your
help in killing her.
OK, what if I say that I don't?
Then I'm going to tell
you the same thing.
She's a vampire?
Dude, you didn't
answer my question.
What's your question again?
Do you believe
in vampires, man?
Yeah.
I believe in vampires.
Are you in?
Is she really a vampire?
Absolutely.
Hey, man, then I'm fucking in.
Far out.
EDMOND: All right, no, I'm
not exactly sure how we're
Going to go about doing this.
I can't fucking believe this.
We're actually driving
to the artists house
Right now to drive a
stake through her heart.
Yeah, I mean, I figured
you just hold her down, OK?
And I'm going to take
the fucking stake,
And I'm going to jam into
her heart three times.
You want me to hold her
down while you stab her?
Yeah.
Oh, OK.
How long have you known that's
she's been a vampire, Edmond?
Basically, since the
first night I met her.
I thought you fucked her
the first time you met her?
I did fuck her.
Look, all right, listen, it was
after we'd finished having sex,
OK?
EDMOND (VOICEOVER): We
left the art gallery,
And we went back to her
place, and you know,
We fucked each other.
It was nice.
I mean, well, anyways, we're
lying there in the floor.
We're talking.
We're laughing, and then
out of the blue she tells me
She's a vampire.
I mean, I'm not going to
believe something like that.
I'm not that stupid.
So I called her bluff.
She gets up.
She walks down the hall.
She comes fucking back in with
this crazy smile on her face
With a fucking
knife in her hand.
She's staring down at me.
And she plunges it right
into her stomach, man.
Blood is spurting everywhere.
I'm like, what the fuck, man.
I jump up.
I'm freaking the fuck out.
I start running back
down the hallway.
I go to grab this phone.
I'm thinking I've got
to call an ambulance.
All of a sudden, she
comes back there.
She's looking at me.
And she says, look, Edmond.
I look down there, and her
stomach is completely unharmed.
I look up, man, she's got
these demonic eyes, man.
They're like glowing red.
She's got these fucking fangs.
She's smiling at me.
I freak out.
I start stumbling
back down the hallway.
Then she starts like
walking after me
In this dubious,
predatory fashion.
She starts telling me
that she wants me to be
Her lover for an eternity.
I mean, she wants to turn
me into a fucking vampire.
You'll find it very
rewarding, she said.
Then there was like
no place to go.
And then she tries to bite me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What are you doing?
I've waited my whole
afterlife to meet you.
Look, we can't do this.
I don't want to be a vampire.
I don't want to
live for eternity.
And I don't want to spend
the rest of my existence
With just one person.
That thought is revolting to me.
I'm revolting to you?
No, you're not revolting to me.
I just don't want to be your
little after life long mate.
I don't want to be what you are.
You're beautiful.
You're talented.
You're a bit eccentric.
And that's good.
Those are all fine attributes
that I look for a girlfriend.
But I'm not the type the
person who likes to come in.
And if you think by
turning me into a
Vampire you're going
to get an eternity
Of love poems and roses...
I hate roses.
And faithful monogamy,
then you're wrong.
I don't want that.
I don't care what you want.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, please,
please, please, look,
I just thought I was
supposed to be your servant.
I don't want any part of this.
I don't want to be a vampire.
I detest the taste of blood.
Fine, I'll allow you
to remain a human being.
But in exchange, you'll
do exactly as I say.
OK, fine.
If you try to fuck with
me, I won't hesitate
To turn you into a vampire.
And now you want to kill her.
Yeah.
And your plan... you
drive to her house,
Take a piece of
wood, and jab her
In the chest a couple of times.
Yeah, that's right.
All right, let me
ask you a question.
Didn't you tell me
a couple of minutes
Ago that Diana once
took a kitchen knife
And stabs herself
in the gut with it?
Yeah.
So what the fuck
makes you think
That taking a piece of wood
and jabbing her in the chest
Is going to do anything?
Well, OK, I hadn't
thought of that.
So... so kill that plan, OK?
Sure, that's easy enough.
If only killing
Diana were that easy.
Hello, sweetie pie,
here's the meatballs.
Mangia, mangia, Italiana.
Listen, you're going
to enjoy these.
You know what this is?
This is an Italian recipe.
Believe it or not, it was
my great-great-grandmother's
Recipe.
Bless her soul.
She was great.
Smell them.
Ah, look, smell.
Oh.
DEE: Mmm.
I forgot about the tape.
I'm sorry.
Do... do you want me
to remove the tape?
Oh, I wish show I knew
what was going on.
Oh, I'll tell you
what's going on.
Your son's a fucking fruit loop.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
Take it easy.
Listen, I came
over here because I
Thought we were going
to... and instead,
He ends up tying me to the bed.
You've got to let me go
before he comes back.
I can't do that.
Why not?
My son told me to make sure
that you didn't get out.
But your son's out
of his fucking mind.
Oh, no, no.
My Edmond's a good boy.
Oh, come on, you
senile motherfucker.
Let me out of here.
Now, listen, you don't have
to be talking like that.
Suck a dick you wrinkled,
raisin-looking motherfucker.
Let me out of here.
You should have
more respect here.
Jesus Christ, fucking you!
All right.
Oh, you be quiet, girl.
I'm going to be nice.
I'm going to sing a
nice song for you.
Be quiet.
Easy, easy, easy.
Listen, just try to calm down.
My son Edmond will be here
in a few minutes, all right?
And he'll straighten
this whole thing out.
Now, in the meantime, I'm going
to sing you a beautiful song,
A Canadian song that I wrote.
Would you like to
hear it, sweetie pie?
OK?
(SINGING) In old Montreal,
they are having a ball.
It's the greatest place in town.
If you like to eat
where the people meet,
It's on St. Dennis Street.
You could see the bell door
hid above that Notre Dame
As far as Pont
Champlain, and all
The French all say parlais vous
francais all over Chinatown.
There are skyways and byways
that tunnel through the town.
And the [inaudible].
[Music playing]
[Crash]
Oh, oh.
Ah!
[Groaning]
[Crack]
[Crash]
What's all this about, Edmond?
I'm not going to be
your servant anymore.
I thought you wanted
to be a painter.
I thought you were
going to be my pupil.
It's over, Diana.
I'm going to kill you.
It's the thing I love
about you, Edmond.
You're so determined sometimes.
But let me ask you, how
do you plan to do that?
Oh, it's the girl, isn't it?
Yeah.
You've fallen in
love with that girl.
Don't be preposterous.
I don't even know her.
I just want to live
a normal life again.
The first time I met you,
I fell in love with you.
What's so preposterous about it?
What's this?
Hmm, oooh, that's not
going to do any good.
And what else [click]
do we have here?
Hmm, a stake, oh, yummy.
And this must be Conner.
I've heard a lot about you.
I see Edmond here has recruited
you to assist in destroying me.
I just wanted to meet you.
And I you.
When I saw you did to
that girl's precious neck,
I knew you were different.
Don't listen to her, man.
She said the same thing to me.
Put the stake down, Conner.
I know you don't
want to hurt me.
Die, whore, die.
[Stab]
[Screaming]
Boo.
Oh!
Jimminy crickets.
Wood, fire,
crosses, holy water...
You can't learn about the
weaknesses of a vampire
From books and movies.
It doesn't work that
way in the real world.
In the real world, only a
vampire can kill a vampire.
What?
Nice try though.
Valiant effort to stop
my reign of terror.
But really, Edmond, is
what I'm doing so wrong?
I'm revolutionizing the
art world, painting nudes
With the life blood
that allows these bodies
To live and breathe.
That is a totally original
artistic concept and one
That I truly believe is worth
the lives of a mere dozen
Expendable creatures.
You're an abomination.
No, Edmond, you're
the abomination, you
And the billions of
shitless human feeblings
That occupy this planet.
Your kind will
never replace us.
I never wanted that.
All I wanted was a companion.
[Loud sound]
[Music playing]
DAD: Hiya, sweetie pie.
I'm going to give
you my imitation
Of Jimmy "Schnozzle" Durante.
Oh, boy, you're
going to like it.
(DURANTE VOICE) Everybody is
trying to get into the act.
What happened to you, baby?
You know I'm mortified.
I don't understand this.
Oh, baby, it's preposterous.
Who tied you to that bed?
CONNER: You know
what I always thought
Would have made a cool vampire?
Carly Simon.
She had the mouth
for it, you know?
Conner.
Yeah?
Where's Diana?
She's gone, man.
You look different, man.
CONNER: I feel
different, Edmond.
She turned you into
a vampire, didn't she?
Edmond, what makes you think
that I want to be a vampire?
Because you're one
fucked up individual, man.
Oh, see, now that's not nice.
I thought we were
supposed to be friends.
We are.
So what happened to your neck?
CONNER: OK, so you
figured it out.
She bit me.
And how you feel about that?
Well, I mean, considering
that I asked her to do it,
Pretty good.
Why do you want to
be a vampire, man?
CONNER: Why do you want
to be an artist, Edmond?
Why does my nephew, Charlie,
want to be a fireman?
I've just always
wanted to be a vampire.
You want to live forever?
You want to feed off the
blood of innocent people?
CONNER: See, now, actually, I've
always had a strong attraction
To the taste of blood, but shit,
man, every time I bite a woman,
She thinks I'm a freak.
But now I'm a vampire,
my actions are justified.
Shit, man, I don't
know what to say.
Then shut up, Edmond
because you're starting
To act like a big pussy.
Where's Diana now?
You know, to be a
vampire, she's really no
Different than any other chick.
I mean, as soon as she
knocked your ass out,
She started screaming
shit like I'm
Going to kill that little bitch
and then he'll see that I'm
The only true love for him.
What the hell is
she talking about?
She's jealous, man.
She's upset.
Oh, well, you know, then
she bit me on the neck,
And she told me
to be a vampire as
Soon as I make my first kill.
And then she stormed out of
the house like a madwoman.
Your first kill.
Yeah.
Obviously, I can't
make the transformation
From human to vampire
until I've killed someone.
So you're not a vampire yet.
Not exactly.
So what's with the
fucking fangs, man?
They're fake.
I just couldn't
[inaudible] of my own.
Dude, so all you got
to do is kill somebody,
And then you're a vampire?
That's right.
And guess who it is
that I'm going to kill?
Oh, shit.
Let me take a wild guess, me.
Well, obviously.
Well, fine, man.
Let's get this shit over with.
I'm sorry about this, Edmond.
[Music playing]
[Punch]
[Punches]
[Bombs sound]
[Machine gun sound]
[Punches]
[Explosions]
[Punch]
Oh!
Ow!
Oh, fucking faggot.
I think you broke
my fucking tooth.
Oh, fucking shit, man,
I think I broke my hand.
Oh, fuck.
How the fuck can I be a
vampire without a tooth.
Oh, fuck.
How can I be an
artist without a hand?
Oh, oh, fuck.
What the... what the
fuck are we doing, man?
Man, this is stupid.
Oh, fuck, tell
me about it, bro.
So how does it feel
to be a vampire?
I'm not a vampire yet.
That's right, man.
How does it feel to
be a half vampire?
Well, actually, I
fell kind of horny.
Dude, you're
fucking always horny.
Yeah, but I feel like my
sex drive been turned up
If you're not just... you know?
Man, I swear I could fuck
a snake hole right now.
You know what I'm saying?
Oh, shit man, I'm fucking
sorry I broke your tooth.
It's all right.
Man, I'm sorry I
tried to kill you.
Dude, It's fucking my
fault. I fucking brought
You in to all this shit.
What are you going to do, right?
Oh, shit, man.
I needed a hug.
Ah, you motherfucker!
You fucking knew I
was going to do it.
Ah, that's what you did.
And take that.
Oh!
I'm sorry, man.
What are you going to do?
[Crash]
[Music playing]
EDMOND: Dad?
Pop, you in here?
Dad?
Oh, my god.
Dad.
Jesus Christ.
Dad?
You OK?
You alive?
Oh, dad.
Oh.
Are you hurt, dad?
Are you OK?
I don't know, son.
How do you feel, pop?
I feel kind of horny, son.
Horny?
Yeah, I feel like I could
fuck a snake hole right now.
Wait a second.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my god.
What is it?
What is it, son?
Oh, come on.
Get up, dad.
All right.
OK.
[Music playing]
Oh, you all right, dad?
Edmond, the girl... this lady
dressed in a sexy outfit,
She barged right in the middle
of my Jimmy Durante act.
And she took the girl.
I know, pop.
I tried to stop
her, but I couldn't.
She's very strong, Edmond.
And she he hit me so hard in the
face, I went out like a light.
Jesus Christ, what the
hell am I going to do?
Oh, I got an idea.
How about going downtown,
and let's pick us up a couple
Of hookers, all right?
Prostitutes?
Dad, I got to
show you something.
Wait.
Can it wait?
Listen, I really want
to have sex, Edmond.
I really want to
have sex, all right?
All right, take a look.
Oh, my, look at that, son.
You know what those are, dad?
Yeah, they look like holes.
That's right, holes.
Yeah.
Pop, you were
bitten by a vampire.
A vampire?
Edmond, what's got
into you lately?
Look, Marguerite at Ball Street
has got all kinds of hookers.
Dad, will you get your mind out
of the gutter for a second, OK?
What's the problem?
The problem is you were
bitten by a vampire.
Diana broke in, she
bit you on the neck,
And she took Dee, the girl I
love, the girl tied to the bed.
Who's Diana?
Diana is the woman I work for.
She's going to kill
Dee if I don't get down
To the graveyard to save here.
Well, I thought you said you
worked in a slaughterhouse.
No, dad, I worked for a
vampire, a vampire named Diana.
But you said you
slaughtered hogs.
Pop, I made all
that shit up, OK?
Yeah.
I work for a woman named Diana.
And this Diana you
say is the vampire.
That's right.
So what are you
going to do about it?
Well, I got to kill her, pop.
It's the only way
I can save Dee.
How are you going to do it?
Hell, no, I mean,
only a vampire...
What?
Only a vampire can
kill another vampire.
I've got an idea, Pop, come on.
Where are we going?
We're going downtown.
Well, we're going to
go pick up some hookers.
No, dad, we're not going
to go pick up hookers.
Here.
Grab your coat.
Come on.
Let's go.
Oh, boy, I'm going
downtown just like crazy.
- No, no.
- I want a young one.
You know, son?
I want a young girl.
Oh.
Pop, just drop
the hookers thing.
I'm very horny.
Here we go.
All right, pop.
Oh, I love them.
We're going downtown,
son, come on.
Let's pick up some nice hookers.
Pop, will you shut
up about the hookers.
EDMOND: The woman who bit you on
the neck, she's an evil woman.
She's probably the most
evil woman alive today.
MARVIN: OK, I
understand that, Edmond.
EDMOND: Now, I've tried
to kill her, but I can't.
MARVIN: Why not?
EDMOND: Because only a vampire
can kill another vampire.
MARVIN: Well,
then, in that case,
Let's go find another vampire.
EDMOND: Dad, I don't know
of any other vampires.
MARVIN: Well, who's
going to kill her?
EDMOND: You are.
MARVIN: Me?
EDMOND: Yes, All right,
she bit you on the neck.
That means you are
a half vampire.
All you got to do
is kill somebody,
And you're going to
be a complete vampire.
MARVIN: Oh, son, what
are you trying to say?
It's simple, dad.
I'm going to get a homeless guy.
I'm going to bring him in
here to the alleyway, OK?
I'm going to take a knife
and jab it in its neck
A couple of times.
Blood is going to
start splurting out.
You position your mouth
underneath the blood,
You take a few sips, and
voila, you're a vampire.
Then we proceed with the plan.
But, it's a [inaudible].
I can't kill anybody.
Dad, listen, hey, vampires,
they get laid a lot.
Ooh, really?
Yeah.
I...
Bella Lugosi... he got more
pussy, uh, by playing Dracula
Than you can shake a stick at.
I heard he was a ladies man.
He's like the Wilt
Chamberlain of horror movies.
I never knew that then.
Yeah, he got sucked off
by more girls offscreen
Than he sucked onscreen.
Wow!
Gosh, hey, who are
we going to kill?
Come on.
That disgusting looking
human being right there.
Gosh.
You couldn't get anyone
more clean then that?
That guy is filthy.
Dad, you're not going
to sleep with the guy.
You're just going
to drink his blood.
Yeah, but you're at
least going to look
Around and pick up someone
more attractive than that.
What does it matter?
Oh.
You don't love Indian
food because of the way
It looks, do you?
Yeah.
All right, look.
I want you to go into
the alleyway, OK?
Take this knife.
I'm going to bring
him around the corner.
When I come around the
corner, you stab him.
OK.
All right, then.
All right?
OK.
[Dog barking]
Hey, fella, can
you help a guy out?
Yeah.
What kind of help do you need?
I need some money to get my
prescription bottle filled.
EDMOND: All right,
I'll help you out.
Come on.
I've got a bad heart.
Yeah?
It's why I take medicine.
Come on.
When I came back from Vietnam,
that's when it started.
[Music playing]
Marvin do it, stab him.
Hey, hey, what is this?
Go Marvin, go.
I thought you were
going to help me.
Marvin, come on.
Kill him.
MARVIN: I can't kid.
Why do you keep
calling me Marvin?
I don't know, but
fuck it, dad, kill him.
I can't.
Here.
You do it.
What are you doing?
Trying to kill me, huh?
You can't just... you can't
just take our knife like that.
Sure, I can.
Look, you just tried
to take my life.
Your life is worthless.
That knife cost me $2.
Shutup!
Oh, oh, this is great, dad.
This is the second time
tonight somebody tried to stick
Something sharp into my neck.
Got that knife
Where's your knife?
Oh!
[Screaming]
Edmond, what's happening?
He's having a heart attack.
Oh.
What are you doing?
Looking for the hear medicine?
What?
He had the prescription here.
Let me find it.
Oh, it's empty.
Do you want me to
call an ambulance?
Dad, don't be ridiculous.
Fine, now's our chance.
Kill him.
I can't.
Kill him, dad.
I see the life going
out of his eyes.
Come on, dad, kill him.
I can't.
Dad, it's not even
like you're killing him.
You're just putting
him out of his misery.
Come on.
All right, all
right, I'll do it.
[Stab]
Oh!
OK, pop, drink that.
No, I can't, Edmond.
Come on, dad, drink it, hurry.
No, you'll have to get
someone else to drink it.
I can't drink it, Edmond.
All right, pop, there you go.
Now, drink that.
Oh, god.
I can't drink that.
Pop, come on.
I know it seems like we're
committing unforgivable crimes
Against humanity.
But it's for the right reasons.
Drink it.
You know, we're going
to burn in hell for this.
No, people responsible for
stopping the greatest evil
Of all time don't burn in hell.
I can't imagine
what your mother
Is thinking about this, Edmond.
Corpses don't think.
Drink it.
It's a horrible thing to say.
Dad, look, mom would
be proud of you.
Now, drink that.
But you could have made it with
some tomato juice or something.
Pop, would you hurry
up and drink it.
If you don't drink it now,
you're going to be holding
A bottle with a scab in it.
All right, I'll drink it.
I'll drink it.
How was it?
Bloody awful.
OK, come on.
Pop, how do you feel?
- Oh, I feel hungry.
- Hungry?
I'm very hungry.
OK.
And I'm horny, son.
You know something I
feel right now, Edmond.
I can eat a horse.
Yeah?
Wait, wait, wait.
Is that an ogre out there?
Goddammit, pop, get your
mind out of the gutter.
Stop thinking about hookers
for a fucking second.
You know you've got
a filthy mouth talking
To your dad like bit like that.
Oh, you should talk, pop.
Yeah, what do you mean?
Like, dad, look, Jesus
Christ, you're a vampire, dad.
What?
You're a vampire, dad.
You're a vampire.
Oh, I got it.
Oh, wow!
Oh.
- Oh, my god.
- I got teeth.
Oh, my fucking god.
Wow!
Damn.
It's great dad.
It looks fucking great.
Where [inaudible].
Ah!
Yeah.
All right.
Hey, hey, what does this mean?
Well, pop, uh, it
means that nobody's
Ever going to say that your
bark is worse than your bite.
Oh, come on, Edmond.
No more jokes.
Stop now.
Let me tell you something.
I know enough about vampires
to know that my life is going
To be different from now on.
That's right, pop.
Fuck, I mean everything's...
Nothing's going
To be the same anymore.
What do you mean nothing
is going to be the same?
Well, vampires can't die, dad.
Oh, they can't die?
No.
In other words, you're telling
me that I can never die?
No.
Not unless you're killed
by another vampire.
Oh.
It's too bad, Edmond.
It's too bad.
I was looking forward to
joining your mother soon.
Oh, I wanted to join
your mother soon.
[Music playing]
Hey, Edmond, why are you
putting your jacket on?
Mosquitoes, pop.
I hate the fucking bloodsuckers.
Whoa, whoa,
Edmond, the sun, oh!
Dad, what are you doing?
The sun can't hurt you.
Oh, oh, I'd like to
say I was a vampire.
You are, pop, but the sun
is not going to hurt you.
And you can't even get suntan.
Oh, I see.
Very interesting.
Don't be afraid of the sun, pop.
Edmond, what are we doing here?
DIANA: We've been expecting you.
Thanks for joining the party.
Hello, Diana.
So I see you escaped
the murderous intentions
Of your friend, Conner.
Yeah.
I had to kill him.
He was a good friend of mine.
And that wasn't easy.
Aren't I your friend?
Once, but not anymore.
That makes me sad to hear.
It's over, Diana.
You give us the girl,
and we'll let you live.
You have no choice
but to let me live.
Only a vampire can
kill a vampire.
Exactly.
Pop, show your teeth.
DAD: [growling] I
got him in, yeah.
I got him.
[Growling]
Me and my old man
are here to stop you.
I wondered how far you'd go.
You'd sacrifice your own
father to see me dead?
I don't know if that's
valiant or vulgar.
My pop's a vampire,
sure, that's a problem.
But we'll settle
it like we settle
All of our family problems, OK?
Thanks, son, thank
you very much.
Why are you doing this, Edmond?
Why have you suddenly decided
that you want to kill me?
Well, there's a lot
of horrible things
That I'll never
forgive myself for.
But I'm going to try.
And I figured killing you
would be a good place to start.
Then kill me, if you can.
[Loud sound]
Where is she?
Pop, she's back here.
[Music playing]
Hey, she's getting away.
Hey, get in the car.
No, you drive.
I haven't driven
a... get in the car.
Dad, fuck it.
Just drive.
Get in the back seat.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
All right, go pop, go.
We can get her.
[Music playing]
All right, dad, pull up
right beside the car.
I'm going to jump out.
DAD: Goddammit, Edmond.
We're almost there.
Pull up.
Pull up beside their car.
Get a little closer.
We're almost there.
I am.
[Crash]
Oh!
[Screaming]
[Crash]
DAD: Edmond.
Oh, my god, Edmond.
[Crack]
Oh!
DAD: Diana, die.
[Stab]
[Roar]
[Growling]
[Music playing]
[Explosion]
Thanks, pop.
Don't mention it son.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
You saved my life.
I had to.
Pop, how do you feel?
Well, I'm all right, son.
I guess, but I feel a little...
Little strange, you know?
And I... I'm hungry.
Right now, you know, Edmond, I
ain't craving for a hamburger
If you know what
I'm talking about.
Pop, there's got to be someone
somewhere that can help you.
Maybe, maybe.
Come sit by me.
First he turned you
into a vampire, huh?
DAD: Yeah.
DEE: Well, vampires are
really trendy these days.
Yeah.
The goth scene is huge.
I wouldn't get
too down about it.
Well, I feel a little better
now that you said that.
Thank you very much.
So what happens now?
Well, I thought I'd
paint your picture.
You want to be an artist, huh?
Yep, that's all I've
ever wanted to be.
You know?
Somebody once told me if you
want to paint a good picture,
You've got to paint
from the heart.
So let's begin.
[Music playing]