Are we there yet?
Do you think we're there yet?
Has the plane landed?
I'm so bored.
Hmm, my heart bleeds
for you.
I would love to entertain you,
but I have to finish this paperwork.
Your father needs it
as soon as we touch down.
Well, at least
he'll be happy to see you.
What did you do
this time, Nicole?
Oh, I love that. "What did I do
this time?" Real supportive.
I'm sorry. I thought
we were talking about you.
Ouch! Catty.
You were tough enough to get
kicked out of three schools,
you're tough enough
to hear the truth from me.
Well, the truth being whatever
happens minus my side of the story, right?
Nicole, I've known you
since you were two years old.
I used to change your
diapers in the office...
"when your mother and
father worked late." - Yeah.
You really got to get
some new material, Andrea.
You used to be this much of a
good kid and this much of a brat.
What happened?
Well, I used to have parents.
Now all I have is the
president and ceo of Teknacom.
And still to this day,
people continue to talk
about how dehumanizing
the computer revolution is.
Well, this is something
I could never understand.
You don't go from selling
accounting software door-to-door...
To becoming one of the largest
software providers in the world...
Without there being a very real,
very vital human presence.
The need for computers is human.
Our desire to enhance our lives...
through computer technology is human.
But computers aren't people.
They're made for
people and by people.
But as accurate
and reliable as they are,
they're... they're
just tools, nothing more.
Now, with this major
expansion of Teknacom,
I'm striving to bring
the human factor...
to this cold world of technology.
Now, when my wife
and I started this company,
we had nothing but an old alegra
computer and a screaming one-year-old.
Now we have facilities
all over the world,
and we have a
screaming 13-year-old.
But, all kidding aside,
the human factor in all of this...
is family.
And it was the support
and patience of my family...
That allowed Teknacom to grow.
Soon people from
all over the world...
Will become part of
our Teknacom family.
And then, and only then,
will the real
computer revolution...
Begin.
Thank you all very much.
Nice to see you.
Very nice to see you.
Brilliant speech, Mr. Stone.
- Thank you, Martin.
Would you mind checking on the
status of Nicole's flight? - Certainly, sir.
Hi, ray. Hi, Marilyn. Hi.
It's good to see you.
"Brilliant speech,
Mr. Stone."
Family is everything, isn't it?
Great speech, Ray.
Great, great speech.
I wonder if anyone would have
liked your speech this morning.
I'm not the first man who's gotten into
a shouting match with his daughter. Mmm.
Hi, Mr. Stone. Hi.
How are you? Nice to see you.
True enough.
- Hi, Mr. Stone.
Still you have to admit,
it's a little bit strange...
To hear you speak about family
values when we can't even have...
A phone conversation with our daughter
without getting into a yelling match.
Watch Oprah. Families yell at
each other all the time. - I enjoyed it so much.
And besides, she started it.
Great. So you're both
four years old. Is that it?
Who cares if Roberto Clemente
was the greatest baseball player...
wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't... wait a minute.
Roberto Clemente was the
greatest baseball player of all time.
And second of all...
- Super, super speech.
You and I both know that this argument
had nothing to do with baseball players.
Hi.
-Hi. Good evening.
She's trying, Ray.
- No, she's not trying.
People who try don't get...
- Hi.
They don't get kicked out of schools
all over the world over and over again.
People who try, try.
I don't get it. On her reports
she used to get straight a's,
but over the last couple of years, now
that things are starting to go well for us,
it seems like all she wants
to do is annoy people.
Shh.
- Hi.
Don't say anything to me.
Why not? - Because if
you say anything to me,
it'll insult me,
and if you insult me, I'll get angry,
and if I get angry,
you'll know what will happen.
Nothing happens
when you get angry, Frank.
You just eat more.
Andrea, aren't you
supposed to be watching her?
Oh, I am watching her.
I'm watching her annoy you for a change.
Can you stop?
Thank you.
I don't get it.
I really don't get it.
What happened to you?
Well, people change.
Look, you used to be thin.
I suppose you think that's funny.
It's not.
It's just mean.
Look, I don't know if you've
heard, Frank, but I am mean...
and obnoxious...
and a disappointment.
You're only gonna be a disappointment if
you keep going down the path you're on.
I don't want to see you turn
into some cold, selfish, rich brat.
I hate what you're becoming.
Listen, honey.
You know your family's
the only family I've got.
And you're probably as close as I'm
gonna get to having my own kid.
You remember...
remember we took you first to the zoo?
Or when your dad and I
took you camping?
Oh, my gosh!
We were such spazzes.
We had all that stuff
happen with the raccoons...
And with those poles
falling down on us.
You remember the fun we had?
No.
No, sorry I don't.
Tower, this is flight 109.
Eta is in, um, 95 minutes.
Roger that, 109.
We've been bouncin' around up here,
catching the tail end of the storm.
Roger, 109.
I'm afraid that's not the last of it.
Beware you'll be
landing in snow.
We copy, tower.
Rain, sleet, lightning
and now snow.
Boy, these El nino
conditions are too weird.
It's freezing out there.
Hi, guys. - What do you mean?
You're from Quebec.
I thought you guys liked the cold weather.
- Why do you think I left?
Hello, night shift.
- Hi.
Hey, check it out. - Can
somebody get me a weather update?
What are the conditions gonna
be like in the next few hours?
A new toy for Jeff!
You're a real man's man,
aren't you, Jeff?
I got the training wheels
off my bike last week.
She digs me.
- Okay!
Once again, we enter the exciting
world of air traffic control, people.
Whoa, whoa. Donovan?
- Yeah? - Take a look at this.
What are all these switches
and buttons and knobs for?
Get rid of the toys.
Ah, you have such a
way with people, hmm?
It's a gift.
Before I forget... cell phone.
- Ah, thank you, sir.
It's getting pretty
rough out there. - Yeah, well,
it's not so good in here either.
- Fourth floor: Toys and games.
Third floor: Electronics.
Second floor: Women's wear.
First floor...
Let's try to scoot around this.
Yes, sir!
I hate flying through storms.
I don't have the stomach for it.
What's Greg doing
with my father's plane?
He's a good pilot. Why don't you
just sit down and strap yourself in?
I don't feel like it.
There's some nasty
weather out there tonight.
Hey, take a look at this.
- What?
Flight 109.
Cutting it pretty close
to that storm.
Bickster, punch up
a profile on 109.
109.
Yes, 109.
It's a 727 private.
Those pilots
are always in a hurry.
You never see a commercial carrier
try to edge around a storm like that.
1087, you are clear
for takeoff.
I'm gonna kill her.
- Nicole, will you sit down?
Calm down.
I'm gonna be airsick.
Do you need something?
- Yeah.
Nicole, would you put that
stuff back, please? - Half a second.
Is that your father's Roberto
Clemente bat? How'd you get that?
He's gonna kill you. - Yeah? Well, he
loves the bat more than he loves me.
No, he's gonna love using that bat
on you when he finds out it's gone.
Come on!
We're supposed to be avoiding this.
Nicole, would you stop playing with
the first-aid kit? We might need it.
Relax! I'm gonna do
a small impression.
Please!
Give me a break!
"Luke, feel the dark side."
Oh, I'm scared!
Something isn't right.
1475, you must hold
your current pattern.
Call 'em up. Find out
what the heck they're doing.
Done.
109, 109, come in.
109, 109, please come in.
Man, that thing's goin'
right through the tail end of that storm.
Any answer?
- Negative.
109, 109, come in, please.
Tower to 109.
Damn!
Always on my shift.
Give me a hard copy of
109's flight plan. - Tower to 109.
Do you copy?
109, this is tower.
Go ahead.
There, it's leveling out.
- Yeah, but it's still descending.
Heading out of the storm?
- No.
Something's still wrong.
109, this is tower.
- Any answers? - Do you read?
109, 109, this is tower!
Do you read?
Just got a message from downstairs.
A guy from Teknacom called,
wanting to know if 109
was landing on time.
It's the boss's plane.
And get this: His daughter's on board.
Mr. Stone.
Excuse me. - Yes, Martin.
We have a problem.
Hey, guys.
Andrea, Frank, are you okay?
Come on, Frank!
Frank! Come on, guys!
Andrea, please!
Oh, my God.
What happened?
There was an explosion.
I think it was lightning. I don't know.
My head.
Come on.
I'm worried about Frank.
He doesn't look too good.
He's really bleeding a lot.
What hit us?
The first-aid kit.
It got sucked right out of the hole.
I know it's my fault!
I'm sorry for playing around.
The pilot.
Okay. Stay here.
Be careful.
Greg.
Terry.
Oh, no. Andrea!
They're both dead.
I think they're both dead. - Nicole!
Who's flying the plane?
Jeff, stay on it up here.
Bickster, go down
and take care of our vips.
Mr. and Mrs. Stone,
come with me.
What's happening with
our daughter? - At this point,
we're trying to figure
that out ourselves.
Tower to 109, please come in.
Whoa.
Give me your hand.
Hang on.
I think I've got something.
There. Try not to bleed
on my dad's bat.
Don't worry.
I'll tell him it's your blood.
This is unacceptable.
- I'm sorry, sir. That's all we know.
When you say there's no radio
contact, what exactly do you mean?
I mean, they're receiving,
but no one's answering.
But the plane is still
in the air? - Oh, yes, yes.
What happened?
- We don't know for sure.
It appears they were trying to
go around the tail of a storm.
The storm shifted.
It caught them by surprise.
Look, our best bit of luck is that
they're scheduled to land here,
not over at international.
They have way too much air traffic.
- Listen, you know who I am.
Whatever it costs to get that plane to
land here safely, I want you to do it.
Sir, right now it's not
an issue of expense.
There's not much we can do
until we get more information.
He's alive.
He's breathing.
They're both alive.
Hello?
Mayday!
Sos. Is anybody there?
Anyone? Sos?
Come on.
This is not working.
Hello!
Mayday, please!
This is insane. They've kept us
waiting here alone for ten minutes.
Ray, they don't know anything.
- Well, they've got to know something!
Ray, why don't you sit down?
Oh, God.
Maybe we should run
the projections again.
Already did it three times.
Look, unless flight 109
changes course, and soon,
we're gonna have a front-row
seat when it comes down.
It's gonna come down hard.
Mayday.
We have to figure
out how to land. - Yeah.
Okay.
Take it easy, okay?
You don't look okay.
- I'm fine.
I'll help out Greg,
get him secure.
I'll be back to
help you, okay? - Okay.
Okay.
Mayday.
Tonight, 300 people paid a thousand
dollars apiece to hear me speak...
Because I'm rich,
because I'm important.
I'm the man of the year.
For what?
Our little girl is up
there in trouble, and...
I can't do anything
to help her.
Man of the year.
Frank.
Come on, guys.
Stick with me here.
Please don't make me
handle this all on my own.
Please!
I tried the best I could.
How's it going?
Andrea!
Oh, my God! Andrea!
Oh, what'll I do?
Oh, um...
Hello?
Anybody there?
How does this thing work?
Hello? Anyone?
Help, please!
Hello!
Work, you worthless
piece of garbage!
Please!
Uh, 109, do you copy?
109, this is tower.
Yes, I copy.
What is your status?
- My "status"?
My status sucks,
that's my status.
Put this on the speaker.
- Listen to me.
There was an explosion in the plane.
There's a hole in the wall.
Everybody's hurt except me,
and no one's flying the plane.
My name is Nicole Stone.
I'm 13 years old, and I really
don't wanna be here right now.
Okay, Nicole, I hear you.
I understand.
Everything's gonna be
just fine, okay?
My name is Jeff,
and I'm gonna talk you through this.
Okay, keep talking to me, Jeff.
You know those scenes in the movies where
the stewardess has to fly the plane,
and somebody like Charlton
Heston has to talk them down?
Well, I'm gonna be
your Charlton Heston.
Can you be my
Brad Pitt instead?
Um, sure, but I'm
a lot better-looking.
Listen up. You've got 109.
Everything else is off your plate.
I'll have Carrie and Dave
pick up the slack, all right?
All right.
Good luck.
Jeff, I'm really scared.
Yeah, I know you are, Nicole,
but we're gonna get through this.
I want you to try
and stay calm, okay?
Okay.
Now, I want you to describe the control
panel to me. Start from your far left.
Look, I don't know what you want me to
tell you. There's rows of lights, gauges,
buttons and switches
and dials...
yeah, and in the middle here
there's this big thing with levers.
I don't know.
- Okay, Nicole, listen carefully.
Do not touch those levers
until I tell you to.
Don't worry.
I won't touch anything.
Nicole, those levers
are for landing the plane,
and you are not ready to
land that plane yet, understand?
Okay. And there's this
light with "autopilot."
Is that what's flying the plane?
- Yeah, so far.
Okay. But there's this buzzing sound
coming from it right underneath the panel.
"Buzzing sound"?
Oh, man.
The autopilot is scrambled.
What's going on?
Somebody talk to me.
Nicole, listen, we want
to test the autopilot.
What do you mean, "test"?
- Honey, it's real simple.
Just hit the switch
below the autopilot light.
If the light goes out,
turn it right back on, okay?
Okay.
It's not going out.
That's okay. Um, we...
want you to try something else.
I want you to grab the controls...
the steering wheel in front of you...
and pull back
as hard as you can.
It may fight you a little bit,
but that's the autopilot.
Pull it back as far as you can.
If you do, that light will go out.
It won't let me move it.
That's okay, Nicole.
Um, let it go.
Just let the autopilot do its job.
Just... sit back and try to relax.
Stay with her.
I'm gonna go talk to her parents.
Nicole, you can call me Bickster.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Run that by me again.
I thought the autopilot
was a good thing.
It is. It's a great thing.
It saves lives.
In fact, it saved your daughter's life.
- So, why is it a problem?
After the accident,
the autopilot took control of the plane.
That's what's flying the airplane, and
it's bringing it down here to the airport.
But isn't that what we want?
The line of descent
is all wrong.
The autopilot's internal
guidance system is scrambled.
We cannot disengage the autopilot.
And the autopilot is telling
your plane to crash.
Oh, it's getting cold.
I guess it's a bad time to say
"I'm sorry for being such a jerk lately."
Listen, it's simple. We just get her
to try to reconfigure the wave points.
That's insane. You need an
aeronautics engineering degree to do that.
Maybe she can fight the autopilot
enough to take it over to lake Crenshaw.
Water landing.
- Crenshaw's too far.
She'll wind up
taking out a city block.
I wonder if they have
any chutes on board?
It wouldn't matter.
They're all unconscious.
And we still have
to land the airplane.
All right, listen.
How about this:
Nobody open their mouth unless
they have a good idea, okay?
Yes. We could
start that with you.
Shut up, Bickster.
Whatever, okay? We still have to
contain the fire when it crashes.
Listen, people.
We don't have
a learning curve here.
We've got to get this right
the first time. There is no second chance!
That's my little girl up there,
my coworkers, my friends!
There is no next time
for them. This is it!
Look, I...
I know you people
know your jobs, but...
That's our little girl.
I'm begging you.
Please!
Mr. Stone, I'm sorry, but it's
against regulations to have you in here.
Donovan, forget
your precious regulations.
He's right. We can discuss
strategies and options all we want to,
but time is
the real enemy here, folks.
Fine. Okay, fine.
Now, two things have to
happen within the next hour.
One: That plane has to
come down safely.
And two: Those people
have to get off the plane.
Wait a minute.
It doesn't necessarily
have to happen in that order.
We're going to have
another plane...
Wait. Say that again.
I can't hear you. There's static
Okay, Nicole, listen to me.
I can't hear you.
I didn't get all that.
Something about another plane.
Nicole, listen to me. We're going to
send another plane up there to meet you.
"Another plane."
Yeah, I heard that.
But the other plane
will be a refueler.
It looks like
a flying gas tank.
I copy.
Good. Out of the back of the plane, there'll
be something that looks like a long pole.
It's called a boom.
They use this to pump gas.
Pump gas?
Am I running out of gas?
No! No, Nicole.
Your fuel is fine.
You don't have any problems at all.
I want you to listen to me.
The people that fly these
planes are very, very good...
at getting close
to other planes in midair.
That's why we're using one.
But instead of using
the boom to pump the gas,
we're gonna transfer you and
everyone else off of the plane,
and put another pilot
on the plane.
Do you understand?
- I can't hear you. I didn't get that.
Nicole, we're going
to use the boom...
To transfer you and everyone
else off of that airplane.
I can't hear you.
There's something wrong with
my microphone. - Nicole, can you hear me?
I didn't get that.
Something about a boom?
There's something wrong
with my microphone.
Nicole?
Can you hear me?
Nicole. Come in.
Nicole!
Nicole.
Nicole?
What happened? What happened?
- I don't know.
Well, how is she?
Is it anything serious?
Flight path is still holding,
for whatever that's worth.
It was just the communicator.
I'm sure it was nothing more than that.
I didn't even get
a chance to talk to her.
Why do you want
to transfer everyone?
That's dangerous.
Why can't you just land the plane?
We can't even be sure that the
autopilot can be disengaged.
And maybe our men will have to make a
crash landing in some deserted area.
Who knows what else
she's dealing with up there.
We know people are injured.
We know they're unconscious.
We cannot parachute these people.
Our options are extremely limited.
I'm afraid this is
the way it has to be.
Yes, we got
an emergency situation here.
Jeff? - Tell me you
have some good news.
We're lucky. There's a guard refueler at
Kensington, crewed up and ready to go.
Night maneuvers.
There's even a medic on board.
And, sir, fortunately,
this crew specializes in trouble.
Well, then, they've done
this sort of thing before.
Well, frankly, no one has
done this sort of thing before,
but their experience and
versatility make the odds a little better.
Okay.
The refueler's empty,
so it's gonna move a lot
faster than it normally does.
Flight 109 is moving
slower since the accident,
so they should be side by
side in about 15 minutes.
That doesn't give 'em
a lot of time.
Sir, this couldn't have
happened any faster.
We're just lucky Jeff here came
up with the idea when he did.
Let's not get
too excited just yet.
The hard part's still to come.
There's a midair transfer
about to happen...
That would be a challenge
to the best professionals,
and no one on 109
knows what to do.
Oh, this stupid thing!
Hello!
I can't hear anything.
Hello. Does anyone hear me?
Jeff, are you there?
Hello, Jeff?
Oh, this worthless
piece of junk!
Hey, Andrea, are you okay?
Please stay with me. Come on.
For once, I could use some adult supervision.
Ohh! Why couldn't you have passed out when
I was kissing Mike Adams last summer?
You were wide awake then.
And what about that time I
wanted to have that beach party?
I would have loved for
you to drop off, but no.
You're picking the worse times to
be unconscious, you know that?
I know you can hear me.
They're gonna rescue us.
You're gonna be okay.
We're all gonna
get out of this, I promise.
I just wish I knew
what to do next.
It's a good thing
I never grew up, huh?
Yeah.
Mr. and Mrs. Stone,
would it help you at all...
If I showed you how
we're gonna pull this off?
Yeah. Please.
- Great. Come here.
Okay. Let's say that
this is your airplane,
and this is the refueler.
Now the boom.
The boom is normally for
transferring fuel...
From one plane to another
while they're both in flight.
But we're gonna do something
a little bit different.
Instead of putting the boom at the
front of the plane for refueling,
we're gonna move the boom
over to the side door here.
There's a hatch in the back
of this refueling plane.
Now, someone's gonna
open up the door,
and we're gonna get a guy to
slide across this boom here.
He's gonna slide over
into your airplane.
Once he's inside, he's gonna transfer
your daughter and everyone else...
Back across the boom
and into the refueler.
Oh, God. - That'll take
care of our first problem.
Then he's gonna try to keep the
plane from wipin' out this airport.
That's the plan,
and it can work.
I just wish there was some way to
communicate this with your daughter.
I'm gonna check on the others. You're
in charge. You think you can handle it?
Okay, excellent.
I knew I could count on you.
Okay, guys.
I'm gonna tell you
like I told Andrea.
We're gonna be okay.
Everything's gonna be fine.
You hear me?
As soon as
the other plane comes,
all of our problems
will be solved, I promise.
It's okay.
We have a problem.
We've got to find a way
to get that side door open.
The refueler, channel four.
The pilot's name is Lopez.
Put it on speaker, Jeff.
Go ahead.
This is tower.
Tower, this is US ang 2-7,
captain Lopez.
Copy that, Lopez. - Am I talking
to the man who masterminded this plan?
Yeah, in the flesh.
You up for this?
We are state of the art, my friend.
But you've definitely made our
night a little more exciting.
My boomer tells me he should be able
to waggle the probe into position.
Wind shear allowing,
I can hold it there.
I just can't hold it forever.
You just need to get
that door open.
I copy that, 2-7. I've just
got to find a way to talk to her.
Understood, tower.
My guys are still rigging
the cabling,
and a medic is standing by.
It looks like the tail end
of the weather's behind you,
so I don't think mother nature's
gonna give us too many more problems.
Roger that.
We are 300 meters
from target and closing.
Tower, I have a visual
on 109 now,
and I'd say mother nature's
already done her worst.
Making our pass now, tower.
Visual survey of damage...
it's pretty much
what you expected:
Scoring along the fore end
of the outer fuse,
and there's a pretty nasty
hull breach in the main cabin.
But there's no apparent fuel leak
and no apparent wing damage.
Oh, thank God for that.
You can say that again. See, if there
was wing damage, we couldn't do this.
The downwash from the refueler
would put too much strain on 'em.
They'd snap right off.
-  Tower, 2-7 moving into position.
What's downwash?
Now what?
I'm seriously gonna lose it.
I'm just gonna strap myself in
before I get thrown out of this.
Oh, my!
Tower, we're holding position.
Copy that, 2-7.
Standing by.
My boomer's ready to go.
We're just waiting on the cabling.
Copy that, Lopez.
- It's time to get that door open.
We have got to find a way to get
back into contact with Nicole.
Well, I'm pretty sure she knows the
refueler is already up there by now.
Yes, but if we don't get her
to disengage the lock,
we have no way of getting
the people off the plane.
Why can't they just open it
from the outside?
Because it won't work. The airplane
doors are specifically designed...
Not to open from the outside
during flight.
It's a safety feature.
I know it's frustrating,
but normally safety features save lives.
This is a one in a bill... no, no.
Jeez, it's a one in a trillion situation.
Yes, it's frustrating, but...
- Wait a minute.
I don't know much about aircraft, but why
does she have to open up the door at all?
Isn't there a hole already
in the side of the airplane?
Now we know why
you're the millionaire.
2-7, this is tower.
When your cabling is in place,
there's something I'd like you to try.
Hey, now where are they going?
Tower, we have cabling in place.
We're rigging our man
to go over.
It's in the hands
of the boomer now.
Roger that, 2-7.
Here we go.
I really wish I knew what
was going on over there.
Target coming in.
Rate:
One foot per second.
Steady.
Go slow and steady.
Even it up.
Keep it steady.
Come on.
That's it.
Pull back, Lopez!
Pull back!
Come on.
Help me out down here.
Uh-oh.
Pull back, Lopez!
We have to try it again.
We'd like to take another
go at it. Please advise.
2-7, we don't have a choice.
Give it your best shot.
Roger that. Go.
All right.
Here we go.
Oh, I can't take it! I have to
go see what's going on out there.
Wait a minute.
Slow and steady.
Come on.
Keep it steady.
All right.
Come to papa.
Pipe: Five by five.
Come on. Come on.
Tension rate's good.
Steady.
Come on.
Contact! It's in!
All right, Reynolds, get up here.
You're on. - On my way.
Excellent work, 2-7.
- Oh, that phone!
Tower!
2-7, can you hold position
for the transfer?
We'll make it happen, tower.
Never lost a man yet.
Jeff! Take the phone!
Hurry!
Yeah. - Do you know how
much lying you have to do...
To get an operator to connect
you to a control tower?
Nicole?
- What's happening, Jeff?
How is she making this
phone call?
I thought the communications
were fried. - Andrea has a cell phone.
Nicole, hang on. I'm gonna
put you on the speakerphone.
Nicole! It's daddy!
- Nikki, are you okay?
Mom! Dad!
Nikki, are you okay?
- Nicole, listen to me! - Please!
Tower, we've got our man
ready to go.
2-7, we have contact
with 109.
Roger that.
Please advise 109:
Stay strapped in
until the cable's in place.
Our man will come to them,
once inside.
Copy, 2-7. Nicole, we need you
to stay right where you are.
Someone's coming over now.
- Coming over on that pole thing?
That's right.
- I'm gonna get everyone ready.
No, Nicole, please.
Stay where you are, sweetie.
Let our man come to you.
Understand?
I can get everyone
out of here faster.
I'm the only one
that's not hurt.
I'm just terrified.
Just do what they say, okay?
- That's right, honey. You listen to Jeff.
Tower, we're catching
some bow wave from 109.
I need some time to stabilize
before I send my man over.
Roger that.
Yeah, the refueler's
getting jostled by...
The air your plane
is pushing ahead of itself.
Usually, this wouldn't
be a problem,
because when the refueler's full of gas,
it's heavy enough not to be affected.
I thought that no gas
was a good thing.
A few minutes ago it was.
What's going on?
Everything's getting shaky.
You're picking up turbulence. The two
planes are batting some air back and forth.
Is that bad?
- It's not good or bad, Nicole.
It... it just is.
Hang in there.
Tower, come in.
- This is tower. Go ahead.
I don't know how much longer
we can maintain connection.
I want to try and stabilize
before I send my man over.
Understood, 2-7, but we
are running out of time.
Tower, I have a suggestion.
Right now the boom is just sitting
there in the breach of the hull.
There's a locking device
in the tip of its probe.
Usually it's activated when
it snaps into the fuel port.
If we can get the passenger to
activate the device manually...
it would help hold the boom in place.
- F.A.B., tower.
That should buy us enough stability
to send our man over with the cable.
No. It's gonna be
too dangerous for the girl.
Yeah. He's right.
- As opposed to the situation she's in now?
Why can't they activate this thing
themselves by remote control?
Because they can't. It has to come
in contact with the fueling port.
In our case, we make it
think it has. - Let me guess.
It's a safety feature.
Let me get this straight. First you tell me
not to move. Now you're telling me to move?
Nikki, listen.
You can do this.
Just do what they
tell you to do.
It's okay.
Okay.
Nicole, on the end of
the boom is a large nozzle.
That's what's sticking through
the hole in the airplane.
Hit it as hard as you can.
If you do, it'll open up like an umbrella...
And help hold the boom
in place.
Hit it? You mean, punch it?
- Yes. No, no, no, no.
Don't hit it with your fist. Find
something stronger. Anything.
Don't sweat it.
I got something.
Okay, I'm going in. You want me to
hit this thing as hard as I can?
That is correct.
- Excellent.
Oh, my God.
Tower, things are getting very
unstable up here. - Copy, 2-7.
Hold still.
I can't stabilize.
We're lo...
Lopez, we're losing it.
I can't hold it.
We're losing it.
The boom's gonna shred the cabin.
- Get the girl outta there now!
Nicole, get out
of the cabin now!
I can't hold it.
We've lost it!
They've separated.
Tower? Tower, do you copy?
Tower. Go ahead.
We couldn't maintain
the distance.
We got knocked out of range.
We've lost the boom.
Repeat:
We have lost the boom.
Oh, God.
There's additional damage
to the fuselage of 109.
And without the boom,
we can't do anything. Sorry.
Hello? Does anyone hear me?
- It's mom and dad. We're still here.
Carrie, get coordinates and try to find
out where that boom's going to hit.
Already on it.
- Nicole, are you all right?
Yeah, I guess.
- We had a problem with the refueler.
The boom got pulled away
from the airplane and...
I know. I was in here.
But listen to me.
The hole is even bigger.
That boom thing
tore it open even wider.
I'm afraid
we're gonna fall out.
Did you copy that, 2-7?
Copy. Tower, we're
out of ideas up here.
Don't see how we can
facilitate a midair transfer now.
Uh, 2-7,
maybe you could, uh,
extend a man out over the breach,
set up the tether that way.
It wouldn't hold for transfer.
We'd lose everyone.
That's why we were gonna
use the boom, for the extra support.
Hey, what's going on?
- Stand by, Nicole.
Somebody give me an idea,
please!
We have to initiate emergency
airport evacuation right now.
You can't leave
my baby up there.
I'm sorry, but there's a lot
more people in harm's way.
Thirty minutes from now, this airport becomes
ground zero, and I gotta worry about them.
I'm sorry, Jeff.
He's right.
Bickster, alert
airport authority.
Priority red one evac plan.
Dave, Carrie, alert all personnel.
We're closing down the airport.
Divert them to their alternatives.
Let's go! Operations, this is tower.
We have a code red.
Repeat: Code red.
Initiate evacuation
procedures immediately.
This is not a drill.
Repeat: This is not a drill.
Carrie, make sure
all inbounds are diverted.
Dave, check the radar and make
sure we aren't missing anybody.
Mr. Stone, we have a...
Situation here where...
Jeff.
Please.
That is correct, sir.
This airport's closed
until further notice.
Uh, please repeat, tower.
If I heard right, then
whoever thought of this is a genius.
Okay, 2-7, if we can get
the landing gear down,
we can have the man
crawl up into the nose wheel.
Literally have him crawl
through the lower fuselage.
If you still got the cabling on,
he can attach it in the wheel well...
And start pulling people through
the floor panel in the cabin.
We'll give it a shot, but please be
aware the air is getting thicker.
There's more friction.
The ride is gonna get a lot rougher.
Copy that, 2-7,
but we have to try.
This is only gonna work if
the landing gear is down. - Roger that.
Nicole, do you understand
what you have to do?
Sure. First you tell me to
go in the cockpit, then in the cabin;
then you want me to go back into the
cockpit and then back into the cabin.
I guess you want me to go in the
cockpit now, right? - Right. You got it.
I don't wanna leave these guys out here.
The hole is really big now.
I understand, but the best thing
you can do for them right now...
Is to get
that landing gear down.
Okay.
I really don't want to fall out.
Okay. I'm here in the cockpit.
Now what?
We're gonna try to do
something we've done before.
I'm gonna talk you through
the control panel, okay?
I understand, yeah.
On the right-hand side,
I need you to find the control pillar.
Okay.
- You see it?
Yeah, I see it. - Now, there
should be six lights right above it.
Uh, I guess,
but they're not lit up.
That's okay. When the wheels
are down, the lights will go on.
Okay.
Lower the handle,
and tell me if the lights come on, okay?
Keep something in mind
before you hit that switch.
If the wheels come down,
it will slow the plane.
Okay.
That's the autopilot
reacting to it.
There's gonna be a lot
of turbulence. - More turbulence?
It should settle out.
We think once the wheels are down,
the autopilot will compensate by
bringing your plane down faster.
Faster? - Your angle of
descent will become steeper.
That's perfectly normal. I do not want you
to worry about that when that happens.
Well, it's worrying me.
Once the landing gear is down, we can
have you off that plane in ten minutes.
Okay, here it goes.
I can't.
It's not working.
Well, try it again.
Make sure you press it all the way.
I guess that's the turbulence.
Tower, I see the landing gear.
- Yes.
All right, boys.
We're gonna try this again.
Let's get it right this time.
All right. Okay.
All right.
Here he goes.
Here they go.
Close in about 20 feet.
Closing.
That's too fast.
Slow it down.
Yeah!
- So did it work? Hello?
Did it work?
- Stand by, Nicole. 2-7?
We have contact.
- Ya-hoo!
Tower, we have contact.
- Nicole, we have contact.
Stay right where you are.
You're about to have some company.
Nicole?
Nicole, come in!
- Why isn't she answering?
I don't know.
Ten minutes, huh?
Let's try and cut that in half.
Jeff said the rescue guy
was coming through here.
The faster I get these people ready,
the faster we get off this thing.
Hey, rescue guy.
- Yes?
Well, let's start rescuing.
There's three more, plus me.
Okay!
We're ready
for the first transfer.
Tower, we're ready
Is it Nicole?
- I... I don't know.
Coming down. Get up here!
Come on! Let's move it!
We have transfer.
Is it her?
Adult female.
Andrea.
It's Andrea.
All right.
She's clear.
A-ask them... what happened
to my baby. Ask them.
2-7, what's the status
on the little girl?
Can't say for sure, tower.
Female is unconscious.
Possible head trauma.
She can't tell us anything.
What happened
to my little girl?
There's two more, plus me.
All right.
Let's not forget about me.
Ready for second transfer.
Lopez, it's getting
real bad out here.
Let's move!
Okay, we got him.
As soon as he's clear, take him
back there. This cable isn't gonna hold.
Tower, we have second transfer...
adult male.
It's one of the pilots.
Tower, it's starting to get
a little rough up here.
There's one more, plus me,
and I might need help
with this one.
He's coming down!
Frank, please!
Please wake up.
Help me! Please!
Please.
Okay. Unhook him.
We got two more, and that's it.
Come on. Frank.
Come on, Frank.
We're running out of time.
Nicole, we got to go now!
- We're not gonna make it.
Tower, come in.
We have the little girl and one
last man still on board 109.
I don't think
we'll be able to get both.
2-7, can you transfer
both of them at once?
Negative, tower.
Cable won't hold.
It's barely holding as is.
Come on!
There's no more time!
We gotta go, now!
Frank! Frank, please!
Please wake up!
Help me!
I love you.
I remember.
I remember everything.
Just please wake up.
Let's get out of here.
Help me.
I'll never disappoint you
again, I promise.
Please!
I can't leave him.
- Come on! We gotta go.
I can't leave him here. Help me, please.
- We gotta go now!
We're losing it. Guys, we're losing it!
Release the winch!
Reynolds!
- We gotta go, Nicole!
No!
Lopez, we've lost Reynolds!
- Tower, we lost a man.
Repeat: We lost a man.
Damn it!
Tower, I have a confirmed signal.
Our man opened his chute.
2-7, what about the other
two passengers? What about the girl?
Negative, tower.
Our man doesn't have them.
They're either
lost in transfer...
Or still on board the plane.
No.
I wish there was
something more we could do.
We'll have to
abort the mission.
S-stand by, 2-7.
Understood, tower.
I'm sorry.
No. No, she's
still up there.
Nicole and Frank are still up there.
Nikki, pick up the phone!
Nikki!
Nikki, pick up that phone!
Nikki.
I really want to get off
this airplane now.
Oh, my God.
Nikki. Oh, Nikki.
What happened to you?
I was trying to speed things up.
I moved everybody over.
I saw a man fall from the plane.
Is he all right? Is everybody okay?
Yes, honey.
You saved their lives.
You did great, honey.
I love you.
I miss you, dad.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I let you down.
No, you didn't let me down.
That never happened, Nicole.
I let you down.
I spent so much time trying
to make things happen...
For all of us that...
no.
You never let me down.
And I've never been so proud...
Or loved anybody as much
as I do you right now.
I love you, dad.
I love you, Nicole.
I love you!
Jeff?
Yeah. N-Nicole,
I'm right here.
You said I could land this plane
like in the movies, right?
Right, but, Nicole,
you can't take over the controls...
As long as the autopilot
won't disengage.
You try, but you just keep fighting
the autopilot, and the autopilot wins.
Well, the autopilot's
not as pissed off as I am.
Where's the autopilot located?
Near the window?
Actually, it's
in the rear of the plane.
It would take an expert to go through the
circuitry to disengage the autopilot.
Understand?
- Whatever.
I figured out how
to disengage the autopilot.
You... you what?
I'm flying the plane,
but I don't know how to fly.
Something's up.
Abrupt change in 109's flight path.
- She's flying the plane.
She's flying the plane!
Nicole, I want you
to grab the controls,
the, uh, the steering wheel
in front of you,
and pull back towards you
until the plane levels out.
Do you understand?
- Okay.
Nicole, to make this work,
you have to do exactly what I tell you to do.
Tell me.
On the left side of the panel
in front of you,
there's a round ball with a
horizontal line running through it.
Do you see it?
- Yeah.
Right. I see it. It's like a small "w",
small, tiny plane type thing.
That's right.
I want you to move the steering wheel...
To keep the part of the ball
where black meets white...
Even with the white horizontal
line that's in the glass.
Move the controllers
forward or back?
Back, Nicole.
Ease it back.
Now what?
I want you to ease
the controls forward now.
The altimeter will change positions,
but try to keep the two lines even,
even though they're not
together anymore.
Okay.
Now what?
Keep the wings of the little
plane lined up with the horizon.
If one wing is higher, move the control
in that direction to level it out.
If the right wing's higher,
I move it to the...
to the right.
- Okay, the right. Okay, I got it.
Good. Now, Nicole, once the wings
are level, start pulling the controls back.
Understand? That will mean your
wings are holding steady...
And that you're lowering
the plane for landing.
Okay, I... I'm doing it,
I think.
You're doing great, Nicole. Now, remember,
there's gonna be some turbulence.
There's always turbulence.
Just remember, stay calm.
Ease the steering wheel back.
Keep the altimeter even.
Okay. I got it,
I think.
You'll feel yourself,
see yourself getting lower.
Yeah, I do. I am.
Good. Now, we should be able to
see you from here very soon.
Any minute now, you should be
seeing a strip of landing lights.
They'll look like they're almost
floating right in front of you.
I can see them. Oh, God, I can't do this.
Please don't make me do this.
Nicole... you can.
You can do this.
You can do anything, if you don't quit.
We need you.
Do you hear me?
Okay, dad.
Okay.
Okay, Jeff, what's next?
Nicole, I want you to aim the plane
right between the landing lights.
At the same time, I want you to
pull back on the steering wheel.
The lights won't fill your
windows anymore. Do you understand?
Yeah. Okay.
Now listen carefully.
As you're landing, I need you to hit the
three levers to your right-hand side.
One, two, three. Left to right.
Then jam your foot into the brakes.
I can't believe
I'm landing this plane.
Nicole, you're doing fine.
Jeff? Jeff?
I don't believe it!
Nicole? Nicole!
I have a visual!
- Where?
Fifteen hundred feet...
And dropping.
How many crash teams
did you send to the runway?
All of them.
- Stand by.
I'm not gonna die. I'm not gonna die.
I'm not gonna die.
nine hundred feet.
She's a little uneven.
Eight hundred feet.
Come on, Nicole.
I'm not gonna crash. I'm not gonna crash.
I'm not gonna crash.
Oh, please, God.
350 feet.
She's still uneven.
Come on.
You can do it.
Two hundred feet.
Please, please.
At least for my mom and dad.
Come on. Come on.
This is not gonna be pretty.
I can do this. I can do this.
I can do this.
125 feet.
Please, God, just for my baby.
- She's gonna do it.
A hundred feet, damn it.
Eighty feet.
Prepare for impact.
Fifty feet.
Oh, shit!
Yes, she's down!
She's going too fast. No reverse thrusters.
She can do it.
- She has to hit those switches in order!
What did he say?
Left to right.
Left to right. Come on!
- She'll do it.
I told you, she'll do it.
Do it, baby.
Come on, Nicole.
Left to right.
One.
- One.
Come on.
Two. Come on.
Two.
Three.
- Three.
Yes!
- Yes!
All right!
Hey!
Oh, good.
Good.
Nicole!
- Dad!
Oh, honey!
Oh, Nikki!
I love you, baby.
Sorry, dad.
- It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Shh!
Oh, it's okay, honey.
It's okay. It's okay.
- No, dad. Dad.
Shh, shh, shh!
- No, I need to tell you...
What? What?
Roberto Clemente really was the
greatest baseball player of all time.
Oh, honey.
Oh, dad.
Hey, Nicole.
Sorry about the Brad Pitt thing.
It's okay.
My folks won't let me date
until I'm 16, anyway.
Left to right?
Left to right.
Closed-captioned by
captions, inc. Los Angeles
Corrected by: suadnovic