Excuse me sir, i
know you've been
waiting for an answer
from the states.
Mr. David sloan has unwisely
declined your generous offer.
Just what did he say?
He was inclined not
to want to cooperate.
What did he say?
Sir, he said it would
bra cold day on
mars before he would
ever kiss your ass
and that you could kiss his.
How unfortunate for mr.
Sloan to misunderstand
the business policies of
the negaal federation.
You have 48 hours in which
to eliminate mr. Sloan
and enlist the new american
kickboxing champion.
Of course.
[Man chuckling]
[roaring]
man: 1, 2, 3, 4!
5!
6!
7!
8!
Hyah! Hyah!
Flower.
Excellent.
Enough.
That's it for today.
Attention.
All: movement without
spirit is nothing.
Movement without spirit is nothing.
That's right.
See you on tuesday.
Practice.
Hey, chalky.
Hey, matt, did you
read the paper today?
No. Why?
Look at this.
David sloan was
murdered last night.
What happened?
Well, i don't know.
It says here
it wasn't robbery;
he still had his wallet.
Could i see that?
Matt, anything you
want me to do?
Send flowers to his family?
Yeah. Please.
Thanks.
[Crowd cheering]
[bell rings]
all right.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the main event...
you listening?
Hey, you listening?
Yeah, yeah.
I want you to pace
yourself, you got it?
Hey, matt.
Hey, close the door, will ya?
There's a draft.
You want to freeze the kid?
What's up, gus?
Hey, matt, you're here, man.
This is great.
Of course i'm here.
I just hope you're
not wasting my time.
You kidding?
I give him 2 rounds.
6 years, matt.
You know, you said it would
take 10 before i won the belt.
Johnny, you haven't won yet.
I won't let you down.
I know.
Hey, hey, do you mind? We got
a fight to get ready for.
Sorry, gus.
Now you just watch his right
heel kick, all right?
All right. Thanks.
Good luck.
Mike.
Johnny: hey, matt?
Sorry about david sloan.
Yeah, me, too.
He was a good guy.
Hey, you keep your
hands up, all right?
This one's for david!
[Bell rings]
[both grunting]
[crowd cheering]
keep your hands up!
Stay strong, stay strong!
Hands up... matty, glad
you could make it.
Hello, max.
I wish it was you in there.
Boy, you brought in the bucks.
Don't get me wrong.
I think what you're
doing is very noble,
sharing your impeccable
skills with your students.
It's new blood.
But, damn it, you could
have made a lot of bread.
There's no money in
kickboxing, max,
at least not for the fighters.
Hey, your kid gonna win?
And does it really matter?
You make money either way.
As long as it's bloody.
Good-bye, max.
[Groaning]
come on, johnny.
Get up.
Referee: 3.
4.
5.
[No audio]
6.
7.
8.
9.
Aah! Yeah!
Go, johnny! There you go!
[Crowd cheering]
matt: there you go! Yes!
Strong, johnny! There you go!
Yaah!
He's out, he's out.
[Ringing]
johnny styles.
Johnny: whew! All right.
Good job, man.
Good job.
Oh, man, you had me scared
in the first round.
Johnny: i wasn't worried at all.
I'm telling you, i wasn't worried.
See the fear in his eyes?
Matt: oh, yeah, i did.
Man: johnny styles.
I have something of the
utmost importance for you.
It's an invitation to join
the negaal kickboxing federation
and a first-class ticket
to johannesburg, south africa
to meet with mr. Negaal.
Negaal kickboxing federation?
Never heard of it.
It's new.
But everybody's joining it.
Wow, matt. Africa.
Let me see that.
Mr. Negaal formed the organization
to bring order out of chaos.
One organization,
one set of rules, one leader.
Every fighter must join.
"Federation rules: wins
by non signatory fighters
"will be regarded as
universally unofficial
and therefore void from record."
What does it mean?
Matt: it means if you don't join,
your win tonight doesn't count.
What, can they do that?
No. Don't worry about it.
Matt: it's toilet paper.
We'd like to have a
meeting with you
later on tonight, johnny,
at the penthouse in the
mid wilshire hotel...
[chuckling] to discuss your
meeting with mr. Negaal.
Well, it doesn't cost anything
to check it out, right?
I suppose not.
Ok, cool.
I'll see you tonight then.
Good.
Oh, johnny, this
is serious.
Yeah.
[Mimicking]
yeah.
Protect this car with your life.
Yes, sir.
Nice car.
Thanks.
[Elevator bell dings]
johnny: how lovely.
Hi.
[Women giggling]
[knock knock knock]
matt, could i talk
to you for a minute?
Yeah, sure, chalky.
Come on in. Are you hungry?
Nah.
You know those guys that you
said were talking to johnny?
This, uh, negaal
something or other?
Yeah? Well, word is,
those guys also had a talk to
david sloan about joining up.
Oh, you know david, he's not one
to put up with anybody's shit.
Well, this was just 2 days
before they found him dead.
[Sighs]
johnny.
Hey, matt!
[Sighs]
johnny: if i sign this, i give
negaal control over everything...
commercials, public
appearances, endorsements.
I'd need his permission
to go to the bathroom.
11 international champions
have already joined
the negaal kickboxing
federation, johnny.
They can do what they
want, but like my
trainer matt says,
this is toilet paper.
Well, then...
if you'll excuse me, mr. Styles.
Gentlemen, i'll leave you to it.
Mr. Styles,
mr. Negaal makes an offer
once and only once.
This opportunity won't be repeated.
Yeah, well, no one's
gonna make me sign
a piece of paper to keep my belt.
I won it with these, and that's
the way i plan to keep it.
And that's your final answer?
Yeah, 'fraid so.
Our apologies if we
offended you, mr. Styles.
Maybe some other
time, huh, perhaps?
Johnny: whoa!
[Motorcycle approaching]
what the... reeves.
Man.
Johnny!
Whoa!
[Crunch]
reeves.
Come on, come on.
Go.
Come on, my boy.
I've got something for you.
Come on.
[Whimpering]
aah!
Jeez.
Pinto.
Ohh...
man: bull! Get in the car!
Now! Let's get out of here!
Driver: what about him?
Just drive!
Johnny?
What happened, man?
You were right.
It was toilet paper.
Get 'em, matt.
Promise.
Promise you'll stop them.
Johnny?
Bull: we've got to
get to a hospital!
Driver: i ain't driving around
with this guy all over my roof.
Shut up, both of you!
Hey! This thing doesn't work!
Yeah?
Try talking to the guy with
the antenna up his ass.
Oh, bull, you've really screwed
up big-league this time.
Ok. Pull over!
We've got to get
pinto to a hospital.
Shut up.
Hello? Long-distance.
Yeah. Get me johannesburg.
He fell on my car.
Yeah, south africa!
Double-1, double-8-0,2, triple 6.
All right, gentlemen, if that
concludes the day's reports.
There is one small problem.
This kickboxing federation of
yours is meeting resistance.
All resistance is
being taken care of.
By killing them?
You don't approve of
my methods, jack?
We're making a fortune with
gambling, drugs, and prostitution.
Why screw it up with the
kickboxing federation?
Man: it's los angeles, sir.
Tell them to hold.
Negaal: i'm busy.
Jack: we can take all
that cash and put it.
Into parking corporations
in the states.
Do you realize how much
money we could launder?
With that in mind, kickboxing
just doesn't make sense.
Doesn't make sense?
The world kickboxing
council accused me
of unsportsmanlike conduct
when i killed a dutch
champion in the ring.
And just so you know it, jack,
it was a legitimate strike.
Hmm.
I formed the negaal
kickboxing federation
to protect the art and the
sport against small minds,
and now you have a
problem with this?
What doesn't make sense?
No, i... i was just...
i'm gonna break the world
kickboxing council.
You got that?
Jack: mr. Negaal, i'm only
trying to serve your interests.
Arguing with me doesn't
serve my interests, jack.
[Breathlessly]
gentlemen...
please excuse me.
I... have an important call.
[Phone beeps]
yes, what is it?
Gentlemen, shall we?
Johnny styles... has met
an unfortunate end.
What? Matt reeves?
[Scoffs]
a job well done, moon.
Idiot.
We'll take care of it from here.
Get back immediately.
Moon: bull?
We've been called back to jo-burg.
Negaal, voice-over: we have
a situation on our hands.
I want matt reeves eliminated.
You can't touch him.
Everyone knows him.
He was undefeated in
his weight class.
I don't care who he is.
He's a witness.
I want him eliminated.
You have a problem with that, jack?
I didn't think so.
You know, boss,
we have the perfect guy for
the job in los angeles.
Isn't he in jail?
We can get him out. We have
a judge on the payroll.
I though this confinement
to maximum security suited you.
Yeah, i was a handsome man
before he did this to me...
but i wouldn't mind
seeing him again.
He made a fool of you the
last time you fought. Yeah.
Negaal: you're lucky to be alive.
Man: ha ha ha! Yeah!
Hey, let's go check him out.
There's a gang war coming down.
You're either with
us or against us.
Doing my own time my way.
Don't want any trouble.
Man, maybe trouble wants you.
I don't fight anymore.
What's the matter, croft?
You lost your balls?
Yeah, so go find someone else.
Who says we're giving you
a choice in this, man?
Aah!
I told you i don't fight.
But when a dog bites...
[speaking afrikaans]
that's afrikaans for
"rest in peace."
Man: croft!
[High-pitched whistle]
let him go.
Warden wants to see you.
Just sign there.
What's this?
It was with your things.
You're talking about organized
crime based overseas.
These murders aren't just
impossible to prove,
they're impossible
to do anything about
without getting interpol involved.
For that, you need
evidence, and all
you've got, kid,
is speculation.
Mr. Reeves.
I'm sorry about your friends.
Thanks.
[Exclaims]
[panting]
all right.
Matt: chalky?
[Yelling]
i've been sent to kill you.
Well, here i am.
If i were gonna kill you,
you'd already be dead.
And when he finds out i didn't,
he'll send someone else.
And he'll keep on sending
people until you are dead.
You came here to tell me that?
Who are you?
Your emotions have taken over.
You're vulnerable.
He likes that.
Who killed my friends?
You know who killed them.
Negaal.
Well, where are you going?
I'm going home.
[Door opens]
you sure you want to do this, kid?
I mean, those sons of
bitches are the real thing.
Just like in the old days.
They're killers, matt.
Chalky...
they were my friends.
[Zipper zipping]
i'm going.
Matt... you come
home alive, kid.
I will.
[Door opens, closes]
woman, over p.a. system: good
afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome aboard flight 297, offering
nonstop service to johannesburg.
The captain has turned
on the seat belt sign,
so if you could please
take your seats,
we can prepare for takeoff.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'd like to change my seat.
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
The flight is full,
but if you'll take your seat, i'll
see what i can do after takeoff.
So why you?
I was convenient.
Just out of curiosity,
what's the going
rate to bump me off?
Plane ticket?
You were gonna waste me
for a lousy plane ride?
It's first-class.
Well, now that you've disobeyed
orders, what's gonna happen to you?
And why go back to johannesburg?
South africa is my home.
Nobody's gonna keep me away.
Oh, i see.
And you're gonna slip right
back into negaal's backyard
and live a nice, quiet life, right?
I'd worry about your
own ass if i were you.
Why? He doesn't even
know i'm coming.
Well, moon, at least
you got the belt.
Negaal: i want you to pick
up croft from the airport.
Of course, sir.
And, moon?
Don't break the other leg.
Too much lime.
Sorry, sir.
It's time for you to get lost.
Excuse me?
[Banging on door]
[woman speaking
indistinctly on p.a.]
you're looking well.
Why the welcoming party?
I wanted to welcome you personally.
Mr. Negaal will, of course,
be expecting a full report.
Well, you'd better start thinking
about what you're gonna tell him.
Unh!
Get him!
Watch it!
Paul: excuse me!
Coming through! Coming through!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Hey!
[People murmuring]
which way did they go?
That way.
Sorry, sir. Sorry.
Back. Stay back.
Aargh!
[Grunting]
ooh!
Hey!
Aah!
You again!
Hello.
[Both grunting]
reeves!
Aah!
You can't take all 3 of us...
at the same time.
[Shouting]
come on. Get up, croft.
Let's go.
Let's get them.
Ohh!
Now they know i'm here.
And alive.
Paul: how do you think
you're gonna find negaal?
I've got his letter
to my friend johnny.
There's an address in downtown
johannesburg i'm gonna check out.
You're looking for a way
to get yourself killed.
I'm looking for a way to live.
Yeah? Well, then, i guess this
is where we part company.
I guess so.
Thanks for your help
back at the airport.
Thanks for not killing me.
Good luck.
You, too.
See you around.
Negaal: good help is so
difficult to find these days.
This guy reeves is different.
He's far more dangerous
than the others.
Tito, what does that
sound like to you?
It sounds like an excuse.
Matt reeves has made a fool
of you yet again, moon.
And, bollen, croft was your idea.
Now he's betrayed me,
and now we have two problems.
Man: excuse me, sir.
There is a mr. Rochambeau
to see you.
Ah, yes. The french champion.
I'll just be a moment.
Sir.
The undefeated matt reeves
in south africa.
I wonder.
Put out the word.
Have him found.
Have him killed.
Mr. Bollen.
Mr. Moon.
How do i feel about excuses?
You hate them, boss.
And how do i deal with them?
Try him?
Severely?
No!
I deal with them lethally.
Now, don't fail me again.
Mr. Rochambeau.
You are negaal?
I am.
I have heard so much about you.
All good, i hope.
Unfortunately, no.
An honest man.
I like that.
As long as you've come to
sign with my federation.
I have heard of the, uh,
misfortune of those who refuse.
You haven't answered my question.
I would be honored
if your federation
would endorse my title
and represent me.
No, it would be my honor.
Take care of our guest.
See that he has everything he needs
till his return to paris.
I'll have a contract
brought to you.
That makes 15 champions.
You see, tito,
they're all falling
into line like sheep.
There you go.
Thanks.
Enjoy your stay in
johannesburg, mr. Reeves.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[Drumming]
[rooster crows]
[bell ringing]
[man speaking foreign language]
[bell rings]
woman: and a thousand.
And nobody's fool in the fifth.
I've got to go now. Bye.
Good morning, sir.
May i help you?
Morning. How you doing?
Aha. An american.
West coast.
Am i right?
You're very good.
I'm fantastic with accent.
Yes, you are.
I'm a little confused.
I thought this was where to find
the negaal kickboxing federation.
Do i have the right address?
May i see that? Sure.
What is it that you need?
I have some business with
mr. Negaal.
Oh, well, maybe i can help you.
[Chuckle]
all right.
Where can i find mr. Negaal?
Oh. Well, i'm afraid
mr. Negaal has just found you.
Heh!
And your plan is to
take me to him, right?
Yeah. I got a car
waiting for us outside.
No thanks.
I think i'll find my own ride.
Oh, really?
Ooh!
Get him!
Outside!
He took off out the back.
Find him.
And when you do, hurt him!
[Grunting]
now i've got you.
[Shouting indistinctly]
damn it!
Unh!
Aah!
Yah!
[Crunch]
[crunch]
[groaning]
ohh!
I thought you were
on your way home.
So i took the scenic route.
Bollen: stand your ground,
you pathetic wimps!
There's only two of them!
Bollen!
Croft.
Unh!
Get them! Kill them!
[Grunting]
aah!
Unh!
[Shouting]
[grunting]
i can't... hey!
Hey! Help me!
Help me!
Ohh.
[Siren]
freeze!
Hands on the car.
Get your hands on the car.
Spread your feet.
Come on, now!
Are these the men?
Yes, sir. They beat me
up, and they robbed me.
Oh, he's lying.
He and his goons attacked
me and my friend.
Are these the same men
who robbed your shop?
Don't be afraid to tell the truth.
You shut up.
Well, not exactly.
Not exactly?
That's not what you told us.
There was a big fight, you see,
and there was a lot of
damage in my shop, and...
are these the men who
started the trouble or not?
Yes.
What? Wait a second.
Come, let's go.
Take them in.
I don't believe this.
Thanks, sir.
You have a good day, now, huh?
You did well.
[Siren]
so what happens to us?
Are there charges?
A telephone call, maybe?
After your transfer.
Transfer?
Hey! What transfer?
This jail is full.
Tomorrow morning, the
most serious offenders
will be taken to a mobile prison.
Prison?
And what do you mean,
"serious offenders"?
I can't learn to mind
my own business.
Hey, we didn't do
anything, all right?
We were just defending ourselves.
I just spent 3 years behind
bars. I don't need this.
Don't worry.
We'll get out.
Ohh.
We just need a chance to
tell our side of the story.
I should have taken the
deal and murdered you
when i had the chance.
Thank you, croft.
That's very nice of you.
Gentlemen, please.
In a small space like this,
we have no choice but to get along.
I'm joseph mabuza.
So what are you in for, joseph?
A small misunderstanding
with a customs inspector.
A few pounds of baby
powder i purchased
turned out to be, well,
not exactly baby powder.
An innocent mistake but one
with drastic consequences.
Joseph.
Here's that copy of "the
hard times" that you wanted.
Thanks, peter.
I knew i could count on you.
Enjoy your book.
Bonded irish whiskey.
Mmm.
Nothing like it.
Can i offer you gentlemen a drink?
No thanks.
We're sitting ducks in here.
We've got to find a way out.
Then how do you plan to pay
for the special service?
We'll owe you.
Hey.
Don't insult my intelligence.
Mabuza...
you ever hear of a
man named negaal?
Who in south africa hasn't?
He's a butcher, a madman.
His charm and intelligence make
him more dangerous than a cobra.
Yeah, well...
he wants to kill us.
Well, you're practically
dead already.
Negaal knows we're here.
We'll be lucky if we
live until morning.
And since you are in
this cell with us...
ohh.
I see.
I guess i'd better
make the arrangements.
And i need to contact
somebody on the outside.
Joseph: peter.
You don't like the book?
Message service, please.
This must be delivered immediately.
There's an extra charge
for express services.
Fine. Just do it.
[Grunting]
[whispering]
are reeves and croft dead?
Not exactly.
Not exactly? What does that mean?
Well, i have some good news.
They're as good as dead.
Nothing's as good as dead.
What are we gonna tell him?
Nothing.
They're in jail.
I've got someone on the inside.
[Man whistling]
i know that whistle.
It's busi.
That means there's gonna
bra cocktail party.
Paul: it's one of negaal's men.
Hi, joseph. Still awake?
You can't sleep?
It's a hot night.
Oh, well.
It's gonna get hotter.
[Screaming]
[inmates shouting]
hey, shut up.
Shut up.
I said, shut up.
A waste of wonderful whiskey,
but it was worth it.
At least you're safe from
mr. Negaal.
Yeah, for a couple hours.
[Footsteps]
wake him up.
Croft.
Well, joseph, i hope we didn't
cause you too much trouble.
I have enemies in
the mobile prison.
My transfer there would have been,
shall we say, hazardous
to my health.
Thanks, joseph.
Sure. I wouldn't stay here too
long if i were you, gentlemen.
Good luck, and godspeed.
[Siren]
[barking]
[men yelling]
come on! Let's get them!
Come on! We've got them!
[Shouting continues]
this way.
Look there!
There she is.
Come on.
[Revs engine]
go, go, go, go, go, go! Go!
Hi, paul. Heh!
It's been a while.
So who's your friend?
Just drive.
[Gunshot]
beautiful animal.
[Ejects shell]
gentlemen?
It wasn't our fault this time.
Stupid prison guard screwed up.
I assigned all 3 of you
to croft and reeves,
and now they're running around
the country like they own it!
We'll get them next time,
mr. Negaal, sir.
I'll stake my life on it.
Do you have nothing
more valuable, moon?
Mr. Bull told me how you
mishandled the situation
at the airport.
But croft was bollen's idea!
Don't blame me.
You should have killed
reeves in the first place!
Someone has to pay for
these absurd mistakes.
Boss.
Jeez.
But it was moon who messed up.
I need moon.
Bull was just muscle.
Think about that, mr. Bollen.
Get this useless sack out of here.
[Snort]
you want to tell me
where we're headed?
Home.
Why? What's there?
Safety.
Pull over!
Please.
Haven't you figured it out yet?
I don't want safety.
I want negaal.
So do you, croft.
You want negaal as bad as i do,
but you're afraid of him,
of getting involved.
You think he's just
gonna forget about you?
You screwed him over.
He'll hunt you down, and after
he's killed you and your family,
he'll find someone else to murder.
We have to stop him.
If we don't and
another person dies,
it's our fault.
What is going on?
Who is this guy?
God damn pain in the
ass, that's who he is.
Matt, wait! Wait!
Do you even know where you are?
You're in a foreign country.
You got no money. We got the
police after us with dogs.
You're in the middle of a
god damn spinach patch.
You think you're gonna
find negaal out here?
All right.
I'll help you,
but you don't know negaal.
I do.
Let's go back to my home
and get ourselves together.
Then we'll come up with a plan.
All right.
Angie, this is matt reeves.
He'll be staying with us
for a couple of days.
Hi, angie.
Hi.
Are you negaal?
I understand you don't
approve of my title.
The federation doesn't
recognize you
until you recognize the federation.
Well, i hardly think you have
anything to say in the matter.
Well, perhaps you'd like
to prove how good you are.
How good i am?
Against whom?
Oh, i don't know.
Me.
You? Ha ha ha!
Heh heh heh.
Well, perhaps it might provide
a minute or two of amusement
and teach you some respect
for your superiors.
Well, it's a lovely day out there.
Perhaps you'd like to give
me this lesson on the lawn?
On the lawn? Ha!
Ja. Gut. On the lawn.
Ohh!
Ha ha ha! Huh?
You want to fight? Huh?
You want some more?
Unh! Ohh!
I concede.
You're a great fighter.
I acknowledge your superiority.
The opportunity for
that was earlier.
A challenge to me is a
challenge to the death.
What? Are you insane?
Come.
Come!
You are joking.
Haah!
I represent the new, higher
standard of world kickboxing.
You represent the old.
Bollen: hey, gents.
You must watch this.
The tiger claw.
It's good, it's good.
He'll crush his throat.
Ohh!
Good fight, boss.
Good fight!
Not too much lime this time, sir?
Better.
Gentlemen, good afternoon.
I'm going for a swim.
And, uh, please don't forget,
my place tomorrow night.
We're celebrating the formation
of our new empire,
the negaal federation.
Champagne, gambling, entertainment.
It's all on me.
Well, gentlemen.
Ahem.
So much for art in the park.
Who knows what dinner will bring?
Shall we?
Ahem.
So how long have you
two been together?
Since birth.
He's my brother.
You know, i really thought
that you two were...
look. I'm gonna ask
you one last time.
What is going on?
And this time, i want an answer.
Do you know of a man named negaal?
I know he's the reason paul hasn't
been home for the past 5 years.
Well, he murdered
two of my friends,
and the police can't touch him.
And just what are you
gonna do about it?
Stop him...
and carry out a promise
i made to a friend.
And you're going with him?
I have to.
Dad would beery proud of you, paul.
Look. I'm sorry, matt,
but i love my brother,
and i'm grateful he's home,
but i can't let you pull
him back into that world.
Angie, i'm not pulling him back.
It's his decision.
Our father died while his
only son was in prison.
You know, maybe you need
to have some faith.
Your brother is a good man.
Angie: you know you can't go
up against negaal and bollen.
Bollen hates you for
what you did to him.
They'll kill you if
you get in their way.
Please, paul, just
leave them alone.
I'm already in their way, angie.
Negaal's put the word out
to have matt and me killed.
Paul, no.
This isn't just gonna go away.
For all the terrible things
i've done in my life,
now's the chance for
me to redeem myself.
I've got to help him.
By going after negaal?
Yes.
[Sheep bleating]
good morning.
Morning.
Thanks.
Pleasure.
Angie, he will be back.
I know he'll be back.
I'm going with you.
Hyah!
Moon has secured the area,
and there's tito
with the investors.
This is a very important
evening, bollen.
There are a lot of
influential people here.
Don't worry, sir.
Everything's been arranged.
You better be right.
Ha ha ha! Tito.
Welcome, gentlemen.welcome.
A couple of pictures.
Yes, sir, mr. Negaal.
One for each of my guests.
Gentlemen, shall we?
Bollen: gonna have
some fun tonight.
Let's go around the back.
All right.
Angie, i'm sorry. You're
gonna have to wait outside.
Paul, you said that i could...
we need you out herewith
the engine running.
If we're not back in
half an hour, go home.
Matt, wait...
angie, we'll be all right.
Yeah, right.
Gentlemen, a game of roulette.
Some chips for my guests.
Eagle eyes, buttie.
Oh.
Hi.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
How can we help you?
Ah, yes. We're here for the party.
This is a private event.
Engraved invitations only.
Don't worry. Mr. Negaal will
be pleasantly surprised.
He's been looking all
over town for us.
Thanks.
No invitation, no admission.
Besides, you're violating
the dress code.
You have to wear a tux.
Oh.
Dress code.
Beautiful animal.
Yeah.
Hey, sammy, george.
[Speaking native language]
munjani.
[Speaks native language]
is that him?
The one and only.
And there's your old friend bollen.
I don't know about you,
but i think i'll try my luck.
Excuse me.
May i use this?
Yes, sir.
Money plays.
Reeves is here.
What?
Negaal is gonna kill me.
I'll get the others.
Dealer: and zero wins.
Matt: oh, that's ok.
Let it ride.
Yes, sir.
Betting again, ladies
and gentlemen.
Thank you.
Hey, bollen.
Oh, croft.
I've been waiting a long
time for this, buttie.
Your head looks good.
Thought i ripped that ear off.
You know, somebody threw
it back into the ring
after you left.
I spent 3 years in prison
because of you, bollen.
You set me up!
Yeah? Well, you would have been
helpful to the organization
had you killed reeves.
Now you're both dead.
Ain't not exactly hurting yet.
What a shame, huh?
How's the pain, buttie?
Dealer: the gentleman wins again.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Well done.
Beginner's luck.
Can i, um, buy you a drink?
I'd love one, but it might
not be such a good idea.
Why don't you let me
worry about that?
Excuse me.
Who is this guy?
Good evening.
Why don't you pick a number,
your favorite number?
35. All right.
What about... all
of it on 35?
Negaal: just
who the hell are you?
Just another dude from the valley.
Of course.
You must be matt reeves.
You're not what i expected.
You're just a kid.
Well, you're exactly
what i expected,
a butt face.
Paul:
you're a dead man, bollen.
Get up!
Please don't kill me.
Please don't.
Matt: ladies and gentlemen, may
i have your attention, please?
I would just like
to take this moment
to congratulate mr. Negaal
and his newly founded negaal
kickboxing federation.
[Applause]
the federation was formed
because mr. Negaal,
a former kickboxer himself,
was kicked out and
banned from competition
for using an illegal move
and killing his opponent.
He now has his own organization...
we need to get him
out of here, tito.
Should they refuse, well,
he kills them, too.
Two of my friends are
dead because of this man.
At least they fought
and died with dignity,
which is more than most men do.
You're a gangster,
a murderer, and a psychopath.
Anyone who's willing to
be seen with you is dirt.
What you lack in intelligence
you make up for in passion.
I like that.
Unfortunately, your friend johnny
suffered the same dilemma.
To the house, tito.
I don't wish to be part of
this undignified brawl.
If he's worthy of me,
he'll come.
Hyah!
Again with spirit.
[Crack]
aah!
Get him in close.
Come on.
Croft!
I'm going after negaal.
Call the cops.
I think it's time we found
ourselves another job, huh?
Yeah.
Well, that party was a
glittering success.
You can wave your empire good-bye.
Oh, really?
And why is that, tito.
Those international businessmen
who were going to fund
our worldwide expansion
find your enthusiasm
for martial arts
a little... well, how shall
i put it... dangerous.
I don't need them.
Do you think famous champions
can disappear off the
face of the earth
and nobody will bloody notice?
It happens all the time.
Missing persons.
Oh, right.
Except they either got on
a plane for south africa
to join the negaal
kickboxing federation
or they received your letter
on your letterhead
inviting them to.
Enough!
We can discuss this
some other time, tito.
Right now, i'm expecting someone.
[Footsteps]
tito: oh, yes.
Someone worthy.
You killed my friends.
You're right.
I did.
What do you think?
My collection of
championship belts.
Isn't that something?
You're never gonna kill
or hurt anyone again.
Dying to fight, are we?
Our time, mr. Reeves, has come!
Aah!
[Gasping]
[coughing]
no, reeves.
Not the belts.
They're mine.
I earned them.
Never have them.
You can't have them.
My... my...
[clattering]
angie:
the police are on their way.
Let's wait outside.