What are you stopping for?
l'm getting a little nervous.
How come?
l don't know.
He's in love dummy.
l am not Mark.
Come on, let's go.
Wait.
l need to know if she's
there before we go in?
You said she's helping
during lunchtime all summer.
l mean l think she is.
She's been in there 3 days in
a row so l'mjust thinking she
does.
Her Dad's the owner.
She's in there.
Let's go.
You go look first.
Just to see if she's there.
This is stupid.
l'd do it foryou Albert.
Alright.
She's in there.
Okay, now l'm really nervous.
Don't be nervous.
Maybe we should just
come back another day.
We're on your side Dustin.
Okay, but you guys
better not embarrass me.
Hey guys.
Hi Tanya.
Hey Tanya.
What can l get foryou?
Um, l'll have a
hot fudge sundae.
Okay, one hot fudge.
l'll have a banana split with
two strawberries
and one chocolate.
No pineapple syrup?
No, l don't like pineapple.
Neither do l.
Dustin.
Oh, um, l'll get a
hot fudge sundae too.
Okay.
Coming right up.
What are you doing talking
so much with my girl?
What do you mean?
You know, talking to her about
the pineapple and stuff.
You talked to her
more than l did.
Someone had to.
l'm telling you Dustin,
l think you're in love.
l am not.
l think you are.
l don't knowwhat
being in love is.
lt's what you're
feeling right now.
How do you know?
ljust do.
How?
You've never been in love.
But my older sister is right now
and she told me how it feels and
she looks at her bofriend the
same way Dustin does when he
sees Tanya.
Ooooo, Dustin's in love.
Dustin's in love.
Come on guys, cut it out.
You'd better watch yourself,
l think Nick likes her too.
But she doesn't like Nick.
She talks to him
when he talks to her.
So that doesn't
mean she likes him.
Dustin's right.
Tanyatalks to a lot of people.
Nick.
l'd like to see someone
knock his block off.
l hate him.
l think l'm going
to ask Tanya out.
On a date?
l'm thinking about it.
You ever ask a girl out before?
No.
You?
You Albert?
No.
What are you going
to ask her out to?
l don't know.
Walk her home from the diner
or invite herto my house.
l'd wouldn't do it.
Not with Nick around.
l told you she doesn't like him.
Yeah but he likes her.
That'll be enough
to keep me away.
Mom, l'm home.
Oh Hi Dustin, Ijust
wrote you a note.
Mrs. Farley called she'd like
for you to mow her lawn tomorrow
and l told her
you'd call her back.
Okay.
Now l have a meeting tonight
So l left you some money.
Why don't you treat the boys to
a pizza and
l should be back around l:30.
Thanks Mom.
Okay.
Don't forget call Mrs. arley.
l won't.
Here we go boys.
Time to dig in.
Great.
l'm starving.
Me too.
l'll take this one.
Hey what are you doing?
Oh hi Nick.
Come on Nick, this is our pizza.
You got a problem with
something Alberta?
No.
Didn't think so.
l hate it when he calls me that.
Out of myway.
Hey, l was playing.
Oh Nick, l didn't
know it was you.
l'd be careful if l was you.
Yep.
l hate him.
Well, it looks like you've done
a real good job here young man.
Mrs. Farley will be vey happy.
Oh, thank you.
l've seen you at our church
many times haven't l?
Ah, Yeah.
You're um you're
Mr. Spery, right?
That's right.
Jonathan Spery.
And your name is ah...
um, let me think.
(struggles to remember)
Dustin.
Dustin Sharp.
Yes l know your Mother.
You know, l used to mow my own
Iawn there but ahh l'm not
getting around like l used to.
So l think it would be a lot
easier if l hired a professional
like yourself.
So, what do you say?
You think you can fit me into
your schedule and mow my lawn?
Yeah of course.
Um, l'll mow it as soon
as l'm done with here.
Well, That sounds just fine.
Okay.
l'll be over in afew minutes.
Just let me know if
you need anything.
Ah, Okay, thank you.
No, thank you.
Mr. Spery, l'm finished.
Okay Dustin.
Come in, come in.
You did a veyfinejob.
Here, come and sit down.
l was watching you
from my window.
And it's vey kind ofyou to
rake the grass the wayyou do.
Thanks.
My Mom wants me to a good
job so, you know, l ty.
Well you do.How about some
freshly squeezed lemonade.
l make it myself.
Mmm.
lt's good.
lt's the best.
l've been drinking it
that way for years.
You have a real nice
house Mr. Spery.
Do you live alone?
Yes, yes l do.
My wife passed away 4 years ago.
Oh, l'm sory about that.
Finest Christian
woman l ever knew.
The Lord allowed us to
be together46 years.
That's sure is a long time.
Oh. Yes.
Seems short now.
Anmay, how much do l owe you?
Two dollars sound fair?
Two dollars?
Well it did take me almost an
hour and that's what l usually
charge.
Well l don't think
that's s fair.
l was really
thinking about three.
Thank you Mr. Spery.
l'd like to have you come back
again, Say in two weeks or so.
Sooner ifwe get some rain.
Okay?
Yes sir.
Alright then.
You have a good day and thanks
for doing such afinejob.
Thanks for the three dollars.
You earned it.
So long.
Oh, l almost forgot, l
got a new customertoday.
Oh really.
Yeah, l was mowing Mrs. Farley's
Lawn and Mr. Spery comes over
and asked me to mow his.
Jonathan Spery from church?
Yep.
Well good for you.
He is such a nice man.
And, he paid me three dollars.
Wow.
Dear Tanya.
How are you?
No.
(he crumbles it up to
ty again)
Dear Tayna...
Where's the note?
l got it.
Well, are you going
to give it to her?
l can'tjust go up there
and give it to her.
Why not?
Cause l can't.
l gotta get it to her in secret.
Just go up there
and give it to her.
No.
l'll go then.
No you won't.
Hey Tanya, here's a
Iove letter from Dustin.
Right over here.
Shhh, come on guys.
l thought you guys were
suppose to be helping me.
Look, why don't you hand it to
the otherwaitress and tell her
to give it to Tanya.
No.
l think l'm going tojust leave
it on the table and when she
comes overto clean
it she'll find it.
Are you going to leave atip?
l was going to leave a quarter.
That guy left fifty cents.
All l got is a quarter.
You got any money?
Not me, l'm broke.
You Albert?
Don't look at me.
You guys are no help.
Don't wory about it.
A quarter is good.
Woe, big time tipper.
That's all l got.
A quarter is good.
lt will get her attention.
Are you going to say good bye?
No, l think l'mjust
going to play it cool.
Here we go.
Let's go.
Bye Tanya.
What was that?
What, l said goodbye.
l wanted to play it cool.
Now She'll think
you left the money.
No she won't.
Yes she will.
Look, you signed the note right,
so at least she'll know that's
from you.
Oh, Albert.
Excuse me, Miss, may l please
have a little more coffee?
Sure.
Thank You.
l'll get your table
for you honey.
Okay, Thanks.
So come on, are you going to
tell us what you said in the
note or not?
Why should l, it's private.
You can tell us, we
won't tell anyone.
Yeah right.
l'm surprised you guys haven't
called her yet and ruined the
whole thing.
l tried to once but
her phone was busy.
Albert.
l'm just kidding.
Come on, what did the note say?
ljust asked her if she wanted
to get togetherwith me and l'd
be back tomorrow so
she could let me know.
Wow, Dustin might be going
out on his first date.
Hey, there's my newest customer.
What do you mean?
Mr. Spery, from church.
Yeah, l mowed his
Iawn yesterday.
Yeah l've seen him before, he
taught my older brother in
Sunday School class.
And he gave me the best
Iemonade after l was done.
He makes it himself.
Does he have any more?
Would you like some more Albert?
Oh, sure.
lt's good, isn't it?
Yes it's vey good.
Mark?
Yes sir.
l made it myself, you know.
Thank you.
And Dustin?
No thank you.
You had three glasses yesterday.
No, this is enough.
He's too busy thinking
about his new girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
She's not my girlfriend.
You wrote her a note.
So, that doesn't make
her my girlfriend.
Her name is Tanya.
Tanya?
Albert.
She's a girl in our class
that works at the diner.
Her father owns it.
The problem is that
Nick likes hertoo.
Quiet Albert.
Nick's a bully.
Quiet.
l told him l thought
it was a mistake.
Albert, will you be quiet.
What am l doing?
You talked.
l was just telling.
So, it's a delicate
situation then.
Yeah, l guess so.
You know l remember the first
girl l had feelings for.
l wasjust about your age too.
Her name was Martha.
A vey pretty girl.
l liked her so much l
couldn't even talk to her.
That's Dustin.
Oh then l know how he feels.
l tried to pass a note to Martha
during class one day and it
dropped to the floor.
The Teacher saw it, picked
it up and read it out loud to
eveybody.
l was asking Martha
if she liked me.
Boy was l embarrassed.
Oh wow, can you imagine.
lf l only knewthen
what l know now.
What do you mean Mr. Spery?
Well, l failed to ask
the LORD about Martha.
Ask the Lord?
Yes, to see if He wanted me
to spend more time with her.
Turned out she wasn't interested
in anything l thought was
important.
Could have saved me
a lot embarrassment.
The LORD is interested
in the girls we like?
Absolutely.
The LORD is interested in
eveything in our lives.
Yeah, l know.
The Bible is always saying don't
do this, and don't do that.
Oh l never look at it that way.
What do you mean?
Eveything in the Bible is
there to make our lives better.
Nowthe Bible says not to steal,
do you want anyone stealing from
you, Mark?
No.
Well, l guess that'ss a pretty
good thing then, isn't it?
Yeah, l guess it is.
And the Bible says not to lie.
Do you want anyone
Iying to you, Albert?
No.
Well l guess that's a pretty
good thing too isn't it?
l neverthought of it that way.
l hardly ever read my Bible.
l'm not sure where my Bible is.
Me neither.
l see.
l tell you what.
Ah, why don't you tyto locate
your Bibles and ifyou do,
come by my house say Friday
afternoon two o'clock.
l have something l
want to showyou.
And it has to do
with chocolate cake.
Chocolate cake?
Yes.
Chocolate cake.
You like chocolate
cake, don't you?
l love chocolate cake.
Well then, can l expect
the three ofyou?
l'm not doing anything,
l can make it.
Me too.
l love chocolate cake.
Good.
l will see you
around two o'clock.
But..(short beat) remember
you must bring your Bibles.
l'm getting a little nervous.
Why, it's just a girl.
You're too young to understand.
What do you mean, l'm
just as old as you are.
Yeah but not in your brain.
What's that suppose to mean?
Like l said, you're too
young to understand.
Cut it out, guys.
l don't think l can do this.
Not again.
l mean what if she says no.
Look, you said in the note you
were going to come back today
for an answer right?
Right.
So, you need to find
out sooner or later.
Yeah, come on.
Think positive,
maybe she'll say yes.
Okay.
Where is she?
Huh?
l don't see Tanya.
Maybe she's in back.
Ah, excuse me ma'am?
l'll be with you boys
injust a minute.
Where's Tanya?
Oh, she had a dentist
appointment this afternoon.
What about the note?
Hey, Mom, can l
ask you something?
Hmm-hmm.
How old were you
when you met Dad?
How old was l?
l met him in high
School, l was fifteen.
So, you guys
started dating then?
We started to go out.
Where'd you go out to?
We went to football
games, basketball games.
He'd walk me home from
school, things like that.
Why do you want to know?
Oh, nothing, just wondering.
Now gentlemen, l have a brief
Iesson to share with you before
we enjoy that chocolate
cake that l promised.
(the boys react) First,
l have hidden the cake.
l have written notes to the
three ofyou to tell you where
that cake can be found.
Mark, you must run across the
street to the Boone's house.
Your note will be
hanging from atree.
That's the white one right?
That's right.
And Albert, you must go across
the street to the Freeman's
house They have a bush
in the front yard.
Your note will be found there.
Okay, l knowthat house.
And Dustin, the note l wrote
foryou is on this side ofthe
street at the Rafino's house,
it's taped to their porch,
alright?
Got it.
Now. l told all these people
what we
were doing so there's no need
for you to wory about them
thinking it's strange you're
coming to their houses.
But what you do have to wory
about is to meet me in the next
five minutes in
the secret place.
And that secret place
is written on your note.
Okay?
Okay.
Alright Gentlemen, your
five minutes starts...
now!
Mr. Spery.
We're back here.
Where were you Mr. Spery?
l went down to the
end oft street,
like the note said
but nobodywas there.
l couldn't even find my note.
Even a couple ofthe
neighbors tried helping me.
Must have got blown
off the porch.
You guys missed out
on the chocolate cake.
Hey, that's not fair.
What happened Mr. Spery,
l did what the note said?
Yes l knowyou did Mark.
But apparantly you had
the wrong directions.
Wrong directions?
At least you found your note.
l couldn't even find mine.
That's because there was
no note to find Dustin.
You mean l never had one?
So we don't get any cake?
l guess not.
You're so lucky, Albert.
And it was great too.
So do any of you understand
the lesson here today?
Ah...no sir, not really.
Well what if finding this cake
here represented finding heaven?
How come Albert was
the only who found it?
Because he had the
right directions?
Yes, that's right.
So why'd you give me
the wrong directions?
Because, Mark, you represent all
the people in the world who are
misdirected.
What about me?
l'm afraid Dustin that you
represent all the people that
never even heard the name
Jesus or even have a Bible.
Therefore, they
have no direction.
With that being said, do you see
how really important it is to
read this book?
lf you follow its directions, l
am sure there will be plenty of
room in heaven
(pulls out 2
pieces of cake and sets them in
front of Mark and
Dustin) for all of us.
Thanks Mr. Spery.
Yeah, thanks.
Thanks again Mr. Spery.
Yes, thank you.
Would you enjoy
another Bible lesson?
We could meet again next Monday
afternoon at the same time?
What do you say?
Sure, l can be there.
Me too.
Will there be more
chocolate cake?
Albert.
Well, l don't know Albert,
l've been leaning more towards
chocolate ice cream
Alright
Alright. l'll see you
Monday Mr. Spery.
Good bye boys
-Talk to ya later Dust.
-See you guys.
Dustin, have you got a moment?
l Really need you
to do me afavor.
Okay.
Do you know Mr. Barnes that
lives across the street there?
l've seen him but l
don't really know him.
Well He's up in age like l am,
but he's really having a hard
time getting around.
l noticed his lawn
really needs to be mowed,
so l was hoping you might do it.
Oh l'll payyou for it.
Are you sure, l don't
want to take your money.
Yes l'm sure.
Just do not tell him l am the
one having you to do it, okay?
Okay.
Ah, l could do it right now.
l mean, it's not too hot.
l could go over
there and ask him.
That will be great.
l am sure Mr. Barnes will
really appreciate it.
Okay.
Who's there?
Mr. Barnes?
Yes.
l would like to mowyour lawn.
Mow my lawn?
Yes sir.
l don't need my lawn mowed.
Mr., you don't understand.
l want to do it forfree.
For free?
Yes sir.
Nothing's free.
Well this is sir.
l reallywant to mow it.
l said l don't
need my lawn mowed.
Whywould he be so mean?
l was real nice to him.
l am sure you were.
l don't understand.
Perhaps you should go
see him in couple days,
maybe he will allow
you to do it then.
But, don't tell him who's
putting you up to this.
Okay?
Okay, l won't.
l wonder why Tanya hasn't said
anything to you about the note?
l don't know.
Well, then go find out.
Now?
Why not?
l can't talk to her in
front of all herfriends.
l'll go then.
Albert, no.
l'm just kidding.
Quit fooling around.
Wait until you
start liking a girl.
Dustin's right.
He can't talk to her now.
l got an idea.
Why don't you just walk over and
pretend to do something nearby
and we'll watch and
see if she notices you.
l can't do that.
Why not?
And if she notices you, then
we know she's interested.
And if she doesn't then
maybe that can save you the
embarrassment of talking to her.
No, that's no good.
Look, this is gonna be a long
summer ifwe have to go through
this evey day.
lf it was me, l'd wanna know
if a girl likes me or not.
And If not, then l'd start
liking someone else.
Albert, it's not something you
can turn off and on
like a water faucet.
lf you like someone,
you like someone.
Okay, then l'm going to go over
there and you guys see
if she notices me.
Then, when l get back, Dustin
you walk over and we'll see if
she notices you.
l'm not going overthere.
Well l am.
Albert.
Well, anything?
Nope.
She didn't even look.
Well l guess that's good then.
Alright Dustin, it's your turn.
l'm not going to do this.
You have to.
This is a good idea.
lf she looks up,
it's a good sign.
l don't know.
Mark, tell him.
He might have something here.
We Could watch her and
see how she reacts.
Might give you a good
idea if she likes you.
Okay, l'm going to do it.
Oh no...
How you girls doing?
Hey Nick.
PerFect plan down the drain.
Mark.
Yes.
Telephone.
Be right there
Hello.
Hey Mark.
Hey Dust.
Hey, let me ask your
opinion on something.
Think l should write
Tanya another note?
Another note?
Yeah, she hasn't
gotten back to me yet?
l don't want to call her.
l could ask her
about the first one.
You really like her, don't ya?
Yes, l really like her.
And l'm not afraid to say it.
So what do you
think l should do.
l don't know.
Oh, let me see
what Albert thinks.
And that was the
Big Tops
on W.A.L.B. radio.
Next up we have a
classic from 1953,
but first we have the weather.
Sunny today with a few scattered
clouds and only a ten percent
chance of.. Albert.
Yeah.
Telephone.
Hello.
Albert.
Dustin.
Hey Dustin.
Do you think l should
write Tanya another note?
What for?
Because she hasn't
answered my first one.
l wouldn't.
Why not?
Because Nick likes her.
But she doesn't like him.
You don't know that.
Yes l do.
How do you know?
You're love blind.
l am not love blind, l
just like herthat's all.
Then you're like blind.
Like blind, there's
no such thing.
You're not helping.
l am too.
Goodbye Albert.
What did he say?
He says he thinks it's
a mistake cause of Nick.
What does Albert know,
he's so immature.
l think l shouldjust
write her another note.
Wait, a second let's
think this through.
You said in the first note that
you were going to come back and
see her at the diner
for an answer right?
Yeah and l did.
But she doesn't knowthat
because she was gone.
Yeah, but what about today?
She had to notice us.
Yeah, but maybe there were too
many people there and she didn't
want to say anything.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
lf l were you, l'd go back down
to the dinertomorrow by myself
and tyto talk to her.
Okay, l will.
Excuse me, ma'am, where's Tanya?
Oh, Tanya and her familyjust
Ieft today for a vacation.
Vacation?
Well, ahh...Do you know how
Iong they're going to be gone?
l think they'll be gone
for at least three weeks.
Three weeks?
Can l help you with anything?
Um, No, no thank you.
Okay.
Three weeks is a long time.
l wonder where they're going?
l don't know.
Her Dad probably makes lots of
money so he can afford the trip.
Yeah.
l think you shouldjust
forget the whole thing.
Why?
Because of one word, Nick
l already told you she
doesn't like him.
Dustin's right, Tanya
doesn't like Nick.
You don't know that.
And she might end up liking me.
Yeah, she might end
up liking Dustin.
Okay, Why are you repeating
eveything he says.
Because it seems that you need
to hear eveything twice so that
it sinks in that skull ofyours.
l know l wouldn't want to be
liking the same girl that Nick
likes that's for sure.
Don't listen to him Dustin.
l'm not.
Fine, don't listen to
me, it's your funeral.
Dustin.
Dinner's ready.
Okay, coming down.
Where you going there Dustin?
Hi Nick.
Roy.
l said: where you going?
Going to visit a friend.
What's that ya got there?
lt'sjust a book.
What book?
lt's a Bible.
A Bible?
Yeah, l'm going to Bible study.
ln the afternoon.
What's this guy going
to do, become a priest?
Well, see you guys later.
Wait a minute.
l didn't sayyou could go yet.
Come on Nick, l gotta go.
Let me see that book first.
Come on, l'll be late.
Let me see the book.
Nick, come on.
l want to see this book
l need the book back.
l gotta go.
Nice book.
Here...Oh...
Oops...Sory.
Okay.
Nowyou can go.
Sory l'm late.
You know l always keep an extra
copy ofthe Bible in case of
emergencies like this.
You know, many men have attacked
this book in order to keep
people from reading it.
You see, l'm almost glad that
this incident occurred today.
Because it will not be easyfor
you to followthe LORD and there
will be many tying times
ahead as you live your lives.
But remember, the Lord
is always with you.
Here you go, your own new
copy ofthe Word of God.
l can't take this
Bible from you.
lt's yours.
No, my friend.
This is yours.
Just agree with me you'll
put it to good use.
Thank you Mr. Spery.
l will.
Yes.
Mr. Barnes?
You again.
Sory to bother you, sir.
But l noticed your grass is a
little higher now and l still
want to mow it if
you don't mind.
l don't need no one to
help me mow my lawn.
But l said l would
do it forfree.
What is your name?
Dustin.
Dustin Sharp.
Who's having you do this?
Well...
Who?
l can't say.
Was it your mother?
No sir.
Your father?
No sir, l don't have afather.
What happened to your father?
He died before l was born.
Oh.
Then who's having you do this?
l brought my mower.
lt's real good, take a look.
l'm not going to let you mow my
Iawn unless you tell me who put
you up to this.
l'll do a goodjob, you'll see.
Nowyou listen to me.
Thanks Mr. Barnes.
Come on get it. Woah...
Double ball.
Nice.
Come on get it.
Come on Albert keep it going.
You're racking up
all those points.
Oh get it Hit it hit it.
l'm tying.
Come on Albert.
Keep it going you may
beat your high score.
l got a chance.
Get it, get it.
l got it.
Come on get in.
Okay, it's myturn to play.
One minute, l'm playing.
lt's myturn to play.
Come on Nick, let
him finish his game.
l said It's myturn to play.
Hold on, l'm about to
beat my high score.
l don't care what your
score is, Alberta.
You're done.
Just let me finish Unless you
want to make something of it.
No, l guess l'm done.
He bosses people around and
picks on whoever he wants.
Yeah, and then you can be
playing pin ball and he
just come and move you right out
ofthe way and starts playing on
your money.
And he's always
taking our pizza.
l just wish someone
could knock him.
l can't stand him.
Nick ruins it for eveybody
Mr. pery, not just for us.
l see.
Excuse me.
lf you boys will,
please follow me.
l have something l'd
like to showyou.
Look around gentlemen
take in this scene.
l come here often.
Yes, look around.
This is an important place to
visit while you are still alive.
And to listen.
But l don't hear anything.
l don't either.
Well, the Bible says in the book
of Ecclesiastes it's betterto
go to a house of mourning
than to a house offeasting.
And why?
Because death is the end of
evey man and the living will
take it to heart.
You see it makes us
think about our own life
death and eternity.
That's why l come here.
Alright, listen.
l don't hear anything.
Alright stand closer
to the tombstones.
And listen vey carefully now.
But l'm still not
hearing anything.
Put your earto the stone.
Why....why didn't you
tell me about Jesus?
Why, why didn't you tell me l
needed the Lord in my life to go
to heaven.
Keep Listening.
l am in agony in this place.
Think of eveyone you love
gentlemen, eveyone you know.
Even people you may dislike.
And realize this.
One day, evey person will die.
They'll either go to
heaven or sadly...to hell.
There's no in between.
No second chance.
And no one can escape this fate.
Now as for Nick, the thought
that comes to mind are the words
of Jesus.
Love your enemies, bless
them that curse you,
do good to them that hate you.
And in Matthew chapter
5 the Lord says,
if a man strikes your right
cheek, offer him the other side.
And if a man compels you to
drive a mile, go with him two.
What's all that suppose
to mean Mr. Spery?
lf your enemy takes a piece
of your pizza, offer him two.
Hi Mr. Barnes.
What do you want?
ljust wanted to stop by
to see howyou are doing.
How l'm doing?
Yes sir.
You tying to make me feel
guiltyfor not paying you?
No sir.
l just wanted to
stop by and say hi.
And who's the one
having you mow my lawn.
l had fun mowing it.
l'm going to find out who it is.
Do you knowwho
Jesus is Mr. Barnes?
What kind of a question is that?
ljust want to make sure you
go to heaven when you die.
You don't wory about me.
l started reading
my Bible Evey day.
ln the gospel ofJohn that's
where you can read about what
Jesus says.
l'm going back inside.
Well, okay, ahh it was good
talking to you Mr. Barnes and
see you again soon, when
your lawn needs mowing.
You have to put some
weight in the cup dummy.
-Weight?
-Like a rock or something.
You gotta get it to go under.
lt was a little scay in
the cemeteyyesterday.
Yeah, l know.
lt Gave me the creeps.
Mr. Spery sure does know
a lot about the Bible.
And he's been real nice to us.
We should do something for him.
Like what?
l don't know, something.
We could buy him a present.
Yeah, but l don't
have vey much money.
He's probably got eveything.
lt would be nice to do
something for him though.
Yeah, l know, he's
always giving us food.
Wait.
l got an idea.
l want to thank you gentlemen
for this nice treat.
lt was a pleasant surprise.
Your welcome, Mr. Spery.
We figured we had to payyou
back for all that chocolate cake
and ice cream that you give us.
And don't forget the lemonade.
You do not have to pay me back.
lt's been my pleasure.
But this pizza is a
vey nice gesture.
Thank you my friends.
We eat pizza here a lot.
You know, When l was young, we
never had a place like this.
We used to walk downtown and
just stand on the corner.
Oh no, look whojust walked in.
lt's Nick.
Nick.
Better hide the pizza.
That's the bully we've
been telling you about.
l see.
He looks familiar to me.
l wish he was on another planet.
Tell me
Hey Nick, look at that
old man overthere.
Well, who do we got here.
Hi Nick.
So Dustin, who's the old timer?
This is our good
friend, Mr. Spery.
Mr. Sparrow, ah isn't
that the name of a bird?
(his buddy laughs)
No, it's Mr. Spery.
Well, isn't it past
your nap time gramps?
'Cause l heard that all old
people took afternoon naps.
Come on Nick, leave him alone.
He's our friend.
Hey, l amjust looking
after gramps' health,
make sure he gets his rest.
Okayjust leave him alone.
l'll talk to whoever l want to.
But he's a nice man
and he's ourfriend.
l said l'll talk to
whoever l want to.
Got it?
Your Nick Meyers right?
Yeah, what's it to you?
Victor Meyer's son?
Yeah, so what.
l want you to knowyou can be
vey proud ofyourfather.
Proud?
What makes you saythat?
Well, we use to work together
on a church committee.
And l got to know him veywell.
He was a godly man did a lot
of good forthis community.
l know he passed awaywhen you
were quite young so ifyou would
ever like to hear more
about yourfather,
feel free to drop by
my home for a visit.
He was a wonderFul man.
You can be proud of him son.
Vey proud.
Come on Roy.
Wow, that was great Mr. Spery.
Yeah, you shut Nick up without
even to have to fight him.
No gentlemen, this is
no time for rejoicing.
But Nick's a bigjerk
like that all the time.
l don't want to make
an excuse for him,
but Nick has had a vey
difficult upbringing and he's
hurting inside.
So tonight, when you go home,
prayfor Nick and ask the Lord
to help him.
Lord, Mr. Spery asked
us to pray for Nick.
l don't reallythink he
wants to be mean like he is,
but ifyou could help
him...Thank you.
Amen.
A couple years
after you were born,
your father came to a revival
service at a church l was
attending.
And During that service, he came
to realize that he was a sinner
like all of us, and he needed
forgiveness forthose sins.
So he prayed and he accepted
Jesus as His Lord and Savior.
He was born again.
You might not know
what that means Nick,
but it's a spiritual birth
in the Christian faith.
A lot of people thought it
just afad with yourfather,
but it wasn't, it was real.
And His life changed
dramatically.
You know what your father did?
He went to all the people
he wronged and asked for
forgiveness and then he did
eveything he could to make
things right.
lt was marvelous to see.
But, sadly, your Mom couldn't
accept his passion for God and
she left ayear laterwhen
you were about 4years old.
But He became a good man
Nick, a really good man.
My mother didn't think he was.
Well, That's because she didn't
Accept his Christianity and it
came between them.
Now l know it was tougher on you
growing up than most young men.
But son, that's no
excuse foryour behavior.
lf you're father
were still here,
l'm sure things would be a lot
different foryou right now.
Yeah, what makes you saythat?
Because you wouldn't have to go
around and act like a bully to
get attention.
You would have had your father
here to give you the proper
attention.
l'm sure of it.
And that's what l think
is really bothering you.
Your mother works all the time.
She's tired, l'm sure she's
cross with you at times you live
in the same house but she goes
herway and you go yours.
So you think you got
me all figured Out?
l may be old Nick but my
eyesight is still pretty good
and l can see a hurting heart.
The Lord Jesus is
here foryou, Nick,
just like He was
foryourfather.
Just call out to Him.
You know the path you're
on is the wrong one.
l shouldn't have ever come here.
Nick,
my door is
always open to you.
Always.
Can l talk to you
for another minute?
Sure.
What did you mean by
''Call out to him''?
Well, it's Really, quite simple.
Just talk to him.
He's always there.
HAH!
What did you do that for?
l could have got hurt.
What do you mean?
You're suppose to ride on
the other side ofthe road.
l am not.
You could have ruined my mower.
You do have a pretty nice mower.
What's this thing?
lt's my gas cap, l need that.
Yeah, you're going to have
to come and take it from me.
Come on, give it back.
lt's right here. awww,
it's over there.
Come on guys.
Got it right here.
Give it back.
Come on Benny.
Come on, give it.
Ah, come on Roy.
Come on Roy.
Give it.
You're going to have to
come and take it from me.
Come on give it to me.
You're not going
to get it that way.
l don't want to fight you.
So, what are you
going about it, huh?
Give me the cap.
l said, what are you
going to do about it,
huh? Huh?
Give it back.
Give him the cap.
Oh hey Nick, we've
been waiting forYou.
Dustin here has been
giving us a hard time.
Give him the cap, Roy.
No way, it's my cap.
Give him the cap Roy.
What do you mean, Nick?
You do this stuff all the time.
Like l said, you're going to
have to come and
take it from me.
Roy.
l said give him the cap.
Okay Nick, l was
just playing around.
(to Dustin) Here's
your stupid cap.
(to the other buddy)
Come on, Benny, let's go.
You coming Nick?
No.
l got something l gotta do.
Nick,
thanks.
Father in heaven, l come to
you now on behalf of Nick.
God...Jesus....
l don't knowwhat
to say....
Draw Nick closer
to you, Lord.
l Knowyou love himjust the way
you loved his father
many yealS a90.
l'm soryforthe way l am.
l'm soryforthe way l treated
Mr. Spery
and for picking on those
kids at school...
l just,
l just wish l could be normal.
ljust wish l could change.
He needs you Lord,
like we all need you.
Keep your arms around
him and guide him...
Lary, come with me.
Me?
Come with me.
Anything wrong Nick?
Oh, you want someone
to cheer you on.
We can do that.
Come on Tyler.
No.
You play.
Huh?
Have fun.
Okay, honey.
l'm offto work.
Okay.
Do you have to
Iawns to mowtoday?
Yeah one.
And then we go to Mr. Spery's.
Alright gentlemen, l want you to
stand right here by that tree
and l'm going take this
five-dollar bill and place it
right over here on this table.
Would you like to have this
five dollar bill?
l bet you could buy a
pretty good pizzawith it.
Probably an extra large.
l knewyou'd be the
first to answer him.
But, you're going to have to
work together in orderto get
the money.
Now one ofyou must be touching
that tree at all times and the
three ofyou must be holding
onto each other at all times and
ifyou can touch this
bill, then it's yours.
You can do with it as you wish.
But.
lf you can't, then
it remains mine.
ls that clear?
Clear.
Alright.
So we can never let
go of each other.
That's right, you must be
connected to each other at all
times.
So now, we readyto ty?
Alright come on
guys, we can do this.
Okay, strategy.
Mark, you hold onto the tree.
Albert, you go next.
Okay come on.
Stretch!
Come on, get it.
Okay, come on Dustin, stretch.
l'm stretching.
Got to get wider legs.
Come on Dustin, Stretch.
l can't reach it.
lt's too far.
lt's impossible.
No, it is possible.
l can't do it.
Let me tythen.
Come on Albert.
l can't reach it.
lt's too far.
Come on Albert.
lt's impossible.
Mr. Spery, we need your help.
No, There is away.
Come on, keep stretching
he says there is a way.
l'm tying, it's too far.
Come on Albert, stretch.
lt's too far.
l can help.
Nick?
What are you doing here?
l asked him to stop by.
You, Mr. Spery.
Yes, l did.
But why?
l think Nick has something
here to tell you.
Albert, Dustin, Mark, l came
here to see Mr. Spery a couple
of days ago and we talked.
He talked about how my
father became a Christian.
Then, l went home and l thought
about it and, l prayed.
l prayed to Jesus.
l'm soryforthe way
l treated you guys.
l know l've been ajerk.
But, ifyou will
give me a chance,
l think that we
could be friends.
lf you would just
give me a chance.
l know Nick has hurt the
three ofyou in the past.
But, if he is truly
come to Christ,
then the Lord has forgiven him
just like he has
forgiven you and l.
The Bible says if a man be in
Christ, he is a new creation.
Old things have passed away,
all things have become new.
This is the new Nick
We understand.
And if you are still interested
in that five dollar bill,
there's one more person
here to help so perhaps now,
there is away.
Alright guys, let's
go for it again.
Nick, we need your help.
Mark, grab onto the tree.
Me, Albert then Nick.
Alright guys let's stretch.
Come on.
Let's go.
Come on guys.
A little more.
Come on Nick.
Fingertips...fingertips.
Come on Nick, you can do it.
Almost there.
Come on guys.
l can't stretch any further.
l'm tying.
A little more.
l got it!
l got it.
Yeah Good job guys.
Nowwe can buythat
extra large pizza.
lt's going to be good.
lt's gonna be tasty.
Now, You don't need
to do that no more.
l can do my own lawn now.
Turn that off.
Hi Mr. Barnes.
What did you say sir?
l said turn that thing off.
Oh don't wory, it
won't take me long.
l'll do a goodjob.
And l want you to tell me once
and for all
who put you up to this.
l hope you started reading
your Bible Mr. Barnes.
lfyou give it a chance,
l think you'll like it.
Nowyou listen to me.
Thanks for letting me
mow your lawn Mr. Barnes.
Hello?
Tanya's back.
She is?
ljust saw her.
l went with my Mom to the
grocey store and she was there.
She didn't see me though.
Okay.
Are you still going
to ty to ask her out?
Yeah, l want to.
She'll probably be working the
Iunch time shift tomorrow.
Yeah, okay.
Thanks for telling me.
Hey Dustin.
Hi Tanya.
What can l get foryou?
Get?
Oh um.
How was your vacation?
lt was good, wejust
got back yesterday.
So it was fun?
Yeah, we had a nice time.
That's good.
Vacations are normally good.
Did you want to order something?
No, not really.
l had written you a note and
l am here to get my answer.
Your answer?
Yeah, to the question l had
written you in the note.
What note?
l had written you a note before
you left on your vacation.
No, l never got a note from you.
Are you sure, yeah
It was the day
Me, Mark and Albert...we
ordered sundaes from you.
l left it right over
there on the table.
You didn't get it?
l never saw it.
What did the note say?
lt said?
l was gonna...
Never mind.
Maybe l'll just write
you another one.
ls there something
you want to tell me?
Ahh,
l'd rather put
it in a note form.
Okay.
See ya.
So, as l was saying.
The next daythe guy l had met
came back down to the beach but
this time he brought
his freshman friend,
the one that was with him
the day before that saw me,
but l never saw him.
So she never got it?
That's what she said.
Well, that will
explain some things.
Yep.
You should have just
asked her right then.
You know l was going
to but Cindywas there.
Was she nice?
Yes, she was pretty nice.
That's a good sign.
Maybe she doesn't like Nick.
What are you going to do?
l think l'm probably going
to write her another note.
Why don't you just ask her.
l already told her.
She's probably going to be
at the pizzeria tomorrow.
l'll drop it offto her after
we're done with Mr. Spery.
l don't want to bother
her at the diner again.
You're going to give it to
her in front of eveyone.
Yep.
You got guts.
Dear Tanya.
l think you are a vey
nice girl...
Dear Tanya...
The Scripture says the tongue is
a fire full of deadly poison.
lt's one of the smallest
parts of the body,
but it can do the most
good orthe most harm.
So be careful what you say.
Use your words to bless people,
not to criticize
or gossip about them.
lt's easyto put people
down, anyone can do that.
But, you, be different,
stand up with your kindness,
showthe love ofJesus in
eveything you say, or,
in some cases,
what you don't say.
Okay my friends.
(the boys react) Let's
close in a word of prayer.
Then he left his
rainbowteddy-bear...
Now remember gentlemen, our hot
dog cookout is scheduled for
Friday at five.
l've ordered 4 dogs for each of
one you so please
bring your appetites.
Alright boys,
Bye-bye.
See you there.
l won't eat lunch on Friday.
Don't you dare do it...
Dustin, are you going down
there and give Tanya the note?
Yeah, planning on it but first l
going to go home and
drop off my Bible.
Okaywe will too and then
we'll meet you there.
Okaywhen you guys get to the
pizza place save us atable.
l'll get there as soon as l can.
Alright.
Hi Tanya.
Hi Sally Hi.
Hey guys.
We're just here
waiting for Dustin.
He's on his wayto
talk to you Tanya.
Talk to me?
Yeah, he's going to ask you out.
Albert.
l didn't mean to
tell you that part.
You got such a big mouth.
l'm sory.
And Mr. Spery was just
saying to watch what you say.
l'm sory.
Howyou going to turn him down?
l don't know.
Stop you're making me
all pressured and stuff.
Ha Ha Ha.
Stop.
Hey guys, sory l'm late.
Hey Dust.
Well, she's here.
This is my chance.
Ahhh, Dustin.
Here goes nothing.
Dustin. Wait.
Hi Tanya.
Hi.
can l talk to you for a minute?
Umm?
Sure.
Tanya, l want you to know l
think you're a vey nice girl
and l've been thinking
a lot about you.
Look, Dustin.
So, l wrote you this note it
expresses myfeelings better
'cause l've never really
done anything like this.
l hope you at least read it.
Thanks.
Come on guys.
Let's go.
Let me see what he wrote.
Hey give me that.
lt's my note.
But l want to see it.
He wrote it to me.
Let me see what it says.
l'm going to read it first.
Ahh, come on.
Oh alright.
l'll read it to you.
Dear Tanya.
l think you're a vey nice girl
(we hear herfriend laughing)
l also think you are cool.
l want you to knowthat
something great
has happened in my life.
l started reading my Bible
eveyday
and praying to the Lord.
l've come to realize that l need
Jesus in my life especially if l
want to go to heaven.
So l just wanted to encourage
you to start reading your Bible,
in the gospel ofJohn.
l think it will help you too.
Well, that's all for now.
Your friend, Dustin.
PS, l am mowing lawns this
summer so ifyou don't have a
Bible, l'll be glad
to buyyou one.
Okay Mrs. Farley.
Yeah l'll be right over.
Bye.
Mom.
That was Mrs.
Farley on the phone.
l'm going to go over right now
and help her clean out
her attic.
She's going to pay me.
Okay, honey.
Then l'm going to
go overAlbert's.
Have fun.
Jonathan Spery was a
God-fearing man, who loved life,
who loved his family,
who loved people.
But most of all, we knowthat
Jonathan loved the Lord and
touched all of us in some way
with the love that he had for
Jesus.
Jonathan would tell us not
to weep for him today but to
rejoice, because he is now in
the presence of his Heavenly
Father.
l know it's hard for us because
we miss our dearfriend.
But if Jonathan were still here,
l am sure that he would tell us
to live on for Christ
and most of all,
to tell others what Jesus
did for them on the cross at
Calvay.
(beat) And now dear Jonathan,
as we lay your body to rest,
we believe that Jesus has
ushered you into heaven by His
saving grace, and may your
memoy continue to speak to our
hearts as we continue
on our earthlyjourney.
The Lord be with us all.
We need to go honey.
Dustin, please tyto eat
something, you'll feel better.
No, l won't.
l knowthis has been hard for
you the past few days but you
have to start moving forward
again with your life.
l'm not hungy, may
l please be excused.
Dustin, there's someone
here to see you.
l don't want to see anybody.
lt's Mr. Barnes.
Mr. Barnes.
l'm soryto bother
the both ofyou.
lt's no bother Mr. Barnes,
please come in, sit down.
Let me get you
something to drink.
No, this will be fine,
It'lljust take a minute.
Dustin, l want to ask if
you will still mow my lawn,
l will payyou from now on.
You don't have to
pay me Mr. Barnes.
l enjoy mowing your
Iawn and talking to you.
l know it was Mr. Spery
who put you up to this.
And l can't let you mow my lawn
anymore unless you let me pay
you, are we in agreement?
You don't have to Mr. Barnes.
Are we in agreement?
Yes sir.
Fine, that's settled.
Now, l knowyou are feeling
sad about Mr. pery and all.
we all are.
(beat) Ifthere was ever a
Christian man in this town,
it was Jonathan Spery.
(beat) So, you come mow my lawn
next week ifyou feeling ready.
Yes sir, l'll be there.
Oh, l thought you
might like to know.
l been reading my Bible.
Just like you said,
Gospel of John.
Reading all about Jesus.
That's great Mr. Barnes.
You got a nice boythere ma'am.
nice boy.
Now you keep talking about
Jesus you hear Dustin.
(beat) Some folks out there
just might be listening.
l will.
Thank you all.
Good evening.
Can you believe that Mom?
Mr. Barnes started
reading his Bible.
Yes, isn't that wonderFul.
ln the Gospel ofJohn.
And it's because of you.
l can't believe it.
Mr. Barnes.
Yes, that is surprising.
What's wrong?
Oh nothing.
No, what's wrong.
Aren't you happy Mr. Barnes is
starting to read his Bible?
Yes, honey, that's
wonderFul like l said.
Then, what is it?
Dustin, did Mr. Spery ever
tell you how his wife died.
Yeah, she died in
a car accident.
But did he evertell
you how it happened?
No hejust said that it
happened fouryears ago.
Dustin,
that accident
was caused by Mr. Barnes.
He had been drinking and he
was the one driving
the other vehicle.
Mr. Barnes caused that accident.
Yes.
And Mr. Spery paid
me to mow his lawn.
Yes.
Dustin.
Always remember, the
Bible is your friend.
And so am l.
Keep living for Jesus.
Jonathan Spery.
Hello.
Mark.
Dustin.
We need to have a Bible study.
A Bible study?
Yeah.
Like the ones we
had with Mr. Spery.
When?
As soon as possible.
You call Albert, l'll call Nick.
We'll get them to call
the rest ofthe guys.
We'll meet at my house tomorrow
afternoon at 2:OO o'clock.
But who's going to lead it?
Guys, l'd like to
thank you for coming.
lf you would please follow me,
there's something
l'd to showyou.
Look around guys
and don't be afraid.
This is an important place to
visit while you're still alive.
And listen.
l don't hear anything.
Neither do l.
The Bible says it is betterto
go to afuneral than afeast.
You know why?
'Cause eveybody dies one day
and when you go to a funeral you
think about it more.
Lean closer to the tombstones.
Closer.
And listen.
Really listen.