Well, let's go see
If we can find any cars.
Hot rod hunter richard rawlings.
And master mechanic
Aaron kaufman.
Get all hot and bothered...
When a 1980 el camino arrives.
At the shop to shake things up.
Earthquake test!
And aaron gambles
To monkey it up in record time.
It's a bet! -This one
will be Blistering fast.
What's over The wall, aaron?
But as richard
Stumbles onto buried treasure...
Holy cow.
And considers an epic gamble
Of his own...
I could just buy
The whole thing, all of it.
The elco build tumbles
Head-first into trouble.
- Nothing lines up.
- Richard's gonna be pissed.
It's a week
Where all bets are off.
Here goes nothing.
Will all this monkey business
Lift the crew's spirits.
To new heights...
Yes!
Or leave them crying...
Come on!
We got to make money, dude.
In the dark?
Good lord.
You have the world's largest
Poison ivy farm in dallas.
No, I don't.
Captions paid for by
Discovery communications
I thought Texas was sizzling,
But phoenix is brutal.
100, 115 is hot.
So, we came out
To phoenix today,
Which is just one
Of my favorite places.
But it's, like, 187 degrees.
And it's miserable hot.
I mean... Horrible.
Well, at least I'm in here
And not out there.
This is pretty good.
I must be moving up
In the world.
I get to get chauffeured around
Now to go buy cars.
Monkey chauffeur.
The only reason
We're enduring this heat.
Is that I was poking around
On the internet the other day.
And clicked on a particular
Vehicle for sale.
That both aaron and I
Have been wanting to build.
For a long time.
Is that right here?
This cream puff sitting outside.
- God, look at that thing.
- That with those wire hubcaps.
- I got dibs on those.
- That is what I'm talking about.
Kickass.
I love it! Man.
El camino!
Sit tight, america!
In just seconds,
We're going to show you.
A truck we think
Is truly amazing...
The 1980 chevy el camino.
Since they first
Popped on the scene in 1959,
Americans have both loved
And laughed at chevy el caminos.
Chevy called it a truck.
But it was actually based
On a station wagon wheelbase.
So it's a little bit of both
Or some of neither.
My parents Actually had a 1980.
But by then,
They were much smaller,
Much more square and much
Less brawn under the hood.
They're kind of weird,
But I've kind of got.
A, you know, soft spot
In my heart for them.
Pretty slick.
If this one's in good shape,
It could be a lot of fun
To play around.
What's up, guys?
- Hey, sir.
- What's going on, man?
Richard rawlings. Calvin.
- Calvin, how you doing?
- Pleasure.
Aaron. Nice to meet you.
How you doing? I'm charles.
Pleasure to meet you.
Hey, nice to meet you.
So, Your dad Bought this new?
Brand new. Right off the lot.
- Rad!
- 1980, portland, oregon.
When he passed away 9 years ago,
I took possession of it.
And it's been here in phoenix,
Arizona, ever since.
That's o.G. Right there.
What is this, velvet?
At first glance, it seemed to be
In pretty good shape,
Especially considering
It's over 35 years old.
But we did know Going into it.
That it had
An older repaint on it.
One thing that I'm
Always leery of.
Is, like, a cheap paint job
Maybe hiding.
A lot of damage or bondo.
Was there any body damage
When it got painted.
Or did it just get Baked off?
No, it just got baked off.
Open the hood.
What motor's in it?
It's probably hot.
This, here, is a 305.
So that's probably
A whopping 182 horsepower in it.
On the day it was born,
Definitely ain't that now.
- I would say more like 80.
- Can I take it for a test drive?
Sure.
Daggone. The key's hot.
Wait for me.
Did I mention
It's about 187 degrees?
Miserable hot.
Well, obviously, we're
Gonna have to fix that problem.
Yeah, it's really, like,
More of a cruiser.
Look at that power! Not!
Cruising in the el camino!
Traffic circle
Coming up, want to do it?
Yeah! Let her rip, Tater chip!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Come on! Come on!
I tried to do a burnout,
Slinging around the corner.
Go...
Not happening.
Those '14s, they were
Sticking to the ground.
Probably 'cause it's
So damn hot here.
It's fricking, like,
187 degrees right now.
Come on. Come on.
Yeah, yeah!
I think That's about all it had.
That definitely failed
The richard-burnout test.
I don't care. I've always
Loved these g-bodies.
Charles is right.
The cool thing about these cars.
Is they're built on
The same g-body platform.
As the chevy sedans, like
The malibu and the monte carlo,
Which means there's a ton
Of after-market parts for them.
It's rad!
You can't go wrong
With a car like this.
Awesome, man! Well...
I guess it is
What you said it is.
So... How much You want for it?
I'd like $10,000
For it, richard.
I think she...
I think she's worth it.
Good god, man. $10,000.
$10,000?
I would like to sell
One of these for $10,000.
So, no surprise, he throws out
A pretty big number.
For a car like this,
Even in good condition.
So 10? I'm not going there.
I know, And this is broken.
Yep.
You know, hit me
With a price, richard.
- What are you thinking?
- I was thinking about $6,500.
$6,500?
- $6,500.
- I can't do it, man.
How about 9, richard?
Yeah, you're getting there,
But I'm thinking 7.
Still a little low.
- It's so damn hot here.
- I can't even think.
- Let's get it over with.
- What is it, like, 187 degrees?
Let's just shake on $8,000.
$8,000?
All right,
We're shaking. We own it.
I like your style.
Eight grand, I think,
Is fair for the car.
I would have liked to have
Gotten it a little bit cheaper.
But it's a good car
To start with.
Yank out that anemic motor.
And throw something
Big and badass in,
Scare women and children,
We're good to go.
Let's do some paperwork.
You got cold beer in the fridge?
Right this way.
Hey, I think
You're gonna have to pass.
You got a long way to get
That thing back to dallas.
Hope you got Your "Aaa" card.
Really like this car.
Growing up, man,
It was one of the cars.
That I always wanted to build.
I'ma put my own little touch
On it on the way home.
The el camino
Is now the el cimino.
- You got to be kidding me.
- No a.C.?
Aah!
1,000 miles with no a.C.
In the summer!
You all right? Sweet!
You made it back From arizona?
Man, I would have
Had the windows down.
- That window doesn't work!
- You want some water?
Yeah.
Well, here.
Have some.
Well, you need
To get up and work now.
You already did the easy part.
You drove here.
I mean, you give a guy
What amounts to, practically,
A paid vacation driving through.
The uncharted pass
Of our great country.
And what do you get?
Just complain,
Complain, complain.
Wow, it's really
Starting to come down out there.
Who cares about that?
I want to know what you think
About my el cimino.
An el cimino,
What does that mean?
Is that, like,
A different model?
It's charles cimino.
- Gotcha.
- No.
I don't know.
El caminos are, like,
Kind of a weird thing.
Somebody has an el camino,
You're not real sure about it.
It's like people who own vans
With no windows.
It's kind of a different
Type of person, right?
I'm not really big
On el caminos.
I've never restored
Or rebuilt one.
But it's kind of a cool car.
It's clean.
Earthquake test.
Whoa.
Suspension needs A little work.
That doesn't sound Super well.
Well, the motor's
Definitely nothing
I'd write home about.
Yeah, it's pretty
Much worthless.
It's hot an awful lot
Of shiny stuff on it.
So what are we Gonna do with it?
Charles wants to name it
El cimino and take it home.
I want to paint it
Like a low rider.
I just don't want it.
What about you, sir?
I want to see it go fast.
Heck yeah. Gas monkey it up.
So, what are we
Gonna do with it?
Let me ask you
A crazy question...
What do we do With all of them?
Make them cool.
So here's the plan.
For our little shady
'80 el camino.
Basically,
It's not really a car.
And it's not really a truck.
But what we're gonna do
Is make it so sexy and so fast,
It will stick a smile
On your face.
And keep it plastered there
For a long, long time.
The first step will be
To lower the altitude.
And raise the performance,
Which will yield a ton
More attitude.
We will slam it down
And motivate it.
With a mass black label
Ls3 engine.
Coupled to a t56,
It should produce
About 630 horsepower.
Once we increase the rubber
Presence substantially,
Add some big brakes
To stop all that power.
And update the gauges
And upholstery,
This car will have
A new lease on life.
And we don't want To mess around.
With the classic el camino look,
Or why start with
An el camino at all?
And since it's black,
We're gonna keep it black.
Now, mike, I know
That's a lot of work for you.
But too bad.
But we are going to
Remove a lot of the bright work.
And then narrow and tuck
Those big, wide bumpers.
To clean up the lines.
The great thing is,
Is since it's a g-body,
It's on a gm platform,
Which means all the parts for it
Should be fairly easy to get.
So I told aaron
I would give him 4 weeks.
And $30,000 to get it done.
And you know what he said?
Four weeks?
I will do you one better.
I bet I can even have
This thing done in three.
Three weeks? I mean, only
A sucker would pass up that bet.
If you ask aaron
What time it is,
He's gonna tell you
How to build a watch.
So, I don't know how
He's gonna finish a project.
Like this in 3 weeks
To his satisfaction.
A g-body? Three weeks?
It's entirely doable.
I just don't see that much that
Could go wrong with this one.
This one will be
Blistering fast.
It's a bet!
I guess we can't
Play outside today.
We might as well start
Tearing this thing apart.
Hey, who needs another motor
Since we're taking this one out?
- Whoa!
- Good lord.
What the hell.
Yeah.
Coming up... I want to rack it.
Aaron's need for speed.
Hits the skids from the start.
I think I want to play
Around with those bumpers.
Knew it was Too good to be true.
So you got Some cars in here.
And tricky ricky goes big...
Wow... Real big.
I will pay you $500,000.
Well, we've got
Blue skies, power.
Let's get this show On the road.
Body seems pretty...
I don't think our job's
Gonna be too bad.
Hope not.
Well, at least it
Doesn't look that rusty.
Well, cool.
We will make it look good.
Y'all make it run good.
It will be fast.
That's all that matters.
All right. I want to rack it.
Yeah. Let's
Just pull it forward.
So our humble goal
For this 1980 el camino.
Is to lower the altitude,
Beef up the performance.
And, thereby, gave it
A much meaner attitude.
That lowered it, Like, 3 inches.
- Shut up.
- Yeah, it did.
With a plethora
Of after-market parts available.
For this g-body frame,
I'm willing to bet
We can finish this thing.
In a quick 3 weeks.
And I'm willing
To bet that, you know,
His mind starts
Going on this thing.
And swirls around
Out of control,
And he finds a way
To stretch this out.
You know... you know
What I'm talking about, guys.
Aaron's definitely not
Playing around this time.
We are off to a fast start.
We already have parts
Coming in for this thing,
And we don't even
Have it torn down yet.
- Already ready.
- And miracle of miracles,
He's even talking
About moving it over.
To paint and body
Right away, like, today.
So tony and I can have
Adequate time, for once,
To finally pull off
The flawless paint job.
That this garage is known for.
All right, soon as
Those bumpers are off,
Give me a shout,
And we will go ahead.
And roll it over To my place.
You know what?
Let's hold off For a few hours.
I think I want to play around
With those bumpers.
Before the new ones Come in.
I knew it was
Too good to be true.
Don't get your panties
In a bunch, mike.
This won't take too long.
You want to sit up first?
Here's the deal
I hate the rubber trim
On the factory bumpers,
Which is not really a problem
Because john's already found.
Replacement bumpers
That don't have all that mess.
But I am planning on doing
Some cutting and splicing.
On the new ones.
They're bigger
Than truck bumpers.
And they hang off on the ends.
So, I actually wanted
To make them narrower.
So they fit the car
Much tighter.
I'm thinking instead of rushing
This thing on into paint,
Why not take a few hours.
And use the old bumpers
As guinea pigs.
To try and figure out
What's gonna work best?
So, what I might do is
Find the last place.
That we can make
A clean cut here,
Go ahead and...
And make that cut.
And then, we will start
Working the chunk out here.
And start moving it over.
It's simple math.
Spend a little bit of time now,
Save a lot of time
Down the line.
Yeah.
Get out here, aaron.
Time and richard rawlings
Wait for no man.
Thank you.
All right,
I put a fresh shirt on for this.
It better be worth it.
Where are we headed?
Hold on.
So this, Guy just called me.
And, he said, I guess,
His family member died.
And there's a bunch
Of cars on the property.
So the rest of
The family's out of state.
They just want to sell the cars
So that they can sell the house.
So any time you hear about
An estate sale,
You can't help
But get your hopes up.
That there's A one-of-a-kind car.
That's been hidden away
In a garage for years.
Just ripe for the picking.
I said, "Where are you?"
Lakewood.
I said, "Well, dude,
What's the address?"
We will come over."
And this estate Is in, well,
A pretty prominent
Neighborhood in dallas.
So, I'm feeling lucky.
Who knows what
We're gonna find here?
Here we go.
Looks a little overgrown.
Absolute pile of doo-doo.
That must be The family's agent.
You steve? Yes, sir.
Richard rawlings.
How's it going, man?
Doing well, man. Cool.
Steve. Aaron.
- Nice to meet you, aaron.
- So, what happened.
To this place, man?
This place looks like it's,
A little run down.
Neglect, abandonment.
So you got some cars In here?
- Yes, sir.
- Where?
'Round back, man.
They're all hidden.
Man. This is gonna be work.
Wow.
Well, the jeep,
Convertible thing here,
That's a hurst edition.
I think they're pretty rare.
We roam all around the property.
And it's... It's totally crazy.
Stuff stacked on stuff
Stacked on stuff.
Wherever something broke,
That's where it was.
Well, the lincoln's worthless.
The 'vette's not bad.
Chrome bumper front and backs,
That's, like, what, a '70?
'71, I think.
Well, that honda's
Pretty fricking cool.
And the rolls,
What year is that?
'61.
They built a shed, and then,
When they filled it with crap,
They needed a new place to work,
So they build another shed,
And they filled it with crap,
Then built another shed.
And the sheds progressively
Got worse and worse.
Don't... don't... d...
I don't weigh enough To hurt it.
Now, that's rad.
That's a pretty good
Shape king midget.
Mini-van.
Aaron, soon as you get married
And have some kids,
Here's your future.
I want to see in the house.
Before I make
Any kind of car deal.
Golly. Is it safe?
Somewhat, just got to
Watch your step, man.
Coming down's A little scarier
'cause that spot where
Aaron's standing right now.
Is really not the strongest
Step in the world.
Holy crap.
Holy cow.
Sheesh.
The house was Built in 1928.
It is, like, in such a state
Of disrepair, disarray...
Yeah.
He's got a bust
Of richard rawlings.
Wow. It's crazy.
But it wasn't sitting
On four wheels.
And that is What I came for.
There's a couple
That could be worth some money.
The problem is,
Is I can't get to the ones
I want without getting
The other ones out of the way,
And if I'm gonna touch them,
I might as well drag them off.
So what's the package deal
For all of them?
Probably 60,000, 65,000.
Really? There's no way.
He's telling me
$60,000 to $65,000.
I mean, there's $6,000
To $6,500 worth of cars here,
Tops. High side.
High side. I mean, not really.
There's probably
20,000 worth of...
Come on!
You know, I might
Just need something else.
To sweeten this deal.
What's the dealio with
The whole piece of property?
He's looking
For investors to buy it.
My mind started
Turning and I'm like,
"It's a very historical
Neighborhood.
People pay a little extra
To be in this part of the city."
I could just buy
The whole thing.
All the cars?
No, all of it.
Dirt, property, house?
All of it.
Are you able To make a deal?
I could give The owner a call.
My number will be low.
- I will pay you 500 grand.
- 500 grand?
That's it, in cash.
I can close now.
Don't need
Anything but a survey.
And if not 500 grand,
I don't even want the cars.
- I will just leave.
- All right.
At $500,000
It's got to be $700,000.
And it's just like a car.
You just buy it and flip it.
All right, talked to him.
He said he will do it.
Really?
500k. 500k.
It's yours.
I fully did not expect
For him to say yes.
All right. I don't know that...
I'm usually excited,
But I'm not.
Guess I'm in
The real estate business.
This is where I'm usually happy.
But I don't... Golly.
I just dished out
A half a million dollars.
So speed is Of the essence.
Plan on this is
Get in and get out.
As quick As humanly possible.
And my first step Is gonna be.
To try to unload
Some of these cars.
Before I even have
To move them off the property.
You know what they say.
You don't make your money.
When you sell, you make
Your money when you buy.
So since you made
About 100k or more,
I'd say lunch is on you.
Did I already make that?
Sounds like it.
I'm just gonna sit here
And enjoy my new porch.
Before it Falls in on me.
Dang, webster, you still working
On that back bumper?
Yeah, it's a little
More complicated.
Than I anticipated.
I think it's time to call in
Reinforcements.
So you're gonna make me work
On the front bumper?
I was really hoping...
Well, I'm not...
You were gonna do
Both the bumpers.
I'm not gonna make you.
I'm gonna ask you.
'Cause I've got, like...
- will you help with the...
- A sandwich to go eat.
Yeah, well, will you help
With the bumpers?
Yeah, sure.
So cutting down a bumper
Seems like a simple project.
But any cosmetic change like
This can open up a can of worms.
For instance, the back bumper
That webster's working on.
Has a subtle art to it.
You got to go slow
And make smart decisions.
When cutting out a chunk.
Because you still need
To preserve the overall line.
But, luckily for me,
On the front bumper,
We've got a crown.
So I should be able
To take it out of the middle,
Suck it up tight.
And if we can just do one seam,
That's gonna speed up
The process quite a bit.
And there were two.
Yeah.
I think it's pretty cool.
Right now, I'm just gonna tack
Weld the seam the together.
You want to test fit?
Sure. Need a hand?
To stay on schedule,
We need to get
This finished today.
Right here is Like this for me.
But I can't go any further
Until a certain someone.
With incredibly high
Expectations gives the okay.
Will that happen? Hopefully.
- I'm hoping so, too.
- See what happens.
Yeah, no kidding.
This is what
You're going for, right?
Bingo. That's the one. 100%.
Got a nice peak in the center,
So that works on the front.
Yeah. Rock and roll.
It's a little bit over
On that side.
On the shortening Up on these,
These actually
Will slide, you know.
They're adjustable?
They're collapsible this way
If you drill them.
Yep, and then you can
Knock it back...
And then weld it.
Weld it up, yeah.
When we're in the middle
Of a modification like this,
My mind's always
Going a mile a minute.
Because there's a million little
Things that need addressing.
At some point, you have
To make the fill piece, too,
Because of the way it comes
In and wraps around.
So just because it meets up here
Doesn't mean it's done.
Yeah,
I wouldn't mind going ahead.
And cutting this
And popping this down.
And filling that gap so that
The car has one clean slope up.
And everything all fits
Real natural, looks real normal.
That's where I tend to get
Into trouble with old ricardo.
I want our finished product
To look like it came off.
The factory floor that way.
And that's not always
Easy to pull off.
This right here,
This really doesn't look bad.
Problem is, though,
Is it's gonna make this.
Weird little edge on here.
So, we might actually
Have to cut it and rotate.
The whole thing, You know?
Otherwise, you're gonna have
This big crease here.
And there's no other crease
Down this side of the car.
You know, so that's
Really strange.
The edge is kind of tucked a bit
More than it is in the center.
It'd be nice if this center
Landed appropriately.
On top of the bumper, like,
If this right here come down,
If this was just Underneath it,
That would be
Really, really nice.
It seems like a pain in the ass
And a waste of time.
But believe me,
It will be worth it.
All in all, I'm really happy.
With the way the bumpers
Are shaping up.
So I think I'm going
To push paint another day.
I think it's more important
To get this right, right now.
Yeah. That's a, a, a-okay, man.
That looks really nice.
That's great.
Okay.
Well, That went pretty well.
I mean, hey, at least
We don't have to take steps back.
And restart a different idea.
That happens a lot
When you're dealing with aaron.
So that's a huge win for us.
Yes!
Coming up...
Whoa! Don't Go fast, dude!
Richard tries to flip his new
Find onto an old friend.
Price just went up.
Get this thing Into the booth.
And the el camino
Build goes dark...
We don't have No power, dude.
At a critical stage.
Least he can't blame
Aaron for this one.
I don't know. Bet's a bet.
Let's make this quick, guys.
It's frickin' hot out here.
- We're going straight in?
- Yeah, go straight in.
Okay.
There we go.
How are you
On your clearance over here?
- All right.
- Hey, mike.
Got a delivery for you. Thanks.
Except I was expecting
It two days ago.
Hey, Better late than never.
And when you buy
This car from richard...
I ain't buying this car
From richard.
You get this motor.
Comes with one horsepower.
Nobody wants that motor.
That's the motor
Everybody pulls out.
So, I guess aaron
Okayed the plan.
For cutting down the new bumpers
Coming in for our el camino
'cause he's finally letting me
And tony get our hands on it.
I think this thing's gonna be
Pretty cool, actually.
I think once the suspension's on
And it's hammered down...
And it's got that
Na-ha-hasty motor in it.
Yeah.
Yep, this thing
Will be pretty tasty.
From what I hear,
Aaron really wants to stay
On schedule with this
'cause he's got some kind
Of bet with richard.
That he can't finish on time
Or something like that.
There's not much
I can do to help.
Car's staying black,
And, as you guys know by now,
You got to work longer
And harder on a black car
'cause every
Imperfection will show.
We're on "Painter time."
So it's gonna be at least 3 days
Before we get to send to prime.
And another week before
They see it on their side.
Come on, dude. You're supposed
To be here by now.
I haven't got all day.
Yeah! Claremont,
Cerrito, corner house.
There's a broken piece
Of the fence.
Just come...
Yeah, just come through there.
Really?
So, a couple of days
Ago, I came out here to lakewood.
To check out a nest of cars.
And, well, ended up
With that nest of cars
and a house for $500,000.
I mean, that's a lot of money.
So speed is of the essence.
I got to get off this much money
Really, really quick.
You were supposed
To park and walk in.
It's a respectable
Neighborhood, man.
Doesn't look like it.
Well, not this general
Area right here.
- What's up?
- What happened here?
Welcome to my first foyer.
Into massive
Flipping real estate.
I don't care about that.
I just want to see the jeep.
Well, there you go.
It's a hurst 4 speed.
Or is it 3?
You don't know, do you?
I have no idea, dude.
You're the jeep guy.
I called dennis because
There's a jeep commando here.
I know it's rare.
I don't know how rare.
But let's just start
The money flowing in.
Well, it looks like
It's real just from the paint.
He was right.
It is a hurst commando.
Those are incredibly
Hard to find.
What'd they make?
Like, 200, 300?
100... when these were
On the production line,
Behind the battery box,
They put a crayon mark
On what number it was.
So this was number 18.
That's very cool.
Price just went up.
You shouldn't have told me that.
I knew I wanted it, so
Here we go on the negotiations.
This thing weighs
About 2,500 pounds.
So what does that mean?
It's probably worth
About $2,500.
I'm not selling it
By weight, fool!
You got to start somewhere.
Even though were best friends,
And almost everybody knows that,
He always starts high.
I say $5,000. What?
Or he thought he did. He didn't.
$3,500, go on To the next one.
All right, $3,500, it's yours.
Whatever, dennis.
You can have it for $3,500.
Let's move on and see if I can
Sell him some more crap.
All right, so what do you think
Is cool down here?
I like the honda.
I'm in for 500 on that one.
This car's A hardtop four-door.
It's too many doors.
Yeah, that's a thomas weeks
Special right there.
So, how much is
This $1,800 corvette?
I think $5,000's fair.
We're not going back and forth.
It's $5,000.
That's how much it is.
And if you want it, great.
If you don't, I don't care.
I will sell it to the next guy.
Okay. I'll do it For $5,000.
Cool.
You got to buy That for $5,000!
Anybody that's ever had
A pre-'73 corvette.
Knows that's a deal.
This lincoln is free
With purchase.
So now you own that.
So in the end,
I could only talk dennis.
Into taking about
Three cars off my hands,
Which isn't gonna make much
Of a dent in my bank account.
- I got to make money, dude.
- I got $500,000 in this.
I think you're just
Getting nervous 'cause you have.
The world's largest
Poison ivy farm in dallas.
No, I don't.
All right, come on.
So now, the fun part.
Somebody's got to get
All this crap out of here.
My guys are here!
Whoa, don't go fast!
We're On the back here.
I mean, it's a lot of crap.
All right.
What do you want to do next?
Yank that lincoln out of the way
So we can get the corvette out.
We need to throw the lawn
Mower out of the way.
Can we pick it up?
Where's the strap?
Just hook it to the jeep.
You came With reinforcements.
There you go!
If you pull it out
As fast as the lawn mower,
You can have it for free!
See you later. Later.
Nice doing business
With you, sir.
Now, get that stuff
Off my property.
I'm trying to keep
A respectable neighborhood.
Well, it looks like
At least tony was.
Getting something done
While you were playing around.
In that lakewood house.
I think we're good to go.
Let's get this thing into
The booth and get it primed.
Okay. Onward.
I'll Start picking up this.
You want to hit the paint booth
And get it cleaned up?
Yeah, we will get
That ready and going.
- All right, phil. Thanks, man.
- Yeah.
Good god, that's heavy.
Hey, mike.
What's up?
We ain't got nothing.
Did you...
It was working The other day.
Well, you ain't got
To turn them all on.
It should just be that one.
None of them are working.
We don't have no power, dude.
That ain't good.
So as painter guys,
We don't need much
To do our job.
But we do need one thing.
What's going on?
We don't Have a paint booth.
Has anybody looked
At the board outside yet?
No, it's...
That's where We're headed next.
Let's go check it out.
Well, see what we got.
The paint booth,
Not only does it provide light.
So we can see what we're doing,
It also provides ventilation.
So we don't die
While we're doing it.
So needless to say,
It's not a good thing.
That it won't turn on right now.
I'm sure It's just a fuse.
Dude, every single one
Of these connectors is burned.
Like, melted.
Ooh, dude, I can
Smell that from here.
Dude, yeah, it's bad.
Well, at least you know why
Your paint booth's not working.
Yeah Hey.
Wow.
Was it on when
We got hit by lightning?
I think it was running.
Yeah, I bet that's The problem.
Looks like the lightning strike
Strikes again.
Well, you know what I mean.
I guess when
That lightning strike.
Hit that building the other day,
It didn't just blow the fuses.
It fricking melted them.
That's toast. Yeah.
Richard's Gonna be pissed.
Shoot, yeah, That's pretty much.
A lot of money
Burnt up right there.
This situation's Bad enough.
But what makes it even
More annoying.
Is that the lightning
Struck days ago.
And if we'd have had any clue,
We could have fixed it.
While we were mocking up
Bumpers and prepping.
And that doesn't look
Like a quick fix either.
We need to get
An electrician out here.
We're already, what,
2 1/2 days behind on the car.
And now you got No paint booth.
But as it is,
We can't do much else.
With the el camino
Until it's painted.
And that's anybody's guess
On when it's gonna happen now.
Look, I'm gonna go
Let richard and aaron.
Know what's going on Because...
- good luck with that.
- That's not gonna be pretty.
Richard can't blame aaron
For this one, can he?
I don't know. A bet's a bet.
Coming up...
While charles presses ahead
With work on a king midget...
Got a feeling this is supposed
To be attached to the motor.
Let's do that one.
I like that one.
Aaron stalls out
On another big decision.
Man, I just hate
The commitment level.
The answer when we return.
The answer is "B".
In march of 2016,
Lady gaga posted
A photo of herself.
In her black el camino
With the caption,
"Some things
Never go out of style."
Hey!
Wait your turn.
Dude, where's...
Where's the pictures?
There is no pictures.
This book sucks.
All right, guys.
Find something to do.
Let's get the shop clean,
At least while we're waiting.
So our el camino build's
On life support right now.
Everyone's waiting on paint.
The fuse box that powers
The paint booth.
Got fried by lightning
The other day.
And it's gonna be
A couple more days before.
We can get it up
And running again.
That is a dope wheel, Isn't it?
I love them, man. I th... I...
I think that is
A righteous setup on that.
I want to be able
To burst out of the blocks.
As soon as we get
The green light.
At least aaron's locked down
The look he wants on the wheels.
But he's still got to
Decide on paint,
Which, I mean, you think
Would be easy.
Because we know what he wants.
It can be any color
As long as it's black.
- Yeah, as long as it's black.
- As long as it's black.
But I was kind of Thinking,
Instead of using a straight
Black like we do so often,
What if this was, like,
A tuxedo black that's got the.
- On there?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We could do a little
Light metallic black.
Hold on, I got something.
Yeah, show me.
It's got a brown flop
To it, though.
Is it flop brown. You sure?
- Kind of brown-ish gold.
- Brown?
Of course, with aaron,
Nothing's ever that easy.
- I know what you're saying now.
- See that gold in it?
That's what gives it
That gold-ish brown.
I think it will look
Like a root beer candy.
I got black forest.
But that's green.
Yeah.
You might be surprised
To know there's actually.
Hundreds of different blacks.
But trust me, aaron isn't.
I bet he's looked at
Every single one of them twice.
I just... I just don't...
I just... I mean,
You know what works.
I forgot that black with
Metallic looks like rainbow.
I like this.
It's different enough.
Let's do that one.
I like that one.
Do you like that one?
Yeah, I like that black.
Man, I just hate the
Commitment level to doing it.
You got a quarter?
Flip it.
61.2.
61.2?
So this morning,
Aaron actually asked me.
For a spray-out
Of this metallic black.
With a tiny, Tiny hint of blue.
So hopefully, that means we're
Getting closer to a decision.
All right. Here goes nothing.
I like it. I like it, too.
I do think it's gonna work,
So I'm happy to go with it.
But it makes me
A little nervous.
But I say let's do it.
All right. I like it, though.
I like it, too. It's different.
So, 16 hours after I asked,
We finally got a decision.
For aaron,
That's actually not that bad.
Now all we need
Is a paint booth.
Still doing All the work.
Yeah, honey.
So, things are getting a
Little lackadaisical around here.
While we're waiting
On the paint booth.
To get back online.
It's taking $4,000 out of
My pocket to fix it, by the way.
Aaron's keeping The guys busy,
Molly-maiding around the shop.
But I need to see some
Return on my investments,
And I mean soon, or there won't
Be a shop around to clean.
All right, dude.
You ever seen once of these?
No, what is this?
Here's your next Little project.
It is little.
This thing's a, -
It's called a king midget.
It has some kind of weird,
Motor in the back.
Um, and, it was
In that collection.
Where I bought the house
And everything.
Yeah. It's almost like
A lawn-mower-looking motor.
That's exactly
What it looks like.
Runs on a belt,
Single-side drive with a chain.
I mean, How ridiculous is that?
So pretty much a go kart
With a body on it, kind of?
I guess, man.
Who wouldn't want a car.
You could build yourself
For the low, low price of $270?
That was the pitch
Behind the king midget.
When it popped up for sale
After world war ii.
But measuring 10 feet long
On a good day.
With a one-cylinder
6-horsepower engine,
This big idea
Never really caught on.
Just under 5,000 were built.
Before this tiny dynamo
Dropped off the market in 1970.
But as you guys know...
Yeah.
I'm not afraid To think small.
It's actually
A little more spacious.
Than the, messerschmitt
That I had that time.
Test drive time!
Evel knievel's messerschmitt,
Well, that thing
Was pretty small,
Kind of like
A three-wheeled motorcycle.
But, as you know,
I like small things.
Remember that autobianchi?
I especially liked that
They both made me money.
So now it's time for the midget
To step up and do the same.
Chunk a battery in it,
Throw some go-go juice.
Down the carburetor,
And let's see what we got.
Just to see if it fires?
Like they say,
There's a butt for every seat.
So there's got to be a buyer out
There for this king midget also.
You figure it all out.
You get it to run and drive.
Can't we make it
A little cooler?
No, it's as cool
As it's gonna get.
It's orange and black.
It's like a halloween
King midget thing.
Like a halloween candy?
Just make it run and drive,
Dude, and then we will sell it.
All right. I got you.
And you will be amazed
At what I get for that.
All right, that's done.
So, I guess
The engine's not firing.
On this thing right now.
Any time you work
On an exotic car like this,
You got to be ready
For the unusual.
That's a pretty simple setup.
I don't think it's supposed
To be that simple.
Have a feeling this is supposed
To be attached to the motor,
Not in the floorboard.
Wow, that was tough.
One probably is, it's actually
Too small to fit on the lift.
- Good?
- Yeah, try that.
- All right. You're done.
- Yep.
This thing literally
Is just a go kart.
With a body on top of it.
After getting the starter in,
Now it's just a matter.
Of going through a checklist
Like any car.
That's been sitting around
For a long time.
Once you get fuel,
Air and spark,
You should have ignition.
Dang, man, this sucker
Fired right up, son.
That's one small step
For gas monkey.
And... Well,
One small step for anybody.
At least something
Works around here.
Coming up...
definitely orange, Isn't it?
Richard hopes
This small package.
Will bring a lot of good things.
It's got to be worth
At least $10,000.
Whoa.
Well, that's
A sight for sore eyes.
And the el camino
Build's back in gear.
But for how long?
Nothing lines up.
Yeah, that sucks.
We're just throwing
That right in the trash, right?
Hey, get a running start
And just hit your brakes,
See if it will slide off.
Aah, aah, aah!
I'm going in again.
Yes!
That deserves
A celebration, man.
Too bad you don't
Have any more horsepower.
Charles! Get your ass over here.
Thanks for getting me
In trouble, jason.
Well, that's
A sight for sore eyes.
So my bank account's
$4,000 lighter.
But at least my paint booth
Is working again.
And mike coy can get started.
It's like we're jumping
Railroad tracks.
Aaron bet me
That he could finish.
This el camino in 3 weeks.
So he's got a lot of
Catching up to do.
As for me, I got to get back
To the business of making money.
And not throwing it away.
There it is.
Bam! King midget.
One king little person.
Come on, man.
It's definitely orange,
Isn't it?
So I picked up
This king midget the other day,
Along with a bunch of other cars
And a falling-down house.
I stuck it on the 'net.
And, a guy gave me a call,
Said he was gonna come over
And check it out.
Awesome! Awesome!
My name's greg westfield.
And I'm from rome, texas,
Right now.
A little town north
Of fort worth, about 25 miles.
So what puts you
In the market for a midget?
I messed around
Restoring old cars.
In the past as a hobby.
And I'd seen these things
As a little kid, you know?
And I've often thought
About getting one.
Well, you ever Ridden in one?
- Never.
- Well, let's do it.
It's powerful, So be careful.
Seems like he's looking
For something to have.
A little neighborhood fun in.
Now, for me, you know,
That's maybe something
With 1,000 horsepower.
That does burnouts
And scares women and children.
But for this guy,
It's king midgets,
Which probably scares women
And children, too.
It's a little weird.
Well, you don't got
To worry about too much.
Pretty much Like a lawn mower.
Yeah, really.
It's kind of cool,
Driving around a little
Bitty car like that.
Well,
There's some folks that like it.
Folks are waving at us and
Taking pictures and...
- pretty cool?
- Yeah, it is.
Fully restored,
These cars can go.
From $4,000 to $7,000.
It's a small-dollar car.
But so is most of the stuff
That was in that nest.
This one still needs
A lot of work.
But there's not a lot
Of them out there, so...
Running, driving,
Doing what it's supposed to do.
It's got to be worth
At least $10,000.
Whoa.
I don't know
About that, partner.
There is no way...
No way under the sun
I would pay $10,000.
I'd be interested
About $2,000, man.
Come on. It's a running,
Driving car.
And it's little.
I'll give you that, It's little.
You can bring it up
A little bit,
I'm sure We can make a deal.
Got any interest at 25?
I got interest at 35.
How about 28?
Come on!
How 'bout $3,000?
Yeah.
I'll take it.
Will do, all right.
Well, let's go inside
And do some paperwork.
Okay. And...
I would highly suggest You don't.
Get on the freeway
With that one.
Okay.
So another car sold.
Only got, like, 14 or 15 more
To go out of that nest,
Get those things gone,
Get the house sold.
I'm on a roll!
Now, I just need
To win my bet with aaron.
Thing is, if that happens,
Well, that means.
He went past his deadline.
And then I'm gonna be pissed.
Woo-hoo! Lordy.
So we've already
Been working on this paint job.
For over a week.
I'm loving the color
Aaron picked out,
But it is black, so we're
Taking it slow and steady.
On our sanding and buffing.
Since the goal is to get
This thing done in 3 weeks,
We want everything on our side
Ready to go back onto the car.
The minute it gets
Back from paint.
Look what I found.
The new bumpers are in.
Aaron hated all the trim that
Was on the original bumpers.
So we tracked down
Some reproduction parts.
We call them repops.
They have a cleaner finish.
But the new ones will
Still have to be cut down.
To achieve that tucked look
He's after.
Shiny.
We spent the first few days.
Experimenting on the ones
That we're ditching.
So, we already know
How we're gonna do it.
All we need to do now
Is make sure the pieces.
We're keeping fit like they
Should and get to cutting.
All right. What's going on here?
What the heck?
Nothing lines up.
The thing about using repops is,
They're supposed to be
The exact same shape.
And size as the original.
But that doesn't always
Happen in real life.
- Hey, webster.
- What's up, buddy?
You know what stinks About...
Not building your parts.
On the actual parts
You're gonna use?
I don't think
The angle matches anymore.
Boy.
So this is up Too high, right?
The mounting flange is curled
Upwards, is that correct?
Yeah, I... I mean,
Bolting this thing on the car,
It ain't even Gonna sit right.
Yeah, that sucks.
All that work to
Contour to that angle.
And now, we have
A totally different angle.
I got two choices...
Spend a whole bunch of
Extra fabrication time.
Making the new bumpers
Somehow work.
Or go with the old bumpers.
We already cut down
The way we want.
Yeah, but if you
Use the old ones,
You still got To have to fill in.
All the holes
Where the trim was.
And that's gonna eat up
A lot of time, as well.
We're already so far behind,
That could put us even further.
And that's if it works.
I know what I think
We should do.
But ultimately,
There's only one person.
That's gonna make That decision.
Jason's right.
I mean, aaron's the one.
Who made some kind
Of a bet with richard.
To finish this thing
Fast anyway.
Ultimately, it's his
You-know-what on the line.
So what's the...
Is it the, the...
The mounting location Business?
The repop is a complete
And utter piece of junk.
When you put this on there,
Look at that angle down there.
- Yeah.
- So...
And that one's flat Over there?
We would have to completely.
Try to re-curl
The whole, entire surface.
On both of them
And then, hope that it's right.
Whereas, I can just weld up.
The holes in the one
I've already got.
I really put myself
Between a rock and a hard place.
When I said we could get
This project done in 3 weeks.
I didn't leave myself
Any wiggle room.
For complications like this.
Whichever way I go, it's gonna
Be a gamble time-wise.
So in situations like this,
You don't want to overthink it.
You just want to go
With your gut.
I'm more than happy
To have you finish this one up.
It's a little more welding.
But, man, we know it fits.
- Yeah, we already know it.
- I'm down. I'm all the way down.
Other than that, Roll it back up.
And throw it in the box
And chock this one up to game.
All right.
At this point, we're gonna
Need luck on our side.
If we want to finish on time,
Which means no more
Lightning strikes or bad repops.
Back to the box.
The last thing that I want.
Is to be eating crow
Whenever the deadline arrives,
Especially when you consider
Who's dishing it up.
All right!
Next week, On "Fast n' loud"...
I think we're gonna need
A bigger hood.
As the push to finish
The el camino.
In record time continues...
You're making My fender shake.
Golf clap.
Holy cow. There's a car in here.
Richard tries To dig up a deal.
On a '68 corvette.
I don't even know How to start.
And spins the gas monkey brand
Into a smoking-hot new venture.
But when the air finally
Clears...
That doesn't fit.
The crew finds one problem...
We got dents.
Are you kidding me?
After another.
Damn it.
And aaron's bet with richard...
She's just being difficult.
She will start in a second.
Comes down to one
Final moment of truth.
What a mess.
Captions by vitac...
www.Vitac.Com.