[FOOTSTEPS RUNNING]
Camryn. Camryn, look at me.
- Why is he doing this'?
- Camryn, please. We need to be quiet.
Where are the others?
We have to find them.
- No, we need to find help.
- What about Walt and Lizzy and...'?
Walt didn't make it.
Listen, if that psycho hasn't found
everybody else by now,
they're probably making a run for it.
Which is exactly what we need to be doing.
We can't leave them!
We need to find help.
That's how we save each other.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Hey, look... Hey.
Just think of it as a track meet.
What would Hansen say'? "If you don't win
this race, I will make you run in six more."
- [SHE LAUGHS AND SNIFFLES]
- That's mygirl.
Listen, if we start running in a direction,
eventually we're going to hit a road and--
No!
[SHE SCREAMS]
[RUSTLING]
[SHE PANTS]
[SI-IE STIFLES HER SCREAMS]
Uuuh!
Oh, Anneke! Oh, my God!
- No! No, no!
- Anneke! Anneke!
- It's me. It's okay. It's okay.
- Oh, my God!
- I'm going to get you out of here.
- [ANNEKE WHIMPERS]
Please!
Everythings okay.
I'm going to get you out of here.
[AN N EKE SO BS]
No! No!
No! Oh, my God! Come on!
You can't have her!
Uuh!
[GROANING]
[SHE SOBS]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
Agh!
Aaah!
Uh!
Agh!
[SHE SCREAMS]
Help!
Please! Somebody help me!
[SHE COUGHS AND SPLUTTERS]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
Agh!
[HE GROANS]
[HER SOBS TURN TO LAUGHTER]
No!
[SHE SOBS]
[SHE SCREAMS]
- Morning, Camryn.
- Hi.
She's filled her quota for the day.
- Ese no es e! Punto.
- Entonces ¢cuéf es e! Punto?
El punto es que él empieza
a roquearse con la cancién.
Y después, cuando termina,
empieza Ia cancién de nuevo.
5 Como un disco rayado?
No. La cancién se repite,
y él empieza a cantarla otra vez.
All right, if you can lean, you can clean.
Lucia, I need you on register today.
Oh! Come on, David. When you
going to find a replacement for Brittany?
Keep that up and you will be
the permanent replacement.
I have someone coming in later
today that will hopefully work out.
Fine.
[HUM OF MACHINERY,
MUSIC ON RADIO]
T hank you, Camry“.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION
IN SPANISH AND LAUGHTER]
- So, did you find the place all right'?
- I did, yeah, actually.
- I get tacos, like, two doors down.
- Tyson's'?
- Uh-huh, yeah. You know it'?
- My doctor's trying to get me to lay off.
But I honestlyjust don't see
the point in getting up without 'em.
Yeah, WOW.
That's Why I don't go to doctors.
[THEY LAUGH]
So, What's your availability?
That was the interview?
I trust Rays judgment.
Oh, WOW. I guess he earned
the five bucks I gave him.
[DAVID LAUGHS]
When can you start'?
[SHE FLICKS TV CHANNELS]
[HEAVY BREATHING ECHOES]
[HEAVY BREATHING FADES AWAY]
[SHE FLICKS TV CHANNELS]
Help.
Please help me.
I'm sorry.
Where are you going?
Where are you going?!
- I'm so sorry.
- Please help me.
Just untie me, please!
[SHE SCREAMS]
Uh!
[SHE PANTS]
Nobody home? Sorry.
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
I'm, er, I'm the new guy.
Register bitch.
Right. Hi.
I'm Nick.
Camryn.
I'm sorry. I couldn't hear you
over the dryers. Come in.
Morning, Camryn. This is Nick.
Yep.
She's a bit shy.
Yeah, I think we can help you.
That's what we do here.
You don't understand.
I need this to be perfect.
Right.
Erm, well, let me see if I can find...
Camryn, hey.
Do you mind giving me a hand?
This is Camryn.
She's, er, one of the cleaners.
She's the best.
I need this clean. Like spotless.
And I mean perfect.
It can't have any sign of...
this.
Please.
What do you think, Camryn'?
- I'll take care of it.
- Oh, you Will?
Oh. God, you're lifesaver.
I can't thank you enough.
Can I pick it up in the morning?
Sure.
This means so much to me. Thank you!
Whafd I tell you'?
Hey. Erm... sorry.
I didn't mean to put you
on the spot back there.
I just... I didn't know what to do.
Call David. He handles customers.
Yeah. No, yeah.
Cool. I'll definitely do that next time.
Well, thanks for the help. I owe you one.
Yeah. Not me dude. I'm a Pippen man.
A Pippen man'?!
Pippen was a chump, man!
- Pippen was a chump'?! Come on!
- Jordan all the Way.
- Oh, my God. Seriously?!
- Not a chump, but not Jordan.
- All right. We're talking about the...
- Nice to meet you.
Very nice to meet you.
Thank you so much, Lucia.
- I appreciate you showing me everything.
- Thank you for saving me from the register.
- You got it! Have a good one.
- New guy, come outwith us.
- We' re going to get drink.
- I would love to. Tonight I can't.
- But definitely in the future, man. Definitely.
- All right, man.
- Next time.
- Bye.
Thank you so much for coming
in on short notice.
- Absolutely.
- I really think this is going to work out.
I think so too. Absolutely.
- We'll see you tomorrow.
- Yeah.
Camryn, you about done'?
I gotta lock up.
- What about this guys shirt'?
- Oh, shit!
Look, I really have to be somewhere.
Can you do it and lock up when you leave?
Please.
You can stay on the clock.
- With overtime.
- Fine.
You're a lifesaver! Okay.
The back should be locked already.
So you just have to lock the front door
behind you when you leave.
Don't stay too late.
Shit.
[BANG]
[DOOR CREAKS]
- [SHE SCREAMS]
- Aah! Aah!
- [SHE PANTS]
- Camryn!
Camryn!
- [KNOCKING]
- Camryn!
I got halfway home and then
I realised lforgot my cell phone,
so I had to come back.
And when you got here,
you didn't see the intruder?
- Er, no, sir.
- All right. Thanks.
Mefam?
Do you have some place to stay tonight?
Any family or friends?
- Did you find anything?
- No, ma'am.
There's no sign of the intruder
or any forced entry.
We'll call the owner.
See who else has keys.
Is there someone we can call for you'?
I don't think it's best
if you stay alone tonight.
You can stay with me.
I mean, me... me and my room-mates,
We've got an extra couch, if...
Sorry.
Are you comfortable with that, ma'am'?
Good.
- I think it's for the best.
- Sure.
Tell you what, let's look this place up so
you guys can get some sleep. All right'?
Okay.
[NICK] So Tyler's been living with me
for about five years, but I've known him
pretty much since I moved here.
And if he's at home, that means that Hannah
and Mae and Griffin are probably there,
cos they/re kinda like
our unofficial room-mates.
Unlike Danielle, who's our official room-mate,
which means she pays rent.
She's only been there for a little vvhile,
but she seems pretty cool.
Er, she's getting her undergraduate
and she's...
prepping for, er... adult life.
You know, I can just take
you home, you know.
If you just want to let me know
where you live, I oan drop you off.
No, it's okay.
Okay.
Do you want to talk
about what happened?
No.
You want me to
just shut for a little while'?
No.
Really. I'm listening.
Just talk.
Okay.
Erm...
Well, Tyler's, er...
[HE COUGHS]
...kind of a social/political artist,
I guess, is What he calls himself.
But really he kind ofjust
makes weird shit out of wood.
- [TYLER] I didn't say that.
- [MAE] Yes, you did.
- You're putting Words in my mouth.
- I'm reading between the lines.
- Oh, come on!
- Hey, guys. Don't wait for me or anything.
Hi, Nick. There's beer in the fridge.
Yeah, I know. I bought it.
Oh. Well, thank you for the beer.
Nick, you got to help me out here.
Tyler wants us to throw away our phones.
- What?
- We're addicted.
I mean, statistics show that people
checktheir phones like 150 times a day.
I'm sorry. What was that?
Well, yeah, but, dude,
where'd you get those numbers?
Did you fix your laptop finally or
did you look them up on your phone?
You fucking hypocrite! I knew it!
So how's the new job'?
It's good. It's, er... It's a change of pace.
It's What I needed, I think.
Everybody, this is Cam ryn.
Er, we work together.
- God, Nick. That was fast.
- Wow!
No, that's not...
Er, that's not cool at all.
Camryn just needed a place to
crash so I offered her the couch.
Where am I suppose to sleep'?
Dude, hovv often do you
actually make it to the couch'?
Sometimes.
We actually... We kind of had
like a sort of weird night.
So we can kind ofjust
take it easy on the initiations, Mae.
- Yeah, Mae!
- What? What did I do?
Is everything okay, sweetie?
I feel like somethings bothering you.
Er, Hannah, why don't we... You want to just
go get Cam ryn something to drink, yeah?
Yeah.
I can get you some water.
Something happened.
Do you want to talk about it'?
Er, Hannah, I, erm... I think maybe
she just wants some space.
Right.
Sorry.
Well, if you ever do want to talk,
I'm a really great listener.
Thank you.
Are you guys still going out tonight?
We were, but I can stay
with Camryn if you guys want.
It's okay. I'm totally fine.
- Do you want to com e'?
- No, but thank you.
- Hey!
- Hey.
- Evening.
- You just get home?
A couple minutes ago, yeah.
- You got a big test tomorrow or something?
- Mm-hm, there's rumours of one.
Erm, Camryn, this is Danielle.
Danielle, this is Camryn.
Oh, hey. Welcome
to the East Side social club.
[NICK] Oh, are they being too loud'?
- I can tell them to shut up.
- It's fine. I'm just messing with you.
When are you going to come out
with us again, Danielle?
Er, maybe tomorrow?
We'll see What happens.
Oh, also, Camryn is sleeping
on the couch tonight.
All right. Well, I'll try not to make
too much noise in the morning.
Oh, you don't have worry... about me.
[LAUGHTER]
That apartment right out of college.
Do you remember that, Hannah'?
- Of course.
- That was the place to be.
Was that the one where Griffin
was sleepwalking all the time?
- Yes! Yes, it Was!
- She's going to tell the elevator story now.
- Nick, have you heard this one'?
- Which one'?
Are you talking about when
Griff fell asleep on the elevator
and was hitting on the poor girl who was
just trying to get back to her apartment?
No, I've never heard this one.
I-low does it go'?
[LAUGHTER]
Hey, you know, that was a really
weird time in my life, all right'?
I talked to that girl a week later and she said
she thought you were a homeless guy.
[LAUGHTER]
Uh!
[SHE PANTS]
[GRIFFIN SNORES]
- You all right'?
- Uh! Oh, God.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
It's okay. I'm all right.
I just had a nightmare.
Do you need anything'?
Water or... tea?
No, thank you. I'm fine.
[GRIFFIN SNORES]
Hey, I'm making tea. Come on.
Oh, hey... Look, sorry about the mess.
Cleaning has kinda been
the last thing on my mind lately.
So, you're Nicks friend?
We work together. Where is he'?
Oh, he probably went out for a run.
As random as he keeps the rest of his life,
that's one thing he does like clockwork.
So you guys work
at the thrift store together?
Dry cleaner.
Shit. Right. I remember him
mentioning something about that.
I didn't know he'd started yet.
He started yesterday.
Oh'? Well, you guys must have really hit it off.
Which is good because Nick needs
somebody looking out for him.
Actually, I was attacked yesterday.
At least, I think I was.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, the cops came.
I didn't have anywhere else to go,
so Nick offered me the couch.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just...
kinda want to go home.
Yeah.
- Thank you. Sorry to put you out.
- Hey, don't worry about it.
This is on the Way to class. Just let
me know if you need anything, okay?
- You know where to find me.
- Thank you.
Seriously. Don't be a stranger.
- What happened last night? Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine. It was nothing.
Look, I swear the back was locked.
You didn't unlock it, did you'?
No. It's all right. He didn't hurt me. He didn't
take anything. Let's just forget about it.
Forget about it'? The police were
questioning me like I was suspect.
I'm sorry. Next time there's a customer
request, you should stay late and deal with it.
'Oh, my God! Camryn!
- Are you okay?
Yes! Would everyone
stop asking me that question?
Look, I'm very sorry about this.
We'll be more than happy
to replace it for you.
But this is one of a kind.
My wife had this hand tailored for me.
I'm extremely sorry about this. Maybe
we can compensate you for the damages?
You! You said you'd take care of it.
You said you'd fix it.
What am I suppose to do with this'?
- Look, calm down.
- No, I just want my shirt back!
Look, let's step over here and
maybe we can sort this out'?
What's to sort out'?
Camryn.
I'm sorry, David. I got carried away last night.
I think I was using the wrong brush.
Camryn, please. I should have taken
care of it yesterday. I'm sorry.
Why don't you take lunch?
I'd rather Work.
Hey, don't beat yourself up over it.
I think you probably did
that guy's wife a favour.
[RATTLING]
[SHE RINGS THE BELL]
Aaaah!
[SHE PANTS]
Camryn'? What are you doing?
What's going on'? What's with the pipe?
- He was just here.
- What? Who?
He came back.
- The guy from last night?
- Yes! I just chased him out here.
I swear. He was just here.
Okay, well, let's just go inside. Okay'?
Come on.
Camryn, are you okay? What happened'?
Who left the back door open?
Camryn, it's always open.
It helps with circulation.
You let that son-of-a-bitch in here! Did
you leave the back door open last night, too'?
- Why are you helping him'?
- Camryn, stop it!
- Right, that back door is shut from now on.
- But, David...
I don't want to hear it.
Lucia, take the front for a few.
The rest of you, give us some space.
Are you all right'?
He's come back for me.
Why don't you take
the rest of the day off'?
I don't think she should
be alone right now.
- Can you take her home?
- Yeah.
I could take her home, yeah.
You shouldn't be around me.
He's not after me.
[CICADAS CHIRPING]
[MUSIC PLAYS IN THE DISTANCE]
[DISTANT LAUGHTER AND CHATTER]
[DOG BARKS VICIOUSLY,
CAGE RATTLES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[DISTANT CHATTER]
[LOUD ELECTRO MUSIC PLAYS]
[CHATTERING VOICES]
Camryn!
Whoa! Sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm just in my own little world.
It's cool. I get like that when I'm studying.
Hey, I didn't know you
were coming out tonight.
Yeah. Er, er, Nick invited me.
Oh, nice! Well, it's about time
he took some initiative.
Come on. Let's go find him.
- Stop it, man.
- You know What to do, right'?
Yes, I know What to do.
- You guys are Way too predictable.
- Oh, hi, ladies!
Come on! Come on!
- You were going to miss anyway.
- Thanks!
Same team here.
You look really nice tonight, Camryn.
Thank you.
Hey. You okay?
- So What's been going on'?
- Tyler was explaining his art.
If you call rambling explaining.
Art shouldn't have to be explained.
All I'm asking, man, is why don't you try
making something a little more useful?
Are you saying art isn't useful?
I mean, how many people want some
oreepy sculpture of Reagan, huh'?
I mean, you Working with vvood, man. You
can earn some serious cash making shelves,
or tables... fucking bowls.
- Who wants a Wooden bowl?
- You could put fruit in it.
Why do you use wood then?
Well, the trees themselves
are an extension of the piece.
- So there's a purpose behind it'?
- Right.
Does it have to do with the tree rings
and, like, how repetitive life is'?
Er, well, no two rings are the same.
I mean, each ring varies
in thickness each year,
depending on Whether it was
a good year or a bad year or, you know.
But they're still rings, right'?
They're still like ring-shaped rings'?
Yes, but each ring tells a different story.
Until you out the tree down
and then you're interrupting the story.
No, I only use trees that fall naturally.
"Ah!
Mother Earth, can I ask you something?
What the fuck does that
have to do with Ronald Reagan?
[LAUGHTER]
Eh'?
So, Camryn, hovv long have
you worked at the laundromat?
- Erm...
- It's not like a laundromat.
It's a... it's a dry cleaners. It's not like
one of those self-service places.
Okay. I-low long have you been
cleaning other people's dirty clothes?
Ivlaelyn.
About four years.
And do you have a degree for that?
Enough!
Come on, Camryn. Let's go grab
a drink and go to the bathroom.
- I'll come!
- No, no, don't do it. It's your shot.
I can't make shit. It's all you.
Look, don't pay any attention to Mae.
She doesn't get along with her own gender.
It's fine.
So Nicks taking a liking to you.
- What?
- Come on.
Why do you think Mae has it out for you'?
We work together.
So'? I mean, where else are
you going to meet someone?
I don't know.
- It's been a while.
- Perfect!
It's been a while for Nick too
from what I understand,
so you guys can be all awkward
and timid about it together.
[DOOR OPENS]
Plus, both you guys seem like
you really need to get laid.
Nick!
- [CROWD GASPS]
- Nick!
Camryn, Stop!
No! I Won't let it happen again!
Jesus Christ!
Fucking psycho-bitch. What the fuck'?
I saw you. Who are you'? Where's the mask'?
- What are you on'?
- Where's the mask'?
Camryn! Camryn, What's Wrong?
Where is it'? Where's the mask'?
- Get the others.
- Who are you'? Who are you'?
- Let it go. Let it go.
- Where is he'?!
Let it go.
Camryn! Camryn! Camryn, stop!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- I know I saw him.
- What'? What are you talking about'?
- [SHE MUTTERS]
- Camryn, what are you talking about?
- We're not safe. We're not safe.
- We' re not safe.
- Who's... who's not safe'?
- We're not safe.
- Who's not safe, Camryn'?!
All of you.
Camryn.
You gotta tell us What's going on.
Ah! What are we doing out here?
It's gone.
What's gone?
- It was right here when you left for the bar.
- Er, you weren't with us when we left.
- Where is it'?
- Camryn, what are you looking for'?
It was hanging right here!
Do you mean the ball
that's usually hanging there?
I sometimes Watch the neighbour's dog.
He comes in, chews the ball off.
It Wasn't a ball.
Can we go back to where she knows when
we left because sounds like she's stalking us'?
Ivlaelyn. Shut up.
Nick, come on!
I mean, it's pretty creepy.
What's going on, Camryn'?
He marked this house with a skinned rabbit.
I need to find it so you guys will believe me.
Did you just say something
was skinned back here'?
There was a dead rabbit right here earlier.
That's how I know he's coming for you.
Nick, she hung a fucking dead
animal in our backyard.
This isn't your backyard.
Camryn, I think it's time we go inside.
Don't invite her inside.
She's gonna skin us in our sleep.
[NICK SIGHS]
Camryn, come on. What's going on'?
What were you doing back here'?
Hey, guys. The side gate's open.
Oh, hey. Ringo probably got in here.
Camryn, I think
a dog must have gotten it.
Yeah, but, er...
you believe me, don't you'?
She came to the bar with you, right'?
No, lthought you invited her.
Cool. So, if you guys are done scaring the
shit out of me, I'm going to go back inside.
Let me know if you guys need anything.
Yeah.
[NICK SIGHS]
Well, somethings got her spooked.
Mm.
Look, I'll... I'll just take her home
and see What's going on.
I mean, who knows? Maybe
she's on something. I don't know.
L_ll'"n!
- I sure know how to pick them.
- Hey...
Take it easy on her, okay?
Yeah.
We'll, figure it out. It'll be okay.
Okay. Call me later.
Let me know everything's all right.
I'm sorry. I just don't want
you guys to get hurt.
I appreciate that... l do.
You believe me, right'?
[HE SIGHS]
Danielle's going to get you fixed up.
I'll talk to you guys tomorrow, okay?
I'm not crazy.
Erm, thanks for the ride.
I can take it from here.
Camryn, I'm not leaving
you alone right now.
Seriously, I'm fine.
I just... I need to clear my head.
Come on, let's just hang out for a bit.
It's Friday night. I don't have
anywhere to be tomorrow.
You just move in'?
- Four years ago.
- Oh.
Can I go to the bathroom?
Of course.
Make yourself at home.
[HEAVY BREATHING ECHOES]
[SHE SIGHS]
I remember hearing
about this in high school.
- You're the one that survived.
- You shouldn't be in here.
Camryn, I'm so sorry.
I had no idea how serious this was.
So you believe me now'?
Well, I believe that you're scared.
And you have every right to be,
but you can't keep living in fear like this.
What the fuck do you know about fear'?
You're right.
I don't know What you've been through,
but I feel like you've been given
a second chance here.
This isn't about my second chance,
it's about his.
You, Nick, Maelyn -
you're all in danger because of me.
Camryn, you killed this guy. He's dead.
What if he isn't'?
So what then?
He's come back to life'?
This thing, this monster,
took everything from me
and I'm not going to let him do it again.
What happened'? Afterwards, I mean?
Twelve Weeks of counselling
and a shit tonne of drugs.
Paroxetine'?
Effexor.
That shit made me so dizzy.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah.
They took me off of it whenever
I started physical therapy.
What happened'?
Oh, you know, Mom had a... drug problem
that nobody really wanted to talk about.
She picked me up from school
one day, senior year.
She got angry the last time
I offered to drive, so I didn't this time.
She took the back way home.
Used country roads to avoid
the main parts of town.
Less people to see her out there, I guess.
The next thing I remember was
waking up on the side of the road.
I could see my mom,
motionless and covered in blood.
And then I saw the other driver
and a passenger.
It was a husband and wife.
None of it set in, though,
until I saw that little shoe.
A tiny...
...little blood soaked shoe.
An entire family was destroyed
because I didn't say anything.
[SHE SIGHS DEEPLY]
It took me six months to look
at myself in the mirror again.
I'm sorry.
Did you ever go see it'?
What'?
His grave'?
Do you know where it is'?
You know what finally helped me'?
Closure.
Jesus! Are we going for a night or a week'?
Sorry.
Precautions.
You ready?
You okay?
Camryn?
Are you okay?
Thought there'd be something more.
He doesn't deserve any more.
You see'?
He isn't hunting you.
You killed him and you put him
in the ground where he belongs.
If it Wasn't for you, more people
would have Wondered into those Woods
and more people would have died.
But you killed him.
You saved lives.
J ust not m y friends.
No, but you lived.
What would they want you to do now'?
Take as much time as you need.
[DANIELLE SIGHS]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
What's going on'?
Camryn.
What are you doing?
Whoa, whoa, whoa! You can't do this!
Yes, I can! This is closure.
I meant seeing the grave, not digging it up.
He is out there, all right. You
don't believe me'? Show me his body.
Prove that I'm fucking crazy.
[SHOVEL HITS SOMETHING SOLID]
Are you sure about this'?
You don't have to do this.
Yes, I do.
[CAMRYN SOBS]
I'm crazy.
No, you're not.
I'm seeing things. I'm fucking crazy.
You just... needed a little help.
The doctors said I was fine.
You are fine.
You just needed some time.
I'm tired of waiting.
Camryn.
Come on.
I think We've done enough.
No, we haven't.
Go out of service for a few hours
and suddenly everybody wants
to get a hold of me.
Nick called.
I knew it!
[THEY LAUGH]
Does he think I'm a psycho?
No.
Nicks a lot things, but he's not like that.
Everyone's going to Tyler's, like...
artist space tonight.
Nick wanted me to invite you if I saw you.
So, I've seen you.
Do you want me to invite you'?
[THEY LAUGH]
Oh, good. I didn't know if
they were in this place or Tyler's.
[CHILLED ELECTRO MUSIC PLAYS]
[HE IVIOUTHS]
You've got to be kidding me!
Er, back off, Mae.
It's okay. Erm...
Hey, guys, I owe you an apology
for the other night. Erm...
I'm sorry. Lvvas kind of crazy and
I'm sorry I took it out on all of you. Erm...
I think you guys are really cool
and if you would give me another chance,
I promise to keep my future
bottle smashing to a minimum.
Hey, er, don't make promises you can't keep.
- Hi.
You didn't have to apologise.
Oh. Well, I wanted to
cos I was so crazy the other night.
[HE LAUGHS] Well, you know,
normal people are boring, so...
don't worry about it.
- You want to get a drink?
- Yeah, thanks.
Where did you guys g0?
Erm... Oh, we just went camping.
Clear our heads.
Like, kinda...
- Clear your heads?
- No.
No. I just had to get out of town.
Get perspective, I guess.
Er, do you want to get
your own one of those?
Yeah.
Nick, you have to introduce me to
your new friend. She sounds fascinating.
Oh, sorry. Camryn, this is Evan.
Evan, Camryn.
- Nice to meet you.
- Thanks. You, too.
- Where is everybody?
- Oh, we open next Friday.
- Is Tyler going to show anything?
- If he ever finishes anything.
- [NICK LAUGHS]
- Erm, well, I'll let you get a refill.
And then, come talk to me
after you've had a look around.
- Cool man. Sounds good.
- Okay.
Erm... come on.
- Hey, GUYS"
_ Hey.
Oh, hey, What's Banksy got
to say for himself over there?
Come on, dude, he's not that bad.
You're drinking his beer.
I'll drink anybody/s beer.
I'm so glad that you're here.
You're practically glowing right now.
- Thanks.
- It's a good thing. Trust me.
What I want to know is how a bunch
of “artistes” can afford a place like this'?
Have you seen the neighbourhood
around here'?
Give it a few years.
This will be the new trendy part of town.
Oh, my God, this conversation is
so boring already. I'm sorry I asked.
I'm going to go stare at this dot
over here until my eyes bleed.
Well, I think it's fascinating and
Evan's gallery is going to be huge for him.
Yeah. Errn, you know What? I think I'm
going to take Camryn and shovv her around.
Oh, hovv fun. Okay. I'm gonna go to
the bathroom then I'll come find you guys.
Okay. We'll go hide.
You're too funny!
Hey, Tyler, Where's the bathroom?
Follow me.
[NICK] Oh, sorry.
All right. Er, hold on.
- What are these rooms'?
- Erm...
Artists rent them out.
It's kinda like a collective.
- We gotta get away from Hannah.
- What?
- Come on!
Guys'?
- [HANNAH] Guys?
- Come on!
Shit!
Go, go, go!
Guys'?
Where'd you go'?
- Ssh, ssh.
- [HANNAH] Camryn'?
Come on, guys. Where'd you go'?
[SNIGGERING]
[HE SIGHS]
- Sorry. She can be a little much sometimes.
- Yeah.
It's okay. I'm having fun.
Yeah, me too.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
- Are you sure'?
- Sorry. Come here.
No!
[BONES CRACKING]
[SHE SOBS]
STOP W').
“Aw.
[SHE SCREAMS]
Oh, my God!
Camryn, what did you do'?
Cl-Camryn?
[HAN NAI-I SCREAMS]
Hey, so when are you
coming to one of our shows?
Don't tell me you actually like this shed.
- [SHE TURNS MUSIC OFF]
- Oh. All right.
We're on the same page.
Quiet. I thought I heard a scream.
It's probably just the drunks on the street.
[LOUD INDIE MUSIC PLAYS]
- This is more like it!
- Dude! Turn that shit off.
Come on. This party
needs some fucking life!
- That's fucking noise!
- It's fucking awesome!
Give me that!
Hello'?
Fine, but it's my art party.
[ARGUMENT CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Hannah, are you just now
finding the bathroom?
Danielle?
Camryn, is that you'?
What the fuck'?! Come on.
I can't see dick in here.
[DOOR CREAKS]
Haaa!
Nick'?
Camryn?
[LOUD INDIE MUSIC PLAYS]
That is exactly my point.
[ARGUMENT CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
What? Yeah, exactly my point.
- Why don't you just calm down'?
- This is insane.
[MUSIC STOPS]
- [HE SIGHS]
- Dude.
- Some of us like to hear ourselves think.
- [CHOKING AND SPLUTTERING]
- Holy shit!
- What the fuck'?
[SHE PANTS]
No, no, no, no. No! No! No!
[SHE SCREAMS]
Tyler, call the fucking cops!
Hey, hurry'!
Jesus!
Aaaah!
[SHE GASPS]
[SHE SNIFFLES]
[SHE SOBS]
[I-IE SCREAMS AND MOANS]
[WOMAN] 911. What is your emergency?
Agh!
This is for Derek and Anneke,
and Sarah and Thomas,
and Walt and Hank.
Oh, my God!
What did you do'?
You can keep coming
back to life all you want.
I won't let you kill any more of my friends!
[DANIELLE SCREAMS]
Camryn, please. Please don't do this.
[SHE SOBS]
No!
I just wanted to protect them this time.
I wanted to save them this time.
You monster!
[DANIELLE SCREAMS]
[SHE SOBS]
[SHE SCREAMS]
Oh, my God!
HEY-
Where is she'?
- In Tyler's room.
- Did you lock her in'?
I hit her with a hammer.
Hard?
You okay?
No.
You want to talk about it'?
Me neither.
Stop it!
Oh, no!
I'm done running. I don't care how
many times I have to kill you!
- No!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[SHE SOBS]
Hey, hey, hey-
Get up.
[SIRENS WAIL]
[DANIELLE SCREAMS]
Aah! No! Oh, my God!
No, please! No!
[SHE SOBS]
No!