Williamsburg Savings Bank
good morning sir,
Welcome to Williamsburg Savings Bank.
Let me give you a call,
We will arrange an interview for you
With a bank employee.
Once someone is available.
What will this device do?
It will shine and shake.
The red lights will turn in a circle.
You can not miss it.
Where do I wait?
In the guest lounge.
Williamsburg Savings Bank.
We are ready to meet you now.
I see overdrafts
On your current account.
It seems that no deposits have been made.
A few months ago.
"Waxler" for mining.
Yes, I have been phoning them for weeks.
I did not get a satisfactory answer.
What about this foreclosure warning?
Yellow warning.
You must have defaulted.
My real estate mortgage tripled.
Between overnight.
I got a short promotion With a reduced
interest rate ended in January.
That's why they call it "short."
Right?
Because it does not last, is that logical?
The new interest rate is much higher,
So monthly payments jumped
To suddenly mortgage you.
We must clarify the possibility of
this happening When refinancing.
- You did it.
- I did what?
You sold me this nonsense.
"Joe Harding".
No. I know the name.
To review my remarks here only.
Terms and conditions are explained.
I personally explained.
The possibility of higher interest rates
During refinancing.
Do you remember that?
You told me.
The odds of exceeding the interest rate
For the basic financing price.
Very slim.
But it is possible.
But you have confirmed
that it is "very small".
- But I did not hide it "possible."
- Listen, "Chuck".
My granddaughter and daughter live with me.
My daughter is a nurse with low wages.
She wanted her daughter to go to a
better school, So dwell with me.
- Many do.
- Yes, as you see,
I can not lose my house.
Do not worry.
It is only yellow warning.
The red alert is the most dangerous.
Can I talk to someone else?
- With whom?
- With someone smarter?
Ladies and gentlemen, Thank
you for your attention.
We came for a withdrawal.
Excluding cashiers,
We would like to lie down on your back,
And lift up your arms and your feet
In the air like cats.
Let everyone land!
Camera 5.
Dear tellers,
Please do not act foolishly
They call the silent alarm.
Police men
They are the last to attend.
The situation will be messy, right?
Raise your hands.
Why is that?
My God, why here? What did you do?
You!
I follow the rules,
Follow the procedure only.
Just stay calm, stay calm.
- Follow the procedures.
- Hey!
You will be shot!
Dear Sir,
It is worth your while to remain silent.
I suffer from muscle spasm.
Please relax, you can sit down.
No! Not you!
In the position of the cat!
And keep putting money, come on.
You can take this.
I am sorry that you are the victim of a
corrupt regime No longer serve people.
Yes, I was saving my money
here 40 years ago. Games.
They only care about your account number.
There is not much in it,
but it's all yours.
No my friend, not you.
It is the duty of society
to care for the elderly.
This "Chuck" never cared.
"Chuck".
- Are you "Chuck"?
- Yes.
I "Chuck", I "Chuck".
Are you the one who will
take this man's house?
- No, not personally.
- Give me your wallet.
Well, I have... I have...
I have many cards here, we agreed?
Liquid money.
Membership is available in a gym.
Take it, I never go.
15 seconds.
Cutting position!
Shut up!
I am happy to say that our meeting is over.
Please do not tell the
police for ninety seconds.
The shooting does not end
Never happy ending.
They make pills to solve it.
"Go style."
This tattoo looks like a ring to me.
The details are many.
I think the artist of all
colors painted them.
If the shop found a snag,
You'll find the artist,
You will find a bank thief.
It seems to me a simple matter.
True, I thank you very much, old man.
We'll get you a job in the police.
Listen, I watch a television series.
Called "Lo and Order"
They solve crimes faster than you.
You should see it.
In the real world,
It takes longer to solve crimes
From an hour-long series.
I think that's all, Mr. Harding.
If we protest any additional information,
We'll call you.
I'll give you my address and phone number.
This is not necessary.
We will find you, this is our specialty.
So how did they look?
Their features are difficult to define.
They were hooded.
I approached one of them,
He was a 180 cm tall man.
He had a tattoo around his neck
I told you about it.
If they find the artist of shame.
- They will find the offender.
- Absolutely.
That's what I told them.
Well, I'm sure he is not supposed to
Talk about these things.
You must be present during a burglary
It was great.
Crime is not wonderful, my love.
He could have been shot.
Or worse.
What is worse than being shot?
Exposure to two rounds of fire.
These details traditionally indicate
To belong to a criminal gang.
We believe these individuals have been used
The artist himself.
If we find this artist, we
will find the criminal.
Bank robbery in Brooklyn -
Client "Heimer", FBI.
It's really simple.
- Hey, that's what we said.
- Are there other questions?
What a creep.
Pay attention to your words.
If you have any information
About the artist of shame.
Police draw for tattoo
I hit it!
"The three men left
With about $ 1.6 million."
Three hooded robbers steal 1.6 million.
"FBI and police 'New York'."
"They say they have no evidence right now."
and what?
No one is hurt only the insurance company,
They will be fine.
They were very quiet gentlemen.
They carried out the
operation very carefully.
Like a dance.
Yes, the "Kunga" dance is immediately
immersed in them In prison.
Will we play or what?
Ask the responsible man.
Milton?
Milton!
Who will play in the second arena?
Yeah.
"J52".
If my condition is as bad as it is,
They fired at me.
Did you receive one of these messages?
Department of Retirement.
She came in a registered mail.
Yes sir.
Have you ever received good news?
Need your signature?
Have you contacted anyone in the factory?
Not yet, but we'll
discover what's going on.
I need pension money.
Yes, we are all this man.
I have something very important to say.
"J52".
Let's go and help the old.
"Easy Rollers."
When we agreed to merge,
Simtek did not have the intention
To close factories in "America".
But with demand falling
On specialized pieces,
And the increasing cost of
production in this country,
They made a decision.
Transfer all manufacturing
operations to Vietnam.
Wixler Mining Company.
Operations of "Waxler" in "America".
Stops in stages within 30 days.
30 days? Are you kidding?
Hey guys, I understand it's tough news.
I can not address you
Unless you are calm.
Excuse me, Mr. Lewis.
Welcome Joe.
What does this mean?
What will happen to our pension?
"Simtech" for mining has been frozen.
All pension payments
During the transitional period.
What does that mean? Frozen?
Wixler kept a box.
To meet the retirement plans concluded
Prior to merger,
Which would eventually unite
With the new pension fund.
Under the new employment contract.
Heaven forbid, can you speak clearly?
With the cessation of US operations, There is no
longer any financial responsibility for SIMTEC.
The retirement fund will be dissolved.
With all my respect, "Donald"
30 years of hard work
Does not mean anything to you!
Restaurant "Nat".
Without retirement money, I will not
even be able to pay this month's rent.
We will appoint and sue a lawyer
For many money.
Damn, we'll be dead
Before we get the settlement money.
This fits them perfectly.
When did the price of
coffee become two dollars?
A decade ago.
If you request additional cream,
You will pay another amount.
Let's blow it by 20 percent.
She can now do a cruise.
Hey guys, I have half a fruit pie.
We have crispy cherry fritters,
But it is a bit old.
I have a pie with chocolate mousse,
What do you bring?
Not today, thank you.
You will not eat a pie?
We maintain our weights.
We are also bankrupt.
Well, do not book the table all day.
I have to earn my living here.
Did I tell you that those who took
over the bank They were carrying guns?
She told us six times already!
Yes, the details of the
incident do not leave my head.
I remember them over and over, do you know?
She may have a stroke.
Please guys, Always eat a pie.
Life is short.
Thanks for the ticket.
It's right.
We must take our share of the pie
And we eat it.
We have at least achieved this.
Good evening, sir. Good evening.
Welcome to the last concert
to present the rose.
Kaitlin, this is the
last rose of the night.
You count your genius!
My heart is beating hard in my chest now.
This week was... amazing.
"Sean" boring, and "Nick" punk man
Multi-Sexual Relationships.
Sincerity in relationships
Obsolete.
I am fond of this and very sexy.
"Ben", it's her only choice.
You will not move to a farm
With this high heel shoe.
I accepted them all, and used her tongue.
I did it with all the crew,
It's a mobile sex infection!
This week and the events that have passed.
Makes my decision seem impossible.
"Kaitlin," I shut your mouth.
"Nick".
- Haha!
- My God!
Shut it up, that's ridiculous.
They never learn.
I'll go home to arrange my drug.
I see you tomorrow.
It was a fantastic meal tonight.
It is impressive
What you can do with frozen fish.
The best garlic bread I've ever eaten.
And the mix of red pepper and garlic!
- Awesome!
In fact, I suspect the reason was mold.
Well, your night is wet.
"Joe".
What?
Will we be okay?
Certainly,
Things always end well.
Then one dies.
Thank you for your inspiration, Albert.
Your night is over, I'll see you tomorrow.
- The night of your night, "Joe".
- Your night.
Williamsburg Bank -
Stop payment warning.
The villains.
Hi Willie, how do you feel?
I'm not at your best, doctor.
I'm not the best.
Well, I will not lie to you.
You can lie, I do not mind.
Dialysis is no longer feasible.
You will only recover
with total cultivation.
I will look at "Ebay".
You are at the bottom of the list of
beneficiaries, Partly because of your age,
Partly because of your health insurance,
And partly.
Because it is difficult to get kidneys.
Yes, everyone clings to both of them.
Have you spoken to your daughter?
With your friends?
It is common to find a donor
Between your acquaintances.
They are usually available
Best match anyway.
I'll talk to them.
Sooner rather than later.
What are we talking about then?
"Fresnos" medical care.
It should be very urgent.
Hello?
Have you got your gift, Grandpa?
Have you sent anything?
"Skype."
Wait a little,
The courier brought me this box,
But it is inconceivable that it is a gift.
She is, she is!
Well, okay, relax, I'm an old man.
Oh my God.
This is the ugliest shirt I have ever seen.
Grand.
Well, let's also see what's here.
You grow up quickly, "Kay".
It grew two and a half centimeters
In a month, my grandfather.
Tell your mother.
That her career
It is not important to see her family.
I will.
- Are you mining me?
- I promise you.
A obedient girl.
- I got my car.
- Okay.
Disconnection.
Oh my God.
"Ezra"!
Must stop,
I can no longer listen.
I was working!
But that does not matter,
Your playing gets worse every week.
It is a miracle,
I do not know how to do this.
What is the feasibility?
I'm not smart, I do not like playing,
You will not become a professional.
I would like to end your case
Factor in a plant like me?
Each bimonthly party is held
For $ 40 in a bar?
Do not want it.
So I do not like this machine.
No, she does not love you either.
Trust me, I offer you service,
You will thank me for this.
Thanks sir.
Welcome and capacity.
I want to be a dancer, like Beyonce.
Well, that's none of my business.
Well, that's good.
Well, stay away from me.
Stay away, I'll look for your grandmother.
It still has to pay for the meeting.
Think about it
Like killing a sick horse.
Sometimes it is thinner
The most moral work you can do.
Well, thank you for your patience with me.
I really appreciate your honesty.
Your grandson does not
have any musical talent.
I know, listening to him was painful
From the other room.
I had to sit in front of him.
Well.
- "Al".
- What?
I never told you this,
But I saw you play a few times.
At West Village.
With Stan Goetz, 1977.
It was amazing.
You saw me play with "Getz"?
Three hundred fifty.
Certainly.
What? Did you follow me?
No, I was following music.
I'll see you in the store, we agreed?
See you at the store.
Yes.
Well.
See you tomorrow!
Goodbye guys.
You know what? At some point,
I would have to go home alone.
I am 14 years old.
I'm not there, love.
The neighborhood no longer
existed 40 years ago.
True, it has become safer
and more sophisticated.
Look
and what is that?
It is a test of biology.
Another day, another excellent estimate.
Well done, my little one.
I almost realized the meaning.
What do you mean?
You told me, I quote from your words,
"If you excel in all materials,
You'll get a puppy."
I like your confidence.
I must have inherited
it from you young man.
Not bad my pet, Not bad at all.
"Knights of Hudson"
Buffet for $ 4 on Thursdays.
Happy birthday, young man.
I did not expect you to buy
me a present, you bastard.
Lighten your enthusiasm.
Not expensive.
This is exactly what you need.
Yes.
One does not get enough time.
Look at that nice picture.
Yes, my pet is "Kay".
When you die,
You can pass it on as a memory.
Thank you, "Al".
I trust she will not want a
picture of herself On an hour.
Of her dead grandfather.
Look at her, she's really special.
Sure, boy.
This atom looks like World War II.
Corn?
I thought it...
I do not know what I thought.
I think I would like to steal a bank.
What did you say?
I'm thinking of robbing a bank.
I'm thinking of buying a Ferrari.
They chose me to play with the Knicks team,
A good week for all?
A good week.
They will take my house.
30 days ahead.
Who will take your home?
A bank.
They will take your house and not tell us?
What will you do? You lend me money?
We are all bankrupt,
The three of us are together.
Those banks have practically
destroyed this country.
The dreams of many have been crushed.
And it does not hurt them at all.
We are three elderly men,
If we are bankrupt and bankrupt,
We will retire with dignity.
At worst, they will catch us,
And we get a bed
And three meals a day.
And health care
Better than that we have now.
Are you talking about us?
You and you?
Yes, if a band of thieves succeed,
It is not very difficult.
I lost your mind.
I spent 20 years
Waiting for death, "Al".
Without a life or a goal.
Will bank robbery give me a goal?
I will give you money.
Willy will be able to ride a plane
And seeing his granddaughter.
It's hard to catch up with airplanes
From prison, "Joe".
Yes, but we will not be caught.
They were not arrested.
Well, they were young.
They were fast.
We have skills, experience,
and intelligence.
Arthritis and gout
And neuropathy.
Wish you wish "Willie".
Happy birthday, "Willie".
Hello?
Just lie here,
I think of all the wishes of my birthday
Over the years.
And how many of them remained secret.
None of them has been realized.
It does not seem to ever materialize.
So risk me
To tell you this is my "Joe".
I mean, what's the worst that might happen?
Nothing at all, right?
You do not have what, "Willy."
I want to live better than I do now.
I want to see my family
more than once a year.
From now on,
I want to eat a pie whenever I want.
Do you understand what I mean?
I agree with you heart and soul.
I was serious today.
I think so.
Actually,
We have nothing to lose.
I'm not a thief, Joe.
Neither do I.
We will take exactly what they owe us
From the retirement account, right?
That's all I want.
And no penny increase.
I pledge that.
Awakened "Al".
Slow down.
"Al".
"Albert"!
Lift the headset!
Who died?
No one, it's "Joe".
I do not talk to criminals.
Did you hear that?
I close the line, I'll call back.
What do you want?
But what do you want, "Al"?
I want to withdraw quietly,
Or are you walking in a noisy way?
I have no problem with death.
But I do not want to die while in prison.
No one will enter the prison.
What is going on here exactly?
Both lost his mind.
Think about it, "Al".
I do not want to think about anything,
I am not a bank robber.
Neither are you, nor are you, "Willie."
What?
Why did you answer the phone?
Because he was ringing.
Because you're interested.
Have you become my psychiatrist now?
But closer to a fortune-teller.
So I know I'll end the call now.
I'll see you tomorrow, "Al."
Happy dreams.
Do not call back.
Well Hey "Willie",
To master the basics first.
Expiration dates are written
In a tiny line.
Take this, I bought two at a price.
Good chicken thighs
Discounted rates.
I can prepare Cordon Bleu.
The Mets team or the Yankees?
Do not congratulate.
New York...
Two beautiful hats.
We have a business here, "Al."
Well, what do you mean?
Give me that menu.
What are you doing?
Wait here, we'll be right back.
What do you do with my list?
Why did you rip my list?
Why should I wait in the car?
Wait in the damn car!
Why?
I do not want to stay in the car,
The atmosphere is hot here!
"Joe", "Joe"!
Behind the bread cut cans.
"Joe", I'll get barbecue.
We need chicken,
We will prepare the Cordon Bleu.
I do not want Cordon Bleu.
Stick to the plan!
Welcome to Valeo.
Hello, "Al".
Hi Annie.
What do you want to buy?
It was planned
Preparation of "Cordon Bleu" chicken,
But the plan seems to be changing.
I have to bring some chicken thighs.
Let me help you.
"Gold Middle"
Accurate and versatile.
Service table BBQ meat.
Give me the big piece.
The whole piece?
The whole piece.
You have what you want.
"Annie," let me carry the basket.
Barbak, you have your own business now.
No, no, this is my work, no problem.
There is a voucher
Multiplied by the ad.
The price is like thighs, but as you see,
These are chicken breasts.
The breasts are better than the thighs,
do not you think so?
I do not mind either.
Pork.
It looks delicious.
Do you like pork?
Well.
This will fit perfectly with.
This is a big bottle.
Yes, listen, I must tell you this.
You are a wonderful woman,
But I know what you are doing.
You are wasting your time,
I do not want a relationship with anyone.
I did not offer you a relationship.
Well, great, so we agree.
Security to foreign foods
department please.
We will discuss this later.
I look forward to it.
Where is my basket in hell?
"Willie", "Willie".
Al disappeared.
I have a new escape car.
Where did you come from?
Stolen.
Skip in Cart.
Who do you think? "ET"?
"Willie", jump in the damned basket.
I will not ride in the basket!
They follow us.
You, stop your place!
Hey! Stop!
- Stop!
- Why do you haunt me?
Stop!
I first heard you.
Do not force me to be dumbfounded!
This is not a confession of guilt!
I'm just tired.
We must get rid of some weight.
Get rid of the damn pork pudding.
What?
Flour, Flour.
Stop!
I think we can get ahead of the signal.
No, the signal will not precede you, Joe.
Hey!
No, "Joe",
Can not precede the signal!
Appreciate that the signal precedes!
We will do it!
- Will not precede the signal!
- Yes, we will!
Do not take another step.
I no longer know what is
happening in the world.
You will prepare "Cordon Bleu"
Chicken thighs?
This is a crime in itself.
I have nothing to say from my side.
Look what you did with "Cindy".
She now looks like a
Colombian drug trafficker.
Never happened
all my life.
That someone stole
Full pork pudding.
What was your mother to say?
Perform a major operation or go home.
The thief must have been black.
And why did you do it?
She did not steal anything.
Because your Nazi officer was chasing me.
No, they were clinging to your friend.
He was chasing me,
When someone comes after me, I run away.
Thus do things.
Listen, you are old.
I will become like you after 40
or 50 years, I understand that.
Take it.
These are some coupons.
We will double it on Tuesday,
But I'm sure you already know that.
So, do not steal, this is wrong.
If you stole, do not steal
from the Valley Town.
Yes, I have two great friends.
You made me a partner
in the crime of theft.
We did not ask you to do anything.
I brought you here. I'll take you,
so I'm the driver of the escape.
Do not give yourself greater than its size.
Leading like my grandmother,
She was driving a horse and cart.
This is a good joke, so you can go back
Walk home.
Do not touch my car.
You will not force us to walk!
I will certainly challenge you.
Lord, you will be great bank robbers.
They catch you stealing from Valle Town!
I hate him when he is right.
We will need the help of a professional.
Do you think so?
Yes, without it
We should turn ourselves in now.
Do you know any criminals?
I know a poor person.
- I do not speak English.
- I know that you are, "Murphy".
What are you doing here, Joe?
I came over the expense of
the girl you do not pay.
Did not I get rid of you divorce, "Joe"?
Open the door.
"Strawberry K" - "O Gosh Kush" -
"Bad Beach."
"Maui and Howe".
"Bad Beach".
"Coconut Bleubery".
"Or Josh Kush".
How are these things legal?
Dear Sir, The embargo period is over.
Marijuana has extraordinary
medical benefits.
It is useful in all situations.
Anxiety, pain, seizures, and tension.
Anxiety, pain, and seizures.
What is your position now?
Currently, anxiety.
"Joe," I do not mean to be rude
With family members.
Former family members.
As you say, but what do you want from me?
We have a project, and we need help.
What kind of projects?
In fact, we prefer not to tell you.
This is difficult for me to help you.
We need to find someone
Doing evil deeds.
Why do you think I know
Such people?
I thought that like you
They mix with the likes of them.
Like me? I mean businessmen?
No, but the abject.
Debt evaders.
I trust you can guide us.
To the right path.
What did he get?
He thinks.
This sounds painful.
I know this,
But I've seen him do it before.
The reason is drugs, you know?
Yes, of course.
"Value Town."
This asshole is a fool.
I wish I could shock this old man.
Here is the fruit of the eggplant.
Welcome.
- Hi Annie.
- Hello!
You work here every day,
Do not you have a day off?
No, I work every day.
Rabah, you have a difficult work program.
What will you do with this eggplant fruit?
I was thinking about preparing
a stew of vegetables.
I love slicing them into thin slices
With parmesan cheese.
They drink all the juices.
Well, this looks good.
You will not taste anything worse.
I'm sure of that, listen.
I think you are nice, and I
find you very attractive.
- You think I'm attractive.
- You are very nice.
I think that's great.
But you're not looking for
a relationship, right?
This is absolutely true.
This is quite clear, "Al".
Would you like to have
dinner with me someday?
What should I do?
I do not think you hear me!
I hear you very well.
Do you know my opinion?
I think we owe ourselves
To live every day we have.
I feel I really want
Get to know you more.
I share a meal with you.
What? What's up dear?
I have a partner in housing.
I have my own home.
- "Annie".
- What?
A wonderful parmesan mining with parmesan.
Thanks.
Of the best quality.
Eggs, sausages, fried potatoes,
Roasted bread and coffee please.
"Good morning, 'Metzi',
Your hair looks nice today."
"Did you cut your hair?"
"Yes, O 'Al, ' his story."
"Do you know what I want?"
"I do not know 'Al', what?"
"Metzee", you find Babe,
And your smell is amazing.
Now bring me some food,
Because I am starving.
Well, that's better.
I did not think you would join us today.
I am old to carry a grudge.
This has never stopped you from doing so.
Talk to you.
Look! It's a newspaper article!
"The Wixler Fund for
Retirement and its Assets.
"Will be distributed to
existing creditors".
They use our retirement funds to pay bills.
And that's not all, look at this.
"Williamsburg Bank,
Liquidation of funds,
"And restructuring the debts of 'Wixler'".
- It's my bank.
- And my bank also.
And my bank too!
They steal our retirement money!
This is what is written.
I worked for that damned company 40 years,
Now they will steal our pension funds.
Take it from here, I'm not hungry.
Would you take him home?
As an external request?
No, no, call it here.
I will not allow anyone
Take something from me anymore.
Do you know "Al"?
It's hard to understand today.
I will not go back to your table.
Do not leave an ink-stamp with coins.
I'm not a washing machine.
I'm OK, I want to steal that bank.
It's a good place to hack
it like anywhere else.
Well, how do we start?
Contact the man who deals with him
My previous month.
Why will it help us?
Because it seems.
These are the best mariguana
In Brooklyn.
Rabah, it's like a pillow.
Yes, but it's a pillow you can smoke.
Dear Sirs, Let us go and
retrieve our money.
I agree with you.
Yes!
Williamsburg Savings Bank.
"Camio" for pets -
Tropical fish - and birds.
Why should I help you?
25 percent, it is not a small amount.
I can steal a bank myself
And reap a hundred percent.
I'm sure of that, but these are easy money.
Without any risk, just the bonus.
Let us know and get your pay.
"Murphy" prepares it properly!
This Marijuana is wonderful.
Are you from the police?
We are practically in the eighties of age.
I do not know you at all.
How do you know "Jesus"
Do you deserve trust?
No, you can trust us.
What speeches?
What do you think of these men?
What do you think?
What do you think? Tell me.
Are they good or bad?
Can I carry it?
Do you want to go to it?
He says he does not mind.
He drinks the whole bottle.
A small dog.
I found him in a ditch.
- No!
- Yes.
People have no pity these days.
Why do you think you can succeed?
I do not know, we saw that we try.
"I do not know, we saw that we try."
You may be imprisoned for life,
It is not long for you.
But you should think, old man,
You must know.
This is not like sitting on a bench
in a park He played the Bingo.
I hear, he shouted.
I am in need of your abuse.
The world hurts me enough.
Within 20 days,
There will be no roof for me.
Social security check is worthless,
And the pension went into the wind.
The three of us will carry out the process.
If you want 25 percent for our help,
There is nothing wrong with it.
But if you do not want to.
Keep your hobbies to yourself!
It was a good speech, O owner.
Will it help us?
Do you have any snacks?
"Willie"?
I like the air blowing in my face.
And I too.
Oh my God!
Look, we have two novice addicts here.
I think I'll get a recipe for her.
And I too.
"Knights of Had."
This food is excellent tonight.
They must have changed recipes.
It's the same nonsense, but you're too.
Do you mind?
Take them both.
Well.
How much do you have to live, "Willie"?
I do not know.
He guessed.
Two or three years?
That's it? Looks great health!
It's just a feeling, you asked me.
What about you?
In my opinion, seven years.
What about you, "Al"?
I have a bad luck,
I'll probably live up to 100.
So, you can throw away both of us.
OK.
So 27 years in total.
Our retirement rate is $ 45,000 per year.
We will steal from the bank two million
And 215 thousand dollars.
Hey, what if we steal more?
We will donate it to a charity.
Yes, but what if we stole less?
I do not want to steal him twice.
"Camio" for pets.
Look, that's our bank there.
Wait a moment, steal your bank?
It's a personal matter.
Well, we'll skip the first lesson.
What was the first lesson?
Never steal your bank.
So we'll move on to the second lesson.
20 days
I have 20 days before I lose my house.
Bank robbery is a work of art.
Can for ten people
Stealing the place with ten methods.
You have to find a plan that suits you.
The cameras are here and here.
One entrance.
One emergency exit.
Proper car escape is very important.
Find a car that does not raise suspicions.
Car Escape.
Learn how to operate a car without a key.
Put them together like this.
Like magic.
16 days.
Improve your fitness.
Good.
You must have excellent physical fitness.
Now I realize that you are old.
This is amazing.
But under those masks,
You should feel
You are twenty years old.
Wait!
Absence argument.
This is vital.
You must have a strong absence argument.
Wednesday the 15th of the month?
It's a fundraising night in the shelter.
A strong absence argument.
Committee selling shirts.
Do we have volunteers to sell shirts?
Put down your hands please in the back.
We are looking for volunteers
for the T-shirts committee.
We volunteer, Milton.
10 days.
Well.
Each drawer is a cashier
Contains dye packs and tracking devices.
Dye packages and tracking devices.
They will give you one of them if they can,
But they will not endanger anyone's life
To do this.
Get equipment.
"Salerno" for surgical equipment.
Wixler Mining Company.
Average police response time
Toward an ongoing robbery.
Ranging from 2 minutes to 4 minutes,
According to the proximity of the
police unit From the crime scene.
And the number of other
policemen at the scene.
Everything is on the Internet.
Set the timing clock to 2 minutes.
And practiced as if it
were the actual operation.
4 minutes 54 seconds.
Now, you are sitting
In the back of a police car.
Your weapons exist only in anticipation
For the worst scenarios.
You must master the shooting,
But the last thing you want
Is to shoot one.
Who guards the door?
I will, I will guard the door.
Do you know how to deal with a pistol?
Made 300 shirts.
Five days.
Whenever you enter,
You become better.
When the time comes.
You will come out of that bank
And with you the amount of money.
You have never seen her.
Very easily.
The police might be late.
One day.
Attica! Attica! Attica!
Attica! Attica!
I do not want to see the end of the film.
Yes, things did not go well.
How can he sleep?
He's having sex.
True.
I remember that feeling.
Are you fine?
Yes, I am at best.
And I too.
No one will be hurt.
That's true.
If we are involved in a problem,
We'll get out of there.
That's right, yes.
If the police come, we will lie down.
We raise our hands up.
Maximum 2 minutes.
Maximum, increase or decrease.
Take a nap, young man.
Well, you too, young man.
Do not let the omelet touch the fruit,
She loves them separately.
Do you do this every day?
- Every day.
- Do not cheat.
Not fooled.
I wish my father had done this to me.
And your daughter wishes that too.
What are you doing here?
It's breakfast for Brock.
I see it, but why?
I teach him, he makes an
effort to be a father.
Good morning.
Your father prepared breakfast for you.
O hell!
- On your messenger!
- Pay attention to your words.
Sorry.
Your father will take you
out of school today.
Have you become a believer
or something like that?
I doubt that, but he realized
what he was missing.
Yes, this week.
He is not good at ending things.
I give him a chance, my dear, for my sake.
Surely "Joe",
But only because you are my best friend.
I love you, my little girl.
You will achieve a lot in life.
What is your story today?
Do you have cancer or something like that?
No, I'm as strong as a bull.
Well.
It's carnival day, I have many tasks.
Yes, I will come after school.
Yes, I'll bring you fried dumplings
Bear your name.
Well, you guarantee me a bit,
I love you too.
Go and achieve success.
I will do, young man.
See you later,
Dad.
I was bothering you
Long ago, "Murphy".
I think I deserved it.
Most often.
This is the smartest thing you
have ever said in your life.
Listen, Joe.
Whatever you do,
You do not have to.
There is always another way.
It is my business, boy,
Forget that you know.
In the end, if I do not,
You have to take responsibility.
I can no longer cover you.
You are a father.
You must take responsibility
She acts like a man.
Even if you have to pretend to do so.
Well.
Welcome to Carnival,
Donations of "Nets" charity!
Well, sir, let us mix with the crowds.
Three consecutive injuries
You get an award!
Hello, "Polly"
Is the weather hot enough for you?
It's a perfect day.
I have to check with the ticket office.
Be sensible.
I will not be wise, but I will be careful.
2.14 pm.
Well, thanks.
You are famous.
Yes, the reason is cocaine.
Do you sell cocaine?
I was joking, Milton.
Well, that's very funny.
Stay here,
I have to check the karaoke machine.
I can not,
Go to the Yarn Girls' Booth.
"Milton," you are in it now.
It's okay, you'd better not know.
The shop is closed, run out of cocaine.
Leave.
Mobile toilet.
Fear Factory.
Watch out inside,
There are many monsters.
Be careful, watch out for your steps.
Time to work!
I'll go, Sam.
- Where did they go?
- I do not know!
I thought they were with you!
2.30 pm
I decided to use empty shots.
No one should be hurt by mistake.
There are none left now, boys.
You guys,
I have had a wonderful time
In planning to steal with you.
There is no better of you
to do this with him.
I agree with you.
And I too.
Williamsburg Savings Bank
2.45 pm.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This is a real robbery.
Lie down, do not breathe.
Do not move.
Do not touch the silent alarm.
Unless you want
To pierce your head.
Lie down, you big!
Throw your gun away.
Well guys, We'll get out of
your life two minutes later.
Move, Blue Eyes.
Here we are.
Dear tellers,
Please stand up and open your windows.
Ten seconds.
No dye packs or tracking devices.
Do you understand?
No tracking devices,
Do not pack dyes, do not try to manipulate.
Yes sir Sinatra.
No one will be hurt. Ten thirty 00: 59:
47,462 -> 00: 59: 48,84220 seconds.
Thank you.
Go ahead, madam.
Do not try to manipulate,
Do you understand what I mean?
Yes, yes.
Put all the money, son.
30 seconds.
Give me everything you have.
You can take it, sir.
40 seconds.
Hey, stick to the plan.
To all units,
They went to Williamsburg.
There is a theft,
I repeat, there is a process of theft.
Min!
I do not want to take your
blood, my sweetheart.
When my granddaughter was like your age,
She had one like her.
What's her name?
Well, my dear, this guy.
He has a job to do.
His work stealing banks?
No, my dear,
I try to see my family more.
Stupid.
What's going on?
Are you okay sir
I will need some help.
He will need some help.
Oh heaven!
I'll do it.
Stay where you are.
Oh my God!
"Lucy"!
His mask is too hot on him.
Thank you my love, thank you.
I can not breathe
When I wear masks, too.
You are very nice.
Two minutes.
The police.
What is going on in Heaven?
Can you get out of here?
Yes, I'm fine.
It's time, boy.
Stay at school, girl.
Do not shoot the banks, do you hear me?
Come on!
Quickly!
This is my bank!
Are you crazy?
Do not move! I do not move?
I'm not telling me not to move,
You do not move!
I will not be a victim anymore.
Ask them not to move too.
They can hear you well.
What plan now?
I work on one.
Lift up your hands.
And leave the money.
Well, after three seconds,
I will shoot you.
What?
I will respond to you by shooting!
Is this your plan?
One!
Two!
The next figure is three!
I can count.
He will shoot us.
Three!
You are a failure in the
correction, O shouted.
Now you will meet your Creator.
Oh my God!
It's empty shots you idiot.
Well guys, enemy of 90 descending
Loud.
Do not stand until we get out of here.
Start counting!
90, 89, 88, 87, 86..
2.49 pm.
What's up, Willy?
Nothing, I felt a bit tired,
I'm fine.
It was a very bad time
to get a panic attack!
I'm sorry.
No need for this.
The hard part is over.
It is time for the big conclusion.
3.17 pm.
Taxi! Taxi!
Not bad.
To Astoria, Queens, please.
City bus "New York".
It will not stop soon.
He will lose consciousness in the end.
Dear Sir,
Do you want some sweetening?
What kind of pancakes do you have?
Lemon cake,
Plant gourd, cherry and mango.
One slice of each.
And more champagne.
Yes, more champagne.
I'll get the champagne then.
No more wine for you.
Prove your place, you can not bear wine.
The reason is not wine.
What? Hey, why not wine?
You can call an ambulance please?
I beg you?
What hurts you, "Willie"?
Everything.
Oh my God.
Heck.
The place is wet.
Call an ambulance!
It happened quickly.
Federal Bureau of Investigation.
Near the picture.
Fix the frame there.
African-American?
It seems so.
It must be at least
In the late 1960s.
Take static photos of others.
I want to publish it everywhere.
Did not he ever talk about it?
He did not say anything.
He hides his affairs a lot.
He is extremely emotional.
Willy suffers from kidney failure.
Needs total cultivation.
What will happen if he does not?
Let's say he will not leave
the hospital without her.
They must have been young and flexible.
They were shot several times,
They managed to avoid all the shots.
I work there a month ago,
The bank has been robbed twice.
I think I'll go back to my previous job
As a waiter in a cafe,
Where the opportunity is less to be exposed
For a fire.
All I can say, Is thank god Ali!
It was a heroic day.
Hello!
We are famous.
But better.
Lower your voice,
We have not been out of danger yet.
So what's going on, Willie?
Do not talk to us,
Do not tell us you're sick.
We are friends, we must stand together.
This is my business.
Your business? It's your business.
The word "Joe", I can not.
Old, selfish.
I do not understand, "woe".
I was to give you my kidney last week.
Most likely it does not suit me.
I used to give it to you anyway.
We are friends, "Willy".
We're supposed to take
care of each other, right?
Let's take care of you, we agreed?
Waiting area.
The suspects are armed and dangerous,
Probably in the late 1960s
Or the early 1970s.
They were disguised as Triple Rat,
Customer "Heimer" - Crime
Investigation Division.
"Dean Martin",
Frank Sinatra and Sami Davies Gunner.
Let's go from here.
Published by the FBI
This tape is for burglary.
If you have information,
Please call the number shown on the screen.
I knew as soon as I saw the watch bar
Of the bank.
Same length and weight.
Many match these specifications.
Yes, but who runs that way?
We'll need a copy of this video.
I have a copy here.
I think there is a reward.
Reward?
Yes, I need money,
My grandmother was arrested last night.
You know how it is, right, brother?
- "Annie".
- Yes.
I must speak with you.
I lost this age yesterday.
Did the tooth fairy come?
She brought me five dollars.
Five... You are a renegade.
You know that the most I've ever gotten
Is a quarter of a dollar?
You can not buy anything anymore
A quarter of a dollar, my grandfather.
My presence and nothing.
"Willie"?
These guys are with the FBI.
FBI?
They must have brought me all together.
Third successful strike!
Well done, girl.
Yes!
This is my girl!
New York police
I have to go to the toilet.
Well.
That was great, Brock.
Here's my opinion.
An old man finds himself
Amid a bank robbery,
This makes him feel thrilled.
He thinks of himself,
"I can steal a bank."
"I'm smart."
"I have nothing to lose."
"What's the worst that might happen?"
"I can spend the rest of my life."
"In a prison like a country club
Without paying rent."
Have you gone to school to do this work?
Well, Mr. Garner,
You seem to have disappeared for an hour.
Between 2.30 and 3.30 pm.
At the same time
Carried out by three elderly men.
Stole $ 2.3 million.
Of the Williamsburg Savings Bank.
Amazing, what a great profit.
I was working in a house of terror
Between 2 and 4 pm?
That's what I said.
Did you never leave that game?
Just to enter it.
I got up as usual, at six in the morning.
I accompanied my granddaughter to school.
As I do every day.
It's a fairly new relationship,
So we spend a lot of time together.
Lennar, in the early morning,
We practiced love twice.
No.
Three times.
That was all.
Annie Santuri.
Then we got up, and I had fried pies.
Then I put on my clothes.
I get dressed,
I ate breakfast at the Nat restaurant.
I go there.
A few times a week at least.
For years, he has been
a permanent customer.
Do you meet one of them?
I am married and have two children.
Take digital, things usually happen.
I wore my clothes.
The cards were collected
for the gaming booth.
I am in the fundraising committee,
Well guys, good luck to all of us.
It's time to get into the bag.
I went to the park about a second.
I spoke with my friend
"Paul" for a few minutes,
Then you run one of the ticket booths.
The tickets.
Hello Tony.
Good evening.
I brought you a gift.
Thank you "Joe", you need a hat.
I stayed there during most
of the Carnival period.
They will all say they bought it
From an old handsome.
He wears a gray hat.
Then we went to the festival,
I was working in a girls' spinning booth
Until the second,
Then a local solution Mr. "Milton Kubchak".
Al was there all day.
At 2.30 pm?
- Who?
- "Al"?
"Garner"?
Yes.
Is he here?
You know what? At the
girls' spinning booth,
Try to sell some cocaine.
I am ready to give my testimony.
Children love horror houses.
Frankenstein is one of
their favorite characters.
I must have been there
More than an hour.
Yes, I've had stomach problems for years
Due to over-drinking.
It is called inflammation
of the intestines,
Says the doctor
I have to remove part of my colon.
I do not like that idea very much.
So, between approximately
2.30 and 3.30 hours,
You are.
In the toilet?
Yes.
It's boring,
But I take what I always read with me.
Helps to spend time.
After that, I met my girlfriend,
And we sing along with the karaoke machine.
Wixler Mining Company.
Admission allowed.
What happens then?
Oh my God!
Watch out!
Do you mind washing my dirty clothes?
Absolutely.
Overall,
It was a nice day at the Carnival.
Hate your best blow.
Water basin They made a spray!
Awesome!
A coherent story, Mr. Harding.
Makes it easy to remember the truth.
Yes, almost perfect.
But let me tell you
something about criminals.
They always make a silly mistake.
Spoil their entire scheme.
I want you to go with me
On a trip Hey Harding.
Get out of the gym,
There is official work.
What is this right?
Get out the back door there.
Well, come on guys, quickly, come on.
Fast, fast.
Here, stand by them.
I want you to start that
guy there, we agreed?
Look well at his face.
I do not see him.
What?
It is not here.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
I have a wonderful memory.
Listen, do you want to look again?
Not really.
Can I go home now?
Yes.
Restaurant "Nat"
I thought you would not come.
Well, here I am.
What good dish are they
offering here, Joey?
Nothing really.
Why come then?
I love bad coffee.
Yes, I understand that.
He got all his vaccines.
Dog, tuberculosis, pordetaila,
And you singled out.
All sheets are organized.
Have you taken your share?
No, not from you.
It is the duty of society
to care for the elderly.
Where is the tattoo?
It's a temporary tattoo, my friend.
See a person with a weak look
A picture he can not forget.
The police will look for years.
This tattoo looks like
a ring in my opinion.
If we find this artist, we
will find the criminal.
Police draw for tattoo.
This is impressive.
It is a tragedy.
FBI directly behind you.
Customer "Heimer".
Do you want to drink bad coffee?
I have an allergy of milk, Mr. Harding.
I left these in the evidence room.
How did you find me?
That's what I do.
I find people.
This is my friend "Jesus".
It houses dogs.
Private client "Heimer",
From the FBI.
"Jesus Garcia", from the
neighborhood of "Queens".
Will you adopt a dog, Mr. Harding?
Yes, it's my granddaughter.
She excelled at school.
This is awesome.
I love puppies.
Do you mind?
He may be asleep.
It's okay, I will not wake him up.
O heaven,
Are not you a small pet?
Let me look at you with your wrinkled face.
When I was young,
I grew up with Boulder Cooley dogs.
This breed is wonderful,
I love the Coley Border dogs.
Yes, it's great.
Yes, come here, little one.
It is small and silvery.
Well, come here, little one.
Yes, come here.
You little villain.
Watch out, his teeth are still growing.
Yes.
You should be careful of his sharp teeth.
Thanks.
We do not want you to bleed to death.
I have to take this young man home.
Before my granddaughter
returned from school.
What a nice surprise to her.
You will be surprised a lot.
Do you have a dog now client "Heimer"?
No, the reason is practical.
Long working hours.
I can not do this with an animal.
OK,
Take this young man to his new home.
Hugs and kisses Young.
You annoy me with these quarters.
Someone left this gift.
Great piece.
Cut them off.
"Everyone deserves his share of the pie."
Everyone deserves his share of pie!
Sorry, Mr. "Garner".
You are not stronger than this.
I'm not solid.
I am a very sensitive person.
I will be honest with you.
I do not want to die today.
This is new.
But if I die, I want to say.
You were a great classmate and friend.
For 25 years.
25 years? Has all this time passed?
Looks like 25 days, right?
Yes.
Under water.
Good teaser.
Well, sir, we'll start.
They say in life.
Come here!
If you are lucky, you will get
On a couple of wonderful friends.
People are standing by you to the end.
You grow up together,
You see and do everything together,
They laugh and cry together.
"Al Garner"
He was one of those people to me.
There will not be many men like him.
Someone willing to risk everything
For others.
Ready to make a nice word.
Or college.
With complaint about it all the time.
That's you.
This is not entirely true.
- "Annie".
- Yes.
It's your problem now.
Thanks.
Good luck, may you enjoy
Every moment of your time together.
We love you.
We love you also, young man.
We toast you all!
We toast you!
To clap the bride and their names!
I will adjust my expectations, Joey.
What do you mean?
I may live another twenty years.
Not with college "Al".
You will live for ten years at most.
It's OK, I'll accept that.
He has come.
What speeches?
My face hurts me,
I have not smiled like this all my life.
So? How do you feel?
What?
You are married, you idiot.
I do not know how this happened.
I do not even remember asking for her hand.
It's wonderful.
I mean, it's exciting,
We practice love a lot.
She is a brilliant cook.
And love me as I am.
So I do not like myself as I am.
Everything is stunning,
But I have to admit.
I have a strange feeling,
I think it might be happiness.
Your cup has been officially filled.
"Go style."
"Go style"