[BIRDS TWITTERING]
ABIGAIL!
WHEN ARE YOU GOING
TO LEARN
TO COME
WHEN YOU'RE CALLED?
ABIGAIL!
OH!
[GIGGLES]
THERE YOU ARE.
I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW THAT
WHEN I WAS A FURLING,
I COULDN'T WAIT TO GET
TO CORNELIUS' CLASS.
YES, DADDY.
AT LEAST HE'S
TAUGHT YOU TO BEHAVE.
I'M GLAD YOU STOPPED
CLIMBING TREES.
YES, DADDY.
SEE YOU LATER.
LOVE YOU.
ME, TOO, ABIGAIL.
[CHILDREN TALKING]
WAIT, THAT'S
MY FINGER! OW! OW!
[CHILDREN SHOUTING]
MOM.
THEY WON'T GIVE ME
A CHANCE FOR BREAKFAST.
WELL, YOU'LL JUST HAVE
TO BE QUICKER, ROLAND.
I'M NOT ROLAND,
MOTHER.
I'M RUSSELL.
RUSSELL.
NO, NO, YOU COULDN'T
BE RUSSELL.
HE'S AT FURLING CLASS.
CLASS?!
[BELL RINGING]
HOLD ON.
ALMOST DONE.
MAMA, CORNELIUS HAS A BIG
SURPRISE PLANNED FOR TODAY,
AND YOU'RE
MAKING ME LATE.
NOW HOLD STILL, EDGAR.
I'M ALMOST FINISHED.
WELL, I...
DON'T I EVEN GET
A GOOD-BYE KISS?
NO TIME.
I'LL KISS YOU
WHEN I GET BACK.
[DING DING]
GUESS WHAT!
YOU'RE NEVER GOING
TO GUESS, I BETCHA.
UNCLE CORNELIUS SAID
I COULD GO WITH YOU
ON YOUR RAMBLE TODAY,
BUT SINCE YOU LATEYS HAVE
PROBABLY FORGOTTEN ALL ABOUT IT,
I'LL NEVER, EVER GET TO SEE
WHAT THE BIG SURPRISE IS.
WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?
MY DAD.
MY MOTHER.
NO BREAKFAST.
COME ON.
WE'D BETTER HURRY.
IF UNCLE CORNELIUS ASKS,
TELL HIM IT ISN'T MY FAULT
YOU'RE LATE.
[CLOCK TICKING]
[HUMMING]
[WHISPERING ]
Good. He's busy.
[CRASH]
THINK HE'LL NOTICE
WE'RE LATE?
HEY!
WHERE'S CORNELIUS?
Shh! He's
experimenting.
On the big surprise,
I betcha.
Oh, I love surprises.
Let's have a look.
DON'T TAKE
ANOTHER STEP.
FURLINGS,
PREPARE
TO BE AMAZED.
Furlings: WOW!
OOH!
IT'S REALLY FLYING!
LOOK! IT'S
COMING THIS WAY!
WOW!
OH, WOW!
WELL,
WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO SAY?
UH...
SORRY
WE'RE LATE?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
ABOUT THIS.
MY LIFE'S WORK.
THE FLAPPER
WINGAMATHING.
OF COURSE, THIS IS ONLY
A TEST MODEL.
[BONES CRACK]
OH!
ONE DAY, I SHALL
BUILD IT FULL-SIZE.
IT'S WONDERFUL,
CORNELIUS.
RUSSELL, YOUR MOUTH
IS HANGING OPEN.
I WANT TO FLY IT NEXT.
PLEASE.
DON'T BE SILLY.
YOU'LL CRASH IT.
CORRECT,
ABIGAIL.
IT'S FAR TOO DELICATE
FOR FURLINGS.
HUH?
I DIDN'T
MEAN ME.
HO HO HO HO HO!
ME! ME!
LET'S HAVE ANOTHER GO,
SHALL WE?
[FURLINGS SHOUTING]
OH, DEAR.
FURLINGS!
NO, RUSSELL!
NO!
Abigail:
THERE IT GOES.
NO, FURLINGS!
TH-THAT'S DELICATE!
MY BOOKS!
ABIGAIL, NOT THAT!
YIPPEE!
WHOA!
Cornelius:
CATASTROPHE!
[LAUGHING]
CATCH IT,
UNCLE CORNELIUS.
OH, NO!
NO! NO!
[LAUGHING]
HUH?
LOOK, I THINK
IT'S SLOWING DOWN.
IT'S GOING THAT WAY!
Abigail:
HERE IT COMES!
I GOT IT.
I GOT IT!
AHH!
[GASPS]
UNCLE CORNELIUS,
YOUR MOUTH
IS HANGING OPEN.
GREAT HONK!
LOOK WHAT YOU'VE DONE!
All: SORRY, CORNELIUS.
WELL, FURLINGS,
THERE ARE TIMES
WHEN WE OF SCIENCE
MUST
LEARN TO ACCEPT...
SETBACKS.
LOOKS LIKE ONE OF THOSE
TIMES, DOESN'T IT?
I GUESS WE WRECKED
THE BIG SURPRISE, HUH?
NO. YOU WRECKED MONTHS
AND MONTHS OF WORK!
THE BIG SURPRISE
IS AWAITING US
ON OUR RAMBLE.
OH. GIVE ME STRENGTH.
NOW...
NOW,
LET'S HURRY ALONG
BEFORE WE HAVE
ANY MORE...SETBACKS.
STEP LIVELY,
FURLINGS.
WAIT FOR US!
LEFT, RIGHT.
[GIGGLES]
[DOOR OPENS]
I'M READY.
COME ON,
YOU GUYS!
HURRY!
MICHELLE!
NOT THAT WAY!
THAT AREA
IS OFF-LIMITS.
WHY,
UNCLE CORNELIUS?
THAT'S NOT OUR LESSON
FOR TODAY.
COME ALONG, FURLINGS.
[RUSTLING]
TODAY IS PLANT DAY.
WE'LL LEARN HOW
EVERYTHING WE NEED
GROWS RIGHT HERE
IN DAPPLEWOOD.
NOW, WHAT IS THIS,
FURLINGS?
I KNOW, I KNOW!
A WILLOW, CORNELIUS.
CORRECT.
AND DID YOU KNOW
ITS BARK CAN BE USED
TO CURE RHEUMATISM?
UNCLE CORNELIUS,
WHAT'S R-RHEUMOTISM?
RHEUM-A-TISM,
MICHELLE.
OH!
I KNOW!
RHEUMATISM
MAKES YOUR BONES HURT
WHEN THE WEATHER
GETS DAMP.
CORRECT AGAIN.
WOW!
NOW, AS WE GET FURTHER
ALONG THE TRAIL...
VERY GOOD,
MR. SMARTY-PANTS.
HEY! GIVE THAT BACK!
OVER HERE!
HEY!
FURLINGS!
WE SHALL GO HOME
RIGHT NOW
IF YOU ARE NOT GOING
TO TAKE THIS RAMBLE
SERIOUSLY.
NO, NO!
PLEASE, CORNELIUS!
WE PROMISE
TO BE GOOD.
COME ALONG, THEN.
WE'VE LOTS TO SEE.
I'LL LEAD THE WAY.
YOU ALWAYS LEAD.
NOT SO FAST,
ABIGAIL.
HEY!
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
YOU'VE BEEN LEADING
LONG ENOUGH.
NOW IT'S MY TURN.
FORGET IT.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHERE I'M GOING.
BUT I KNOW
WHOA!
[THUD]
HEY!
WAIT FOR US!
RUSSELL.
WHERE HAVE YOU
LED US?
I DON'T KNOW.
THIS GROUND
ISN'T NORMAL.
IT'S...
IT'S HARD.
[SNIFFS]
AND IT SMELLS
KIND OF FUNNY.
[ROARING]
FURLINGS!
GET AWAY FROM THERE!
GET OUT OF THE ROAD
THIS INSTANT!
FURLINGS...
MOVE!
RUSSELL,
YOU ARE
ONE LUCKY HEDGEHOG.
IT'S RARE THAT
A FURLING SURVIVES
AN ENCOUNTER WITH...
WITH...
A MONSTER?
THAT...IS
A GOOD NAME FOR IT.
WHAT WAS IT REALLY,
CORNELIUS?
NO MORE QUESTIONS.
I WANT YOU
TO FORGET THIS PLACE.
OHHH!
WHEN ARE WE
GONNA SEE IT?
ARE WE THERE YET?
YES, YES. I BELIEVE
THIS IS THE RIGHT TRAIL.
READY, FURLINGS?
HERE'S THE BIG SURPRISE!
WOW!
LOOK AT THE BOAT!
ARE WE GOING
TO RIDE IN IT?
OF COURSE!
GET IN!
YIPPEE!
[GIGGLING]
I GET TO STEER.
DON'T BE SILLY,
RUSSELL.
YOU'D JUST SINK US.
WOULD NOT!
GIVE ME A CHANCE.
YOU TWO SETTLE DOWN.
EVERYONE
WILL GET A CHANCE.
HOP IN, EDGAR.
HA HA!
NOW, IN YOU GO.
OH!
GREAT HONK!
ALL RIGHT.
ABIGAIL.
RUSSELL.
YOU PADDLE FIRST.
NO. NO.
[MUMBLING]
STOP, STOP, STOP, STOP!
NO. NO.
WE'LL NEVER GET ANYWHERE
THAT WAY.
NOW, TOGETHER.
STROKE.
AND STROKE.
GOOD.
STROKE.
SO MUCH BETTER.
[HISSING]
[GASPS]
GAS!
I'VE GOT TO GET HELP.
[HISSING]
OH, GREAT.
YOU'RE GOING TO LOSE
MY PADDLE, TOO.
I DON'T LIKE THIS.
YIPPEE!
THIS IS FUN.
FURLINGS,
FOR THE LAST TIME...
SWIM FOR SHORE,
FURLINGS.
ABIGAIL,
YOUR PERFORMANCE
OUT THERE
COULD HAVE COST US
OUR LIVES.
AND AS FOR
THE REST OF YOU,
IN ALL MY YEARS,
I'VE NEVER HAD
A MORE UNDISCIPLINED--
[SQUAWKING]
[SCREECHING]
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
CORNELIUS?
SHH!
SOMETHING'S WRONG.
THE WOODS
ARE FAR TOO STILL.
WE MUST HURRY HOME.
BUT WE'RE ALL WET.
NOW, FURLINGS.
NOW!
OH, DEAR HEAVEN!
NOT HERE.
WHAT'S HAPPENED?
WHERE
IS EVERYONE?
MOMMY!
DADDY!
MICHELLE!
NO!
Cornelius:
WE MUST STOP HER!
IT'S NOT SAFE.
MOMMY, DADDY,
WHERE ARE YOU?
MOMMY!
MICHELLE, WAIT!
NO!
HELLO?
[ECHOES]
MOMMY,
IS THAT YOU?
WAIT, MICHELLE!
IT'S DANGEROUS!
NO, FURLINGS!
THERE'S A DEADLY GAS
IN THERE.
BUT--BUT WHAT ABOUT
MICHELLE?
JUST A MOMENT.
I'LL--I'LL
THINK OF SOMETHING.
WE'RE NOT WAITING.
COVER YOUR MOUTH!
DON'T BREATHE THE GAS!
[HISSING]
[COUGHS]
[GASP]
MICHELLE!
[SHALLOW BREATHING]
OH, MICHELLE.
[COUGHING]
ABIGAIL...
FOR ONCE I'M GLAD
YOU DIDN'T
LISTEN TO ME.
[SQUEAKS]
[COUGHS]
Cornelius: WE MUST
GET HER TO HIGHER GROUND.
QUICKLY, FURLINGS!
TO MY HOUSE.
DID YOU FIND
YOUR MOTHER?
NO.
JUST--JUST
HER APRON.
THEN...
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
LEFT.
I WAS IN SUCH A HURRY
THIS MORNING.
[SNIFFLES]
I NEVER KISSED
MY MOTHER GOOD-BYE.
TELL ME
THERE'S GOOD NEWS.
CAN WE STAY
WITH YOU TONIGHT?
OF COURSE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO
OUR HOME, CORNELIUS?
I HAD HOPED YOU'D
BE A LITTLE OLDER
BEFORE WE HAD
THIS LESSON.
A LONG TIME AGO
WHEN I WAS A FURLING,
I LIVED FAR AWAY
IN A PLACE
CALLED WILLOWBROOK.
IT WAS WINTER...
DURING OUR BEDTIME STORY
WHEN WE--
[THUD]
WE HEARD THE SOUND.
MOTHER AND FATHER
TOLD US TO RUN.
I WAS THE FIRST
TO THE DOOR,
AND THAT'S
WHEN I SAW THEM...
HUMANS!
[SPRAYING]
WE GOT OUT,
BUT MOTHER AND FATHER...
THEY DIDN'T.
THERE WAS NOTHING
I COULD DO
FOR MY MOTHER
OR FATHER.
[MICHELLE COUGHS
AND GROANS]
BUT THERE IS SOMETHING
YOU CAN DO FOR MICHELLE.
US, CORNELIUS?
I NEED
SPECIAL PLANTS.
EYEBRIGHT TO SOOTHE
THE BURNS ON HER EYES.
AND HER LUNGS
ARE BADLY DAMAGED,
SO YOU MUST COLLECT
PLENTY OF LUNGWORT.
BUT EVERYTHING IN
OUR MEADOW'S DEAD.
THEN YOU MUST
FIND ANOTHER.
ANOTHER MEADOW?
THERE'S NO CHOICE.
YOU ONLY HAVE
2 DAYS TIME.
THE HERBS
MUST BE APPLIED
BEFORE THE MOON
WAXES FULL,
OR IT WILL BE
TOO LATE FOR MICHELLE.
YOU'RE COMING
WITH US, RIGHT?
I WISH I COULD,
BUT I DARE NOT
LEAVE HER SIDE.
WE'LL BE
BY OURSELVES?
NO. YOU'LL HAVE
EACH OTHER.
YOU'LL WANT
AN EARLY START.
NOW GET SOME SLEEP.
AND IF YOU DREAM,
DREAM OF BETTER TIMES
FOR MICHELLE
AND DAPPLEWOOD.
* I CAN TELL TIME
BY THE MOON *
BY THE SUN *
* NO MATTER HOW I MARK
* THE HOURS LIGHT AND DARK
* I TELL YOU,
YOUR TIME'S JUST BEGUN *
* IT IS MORNING
IN YOUR LIFE *
* DAY IS BREAKING,
OH, SO BRIGHT *
* YOU'VE BARELY
MADE A START *
* JUST ONE BEAT
OF MY HEART *
* DON'T SLEEP AWAY
THE MORNING LIGHT *
* PLEASE WAKE UP
* LEAVE
DARK DREAMS BEHIND *
* PLEASE WAKE UP
* IT'S YOUR MORNING
* GOLDEN DAY TO FIND
* ONCE I HAD
A MORNING, TOO *
* I WAS YOUNG ONCE
* JUST LIKE YOU
* IT'S EVENING IN MY LIFE
* ALL I HAVE
IS THE NIGHT *
* BUT IT'S STILL
EARLY MORNING FOR YOU *
* FOR YOU
[SNORING]
IS THE PACK
FULL YET?
I HAVE MORE ROOM
IN MY POCKETS.
WHOA.
THIS ISN'T A PICNIC.
HERE. PACK
SOMETHING USEFUL.
[GIGGLING]
BOY, I'M ALREADY
WORKING UP AN APPETITE.
[GASPS]
THINK WE SHOULD
TAKE THIS?
OH, EDGAR.
HMM.
WELL, I'M READY.
LET'S GO.
WAIT.
I FEEL LIKE WE'RE
FORGETTING SOMETHING,
AND I'D HATE TO BE
UNPREPARED.
IS THIS WHAT YOU'RE
THINKING OF, EDGAR?
CORNELIUS! YOUR MAP.
IT WILL TAKE YOU
TO THE EDGE
OF DAPPLEWOOD FOREST.
THEN YOU WILL BE
ON YOUR OWN.
NOW, I WANT YOU
TO STAY TOGETHER.
THE ONLY OTHER THING
I CAN GIVE YOU
IS THIS WARNING.
AVOID THE HUMANS,
AND TRY TO WORK
TOGETHER.
GOOD LUCK,
MY FURLINGS.
MICHELLE IS
COUNTING ON YOU.
[PANTING]
WAIT, ABIGAIL.
HAVEN'T WE COME FAR ENOUGH
FOR ONE DAY?
EDGAR,
LOOK AT THE MOON.
CORNELIUS SAID
TO GET THOSE PLANTS
TO MICHELLE
BEFORE IT'S FULL.
WE HAVE TO TRAVEL AS FAR
AS WE CAN TONIGHT.
BUT--BUT IT'S NOT SAFE
OUT THERE.
THERE'S NO COVER.
[WIND BLOWS]
OK...IF IT MAKES YOU
FEEL BETTER,
WE'LL RUN FOR THAT TREE,
CATCH OUR BREATH,
AND PLAN THE NEXT MOVE
FROM THERE.
READY?
LET'S GO.
[PANTING]
HOLD ON.
I GOT TO STOP.
RUSSELL,
WE CAN'T REST NOW.
EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
YOU'RE NOT CARRYING
OUR SUPPLIES.
WELL, I WILL.
HAND THEM OVER.
ABIGAIL, NOT SO LOUD.
[GRUNTING]
AAH!
HELP!
OHH!
AAH!
HELP!
UHH!
[SQUAWK]
AAH!
EDGAR! RUSSELL!
ABIGAIL!
HELP!
[SQUAWK]
OH! UHH!
[GASPING]
UHH!
[SQUAWK SQUAWK]
OHH!
[PANTING]
WE'RE GONNA...
[GULP]
CLIMB?
WE CAN'T
DIG OUR WAY UP.
[GRUNTING]
[COOING]
[SQUAWKING]
[GASPS]
[COOING]
OHH!
[SQUAWK]
[GASPS]
GRRR! GRRR!
[SQUAWKING]
AAH!
CAN YOU SEE HER YET?
UH-HUH.
AAH!
OOF!
OOH!
UHH.
OOH.
GOOD THING YOU'RE
A SLOW CLIMBER.
OH!
HURRY! LET'S GET
OUT OF HERE!
[SQUAWK]
OHH!
THERE!
UNDER THAT LOG!
[PANTING]
THAT WAS CLOSE.
OHH!
AAH!
OHH! AAH!
SHOO!
GO AWAY!
AAH!
[SQUAWK]
EDGAR,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
[SQUAWKING]
[SQUAWK]
THAT'S IT, ABIGAIL.
THAT'S THE LAST TIME
I'M GONNA LET YOU
GET US INTO TROUBLE.
FROM NOW ON, I'M--
YOU'RE RIGHT, EDGAR.
I WAS WRONG.
[SNIFF]
THANKS FOR COMING
TO MY RESCUE.
WHAT ABOUT ME?
I BROKE YOUR FALL.
YOU, TOO, RUSSELL.
[SNIFF]
WELL...
NOW THAT THAT'S
SETTLED,
OUR ONLY PROBLEM
IS THAT...
WE'RE HOPELESSLY LOST.
DON'T WORRY.
IF ANYONE CAN GET US
ON THE RIGHT TRAIL,
YOU CAN, EDGAR.
WHAT ABOUT OUR FOOD?
MOST OF IT GOT LOST
ON THE HEATH.
YOU'LL FIND MORE,
RUSSELL.
THAT'S NEVER BEEN
A PROBLEM FOR YOU.
[YAWN]
THAT'S TRUE.
AFTER ALL
WE'VE GONE THROUGH,
THE WORST
HAS TO BE OVER.
I SURE HOPE SO.
[YAWN]
YOU KNOW, ABIGAIL,
SOMETIMES I WISH
I WAS BRAVE...
LIKE YOU.
YOU ARE.
GOOD NIGHT, EDGAR,
RUSSELL.
[YAWNS]
[DISTANT SINGING]
OHH.
HUH?
WHAT?
[SINGING AND DRUM BEATING]
* HE'S GONE
* OOH
* OH, MY LORD, HE'S GONE
* I'M GONNA MISS HIM SO
* GONNA MISS HIM SO
* OOH OOH
HEY. MAYBE THEY KNOW
WHERE A MEADOW IS.
* ONE MORE IS GONE
BROTHERS AND SISTERS,
IT IS INDEED A SAD DAY.
ONE OF OUR FLOCK
HAS CROSSED OVER
TO A BETTER PLACE.
EXCUSE ME.
MY FRIENDS AND I
ARE LOST, AND WE--
SAY NO MORE, CHILD.
WE, TOO, ARE LOST.
LOST IN OUR GRIEF.
AMEN, BROTHER PHINEAS!
BUT VERILY, VERILY, VERILY,
THE END THAT COMES
TO US ALL
HAS COME TOO SOON TO ONE
OF OUR FEATHERED BROTHERS,
WHO HAS BEEN BROUGHT DOWN
BY AN EVIL SCOURGE.
All: EVIL!
AND BY WHAT NAME
DO WE CALL
THIS SCOURGE?
YELLOW DRAGONS!
YELLOW DRAGONS
HAVE DRAINED OUR MARSH
AND TURNED
OUR NESTING GROUND
INTO A MUDDY GRAVEYARD!
* OOH
* OOH-OOH OOH-OOH
WHAT'S HE SQUAWKIN' ABOUT?
SHH!
SOMEONE'S DIED.
OH.
SO, BRETHREN...
STEP FORWARD,
AND PAY YOUR LAST RESPECTS
TO OUR DEARLY DEPARTED...
BOSWORTH!
MA-MA-MA-MA-MA-MA-MA!
[SINGING]
GOOD-BYE, MOTHER.
BOSWORTH!
OH, MY SON!
[SOBBING]
WAIT. IT DOESN'T
HAVE TO BE THAT WAY.
NO?
IS THERE
A RAY OF HOPE?
OHH!
THERE IS
A RAY OF HOPE.
BROTHERS AND SISTERS,
WE CA SAVE BOSWORTH.
HALLELUJAH!
RUSSELL, YOU FIND US
A COUPLE OF BRANCHES,
AND, ABIGAIL, WE'LL USE
THE TWINE YOU PACKED.
[ALL GRUNTING]
EEE!
BOSWORTH!
YOU'RE BACK. OHH...
All: HE'S BACK!
* OOH
* I SEE HIM MOVIN'
* MOVIN', MOVIN'
* I SEE HIM MOVIN',
MOVIN' *
* I SEE HIM MOVIN'
* I SEE HIM MOVIN',
MOVIN' *
* WHAT A SURPRISE
* MY, MY, MY
* SURPRISE
* AAH!
* HE'S BACK
* HE'S BACK,
THERE'S NO DOUBT ABOUT IT *
* HE'S BACK
* HE'S BACK,
I'M GONNA SHOUT IT *
* STUCK IN THE MUD
UP TO HIS KNEES *
* THEY CAME ALONG
* AND THEN, WELL, WELL
* HALLELUJAH
[TOOT]
HA HA HA!
* WELL, WELL, WELL
* WELL, WELL,
WELL, WELL, WELL *
* I'M SO GLAD
* I'M SO GLAD,
I'M SO GLAD *
* WELL, WELL, WELL, WELL,
WELL, WELL, WELL *
* WELL, WELL
* AIN'T YOU GLAD ABOUT IT?
* I'M GLAD,
I'M SO GLAD *
HA HA HA!
* HE'S BACK
* HE'S BACK,
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT *
* I SAID HE'S BACK
* HE'S BACK,
I'M GONNA SHOUT IT *
* HE WAS STUCK IN THE MUD
UP TO HIS KNEES *
* THEY CAME ALONG
* AND THEY
* WELL, WELL
* OOH
* HALLELUJAH
* HALLELUJAH,
HE'S BACK *
* TALK TO ME, NOW
* LA, LA, LA
* TALK TO ME
* YES
* LA, LA, LA
* HE'S BACK
* HE'S BACK,
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT *
* I SAID HE'S BACK
* HE'S BACK
* HE WAS STUCK IN THE MUD
* UP TO HIS KNEES
* THEY CAME ALONG
* AND THEY--WELL
* WELL, WELL
* WELL, WELL, WELL
* HALLELUJAH
* HALLELUJAH, HE'S BACK
HALLELUJAH!
HAL-LE-LUJAH!
THERE'S GONNA BE
SOME CELEBRATIN' TODAY.
I HOPE YOU PLAN
ON STAYING.
SURE. WILL THERE BE
ANY FOOD OTHER THAN WORMS?
SORRY, WE CAN'T STAY.
WE ONLY HAVE UNTIL TONIGHT
TO FIND A MEADOW.
OH, ON A PILGRIMAGE,
EH?
THERE'S A GLORIOUS
MEADOW JUST YONDER,
BUT YOU HAVE TO WALK
AMONG
THE YELLOW DRAGONS.
THAT'S THE SECOND TIME
YOU'VE MENTIONED THE...
YELLOW DRAGONS.
ARE THEY AS TERRIBLE
AS THEY SOUND?
WORSE.
THEY ARE
HUGE MONSTERS
THAT BREATHE FIRE
AND BRIMSTONE!
[GASPS]
[WHIMPERING]
WE CAN TAKE CARE
OF OURSELVES, THANK YOU.
YEAH, WELL, AFTER WHAT
YOU DID FOR BOSWORTH,
I TRULY BELIEVE
YOU CAN.
IF YOU'RE
STRONG OF HEART,
THE ONLY PATH
LIES THAT WAY,
ACROSS ACCURSED GROUND
OVER WHICH MY FLOCK
WILL NOT EVEN FLY.
[WIND BLOWS]
[GASPING]
[COUGHING]
OH! IT'S THE YELLOW DRAGONS!
AAH!
[COUGHING]
RUSSELL, NOW'S NO TIME
TO GET ALL BALLED UP.
OH! OHH!
OHH!
All: AAH!
OOF!
AAH!
[COUGHING]
HEY.
MAYBE HE DIDN'T WANT
TO EAT US UP AFTER ALL.
NO,
BUT THAT ONE DOES.
All: AAH!
OHH!
[ENGINE ROARING]
WHOA!
SUCK IN YOUR
STOMACH, RUSSELL!
OHH!
WIGGLE.
WIGGLE HARDER!
UHH! UHH!
AAH!
All: AAH!
[SPLASH]
I'M DROWNING!
HELP! HELP! HELP!
EDGAR...
HEH HEH HEH...
GET UP.
OH...HA HA HA.
OH...HUH.
WOW! LOOK
AT THIS PLACE.
GIVES ME THE CREEPS.
WE'RE ONLY UNDERGROUND.
YEAH. AND YOU'RE
A MOLE, RIGHT?
THINK OF THIS
AS HOME.
[SNIFF SNIFF]
ONLY STINKY.
WE'RE NOT HELPING MICHELLE
BY JUST STANDING AROUND.
WE'VE GOT TO GET MOVING.
[CLANKING]
LISTEN.
WHAT'S THAT NOISE?
[GASPS]
HUH?
OHH!
All: AAH!
[GASPING]
[SIGH]
NOW WHERE ARE WE?
I DON'T KNOW.
NONE OF THIS
IS ON THE MAP.
IT'S ALL OVER.
WE'LL NEVER
FIND OUR WAY NOW.
DON'T SAY THAT, ABIGAIL.
MICHELLE'S
COUNTING ON US.
MAYBE IF WE
CLIMB THAT HILL,
WE CAN START OVER.
[PANTING]
BOY, WE COULD BE ANYPLACE.
UH! UH!
[GASPS]
HUH?
Abigail:
IT'S A MEADOW!
WE MADE IT!
[LAUGHING]
NOW ALL WE NEED IS
THE EYEBRIGHT AND THE--
WHA--AHH--OHH!
OOF!
OW!
OOF.
THANKS, PAL.
HEY, WHY'D YOU TAKE THAT?
OH, COME ON, NOW.
YOU GIVE THAT BACK TO ME.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
EDGAR?
WHOA!
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
[SHOUTING]
HA HA!
HUH! UH! HEY! UH!
[SHOUTING]
GEE,
AND I THOUGHT MEALS
WERE OUT OF CONTROL
AT MY HOUSE.
I SAW IT FIRST.
YOU MICE
ARE ALL THE SAME--
GREEDY
LITTLE COWARDS.
[SHOUTING]
HOW WE GONNA GET ANYBODY
TO HELP US FIND THE HERBS?
MAYBE THESE GUYS WON'T BE
SO GROUCHY AFTER THEY EAT.
WELL, WE CAN'T
WAIT THAT LONG.
HEY, LET GO!
WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA?
WHOA!
PBFLLT!
HEY, JUST WHAT
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE--
YOU'RE...
GOSH, I HOPE
I DIDN'T HURT YOU
WHEN YOU
THREW ME DOWN.
HURT ME?
NO.
I'M FINE.
YOU'RE NOT FROM
AROUND HERE, ARE YOU?
MM-MMM.
AHA! NOW THE TRUTH
COMES OUT.
THEY'RE JUST HERE
TO STEAL OUR FOOD.
NO. WE'RE JUST LOOKING
FOR LUNGWORT AND EYEBRIGHT.
LIAR!
IT'S TRUE.
WE NEED THE HERBS TO HELP
A SICK BADGER BACK HOME.
MORE LIES.
WHY WOULD A MOLE,
A MOUSE,
AND A HEDGEHOG
WANT TO HELP
A FOUL-SMELLING,
WORM-EATING,
GOOD-FOR-NOTHING
BADGER?
[LAUGHTER AND JEERING]
MICHELLE'S
NONE OF THOSE THINGS.
SHE'S OUR FRIEND,
UNDERSTAND?
WE'VE COME TOO FAR
TO BE STOPPED NOW.
STEP ASIDE!
[CROWD GASPING]
RUSSELL, ABIGAIL,
ARE WE DOING THIS TOGETHER
OR NOT?
WAIT FOR US!
I'M PROUD OF YOU, EDGAR.
HEY, LOOK AT
ALL THE EYEBRIGHT.
FOR ALL THE GOOD
IT'LL DO YOU.
I'D LIKE TO SEE YOU
GET THE LUNGWORT.
NO ONE IN OAKDALE'S EVER
BEEN ABLE TO REACH IT,
BUT I'LL BET
YOU THREE CAN.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'VE ALREADY GOT A PLAN.
RIGHT, EDGAR?
I DON'T KNOW.
HA HA HA!
JUST LIKE A HEDGEHOG--
BIG MOUTH
AND NO BRAINS.
HMPH!
[LAUGHTER]
DON'T LISTEN TO WAGGS.
HE JUST LIKES
TO PICK FIGHTS.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I KNOW HOW
TO GET UP THERE.
WE'LL USE CORNELIUS'
FLAPPER WINGAMATHING.
RUSSELL,
GOOD THINKING.
WE'LL FLY TO THE TOP
OF THE CLIFF.
YOU DON'T
REALLY MEAN FLY.
YOU HEARD THEM, WILLY.
THEY'LL FLAP
THEIR LITTLE PAWS
AND FLY LIKE BIRDIES.
HA!
[LAUGHTER]
LAUGH ALL YOU WANT.
WE'LL SHOW YOU.
IT LOOKS LIKE
IT REALLY MIGHT WORK.
TO YOUR STATIONS!
CRANK THE WINDER-UPPERS!
[GRUNTING]
YAY! WE'RE FLYING!
THEY DID IT!
THEY REALLY DID IT!
ABIGAIL!
I'M LOCKING THE WINGS.
WE'RE ON FULL GLIDE.
EDGAR, GET READY
TO GRAB THE LUNGWORT.
DON'T WORRY, EDGAR,
I'LL DO IT.
BE CAREFUL, ABIGAIL!
YEAH, THE WIND'S
PICKING UP.
OH, NO!
WHAT?
[MUFFLED]
OH!
AAH! AAH!
ABIGAIL!
AAH!
RUSSELL,
DO SOMETHING!
I'VE GOT MY HANDS FULL.
YOU'VE GOT TO SAVE HER!
[GULP]
HANG ON, ABIGAIL.
I'M COMING.
I CAN'T HOLD ON!
HELP!
AAH!
IS EVERYONE
ALL RIGHT?
UH...
YEAH?
I GUESS
WE HAVE TO TRY AGAIN.
IT'S NO USE NOW.
THE LUNGWORT'S GONE.
WE FAILED.
NO, WE HAVEN'T.
LOOK! WE GOT IT!
WE GOT IT?
THEY GOT IT!
YOU'RE SO BRAVE, EDGAR.
HA HA HA!
LOOK! THE LAND
OF THE YELLOW DRAGONS!
WON'T CORNELIUS BE EXCITED
TO SEE WHERE WE'VE BEEN?
ABIGAIL, YOU'RE STANDING
IN MY LIGHT.
IT'S NOT ABIGAIL.
LOOK!
[GASPS]
WHOA!
OH!
WHOA! OH!
UH-OH!
All: WHOA! WHOA!
AAH!
OH!
OHH!
WHEW!
[GASP]
AAH!
All: WHOA!
HOLD ON!
WHOA!
[GROANING]
WHERE ARE WE?
RIGHT WHERE
WE WANT TO BE!
LOOK! THE WILLOW
FROM OUR RAMBLE.
All: WE'RE HOME!
MICHELLE.
COME ON!
CORNELIUS...
MY FURLINGS,
YOU'RE BACK.
DID YOU GET
THE HERBS?
YES.
HOW IS MICHELLE?
I'M AFRAID
SHE'S SLIPPING AWAY.
I MUST ADMINISTER
THE HERBS IMMEDIATELY.
ANY SIGN OF OUR PARENTS,
CORNELIUS?
NONE. I'M SORRY.
[RUMBLING]
HUH?
WHAT WAS THAT?
LET'S SEE.
SOMEONE'S OUTSIDE!
CORNELIUS,
COME HERE. QUICK!
OH, NO, NOT AGAIN.
IT'S THE GAS.
WE CAN STILL
GET AWAY.
OUT THE BACK!
THIS WAY.
AAH!
CORNELIUS?
RUSSELL?
ABIGAIL?
[GASPS]
EDGAR!
AAH!
[WHIMPERING]
[ALL GASP]
THERE YOU GO,
LITTLE FELLA.
EDGAR!
OH, EDGAR.
[CRUNCHING]
IN ALL MY YEARS, I...
I'VE NEVER...
ALL RIGHT, GOOD.
THIS AREA'S CLEANED UP.
HERE YOU GO,
EDGAR.
THANK GOODNESS.
THIS WAY, CORNELIUS.
WHERE ARE YOU
LEADING ME, FURLINGS?
SOMEPLACE SAFE.
[COUGHING]
DID WE MAKE IT
IN TIME, CORNELIUS?
[MOANING LIGHTLY]
WE'LL KNOW
IN THE MORNING.
WHATEVER HAPPENS,
YOU'VE DONE
YOUR BEST.
OH, MY DEAR MICHELLE.
[SNORES]
[YAWNS]
[SNORING]
HUH? WHAT?
MICHELLE?
OH, MICHELLE.
WE WERE
TOO LATE.
NO, NO, MY FURLINGS.
YOU DID EVERYTHING
POSSIBLE...
OH. EVERYTHING POSSIBLE.
[WEEPING]
OH, MY DEAR MICHELLE.
MAMA?
PAPA?
UNCLE CORNELIUS...
WHY DO YOU LOOK
SO SAD?
MY GOODNESS!
MICHELLE!
YOU'RE ALL BETTER!
OH, MICHELLE,
MY CHILD,
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
OF COURSE
I'M ALL RIGHT.
I JUST HAD...
[YAWNS]
A LONG NAP.
HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
GREAT HONK!
MY FLAPPER
WINGAMATHING!
YES, WE BUILT IT.
YOU BUILT IT?
BUT HOW DID IT
GET HERE?
WE FLEW IT!
YOU? MAGNIFICENT!
NO, NO...
STUPENDOUS!
YOU THREE...
YOU HAVE CHANGED SO MUCH
THESE PAST FEW DAYS.
I HARDLY RECOGNIZE YOU.
YOU'RE NO LONGER
MY FURLINGS.
YOU'VE GROWN UP.
[GIGGLING]
HUH?
LOOKEE,
UNCLE CORNELIUS.
RUSSELL!
HEY, WHERE WERE YOU?
WE STAYED IN THE FOREST
UNTIL IT WAS SAFE.
ABIGAIL!
DADDY!
OH, DADDY,
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH!
UNCLE CORNELIUS...
ALL THE MOMMIES
AND DADDIES
ARE COMING BACK.
NOT ALL, MY DEAR.
I'LL NEVER
BE ABLE TO REPLACE
YOUR MOMMY AND DADDY...
BUT I'LL DO MY BEST.
[CRYING]
MAMA?
EDGAR!
MAMA!
OH, EDGAR!
WHEN WE RAN
FROM THE GAS,
I WAS WORRIED SICK
ABOUT YOU.
OH...DID YOU FORGET
YOUR SCARF SOMEWHERE?
NO, MAMA.
THIS IS WHAT I FORGOT.
OH, EDGAR.
I GUESS NOTHING
WILL EVER BE
THE SAME AGAIN,
WILL IT,
UNCLE CORNELIUS?
WELL, MY DEAR...
IF WE ALL WORK AS HARD
TO SAVE DAPPLEWOOD
AS YOUR 3 FRIENDS
WORKED TO SAVE YOU,
IT WILL BE.
* COME AWAY
* AND YOUR HEART
WILL UNDERSTAND *
* YESTERDAY
* FLIES AWAY
* BUT TOMORROW'S
IN YOUR HAND *
* COME AWAY
* THERE'S A PLACE
THAT IT CAN BE *
* THAT YOU CAN BE LIKE
* ONCE UPON A TIME
* WITH ME
* WE WERE FLYING
* ONCE UPON A TIME
* WE WERE FREE
* LIFE ONCE LET US GO
* AS FAR AS WE COULD GO
* ALWAYS REMEMBER
* ONCE UPON A TIME
* WITH ME
* COME AWAY
* AND YOUR HEART
WILL UNDERSTAND *
* YESTERDAY
* FLIES AWAY
* BUT TOMORROW'S
IN YOUR HAND *
* COME AWAY
* THERE'S A PLACE
THAT IT CAN BE *
* THAT YOU CAN BE LIKE
* ONCE UPON A TIME
* ONCE AGAINST THE ODDS
* WE WERE WINNERS
* WE WERE ALL WE DREAMED
WE COULD BE *
* YOU TOUCHED
NIGHT AND DAY *
* AND MADE THEM GO OUR WAY
* ONCE UPON A TIME
* WITH ME
* WHEN WE LIVED OUR LIVES
* LIKE A STORY
* AND THE STORY ENDS
* WHAT WILL BE?
* WHERE THIS LIFE WILL GO
* I DON'T PRETEND TO KNOW
* PLEASE DON'T FORGET
THAT ONCE UPON A TIME *
* WITH ME
* COME AWAY
* AND YOUR HEART
WILL UNDERSTAND *
* YESTERDAY
* FLIES AWAY
* BUT TOMORROW'S
IN YOUR HAND *
* COME AWAY
* THERE'S A PLACE
THAT IT CAN BE *
* AND YOU CAN BE LIKE
* ONCE UPON A TIME
* WITH ME
* WHEN ONE STORY ENDS
* THERE'S ANOTHER
* IT'S ALL UP TO US
* DON'T YOU SEE?
* YOU SAY LET'S BEGIN
* AND I SAY ONCE AGAIN
* AND YOU'LL FIND IT'S NOT
* ONCE UPON A TIME
* BUT HERE AND NOW
* AND YOU AND ME
* COME AWAY
* AND YOUR HEART
WILL UNDERSTAND *
* YESTERDAY
* FLIES AWAY
* BUT TOMORROW'S
IN YOUR HAND *
* COME AWAY
* THERE'S A PLACE
THAT IT CAN BE *
* AND YOU CAN BE LIKE
* ONCE UPON A TIME
* WITH ME
* GO
* WITH
* ME
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--