(soothing music)
(eerie music)
(music intensifies)
(music swells)
[Voiceover] Now it begins.
My name is Jack Deth.
I come from the year
2353, and I hunt trancers,
super-strong single-minded
zombies who exist mostly,
I think, to make my life difficult.
Except I finally managed to
wipe them out once and for all.
And my life is still difficult.
I work for the council
now, jumping up and down
the timeline, preserving the
correct chronological order of things.
Time is fluid, and I'm
the guy who makes sure
the glass doesn't get knocked over.
Welcome back, Jack.
How did the mission go?
You're the whole
welcoming committee, Harris?
Where's Alice?
Where's Raines?
I'm starting to feel
pretty damn unappreciated.
First things first, Jacky.
The Solonoids.
Rest easy, Harris.
Those disgusting plant
creatures may have invaded 2093,
but that's as far as they got.
Good work, Jack.
Where's Shark?
About Shark.
Jack.
Shark is a state of the art android.
Where is it?
I gotta admit, I had my doubts at first,
but he saved my life.
The best partner I ever had.
Had.
God.
Ugh.
Tell me at least there's
something salvageable.
Define salvageable.
Oh, lord.
Look at it.
Don't call him it.
He was my partner.
Give him some respect.
So what do we suggest we do with him?
I dunno.
A hood ornament.
A lamp, maybe.
What a crime.
You coulda used him as
backup on your next mission.
Next mission?
Fuck that. I need some time off.
Look, Harris.
I need to see Alice.
She was my wife.
Now where is she?
Jack.
Things have changed a little around here.
Alice and I, we're...
We're pretty close to each other.
You son of a bitch.
She didn't have the heart to tell you.
And you got no heart.
That's not fair, Jack.
I need a drink.
You know, I should've saved
the solonoid for you, Harris.
(upbeat techno music)
Scotch.
[Voiceover] How do you want that?
In a Glencairn.
Hi, I'm Jack Deth.
You're kidding.
Your name isn't really Jack Deth.
No, but in my line
of work, I didn't think
anyone would take Maurice Deth seriously.
Hit me again, barkeep.
What is your line of work?
Trancer hunter.
Well, I wiped them all out.
Now I work for the council,
pretty much doing the same thing.
So you're a professional killer.
Look, lady.
Lyra.
My name is Lyra.
You know jack shit about me.
Jack shit?
Cousin of yours?
My mistake.
You look lonely.
It'd be a shame for a woman
like you to be sleeping alone.
Youarrogant.
Hey, babe.
This old man bothering you?
Let me take care of him.
Why don't you take
care of yourself, pal?
Fuck you mean by that?
You explain it to him.
Use lots of small words.
Hey, asshole.
Feel proud of yourself?
Feeling tough?
Lady, I am tough.
All this, just because you were worried
I'd be sleeping alone?
Is this your usual way
of attracting partners?
I never sleep alone.
♫ I just don't see
♫ Why is it so hard to be relieved ♫
Excuse me.
I'm supposed to pick up some
weapons from a doctor...
Surrell?
Dr. Lyra Surrell.
Jack Shit, isn't it?
So you were just
screwing around last night.
You knew damn well who I was.
You make weapons to help
guys like me kill people?
I make weapons to help
guys like you stay alive.
You could convince me otherwise, though.
You might remember this?
The long second watch.
One second becomes 10.
The rest of the world slows down.
Saved my ass a couple times.
Too bad it only has a
single charge element.
We've made some improvements.
It now has a self-regenerating power cell.
You can use it indefinitely.
Multi-purpose blade.
Cuts through anything.
An RBG-7.
Latest technology.
RBG-7.
What does RBG stand for?
Really Big Gun.
It's not that big.
It's not the size that matters, Jack.
It's how you use it.
Fires plasma blasts, and is equipped with
an atomic distillation
chamber in the gun butt.
No ammo clip necessary.
If you're in the desert, use sand.
A forest, rocks, pebbles, twigs.
It all breaks down, it's all the same.
All you've got to do is shove
it up your butt, so to speak.
Nasty piece work.
You should be very happy together.
Is that all the retorts
you can come up with?
I would've made you an
inflatable doll of me,
but I didn't have the time.
Too bad.
I coulda let out some of its hot air.
Use your little pen to prick it.
Better than the other way around.
You know what your problem is?
You're going to tell me, right?
Your problem is that
you're a beautiful women,
but too smart for your own good.
You got a body that won't quit and,
unfortunately, a mouth to match.
You might want to be a
little less smart sometime.
You know what's nice about you?
Yeah.
Nothing, right?
You don't know what's nice about you.
That's your problem.
And you do.
I do.
But I won't tell you because
that's just me being smart again, right?
Right.
Be careful.
Those weapons are expensive.
I knew you'd be back, Jack.
You're one of those guys who's not happy
unless he's working.
Any one of those guys
who's not happy unless
he's fucking someone's old lady.
How long did you expect her to wait?
So where the hell are
you sending me this time?
What we've got is an indication
of the time distortion,
emanating for the year 2160.
Could be nothing, but...
It could be something.
(machine whirring)
Can you hear me, Jack?
[Jack] Yeah.
The point of origin
seems to be Topeka, Kansas.
We've preset the time
and space coordinates.
Cycle is now activated.
There's no turning back now, Jack.
I wish I could give you a
better idea of what to expect.
Don't worry about me.
I love surprises.
Solonoid.
Shit.
Jack?
(machine beeping)
What the hell is going on up here?
A solonoid.
It must've regenerated
itself in the TCL chamber.
Jack's trapped in there with it.
We can't override the system.
I can.
Hurry.
It's gone.
He's gone.
Where is he?
We lost telemetry.
He could be anywhere.
(foreboding music)
(solonoid growls)
Something tells me I'm not in Kansas.
Swell.
(woman screams)
(woman groans)
Hold it.
What the hell?
A trancer.
You're a fucking trancer.
Whose meat are you?
I'm nobody's meat.
I'm Jack Deth, and you're coming with me.
I'm Borgia.
Where do you propose to take me?
Run.
Run like hell.
He'll drain you dry.
Run.
Charming toy.
You must let me play with it.
(dramatic music)
I think not.
(discording piano music)
(foreboding music)
Lord Caliban.
Lord.
Lord?
(serious music)
(lady moans)
Why do you disrupt my feeding, Lucius?
My apologies, Lord.
In the Hall of Nobles, disastrous, lord...
Softly, Lucius.
You're in my sanctum.
Not the greater halls during a feast.
Compose yourself.
Compose myself?
My lord, Borgia is dead.
How am I expected to compose myself?
Composed now?
Good.
Now, what is all this about Borgia?
We were in the Hall of Nobles
where the best and
greatest of the trancers
have their talismans and representation.
I'm well aware of the condescents
in Hall of Nobles, Lucius.
Then Borgia's statue
suddenly started to smoke.
The chest almost exploded.
Then the statue simply collapsed.
And when was the last
time anyone saw Borgia?
He went out hunting some hours ago.
He said food always tastes
better after a struggle.
Yes, well it appears
that Borgia's last meal
struggled more mightily
than he anticipated.
Lord Caliban, what does this mean?
Means that Borgia was a fool.
But it also means trouble.
You'll find, my dear Lucius...
That death can come in the
most unexpected manner.
(birds chirping)
(horse neighs)
Here we go.
Here we go, girl.
Come on, come on.
What?
The man had...
An exploding light hammer?
What is an exploding light hammer?
She was merely frightened
by the trancer's attack.
Nothing more.
Obviously, there is
something more, Harson, for
she is here and frightened,
rather than there and dead.
Tessa, why did you not talk
to him after it was all over,
after risking your skin chasing after him?
Why run off?
I was afraid.
He was very fearsome.
If I could do it over
again, I would've asked him
to join us, to help lead us.
Nonsense.
We do not need some stranger to come here
and lead us to the death and destruction.
The stranger overpowered
and killed a noble.
If he can kill one, he can kill more.
And I'd follow a man like
that into the gates of hell.
If he truly existed, which he does not.
Do you believe that?
It makes more sense than
exploding light hammers.
Tessa.
Are you certain?
Perhaps it was not a hammer.
Maybe it was...
A gun.
It is called a gun.
It is a weapon.
I have seen it coming.
Tell me, Tessa.
The man you saw.
Did he look like this?
And the weapon.
Did it look like that?
Are you convinced now, Harson?
This man could put an
end to our nightmare.
We must find him.
He could be anywhere.
It will be like looking
for a needle in a haystack.
(men clamoring)
Hey, you.
Me?
Yeah.
Why do you not bow?
There's no applause.
You think you are amusing, yeah?
(serious music)
You're one of those
blood-sucking creatures
I saw in the woods, like the one I offed.
You killed Borgia?
Hoy!
After him!
There he is!
Follow him!
(energetic violin music)
[Voiceover] Look down there.
[Voiceover] Go find the horses, quickly.
[Voiceover] Come on!
[Voiceover] Quickly!
There it is!
[Voiceover] Up here!
Our enemy takes form.
He killed no one this time.
Not for want of trying.
Lord.
Have you considered that this new threat
can be in league with, with Oberon?
Oberon is dead, Lucius.
I destroyed him myself.
Do you doubt my word?
No, no, not at all.
But whatever this intruder's
origins, he must be dealt with.
With your permission,
I would like to assign
all the nobles of Orpheus
to hunt down and...
We'll do no such thing, Lucius.
But, my lord!
The rebirth ceremony
of my son is imminent,
the single most important
event in Prospero's life,
and I will not let it be ruined by nobles
running here and about like mere sheep.
Now we have a wolf in
the fold, true enough.
But sheep, under terror from the wolf.
Hawks, however, fly undisturbed.
Would we be sheep or hawks, Lucius?
And if more should die to his hand?
Well, then, they were
not worthy, Lucius.
I will capture this wolf's head.
(serious music)
Prospero.
Your father has requested
not to be disturbed.
May I be of service?
No, Lucius.
As you wish.
(soft violin music)
My lord Prospero.
Yes?
[Woman] Not to be too bold,
but have you yet chosen a maid
to serve you at your rebirth
because if you have not,
I would be honored.
Why would you willingly
offer yourself to this?
[Woman] My lord?
I'll contemplate it.
Thank you, my lord.
(foreboding music)
No, no.
Do not sit up.
What happened?
You passed out.
I believe the bleeding has stopped.
Who are you?
Sebastion.
Sebastion?
Who are you?
Jack Deth.
Deth, a harsh name.
Well, it's a harsh world,
whatever world this is.
You mind filling me in?
Filling you into what?
Where the hell am I?
You do not know?
You're quick, you know that?
You truly do not know where you are?
That's right.
Well, this place is called Orpheus.
There used to be others like
me until the nobles came.
Nobles?
Bloodsuckers.
Yes.
Some people say they
came from another world.
We're not sure.
One night, one hideous night,
they came swarming over the hills.
The slaughtering was...
There are so few of us left.
The nobles, they have powers.
They can become stronger than us, faster.
When they use these powers,
their faces, they go crazy, yes?
Yes, that is right.
They call it trancing.
Yeah.
They do not stay that way, of course.
They don't?
No, they restore
themselves using humans,
draining our life energy.
They call us meat.
Oh, they can't kill all of you.
They'll run out of food.
Right.
So they draw off a little at a time.
There can be no harm to us as
long as it's done carefully.
We regain our strength given time.
Sometimes, though, when they're
feasting, they lose control.
There's warning.
You can actually see them glow.
Their aura changes.
As long as it is white, you are safe.
When it turns blue, that's danger.
And when it's red.
There's nothing left.
We all live in fear of it.
You can't live in fear.
You gotta fight back.
Well how can we fight back?
Well, if I get a little
stronger, I'll tell you.
What is this shit?
Herbal remedy.
It will replenish your strength,
but first you must rest.
(bird coos)
(festive music)
(crowd chatters)
Quiet.
Make your places, everyone.
My good friends, my good friends,
I thank you all for coming tonight,
for as you know, this
is a momentous occasion.
This is the night when my son,
my Prospero, will be reborn.
Prospero.
(triumphant music)
There comes a time in the life of everyone
born to the nobility when his
or her heritage calls to him,
pulls at him, as the moon pulls the tides.
It is at this point
when a noble comes fully
into power, the strength
that is his birthright.
The time has come for you, Prospero.
The need surges within you.
The need for meat.
Prepare my son's first meal.
(suspenseful music)
Look at them, Prospero.
Ready, willing, eager
to be your first meat,
and be the first meat for son of Caliban.
There can be no greater honor than that.
Alright, my son, choose.
Choose.
[Together] Choose, choose, choose!
Choose, choose, choose!
Meat, meat, meat!
Meat, meat, meat.
[Prospero] No!
I cannot do this, father.
I will not.
(soft flute music)
(foreboding music)
There's a message, my lord.
What message?
Who fights these noble trancers?
There are rumors about,
they call them tunnel rats,
the people who hide from the nobles
in the many caves and forests of Orpheus.
But it is unlawful.
If you are a temple rat,
you are apprehended.
Yeah, yeah, I know the routine.
All I gotta do is find these tunnel rats
so I can nail these trancer
bastards once and for all.
But no one knows where they hide.
Someone knows.
No, please.
Stay just a little longer.
What the fuck's wrong with you?
(horse neighs in background)
You son of a bitch.
The nobles take care of me.
They're not so bad.
Yeah, they're fucking vampires.
Are you hurt?
No, my lady Titania.
If you harm him, I'll kill you.
Like this, huh?
One move and this meat becomes prime cut.
(dramatic music)
Pleasure to meet you, wolf's head.
I am Caliban.
It appears that you have run out of time.
Bullshit.
I got plenty of time.
Is this some bizarre attempt at levity?
Clearly, the device
on his wrist possesses
some sort of crude magic.
(crickets chirp)
[Jack] Lyra.
If that's what you wish
to call me, I am now Lyra.
Oh, hell.
Oh, shit.
This is not a dream.
What the hell are you doing here?
I was born here.
I have always been here.
Always will be.
You're crazy.
I do not think I am crazy.
I haven't had any other
life that I recall.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
Let's just say you're who you
say you are, just for laughs.
You did not want me to laugh?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you acting this way?
Tell me how you want to act and I will.
Why?
It's what Caliban wishes me to do.
Caliban.
That's the guy that waltzed
in and knifed Sebastian.
He is the master of
the castle of all of us.
Hell, not to me.
I'm getting the hell out of here.
No.
Please don't.
What is this?
Some kind of trick you
people think you can pull...
Can what?
Kill you?
You laid there helpless.
We could've killed you a dozen times over.
Why are you here?
Because Caliban told me to be here.
Because I'm to do for you
whatever you wish, to please you.
Whether you want to or not.
Of course I want to.
Please, don't go.
Caliban's already furious with me.
I failed his son.
I wasn't attractive enough.
Caliban told me he would
give me one last chance.
He sent me here to give you pleasure.
Hmm.
He's got respect for you.
I beg of you.
Let me please you.
My life depends on it.
Well, anything to save a life.
(serious music)
Prospero.
One leads by example,
and one does not lead
by having one's only son
publicly shun our way of life.
Father, I've walked among them.
I have seen their faces.
I have seen their fears.
We're nothing more than parasites.
We take and take.
My son.
I never realized until
this moment just how much
you remind me of your mother.
I wish I remembered her better.
She was bold, but very foolish.
It's subversive.
She actually harbored a
distaste for our way of life.
So misguided.
I never dreamed, Prospero,
that she had managed
to pass her misguided ways onto you.
You cannot deny your heritage.
Food may sustain our
bodies, but life force.
That is what makes us what we are.
Prospero, I have never
ever raised a hand to you.
I know, father.
But you will feast.
[Prospero] Go to hell!
Those were your mother's last words.
Pray that they're not yours.
I saw him brought into the castle.
If we're going to get
him out, the only way
is through the forgotten tunnels.
We closed them off for a reason.
If they discover those tunnels,
they will use them against us.
We have no choice, Harson.
Who knows what manner of torture
they're putting him through?
Lyra, isn't there anything
you're interested in?
You think I am stupid, don't you?
Hell, no.
It's real genius to live
like this, do this, do that,
quake when Lord Caliban to come around.
And you're satisfied with that?
I am not satisfied.
You don't know how
difficult it is, living...
Save it.
I was hoping you'd turn
out to be something
more than just another
whining squid brain,
some dizzy ditz from Melrose who shops...
How dare you?
You sit in judgment of me.
You are the one who is the
squid brain, Jack Deth.
Good.
You don't take any shit from me.
You're showing signs of life.
You are pleased that I let you.
Yeah.
You know, there's this woman
where I come from, Lyra.
You know, I would love it if
she would be more like you.
So instead, I wind up trying
to get you to be more like her.
Where did you come from, Jack Deth?
Another world.
A parallel universe, another dimension.
All I know is I ain't from here.
Back home, the trancers
aren't running the joint,
and my weapons work right.
Damn.
My weapons.
This guy, Caliban.
How long has he been in charge?
For as long as I can remember.
Did he ever get hassled
by the tunnel rats?
They're afraid of him.
Everyone is.
He is very powerful.
Really?
You try and trance me, I swear to god,
I'll rip your throat out.
You got that?
Please, please, I beg of you.
Let me live.
I'll do anything.
Just take me to my weapons.
Let's hurry.
(lively flute music)
It is through here.
Excellent work, Lucius.
Thank you, my lord.
[Voiceover] Well, well.
That will hold you.
So, wolf's head.
Enjoying the pleasures that
life here has to offer you?
You're on this little setup, huh, Lyra?
Lyra?
Is that what she's calling herself now?
Lyra's a charming creature.
But subterfuge is not her strongest suit.
What's the point, then?
The point is, wolf's head,
I have a great deal to offer you,
and all you have to do in
return is to be honest with me.
Lucius.
What have you learned?
I admit, I did not understand much
of what he was talking about, my lord.
Something about dimensions,
parallel universes.
Mm.
As I thought.
There are worlds, Lucius, within worlds
with things like this.
A weapon?
And this is the trigger, I assume.
Why don't you put it in
your mouth and find out?
Now this...
Mystifies me, I must admit.
It appears to have a handle, but for what?
There's no weapon.
A charm, perhaps.
Where did you get it?
Charm school.
Show me the way to
your world, Jack Deth,
and I will give you power.
Power beyond your wildest dreams.
The only thing I'm dreaming about is
kneeling your sorry trancer ass.
So, you will not lift a
finger to avert your death.
I got your lifted
finger right here, pal.
And I got your death right here...
Pal.
(suspenseful music)
Master, please.
Release him.
I promise you, I'll do anything.
You'll do anything anyway.
Costel.
Take your iron right
down his dying screams.
It may be of use later.
Jack.
Lucius.
I'm very sorry.
(suspenseful music)
(soft music)
Harson, no!
Wait!
Will you help us?
What?
He's not like the others.
I've seen that myself.
What do you want?
Not what, who, and before it's too late.
[Voiceover] The prisoner, he's escaping!
(energetic music)
Stop!
Please, hang on.
Don't do it!
This way.
Here, come on.
Bolt the door.
We broke the lock.
Pile things up.
Hurry.
You're the tunnel rats.
Yes.
There's no way out of this place.
We got weapons.
We can fight our way out of here.
Not necessary.
Our way in is our way out.
What about him?
[Shaleen] He comes with us.
[Jack] You're crazy.
What would you prefer?
We leave him here so he can
show them our escape route?
I'll take care of him.
He spared your life.
How do you pay that back
where you come from?
With bloodshed?
Stand aside.
Find them.
Now!
I'll be damned.
You saying that was
painted before I got here?
Our wisest, Farr, made them.
He has the sight.
Mm-hmm.
Now, this.
What's happening there?
Your future.
Jack Deth, this is Farr.
You're saying it's my future to climb up
on a cliff and be struck by lightning?
It is your destiny.
Yeah, right.
(soft piano music)
We do not seek out your fate.
It will you seek you out instead.
(soft flute music)
(music swells)
Prospero?
Get away from me.
Let me die in peace.
You can fight this.
You don't remember me, do you?
I remember you.
It was three seasons ago.
I was a new bride and my
husband was young and loving.
We were on our way to our new home,
and that caught the eye
of a noble named Lucius.
He and several others came after me.
My husband fought them
and they drained him dry.
And when they turned to me,
and was about to do the same.
In that last moment, a
young noble came riding up.
Do you know what he said?
Enough.
Gods above, she's suffered enough.
Yes.
And you told me to run and
I've kept running until now.
I swear to you, my lord.
We've been through the weapons room.
There is no exit.
Then look again, Lucius.
They couldn't have just disappeared.
With all respect, my
lord, if they are back by
the magic of Oberon, I...
Speak that name again,
and you will speak no names ever again.
There is one more problem.
Prospero is nowhere to be found.
He may be with Jack Deth
and whoever took him.
We think it may be the tunnel rats, but...
Perfect.
(mystifying music)
Something personal.
Something.
Personal.
(chants in foreign language)
Prospero.
(dramatic music)
(music intensifies)
No exit, huh?
We have some rats to exterminate.
This guy, Caliban.
What is he afraid of?
He got any weak spots?
Caliban and his trancers
did not always rule.
The power of Orpheus comes rested
with a very potent and
benevolent wizard named Oberon.
Caliban did away with
him, but he still fears
the wizard and his vengeance.
How did he do away with him?
Poisoned him then
burned his body to ashes.
There's something I'm missing here.
How could this Oberon
be any kind of threat?
Something as trivial as
death won't stop a true wizard.
Wizards don't die.
They're just metaphysically
inconvenienced.
Magic again?
I don't buy any of that bullshit.
It only hurts if you let it.
There's a technical term
for someone such as you
who believes they can survive an encounter
with a wizard shielded
only by their disbelief.
And that term is...
Skeptic?
Dead meat.
Why do you have to feed?
We have no souls.
Inside, we are just cold.
When we feed, it is the only
time that we know warmth.
I was cold, too, the day your people,
the nobles killed my husband.
Please, I will not be able to hold back.
I do not want you to.
I am tired of running.
(soft flute music)
We do not need you here.
We fared well enough on our own.
Yeah, right, living
your lives on the run
from vampire trancers.
You guys had a way into the castle,
and you didn't use it 'til now.
You know why?
'Cause you're afraid.
It wasn't fear that
stopped us, Jack Deth.
How would you fight nobles?
I'd take the fight to 'em, god damn it.
Now, we're even.
Trancer son of a bunch.
No, he wasn't hurting me.
I was helping him.
You gave yourself over
to him on purpose, why?
That may not matter much longer.
What do you mean?
My father approaches, I sense it.
Who's your father?
Caliban.
We gotta work fast.
(dramatic music)
Rats are here.
Farr, we haven't much time.
I'll be along.
Angelo, Serene, Provost.
Scout on ahead.
Spread out.
Find them and kill them.
Kill them all.
There!
Look at this.
Such fools.
Who are you?
No one of consequence.
That's for sure.
I'm going to give you the
fair fight you never gave my husband.
You bastard.
I knew I'd find you here.
Time to come home with me, son.
No.
You've changed.
Yes.
You've been reborn.
Just as I anticipated.
Here amongst the meat,
you could not resist,
and now, now we'll be together.
Together in hell.
Your heart's not in this, boy.
Mine is.
En garde, motherfucker.
(dramatic music)
Have you seen them?
Hey.
(dramatic music)
(music swells)
You made a major error, wolf's head.
The last thing in this world
that you want is for me to notice you.
And now that I have, you're dead.
Beautiful.
You will not harm her,
not while I am alive.
Then you shall die.
How can you be the son of Caliban?
It is I who by all rights should
fill his lordship's boots.
Prepare to die, son of Caliban.
I must find Jack Deth.
(foreboding music)
[Voiceover] You still don't
get it, do you, wolf's head?
I am Caliban.
This is my world, my universe.
You have no place here.
This place.
This is the place that Farr talked about.
Wolf's head.
I've got you a present.
Jack!
Let her go.
Tell me how to get to
your world, Jack Deth.
I don't know how.
I'm trapped here.
My showing up was an accident.
That is unfortunate.
No!
(triumphant music)
Oberon.
I got nothing to lose.
Jack Deth, wait.
Where are you?
It's not where I am.
It's where you are.
You're knocking at death's door,
and I've got the goddamn key.
(music intensifies)
Wait, kid.
He would've killed us all.
Is that what you want to save?
Huh?
I'm sorry, father.
I had no son.
You hear anything?
Just the pounding of my heart.
What else?
Nothing.
Caliban, is he?
Gone.
My father is gone.
I should feel relieved now that it's over.
It's not over yet.
I'm still stuck here with no way home,
and I hear wizards don't die.
They're just metaphysically
inconvenienced.
(laughter)
(dramatic music)
(music swells)
(music intensifies)
(music softens)
(soft flute music)