- Art Subs - 9 years making art for you!
The Ciambra
Will break the door so! The father will kill you!
When I get out I'll give you a punch
that will make you fly with the door
and will stop where the dogs are!
You can not, Pio.
Pio, stop, Grandpa needs to make breakfast!
Come on, Pio, hurry up it's late!
Pisa but strong.
Come on, I'm hungry.
Pio! Pio! Pio, help me!
Pega este, Cocchi.
Pio, this bike is broken.
- Just missing gasoline. - You are spoiled.
Pio, why not stop it?
And look here!
Pio, stop it!
- Will you stop? - Is that you?
Play this bike out!
Come out, come soon.
Do not fill my bag.
I'll piss in your mouth!
I see a beer.
- Have you seen my brother? - No.
I'm not listening.
Who is it? I'm not listening.
Everything in order?
How's it going with that there?
Well. I'm almost there.
- Want to help? - No need.
What help?
He said he could get that there.
You will not get.
- So you can not. - I can not worry.
And when a heart attack who will take you to the hospital?
The blond here will take you?
Can you or not? Can It?
Let's see if you can.
Do not put everything.
You do not know burn copper.
For God's sake, it is wet. What the fuck is my fault?
You're ruining everything.
So do you.
I just got home from school. You do it.
I am not going to school.
You will never, so do not know how to read.
To learn to read? Look at this.
Lele, come here.
My sister put a nice outfit and maquiou.
Come here to kiss her.
- It is true, Pio? - How do I know?
Want to see? You want to show you?
Stop this. Want to see?
Stop it!
- Enough! - African fucking stop!
At home we get hits.
Hi guys.
What the hell do here? Go away!
Are you still here? Will soon!
- Police!
Police!
The police! Police!
Leave him alone, damn it.
- What were you doing out here? - Just came out a little.
- You must stay inside. - He went out to get some air.
- Shut up, lady. - I'm the mother and I shut up?
There have now been put handcuffs.
What the police doing here?
- they came because of the light? - No, just because it came out.
Curse! I hope to die these cops burned!
- You turned off the light? - I hung up.
well yet.
Come help me.
You go with the bike.
If you see the police, the lighthouse flashes.
- Combined? - Combined.
When you get a car, unlock the steering wheel,
push the washer and turn the ignition
with the screwdriver.
And one more thing. This is the engine control unit.
Pull the lever.
Then remove it and pull out.
That's how it's done. Paid attention?
Under has two steering wires,
one red and one black,
you join the two and the engine starts.
And then just bring the car here.
I give you 50 euros.
No, I will not go.
Do not worry, I'll take the car for you.
Yes, I'll take, I take.
Yes. Give me the number.
All right then.
Yes, all right. I'll call you tomorrow. Goodbye.
Pio!
Let's go. It was not, hurry up.
It was nothing. Move yourself.
Your logo!
And do not wash your hand, I need that number.
- With the! - I have four women.
- When we drink? - Now.
- Give a little to Grandpa. - Drink this.
- Mom I'm hungry! - I will soon, I'm starving.
You just gets a dish at a time?
Give a little to Cocchino.
- We eat like Italians. - Grandpa, let's eat like Italians.
I want more noodles, will soon!
I can not go.
Goodbye.
- It was the Licca, your girlfriend? - Yes.
- And what did she want? - Why do not you see it?
I can not go, I must stay here if the police appear.
I can not find her.
- Why not talk to her? - I'll be busy tomorrow.
Drink slowly, calmly.
"Drink wine that gives you a little help."
Let's drink to that.
No, Pio. Do not ... Did you see? He drinks really.
Look at him. Soon end up like them.
- Health, mother. - My God! By Cosmas and Damian.
Leave that bottle or I will give you the same end of the Africans.
- I will break it in your face. - You are drunk!
The end of africa ... What did you say?
But why do not you slap him?
Lower that glass, wine is bad. Look at her.
You do not see how it is? And then I'm drunk?
I do not! No, you're drunk, I do not.
Throw away this wine.
- Play the wine. - You should hit her.
Damn ... Now go get drunk! I'll break you.
You'll get drunk, little sister!
- You doubt it? - Dad, she's drunk.
I want another drink.
I will break the bottle in your head!
Leave her alone, just a little wine.
Cheers!
- mixed with soda. - not mixed! You are drunk!
I have a lot to do tonight, but ...
But what happens?
They are all drunk as Africans.
It is how do Africans.
African ...
Africans do so, get drunk,
bottles break after each other in the head.
And then they slap. You do the same thing.
You will end up as the Africans who drink.
Last winter, my daughter Carmelina,
He had hurt his hand on the door and took her to the hospital.
It was December or January and saw an African shirtless.
It was almost naked, and very cold.
He was naked and you could punch the wall.
He could punch in the door.
It was all broken out, face, arms,
It was full of blood. I was scared.
- He gave punch at all. - And the police were there.
- I had police there. - They beat him with ...
The officers were dismayed with the baton.
You know what happened once? I saw one while making purchase.
And he told me: "Come here." I said, "What do you want?"
And I said, "How ugly is ugly African, go away."
He said, "No, come here."
He took my hand and said, "Wow, what a great hand."
And I said, "Your ugly black, go away I'm afraid."
He scared me.
I did not understand what he said.
He said that when drunk trying to steal his animals.
When I drank.
No one could fool the dad.
- Do not smoke much, Pio. - Leave me alone.
- Pio, you turned off the power? - No.
How not?
You can not go on like this. How will we pay the light?
- Who will give us money? - How do I know?
- Did not know? - How do I know?
Instead of walking behind his brother,
do what I say.
- Understood? Go, get moving. - Go connect the wires.
Mother. Mother!
- At where? - Out there.
- Good evening. - Good evening.
A word.
- Where are you going? - Let me go.
- You can not come with me. - Do not fill my bag!
You can not come with me!
- Let's see if you now to. - No, no.
If you drop, you go to the shop?
No, I'm not going! Stop!
- I will not follow you. - Are you sure?
Have. Please...
Go back inside. You can not come with me.
- Will soon! - Will you stop it?
Close the door!
- That's good? - Go to sleep and do not fill the bag.
And do not cry.
Gosh, I do not know what to do.
He did not listen to me.
It's driving me crazy.
I do not know what to do, can not stand it.
How often should I say not to steal in Gioia Tauro?
No one took nothing there.
Only we took cars in Reggio Calabria.
They do not know the black Fiat Punto?
No, no.
But if he were here, I think would not you?
- Only if you talked about it all day. - he's gone a Fiat Punto black.
I also theft, but did not get that car.
- And you do not know anything? - Anything. I'll get them in Reggio.
- All right, beauty. - I'll pretend that nothing happened.
Let's let it go, it's just a car.
But we have work to do. We will go to a house in Tonnara.
- When? - Today they will go to a wedding.
- You can go? - I go. I am free.
Go alone?
Thank you.
I get this room. I do not want to be arrested, hurry up.
Come here! Where do you think you're going?
Gypsy shit.
Hello, is the police?
Send a car to my house.
It has to be fast.
It has a gang of gypsies who are stealing everything.
Scinà, nº 15.
They must come soon if you can, do not know what to do.
Please send the car soon.
Where are you going?
- Has a suitcase here. - You can check.
I want to see the documents.
- They are at home. - Give me the documents.
Stay still.
The car!
Police!
Leave him alone.
What's this here?
- Two wires. - Two wires?
Can hold it, it goes to the police station.
Why will arrest him?
Never go in the other houses, always come here.
You just come here. Leave him alone!
Doin 'it!
Let go! What did he do?
You run, run and always come here!
It seems like they are holding Totò Riina.
Run, run, and always end up here.
Mother, you see, are the Italians.
They go inside.
Come on. Quick, go inside.
- They made fire, Iolanda? - Yes i's cold.
- Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
My boys.
- For him. - Thanks.
I heard they arrested the boy.
- What can we do? - It happens to the living.
What's that saying?
Best hear the sound of chains that the sound of bells.
- He'll leave.
- You will not be there forever.
And he did nothing. Will soon, for sure.
I spoke to the car owner.
Will be in Piazza dell'Incontro tonight.
- All right.
- We combine 300 euros.
- That 's right.
- You take care of that?
Do not worry.
Later send a boy to resolve the matter.
- It's all right. - It's all right?
- Thank you, Mrs. Iolanda.. - Thanks. Good afternoon.
- If you need anything, let me know. - Thanks.
- We see later.
- Bye.
Pio! Pio ...
I know you're back there. Come here.
Pio;
-  - No, I take.
- You can not go. - Why not?
Nanà will take you! Why do not you listen?
-  - Why do not you listen to me?
Like his father is not here, do you think that says?
Why that?
Come on, move. Listen to what I say.
Or.
You're hurting me.
What the hell do you want?
Read this message to me.
- Read it. - I can read by any chance?
"I tried to call you, but no one answered."
- Get out of here. - Not thanks. Fuck you!
Hello?
Because the car.
Yes sure. See you tonight.
No, not in the square. At the station.
Yes of course.
Beauty. It's all right. Goodbye.
He's a big jerk, but you're cute.
- Leave him in peace. - Fuck you both.
Forget it, it's a bitch.
Why are you here? I knew your brother.
- He is fine? - It is.
- Why are you here? - I was looking for you.
- Looking for me? - That.
- What you want? - Need help.
Yes Yes.
We are coming.
Give me about 20 minutes.
Beauty? Goodbye.
Now try to join the two wires.
- Beauty. - That's how it's done.
- Thanks. Goodbye. - Wait, where are you?
Take the car.
You can not drive, leave to another.
- Because? - You are child.
- What a child! - Send someone else to take.
- Screw U. - Hang on! Where are you going?
Stopped.
I know how to drive.
Will soon it's late.
Beauty. Goodbye.
- Enough. - Got it arrives.
Come here. Look deep into my eyes.
Ended.
I do not want to go to jail or go back to Burkina Faso.
And I do not want to send you to boarding school.
Yes, arrives.
- Understood? - Got it.
- Did you understand what I said? - Yes.
Thank you for real.
- You're the guy from Turin? - And who are you?
- The guy's car. - The car? And where is he?
First pass the money.
That's right.
Are 300 euros, should give me 10.
Ten more? But the deal was 300.
We are a station, take the train and go home.
I'm leaving when you give me the car.
No, the car still with me.
But the deal was 300. Come here, come back here.
He knew he should not come to this city.
Take, here are 310.
- Where is my car? - is nearby.
- Close to where? - At Palazzo Verdi.
- But I'm not in town. - You will find the car.
But look ...
Stop it, please return.
You will not do it, is not an idiot like him.
You threw my phone on fire and the idiot am I?
No problem, buy one for you.
How much do you want?
- Where did you get this money? - In the bank.
- Of course ... - It's true.
- I'm not kidding. - Tomorrow we will go together to the bank.
Can be. Tomorrow up early and come with me.
What caught?
give you 200, do you?
- Do you want? Whether or not? - Stop this!
- Would you like? - Stop, Pius!
- Give me 10 euros. - Only that? I'll give you 50.
Come on, give me 5 euros.
Only if you wash your ass with the air pump.
- As you're mean! - His face is black.
Look who's talking, the girls do not want you.
You are the handsome, with those teeth excavator.
- Beauty, I go home. - Pio, can not go home.
- Because? - They are talking.
- They sent me out too. - Because you're small.
- Screw you, go! - Go take a shower!
Pio, where the hell have you been?
I sent you take the car to Nanà and come back here.
Two hours ago I'm waiting for you! Where did you go?
- And the money? - Is the car money.
Of car? But why not venture?
Longer worry about your brother, you also want to be arrested?
- And how he took the car? - Alone.
- What if the police stop you? - Do not do anything.
No? They would take you to the bar and would take coffee together.
The whole family in jail!
They in jail and you too, just like family.
And then I am alone, right? Tell me how to nourish home.
- Grandma, he brought you the money. - Come out! Get out of here!
Stop this!
You'll drive me crazy, you know?
It is two hours that you expect and did not know what to think.
You took the car! Why not venture?
If I gave the car to Nanà, he would take our money!
But why did you take? I will break you!
- Why do not you listen to me? - Okay, I brought the money.
- Now I'm leaving. - And where are you?
- Where are you going? - I'm going for a walk.
Can not stand it, I'll go crazy. They will kill me.
- Pio, where are you? - Up there.
What did you steal?
Baby.
- Take the glass, Pio. - Five euros.
Five euros.
- Cheers. - Health.
What will you do?
Good evening, ma'am.
We seek the covers that you stole.
At this time?
Here you go, ma'am. This is the warrant.
Now they will break down the door.
Check right there, then see the other room.
- Look good and will find it all. - you will not find anything.
- And who is this boy? - My son.
Come on.
This will not be the last time.
- This is the account. - How much is it?
- Nine thousand euros. - Nine thousand euros?
And it is written to when you need to pay?
- Is it not written? - No.
I still had plenty of time to pay.
- No, this is the consumption of light. - How shall we do?
- Sergio, you saw Ayiva? - No, but it must be there.
- Did you see the Ayiva? - No.
You saw the Ayiva?
No, no.
Your friend is there.
- Come see a thing. - How is it?
- I want to show you something. - What is?
Works.
- How much do you want? - Hundred.
- Hundred? - That.
- I do not need this. - But nobody wants to buy?
I need money, find someone who wants to.
Jennifer! Come here.
- Let's go. - Where?
- To Rosarno. - And how are we going?
- By train. - No, I will not.
- Want to sell it? - I'm afraid to train.
I will not go.
- Because? - I do not want.
Pass the tablet here.
I'll wait on the bike.
- Want beer? - No.
- How much you got? - Seventy.
As well? I said a hundred.
I only got 70. Take this. And this is for me.
- Do not. - Stop it, Pio.
- I sent stop. - Give me.
- Stop! This is how it works with me? - Yes. Give the money here.
- Really? - Yeah. Give here.
Okay, you can stay. See what I do with you.
Observe.
Take these 10 euros, buy train passage
and go home, okay?
Where the hell you going?
Run the train comes, this is the last.
Or catch the last train or going to sleep here.
Now I take you home. Come.
Expedite. Expedite.
Expedite.
Expedite!
- Grandpa, want a ride? - I have no shame.
Let's raise some money?
I need to finish something.
Pass here.
- Are you alright? - I am.
Those two are his wife and daughter?
No. I am my sister and my daughter.
And your wife?
We are only three of us.
- You also smoke? - What?
- What? Look. - No, not that.
- Why not? - Its make bad.
- Give me this. - Its make bad?
Try it, it will not hurt.
No, no.
- Where did you find this? - Around.
- Around? - That.
Beauty.
- I need TV. - What did he say?
He spoke Italian, he said it needs television.
This one is for me, but just for me.
I need a big TV for everyone.
Because you will have football game.
What? What did he say?
He said he needs a TV.
I have one, but I can not bring today
- because I have to work. - So I bring.
- I need to work. - I bring myself.
Alone?
What did he say?
- What gives 200 for everything. - Right.
- Two hundred for everything? - No.
I will not come here for four hundred.
- I bring. - I can not wait.
- Tomorrow no longer need. - Not now.
- Now? - I swear.
You said you swear?
You know how to say "I swear" in my country?
What did you say?
Now that you said it should bring the TV tonight.
- Beauty. See you. - I will be waiting for you.
I'll wait.
What is all this?
I will fill this warehouse and when full,
picked up a container, send everything to Burkina Faso,
seeing and I'm done.
This is called trade.
The TV is this.
But I'm finding you very strange, why?
I am fine.
Life is a little complicated.
When do you think is advancing
begins to turn back.
But is not it better to get a train?
That's right. Need to work. How will you take?
You work in the same place where my sister works?
Yes, but only when they need it.
That house is beautiful, there is real money.
Bother to take the TV and not on other things.
How will you take?
So, you see?
You are just like an African woman.
I'll put you in the container, send to Africa
- and you'll be fine there. - Goodbye.
- Send for Kingsley. - Leave it to me.
Klinsere.
- How is it? - Klins?
- O homeland? - Klins.
How's his name ... that you were here.
- you mean Kingsley. - Yeah, where is he?
- It's in the bar. - What bar?
- That one. It's not far. - Where is?
Come to show you.
Kingsley!
- What's it? - He's looking for you.
- thought? - I found.
No, give me money, I need to come back.
- No, stay here. - Give me the money.
- I need to go. - Pio, do not do it.
Friends, he brought television and is called Pio.
- Pio. - Pio.
Did you see?
- Pio, Pio! - Pio, Pio!
Come on.
Take the beer here.
Pio, Pio!
How are you? You are at ease?
You see all these people?
They are Ghanaians.
I am Nigerian.
- Where you are from? - From Gioia.
Gioia Tauro? You gypsy?
I like the Gypsies.
Legal.
- Do you have a house? - No.
Por countryside?
You're beautiful, why not have a house?
- Pio, Pio! - Pio, Pio!
- I'm sure. - No, no.
Our mother.
Okay, you're a good boy.
That's the way I like it.
See, we are all Gypsies.
Here we are all equal.
- You are here? - Yes.
What the hell are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
- Are not you working? - You know what time it is?
No, what time is it?
He's fine, Ayiva.
- All right, all right? - I am.
- Are you alright? - Yes.
- Are you alright? - I am.
Since you are a good boy. What a good boy.
Are you sleepy? It is stinking of beer.
- What you want? - You stink of beer.
It is stinking of beer.
- Did you drink beer? - No.
- No? Are you sure? - No!
You stink beer, get out of there!
You will hurt him. Will make you choke.
Will leave you dizzy. He will choke.
I'll kill him.
You're crazy, go there.
Pass the ball!
Pio!
Grandpa is in the shop, go help him with the car.
Pio, I was born in this wagon.
Come here. Come, Pio.
Before we were always on the road.
Always on the road.
We were free, without bosses.
We were free, we should not have anything to anyone.
We were free and we were always on the road.
And now we're here.
Remember if.
Us against the world.
Against the world.
What are you doing?
What the fuck are you doing?
- If playing in front of the car? - Excuse me.
Do not fill the bag!
Take your hand away and get out.
- What's it? - Anything.
There are many Africans who have car?
There are some, but not many.
Por countryside?
Why not sell spare parts for them?
You should not think about stealing cars.
Come on.
Pio ... Pio!
An important thing happened.
In the name of the Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit. Amen.
Let's pray.
Hail Mary, full of grace, the Lord is with thee,
Blessed art thou among women
and blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
Santa Maria ...
Dear brothers in the pursuit, according to the Christian rite,
the compassionate due to bury the body,
let us pray with confidence to God our Father,
to whom all beings live.
We deliver to earth the body of this our brother, Emiliano.
in the hope of his resurrection and ask that his soul
is received in the glorious Communion of Saints.
The Lord open the arms of his infinite mercy,
for our brother Emiliano,
acquitted of all guilt, reconciled with the Father,
in the presence of the eternal King.
Let us leave because Grandpa.
Let us pray for families.
The Iolanda daughter, her husband Rocco,
their sons, Simona, Antonella,
Susanna, Riccardo, Cosimo and Pius.
His grandchildren, Nicolas Damiano, Patrizia,
Cosimo, Gesuele Massimo, Cristina
and Francesco Pio.
And her other daughter, Simona.
Why do not you tell me things of jail?
What the hell do I care chain, Pio?
When you were arrested, I supported the family.
Why do not we do something together?
I know what you want?
Let's steal.
You are small, where you want to go? Tell me where you're going.
Do not fill my bag.
- You will take care of the Italians? - I'm not afraid of them.
Get out of here! Skirt that is filling me.
I sent out.
Get out as soon as it is annoying me.
Excuse me, my ball fell inside.
And what you want now?
Want to play ball?
It's just a boy, go get the ball this time.
But soon I'm hungry, Dad.
That's right.
Here's your ball. Go play somewhere else.
If it falls here again, I will stick it, you know?
Go, get out of here.
- What are you doing here? - I came to get the ball.
Come here.
so enter the homes of others? How dare you come in here?
- What was I going to do? - I came because of the ball.
- Are you sure that was the ball? - It's the ball.
And what's that bag?
Bring it here. You can bring, Michele.
You got something?
Tell your father what you done.
Tell what you've been up to.
If you do not explain, I'll explain.
I went to get the ball,
I saw a computer and a picture, and got it.
And what else?
Come on, talk. Tell me what ready.
Tell your mother what ready.
You know how long I know your family?
You come into my house,
sacaneia me and politely asks you to return the ball.
I was leaving in a hurry with my family.
I stopped to return the ball. He said, "Come back tomorrow."
I never dare to go to my house.
Or you'll end up dead. Understood?
If he does not know you, I would have killed you today.
That is wrong.
Thank that I know his family.
By knowing your brother, you know?
Otherwise, tonight would not have ended well. Understood?
- Apologize to all of them. - I'm sorry.
For all. Even to his sister.
Excuse me.
Rocco, you'll pay the damages of the house.
How much damage he gave?
About 8000 euros injury.
You will pay the damage he caused.
Of course, Pasquale. See value and pay without problems.
- What can we do? - You are a bastard.
- It's not right, Pius
You will steal my house?
There is more to steal from me or anyone, right?
Bring my coat, please.
Pasquale, let's get an agreement.
We will talk tomorrow. Teach good manners to it.
For small as well.
- See you later. Good evening. - Goodbye.
Get out of here!
You will not sleep here! Get out immediately!
Hurry up, get out! Skirt!
Get out, walk!
- Let me in! - Again? Do not come back here!
Get out of here!
Take water.
Where are you going, Pio?
Pio! Where are you going?
Ayiv to?
Ayiv to!
He can not stay here. This house is not appropriate.
It's just for tonight.
- What happened? - Anything. Try to sleep.
About what they are talking?
You can sleep soundly today.
Try to sleep, tomorrow morning call their parents,
tell that you are well and will return home.
Beauty.
- You promise? - Promise. Thank you.
What's it?
You want to know about the chain?
In the prison of Palmi, do not let us miss anything.
All there they respect us.
Africans do not.
Africans, no way.
No one even looks at Africans.
But we are respected by all.
Up by the Italians.
In the prison of Palmi,
I had a guy who had been arrested in Brazil.
In his cell, they pissed and cagavam on the floor,
if they are holding the bars not to fall in the shit.
Inside they behaved like animals.
You missed, Pio.
What are we going to do now?
Do not know.
You want to do something with me?
Let's do one thing and everything will straighten.
Beauty.
- You got it, Pio? - Got it.
- But what do we do? - I told you.
A friend of mine will come with the truck and I will help you.
They give us the money on time.
I will not do that because I know him.
Stop getting involved with these Africans!
Why call it African?
We need to think of ourselves
and you care about the African?
No other way, so do not!
Which way? Tell me that way.
Or they'll kick you out, you can not go back to Ciambra.
You need to call him and keep him here.
Let's do it and everything is solved.
I will not do enough!
Do not be a child, Pio.
The guy who comes with the truck is my friend.
Let's carry and he pays on time.
Call him! African trusts you.
Why do not you come home?
I like you so much.
What happened to you?
Me tale.
You are scarring me. What happened?
Can you take me home?
Here we go! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Did you see? It's all solved.
What's it?
Pio!
Does it hurt?
You did the right thing.
- Now you became man. - I already am a man.
Really?
You are a man?
Sou.
Wait here.
- Good evening. - Good evening.
I brought my brother he never had sex. Never.
- Who agrees to do the job? - I did.
I do not because I know him.
- So I do. - You? Are you sure?
- Absolute. - I can call him?
- You can. - Beauty.
Go! You see if you are real man.
Come in, boy.
- What did you do here? - I fell.
- Does it hurt? - A little.
But you're well? Are you sure?
You run a lot.
You should not run, but it hurts.
Pio! Come here!
Go Pius.
Come here, Pius!
Come on!
Legenda - JuLima -
- Art Subs - 9 years making art for you!
Curta to people no Face:
facebook.com/ArtSubs
And visit CineMio Downloads:
cinemiodownloads.blogspot.com.br