(MEN STRUGGLING)
MAN: Look out!
(GUNSHOTS)
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
(ROARS)
(EXCLAIMS)
(WHIMPERING)
Hey! Trying to work here!
Perhaps you could work
a little faster.
Perhaps if you hadn't
tripped the damn alarm.
Pamela, we are out of time.
The police will be here soon.
Or worse...
Batman, I know, I know!
But it's like trying to find
a needle in a... Haystack.
Come on, come on...
(GROANS)
Bingo.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
(DISTANT SIRENS)
WOMAN:
Nothing was physically stolen.
Obviously.
There was no effort
to minimize collateral.
This was about information.
There's no way Poison Ivy
could've accessed
S.T.A.R. Labs' secure data.
Got it.
Here's the file they copied.
Looks like this is the only
thing they cared about.
Oh, no.
Holland.
"Holland."
Why does that
sound so familiar?
Be my guest.
BATMAN: Alec Holland was working
on a bio-restorative formula
to turn deserts into forests.
(TYPING)
Until a saboteur's bomb
destroyed that dream.
His body engulfed in the
burning experimental compound,
Holland tried to
douse the flames.
The chemicals reacted
with the surrounding bayou.
His entire
physiognomy changed.
Holland was
transformed into...
- Swamp Thing.
- That's it!
That's what attacked me.
Not quite.
BATMAN: This is Jason Woodrue,
aka the Floronic Man.
Terrific.
Poison Ivy teaming up
with Jason Woodrue.
We're in for a ride.
I see two
immediate objectives.
If you'll excuse us.
A, figure out what Ivy
and Woodrue were up to...
And B, find out where
the green team is hiding out.
I'll take A. I have a hunch
I need to look into.
You take B.
Check previous addresses,
known associates.
Oh, crap.
Right.
We need Harley Quinn.
Last I heard,
Harley went off the grid
after she got out on parole.
No one's heard a thing since.
Rumor is she's gone straight,
but also, just plain gone.
No one disappears
without a trace.
Someone knows something.
Someone always does.
BATMAN: It's just a matter of
shaking the right tree.
Hey, thanks again
for helping us out
with that
League of Assassins thing
in Nanda Parbat.
Oof. That Lady Shiva.
Wouldn't say no
to a slice of that pie,
you know what I mean?
So, what can I do for you,
Batman?
A lot going on today,
but I can spare a few minutes.
A man was abducted
from his home two days ago.
Harold Goldblum.
Stupid hand.
Henderson!
How do you
even know about that?
We've got a total
media lockdown.
Let's just say I've got eyes
and ears everywhere, Sarge.
Hacking the
A.R.G.U.S. computer
is a federal crime, Batman.
Goldblum is a former
professor of chemistry
at Metropolis University.
Spent 15 years
heading up GothCorp
Chemicals' R&D division.
Most recently, he's been
working for the NSA,
specializing in
biological warfare.
He was their top mind
in biology,
botany and toxicology.
I need to know
what he was working on.
That'll be all, Henderson.
Right, Sarge.
Big fan.
I'm sorry, Batman,
that's classified.
My hands are tied.
Strange that you would
put it just that way.
Why?
A fringe hacker group
recently accessed information
about key
A.R.G.U.S. employees.
Some of them seem to be
engaged in, shall we say...
Questionable
nocturnal activities.
Are you blackmailing me?
I'm explaining
that I can help stop a crime
in exchange
for some information.
Fine.
But for the record,
what Mistress Ilsa does for me
is considered therapy...
In some countries.
SARGE: It's an odd case.
No ransom demands,
political requests, nothing.
He just vanished.
Whoever took the guy,
they either killed him,
or they're keeping him alive
for reason or reasons unknown.
Any leads?
Nothing viable.
The investigation
is at a dead end.
Goldblum's field of expertise
is man-made,
pandemic terrorist attacks.
Anthrax, Ebola, flesh-eating
bacteria, you know?
Yes, I do.
In fact, he's the world's
leading expert on the subject.
Jesus, the stuff
that guy knows.
I don't mean to be callous,
but a part of me hopes
they just kill them.
No, sorry.
Uh-uh.
Nah, man.
Mmm, no.
Haven't seen her.
I would've liked to.
(CHUCKLES)
Dame owes me
three weeks' back rent!
If you find her, you tell her
she can eat my...
She had...
The cutest smile.
Morty,
that was your niece, Irene!
Always saying she looks like
this Harley Quinn,
but I don't see it.
And an adorable tuchus.
Morty!
Hasn't been around.
Afraid not, my son.
Lo siento.
Can I have that picture?
It was at that deli
on 3rd Street.
Morty, that was
two years ago...
In Miami!
I could go for a Reuben myself
about now.
With extra kraut.
Hang on...
(SMOOTH JAZZ PLAYING)
Okay, we got
one Power Girl jumbo combo,
one Black Canary
leg and thigh, with coleslaw.
HARLEY: Gonna lose
that hand, pudding.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Anything else
for you today, boys?
- Uh, no.
- I'm good.
- Yeah, me, too. Totally good.
- (MAN GROANING)
Crazy broad
broke my freaking arm.
Hey Chet, this crazy broad
broke my freaking arm!
Got to be her...
(YAWNS)
Come on out.
I know you're there.
I got good ears.
Your hearing gets
mighty sharp in Arkham.
Things go bump in the night.
Hi, Harley.
Long time no see.
I'd like to keep it that way.
You're a hard girl to find.
Pretty clever,
hiding in plain sight like that.
I have a few questions.
For example,
where can I find
your BFF Poison Ivy?
We need your help.
- Ivy is...
- Save it, honey.
I don't mix it up with
the costume crowd anymore.
I turned over a new leaf,
as it were.
Listen,
Ivy's fallen in
with the wrong crowd.
She and Jason Woodrue
are up to something,
and we have to stop them.
They're a lethal combo,
Harley.
Lots of people
could get hurt or killed.
Ivy could get hurt or killed.
Nuh-uh.
I am done with capes
and tights and masks.
Just trying like hell
to lead a normal life.
Really?
Funny that you're not, say
using your
psychiatric training
to make a decent living,
instead of dressing up
in skimpy red and black
for a minimum wage, plus tips.
Pretty weird way
to kick a habit.
You've got to be just itching
to get back in the game.
Nice try, but you're
on your own, Nightwig.
You haven't reported to
your parole officer in months.
I should just drag
your crazy ass
back to jail right now.
Oh, yeah?
- (GRUNTS)
- Just freaking try,
you butt-wipe!
(GRUNTING)
(CLANGS)
Sorry, kiddo, but you're
getting the payback
for every pinch,
goose and butt-slap
I've gotten
for the last three months.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
Give up?
Just when things
are getting interesting?
Fat chance!
(EXCLAIMS)
(GROANS)
(GASPS) Whip.
(EXCLAIMS)
Ready to call it a night,
Harley?
(LAUGHING)
What's so funny, Chuckles?
(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
Some girls like Mace.
I prefer a little
low-grain Joker venom.
Only useful thing
I ever got from that ass-hat.
(NIGHTWING LAUGHING WILDLY)
Nighty-night, jerk.
(EXCLAIMS)
Don't know
what you expect to find.
My best people have been
over this place a dozen times.
No offense
to your best people,
but they're not me.
What is it?
Oh, yay, a leaf.
Kind of like all of these.
No,
not like those.
It's a completely
different phylum
from every other leaf in here.
Great, you're the world's
greatest florist, too.
Look closely.
Have you ever seen
a leaf like this?
Can't say that I have.
That's because
it isn't from our planet.
Not even from our dimension.
Wait, you mean
Jason Woodrue?
That freak was here?
This is bad.
Your forensic people are bad.
This...
Is catastrophic.
Nightwing, this is Batman.
Come in.
Nightwing?
Everything okay?
He should've
reported in by now.
You want me
to send out a search team?
They're the best that...
Well, they're pretty good.
Like I said,
eyes and ears everywhere.
Besides...
Nightwing can handle himself.
- (GROANS)
- HARLEY: I know, I know, freaking stupid.
Bringing him back to my place.
But what was I supposed to do?
I couldn't just let him go.
He knows the secret location
of my hidey-hole.
He'd blab to Batman for sure.
Could've just killed him,
dumbass.
HARLEY: Nah,
I'm not a criminal anymore.
Plus, he's kind of
too cute to kill.
And anyway,
maybe I should help out.
Sounds like Ivy could be in
some serious trouble...
Don't bother yelling for help.
This dump is condemned.
Nobody in the whole building
but us, Nightwig.
"Wing."
Eh?
It's Nightwing.
Really?
Guess I was thinking of
that goofy mullet
you used to have.
Yeesh. That was like
a whole decade of bad-hair days.
Sticks and stones, lady.
I've taken trash talk from
bigger criminals than you.
"Criminals"?
If you hadn't noticed,
I went straight.
I'm a freaking waitress
already.
Oh, golly, that's right,
I stand corrected.
Check this out, smart guy.
My pile of rejection letters.
Evidently, the Mayo Clinic's
got some dumb policy
of not hiring former
costume super-villains.
Just like every other hospital
in the world.
There are other jobs.
Oh, sure.
I got a ton of offers.
"We got a very
special role for you
"in Bad Girls After Dark."
And you got to love this one.
"A tasteful pictorial
to be shot in Thailand
"for legal reasons."
You say I'm a criminal,
they say I'm a whore.
Well, I'm sick of other people
telling me what I am!
Whatever.
Got to say,
you gave me
a heck of a workout.
Got me all sweat-stinky.
(SNIFFS)
Phew!
Definitely could use a shower.
I think better
when I don't reek.
Still got to figure out
what to do
about Nightwig over there.
Hmm, what to wear,
what to wear?
Sucker-punch Harley.
Arctic Harley.
Street-luge Harley.
Roller-babe Harley.
Steampunk Harley.
Goth-Lolita Harley.
Hey, Nightwig,
is it true you
used to be Robin?
Hmph.
Ain't that
a kick in the pants.
Little boy-wonder
all grown up.
Okay, now...
Don't be getting
any funny ideas.
Too late.
It's funny.
I always kind of thought you
and Batman didn't like girls.
- Wait, what?
- You know, that book
with the headlights
and the eyeball-gouging,
I had to write a paper on it
back in college.
Got a B-minus.
Look, Harley, I...
Pretty lonely
these last few months,
if you know what I mean.
You don't meet
a lot of likely prospects
at Superbabes.
I'm kind of choosy.
I'm not saying
I don't want to,
'cause that could be nice.
All sorts of wrong, but nice.
Right now, I just really
need to find Poison...
(SHUSHES)
Face it, sugar.
I got something you want,
and you sure as shooting
got something I want.
So, be a good boy,
and maybe, maybe...
Mama will give you a cookie.
The things I do for Gotham.
I'm taking that as a yes.
(MOANS)
JASON: It's disgusting.
It's an abomination.
You think I like swapping spit
with this geezer
every six hours?
If you've got a better way
to keep him under our control,
I am all ears.
There's always torture.
I don't torture.
The seven-billion meat bags
who infest this world
would probably consider
our plans for them torture.
Or at least
cruel and inhumane.
Our plans
are for the improvement
of every organism on Earth.
The very
definition of humane.
(SCOFFS)
"Humane."
What an ironic word
coined by a species
completely devoid
of compassion
for any other life forms,
or each other,
for that matter.
They all talk
about climate change,
but have they actually
changed anything?
Indeed, they have.
JASON: They've doubled
their output of greenhouse gases,
increased the rate
of deforestation,
ravaged the planet.
You said it yourself, Pamela,
and I quote,
"Humans simply
will not give a crap
"unless we force them to."
Well,
once our virus
is activated,
every single person
on this planet
will have a vested interest...
In going green.
(BEEPING)
(HARLEY LAUGHING)
NIGHTWING: Oh, God, no.
Stop, stop!
HARLEY: You stop it!
You're gonna make me pee!
(NIGHTWING CHUCKLING)
Hey, hey, hey.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT)
(BATMAN CLEARS THROAT)
Harley Quinn
reporting for duty, sir.
I was...
I was just about to call you.
Meet you at the car.
(HUMMING)
Did you get what you needed?
Well, yeah...
Ivy's whereabouts, of course,
that's what you meant.
No, not yet.
Like you never made out
with a super-villain.
So, here's how it's
gonna work, dynamic duo.
Nobody knows Ivy
like I know Ivy.
Now, I can help you find her,
but you're gonna let me
talk some sense into her
before you come in, swinging.
And then,
when this whole thing is over,
you're gonna put in
a good word
for me with the parole board.
Tell them what a fine,
upstanding citizen I am,
et cetera, et cetera.
Hmm...
No.
What the what? But, I mean...
Aren't you gonna...
Don't you need...
I don't make deals
with psychopaths.
Sociopath!
So-ci-o-path!
Jeez, why does everybody
always get that wrong?
If you aren't willing
to agree to my terms,
why should I help you?
You'll help us,
or the rest of the world
will cease to exist.
As insane as you are,
you enjoy living.
How about
just a little something
to sweeten the deal?
Spa day? Autographed picture
for my little cousin?
He's real sick.
Okay, fine, whatever,
you're the boss.
Wait, she's coming with us?
Is that really a good idea?
It's not my first choice.
But we can't afford
to let her out of our sight.
She might tip off Ivy
that we're on to her.
Yeah, dangerous loony
over here.
Never know
what she's gonna do.
Here,
there's a little trick to it.
Hey! Watch the hands,
Buster Brown.
Sorry, I was just...
Jeez, 20 minutes
of naughty fun time
and they think they own you.
I wasn't,
I was just trying to...
Look, maybe I'll call you
sometime, okay?
Like when I'm out of batteries
or something.
(ENGINE REVVING)
BATMAN: Based on Goldblum's
area of expertise,
Woodrue and Ivy's
ideological profiles
and the S.T.A.R.
Labs break-in,
there's only one conclusion.
They're going to
synthesize the formula
that created Swamp Thing,
convert it into
a fast-spreading virus
and "save the world..."
By turning humanity
into animal-plant hybrids.
What? Ew.
Look, don't get me wrong.
I ain't no racist.
I mean, some of my
best friends are plant people.
Well, on the bright side,
at least they aren't
actually killing anyone.
BATMAN: Perhaps
not intentionally.
Here we go.
It's bad enough
if they succeed
and we all
live as plant people.
But that's not even
the worst-case scenario.
If any part of
their plan is off,
even a slight bit,
within weeks, days maybe...
We could be looking at the
extinction of all life on the planet.
Jeebus.
But wait a minute.
Why do they need
the Holland formula?
Why not just make
the virus from themselves?
It's a shortcut.
Reverse engineering their
own DNA could take years,
maybe decades.
Neither of them was ever
fully human to begin with.
She's a natural mutation.
And he's an exile Dryad
from another dimension.
"Exile Dryad from..."
You shitting me!
We've seen weirder things.
Harley, we just
need you to help us find Ivy.
That's all.
We'll handle the rest.
No problem. I know this guy.
One of Ivy's top henchmen,
probably still tight with him.
And he is...
Oh my God!
Stop the car!
- No.
- But it's him!
- Who?
- That guy!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Hey you! Bobby Leibowitz!
Oh crap!
Harley. Wait!
(GRUNTING)
(HONKS)
(CARS HONKING)
- (HONKING)
- (CRASH)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(DISTANT HONKING)
(EXCLAIMS)
Lousy,
stinking,
stand me up
for senior
- prom!
- (GROANS)
BATMAN: That's enough.
Dumps me for that chick
with the big...
Sorry, she's off her meds.
Won't happen again.
(MUFFLED PROTESTS)
But seriously dude,
sounds like
you kind of had it coming.
...made my mother cry!
HARLEY: Was she worth it,
douchebag?
Waited ten years
to get that...
I was just...
But...
- He...
- (TIRES SCREECH)
Pull a stupid stunt
like that again,
and I'm dumping you off
at the nearest police station.
Oh, big whoop.
"You're living under my roof.
"You play by my rules."
Is that it?
Newsflash, gruesome.
You ain't my dad!
This isn't a game, Harley.
I need you to stay focused
on the job at hand.
Focus-schmocus.
You know, I'm starting
to rethink this whole deal.
Here I am,
helping you guys out,
pro bono, I might add,
and you got to go and get all
mega control-freaky on me.
"Do this. Don't do that!
"Sit up straight.
Brush after every meal.
"Don't bite your toenails.
"Keep your knees together
when you're wearing a dress."
Harley! There
are lives at stake.
Oh my God!
Yeah, yeah, the
whole world's gonna plotz.
I get it. I get it.
You think I'm just
some dizzy airhead
that don't know nothing.
Do you know what I am?
My punishment for
dropping out of med school.
(IMITATES BUZZER) Wrong.
I'm the answer to
all your prayers, pally.
Take the Donnenfeld
Expressway to Bludhaven.
Come on. Trust me this time.
Okay, you really wanna
stop the car this time.
Those Hawkgirl spicy wings
I had at Superbabes
are doing a tango in my tummy.
Seriously.
I'm dying back here.
Fine.
(FARTS)
Ugh!
- Holy...
- It's not so bad.
Smells like discipline.
(FARTS)
Oh man!
Batman, I'm begging you.
(TIRES SCREECH)
(HARLEY HUMMING)
I'll give you ten bucks
if you floor it
and don't look back.
(ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING)
I know.
It looks like a total dump.
But trust me...
It is a total dump.
Howsomever, all the cool
hench-people hang out here.
Bet you dollars to donuts,
Shrubbie's inside.
Guy just loves to dance.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
I have nightmares like this.
Not sure just how
welcome we are here.
Oh relax. You'll fit right in.
Try to look a little less
stick-up-your-assy.
♪ Don't pull your love
out on me, baby
♪ If you do, then I think that
maybe I'll just lay me down
♪ Cry for a hundred years
♪ Don't pull your love out on
me, honey
♪ Take my heart, my soul,
my money
♪ But don't leave me here
drowning in my tears
♪ You say you're gonna leave
♪ Gonna take that
big white bird
♪ Gonna fly right out of here
♪ Without a single word
♪ But you know you'll
break my heart
♪ When I watch you
close that door
♪ 'Cause I know I won't
see you anymore
♪ But don't pull your love
out on me, baby... ♪
Oh look! I was right!
There's Shrubbie.
Hey, Shrubbie!
Be right back.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Long time, no see, Shrubbie.
♪ Haven't I been good to you?
♪ What about that
brand new ring?
♪ Doesn't that mean
love to you?
♪ Doesn't that mean anything?
♪ If I threw away my pride
♪ And I got down on my knees
♪ Would you make me beg you
pretty please? ♪
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Still got the moves, Shrubbie.
Milk for the gentleman.
(LAUGHING)
♪ There's so much I wanna do
♪ I've got love enough for two
♪ But I'll never use it girl
if I don't have you
♪ Don't pull your love out on
me, baby
♪ If you do, then I think that
maybe I'll just lay me down
♪ Cry for a hundred years
♪ Don't pull your love out on
me, honey
♪ Take my heart, my soul,
my money
♪ But don't leave
me to drown... ♪
I got to do
something for Shrubbie
or there's no deal.
(APPLAUSE)
(CLICKS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ I'm in the phone booth,
it's the one across the hall
♪ If you don't answer,
I'll just ring it off the wall
♪ I know he's there,
but I just had to call
♪ Don't leave me
♪ Hanging on the telephone
♪ I heard your mother now
she's going out the door
♪ Did she go to work
or just go to the store
♪ All those things she said,
I told you to ignore ♪
Hey buddy, watch this.
♪ Oh why can't we talk again ♪
Oh man. Don't do it.
♪ Oh why can't we talk again
♪ Don't leave me
hanging on the telephone
♪ It's good to
hear your voice,
♪ You know it's been so long
♪ If I don't get your calls
♪ Then everything goes wrong
♪ I want to tell you something
♪ You've known all along
♪ Don't leave me
hanging on the telephone ♪
(CHEERING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLS)
Wait.
♪ I had to interrupt
and stop this conversation
♪ Your voice across the line
gives me a strange sensation
♪ I'd like to talk when
I can show you my affection
♪ Oh I can't control myself
♪ Don't leave me
hanging on the telephone
♪ Hang up and run to me
♪ Whoa! Hang up and run to me
♪ Whoa oh oh oh
♪ Run to me ♪
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
(MICROPHONE FEEDBACK)
Happy?
Thanks a heap, Shrub.
I got it. Let's go.
You put a lot of bodies
in the slammer, Bat fink.
Only way you
getting out of here
is in a black plastic bag
with a zipper up the front.
- A body bag.
- He knows what it is!
Okay, boys.
Let's dance!
- (CRASHING)
- (EXCLAIMING)
See? That was fun, right?
(DEVICE RINGING)
Go ahead, Watch Tower.
Hey Bat, this is Booster.
Got your emergency alert.
Hey the thing is,
most of our heavy hitters
are out near Rigel
trying to stop a rogue comet
or black hole or something.
And a bunch of them are at
that christening at
Aquaman's place
and you know the reception
down there kind of sucks.
I only got a handful
of guys here on standby.
I could send...
Uh, let's see.
Black Condor.
The Elongated Man.
Triumph.
Bloodwind.
Or I could just come down
myself, give you guys a hand.
Not much going on up here and
the Foosball table
is still busted.
That's all right, Booster.
Thanks anyway. We'll make do.
You sure?
'Cause it's no problem.
One of these can
totally cover for me.
Sorry, Booster.
Going under
some high-tension wires.
That sounds like paper.
(SIGHS)
Over and out.
That was too close.
HARLEY: We got any
of them fries left?
(SQUEAKING)
You're just
going to feel a bit of
pressure here, little fellow.
Everything's going
to be just fine.
JASON: It's working.
He's stable!
(GASPS) Oh!
Look how beautiful you are!
Come to Momma, cutie pie.
It works.
It works!
This is no
ordinary leafy mouse,
but a harbinger
of the new age.
The dead
grinding factories of man
will be replaced by cathedrals
of mighty redwoods.
A verdant green
life-covered Earth
- will burst for...
- (GASPS)
Eww!
Subject response, negative.
Why isn't it working?
He's faking.
He's not even trying!
Your persuasion
kiss has worn off!
He's still under my control.
Harold, tell us
what went wrong.
This is an incredibly
complex azeotrope.
The virus conversion
of the formula works
perfectly on paper.
There are literally
millions of variables
that could be
corrupting the process.
Take a guess, meat bag!
Well, guessing
is hardly scientific
but I suspect
it may have something
to do with the fact
that we've been using
plain old swamp water from
nearby Slaughter Swamp
for our experiments.
No, what we need
is the precise
bio-nutrients and chemicals
from the water
at the exact place
where the Swamp
Thing was created.
The Ween Right
Swamp in Louisiana.
Oh for God's sake.
What a pain in the ass!
No Pamela, no.
It's perfect! Don't you see?
The lagoon feeds directly
into the Gulf of Mexico.
Where the Gulf's
stream currents will
carry the virus
into the greater Atlantic.
And then, the world!
Mother Earth's salvation.
Ground zero!
- (GLASS SHATTERS)
- (GASPS)
I said it last time.
Your turn.
It's over, Ivy.
Harley?
Hiya Red.
You're with them?
Oh, Harl!
Come on, Pammy,
what are you doing?
You're really gonna
change us all into plants?
You know I don't
look good in green.
I'm sorry, Harley,
but there's no other way.
Humankind have
had their chance.
And you've had yours!
(EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTS)
(SIZZLING)
Oh, gross!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CRASH)
(GRUNTS)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(GROANS)
(FLAMES ROARING)
(SCREAMS)
Jason, the work!
Whoa, what's happening?
He's waking up.
I need to keep him hypnotized.
Hmm... No.
(EXCLAIMS)
Occam's Razor.
Red!
You can leave me here, Pammy.
You know my skin. I burn easy.
That idiot meat skate
betrayed you, Pamela.
She's your worst enemy.
Leave her to her fate!
(GRUNTS)
(WHIMPERS)
(FLAMES CRACKLING)
(CRASH)
(EXPLOSION)
Nightwing?
NIGHTWING: (GRUNTS)
Over here!
(STRAINING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
You okay?
My ears are gonna
be ringing for a week.
But no broken bones.
Ow!
I think.
Where's Harley?
(SIGHS)
- (SHUSHING)
- (WHIMPERING)
It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
Just hang in there, Doc.
Look, here's Batman.
He'll fix you right up.
Sure he will.
Don't pull it out.
Lift his head up.
(GURGLING)
(WEAKLY) Louisiana!
Don't try to talk.
- It's okay.
- No.
(COUGHS)
Must...
They need swamp water.
Complete...
(COUGHING)
...process.
We're losing him.
(SIGHS)
It's okay, Doc.
You did good.
You did real good.
HARLEY:
We'll take it from here.
Hey Doc.
When you get to heaven,
you should look up my bubbe.
Fran Quinzel.
She's super nice.
I think you two
would really hit it off.
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(CARS HONKING)
It was wrong.
We shouldn't have left
them there, not in the flames.
- What if she...
- Died?
Good.
She's on the
wrong side of this, Ivy.
Don't tell me
you are getting cold feet.
No, I just...
Never mind.
Safe to say
we are thoroughly screwed.
They're bound to have
all the airports and train stations
covered by now.
And I can maybe
disguise myself
and squeak through
the cordon,
but you? (SCOFFS)
Well, it was a nice dream
while it last...
Is that a yam?
A very special yam, yes.
With certain
unique properties.
I removed half
a dozen of these tubers
from Swamp Thing's
corpse a few years ago
while he was
temporarily deceased.
This is my last one.
I've been saving it
for just such an occasion.
Not hungry.
Eat.
It's frozen.
Eat!
(CRUNCHING)
More!
Ugh!
It tastes awful.
Whoa!
Take my hand.
What the...
Relax.
(ECHOING) Concentrate
on our destination.
Become one with the green.
With the green!
Silly me, I almost forgot.
(DISTANT SIRENS)
Oh, man, I'm beat.
How are you doing, Nightwig?
(SIGHS)
Oh, right,
Nightwing, sorry.
It's like that thing
when you can't remember
if it's suppose to be "their"
with E-I-R,
or "they're" with Y-apostrophe-R-E?
You know, you got a 50-50
chance to getting it right
but somehow you always
pick the wrong...
Anyhow... Sorry.
Forget it.
Yeah?
So, we're good?
Sure.
The police
are setting up roadblocks.
Covering the airports,
bus terminals, train stations.
Sarge Steel is calling in the
FBI and the National Guard.
- What about us?
- We're headed to Louisiana...
Fast.
(TURBINES WHIRRING)
The GPS coordinates
for the Holland lab are locked in.
Saddle up.
Thanks for your help.
Hey! Now wait just
a goddamn minute.
That's it?
You got what you wanted
and now you just
gonna dump me?
Like Nightwing over here?
Captain Kirk'ing me for info
and then...
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
"See you later, toots"?
Hey, you were the one who...
And I never...
You need me, Batman!
Uh-huh. That's right.
You need me!
You saw how tough
Plant Guy is.
Tossing you guys
around like raggedy dolls.
If he kicked your butts again,
then what?
You think you're gonna be able
to sweet-talk Ivy
into giving up
her diabolical plan?
Huh, Mr. Smoothie?
Because I got to tell you,
your line ain't that great.
- And beside...
- Enough!
I can't trust you.
But I thought...
I mean, we...
You are the walking definition
of "loose cannon", Harley.
For all I know,
you might decide
at the last minute
that Ivy's plan
doesn't sound
so cockeyed after all,
because the wind
changed direction.
Or because it's Thursday.
- But...
- I can't risk it.
The stakes are way too high.
- But...
- But what?
But I'll never survive
the veggie apocalypse!
Once I begged
my mom for a cat,
but I left the back door open
one day and it ran away.
And then I begged her
for a hamster
and I forgot to feed it
for like a month.
So then, then she said that
maybe I could have a plant
so she got me this
itty-bitty fern
in this cute little yellow pot
and I forgot to...
(SOBBING)
Water it!
Well, what if I forget
to water myself?
(HARLEY SOBBING)
Oh, please, Mr. "Kind of scary
"but actually really nice"
Batman.
Please let me come with you.
I can make Ivy change her mind
and give up her diabolical
plan with Tree Guy.
I know I can!
We're pals.
Yeah, good pals
like Jack and Jill.
Or pork and beans.
Oh please. Please!
(HARLEY SOBBING)
You know,
you're always saying,
"Have a contingency plan."
So, your plan B
is Harley Quinn.
God, help us.
HARLEY: Probably should
have mentioned...
I sometimes get
a little airsick.
(VOMITING)
(FLIES BUZZING)
Eh! Eating me alive
out here.
Thank God.
Can I have some of that?
It's concentrated
sulfuric acid.
A super dehydrating agent.
All of the crazy crap
you got stuffed into that belt
and you didn't think
to bring bug spray?
To a freaking swamp?
Um...
What are you good for? Huh?
You're probably just low
on Vitamin B.
Never mind!
Some Boy Scout
you turned out to be.
Ow!
(CHUCKLES)
(CLEARS THROAT)
I can't see how they could
have gotten here ahead of us.
With the airports and
train stations locked down?
Probably not.
But super-villains do tend
to be very resourceful.
All I know is,
if they are here already
you could bet your tushie
Ivy's turned some of these
bushes and trees into
monster watchdogs.
Like Little Shop of Horrors
on steroids.
No fooling.
One time, she turned my stick
and lollipops stick
into a three-headed
snake twig thingy...
While it was still
in my mouth!
HARLEY: I haven't had
a lollipop since.
(CHUCKLES)
What?
What you said before.
I keep thinking about
Plant Guy riding on the subway
in a trench coat and hat.
Like some kind of
seven-foot-tall flasher.
All made out of celery.
(CHUCKLES)
(GASPS)
(MAN SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(BELCHES)
Guess they're
definitely here then.
(HISSING)
They're coming.
I can feel it.
Would you please
stop fidgeting?
I really need to concentrate.
Just hurry.
Almost done.
One last step.
(TAPPING FINGERS)
(SIGHS)
Look out! Ivy trap.
Come on, this way.
Harley!
(GRUNTING)
(ROARS)
What are you doing?
Just what you expected
me to do.
Sucker.
Because it's Thursday.
Harley.
Hiya, sweetie.
Look, sorry about before.
I had to make these jerks
think I was on their side
so I could bring them here
and wrap them up for you,
so you can get on
with your plan.
Nice, huh?
Pammy honey, you got to give
up this crazy plan.
It's really, really nutzoid.
Please don't turn us
all into veggie-people.
There's got to be another way.
You're tampering with things
man was never meant to know.
I'm sure I could put in
a good word for you at your trial.
Because after all,
your heart's in the right place
even if you did kill
all those people.
But please give your plan,
Pammy sweetie honey baby.
Please, please, please.
Please, give up your plan.
What? No, Harley,
the Earth is dying.
I am not destroying the world.
I'm saving it.
IVY: Saving it from the
takers and the users.
We've been surrounded by
men like that all our lives.
But we can change them,
trim them, shape them
like a good gardener.
I don't wanna do it,
I have to do it.
Well, you can't blame
a girl for trying.
(SCREAMS)
Concentrated weed killer.
I always keep them on hand
since the lollipop incident.
I thought we were friends!
Red, friends don't
let friends
kill seven billion people.
- (GROWLS)
- Uh-oh!
- (GRUNTING)
- (EXCLAIMS)
(YELLING)
You really are
an idiot, Harley.
We could have
changed the world,
but you're too dumb
to see that!
Oh yeah?
Smart enough to take
away your spanking stick.
Pretty cool, huh?
(EXCLAIMS)
No, that is cool.
You suck.
(BATMAN GRUNTING)
(ROARS)
(EXPLOSION)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(GUNFIRE)
(STRAINING)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(GRUNTS)
(EXCLAIM)
Seriously, Pammy,
your plan is totally
bat-shit bonkers.
They're killing our world.
What else can I do?
I don't know! Vote Democrat.
Give money to Greenpeace.
That's for saving whales,
moron.
Whatever!
Anything is better than turning
us all into walking brussel sprouts.
(GUNFIRE)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(SQUEALS)
(SCREAMS)
I can do this all night.
I don't have
that kind of time.
(SCREAMS)
No fair!
(GROANING)
That's it?
The virus?
The solution...
To all the world's problems.
One way or another.
What's that's supposed
to mean?
My God, Pammy.
You haven't even tested yet,
have you?
Have you?
Batman said that if you get
just one teensy weensy thing wrong
you could wind up
killing everything on the planet.
Everything, Pammy.
Plants, people, animals.
Everything.
It doesn't matter.
Earth will die anyway
if I don't act.
I'm sorry, Harley,
but I have to roll these dice.
You're gonna make me do it,
aren't you?
Well, when this is all over
just remember,
I gave you a chance.
What are you...
- No.
- That's right, sweetie.
The nuclear option.
You promised me,
you'd never...
Harley, I'm warning you.
Don't you dare!
(SOBS)
(SOBBING) I hate you so much.
Works every time.
Phew!
(GRUNTING)
Holy crap!
Pamela, have you...
So...
This is where your true
allegiance lies,
with that cancerous meat.
We can't do this, Jason.
If we've made
one miscalculation
the whole Earth will die.
A small risk.
And one I'm more
than willing to take.
Well, I'm not.
Pity.
(GRUNTS)
(STRAINING)
Get him, Red!
The plant world belongs to me!
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
Red!
Okay, fugly!
You just bought yourself
a first-class beating.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
At last,
humanity's lunatic reign
is over.
JASON: No longer will this
beautiful Earth be ravaged
by poison and ignorance.
No more will this be a world
of screaming meat!
(RUMBLING)
(WIND WOOSHING)
Is... Is that...
Yes.
Swamp Thing.
Jason Woodrue,
the Earth has indeed suffered
at the hands of mankind.
However,
this is not the way
to right the wrongs
done to Mother Gaia.
Though your cause is just,
your actions
have upset the balance
in the green.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- Yes.
- Watch.
Bet you he's gonna turn
Plant Guy into a stump or something.
But it is not
my place to judge.
Wait, what?
SWAMP THING: All will be
as it will be.
I return now
to the Parliament of Trees,
to seek the hidden truths
at the center of eternity...
No, no, no. No, don't go!
...to know unknowable nature
in all its
infinite splendors.
Screw unknowable nature!
Kick his butt!
Farewell.
Well, that was
a big ass bucket of nothing.
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHING MANICALLY)
- Now what?
- There must be a way.
- I got...
- We've tried everything.
The sonic disruptor
barely fazed him.
- What about...
- And the bio-feedback Batarangs didn't do squat.
- Guys!
- BOTH: What?
Look, you are pros here
and all, but...
Well, he's all
leafy and everything.
Anybody got a match?
(MATCH STRIKES)
Oh, shucks.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCREAMING)
WESLEY: After my wife ran off
with the pizza delivery guy
my OCD started flaring up
and got really bad.
I've been getting up
six or seven times a night
making sure the windows
and doors are locked.
My boss is on my case
all the time
about my productivity
since I have a hard time
peeing anywhere
but my home bathroom.
I lost my wife.
Now I may lose my job,
my house, my cats,
my collection of vintage
toasters and vacuum cleaners.
If I can't get this problem
under control
I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
It sounds to me
like you're a little bit blue.
Oh, yeah?
And that part about you being
wee-wee shy...
That's rough.
I had this cellmate at Arkham
with the same problem.
I says to her,
"Sugar, we got a glass wall
"and a toilet
in the middle of the floor.
"You're in trouble."
(LAUGHING)
Can you help me?
Of course I can, silly.
I'm a regular
Dr. Quinn Medicine Person, ain't I?
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
I'm legally required
to remind you
that my doctorate
is purely honorary
and I'm not a currently
accredited mental-health professional.
Okay.
Well, Wesey.
Okay if I call you Wesey?
- I don't really like it.
- Well, Wesey...
- You could clearly benefit from therapy.
- (INHALES)
I know I did.
But one thing I learned is that
you never get the most out of stuff
when it's just handed to you.
You gotta earn it.
- Right, everybody?
- (AUDIENCE APPLAUDS)
Now, as everybody knows,
the road to mental wellness
is paved with pit bulls.
But all you got to do is
make it to that finish line
way over there
to win a full year of therapy
from a real,
honest-to-goodness shrink.
- (WHIMPERS)
- (AUDIENCE CHEERS)
Come on, don't be like that.
I've got faith in you, Wesey.
Time to turn your life around and
start feeling good about yourself again!
On your mark, get set...
Get healthy!
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
(AUDIENCE GROANS)
You have to look through
the rain to see the rainbow.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
You'll find love
when you stop looking.
(STRAINS)
Hang in there, baby.
(YELLS)
- (SPLASHES)
- (AUDIENCE GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
It takes more muscles to frown
than it does to smile.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(AUDIENCE GASPS)
(COUGHING)
Aw! Ain't that a shame?
Wendell is headed back
to his crummy house
and all those cats
without getting the help
he so desperately needs.
Oh well,
that's it for today's show.
Till next time, folks.
Be good to yourself.
Because everyone else
in the world
is probably out to get you.
Bye-bye.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Subtitles by explosiveskull