[Music playing]
At 7:00, a meeting
with His Holiness
At the Plazo del Gubenaturato,
and then a dinner
At 8:00 to follow.
And to eat?
What?
The course.
Ah.
It was beef last
time, perhaps fowl.
On a Tuesday?
Nothing is guaranteed
except cake.
The pontiff loves his cake.
Road block ahead,
your eminence.
Rock slide ahead.
You'll have to wait
here until it's clear.
I don't hear any machines.
Where are the other workers?
Well then, tell
Cardinal Ponti his bill
Collectors have arrived.
Please, man.
You've gone back on your word.
Too bad that's not
an official sin.
I could go through
the usual channels.
All I want is what's mine.
My soul is no longer for sale.
One way or another, I
will have you in Hell!
Hey, hey, hey!
Harry, I'm not gonna hurt you.
Oh, shit, man! [Screaming]
Stop acting like
a two year old!
But you're scaring me, Dario!
Dickhead!
If I don't get some new
leads, I'm out of a job,
And you're out of a job.
Some fucking job, you prick.
I was making more money when
I was pimping your old lady.
Hey, don't mess with me, Harry.
I'm a scary man.
Ooh, all right, all right.
I surrender, oh lord
of intense emotions.
I got your leads
right here, man.
I'm sorry.
OK, but get this, man.
It's like these
are all connected.
It's really fucked up, man.
It's something big.
Something really big.
All right, all right.
Terminator pope plans
to nuke the Vatican.
OK, OK.
An 18-year-old brain
is transplanted
Into an 81-year-old's body.
And I quote, "I want to get
to heaven fast," he says.
OK, OK.
Elvis caught in bed with Satan?
Meat gone bad?
Uh, freak boy loves his
bathtub full of pudding, Perry.
Those stories have
already been done.
But man, they're all connected!
Don't you see?
What's wrong with you?
Forget it.
I'll find a goddamn
story by myself.
Dario!
Dick!
Go to Hell!
[Music playing]
Ryan, I just heard the news.
Will you be all right?
It's a temporary restationing.
Nothing more.
Yeah, but I know.
In USA?
Cardinal Ponti's orders.
He wants to make a very
public appearance there
To drum up support.
I think it's a good idea.
Really?
[Laughing]
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Watch your back.
It seems if a betrayal
is an order of business
In Vatican City nowadays.
I'll be fine.
You lazy bum!
Get the hell out of my house!
Hey, hold on!
Fuck you, Eugene!
Don't call me Eugene!
Hey, when are you
gonna make some money
And pay the rent around here?
Work's been slow.
You're slow, you bastard!
Hey, Art said I'd be
getting the next head story.
He promised!
Shut up, you wimp!
Just one more week, Allie.
Please.
Fuck you, Eugene!
Go to Hell!
[Screaming]
[Music playing]
Why did His Eminence pull
me off of this assignment?
Cat, we had no idea that
your cover as a performer
Would go over so well.
Your fans don't even
suspect your affiliations
With the secret workings
of Vatican City.
Things were just
shaping up in there.
Yes, yes.
You were marvelous, weren't you?
But Agent Powell
had advised you not
To get too close to
your fans or your music.
After all, next week,
you might find yourself
In a nunnery in South America.
What do you mean?
Cardinal Ponti has arranged
for a public display of power
In the United States.
You are a senior agent.
He wants you there as
a security measure.
You leave tonight, and
will meet with Agent Tango
At a prearranged rendezvous.
Is she any good?
Yes, well, you'll have to
decide that for yourself.
And Cat, please.
No funny stuff this time.
The American press
will be all over this,
And you know how much power
they have over world events.
Hey, Ursula, is Art around?
What?
Is Art around?
He's arguing the finer points
with the art department.
Thanks, babe.
Thanks for thanking me.
So, uh, are you a female
Elvis impersonator,
A female impersonator
impersonating Elvis, or...
Check this out.
It's like a Victor
Victoria thing.
I'm a man impersonating
a woman impersonating
The king of rock and roll.
Oh, I see.
Oh, Dario.
Don't go in there, man.
Ken will be all over your ass
like a big pair of undies.
The man is a spud.
Make sure Davecki
knows we mean business.
We're dealing with a
readership of... Dare,
What the hell are you doing?
Playing cowboy.
Well, you can't do that here.
It's bad for business,
you lousy screw!
Dare, I want you
in my office, now!
Gee, Art, I didn't
think you cared.
All right, Dare, what
the hell's wrong with you?
Got a lot of personal problems.
Yeah, you got that right.
Here.
Take a look at these covers.
Pretty good stuff.
Right?
Huh?
Nice and safe.
A little Michael Jackson.
A little celebrity dirt.
Not too outrageous.
And if we're feeling
particularly feisty,
Maybe we'll even
do an Elvis story.
Did you write any of these?
No.
Now, take a look
at these and see
If you spot a recurring motif.
Huh?
Look at this stuff.
The Vatican threatened
a libel suit, Dare.
I mean, you can't go around
saying that the Pope is a 5,000
Year old hairdresser dropped
on Earth by the Martians
In the fifth century BC!
But the facts!
The proof spoke for itself!
Oh, forget it, Dare.
This job just ain't your style.
Clean out your desk.
You can go.
Wait.
Right now, I'm... I'm in a slump.
I'll be the first to admit.
My girl kicked me out, and...
Oh, look, is that all?
You need a place to stay?
Why don't you stay
with your brother?
Doesn't he have a big place?
Anthony?
Forget it!
No way!
I am not hanging
out with that freak.
Well, my wife and I
have a spare bedroom.
No one's using it right
now, since my kid went off
To tabloid journalism school.
So, uh...
Yeah?
[Growl]
So here's $30.
Go get a motel.
Dare, we hired you on the
basis of your experience
With the paranormal, so
I've decided to put you
On the Cardinal Ponti story.
What?
The guy's a fake!
Any choir boy worth his weight
I n wafers will tell you that!
Well, he's coming
to town in 36 hours,
And the guy always
puts on a good show!
Why don't you give me that UFO
lead I was telling you about?
Oh, Dare, we missed the
last miracle the guy did.
He's a pariah.
People love that shit.
Catholics are our second biggest
audience after homemakers.
Ponti makes the
cash registers ring!
So get out there!
The guy's a fake.
Those miracles he does are
just old tent revival gigs.
The man's practically a saint.
He's been shot at more times
than he can count, and lived!
Oh, and those assassination
attempts are fake too,
Mr. Cannon.
The ballistic reports the
FBI published are fake.
I got a guy on the inside.
And, uh, check this out, Art.
[Singing]
Hey, that's a good angle.
Let me take that, Art!
Art?
No more conspiracies.
Give me pop stars!
Professionalism!
Photos!
And proof!
The golden Ps.
Isn't that P, S, P, F, and P?
Oh, get the hell out of here.
And take that yodeling
Elvisita with you!
What the hell is this?
MAN: Mecca Arena,
get me the Skull.
No lacquer.
What are you going to do?
Tell them, Dario.
Dario Dare here!
Let me tell you something.
Jimmy the Skull?
It's all over for you
tonight at the Mecca!
My man, the Rock and
Roll Miracle... oh,
Let me just say this!
1991 has been the year that
rock and roll has been reborn!
The Rock and Roll Miracle
came down from the sky,
And he's looking right
at you, Jimmy the Skull!
Tonight, it's all over!
Steel cage match, Jimmy!
That's right.
Tonight, on the WWW Square...
I need a room.
Aye, we can do
that for you, sir.
Say, you look just
like that fellow.
Like... like... like Dario
Dare, the wrestling fellow!
You look just like him.
Yeah, I look like
him, sound like him,
I even dress like him, too.
Man, I am Dario Dare.
What an honor!
The Dario Dare in me very
own bed and breakfast!
You know, wrestling
is me favorite sport.
How about that room?
Aye, we got our
best suite open.
Number seven.
Lucky seven.
Would you autograph
this for me, please?
To?
Polo.
My name's Polo, like the game.
Or like that smelly
stuff, the cologne.
Polo McCrimmin, of
the clan McCrimmin.
To Polo.
So what are you doing now?
Not enough.
A man with your reputation?
I'm working for the
National Explainer.
I'm a writer now.
The Explainer!
That's me favorite
magazine, lad!
Would you... would you... would
you sign this, too, please?
To Polo.
Would you give me
the fucking room now?
Dario Dare.
[Laughing]
You wrestling managers!
You got such a way
with the language!
Sure, your room.
You rang?
Aye.
Please take Mr. Dario Dare's
things to our celebrity suite.
Which one is that?
Number seven.
They're identical.
No they're not.
I don't have anything
to, uh, carry.
Thanks anyways.
You could take me
to my room, though.
This way, Dare.
That's Mr. Dare.
He's a celebrity.
This is the big night, Jimmy!
It's all over!
The little mask thing
isn't going to work!
The hokey pokey
and the spookiness!
Put your mojo bone away, pal.
It's all over.
Ring the bell.
Oh, the referee!
I can hear him
counting to three!
You hear that, Jimmy?
It's all over!
Oh, boy!
Celebrity, huh?
Not anymore.
I'm a working guy now.
Sort of.
Hey, uh, want to step back
later for a night cap?
Here.
You're going to need this.
You know, I have
the strange feeling
I've seen you somewhere before.
Miss April, 1988.
I knew it!
You have the greatest... ow.
[Phone ringing]
MAN: Hey man, it's
back in a motion
Picture that will make you never
want to see another film again.
Hello, Nancy, a tale of lust
and honor in the Third Reich,
With Nancy, mistress
extraordinaire
On the Sieg Heil set.
She must come after
the pastoral herd
Animal love making
montage, otherwise
The motivation is for poo poo!
[Phone ringing]
Wait.
What is that effect?
How could a phone be ringing?
It's off the hook?
It's your cell, Van Halen.
Pick it up.
Hello?
Oh, Dario!
What a super prize surprise!
Hey, everybody!
It's my brother!
Listen, Tony.
I need...
Please call me A Man, Dario.
You changed your name to A Man?
What's wrong with my name?
It's a name of stage and screen.
Everybody knows Dario isn't
your real name, Eugene.
Eugene, Eugene, Eugene.
Fine.
Listen, A Man, Alison
kicked me out, and...
A monstrous decree of travesty
has befallen my dear Dario.
The she wolf will pay for this.
Alison kicked you out
of your own house?
No, no, no.
She was perfectly
justified in what she did.
Why, that little
Sadian wench biscuit.
It's not your house?
Well, I mean, you pay
rent on the bloody thing.
It may as well be.
You don't?
Oh.
Ho hum.
Maybe you can live with me,
humble servant of Dionysus
In the palace of pleasure.
Bedazzled by a glowing in my
presence once again, brother!
But you'd have to share a
room with the mountain lion.
Hello?
It appears his
desires have changed.
Gino, where's my cappuccino?
Why are you looking at
me, you filthy thing?
Get my cino!
You are the ginkiest A Man!
That's me.
Mm-hm.
[Laughing]
Jimmy the Skull!
You went down!
Oh, you didn't last
very long in that cage!
One, two, three, it's all over!
Rock!
What's... what...
Yeah!
Hello, lady.
Welcome to Polo Celebrity Motel!
Oh my God!
Oh, God!
Oh.
That's me favorite sport.
You like wrestling too, maybe?
[Screaming]
With the right person.
I need a room.
Very good.
Cash or credit?
Ah.
We take this.
Miss, uh... Catalina Powers?
Cat.
I knew it!
You're that singer from
New York, aren't you?
Among other things.
How do you now?
There isn't a whole lot to
do out here in the sticks.
I read a lot.
I really loved your last CD.
Thank you, Miss?
Tango.
Marian.
Uh, I read too, you know.
You read tabloids, Polo.
Not exactly Oscar Wilde.
Only the Explainer, lassie.
It's me favorite magazine!
How long are you staying?
Until my work is done.
Oh?
What are you doing here in town?
Ponti sent me.
Ponti?
No need to play coy with me.
These bags contain
your equipment
And mission briefings.
The usual security
measures apply.
Do you have a map of town?
There's this.
Not very detailed.
I can't believe
you're one of us.
The Cat Powers.
Sore?
Take off your shoes.
Relax.
You can trust me.
I may be a secret agent for the
Vatican, but I'm just a girl.
You are so amazing.
[Burp]
You seem very familiar to me.
Have I seen you in the academy?
I modeled a few years ago for
a couple of men's magazines.
Cardinal X wants this all
to go off without a hitch.
Yes.
Do you understand your orders?
You got the greatest...
Oh my god.
So, you ever thought about
returning to the ring, lad?
Hell no.
Are you kidding?
It's too violent.
It nearly killed me.
Serious now?
Oh, yeah.
Listen, I'm no fighter.
Writing for the Explainer
is more respectable anyway.
Hmm.
What kind of stories
they got you writing now?
Some sports, but mostly
reporting on the paranormal.
Aye, me cousin was a
wee bit paranormal, too.
No, no, no.
It's like, the strange, the
bizarre, the unexpected.
Well, you know, we've got
a lot of that around here.
Really?
The other night, down
by the sausage factory,
I saw something that scared
the bejeezus out of me!
That... wait.
If I tell you, do I get
to be in the Explainer,
Next to the two-headed
lizard lovechild?
Aye, I saw...
Polo, what did you see?
You know we're going?
Oh, aye, sir.
Just you wait and see.
Great rocks, Polo.
Shh.
Get down.
You don't want them to hear you.
The rocks?
The demons!
Sit down.
It may be a while
before we see them.
Sometimes, there will be
groovy bright lights, too.
Maybe a space ship or something.
It'd make a great story.
Will the hotel get mentioned
if it's printed, lad?
[Snorting]
That's them, lad!
Fantastic.
They don't look like aliens.
It be the devil's work.
Yeah, well, Satan
makes great press.
Got a built in audience
of every God-fea...
Where the hell are they?
Do you think
they've seen us, lad?
Uh, yeah.
[Screaming]
[Laughing]
Took a wrong turn there, Dario.
You have an appointment in Hell.
Oh, shit!
[Non-english speech]
[Laughing]
Eat this!
Bloody hell, let's
get out of here!
Damn it, lad, that was close.
Well, Cannon's
got his story now!
I don't understand.
You go to this quarry, and
these robed demons chase you,
And then you run into
this guy with a hat...
A hard hat.
And then he says
something in a... in a...
Weird otherworldly voice!
How many of those
beers have you guys had?
Damn it, lassie, it was real!
Mr. Dare, he's got
pictures to prove it!
Is this true?
It is, my dear.
It is.
You have failed.
How could you fail?
Their strength
is great, master.
You ruined my robe, great one.
Silence!
No excuses!
It's falling apart, just time.
Get there, and get him alone.
The robed creatures, along with
their supernaturally endowed
Suited accomplice, all
seem to add up to... yeah!
Get him!
Get him, get him,
get him! [Shouting]
Don't open this
door for anyone.
Why?
Those guys are full
of shit, aren't they?
Maybe.
Come on, you bastards!
I know you're out there!
Come and fight me!
What are you doing out here?
Uh, protecting you ladies.
Super.
And the honor of
the Clan McCrimmin.
Bozo.
[Screaming]
Ow.
Idiot.
What took you so long?
I'm tired.
Huh?
[Gunshots]
Hey!
Stop it!
That hurts!
Quit it!
Stop it!
Whoa, Mr. Dare.
Report.
We have Dario Dare,
my lord, but we
Got more than we bargained for.
One Polo Angus McCrimmin,
motel owner, and Catalina
Powers, agent of Vatican City.
Vatican, eh?
Erase Miss Powers
from existence.
Don't want any of those
fruitcakes down here.
Enslave McCrimmin on
Level D. And as for Dario,
Strip him and bring
him before me!
Sign in!
Greetings, Dario.
You look like hell.
[Laughter]
What is this place?
Let's just say you went south.
Come on, guess.
Guess.
What, no?
It's Hell!
I'm not surprised.
I lived my life the
way I wanted to.
Oh, you're not dead.
And I suppose you're not Satan.
You flatter me.
Beazley.
Bob Beazley.
Beazley Bob.
Beelzebub.
Very funny.
Prove it.
Prove that any of this is real.
We are a very
shapers of reality.
Each and every one of us.
For example, you and I both
know that professional wrestling
Is real, but how many
people claim otherwise?
And how many people have laughed
off the National Explainer
As a rag full of lies?
Hey, everything I write
is the God honest truth!
No offense.
People put down the
National Explainer
Because it doesn't fit in
with their predetermined
Sense of reality.
Just because people haven't
seen a Bigfoot in person,
They assume it doesn't exist.
But the very same
individuals will never
See a platypus or
an emu in person,
But believe in them
unquestioningly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I've said that too.
But listen, Bob.
This whole Ronnie James
Dio playhouse you got here?
Um, I'm not buying it.
I admit you had me
hooked here for a while,
But when that broad came in
with the gun firing blanks?
I mean, come on, guys.
It's not even Halloween.
I'm sorry, but the Shriners
put on a better spook show
Than you dudes.
Hey!
[Screaming]
[Laughter]
Fuck you, Bobby, my man!
That's the Dario
Dare I know and love.
Now look, chum, I'll make
this painfully obvious to you.
I need you.
You are going on a mission...
An assassination, to be exact.
You are to terminate
Cardinal Giancarlo Ponti
And bring his soul to me.
Sorry, Bob.
You got the wrong guy.
I'm a reporter, not a lone nut.
Besides, can't you
guys kill him yourself?
You don't need a killer.
You need a patsy.
Oh, we tried the usual paths.
But his powers are the
equal of my own by now.
Only a surprise
attack will work.
No more of this frontal
assault nonsense.
Powers?
But I thought...
Oh, it's real, Mr. Dare.
Ponti and I had a deal.
I gave him some minor powers
in exchange for his soul.
A routine transaction.
Bait and switch, as
we call it down here.
And now, as usual, the asshole
wants to keep his little soul.
You mean all his
miracles are Hell powered?
Far out.
I knew that Ponti wasn't
as pure as Perrier.
But what does he want?
He wants to be Pope.
Pope is power.
Some men will do anything to
be in a position of leadership.
And what do you get?
Even.
Oh, I had aspirations.
An agent of Satan in the
Vatican, a car in every garage,
A baby in every stove.
You see, soul ownership is a
bit of a trade here in Hell,
And I've got some real
winners in my collection.
The Marquis de Sade, Edgar Allen
Poe, John Holmes, Liberace.
That's how I got this palace.
Overachievement!
In the service of
our King Satan.
And do you know what my crowning
Earthly achievement was?
What?
Jonestown.
The Guyana tragedy.
You did Jonestown?
Let's just say I had agreements
with a few key people.
Kool-Aid, Mr. Dare?
Later.
Ponti would have
been my masterpiece.
[Grunt] A toast to all
my friends, and to you,
Dare, for taking the job.
I'm not taking the job.
Oh, too late to back
out now, old chum.
I have something you want.
Look familiar?
Oh, I suppose not.
You've never seen a soul before.
It's yours, Dario.
Shake shake shake, shake shake
shake, shake your soul jar!
Well, it's a bit tarnished,
and a little bit smaller
Than when you first started.
But it must mean
something to you.
What now, goddammit?
Missile attack, my liege!
Mistress Gumbata is at it again!
Gumbata!
Ow!
Enough!
Playtime is over.
So long, Dario.
We'll be in touch.
Dickhead.
I don't care about security.
I want to speak to Cardinal X,
Vatican facilitator right now.
I've got a missing
agent on my hands.
Agent Tango, why are you
using an unsecured line?
X?
Screw you.
I'm not in the mood
for formalities.
What did you do with Cat Powers?
Why would we do anything to one
of our own operatives, Maria?
Now, tell me where you are.
So you can have
me eliminated too?
Cat Powers left the motel at
11:36 in full battle dress.
Where did you send her?
Surely I don't know what
you're talking about.
We've issued no
orders of any kind
From this office in
the last 10 hours.
Now get a grip.
Cardinal Ponti will be
arriving in just a few hours.
A few hours? [Muffled shout]
Didn't you read
the briefing yet?
Tango?
Tango!
It's me, Your Holiness.
You idiot!
Get Tango out of sight now!
[Screaming]
Check me out!
I'm not naked!
No one naked over here!
Not naked.
Yeah.
Check me out, because
I'm not naked!
Yeah!
No one naked over here.
BOB (VOICEOVER): This
is your mission, Dare.
Should you decide not to accept
it, your soul will rot in Hell,
Your body will become
demonized, zombified,
And eventually give out.
So don't waste
any time reporting
This to the
authorities, or trying
To get anyone on your side.
This the Hellion
7,000 sniper rifle.
Bolt action, 7.62 millimeter,
with an eight power scope
And a specially outfitted soul
catcher... the chrome cylinder
You see before you.
When fired at a living human,
the bullet takes the life
While the soul catcher
attracts the life
Force contained therein.
It's simple, Mr. Dare.
His life for yours.
His soul for your own.
Just shoot straight and leave
the rest to the soul catcher.
At the moment the soul
catcher is occupied,
We will teleport
you back to hell
And reunite you with your soul.
Sounds peachy, huh?
Don't mess it up.
Too tight?
Ow.
Too bad.
Your reputation
precedes you, Marion.
Three years in Laos,
two in Costa Rica.
Personal assistant to Bishop
Schikel Gruber in Berlin?
Quite a dossier.
If you two are that fond
of me, a simple fan letter
Would have sufficed.
Idolatry is a sin, Miss Tango.
But so is killing, and
that hasn't stopped us yet.
As long as we
confess afterwards,
I suppose there
isn't anything we
Won't do in the line of duty.
A quote comes to mind.
Kill them all.
God will know his own.
Arnold Amelrick
Pabelaget, 12:08.
You guys are crazier than
you look, you know that?
Take Cardinal
Ponti, for instance.
A real up and comer, they say.
A shoo-in for the
[inaudible], the next Pope.
Let's just say he
hasn't got a prayer.
Not with his cheap
bodyguards out of the way.
So what do you think
you can get away with?
This is the 20th century, in
case you haven't been counting.
The Holy See transcends
time, my dear.
Since when have local laws
and rules of etiquette
Applied to its membership?
The Pope is the last
true sovereign figure
In all of Europe!
Are you paying attention?
She could confess at any moment!
You're ranting.
I am not ranting.
I am warming her up.
What is this?
Good agent, bad agent?
Hey, handsome, give me
a hit off that shake.
God, how could you?
Sharing straws. Ugh!
Do you mind?
Go sit down.
There's just a few things we
need to know if our plan is
To go off without a hitch.
MAN: Finally, the JFK
board game was here.
I've been waiting six
weeks for this thing.
[Knocking]
Come in!
- Hey, Kirk.
- Dario!
I don't believe it.
You're just in time!
I invited you over here
five years ago, man,
And you're finally here.
I just... look what I just got!
The JFK board game!
You're just in time to play it.
Oh, this is great.
You want anything?
Like some ice cubes, or...
Oh, hey, muffins!
Muffins, muffins, oh, hey!
Yeah.
Those are... those
are my muffins.
No, those are my muffins, Dario.
Jesus Christ, man.
Special, uh... special
muffins for me.
You're a big
conspiracy nut, right?
Oh, am I?
Oh, god, you
wouldn't believe it!
I mean, I got books,
tapes, CD-ROM, cassettes.
I mean, I got a subscription to
Paranoid Creep Magazine, even.
I mean, you can ask me
any question you want.
Any question.
Go ahead.
Like who did the
autopsy on Kennedy
At the Bethesda Naval
Hospital and then
Burned all of his notes?
Go ahead, ask me.
Who?
I don't know, but
I can look it up.
I got it right here.
Uh, here it is.
Humes.
Commander James Humes.
No.
He's the guy who... he...
He burned his notes,
And... oh, man.
I know.
Amazing.
I want you to go
to the Basilica
And take some pictures for me.
Get a camera.
Take some pictures
for me of Ponti.
Oh, no, that's your story.
Cannon gave it to you.
That's not... that's your story.
Yeah, but how
many pictures have
You seen of Ponti
with his head exploded
From a sniper's bullet?
What are you talking about?
Well, if you just show up
at the Basilica with some
Pictures of Ponti, for me...
Yeah?
You will have the
scoop of the century.
Huh.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
Can you do that for me?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- By the way.
- Jim Jones?
Yeah?
The Kool-Aid is
green and not red.
You owe me $5.00.
I'll pick it up later.
Oh.
Don't forget, an hour from now.
Basilica!
Be there!
I'll be here if you want
to come over in five years.
I'll...
Be there in an hour!
Oh, yeah!
I'll see you.
This is XD253, a truth
drug engineered right
Here in the United States.
Used successfully numerous
times on intelligence gathering
Missions such as this.
You guys can use about as much
intelligence as you can gather.
It would be wise to keep
your mouth shut while you can,
For as soon as the XD253
reaches your brain,
You're going to be doing
a lot of talking that
You'll wish that you weren't.
Oh, baby, I get her
when you're finished.
Uh, yeah.
You look like you could make me
sing without any fancy needles
Or formulas.
How about you and I abscond to
the next room for a little tete
A tete?
What's abscond mean?
She's trying to trick you.
Forget it!
I'm gonna do it to her now!
What are you...
Relax.
Idiot!
This is a complete
waste of time.
Maybe for you it is.
Can I at least ask
you some questions?
It's your thing!
Go ahead.
Where is your partner?
Here I come, baby.
Now I'll try again.
Where is Cat Powers?
Ow!
I don't know!
I thought Cardinal X...
Cardinal X?
Cardinal X what?
Took her.
Oh my god.
So wait, you do or you
don't know where she is?
Is that yes to the first
and no to the second, or...
Could you stop talking?
I'm trying to pay attention.
What is the
Cardinal's itinerary?
I don't know that either!
I haven't read it yet.
By the merciful son of God,
don't you know anything?
I don't think so!
[Groaning] Thank
you very much! Baby!
Thanks, sweetheart.
You're a real charmer.
Hey, uh, what can
I get you for lunch?
Corn dogs?
Finally, back on schedule!
I can't.
[Screaming]
[Laughing]
You know, I read
every manual on torture
In the Vatican library.
Really.
I just finished last
week, oh, what was it?
Um, Malleus Maleficarum.
Oh, what a book.
Words to live by!
Now, an opportunity
to use that knowledge.
What luck!
You, my dear, are a door.
Your body, your
mouth, your lips,
All are a doorway to the
knowledge that lies within.
Now I just need
to find that key.
What is your key?
What do I need to twist to get
you to give up your secrets?
No fair.
Oh, yes!
Oh, come to papa!
Bet she's got some
some hot panties on!
Oh, she's the one.
Oh yeah!
No, that one!
That's the one!
Oh, yeah.
Fucking lone nuts.
Damned if you do,
damned if you don't.
Oh my god!
[Groan]
[Groaning]
All right, Beazley, or
whoever the hell you are!
I did my job!
Now give me back my soul!
Give it back!
Mr. Johnson, do you have any
connections with the Vatican?
The Vatican?
I'm not even Catholic.
Uh, how about a militia group?
Do you belong to
a militia group?
No, I'm a security guard.
I work for Stone Security.
Any idea what... what
groups may be involved
In this particular conspiracy?
No, I have no idea at this
time what other groups may
Be involved in this conspiracy.
Is it true that you have not
found a murder weapon yet?
Yes, it is true we have not
found a murder weapon yet.
Do you have any other
targets besides the Cardinal?
No, you're not listening!
I didn't shoot anyone!
I didn't shoot the Cardinal.
Why would I have other targets?
I'm a patsy.
I need a lawyer.
[Shouting]
[Screaming]
Security cameras and
witnesses at the scene
Corroborate the presence of
this man, suspected to be
Joey Ramone, rock musician and
member of the band Ramones.
If you have any clues as to
the whereabouts of Joey Ramone,
Please call the
number on your screen.
Then, out of the
corner of my eye,
I spot the rifle
barrel coming into view
On top of the Warren building!
Boom!
Bravely into the hail of
bullets I went, charging ahead,
My camera rattling
off shot after shot.
And before I know it, I got
the photographs of the decade!
I tell you, Ponti's not dead.
He's gonna pull a
Christ in three days.
According to this diagram
I had the boys at the lab
Draw up for me, there
were two gunmen.
As an overwhelming
number of witnesses say,
There were two shots
fired, one from on top
Of the Warren building,
the other across
At the gas and power office.
The paths of the bullets
fired, along with the street
In front of the
Basilica, form a pyramid.
Which is the symbol
used by the Freemasons!
Which means CIA.
What about his palm
print on the rifle?
Ah, forget about it.
The paraffin tests on James
Johnson's hands were positive.
Positive for what?
He fired a rifle today.
Guilty.
Johnson didn't do it!
Patsy!
Guilty!
Patsy, patsy,
conspiracy, conspiracy!
Well, if he didn't
do it, then who did?
[Groaning]
Dare, where the
hell have you been?
I thought that was
your goddamn story!
I mean, what the Christ?
Oh, it's my story, all right.
But I could do one better.
Disillusioned Catholic kid,
spirited to Satan's court,
Forced to commit acts of
murder in order to save soul.
Kills member of the
Roman Catholic Church.
Dare, I said no more
bullshit fantasy stories.
Kuric Camp here managed
to get the major league
Snaps today at the Plaza.
He's not feeding me a
line of crap like you.
Oh, but then it gets better.
Devil goes back on his word.
Kid becomes demonized.
Kid kills his boss!
Wait, wait, wait a minute.
What are you doing?
Wait, wait, hold it, hold it!
[Screaming]
[Thunder]
If I can't kill him, I'll
settle for all of your panties.
[Laughing]
[Screaming]
I think Dario killed
the Cardinal, Mr. Cannon.
No fucking shit!
I think he was working
for the... the builder
Burgers or Rosicrucians.
J. Jonah Jesus on a... on
a dangling rubber crutch!
Did anybody get that?
Get the printer on the line
and hold the front page!
We're going exclusive on this!
[Laughing]
Rock!
I thought I might
find you here.
Why?
Star reporter?
Shit, I gotta ask
for more money.
Kid, I know you
better than anyone,
And I know you may be a
misogynistic caveman, a
Stupid pervert, and a knothead.
But you're not evil.
What the hell's going
on with you, man?
I lost my soul, Rock and Roll.
It's gone.
It's rotting in Hell
for all eternity.
OK, maybe.
But you're a man with friends,
and a man with friends
Can work his way
through any situation.
Well, eventually.
I want to be good again, Rock!
I want to be the good guy!
I want to go into that
ring, guaranteed victory!
No more this
designated loser crap.
You can do it.
Impossible.
It'll take some kind of miracle
for me to get my soul back now.
Oh, you got the magic, kid.
It's inside you.
It's inside us.
It's family.
What are you talking about?
You got a big question, right?
A big Q?
Yeah.
What's every Q have?
An answer.
An A, man.
A Man!
My brother Anthony!
Of course!
You're coming with me, right?
Nope.
Then what's with all this
friends can help you shit?
[Laughing] Screw that!
I got better things to do
than be killed with you, you
Little butt.
At least give me a ride.
Forget it.
Start again.
Rethink it.
Yes, yes, more of that!
Excellent!
Oh, yeah!
Big company.
Oh, more of that.
Yes!
Yeah, that's it.
Yes.
Let it go.
That's it.
Get the hair back,
get the hair back.
Excellent.
I like it!
Yeah!
Make it pop.
Looks like crap.
Edge, who is this victim?
Will someone please
shoot him with a gun?
Oh, no killing, no killing!
He is mine.
He is my blood.
He comes in here
again, he's going
To be blood all over the floor.
All right.
Ava Maria.
Take five.
Dario, oh cheeky one,
how many times have I told
You never to interrupt my work?
Never.
You never said that, ever.
I need your help, Tony.
Please address me
as A Man, Dario,
Especially in the
presence of my entourage.
Entourage?
Aren't these the people
that used to work
With you at the Dairy Queen?
I should say not!
These are some of
the high fashion
Models lucky enough to be
photographed at my site today.
Aren't they super?
[Growling] Anyone willing to
part with their panties today?
My doctor recommends it!
Say, I have a problem.
You can say that again.
By the way, did you say
my name with a capital A,
Or with a small A?
Will you knock it
off with that A shit?
Oh, what a drag
you are, my brother.
Hey, do you still
have that book?
That one by John D. That
was found in Austria?
This one?
You bet, baby.
Great bedside reading when
I'm entertaining members
Of the local witches coven!
I need to go to Hell.
You're here, man, you're here!
No, I'm serious.
I was just there.
Now I need to go back
and settle some business
With Bob Beazley, a very
powerful and influential demon.
Now, if you don't mind, we need
to do this pretty damn quick,
Because I'm turning into
Eddie fucking Munster.
Zounds!
What an accessory!
It's beautiful.
Why would you want
to... can I touch it?
Maybe we can use
you in the spread.
Just give me the
damn spellbook!
No.
Teddy, can we use
the studio tonight
To perform a
mystical incantation
Designed to send my brother
to the very pits of Hell?
No.
We will perform the
most magical ceremonies
This very eve!
Get your things, my
mystical confidants.
We begin at once!
[Cheering]
Bless me, Father,
for I have sinned.
It's been zero zero five niner
since my last confession.
Agent Tango?
I know who killed
Cardinal Ponti.
I was there when it happened.
And it wasn't that
guy on television,
And it wasn't the dark haired
agent on the roof of the gas
And power building, either.
It was Dario Dare.
Dario?
Dare.
He's a tabloid journalist.
He's a weaselly little man.
Hardly significant.
And certainly not an
agent or a hired gun.
I'm sure he did it.
The only thing I can't
be sure of is why.
I think it has something
to do with the attempt
On Ponti's life last
month at Castrovillari.
At which you were also present.
Well, I didn't include
this in my official report,
But they were robed
soldiers there.
Men.
Dead men.
Raised by some unholy power.
And Dare had congress
with them the night
Before the
assassination, when he
Met the man with the hard hat.
The man in the hard hat?
Oh, I know this all
sounds ridiculous,
But Dare is the shooter
at Basilica Plaza!
I know that!
Now I just need to
determine if he's
Involved with the anti-Ponti
constituent at Vatican City.
I think you should
come with me, Marion.
Cardinal X will be very
interested in your findings.
What do you mean?
We see it somewhat
differently, Agent Tango.
First, the incident
at Castrovillari
When you failed to
protect Cardinal Ponti,
Stands as a noticeable
but forgivable
Blemish on your record.
Then, I'm disturbed by the
unexplained disappearance
Of Agent Catalina Powers
from your remote station.
Are you suggesting that I
had something to do with it?
Then, when he was
under your protection,
The absolutely inexcusable
public execution
Of a member of the Holy
Roman Catholic Church.
I have no option but to take
you in for further questioning.
Please, no flash
photography during the event.
OK, so how's this work?
First, we sit on
the ancient stone.
It's styrofoam.
Ancient stone!
Pretend!
Before we send you to the
darkness of the great pit,
We need to bring you
a little sunshine!
Hey!
How now, my brother?
The demon in you is strong.
To kill you will take
extreme measures.
Thank you, Kristen.
Get that shit away from me!
Blasphemer!
Body of Christ!
[Growling]
Blood of Christ.
[Gagging]
It has begun.
Hey!
Tony, get these
chains off of me!
Goomba, he lives!
[Applause]
No thanks to you.
Oh, please.
I rock the material and
the spiritual world.
Sorry about the anguish, but
it's only part of the process.
Do you want to go to
the burning hell or not?
But first, you must
dress the part.
Come!
Much improved.
My brother dresses me funny.
Can you believe this?
And also, a gift, to
help you on your way.
Oh, candy!
[Non-english speech]
I didn't know he was
multidenominational.
I call upon the powers
of good and evil!
Hear me, powers, and know that
this priest means business!
[Non-english speech]
Hey, man.
You're doing it wrong.
What?
The chant.
It's [non-english speech].
Dionysus!
Oh, great god of
all that is super!
How's it going?
Dionysus?
Oh, please, Dario.
Everyone knows
he's my patron god.
My apologies, oh partying one.
My lame-o brother knoweth
not what he speaketh.
Your guidance is always welcome.
Thank you, A Man.
But you know, my assistance
is not without its cost.
Not you.
Oh, you, beauties, come to me.
[Laughter]
Ciao, mi amores.
Godspeed, Dario.
Dickhead.
Bing, bang, boom.
Deus ex machina special effect.
OK, Dario has gone into Hell.
Wait.
Can't send mortals into
hell without special help.
I'll lend him my ivory chariot.
Nope, not insured for mortals.
Uh.
Oh!
I'll give him some
able-bodied help.
Miss Marion Tango.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Hey, you're that
maid at Polo's motel!
What the fuck are
you doing here?
Why did you kill
Cardinal Ponti?
Cardinal Ponti
was my benefactor,
And it's my job to protect him!
And it's my job to see
that the man who shot him
Is brought to justice.
Is that before or after you
get done cleaning motel rooms?
I'm not a maid!
Good, because
those rooms sucked!
Are you trying to deny it?
Listen, lady, I was
just doing my job.
And I'm doing my job.
So I'm going to
bring you to justice.
Now put your hands up on your
head and come along quietly.
Come quietly where?
This is Hell!
And since when do motel maids
go around enforcing the law?
Uh-uh!
I am not a maid!
I am an agent of Vatican City.
Vatican?
You mean pope, tall
hat, and stick Vatican?
So what?
Don't you have any
remorse for what you did?
I'm in Hell, aren't I?
That should tell you something.
So this is Hell.
Could be worse.
I guess I expected
something more dramatic.
More fire or something.
Is it all like this?
No.
There's a palace up ahead.
How did we get
down here, anyway?
My a-hole brother
did a spell on me.
Why did you let your
brother send you to Hell?
Look, some guy stole my soul.
He's holding it ransom.
Only I paid that
ransom, and that
Was killing Cardinal Ponti.
And he still won't
give it back, OK?
Get up to speed on this.
I'm only here to
get my soul back.
Got it?
So am I dead?
Oh, Christ.
No more questions!
Boss, boss, white alert.
Two humans spotted
in the Elysian Plain.
What?
MAN (ON INTERCOM): Human
beings approaching the palace.
Patch it in.
Blood red, Dario Dare,
how did he get here?
[Screaming]
There he is.
Cat?
You're alive!
Well, sort of.
You are alive, aren't you?
Alive, dead.
We're in Hell.
Well, come along with us.
We're getting out of this place.
Dare knows the way.
Hey.
How are you doing?
I can't.
My people need me.
I found my true calling.
I don't understand.
I'm saving souls.
That's what I joined
the Vatican for.
That's what it used to mean
before people like Cardinal X
Turned it into an
assassin's cult.
So you knew about the
plot to kill Ponti.
I suspected.
No, the world of the
living isn't is for me.
My underground railroad is
doing far more good here than I
Could have ever done topside.
Good luck, Marion Tango.
And I hope someday you find
what you're looking for, too.
Hey, wait a minute!
How do you rate?
I had to kill a cardinal to
get out of Beazley's palace!
What did you do?
I killed a few guards.
Damn, I should have
thought of that!
My candies!
Hey!
Let's go!
Yes.
Look, dearie, I've
been here before.
I know the way out of here.
Stick with me.
I'll protect you.
Thanks, but no thanks.
What makes you think I
can trust you, anyway?
Does this look like
the face of a liar?
Whoa!
My everything!
An idiot, maybe.
Did you watch, uh,
Lawrence Welk last night?
Are you kidding?
It's the closest thing to music
we've got down here. [Humming]
Ugh, can't you smell that?
Choose not to.
Besides, it's going to get a
lot worse than that upstairs.
Lord Kuric, an intruder
has entered the palace.
You must find and dispatch
him with violent haste.
Come on!
Hey, you don't belong in here.
This is a restricted area.
Commander, I'm relieving
you of your duties.
Who are you?
Dario Dare, motherfucker!
Bam!
You.
Hey.
You're Dario Dare.
I was just telling the
guys down in torture
That if anybody would end up
down here, it'd be Dario Dare.
Can I get your autograph?
Wow.
Thanks.
So, uh, Gus, how's this
setup of yours work?
Well, you've got the
map here, and then you've
Got the switch up here where
you lock on your coordinates
And hit your target.
Then you hit this
button, and major damage!
[Phone ringing]
Yes?
Sir, Dare is in the
missile command center.
[Growling]
Lord Kuric, Dare is in the
missile command center!
Get him at all costs!
Stop at nothing!
Targets locked on.
Gambada's [inaudible].
Gambada?
Lock and load.
Launch 'em, baby.
Missiles away.
What?
These disguises
aren't going to help.
If this Gambada has
missiles and counterattacks,
This place is gonna be hopping.
They're not going to
worry about little old us.
Yeah, and I can
get my soul back.
With only minor setbacks!
Who's this?
A minor setback.
You have been a
very naughty boy.
My lord Beezley has sent me,
and Kuric, his errand boy,
To wreak exquisite pain upon
your naughty little behinds.
Which one do you want?
I'll take the French guy.
You get the quarterback.
Sorry, my sweet, but I
called dibs on Dario, dear.
Bleh!
Un.
Deux.
[Laughing]
Trois!
[Screaming]
So, you are ready to play, huh?
Don't worry, I won't break
anything important yet.
I'm a very big fan
of yours, Mr. Dare.
This is a very big honor for me.
I've seen everything that
you do on the wrestling.
Very violent.
I like it a lot.
But you know, I've
always wondered,
You do that thing with that
girl in Michigan, that blonde?
How did you learn that?
I've never even
seen that before.
Very incredible.
Do you mind if I use that?
Oh, sacre bleu, you
stepped on my foot!
[Screaming]
Merde!
[Explosion]
[Shouting]
Thank you.
Right.
No, I mean it.
OK, sure.
Idiot demon boy saves
ex-centerfold nun.
Now, everything's fine.
I'm not a nun.
No?
Does that mean you're...
What?
Celibate?
No.
Are you?
Hell no.
I gave that up for Lent.
Are... you wanna...
You're gonna have to try
a lot harder than that.
Oh, I will.
[Shouting]
Polo?
Mr. Dare!
Marion!
Sorry about trying to kill you.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to save my soul.
Well, it's a strange
place for that, lad.
This is Hell.
Are you dead too, then?
I don't... I'm not dead!
Neither are you!
You got sucked down
here when I did!
Sucked down into Hell?
I don't remember that.
All I remember is fighting,
fighting, fighting!
I've taken over
this whole level!
It's mine now!
I reign supreme!
Polo McCrimmon's level in Hell!
How do you like it?
It's terrific.
It's a... it's a real
fixer upper opportunity.
But do you know
where the souls are
So that we can get out of here?
Souls?
Ah, I think so.
But, uh... oh, I don't remember.
But I'll help you find them,
or I'm not Polo McCrimmon
Of the Clan McCrimmon!
Yeah!
Welcome to the romper room.
Kuric?
Where can he be?
Kuric, do you read me?
Sir, more bad news.
It's Mistress Gambada for you.
Oh, what does she want?
Ah, oh my dear, dear Gambada.
You look positively
radiant today.
Ooh.
I like what you've
done with the place.
Shut your shithole and
listen good, Beezley Bubba.
I'm not radiant.
I'm radiated!
And can you guess why?
Perhaps it was that volley
of missiles your boys just
Shot at my palace.
Hmm?
Well, let me tell you this, you
stupid sack of maggot sputum.
In 16 minutes, you're going
to be crying for mommy,
Because I'm going to
pump enough labidium
Warheads up your tiny lying
ass to fill the Durham Canyon.
How do you like me now?
That's Cardinal Ponti!
Why are they doing this to him?
He's been conditioned.
Converted into one of
Beezley's supreme guard,
There's a ton of warriors.
Those are the same warriors
that Mr. Dare and I saw
In that bright green field
on that fine summer day,
Long, long ago.
You remember.
Isn't that sweet?
You remember that.
Why can't you remember
where the fucking souls are?
Shh!
Why would he... he, a man
of God... end up here?
You know those little
miracles Ponti did?
He made a deal with Beelzebub.
Didn't keep his
end of the bargain.
I can't believe he sold out.
Buck up, little trooper.
There's a lesson
to be learned here.
Always be brave and true?
Always side with
the powers of good?
Always read the fine print.
Wanna bring your earplugs.
[Shouting]
BOB (ON INTERCOM): Ahem.
Ladies and gentlemen, this
is your leader speaking.
In just under six minutes,
this palace will be
Vaporized by incoming missiles.
That is the good news.
The bad news is that
since this is Hell,
We will all survive and spend
the next several centuries
Healing and then rebuilding
the palace from scratch.
Lock and load?
Missiles away?
Sounded like a good idea!
Quit bitching!
Start running!
BOB (ON INTERCOM): By the way,
if the renegade mortals wish
To know, this excludes them.
They will evaporate for
all eternity, wiped clean
From all metaphysical slates.
No afterlife, no
reincarnation, no nothing.
So screw you, Dare.
I win anyway.
Oh, Mr. Dare.
When I killed the Satono,
captain on the level...
On Polo McCrimmon's
level of Hell...
I overheard something
about the chamber of souls!
Which is?
A chamber!
Yes?
Where the souls are kept!
I know that, you moron!
Where is it?
Um, level 92!
[Laughter]
[Explosions]
Not a chance in Hell, Dare.
In four minutes, you
and your earthly friends
Will be scattered to the
winds of Hell. [Inaudible]
For all eternity.
While despite your
great efforts,
Things will go as they always
have here, with me in charge,
And fools like you
cowering at my feet.
Only four minutes?
Oh, three minutes, 40 seconds.
That doesn't leave much
time for me to kick your ass.
You!
You tricked my boss!
And stole my soul!
And have a really
sloppy palace!
I'll have to
redecorate extensively
When I take it over!
Your enthusiasm is priceless.
It really is.
Pointless, but touching.
For those about to
rock, we salute you.
[Gunshots]
Come on.
Come to me, you
little mortal prick.
[Screaming]
[Groaning]
[Shouting]
Oh!
[Scream]
[Shouting]
[Screaming]
Do you have anything
left, lassie?
Just holy water.
Throw it!
[Screaming]
Dare, come on!
That can't be right.
[Explosion]
Oh, no!
God, who cares?
Put that back.
Oh, that can't be good.
Oh, they're all messed up!
No.
It's going in.
Quiet.
This'll work.
I know it will.
Ew.
Bleh!
Brother, run!
[Laughing]
Agent Tango.
I should've known that you'd
be associating yourself
With these devil worshippers.
Who are you?
Cardinal X, also known
as Father Ignatius Khan,
And the Archbishop of Brooklyn.
And the man who arranged
his own assassination
Of Cardinal Ponti.
Very good.
You always were a quick learner.
But you see, Cardinal Ponti
was in league with Lucifer.
Uh, Beelzebub, actually.
He had to die
before he could rise
To leadership of the Holy See.
Thou shall not kill!
Except, it is the way
that it has always been.
Then I'll take my information
to the... to the press.
You already have.
And who are you?
I'm the big bad wolf. [Howl]
I will give you one more
chance to get back with us.
No reprimands.
Just resume your
duties, and we can
All get on with our business.
It's your business.
It's not my business anymore.
Fine.
Then I will file for the
order for your excommunication
From this church.
Ooh, now we're really scared!
[Groan]
You don't have a
case, Miss Tango.
Oh, Mr. Dare, what's it like
to be kicked in the groin
By a holy man!
Like this!
Not much different.
OK, everybody.
We made it.
Cake and ice cream for everyone!
I'll get to the A car!
Whoo!
Well, we made it.
Barely.
Aye.
But I knew we would.
Why?
Because we're the
good guys, lad!
What about all that Polo
McCrimmon's level of Hell
Stuff?
A man can dream, can't he?
Sorry about getting
you excommunicated.
Yeah.
What does that mean, anyway?
Uh, well, I can't get
married in a Catholic church.
That's OK.
We can do it somewhere else.
Well, it's over now.
I wonder what
happened to Beezley.
I dread the events
of the future,
Not in themselves,
but in their results.
I shudder at the thought of
any, even the most trivial
Incident, which may operate
upon this intolerable
Agitation a soul.
What?
Not but this, my
little rosebud.
Not but this.
Anticipating cruel pleasures
and sweet blasphemies
To wreak upon our
naughty little behinds.
Mr. Dare, are you all right?
I... I don't know.
I... I... I wish my
brother George was here.
[Coughing]
De Sade, Poe, Edgar, Liberace?
[Laughter]
[Rumbling]
[Explosion]
[Music playing]