- Excuse me.
- Yeah?
Just wondering. We're making
a little documentary
Do you guys wants
to be interviewed?
No, I don't think so.
A dance that has no beginning
and no end.
Would you wanna talk about
your relationship on camera?
Don't move.
Let the music move you.
How do you move in silence?
If you feel it,
take a partner.
Have both of you been
in long-term relationships
before you met?
- No.
- Not really, no.
So this is like your longest
relationship by far.
We've been together
for almost, what...
- 10 years.
- 10 years?
- December.
In December,
it'll be 10 years.
We are so much more powerful
when we are not two,
we are one.
- Yeah, I totally liked it.
- Yeah?
Doesn't it feel good?
Doesn't your body feel alive?
- I feel like free and open.
- And light.
I was not making fun.
I was just...
I was just drawing your
attention to your patterns
and your habits.
- And I appreciate it.
- Okay.
Wow. That long-haired guy
was into you.
- He was all over you.
- That's not what it's about.
but the guy I thought was gonna
put his hand down your pants.
Okay, Danny, no, no.
It's not a sexual connection.
It's like...
I just love those guys, how they
pretend they're all spiritual,
and it's really they're trying
to get ass, you know?
- I mean, it's like, come on.
- That's not what's happening.
- Come on, really?
- It's not.
No, it's not.
It's deeper than that.
Listen, I love all this stuff.
It's great. It's really great.
We're kinda pathetic
as a race, you know?
- All guys?
- All guys.
- Including you?
- Well, I'm the one exception.
That's why I notice it
when I see it in other guys.
I'm sensing a little jealous
energy from you right now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- I'm just looking out for you.
- Oh.
It's all right.
I can handle myself.
I know you can.
That's what I like about you.
Yeah.
- You know what? I...
- What?
I think we should shift this
energy before we go to dinner.
What do you mean?
Can I hug you right now?
Yeah. What, right here?
- All right.
That was amazing.
- Good. Feel good?
- Totally. How did you do that?
Just changing the energy
a little.
You're so good at that.
We all are, Danny.
I like it here.
It's beautiful.
Beautiful spot.
Yeah, it's got a good feel.
Great place to come
after the dance.
It is! It is a good place
to come after the dance.
- It's all raw, right?
- Yeah.
Or is it some? All raw.
- Is that okay?
- Absolutely.
- You sure?
- Love raw.
It's really nice.
I can't wait.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Hi, hi, hi.
Thank you.
- Hi.
This is Danny.
- Hi, Danny.
- Nice to meet you.
- This is Gayle.
- Hi, Gayle,
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah.
Just a moment of sadness.
- But it's passed.
- That's good.
- I haven't seen you in so long!
- I know!
- The moment's gone.
- I know.
I know, but it's so good
to see you now.
- You too.
- She is so special.
We all are. We all are.
- Green smoothie?
- Yes.
- Uh, what is it?
- Yeah. Just say yes.
Yes, I'm saying yes
to everything today.
Yes to the world.
The service here is phenomenal.
It really is.
So you wanted to know
about my open relationship?
If you're okay with that.
- Sure.
- Yeah.
So basically how it worked
is I had a primary partner,
and he had another
girlfriend in L.A.,
and he would see her
when he was there.
Wow. So you knew that
that was going on.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Wow.
It was a very open...
open relationship.
Hence the name.
And were you ever seeing
somebody at that time too?
Um...
I explored things a little
with some people, but...
nothing really stuck.
So you didn't feel jealous
or anything like that?
- No.
- That's amazing.
No, no, no.
She was really amazing.
She was great,
and she was great for him.
So this is something like
you guys would talk about.
Yeah.
because it's sort of
totally what I'm looking for.
Oh, yeah?
No. I mean,
not like that.
I mean, it sounds
interesting to me, maybe,
but just more
in terms of the film.
Like that's why I would like
to interview you on camera
and have you explain
your experience
with an open relationship.
If you'd be into that.
Sure, Dan.
All right. Let me try
and explain this to you.
I feel like
you're not getting it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- I'm trying.
- I know.
It's like I'm here with you
right now, right?
But I'm not totally present
with you
because I feel very drawn
to that person over there.
- The guy with the book?
- Yeah.
- Really?
He's your type?
Wait.
Are you being serious?
Because it's not
a reality to me.
I invent some fantasy
in my mind
and follow my impulse
and see what's drawing me.
What, you mean you
really wanna do that?
Or are you making
like an example?
- Hi.
- Hey.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
- Good. I'm John.
- Theresa.
It was nice to have met you.
Thanks, John.
What the hell was that?
So that was totally not
what I thought it was gonna be.
What was it?
But now I can just,
you know,
I can just let it go,
and I can be here with you.
Totally and completely.
- Wow.
- Right?
Actually, that might be a little
too much for me at the moment.
But okay.
Hey.
- Hi.
- Mmm.
- How are you?
- Good.
- Are you tired?
- Mm-hmm.
- Already?
- Yeah.
- It's so early though.
- Not that early.
- Okay.
- What?
Um, do you wanna stay
and just sleep?
Uh, is that my only option?
- Maybe tonight, yeah.
- Tonight it is.
All right, awesome.
Let's sleep.
You're that tired?
- I am.
- Oh.
Mmm!
I need to do some dreaming.
- Some dreaming?
- Yeah.
All right.
- Will you turn off the light?
- Yeah, I'm gonna do it.
That's good.
Well, all right then.
Good night.
Blessed dreams.
Blessed dreams to you too.
Why do you torture yourself
with these women, Danny?
Is it just for the film?
Is it worth it?
It's about the film,
but she's a nice person.
the film is just an extension
of where I'm at lately.
And yeah, maybe I'm getting
a little involved with her,
but it's sort of
part of the work.
Right, but it's like this
girl's got your brainwashed.
If she doesn't wanna
have sex, then...
suddenly you
don't wanna have sex.
Obviously I would like
to have sex more than I do.
I think you're better
than this situation.
Well, thank you.
I appreciate you saying that,
but I feel more connected
sometimes
when we don't have sex.
But I know what you're saying
because at the same time,
there's like...
I would really like to get...
Your cock sucked?
It might be nice.
This is what I'm saying!
There comes a time
when, you know,
every woman knows
you gotta suck a cock!
How would you know that?
'Cause I've done it before?
You've sucked a cock.
Yeah.
When was this, and how come
I didn't know about it?
My man days.
You know about my man days.
No, I don't.
You had man days?
- Does Emmy know about it?
- Yeah.
She does?
And she's cool with it?
Well, she can't
do much about it.
They came before her.
That's amazing.
I mean, it doesn't surprise me.
I've seen you with men,
and I've thought like,
"For a lesbian,
she's very flirty with men."
No, I'm just kidding.
- I'm kidding.
- I have to open the studio.
If I pull down with two hands,
it's a fumble!
You should actually
have a relationship
instead of making movies
about them.
It's so boring!
I mean, what did
Woody Allen say?
He said, "I can only live
in my art, not in my life."
And I totally relate.
- What?
- It's so fucked up
that you're taking life advice
from Woody Allen.
I'm not taking
life advice from him.
I'm just saying I relate.
I don't know. I think
I just like being alone.
You gotta stop
saying that, dude.
- Why? It's true.
- I know it's true,
but when you say that to girls
when they first meet you,
they think you're a weirdo.
- I am a weirdo.
- No, you're not.
You're not a weirdo
because you like to be alone
some of the time.
That's totally natural.
Everybody feels like that.
I just like being
in my day, you know?
- That's great.
- Is it great?
how could it be any better
than this right now?
We got music,
it's two degrees outside,
we're having coffee.
I mean, getting laid would be
nice every once in a while.
Totally.
How long has it been?
I'd rather not say.
Oh, my God.
- What?
- Oh, my God.
How many weeks?
It's been months!
- Will you stop?
- How many months?
Maybe-- I don't know.
I don't have a sex calendar
where I mark off the days.
It was definitely warmer
the last time I had sex.
- Oh, my God.
- It's not that big a deal.
You remember it's like
some distant season.
In spring.
There were buds on the tree.
Will you have sex
with my friend?
Ow.
You are so in love with him.
Shut up.
I'm not in love with him,
I just love him.
There is a distinction.
You know,
he's sweet and charming,
and I just wanna see him
with a nice girl, that's all.
Maybe he doesn't want
a nice girl.
Oh, come on.
Of course he does.
Who doesn't want
a nice girl?
I don't know.
Maybe he likes being alone.
That's what he says, but...
I don't know.
I don't buy it.
Why not?
I love that he doesn't need
to be with someone all the time.
I'm not saying he needs to
be with someone all the time.
Just, you know,
some of time.
I mean, I've never seen him
with anyone except these...
creepy new-age girls
who torture him.
I mean, you would not
believe some of things
he's told me
these girls say and do,
in the name of
going with the flow.
It sucks.
I know.
Yeah?
Hmm?
You know?
What do you know?
What do you mean?
Oh, my God,
I caught you!
Em, I know when you're
not listening to me.
I'm sorry.
- Unbelievable.
- I'm sorry!
I'm distracted.
You know that work
is crazy right now.
So why don't you close your
computer and hang out with me?
I will in a second.
Let me just do
this one thing, okay?
I'm meeting with the election
committee woman tomorrow.
- Okay.
- What?
Nothing.
What are you doing?
- Nothing.
- Mm-hmm.
I thought you were
making us dinner.
It's cookin', good-lookin'.
- So tell me this.
- Mm-hmm.
Can your election
committee woman do this?
Stop that.
That's disgusting.
Oh, come on.
- Do not be mad at me.
- I'm not mad.
I'm very, very sorry.
You did stick your tongue
in my ear.
It's kinda wet and gross.
No. You know what?
I'm not into it anymore.
Yes, you are. You're always
into it, you little nymph.
- Fuck off.
- Sweetie...
I'm sorry if I'm attracted
to my girlfriend.
I was kidding.
Come on, I was kidding.
Huh?
- Huh?
- You always do this!
- What?
- No, you know what?
If I have to explain it,
just forget it.
Come on.
Don't be such
a little baby, huh?
- Can't take a joke suddenly.
- Fuck you.
Why aren't you ticklish?
It's so unfair.
Oh, fuck off.
I'm going.
I'll make you your dinner,
madam!
One of these nights,
you're cooking.
In your dreams,
sweet cakes.
Oh, my God.
Why do I have to be
the mom?
Uh, I think I burnt this.
Well, it doesn't
make a lot of sense
because I have
a really close friendship...
Hey, did you finish
the behind-the-scenes?
Oh, that was
the airline thing.
No, before that.
What is that you're working on?
It was nothing.
- No.
- Everybody does it. Show me.
- Really?
- Please. I'm bored.
- What is it?
- It's nothing.
It's this doc that I've been
working on for years.
It's going to be a cure
for boredom,
but if you really wanna
see it, uh, here.
What's it about?
It's about uh,
you know, people's lives
and relationships and...
Here.
I started like...
I don't...
I... First of all...
I did the camera shake
intentionally.
Yeah, it looks like
a battle scene or something.
...to avoid it.
Back-lit.
It's supposed to look bad.
So is she,
is she like mentally ill?
No, she's not mentally ill.
She's just talking about
her relationship history.
Romantic relationships.
Or other kinds. If they don't
have romantic relationships,
then how they, you know,
subvert that emotion
in other ways
and, you know,
just connection, basically.
Highbrow.
Sort of, but I don't know
where it's going right now.
I'm just trying to find
the heart of the doc.
Hey, there he is.
Zack, what's up?
done by the end
of the day, right?
Yeah, I was just, uh,
I put that in the bin for you.
Is this still H.264?
- Oh, we're great.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, no problem.
- You got it.
Did you start this?
No, not at all.
- All right, uh...
- You got it?
Yeah, I'm on it.
All right. okay.
Thanks, man.
Oh, hey, speaking
of relationships.
You still with that
hot freaky chick?
- Oh, Theresa?
- Yeah.
She is hot.
Not that freaky though.
She's into that
like new-agey stuff.
I mean, with her?
I don't know.
because she's into
open relationships,
so it's a little weird.
- It's perfect.
- Really?
Dude, don't fuck it up
by asking questions.
You're probably right.
Seriously, yeah.
- All right, man.
- I'll see ya.
...relationship rather than
just being myself, so...
I'm uncomfortable,
and I want out.
What?
All right, Mr. Cameraman,
what do you wanna know?
Give me some good stories
about open relationships.
Um, okay.
Um, my primary partner
had his L.A. girlfriend
come in to town once,
and I was going to New Jersey
to stay with my parents,
and I spent the whole day
cleaning and getting ready,
and I bought flowers.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I just wanted it
to be perfect for them.
- Really?
- Yeah.
That seems so amazing to me
that you can just like--
So you don't have
jealousy at all, ever?
- No.
- Come on.
No, we're all on
our own paths, you know?
Everybody's got...
their own needs.
But do you even have the
feeling, and then you say, like,
"I'm not going to go
with this feeling,"
or do you just not even have
the feeling of jealousy?
Um...
The only feeling I have is like,
"Oh, I really wish..."
If I suddenly wish that he
was there, but he's not there.
Mm-hmm.
But that's, you know,
that's my own shit.
That's your own shit?
My teabag says,
"You are unlimited."
You are unlimited.
What does mine say?
Trust creates peace.
- Oh, see?
- That's appropriate.
Can we put the camera
away now?
I know, but sometimes
I just wanna be here.
Okay.
Just the two of us.
Without a camera between us.
- That sounds good.
- Yeah.
- Good breath.
- I know.
- I'm getting better at this.
- You are.
It's so interesting
to do this, isn't it?
It's good. Feels good.
Yeah, 'cause it's funny,
the first few times we did it,
it's like, the eye contact
always seems to be like,
we should either make out
or cry or you know...
- Yeah.
- But...
- You don't have to talk.
- You don't have to do it.
- I should shut up now.
- You don't have to qualify it.
See? So much better.
Totally.
We'll take it
to the next level.
All right.
That's good.
- That's nice.
- Yeah?
- That's good.
- Wow.
- Feel good?
- That's amazing.
Yeah, that's like third-eye
to third-eye, you know?
It's like kind of
an inner seeing.
- Do you wanna, um...
- I like it.
Do you wanna trade massages
right now?
I would love that.
You mean like right here?
- No, let's go upstairs.
- Okay.
- Should we bring our tea?
- Bring your tea.
Trust is peace.
Oh, that feels good.
- Really?
- Oh, my God.
Yeah, you got
some tension going on.
- Whew!
- Wow.
Too much?
- It's a lot.
- It's a lot?
It's a lot,
but in a good way.
Oh, my goodness.
- Yeah, you need that.
- Ooh!
This shirt is kinda
getting in the way here.
Do you wanna take it off
and then we can use the oil?
All right, sure.
Yeah, let's do that.
Let's see,
this looks like good...
- massage oil.
- See where the oil is?
Yeah, it's pretty handy here.
You must get massages a lot.
Well, sometimes,
when I'm lucky.
It's a nice thing to do.
All right, here we go.
This'll be nice.
- Do these go up?
- Mm-hmm.
I need more oil for this.
- It's a very kissable back.
- Oh, okay.
- It's just part of the massage.
It's a very...
special technique I have.
I see. Uh...
- Danny.
- What?
- I...
- I think maybe we should stop.
- What do you mean?
This is just getting going.
Yeah, I just,
I'm not really...
- I think we should stop.
- What? Really?
Yeah, yeah, I just, um...
I just don't wanna be
sexual right now.
- Oh, no, I don't either.
- Okay, good.
It just doesn't...
Hate isn't what wants to happen.
Oh, okay, sorry.
I just get a little excited
because you're so beautiful.
Oh, that's so nice.
That's so nice.
Okay, so much love,
so much love.
Yeah.
Mmm!
- This is nice.
- Yeah.
Although, it still does
feel slightly sexual,
I understand, I understand.
Just gonna help myself
out here where I can.
See? There we go.
Perfect.
That looks great.
- Now can I hug you?
- Absolutely,
- Now it's like we're cousins.
- Okay.
Mmm.
Yeah, this is great.
I don't feel anything.
Well, um, we were...
should I look at you
or should I look at your thing?
Into the lens
or at your face?
- No, you can look at me.
- Okay.
- Um, I was into her for a--
a long time, a while.
- She was?
- Did I talk during your turn?
- Um, yeah, you did.
- Oh, my God.
I'm so excited that there is
documentation of this
because we can
actually rewind.
First of all, you did talk
through my whole turn.
And second of all,
it doesn't actually matter
'cause technically
there are no turns.
That's good.
I like the bickering too.
- .Keep that going.
- Oh, great.
So, um, she was
going out with a guy.
- A man person.
And so I didn't even know
if it was a possibility.
- And she was dating a shrew.
- That is not true.
- She was--
- Oh, my God, she was awful.
She was this
controlling psychopath
who literally never laughed.
She did laugh.
She laughed
all the time in private.
You don't think that's weird?
- A little bit.
- You're not allowed to ask him.
She's a private laugher.
She can't ask you
for validation.
Um... You are so mean.
when your partner's last person
was such a square
because it's so easy
to please them.
All I have to do is
laugh over brunch,
and you feel like
I'm the most delightful woman
you ever dated.
Um, oh, my God.
You're such a bitch.
Do you have any fistfights?
'Cause I feel like we could do
a cat fight for you.
That's nice, but let's go back
to Carla and her man.
Oh, God, do we
actually have to?
And had you
dated men before, Carla?
- You know this.
- I know it, yeah,
but we're talking to the rest
of the film audience here.
All right, sorry. Um...
- Yeah, let's hear it.
- Shut up.
What's the other story?
So I wasn't
that comfortable with it,
and I, uh...
and I wasn't out.
So I was dating Brad
and experimenting with women.
And Brad knew about
this experimentation?
No, no.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
And Emmy was friends
with his sister.
Oh.
Was that weird?
This is good stuff.
This is really good.
Yeah, well, you know,
it was a long time ago, so...
That's it. We don't have
to talk about Brad anymore
'cause this has really
gone down a different turn here.
No, I... She's right.
It's probably--
I just feel bad about it.
Okay, we don't have
to talk about him anymore.
It's fine.
So because
she was dating Brad,
I didn't know
if it was a possibility.
Back to me.
Take it back to you.
But then I found out
about all this experimenting.
And that was it?
And that was it.
And the buck stopped there.
Let's hope.
So far.
- We can cut it now.
- Okay.
- Why?
- You are not talking to Brad.
I have to talk to him.
The subject reveals
where the story goes.
Didn't you see Hoop Dreams?
No, really.
You can't talk to him.
- Why not?
- Because he was traumatized.
Seriously, he's my only ex
that I don't talk to anymore,
and it ruined the relationship
between Emmy and his sister.
I'm gonna be totally
sensitive to that.
It's a really
bad idea, dude.
It's not.
No, it's a good idea.
This documentary is gonna
bring everyone back together.
- Oh, my God.
- And it's gonna be great.
You guys are gonna
go to the premiere.
- I'm serious, Danny.
- I'm serious too.
Actually, do you wanna become
the center of this film?
You know, it's so sweet
of you to ask me that
because I've been wanting
to say to you that,
"Yes, I want to be
the center of your film!"
Oh, my God.
You're fucking with me, right?
- No.
- This is not okay.
Holy shit.
- That's Rosie.
- Wow.
She just ate that pigeon
over there in the grass.
Yeah, rubbed one out.
Bobby and Violet
were there years ago,
and then Violet died
and this one moved in.
Bobby and Rosie, they live
together in the white building,
or that red building over there,
those two windows.
Her and Bobby met right up there
on top of the building up there.
But Bobby had his choice.
because he watched her catch it
right here in the grass.
And she was messed up.
She died.
- She ended up dying.
- Oh, man.
But then she moved in.
She just took off.
Where did she go?
- I lost her.
- I know.
Where'd she go?
Did you see her?
Um, so, well,
I was into her for a while.
Hey, Aunt Lily,
how are you?
- Good! How are you?
- Good.
Good! Were you at the church?
I didn't see you there.
No, I just came right from work,
so I missed the church part.
That's too bad.
It was wonderful.
- Carol was so beautiful.
- Was she really?
- Would you like something?
- I'm good. I'll see you later.
- Good to see you.
- Yeah, you too.
- Hello, hello!
- Danny!
How you doin', Aunt Jules?
- Nice to see you, Trevor.
- Danny.
- Nice to see everybody.
- How was work?
It was good. I'm sorry
I came right from work.
- I missed the church.
- That's okay,
We're just glad you're here.
Aunt Lily said it was
beautiful though, yeah?
- It was somethin'.
- Not a dry eye in the house.
Nice.
Really?
Go say hi to Carol.
Oh, she looks busy,
I'll get her later.
You know, she brought a whole
lot of cute, single friends.
Okay, Aunt Jules,
thank you very much.
There are a lot of
cute, single girls here.
Trevor's noticed them.
Good observation.
I'm taken.
- Right, honey?
- Yes.
And you're too old
for any of them
to be interested
in you anyway.
Oh, so I'm monogamous
by default.
By default, yeah.
You never know though.
Sometimes they go
for the older guys, Mom.
You'd better be careful.
Danny, what are you
editing now?
Oh, I mean,
just dumb shit.
Commercials mostly, but now
I'm starting to get more films.
My cousin was an orderly
on General Hospital.
Oh, really, that's exactly
the same thing as a film editor.
- What do you do?
- Uh, I, um...
Investment counseling.
- She had to tell you that?
- No, no, I do.
I counsel people
on their investments.
Yeah, that's great, man.
You like it?
No, but I make
a shitload of money.
Well, there you go.
That's a good thing,
I guess.
You just got a husband here
to dance with.
I gotta get the ol'
ball and chain off my back.
Already? Come on.
That was quick.
Have fun.
We'll dance together.
You haven't always tried
new things.
- I'm trying it, believe me.
- Awesome.
You don't think of me
here anymore though.
I know you don't.
You forget all about me.
That's not true at all.
You were always
my favorite cousin.
- We just never see you anymore.
- No, I know.
It's true, it's true.
I've sort of like cut off
because you're the only one
I can talk to.
The rest of these people here
I don't feel comfortable with.
Well, I mean, you never
give people a chance.
That's true, I don't,
but you know what it is?
It's like I feel like everyone's
just trying to figure me out,
put me in a box or something.
Yeah. You know my friend Suze
was asking about you tonight.
- Oh, Suze.
- She wanted to see you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You can just enjoy your day,
you know what I mean?
This is ridiculous!
He's just unconventional
when it comes to relationships.
That sounds like
code for gay.
What, Danny?
Are you kidding?
No way.
That guy gets all the tail
he wants. I've seen.
What have you seen?
Well, like with that
hippie-dippie girl we met.
Oh, Theresa.
Exactly. What kind of
straight man has women friends?
Why when someone
shows up solo
that everybody thinks gay?
I mean, if he was gay,
wouldn't he bring a guy?
Not if he was
in the closet.
Oh, why are you so concerned?
- Hey, Charlie, how you doin'?
- Good. How you doin'?
All right, I will.
I'll be over in a second.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
No, no, no, no.
I don't think you're gay.
Yeah.
because they've never
seen you with women.
Right, because if you're alone,
that's not an option. I get it.
I was alone for a long time
before I met your mother,
and I loved it,
but then I met her and...
it was like, I really dug
hanging with her.
Yeah.
Yeah, she's a good lady.
Yeah, yeah, she is.
But you know,
once you get older,
the body and the sex
and all that,
it becomes less.
I used to be really into
like tight bodies
with pow-wow curves.
but she has more of a roly-poly
kind of beautiful, you know?
Right.
Not to say that...
not to say that the sex
is not fucking fantastic.
- Okay.
- Yeah, no, I'm sorry.
That's probably
not very appropriate.
No, no, that's fine.
It is great to be outside.
Yeah, it's a beautiful night.
No, no, man.
I mean outside of convention.
You know?
I don't know.
What?
What? What?
This fucking suit, man!
- It's fucking terrible!
- Really?
No, no, no!
But it's beautiful.
It is beautifully terrible.
It says, "I couldn't bother
being conforming to you,
you conforming automatons."
- No, it's noble, man.
- Really?
Yes. It's noble.
It's like...
fucking nobility
from a time gone by.
Don't ever stop.
Wow. I don't think I can.
Like Rilke says,
"You build your life
in accordance
with that necessity."
What's your necessity?
I don't think I have one.
Oh, come on!
Come on, come on, man!
- What's your necessity?
- I don't know.
I never really...
Okay, like my necessity is to...
do nothing.
Like I wake up
in the morning
and just let the day unfold.
That's beautiful, man.
I fucking love that.
See once you find
your necessity,
it's all gravy
from there on out.
Carla, where are you
right now?
Why is your phone off,
first of all?
Second of all,
I'm so high right now.
I'm still at the wedding,
and my family is insane.
I just got high
with my mom's boyfriend.
You know what he told me?
He told me that sex with
my mom is still fantastic.
So I've got that image in
my head for the rest of my life.
I so wanna talk to you
right now.
I just feel like I'm at
that perfect high place,
and I just need
to talk to you.
I love talking to you high.
It's one of my favorite
things to do.
I need you right now.
Where are you?
God!
Call me back
as soon as you get this.
Before you get this,
call me back.
All right, love you, bye.
- Uncle Bob, you takin' off?
- Yeah.
- Good to see you.
When are we gonna see you
getting married?
Me? Oh, I don't know.
I'm too young.
You better hurry up.
You don't wanna end up like me.
Oh, come on!
That wouldn't so bad.
You think?
- Have a good night.
- You too.
- Hey.
- What happened?
I don't know.
I have no idea, Danny.
I mean, is she seeing
somebody else or what is it?
She wouldn't say.
Oh, God.
It's impossible.
I really... I don't know
how anybody does it.
Well, you're asking
the wrong guy.
You are so lucky you don't
have to deal with this shit.
No.
I don't know about that.
Do you have any weed?
I think I might
have some weed.
Look at who you're
talking to right now.
- Can I have some?
- Do you want some?
- Yeah, I want weed.
- I'm getting you weed.
Gonna make it all better.
I want wine and weed.
I'll do what I can here.
I don't know how much...
I don't know how much
weed and wine we have,
but I'll do my best.
- Pills.
- Pills? Heroin?
- Heroin.
- All right.
So let's start you off
with weed.
I'm gonna get you wine.
How is cheap red wine for you?
It's fine.
This is really good weed.
Where'd you get it?
I got it from
my tai chi instructor.
Oh, my God.
You have a tai chi instructor?
You don't?
Oh, my God, what are you?
Like an 85-year-old Asian man?
I am, in the body of...
You're very well maintained.
You never know what it's like
inside the relationship
That's so true.
Well, it was fun.
It used to be fun.
How long has it
not been fun for?
I don't know.
Are you okay?
Hey.
Hey, come here.
You're gonna be okay.
Really?
Really.
How do you know?
I can feel it.
I know these things.
I do.
You know what we're gonna do?
We're gonna go for a walk.
You're gonna be fine. Come on.
I have a good plan for us.
- You do?
- Yeah.
- Can you do it?
- Yeah, I can do it.
- Can you see?
- It's a meadow!
- What is it?
- It's a whole meadow!
- Are we in the right space?
- Yeah. Straight.
What street is this?
Suffolk.
We're not there yet.
We're almost there.
- What is your name?
- I'm Megan.
- Hey, I'm Danny.
- Hi, Danny, nice to meet you.
- This is Carla.
- Hi, how are you?
- Yeah, good. How are you doing?
- Good. It's good.
Tequila?
- Where are you from?
- I'm from Ireland, from Dublin.
- Do you like it?
- I love it here.
- Do you live in the city?
- Well, I don't know now.
I'm sort of homeless
as of tonight.
- You gotta drown your sorrows.
- Yeah!
She's like
an Irish Brigette Bardot.
- You should have one more shot.
- Really? You think?
Have you got to work tomorrow?
How can you say no
to that accent?
No, I can't
say no to that accent.
Here's to New York.
Come on.
It's a good tequila.
I wouldn't give you bad tequila.
I already can't feel my teeth.
You got the basic stuff.
You haven't met that guy
or that girl, right?
Yeah, exactly.
I haven't met that person.
You never know. You come into
a bar and meet a guy or girl.
Completely depends.
And that's a good way to be
because you double your odds.
No, I've never dated
a customer.
Thanks for answering that.
I'm not doing a number slide.
I'm just asking!
I'm gonna get a number slide!
I want you to be happy.
This is your night.
I don't even know
what's going on with her.
and she wouldn't tell me
if she was with someone else.
When you ask someone,
"Are you with someone,
"are you seeing someone else,
have you met someone else?"
and they don't
answer that question...
Right, but I mean, you don't
ask that question unless like...
- What did you... What?
- Let's stop talking about it.
But she's also--
Where are you going?
I dropped my napkin,
you fucking pervert!
- This is your life, right?
- No, I know.
Do you want something
that's extraordinary
Or something that's like...
- No, I want that.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Sorry, if I spat on you.
- No, I just wanna hug you.
I just wanna hug you.
- She's doing her thing.
- What are you saying?
- Then you go like this.
- I don't need the criticism.
We should really...
We should go?
But I tried to get that
out of her.
Did you see how I tried
to get that out of her?
- Yeah.
- Did you try?
I feel like there's a level
that we're so close,
and we're like
really good friends,
but I get to a certain level,
and then it's like,
boom, door goes up.
Like, it's like
"That's as far as you get."
- You wanna get a bit further.
- No, no, no!
You joke about it
and you make jokes,
but like I really
feel that sometimes.
I'm just being honest.
You know, you can trust me.
Like I don't know why you feel
like you can't trust me.
Why are you taking
all the drinks?
It's like you get it,
like you fucking get it,
and you don't even know
that you get it.
Like you're just like so cool,
and you're
a fucking great woman,
and you seek these relationships
where if you're not appreciated,
No, I was crazy in college.
and I would fuck these women
that I had no connection to.
Oh, my God,
that's so unusual!
Wait, in college, you got
really drunk all the time
- and fucked women?
- Isn't that crazy?
So you were that one
that did that in college.
- You were the one guy...
- That did that.
No, I'm not saying
I was a one guy.
I'm just trying
to make a point.
I'm saying that I did that
with these girls
that I would be attracted to,
but then I also had these
really good girlfriends
that we would
stay up all night
and talk and bond
and everything,
but I would never even think
about sleeping with those girls.
It was like I wanted to keep
those two things separate.
Right, right,
but did those chicks,
the ones that would stay up
braiding your hair every night...
- You are such a bitch.
- Did they wanna have...
Did they wanna
have sex with you?
No, because I had
braided hair at that point.
Why would they wanna
have sex with me?
No, that was not
part of our thing.
They totally wanted
to have sex with you.
And they were like, "When is he
going to make a move?
How long do I have to talk about
feelings with this fucking guy?"
Really? They were waiting
for me to make a move?
I hope they weren't.
I thought we were bonding.
You couldn't
handle the intimacy
like full-on altogether.
You could either have
sexual intimacy,
which wasn't really intimacy;
it was just banging.
- It was banging.
- Or intimacy without the sex.
You weren't ready
for the whole shebang.
I get it. You're really
not there even now.
That's what I'm saying.
I have not made
that much progress.
Did she call?
I have not
looked at my phone.
Good.
Don't.
Yeah.
I don't want to.
Thank you so much
for tonight.
Of course, it was fun.
I had a good time.
Do you have
everything you need?
- Glass of water, anything?
- No. I'm good.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going to sleep.
- Where?
- On the couch.
You should
get in here with me.
There's plenty of room.
Look.
No, it's all right.
- What's your problem?
- Couch is comfortable
I don't know.
You wanna share the bed?
This is stupid.
It'll be fun.
I don't wanna sleep alone.
All right.
I'm good with it.
I can't really sleep
in these, but...
- Can you turn around?
- Are you kidding me?
so I just feel a little awkward,
and I don't like these boxers.
But I've seen you
in swimming trunks before.
But I don't like
these boxers.
Just...
turn around for two seconds!
This is ridiculous.
Oh, just shut the fuck up
and turn around.
- One.
- Wait a second.
- Two.
- No, no, I meant...
Two and a half.
I saw your boxers!
They're horrible, aren't they?
- No, I didn't see them.
- I have no idea.
You're shy, huh?
I'm a little shy.
We've never been
in bed together.
- It's the first time.
- Oh, my God!
Is this what you do
usually in bed?
Face the person
and talk to them?
Yeah. Can we kill the lamp?
- Do you mind?
- Not at all.
- Sorry. I gotta reach over you.
- So fuckin' rude.
I can't believe
I just did that.
Are you tired?
I'm a little tired, but...
You wanna talk at all?
I'm not tired at all.
A little chitchat?
Yeah, you seem wired up.
What's up with Theresa?
I don't know. I'm not really
talking to her right now.
Huh? Why?
Just haven't.
Not into her anymore?
No, I'm into her, I mean...
I don't know.
I guess I'm into her.
I guess I was kind of like
into her in a way
unconventional
relationship thing.
Like the open relationship
thing seems interesting to me.
Yeah, because you're a weirdo.
Is that really weird?
I thought it was progressive
and open minded.
Uh-huh.
I just feel like there's
gotta be something else
that doesn't feel
so oppressive,
like I'm totally
losing my freedom
and any sense
of identity I have.
Yeah, but relationships
don't have to be oppressive.
Like it can be
what you want it to be,
you know,
like with me and Emmy.
Okay, that's not
the best example right now,
but still, you make it
what you want it to be,
what suits you and your partner,
do you know what I mean?
You know, if you're
starting to feel,
if you actually
take it that far,
you can actually just say
to that person,
"Hey, you know, I need
a little space here."
I just feel like you never
let it get to that point.
- You know?
- No, you're right.
You decide that
it's gonna be oppressive
before you've even
tried it out.
And I guess I haven't really
been in a situation lately
where I thought that,
you know,
the person was worth like
making the sacrifices for.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's rare.
I don't know.
I'm kinda getting tired.
You wanna go to sleep?
Yeah.
I'm kinda fading.
Okay.
I'll see you
in the morning then.
Thank you for tonight.
Of course.
It's fun here.
Nice to have you.
It feels like there's
a blanket folded up
inside the pillowcase.
Man pillows.
What?
No.
No, I'm not doing this
right now.
He's on the couch.
I'm in the bed.
What?
Yeah.
You too.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
What'd she say?
I don't wanna talk about it.
Why are you being
so nice to me?
What do you mean,
why am I being so nice to you?
I care about you,
that's why.
Don't be sorry.
It's okay.
Ready.
Ohh.
Step.
Chi.
Ahh.
Ohh.
Chi.
Around.
Hold.
Chi.
Half step.
Ahh.
Chi.
Haven't seen you in class
in a while.
What?
I'm starting to think the only
reason you come to class
is when you need some weed.
I come for the practice.
The weed is the added bonus.
You know that.
Namaste, my friend.
- I'll see ya next week.
- All right.
Because, Mom,
I have like 80 cousins.
They all eventually get married.
I'm not going to every wedding.
I'm doing her a favor.
She only invited me
out of obligation.
You know how expensive it is
per person?
They're gonna be psyched
that I don't go.
Because!
All right, Mom, listen, my ear
is killing me from the phone.
I do have a hands-free device.
I just didn't bring it with me.
I'm going! I have to go.
I love you too.
Okay, okay,
I'm hanging up now.
All right, I gotta go.
All right, I'll see you.
Oh, my God, Em!
How are you?
- Good. How are you?
- Good to see you!
How have you been?
Where have you been?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's just been crazy.
She's good, yeah.
What's up with that?
- What are you talking about?
- I don't know, a fight?
Oh, no, no, no.
I've just been crazy.
How's the documentary?
Are we going to Sundance?
It's kind of my
forever project, you know.
Don't wait too long.
Sorry.
Okay, I better go, but you're
gonna vote tomorrow, right?
Only for you because I usually
come out for the big ones.
- They're all the big ones!
- I know, I know!
Vote on
the Working Families Party.
- I will, whatever that means.
- Okay.
I gotta go.
And come to our night.
We're gonna be at
the Soho House on Crosby.
- Okay, I'll try, yeah.
- Hopefully a celebration,
- Carla wants to see you.
- Okay. Tell her I said hi.
- Okay, bye.
- All right.
Hey. Hey, it's me.
Hello!
Oh, my God,
I'm so glad to be...
Hi.
...here with all you guys.
- What's happening?
- You guys know each other?
Yes. Yeah, how are you?
- From dance class.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, how's it going?
- Good, good.
What are you kids up to?
- Just being.
- Yeah.
Just being. Nice.
That's nice.
It is nice.
It feels you guys
are just being in here.
- We missed you at class today.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
- 'Cause I couldn't make it.
- It was amazing.
Yeah, it always is with
this guy. He's awesome.
I love your class.
This is really great.
You guys should know each other
Yeah, I feel like
there's a good thing, yeah.
- All good.
- It's all good.
It's all love.
It is?
Sit, Danny, sit.
Oh, no, I was just on my way
around the block,
and I thought of you,
and I didn't know
this was happening,
so you guys should
just do your thing.
- It's not our thing.
- No.
It's our thing.
- Yeah, you're included.
- I'm included?
- You are.
- Sure.
That's so nice.
What am I included in,
exactly?
- Not sure what's going on.
- In the love.
I don't know if I'm in the
same vibe as you guys, though.
- That's okay.
- Well, get into it.
Come on, sit down.
No, I really don't
wanna sit right now.
I'm kinda amped up, so...
You don't have to do the
whole alpha dog thing here.
It's not like I'm gonna
steal her away from you.
She's not mine to steal.
We're just friends.
I just have some stuff
going on.
I'm good, I'm good.
- Hey.
- What?
Can I just hug you?
I really don't want a hug
right now, all right?
- Okay.
- Sorry.
Maybe we'll talk later
or something, but you know...
Have a good day, dude.
Okay, take it easy, guy.
Take it easy, guy.
That's awesome.
This guy's awesome.
- He is awesome.
- He is, yeah.
Is this like for real?
Or is this just like
an act you put on or like...
What's going on?
I don't really
understand the question.
you got your shirt off
in November, like, all love,
is that really who you are?
What's happening?
No. Don't put a shirt on.
Just be whoever you are.
Do you really believe
all that shit, man?
Like the shit you teach
and all that, you know.
It's not a matter of belief.
It's a matter of knowing.
I hear you, and you're right.
Your truth is not my truth.
Totally, yeah, thank God.
I'm gonna go,
I'm gonna go.
Don't.
Nothing's happening,
We had an amazing class,
and then Jarrod wanted
to borrow a book,
so that's all
that's going on.
That's nice, yeah.
What book?
- Good book?
- Yeah.
- He looks like a big reader.
- What's up?
Nothing's up! I just thought
we were gonna hang out like--
and you don't have to
explain yourself to me.
I didn't realize
what I was coming into.
and I want you
to be able to let that go.
No, I just wanna
let you guys just be
'cause that's
what you're doing.
Hang on, take a step back.
Look at this fucking guy.
I think we should
just ask ourselves
What do you mean,
what's really happening?
You want me to tell you
- Yeah.
- You're here,
you got the no shirt on
in November,
she's a fuckin' beautiful woman,
and you wanna fuck her,
but you're using
the spiritual thing as like...
- Hey, hey.
- No, I'm just saying.
He said he wants to be real
like I'm being real.
But you're not gonna
admit that.
You're gonna say,
"It's all love,
and it's about
the connection, man."
Okay, look,
you don't know me, man.
Sex is one emotion
on a much larger compass.
Do you have like spiritual
Tourette's or something?
What are these platitudes?
I'm gonna go.
This is so weird.
I feel like
really weird right now.
- Don't go like this, Danny.
- We'll talk later.
You should have told me
you had shit going on.
- No, no, no.
- Danny, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't walk out with this,
this anger on you.
Can you just adjust your
expectation and be with us?
I feel like I'm doing that
all the time when I'm with you.
that we were gonna just have
a one-on-one thing,
and there's sometimes
always a party here,
and I just wasn't ready for it,
you know what I mean?
Okay.
And I love who you are,
and I want you
to be who you are,
but it's just hard
for me sometimes
'cause I wanna have you in a way
that I know I can't have you.
But you're great,
and I'm grateful for you.
So I just need to go
right now.
- Okay.
- All right?
All right.
- Bye.
Be well.
Do you ever have times
where you do feel
jealous or angry?
Yeah, I feel
those things,
but I know that
they're not real
and that you...
They're just,
they're just ego,
and you have to...
breathe and come back
to yourself.
Oh, I'll be right back.
If you were smart,
you'd use Grand Marnier.
- Hi!
- How are you?
- Good. How are you?
- Good to see you.
Thank you.
Come meet these guys.
This is Danny.
I want to introduce you
to Danny.
Oh, good to see you!
What's going on?
Nice to see you.
Congratulations.
We're just discussing really
important political matters here
like how to make
a good margarita.
That's important.
That's how we're
gonna win this thing!
Guys, I'm gonna
check in with you later.
I'm gonna show
this gentleman around.
Of course.
Good to meet you guys.
Nice to meet you.
All right.
Have a good time.
Yeah.
That guy's a real asshole.
Sit over there.
I'll come find you guys later.
- Oh, right.
- His way.
No, that's all
it comes from.
What are you doing here?
You wanna sit down?
It's good to see you.
How are you?
I'm gonna take my coat off,
all right?
Can I have a sip
of your beer?
Yeah, of course.
How you doin'?
Good.
It's been a while.
Are you drunk?
I miss you, Danny.
It's so good of you to come.
I mean not yeah.
You know what I mean.
Shut up!
No, no, I'm not drunk.
It's a good party.
It is!
It's a dumb party,
but it's fun.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
I love this fucking song.
Will you dance?
You're gonna dance with me.
You're gonna dance with me
right now!
I just got here.
Let me have a little drink.
Okay. Drink that
in the next five seconds.
I don't wanna dance just yet.
We have to dance right now?
Yes, come on.
All right, fine.
It's all about grass roots.
And tonight you saw that.
'Cause it's all about people,
it's all about
every one of you,
Democrats, Republicans,
inclusive.
Hey.
What're you doin' in here
all alone?
That's how I like it,
I guess.
Too bad.
I wanna come bug you.
- I thought you'd left.
- Nope.
- It's good to see you.
- You too.
It's weird. I feel like
nobody sees me like you do.
It's true. I just think
these last couple months,
like I've just felt like...
invisible or somethin'
from not seeing you.
I know.
Me too.
So what happened?
What do you mean?
Like after that night.
- Oh, that.
- Yeah.
Sorry. I don't mean
to make you uncomfortable.
No, no, I wanna...
I just can't be fake
with you, you know?
It's just impossible.
I know.
I don't know
what happened, Danny.
I guess I just...
freaked out.
You freaked out?
Wow. The tables turned.
I don't know.
I didn't wanna lose you and...
I just couldn't deal.
Welcome to my world.
Yeah, I guess we both
couldn't deal.
Yeah. I've been not dealing
my entire life.
I'm so tired of it.
I just wanna deal for once.
See how the other half lives,
you know?
What?
What's goin' on?
I don't know. It's dumb.
Well, you do too.
I'm just not saying it.
Like you want me
to really say it?
I don't know. I don't know
what you're talking about.
I wanna kiss you right now,
okay? That's the truth.
And I feel like
that's all I ever do
is like I have to pretend
that I don't wanna kiss you
every time I'm with you.
And I get to like
hang out with you and Emmy
and have dinner
and come party here,
and it's just...
I'm just tired of it.
I like you, you know?
And I like being around you.
I'm just waiting, you know,
for them to leave
so I can be alone again,
and I never feel that
with you.
Shut up.
No.
I love you like this.
You do?
- Danny, Danny, stop.
- What?
- We can't.
- Yes, we can.
- No, we can't.
- Why not?
There are people involved.
What are you doing?
- I'm trying to shut you up.
- Danny.
- What?
What?
Danny.
- What?
- Danny, don't do this.
What? This is me dealing.
You're happy.
That's not what you were that
night with me, that's for sure.
Look, we were--
Emmy and I were fighting,
I was upset.
You can't just use that.
I felt it, okay?
And I felt it from you.
Tell me you're happy.
Fuck you!
Who do you think you are?
I'm not gonna prove myself
to you, okay?
Tell me you love her.
Hi, you guys!
Hey!
Whoa.
- What's goin' on here?
- What are you talking about?
- Am I interrupting, huh?
- Don't be ridiculous.
I gotta go, actually,
but this was a great night.
- Oh, my God.
- I had a great time.
Wait a minute.
You stay here for a second.
You guys do me a favor.
I just want you to make out.
Because this weird
sexual tension between you guys
is driving me insane.
And if you just make out once,
you'll see that
there's nothing to it,
and it'll be gone.
- Uh, no.
- Yeah. Please?
- No. For me.
- No thanks.
Come on, one little kiss.
I don't think
she's gonna leave us alone.
Come on, it's my big night.
We'll just give her
one little kiss.
- That's all she wants, right?
- There you go.
That's it.
That's fine, right?
See? Nothing.
She's right.
I gotta go.
I'll see you. Have a--
Congratulations again.
What the fuck was that?
What the hell's going on?
I'm not bullying you!
I'm asking you a question!
Okay, so I don't get
to ask you any questions,
even though you were crying
and you were back here
instead of being out there
with me on my big night.
You didn't even know
I was gone.
Oh, give me a break.
Now you're gonna be a crybaby,
that I wasn't paying
enough attention to you?
Do you know what I've
been doing all night?
- Come here.
- I'm gonna go.
- Oh, come on.
- No, no.
Oh, come on!
Carla.
Come on!
- Come on, Carla.
- Let go.
Yeah, I'm gonna go.
You stay. You enjoy this.
No, I'm not gonna stay.
You're just gonna leave like...
What is going on?
I don't know what else
to say to you.
I'm done.
We all have impulses
and feelings,
but you can't act on it
just whenever you feel it.
I always feel kinda like
invisible in the world.
Do you want something
that's extraordinary
or something that's like
Right, 'cause being
alone's not even an option.
That sounds excruciating.
Just stick with us.
Stick with us.
- Did you pack the charger?
- The charger?
- The charger.
- Phone charger?
- Yes.
- I don't have a charger.
- You had the charger.
- What do you mean?
You said you were
going to pack it!
No, you said you were.
Grace, stay away
from the railing.
I said I was gonna
pack the charger?
Oh, I'm the charger man.
I see.
What's goin' on?
Nothing.
Wanna hear something?
What?
I'm a dancer.
You're a dancer?
Yeah.
What kinda dancer are you?
Jump, jump.
- Wow. That's pretty good.
- Twirl.
Oh, she's just teaching me
a little dance move.
Shh! Don't pay attention
to them.
- Are those your parents?
- No.
No, 'cause they're not
dancers like us.
They're not dancers like us?
How do you know I can dance?
I'm not that good.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Because you are.
I know that.
- You know it?
- Yeah.
Oh.
What? Ready?
Here I go.
Twirl.
Jump, jump and up.
I told you a hundred times
to pack the charger!
Now you twirl me.
I am not responsible
for the charger.
It's gonna be
down the hall to your left.
- Thank you so much.
- No problem.
Thank you. We're gonna have
a Q&A with the director.
Please stick around
as I introduce Daniel Sullivan.
Um...
I don't know. I mean,
I like movies that just end.
You know, I never buy it
when they're like
tying it all up in a bow
at the end, you know?
Yeah, but there has to be
some sort of conclusion.
Does there? I don't know. Why?
Why can't it just end?
Because as an audience,
there has to be a reason
we're watching.
because you're engaged
by what's going on
and you're interested
in the characters and...
Yeah, but there has to be
a journey to follow.
That's not my favorite word
"journey,"
but I mean, everything's
a journey, isn't it?
I mean, this conversation,
for example,
But we have to take something
from any piece of art.
But what does that have
to do with endings, really?
You can't just
stop things happening
But I think you can.
That's what an ending is.
then all of a sudden
there is a journey,
I think you're taking this
the wrong way.
but I felt like I was
missing something,
Right, but for me
I take that as a compliment
because I think
that life is unfinished,
and I think that art and film
should reflect that.
I think that, you know,
there are structures to a movie
but now even
in small independent
and, you know,
documentaries like this,
you have to fulfill
this preconceived idea
and if you don't hit
all these points,
somehow the audience thinks
there's something missing
and in that constantly
looking for what's missing,
we're not seeing what's there.
And, I mean,
for me personally,
it's really in the looking
that we are missing.
I mean, that's just sort of
my personal thing on endings.
I don't know if that
answered your question, but...
It's an interesting
discussion anyway.
Um, I think we have time for
one more. One more question?
Yeah, I could totally fall
in love with the process.
But that was probably
I was in love with the film.
- Hi. Thank you for you coming.
- Thank you.
Yeah, have a good night.
I, uh...
Yeah, I loved everything
about it.
Um, it was great.
It was a really great process.
Thank you, guys, so much
for coming.
It was nice
to meet you all, yeah.
We'll see you later on, okay?
What are you doing here?
I come to this festival
every year.
You do not.
Oh, my God.
It's so nice to see you.
Hi.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
I can't believe you're here.
It's so wild.
- I loved it so much.
- You did?
- Yeah, I was really...
- Are you just saying that?
Yeah. Isn't that
what I'm supposed to do?
- No, I really loved it.
- You did.
- Yeah, I was so moved.
- I'm glad you saw it.
Where were you sitting?
I didn't even see you.
I was hiding.
I was in the back.
- You hid?
- Mm-hmm.
But you have bad vision.
That's true.
I didn't have my glasses on.
- Yeah, it's awesome.
- Thank you.
And it's impressive
that you actually finished it
after all these years.
I mean, well,
apparently I didn't finish it,
according to some people.
That guy was such a douchebag.
No, really,
there's one at every Q&A,
and they're always
some frustrated filmmaker.
There's always one at every Q&A,
and you can tell.
Now that I think of it,
that's who that guy was.
Yeah, that's who he was.
But I liked what you said.
"It's in that looking
that we are missing."
- You liked that one?
- Yeah.
I thought it was maybe
a little pretentious or--
It was totally pretentious,
but he deserved it.
It's so good to see you.
You look great.
- I do?
- Yeah.
- Do you wanna...
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
You walking out?
Let me grab my coat.
I can't believe you're here.
It's so crazy.
Where are you staying?
I don't know.
Just got into town.
Well, what are you doing
right now?
Um... I'm free.
Really?
You're free?
- I'm so lucky.
- I'm available.
You're available.
Wanna get a cup of coffee?
Yeah, but I have something
kind of serious news.
What?
I quit coffee.
Get out of here.
You quit coffee?
Of all the people
in the world.
Yeah.
Who are you?