Guys.
I'm gonna pass out cookies
in a minute, but first...
I need you to fill out
these test cards.
I want you to rate the features
you like best.
You know,
sound, weapons, game play.
And then in your own words,
just tell us what you think of the game.
It sucked big time!
And the monster looked like
a Sesame Street reject.
- It was not scary.
- That blows.
- So lame!
- Boring.
This game is supposed to be scary.
That's why we called it "EVIL-UTION".
"We'll show you the face of evil--
Where death is the only escape."
"Be afraid"?
Do these kids look afraid?
- You guys are so canned.
- What?
But who's gonna finish the game?
Well, starting over
isn't gonna be easy, Miss Clayton.
But let's remember what this
is all about-- 7.4 billion.
That's right-- $7.4 billion.
That's what the video game industry
netted in profits last year alone.
These games are like crack to kids,
only legal.
You know that.
But do you know how to hook 'em?
How to separate them
from their $7.4 billion?
You scare them.
Yeah, Hardcore's my real name.
I had it legally changed a year ago.
I wanted Diablo,
but it was already taken.
I plan to reapply for it
when the other Diablo...
passes on.
Today's kids have seen it all.
So if you want to scare them,
you gotta be, like, out there.
Like, crazy.
Like these guys.
I started at Joystick Graphics when I
was 12, but before that I was at Asari.
We were responsible for "Star Rumblers."
I developed the sound effects driver...
for that game when I was eight,
along with "Lunar Loons."
But I had to get out of that company
on account of-- I don't really know why.
People say I'm annoying, but when it
comes to crunch time they always call.
It's like, "Bug, can you do this?
Bug, can you do that?"
They never call Bug when it's time for,
like, say a company picnic.
No, they never extend
an invitation for old Gordo.
Gordon, which is my real name,
but you can call me Bug.
Everyone calls me Bug,
although I really don't know why.
But I have a few theories.
Back in 1985, I set up my first bug
collection. I took a magnifying glass--
Now, I know.
I know these guys seem difficult.
I know they seem unconventional.
The thing is...
you can't expect some ordinary,
boring dweeb to program you scary.
No way. They don't know scary.
These guys do.
The name is Sol.
As in Solomon.
As in "the king that is wise".
As in "the solution
to all your problems."
Why should you hire me? Why?
That's just dumb.
That is a dumb question.
Why do they call that a chair?
Why is the sky blue?
Why are you dressed like a 32-year-old
when it's obvious you're at least 56?
This game will kick ass,
because these guys are kick-ass.
They will give this game muscle,
insanity, attitude.
I don't blame you
for being scared of these freaks.
I am.
But that's what makes them
perfect for this game.
So, guys, what do you think?
It's a dump.
I love dumps.
Hi, everyone.
- Welcome.
- Who are you?
Laura Wheeler.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
What game engine you responsible for?
I'm not.
I'm just the intern.
You know, I make copies
and feed the fish.
Clean up. Cookie?
Shit, you're a spy.
You're here to steal our work.
- I'm the intern.
- Sure you are.
Who sent you? Microsync?
Compu-Rom? Who you work for?
These are all chocolate chip. You have
any plain oatmeal? I'm allergic.
Careful. You don't know
what she put in those.
They're cookies, not hemlock,
you paranoid sociopath.
Kids? The game?
Oh, yeah, the game.
Where's it at?
It's there, but the other programmers
actually locked us out.
- I tried to call, but they couldn't-
- Guys.
You heard the man.
Let's work.
All right.
Let's go, let's go!
Guys, I'm just tryin'
to impress the intern.
Why?
We're in. Game on.
I thought we were working on a game
and not a piece of shit.
What congenital imbecile
hired these quasi-coders?
This is weak. There's no plug-in
for virtu-goggles, cyber-gloves.
- This is grim.
- But can you make it scary?
That is why I hired you.
Guys, you remember Faye Clayton,
the money.
Lady, scary's what we do.
- Good. You have four weeks.
- What?
Four weeks?
I think I speak for everyone
when I say "no fuckin' way".
That's not enough time to even
develop the architecture...
much less the plug-ins
for the 3-D sound.
I thought these guys were good.
Well, they are good. They already
hacked into the system and--
I know you guys are bad...
but I'm not sure
you're real bright...
so I'm going to make
this pep talk real simple.
Three things you need to know.
Number one: Time. We don't have any.
Production starts in one month and we
don't have a monster, much less a game.
Now, that's scary.
This here isn't!
So forget the plug-ins.
Forget the sound.
Fix the monster,
and fix it quickly.
This is ridiculous.
- Do you know how long this takes?
- This isn't gonna work like this.
- We need a little more time, okay?
- Number two: trust.
No telling what the competition
might do. Spies are everywhere...
which is why we have security.
There will be cameras
recording everything you do.
Each door is fully alarmed. So if you
were even thinking a nasty thought--
Total lockdown.
Nobody gets in or out.
I don't need this. Last I checked,
the 13th amendment abolished slavery.
Forget the sound?
That's crazy.
We're programmers,
not miracle workers.
Number three: A task group
will rate your work...
and based on the feature they like
the best, there will be a bonus...
of$1 million.
That's right-- $1 million.
Whoever makes the monster scary
gets $1 million.
Share it. Don't share it.
Give the little guy less. I don't care.
- I just want results.
- Oh. God.
You've got four weeks
to get it right, people.
Four weeks to make me a monster.
I'm back.
I've got supplies.
You hungry?
Fresh meat.
You shouldn't fuck with other
people's stuff, spy, especially mine.
I just wanted to feed the fish.
Like it?
It's called the "soul claw".
Goes in clean...
comes out messy.
Scary.
Scary is as scary does.
Which is why the bonus is all mine.
Why do you waste time
with those damn things?
'Cause you can't just let 'em die.
Sure you can. If you wanna make it
in this world, you gotta be PFD--
Programmed For Damage.
I got you some mouthwash...
and deodorant.
Please use them.
God! What is with you guys?
Can't you enter rooms
like normal people?
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
Laura, actually,
I was gonna ask you a question.
- And if you say no, I can--
- Hang on a second.
I got you something. Acne Buster.
Extra-extra-strength.
What'd you wanna ask me?
Stupid. Stupid!
Are you in here?
Your childish antics...
will not slow me down, Bug,
you pimple-dicked runt!
It wasn't me!
A '78 Chateau Neuf.
Did Hardcore put you up to this?
Can't I just bring you something
every once in awhile?
Don't ever play me, intern.
I need your technical expertise.
Of course-- you do.
Impressive.
Most impressive.
- Did you steal this from Daddy's cellar?
- Something like that.
Anyway, if I wanna deliver nine gigs
across a T-3 line...
what's the best way to compress
and encrypt the data?
Big question for an intern.
Well. hopefully I won't be
an intern forever.
I have this idea for a .com, and I'm
hoping that after EVIL-UTION is done--
- What is that?
- I ran a search on the word "monster".
There's a lot
of heinous shit out there...
and all of it's going on
my million-dollar AI engine.
The test kids aren't gonna
use words like "AI engine".
But they will use words like
"challenging", "exciting", "kick-ass".
They're gonna know this ain't
no Crackerjack game...
you can just memorize
a bunch of keystrokes to win.
This game is gonna help you think.
It's gonna learn as you play.
No game will ever be the same.
No game will ever be dull.
And your AI engine
is gonna give EVIL-UTION a brain?
No, better.
It'll give the game personality.
See, a game is only
as good as its programming...
Which is a direct reflection
of its programmer.
It's a whole zen-flow,
marriage-of-the-soul kind of thing.
And if you input all of this
into my objet d'art, it's--
You'll get one psycho monster.
One brilliant psycho monster.
That's it.
Give me skin on that. baby.
What? You think those meat puppets
are doing better work?
You think I should be concerned
with Bug's lame-ass musical sec-re?
Well, Hardcore does have
some pretty intense stuff.
He does? Really?
Intense?
That's funny.
I don't see a thing.
Goddamn it!
Fuckin' machines!
That's kind of unfair,
don't you think?
Well, you have to be mean...
to make the green.
Fa ye, please.
The bonus is not helping,
it's hurting.
These guys are overloading the system
trying to outdo each other.
Yeah, Faye,
I know it's your money...
but we can't afford
another overload.
I can't-
I am being professional!
Listen, these guys are pushing
everything to the max.
If we don't get some more hardware,
the whole system is gonna--
Hello? Hello?
Goddamn it!
Sol, we crashed again.
You figured that out, huh?
Impressive.
Just fix it, will you?
Back up the game...
reset the phones,
and do something about these overloads.
Yes, sir.
I'll gut right on it.
Laura, what are you doing?
Well, I've been working
on this idea that I have.
And actually, I was hoping that maybe
after EVIL-UTION was finished--
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry.
I'll get out of your way.
That's not what I meant.
Look.
Young attractive girls like you...
do not hang out with
grubby, desperate geeks like us.
Not by choice.
I'm serious.
Now, you should be out there
living it up...
looking for your Mr. Big.
You know, a friend of mine tried that.
She found her Mr. Big,
or so she thought...
until his trust fund ran out.
Still, she's gotta be
having more fun than this.
I'm sure it was a blast
for a while...
until Mr. Big suddenly became
this asshole stalker...
and graduated to
Mr. Get-Your-Hands-Off-Me.
So...
I think I'll take my chances
with the geeks.
Well, the geeks are flattered.
So, what's your idea?
- Now?
- Yeah.
Really? Okay.
- I'm gonna fucking kill you!
- Bring it on!
I'll kill you, you little twerp!
Not again.
You pussy
You fight like a lesbian biker bitch!
That's funny. You look like one.
Goddamn it, guys!
What the fuck is going on?
We don't have time for this.
You told me to fix the overload problem,
right? Well, here it is.
This pig rewired everything so he could
gorge the mainframe with his crap.
Hey, this crap can filet
your know-it-all little ass.
Maybe, but it won't get you
any closer to my bonus!
- That'll be the day!
- Get out of my face!
Stop it!
Stop trying to kill each other,
and start working on the game.
- I am working on the game.
- No, you're not.
You're working on that bonus.
I mean, Jesus!
You guys are stupid.
Do you know that?
You think all this
is worth a million dollars?
Well, it isn't.
It's worth more.
A lot more, and Faye knows that.
Only it's not gonna be worth shit
if we don't finish.
Now, I know you guys
don't like each other very much.
Hell, I don't like you.
But if this game does well,
we all do well.
There'll be bonuses for everybody...
and then we will never have
to see each other again.
But first,
we have to finish the game!
So please, don't overload the system
and don't fight.
- Okay?
- You got it, boss.
Why don't they just share the bonus?
You'll learn, intern.
You'll learn.
I'm a really big fan, Julie--
Miss Strain.
Your work in Heavy Metal 2000
to El Chupacabra...
the way that you handle a--
A sword is just a perfect blend...
of brawn and beauty that we need
for our game heroine.
My agent said
this was an acting gig...
and I only drive in the rain
for acting gigs.
This is. In fact, these games
require a lot of acting.
But in our line of business,
we call it a "motion capture."
So, where's the camera?
Actually. we'll be using
an Apex 1600 telemetry suit.
It's real next-generation type stuff.
It's got shape memory alloys
and everything.
A group of electronic impulse sensors
linked with a computer digital model...
records your every muscle movements--
So, where's the crew?
Get off.
Here's your wardrobe, honey.
- You're kidding, right?
- You're right. We don't need these.
My agent said no nudity.
Miss Julie, we need to scan you.
And in order to get
the best digital transfer...
it's essential to keep all
analog interference to a minimum.
Which means no jewelry,
no shoes and no clothes.
Hey, we just wanna get all of you
in the computer, honey.
You boys want to see the big guns,
we renegotiate.
I want options.
Don't play dumb with me.
I know these games are big business,
so I want in on the IPO...
I want preferred stock, and none of this
crap that you dump on the pension funds.
And I want it in writing.
- Not a problem.
- It's all good.
Great. Who's scanning me?
Okay, honey, strip.
Untie me, damn it!
Untie me!
This is unfair!
This is so unfair!
You guys suck!
I brought her in. I should at least
get to play with her too.
Shut up, Bug.
Oh, fine. Yeah, fine.
I see how it is.
You guys are just jealous because my
game module's the best. Well, go ahead.
Have your little fun. Then let's see
who gets a chance at the bonus now.
Give it up, little man.
This game's as scary as white rice
without my Al engine.
But without my weapons, what are you
gonna do-- think someone to death?
Without my sound...
all you guys have
are a bunch of mimes on crack.
Shut up, Bug.
So, where's my mark?
Anywhere you'd like. The remotes
in the suit are fully charged.
Hey, is this thing safe?
- Absolutely.
- A hundred percent.
All right. then,
what do you want me to do?
- Jump.
- What?
Jump. You know, up and down,
sol can calibrate the system.
Okay, my turn.
Come on.
What's going on here?
- What now?
- No problems.
It's all under control.
What you doin' later, honey?
Because you've got a nice--
I said hands off, creep!
- That's it. I'm out of here.
- No, don't go.
Shit. I think we lost everything.
It serves you right for tying me up.
Now, we have to do her all over again.
Yeah. Do her again.
Guys, give me a status report.
- I'm down, Captain. My hands are tied.
- Mine too.
- Sol.
- I'm working on it.
- Well, what? wrong with it?
- Looks like the power surge...
fried out most of the IC chips
on the motherboard.
In English.
We're down.
Total system overload.
Shit! I'm on my way.
Anything I can do to help?
Yeah. Pray.
I told that idiot not to overload.
Listen. can I just remind you
we're days away from test group?
If we have to start over,
we're fucked.
Thanks. That's just the Kind of Kick
I need to motivate my black lazy ass.
So what are we supposed to do
if the system's down?
- I don't know.
- You could help me clean.
- Maybe we can get out of here.
- Yeah.
This place is starting to smell.
Well, the good news is,
the mainframes fine.
- Well, thank God.
- But the code's corrupted.
- We lost everything.
- Goddamn it!
But I finished the backup.
All our work is right here.
- How long to load it all in?
- Well, we got a lot of stuff here.
- Probably gonna take all night.
- That sounds like a one-man job to me.
Yeah. Sol can handle it.
Like hell.
I'm no data-entry clown.
Come on. I'll do it.
You guys get out of here.
- Just tell me what I need to do.
- Well, it's simple.
All you have to do is
defrag the hard drives...
and run a batch relink
on the media files.
That was in English.
You know, for someone who's on
his third software company...
your technical skills
are sorely lacking.
Remind us again why you're the boss.
You're supposed to be Mr. King Business.
What are you doing in this dump?
- Yeah, why are you the boss?
- Because I get you guys the big scores.
Oh, yeah. And that's what happened
with the Wild Tangent gig?
- And the Compu-Rom debacle.
- And now this-- the big score.
You guys think you could
do better on your own?
You're welcome to try. Charming
personalities like yourselves...
should have no problem getting work
at the Burger Palace.
All right, then.
Who stays?
I'm okay.
How about Laura? I could stay behind
and help her get started.
- Yeah, give it to the intern.
- Leave her alone.
- Don't you think she's done enough?
- She's the intern.
Okay. We'll draw straws.
Yeah, that's easy
for the tech retard to say.
I mean, you're useless.
You don't have to draw.
Yeah, draw straws.
How pre-military industrial complex.
You guys have a better idea?
Hey, guys.
What's goin' on?
Okay, game's not fully finished...
textures aren't rendered,
and this is still a rough draft.
But tournament mode does work...
so the first person to lose all their
lives stays the night-- no excuses.
Oh, yeah. You boys
are ripe for the pickin'.
Game on!
- Here come the pain.
- Which one moves backwards?
EVIL-UTION.
In the great eruption of Mt. Edo...
a break in the earth
opened the gate way to hell
For thousands of years,
we have held back the demons below.
Now, the forces of evil
have a powerful new overlord.
He has overrun our defenses.
You are the last hope.
You must destroy the overlord.
Stop the EVIL-UTION.
Kill or be killed!
- All right, here we go.
- Here we go, boys.
Let's do this. Yes!
Come on, man!
You suck, you guys.
I'm on top of this.
I'm dominating the world.
Time out.
Defective controller.
Come on, baby.
Let's-- Come on. Come on.
Motherfucker! Which one
of you crackers disconnected me?
Come on, now!
I demand satisfaction.
- It wasn't me.
- It was Bug.
I just said it wasn't me.
- You did this!
- I didn't do it!
Give me mine back!
Give me back mine!
Oh, come on.
This sucks!
Shit! I'm out.
I taught it that.
- Get ready to be taught.
- Come on, guys. No fighting.
This is not about fighting.
This is a killing.
Go, Laura.
Girl got game.
Ms. Pac-Man champion
three years in a row.
We're a long way
from Pac-Man, little girl.
Ten bucks says Miss Pac Man
kicks your ass.
Shit, Drummond. Ten bucks?
Why don't you make it hurt?
Actually, I got 50 on the intern.
I got two hundred and twenty-six.
- No way you win. No way.
- Come on, Laura.
Come on, Laura.
Kick his ass!
You know why Pac Man
was so popular?
It was a whole metaphor for the '80s.
It's like all the power and greed.
You know, gobble up as much as you can
as fast as you can.
Hostile takeovers, leverage buyouts.
Oh, look.
- There's a power pellet.
- Shut up, Bug!
Not fair! I couldn't nuke 'em.
The fuckin' sword blasters don't work.
Yeah, they don't.
That's just too bad.
Loser.
- Beginner's luck, intern. That's all.
- Shut up, shut up.
She's still in it.
You need some more life points.
Grab some of that armor.
Oh, my God.
That is scary.
Not bad, guys.
Still a lot of work to do.
Not bad.
Sol, you make those fixes
to the game tonight?
Got 'em right here.
- With or without the Al chip?
- With.
- And you'll back up the changes?
- Yes, of course.
What?
- You need anything?
- Yeah.
- A night away from you losers.
- You got it.
I'm goin' out
and gettin' piss-drunk.
Oh, yeah? Well, I'm gonna get me
a girl and two tubs of Cool Whip.
- Cool Whip?
- I'm lactose intolerant.
Don't worry, guys.
I'll be back.
"The computer. It's more
than just a box of wires.
It's an extension
of our own humanity...
only a thousand times more powerful.
If you believe that the computer
can expand our abilities...
then why not expand upon our instinct
to care-- our capacity to give?
If we did that, we could make
every day like Christmas."
And that's the idea behind
secretsanta.com.
My God.
You hate it.
No, no. It's--
The thing is,
no one really cares about giving.
People are far more interested
in taking.
- That's a pretty dim view of things.
- Is it?
Think about it.
"Rook takes pawn."
"I'll take Park Place."
"Winner takes all."
Every game in the world
is judged by who can take the most.
- This isn't a game.
- Everything's a game, Laura.
You're either a winner
or you're a big fat loser.
So this job is what?
Like, just a giant game of Twister?
Yeah, right foot, green,
EVIL-UTION takes off.
Left hand, yellow, Faye sets us up
with first-run financing...
a place of our own,
business cards, the works.
We win if we deliver.
If we don't,
we spin a left foot. Red.
The game is gonna be great, Peter.
I mean, home run.
- And it couldn't happen to a nicer guy.
- Don't say that.
Nice is not a luxury
you can afford in this business.
Winners aren't nice.
You do not get your name
on the building by being nice.
Who are you kidding?
"Nice is not a luxury you can afford."
- Peter, you are a great guy.
- How do you know?
Maybe I'm not.
Maybe I'm a real pig fucker.
Yeah, right.
You gotta toughen up, Laura.
Life doesn't give you enough time
to be nice-- only efficient.
If you keep putting your trust
in things like "good" and "mercy"...
you're gonna lose every single time.
It's not much c-fa choice then. is it?
I mean, you either
become this monster...
or be a victim.
You'll learn, intern.
You'll learn.
All right, it's magic time.
Come on!
All right, all right, all right.
That's my million-dollar baby.
Oh, dang.
Come on, come on.
Come on, now.
Don't get uppity with me.
All right. Let's work.
Game's finishing itself.
But that's impossible, unless--
Oh, yeah. My Al chip.
Nothing artificial about your
intelligence. baby. Nothing at all.
Let's see what else you finished for me.
Let's do this.
Yeah, baby.
Hello?
Motherfucker!
Burn, baby, burn.
Hello?
I have got to get me some "me" time.
Where you at, bitch?
Impressive. Most--
Sol, what's with the mess
you left downstairs, man?
Bug, don't freak out.
Goddamn it, Bug!
What the hell's going on here?
- What happened to Sol?
- He's dead, Bug.
- Sol is dead.
- But how?
I don't know.
He was like that when I came in.
Who would've done this?
I mean, why?
And the back-up disc is missing.
Who do you think did this--
Microsync, Compu-Rom?
Does it matter? Pick one.
Fuck! Fuck!
We have to call the police.
Wait a minute. Hold on.
Let's just think about this.
Think about what?
You call the police,
they're gonna lock this place up.
Whoever stole that back-up disc can beat
us to the market with a copycat game.
Yeah, but Sol is dead.
And?
And he's-- Well, he--
You can't--
He's fucking dead. Hardcore! Jesus!
Of course.
Come on, Bug.
Are you happy
with your shitty little life?
Don't tell me you dress like that
because you choose to.
Shut up. You just don't want the police
to take you back to your little cage.
No, that's not it, man.
Let's face it.
The market's getting tougher.
The big scores are all but gone.
- This game's our last chance.
- What-- to see what prison's like?
Oh, please.
You already know.
What did you do with your big night off?
Go out with a couple of friends?
- Meet your future ex-wife?
- It's none of your goddamn business.
You did nothing, Bug. You went home
and fell asleep watching TV.
Shit, we might as well have
stayed here at work, right?
Failures the worst prison there is.
You eat alone, you sleep alone.
No one gives two shits about you.
No one.
Not even the interns.
But it doesn't have to be like that-
not anymore.
We can finish the game,
get EVIL-UTION out first and cash in.
But how do you explain that?
He couldn't take the pressure
and bailed out. Whatever.
All we need is a couple more days.
The backup disc is still missing.
The game's still playing
on the mainframe.
All I have to do
is add my sound module.
That's one less person
eligible for the bonus.
- What's wrong?
- How do I know you didn't kill him?
The same reason I know
you didn't kill him.
I'm gonna check the security cameras.
Hey, Laura, wait!
Can't have the intern beat me
to the office. I overslept.
Thank you for dinner last night.
Next time, I'll bring forks.
Good morning.
How you doin', bug?
- What's going on?
- I'm good.
Everything's good.
Everything's really good.
Are we back in business?
Good.
Get in there.
Goddamn it, Sol!
Good morning, Hardcore.
Where's Sol?
Beats me.
I think he took off.
His car's still here.
Hey, wow! Brownies!
Thanks, Laura.
Hey. What's wrong with him?
Nosy little bitch.
Oh, God!
Ah, shit!
- What's up, boss?
- Have you seen Sol?
- I need the backup disc.
- Hey, don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it for you.
But stay away from the mainframe.
Last thing I need...
is some Ivy League know-nothing
fucking with my shit.
Fine, just get it done.
Yeah, get out of here.
Some boyfriend.
No. Shit.
Goddamn it!
God, Bug!
What are you doing?
I'm finishing up
the monster's voice.
In the bathroom?
The acoustics are better in here.
Ready to die?
Sure, Bug. Whatever.
Laura, why--
What's wrong?
I just need to make a phone call.
Do you know how
to reset the phones?
Did you try
Drummond's cellular phone?
Not yet. I will.
Thank you.
- Sure.
- In a minute.
Goddamn it! Shit!
It's gonna be one of those days.
Laura, I can clean it up.
I can do it.
It's fine.
It's fine, Bug.
I got it.
Come on.
Son of a bitch.
Bullshit, they're deleted.
Yes! Gotcha.
Okay, let's see
who's fuckin' with us.
What the fuck?
Son of a--
Come on, Jeremy, pick up.
- Sol and Hardcore are at it again.
- What?
Hardcore, did you move Sol?
Because I can't find him--
Bug, listen.
There's something freaky
goin' on here, man.
I knew it. I knew you killed Sol!
I knew you killed Sol!
It was the telemetry suit.
The suit did it!
Just check the security camera.
- Don't take another step closer.
- Bug, shut up and listen!
I know it sounds crazy,
but the suit's alive, man.
It killed Sol,
and it tried to kill me.
- Please don't come any closer!
- Bug, shut up and listen!
I'm tellin' ya,
I didn't touch Sol.
It was the suit.
- Shit! Where is it?
- Help! Somebody, help!
- What is it?
- He killed Sol!
- Where is it?
- Guys, what--
- He killed Sol! Look!
- Sol's dead?
It wasn't me. It was the suit.
It was the goddamn suit.
Okay, okay.
Listen, big guy--
Leave. Everybody out.
Okay, Hardcore,
let's talk about this.
Okay? All right?
Come on, man.
Leave now!
Okay. All right.
I'm leaving.
Come on. Where are you?
Shit!
You want Hardcore?
Come and get some!
Let's get it on!
I knew something was up
when Hardcore didn't want me--
Sol's dead, and you knew?
We have to call the police.
Give me the cell phone.
I'll 9-1-1 his ass right now.
Call him.
Oh, shit!
Help me!
Help me, please!
- Oh, shit!
- Open up!
Oh, Jesus!
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
Oh, God!
Lines are all dead.
This is not good.
- What the hell's goin' on?
- I don't know. But best guess?
Yes!
As near as I can tell, it happened
yesterday with the power surge.
The storm must've nailed a transformer,
causing a surge of such magnitude...
that it overloaded the entire system.
Which normally isn't that bad,
but with Hardcore rewiring the system...
and God only knows what Sol
was doing with the AI chip...
the combination must have had
a devastating effect on the mainframe...
causing a complete in verse of code.
That's just a guess.
You know how
the telemetry suit works?
The suit moves,
the computer records it.
The suit is linked to
a digital model in the computer.
Whoever controls the suit
controls the model.
Somehow during the surge,
everything got reversed.
What's goin' on?
You guys stop this!
So the computer's
controlling the suit?
And the computer's
playing the game.
Houston, we have a problem.
Wait, wait. Stop.
Hardcore and Sol are dead
because this thing is playing a game?
Our game. EVIL-UTION.
"Kill or be killed.
Where death is the only escape."
Can't you just stop the game?
I can't. It won't let me
into the system.
Well, then can't you shut
the system down or just turn it off?
- Good idea. Let's do it.
- We can't!
Why not?
In English, Bug.
The backup disc is missing.
- Bug, who cares?
- The backup disc is the only copy...
of the game that we have
outside the mainframe.
We shut down the mainframe, we could
lose all the data, all the programming.
Well, can't we run
one of our utility programs...
and recover our work?
Well, even so, you can--
You can rebuild the game, right?
I can recreate the music.
And the sound effects.
What about the Al engine?
- That was Sol's.
- The weapons?
Jesus Christ. Didn't you guys
ever work on anything together?
- So we lose everything?
- Well, not everything.
- We'll still have our lives.
- Yeah.
Our miserable, pathetic,
poor lives.
God, you guys. What are we doing?
This game is not worth dying for.
Guys? Guys?
Come on, Bug.
Come on, Laura.
Look at me.
I'm not stupid. I know what people
think of me. I know what I am.
What are you talking about?
They just haven't
spent time with you.
You have.
Tell me.
Would you kiss this face?
Be honest.
Maybe.
"Maybe."
Well, I'm tired of being a "maybe".
I wanna be a "yes".
I need that bonus.
I need this game.
You really think that money's
gonna do all that?
Yeah, I do.
Laura's right.
I'll go.
I'll shut it down.
No, I'll go.
At least I still might be able
to save some of the work.
You go,
we'll lose everything for sure.
- Just a "maybe", huh?
- A definite "maybe".
Okay, come on!
Go, go, go!
All right.
- What? What?
- What's taking so long?
- I'm looking for the back-up disc
- What?
If that thing killed Sol,
and the back-up disc is missing...
it's still playing the game;
it wouldn't take the disc.
But, fuck the disc! Shut it off!
Come on, come on.
Look, I'm trying to save
our livelihoods here.
All right?
This is a delicate piece of machinery.
You can't just flip on a switch
and walk away like some fucking light.
Fine, fine, just hurry it up.
All right,
the RAM board is connected to--
Guys?
The 3-D board is connected to the SCSI.
The SCSI is connected to the-- what?
- Hurrying.
- Good, 'cause it killed the camera.
What do you mean,
it killed the camera?
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, man, oh, man.
The SCSI is connected to the what?
To the what?
To the red wire.
Red wire. Red wire.
Bug, are you all right?
Where is it?
Where's the monster now?
Don't shoot!
- Shut it off! Kill it!
- Jesus!
Red wire.
Goddamn it! God--
Come on, you son of a--
Shit!
Come on, come on.
God, give me something!
Come on! Okay.
Shit.
Shit!
- You okay?
- Yeah. Is it gone?
- It didn't work!
- No shit!
Can you kill it?
All right.
What do we do now?
Get outta here!
- Come on! Why's the door locked?
- Security system's fried.
- Well, override it!
- I'm trying!
Oh, come on!
Don't tell me I'm trapped in here!
Wait!
Where is that thing?
Laura, it's Jeremy.
I know you're in there.
I can see your car. Hello?
Jeremy, I'm in here!
I need your help! Please!
- In here! We're in here!
- Help! Help!
Jeremy, help us, please!
We're in here!
Come on, baby. Open the door.
Are you trying to punish me?
Is that it?
Fine. Be that way
You know, I don't need
this shit, Laura!
Why don't you go fuck yourself?
Why don't you go fuck the freaks
while you're in there?
I know that's what you
fuckin' want to do, right?
Fuck!
Laura, you better fucking hide in there,
you fucking bitch!
You fucking whore!
You fucking slut!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Fuckin' stay in there
and die, bitch!
Fuck this.
Laura, it's okay. It's me.
- Okay. That hurts.
- Oh, my God.
Here.
Jesus, Laura.
- It's nothing.
- Sorry.
Thanks.
Come on. We're gonna use
the air ducts to get outta here.
- What are you looking for?
- A way out.
See, we didn't have time to build
the game levels from scratch.
So you used the building layout.
Okay, if we just follow
the air ducts--
What's that over there? Right above
the fire engine under Edo's point.
That's it. That's how we
get outta here. Roof vent.
Oh, please.
Oh, come on.
This...
isn't...
happening.
I don't wanna die!
Fresh meat.
Damn, that was scary.
Damn, I'm good.
Programmed for damage.
Yes, you are.
- Scary is as scary does.
- That was always my favorite.
Shut up, Bug.
- What?
- Careful. Spread out.
These panels can't hold
both of us.
Do you think
we're gonna make it?
Sure. Left foot, red.
Just a tough spin,
but we'll finish the game, right?
That's not what I meant.
Bug, where are you?
Somebody help m--
Ready to die?
Maybe.
Definite maybe.
- What was that?
- I don't know.
- Get back! Get back!
- Oh, my God!
God, what was that?
Hold on. We're coming.
- Oh, my God.
- Laura, careful.
Shit.
I'll check the front door.
Come on, damn it!
Open!
- Hardcore's Palm Pilot.
- What?
Hard-cores Palm Pilot has wireless
access. It's gotta be here somewhere.
Okay, you e-mail for help.
I'm gonna get this door open.
Gross.
I got it!
No, I don't.
It's controlled by the digital model,
and the model is playing the game.
- So, how do we get outta here?
- We beat the game.
- Okay, I'm in.
- This gonna work?
Yeah, if I can kill the monster.
- Think you can win?
- Gonna try.
- This isn't Ms. Pac-Man.
- Yeah, I know.
Kill or be killed
Damn.
- Game over.
- Goddamn it!
- What is it? What's wrong?
- It's learned all my moves.
- It's getting smarter.
- It can't do that. It's just a game.
It's not. It's everything.
It's Hardcore's intensity and Sol's
attitude, even Bug-- it's all in there:
all the fighting, all the greed.
All that shit is in there,
and it's gonna get us killed!
Good.
I was wondering
when you'd learn.
Here.
Try it with these.
Ripe for the picking
- What? What is it? What's wrong?
- It's here.
Where?
I could swear it was here.
It's only me.
Laura, I promise you,
if that thing gets near to you at all...
it's gonna have to
kill me first.
Where'd it go?
Game on.
Shit.
Oh, shit.
Come on, where is it?
Where is it?
Come on, come on, come on!
Shit.
God, where is it?
Yes!
No shit!
Shit.
The back-up disc was never missing.
You took it.
You're the spy. You were gonna
sell us out from the start.
Laura, thank God
you're all right.
Where is it?
How could you?
Laura, put the gun down.
Trust me. I'm--
Don't say that.
My boyfriend--
My ex-boyfriend
used to say that.
Tell me why.
Why?
What answer do you want
to hear, Laura-- greed?
That's too simple...
even though Compu-Rom is
paying me a lot of money for this.
Ambition?
No, selling out your own company
never looks good.
Mom needs an operation.
Wouldn't that be nice
if it were true?
See, I wish I could boil it down to one
convenient answer for you, intern...
but the thing is,
if you have to ask...
then you really haven't
learned a damn thing, have you?
So don't ask me why.
Ask yourself: Why not?
But what about
your deal with Faye--
The business cards,
your name on the building?
Who cares?
That Kind of thing may impress your
folks. but out in the real world...
money is the only way
they keep score, darling.
Even if it means killing
Hardcore and Sol and Bug?
Hold on. I didn't create that monster.
They did. You said it yourself--
All that fighting, all that greed.
Put that into a computer and,
yeah, you get a real scary mess.
- Just like the real world, right?
- That's right.
The real world is messy
because people are messy.
Now, maybe you're too naive
to believe that...
or maybe-- you're just
too stupid to learn.
Either way, that fact separates us
into the haves and the have-hots.
It makes me a decision maker
and you a doormat.
It makes me a winner,
and you a lo--
You fucking bitch.
Oh, that's good, intern.
That's really good.
You're finally learning.
It's over for you.
Over? Oh, please.
I'll tell the jury
it was the pressure.
It was my childhood!
It was the game!
Because no one wants
to believe...
that we're capable
of such darkness all on our own...
that deep down inside
we're all monsters.
So it's not over.
Not yet.
That's not what I meant.
Oh, shit.
Hey, pigfucker!
Game on.
Come get some.
You'll learn, intern.
You'll learn.
- Yes! I rule!
- I beat it!
I told you I could beat you!
I beat you!
I think we have a winner.
I don't approve of the mess left behind,
but I can't argue with the results.
- Good job, Laura.
- And?
And thank you?
Three things.
One: the bonus.
The million-dollar bonus,
I believe.
But you're an intern.
Yeah, but you are happy
with the game.
Pity nobody could back up your story
that Drummond committed the murders.
Compu-Rom claims that
they've never heard of him.
And there's no security footage.
Seems odd, don't you think?
Two: Microsync releases
EVIL-NATOR this fall.
I know the name sucks, but it is
remarkably similar to EVIL-UTION--
AI engine, scary monster.
Practically identical, I hear.
Be a shame if they were
to beat us to market.
Not a chance. They're months behind us.
How could they Po-
Three:
It's like you said-- you never know
what the competition might do.
Spies are everywhere.
Miss Wheeler,
the new intern's here.
- Fine. Send her in.
- Okay.
It's not scary, it's shit.
Yes, I'm looking at it
right now, and it's not scary.
You know, I don't want to hear this.
I just want you to fucking fix it.
I really appreciate you taking the time
to do this, Miss Wheeler.
Opportunities like this are rare.
- Even more so--
- Do you have a question?
Okay. Sure.
What's the most valuable lesson
you've learned in your career?
Stupid question. Next?
What's the most important asset
for a woman to have...
- in her line of work?
- Next.
Fine.
What's the secret
of your success?
You're kidding me, right?
Look, Miss Wheeler,
I am trying to be nice here.
Don't.
What?
Don't be nice.
But why?
Because the world is not nice.
It is complicated
and it is messy.
It is overflowing with arrogance
and greed and uncertainty.
It's a lot of heinous shit.
It's a world where bad wins out
every single time.
Now, maybe you're
too naive to believe that...
or too stupid to learn it.
But if you believe in
the good and mercy of others...
you will always lose.
You will always be the victim.
And then you'll learn, intern.
You'll learn.