♪ Sharks, swords,
yogurt, kicks ♪
♪ Fries, smart phones,
hot tubs, yeah ♪
♪ Shades, bagels,
grills, airbrush ♪
♪ Chrome, blankets,
mopeds, yes ♪
♪ Drop top, laptop,
breath mints, scars ♪
♪ Kittens, wet skis,
drive-thrus, fresh ♪
♪ Tight pants, wide screens,
tacos, wheelies ♪
♪ Freestyles, thrift stores,
mini-trampolines. ♪
♪ Pickle and Peanut ♪
♪ Pickle and Peanut,
pi-pi pi-pi-pi ♪
[fluorescent lights buzzing]
Hmm.
Hmmmmm.
Let's leave.
Oh, come on man.
Let's keep thrifting.
I'm finding
some pretty good stuff.
All I found is this weird doll,
Diver Diva.
Oh, Diver Diva's great.
She tells you facts
about the ocean.
But watch out.
[singsong] She's sassy!
[girl] The Pacific
is the biggest ocean.
It's massive,
kind of like your forehead!
[giggles]
Oh, come on, man, Pickle,
you can find anything here.
You just gotta hunt
for the good stuff.
Okay, okay.
Hmm, let's see.
Scuba gear, boring.
Oh, hey, is that a toaster?
Oh, yeah, come to mama,
sweet baby.
Hey, what's this?
- [gasps] Peanut!
- What'd you find?
It's the cassette version
of Tinfoil 2000's
- Linens on Fire!
- Tinfoil 2000?!
[electronic music playing]
Pickle,
you hit a gold mine!
This album is basically
our childhood.
It helped us navigate
those dark days
before everybody figured out
how cool we were.
[electronic music playing]
[Peanut] Track three
got me through the talk.
♪ Rage, rage, pump, pump,
fist, fist, punch, punch ♪
[Pickle] Track six got me
through my first heartbreak.
- [computer chimes]
- "Let's hang out sometime."
[bleeping]
[whimpers]
That's when it was time
to turn those splashes of tears
into buckets of rage!
- [humming out-of-tune]
- [sobbing]
The 12 songs on that album
defined our whole life.
[gasps] Peanut!
This tape has a--
[stammering]
Bonus track!
Bonus track?
That wasn't on the CD.
Pickle, it's like we found
a brand-new
- Tinfoil 2000 song!
- [electronic music plays]
- Oh, hey, Big Duke!
- Big Duke!
[whispers] Psst! Guys!
I'm on the phone.
[both whispering]
Big Duke.
- Big Duke.
- Big Duke!
Uh-huh, yeah, okay.
You'll have to quit
your squawking.
I'll get back to you later,
Mr. President.
Hey, what's up, honkers?
One tape, please.
This is the greatest day
of my life.
And, uh, two of these?
Not a whole lot going on
for you, huh?
- Nope!
- No, no, no, not really.
Ready to meet your destiny?
- What do you mean?
- I'm gonna play the tape.
Pickle, the van doesn't have
a tape player.
Watch and learn.
[grunting]
- Don't say it.
- That's okay, man, look, okay?
We just gotta think
about who do we know
who has the most banging
system in town.
That-- uh, that's
retrofitted for cassetteses.
- [hip-hop music playing]
- [grunting to music]
Better, better, yeah.
[grunts]
Okay, McSweats, so can we
listen to our song now?
As you can see,
this is a top-of-the-line
machine.
How about you fellas
just hold your horses
and just watch ba--
watch the bottom
drop on this?
McSweats, we don't
have time for that!
[grunts angrily]
I don't care.
Oh, great, thanks, McSweats.
I-i-ntercepted.
Oh, come on, man, I just want
use your tape player.
First y'all gotta do
something for me.
Okay, are we live?
Hey, America.
My name's McSweats,
and this is my audition tape
for Extreme
Black Belt Warrior!
[stage whispers]
Okay, give me a close-up.
Apologies in advance
for blowing your mind.
Ichi, ni, san, shi.
[screams]
Oh, my gosh,
we gotta do something!
This is terrible!
Quick, get the tape!
- Get the tape out!
- Stop! I can't! The buttons!
- They're all jacked up, man!
- We gotta take this
to a professional!
[warbling electronic
music playing]
Oh, yeah,
this'll be no problem.
- Thanks a lot, Lazer--
- Oh, hey, thank you--
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Lazer!
We need you to fix this.
What? I'm basically
a scientist,
and even I
couldn't make this
thing work again.
Come on, there's a track
on that tape we gotta hear!
Ugh! Look, I can't make
your cassette stop playing.
The tape's gonna get
shredded no matter what,
but maybe if you replace
the speaker,
you can at least
still hear the track.
Check the bottom
of the lake.
We just
dumped one of those
stereos last week.
You guys just dump stuff
in the lake?
That's, like,
our drinking water.
We're called the Gadget Dump!
What the brown
did you think we do here?!
[warbling electronic music
continues]
[gasps] That's the baseline
to track 10.
We're running out of time.
Man, how the heck
are we gonna get
- to the bottom of the lake?
- You know what?
Remember back
at the thrift store?
They had those two big boxes
of scuba gear.
- We can go back and get those.
- Yeah, let's go, man!
Let's do it!
- Hurry up! Hurry up,
dude! Let's go!
- Okay, geez.
Hey, sorry again, man.
There's only one box
of scuba gear,
and one box
of five Cuban sandwiches.
Yeah, hey, no problem.
"A," I like Cuban sandwiches.
"B," I think I found something
that'll do the trick anyhow.
Magellan was the captain
of the first ship
to circumnavigate the globe.
What have you done
with your life?
[warbling electronic music
continues]
[gasps]
Peanut, the tape's on track 12!
We only have a few minutes left!
Then let's find that speaker.
[grunting]
Some scientists say lampreys
have the greatest suction
of all sea creatures,
but I think it's you.
Ugh, smells like plastic
in here.
[muffled speech]
What?
"I can't hear."
Oh, got it.
These emojis are getting
real specific.
Okay, Peanut,
we have five minutes
to get down there
and find that stereo
or we'll never hear
that bonus track.
[muffled]
I can't hear you!
[electronic dance music plays]
[grunts]
- [roars]
- [muffled] Lampreys!
[grunts]
[gasping]
Peanut, are you okay?
[muffled]
Look, the stereo!
Huh? Oh!
The stereo!
Oh, no!
♪ Dootly doot doot doot,
I love my job ♪
We gotta get that speaker!
[grunts]
I can't get a grip!
[muffled] Pickle! You can use
one of these guys! These guys!
Oh, yeah,
pretty good there, rookie,
but check this out.
Hey, look at me,
I'm a tapir! Agh!
[sighs] Don't say it.
[muffled]
Oh, come on man, don't--
[both scream]
Hey, why do we have
to dump the truck, too?
Look, I don't make
the rules, Kent!
Let's get out of here!
[warbling electronic music
playing]
We can still pull this off,
Peanut!
[grunts]
[man] Exclusive
[stammering] bonus track.
We did it! We're only
gonna hear it once,
but at least we'll
hear it together.
[dance music plays]
Oh, right.
[grunts]
This thing is stuck
on your fat head.
What are we gonna do?
[muffled] Stop trying!
I got it!
You're right, you're right.
We'll call it off.
We can't hear
the bonus track together,
- I don't want
to hear it at all!
- [muffled shouting]
Stop being a Diver Diva!
I'm not listening
to this song without you!
- Peanut! Peanut!
- Pickle, stop! Stop!
Pickle! Pickle, no more,
come on, stop it!
- Peanut!
- [gasps]
Finally, some circulation.
- [music stops]
[moans]
Oh, we were so close.
The octopus has nine brains.
Looks like you don't
even have one.
Pickle, no, whoa, whoa,
Pickle, hold on a minute.
Peanut,
shut your voluptuous lips
and let me mourn.
Look, I recorded
the whole thing on my phone.
- Wha--?
- Yeah, that's what
I was trying to tell you
when you were about
to throw the stereo in the lake.
Oh, my beautiful baby boy!
You ready to finally meet
your destiny?
Ready as I'll ever be.
[Pickle and Peanut shouting
over dance music]
Actually, it sort of has
a flow to it.
Like a remix.
I love it.
It's perfect, Pickle.
I guess it all worked out
in the end, huh?
It always does, buddy.
It always does.
[hip-hop music plays]
♪ Big buns, big meat,
what you want to eat? ♪
♪ Big fun, fresh meat,
sniff up on my meat ♪
♪ You want some fries
with that? ♪
♪ Fries with that?
Yeah, we want fries with that ♪
♪ Gimme some fries with that ♪
♪ Sucking big shakes,
make that belly quake ♪
♪ All that you can take,
chicksy nugs was a mistake ♪
♪ You want some fries
with that? ♪
♪ Fries with that?
Yeah, I want fries with that ♪
♪ Give me some fries
with that ♪
♪ The meat and the buns,
the meat and the buns ♪
♪ What you gonna want,
then you get some fries ♪
♪ Eat up all your fries,
then you want some fries ♪
♪ Gotta eat some fries,
then you put some ♪
♪ We're doing
movie business, holy cow ♪
♪ Can you believe
we're making movies now? ♪
Oh, hello,
and welcome to a special
behind-the-scenes look
at Pickle and Peanut.
Let me just slip out
of this old costume here.
[sighs happily]
Oh, yeah, it feels good
to get out of that fat suit.
Now, we're not just here
to give you
a little sneak peek
behind the scenes.
We're here for
a special purpose today.
Now as everybody knows,
one of my biggest passions
outside of the show
is raising awareness
for my boneless cats charity.
It's a little-known fact
that one in every four cats
is actually born
without bones.
[Peanut] When Pickle told me
about this problem,
I knew we had to take action.
Plus with our gargantuan
celebrity cachet...
We'll raise the money
in no time.
Because everybody knows
that we have the best fans
in the entire world.
You guys are insatiable.
Unquenchable. Bottomless.
So to raise money to change
the sweet little kitties' lives,
- we're throwing a...
- [both] Clip-show telethon!
And we got
our number-one man
running the deck,
ain't that right, McSweats?
Yeah, I'll do
whatever you guys want
as long as you keep paying me
in that sweet black licorice.
Oh, man, take it easy
on that stuff there, McSweats.
Now roll those titles.
- [grunts]
- [upbeat theme plays]
You know, oftentimes,
we often ask ourselves...
What makes you guys so hungry
for so much Pickle and Peanut?
Our torrid platonic
friendship?
That's right, remember the time
we took our friendship vows?
I will never forget.
[blows kiss]
Thank you for being here,
Pickle.
I trust our friendship,
and I cherish our friendship.
Thank you for that, Peanut.
I trust our friendship,
and I cherish our friendship,
[both exclaim happily]
Hey, look,
donations are coming in.
Well, if you like that,
you know what else
they're gonna love?
No.
Well, it's not just about us.
How about all the people
we met along the way
that you fell in love with?
Roll the clip.
♪ Champion horse ♪
♪ Hey, everybody, Speda ♪
- [man] Sneaky... Patty.
- Shh!
♪ Everybody in the world
loves Mr. Mjart ♪
[cow moos]
♪ '90s adventure bear ♪
Papa fly.
[hip-hop music plays]
[reggae music plays]
- [crowd] It's Philip!
- [metal music plays]
I guess I'm always just gonna be
the bully to you guys, huh?
- That makes me so mad!
- [screams]
[man] Scampi!
♪ Scampi, Scamp, Scamp,
Scampa-dooby-da-bee-bow ♪
- You're the best, Ryan!
- [screams]
- [man, flatly] Ryan.
- [screams continue]
Hey, looks like those clips
did the trick, Flopsy.
We're gonna reach our goal
in no time.
- [meows]
- You said it.
Not only do we have a bunch
of crazy friends,
we also got to see
crazy places.
- Like the sunbaked wilds
of Australia.
- [groans]
- ♪ You can't make a cookie ♪
- ♪ Without the chocolate chip ♪
Oh, that was kind of
a strange clip to play
from that
action-packed episode.
Oh, no, no, sorry,
wrong clip.
Check this one out.
[slow motion]
♪ You can't make a cookie... ♪
[Pickle] This is the good stuff.
They're getting deep.
[Peanut]
Oh, yeah, that's exotic.
Oh, no!
- No, wait, wait, wait!
- Peanut, friendship tunnel!
We're never gonna be able
to help these cats at this rate.
I think we might just be
on the wrong track, man.
The stuff is just going
right over their heads.
- What are we gonna do?
- We gotta go for
the lowest common denominator.
We're talking slack-jaw,
mouth breather kind of stuff.
Okay?
We're talking action clips.
Hey, McSweats, why don't you
crank up the intensity?
I'm afraid not, boys,
this young man's
black-licorice levels
are off the charts.
One more sweet bite
and his blood
would've turned
into a delicious
black jelly.
Wait, hold on, hold on,
we're doing a fundraiser here.
He needs to stay here
and do the action clips.
No, this man needs
to go to the hospital.
- Well, maybe we can get
a second opinion?
- Hmm?
[shudders]
You dark merchants.
All right,
now run those action clips!
[muffled] You're the boss.
[screaming]
- Don't sting it!
Don't sting it!
- [screams]
[explosion]
[both screaming]
- No, no, no, no, no!
- [screams]
- [roars]
- Six-point buck!
- [screams]
- [coughing]
[screaming and grunting]
[Peanut] Okay, yeah,
that's the spirit.
But what are we gonna do
to take this to the next level?
What are you guys doing here?
[both] Melissa Joan Hart?
[singsong] That's right!
I thought you guys
weren't allowed
- back on company property.
- They said never come back.
And technically,
we never left.
♪ Loophole! ♪
[trills tongue]
Wait, that's it!
We need to use the power
of our celebrity guest stars.
Hey, MJH,
you were on our show once.
Uh, I was
on your show a bunch.
- Uh, what?
- Check out these clips.
- [electronic beat plays]
- ♪ They call her ♪
- [man] Melissa Joan Hart.
- Melissa Joan Hart.
- ♪ They call her ♪
- ♪ Pi-pi-pi ♪
Hey, wait, where was I
in all those cli--
[shouts]
Never mind, never mind.
If that's what the fans want,
that's what the fans want.
Yeah, and actually,
you guys never paid me
to be in those episodes.
- [buzzer buzzes]
- [both gasp]
Yeah, thanks, I'm gonna go blow
this pocket change
on some, uh, luxury SUVs.
♪ Bye ♪
[engine revs, tires squeal]
- Ahh...
- [horn honks]
- Dang, that's a sweet ride.
- Hey, don't give up, Peanut.
- There were other guest stars.
- Oh, that's right,
Hey, what about Little Chugger
the face train?
Everybody loves
a little chuggin'.
[deep male voice]
There's no problem
when you've got friends.
[screams]
- [screams]
- What's going on?!
Mm, uh, hey, guys.
Good news and bad news.
Good news is I'm feeling
a whole lot better.
Bad news is I puked
sticky black licorice
all over this AV equipment.
Ain't no more clips
coming out of this
bad mama jama.
- Oh, no.
- In other bad news, I guess,
this doctor is
riding the black rope
to pleasure town.
He may never come back.
He may not want to.
[somber music plays]
- [sighs sadly]
- Peanut...
Oh, sorry, cats.
Sorry, Pickle.
I guess my star doesn't shine
bright enough to help anybody.
Oh, come on, Peanut.
Here, have some licorice.
Get that outta here, man!
I'm not getting
on that junk again.
This clip show
was a stupid idea.
Oh, hey,
don't talk like that.
Your stupid ideas have gotten us
into a lot of stupid situations,
but we always find
a stupid way out.
Yeah, but how are we
supposed to have
a clip show
without the clips?
Well, there's one other way
we can show them
our memories.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about
a direct mainline
right
into our subconscious.
Wait, wait, hold on,
you can't mean--
Yes, we let everyone
into the friendship tunnel
at once.
I don't know, Pickle,
that sounds so dangerous.
We're gonna be sore
for weeks.
- [pan flute playing]
- Our friendship
is the only thing
that's gonna save
these Dumpster cats.
You know what?
You're right.
I trust our friendship,
and I cherish our friendship.
[both]
Friendship tunnel!
[electronic music plays,
no voices]
Friendship!!
[dub-step music plays]
[music stops,
both panting]
- That was amazing!
- Yeah! Let's check the chart!
[buzzer buzzes, both groan]
Guess it didn't work, huh?
I'm sorry, Flopsy.
Wet Tissue.
Puddles. Bonesey.
That's kind of ironic.
We really let you down.
[crying]
We tried so hard!
And I just--
I don't know what else--
[Lazer] Will you two
lady babies quit sobbing?
[both] Huh?
[Peanut]
What are you guys doing here?
We saw your pathetic
failure on TV,
and I want to help you out
with your soggy-cat problem.
[both stammering]
Yeah, I'll help you guys.
Oh, runk-a-dunk,
I'll help you, too.
I'd do anything
for you boys!
[all chattering]
- Oh, thank you so much!
This is amazing!
- Thank you, everybody!
Oh, my gosh,
you guys really do love us.
Wow, we really are
the world's biggest stars.
Listen, every penny
of your generous donations
are going directly to
the enrichment and betterment
of these poor cats' lives.
Yeah, starting with
the bare-boned essentials.
[upbeat music plays]
[horn honks]
[both]
Boom-ba-boom-boom-boom-boom!
Boom boom boom!
Boom boom boom bo--
Boom-ba-boom-boom-boom-boom
boom-ba-boom-boom-boom-bo--
♪ How's your mom? ♪
♪ She's doing pretty well ♪
♪ Her ankles kinda swell ♪
♪ How's your mom? ♪
♪ I'd rather not tell ♪
- ♪ How's your mom? ♪
- ♪ Okay ♪
♪ How's your mom? ♪
♪ Not so great,
but she'll be better ♪
♪ How's your mom? ♪
♪ She's knitting me a sweater ♪
♪ I don't think
that you've even met her ♪
- ♪ How's your mom? ♪
- ♪ She's okay, please stop ♪