Do not be afraid, my friends.
This is the only way to fly.
It'll be worth it, Scoob.
Just think, royal food tasters.
All the food we can eat,
and we get paid!
Yeah!
That'll be 14 dinar.
Don't worry, Scoob.
It'll be over soon.
- I hope.
- 14 dinar, please.
- Just whatever you do...
- 14 dinar.
...don't look down.
The ride is over.
14 dinar.
Over? Over!
You mean we're there?
And we're still alive?
I knew that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You did not.
And it's 14 dinar, please.
Come on, Scoob.
We made it.
Cut it out, Scoob.
We'll be late for our interview.
Hey!
Oh, like, sorry.
- Like, hi!
- Yeah, hi.
We're here about the job.
- You know, royal food tasters.
- Yeah.
Like, after you.
Suckers.
Hear that, Scoob?
- Suckers for dessert!
- Yum!
So you two fellows
want to be royal food tasters.
You bet!
Do you have any previous experience
with food?
- This morning.
- Yeah, breakfast!
Well, you look like two fellows
with hearty appetites...
...and cast-iron stomachs.
- You're hired.
- All right!
We're royal food tasters!
Dance later. Taste food now!
Wow!
- Like, what's this stuff?
- That is hummus tahini.
Yeah, but, like, what is it?
Mashed garbanzo beans in tahini sauce!
- What's tahini sauce?
- Tahini sauce is good!
- Eat!
- Okay.
Yum!
We sure were a couple of lucky pups
to score this gig, Scoob.
Yeah, yeah!
Yum, yum, yum.
Stuffed eggplant!
Can you imagine quitting this job?
Nope.
Neither can I.
Like, I finally found my true calling.
Yummy, yummy, yummy!
Stuffed grape leaves.
That caliph is in for
the lunch of his life, Scoob.
I wonder what he's
gonna have for dinner.
Me too.
The last food taster
never made it to dinner.
Like, you won't have
to worry about us.
We'll be plenty hungry
by dinner, right, Scoob?
Yeah.
- Famished.
- You do not understand.
It isn't your appetites you should
be worried about losing.
Oh, no, Scoob!
We aren't supposed to see
if the caliph's food tastes good.
We're supposed to see
if the food is...
...poisoned!
- Poisoned?
You got it, bubee.
- That's Scooby.
- Scooby, bubee, whatever.
Soon it's going to be R.I.P.
- Shaggy.
- Are we in heaven?
No, if this was heaven...
...all those empty plates would be
piled high with food.
Like, that must mean
we're in the other place.
Oh, no! No, Scoob!
I'm too young to die!
No, no! There's still
so many lunches to eat...
...and breakfasts and dinners too.
Relax. The food wasn't poisoned...
...this time.
Oh, boy. Like, that was a close one.
Yeah, close.
But you're still probably dead.
You ate the caliph's entire lunch.
How are my royal food tasters?
They aren't here,
so they must still be alive.
Oh, good!
Well, mustn't keep the caliph
waiting for his lunch.
Today's a big day.
He has his usual share of ruler-type
duties to attend to...
...plus the important, but happy, task
of choosing a wife.
My mighty majesty...
...prepare to feast your eyes
and your stomach.
That's lunch?
Yuck-o!
No, no, sire,
that's not lunch.
They are the ex-royal food tasters.
- Ex?
But we're great food tasters.
We ate everything and...
You guys ate my lunch?
The royal lunch? All of it?
Yeah, and it was terrific.
Great work, dude...
Sir.
Yeah! What's for dinner?
I'll be in the kitchen
fixing a little snack...
...if you need me.
Wow. There's a heavy penalty
for scarfing up the royal lunch.
Now, let's see.
What was that penalty again?
Oh, yeah!
Like, isn't that kind of excessive?
How's about we just go to bed
without dinner or TV?
- Yeah.
- Guards!
Yipes!
Hey, you come back here, all of you!
I'm sure glad it's you.
- They're around here somewhere.
- No kidding.
I would have never guessed they'd
actually be someplace we were looking.
- We must be great at our jobs!
- We should ask for a raise.
All right, all right.
Just don't let them get away.
Let's try in here.
I wouldn't want to be them
if we catch them in there.
Hey, what are you guys doing in here?
You know men are not
allowed in the harem.
Except for me, of course.
Yes, my sire, but the intruders...
Forget them. I've got real stuff to do.
- Like choose my wife.
- Whatever you say, sire.
Good. Then I say, so long.
Now, then, who is it going to be?
Let's see now.
She's gotta be very up
on the latest stuff.
Yeah, music, fashion, books.
She should be cool and with-it.
But smart too.
Good grades and everything.
And of course,
she's gotta be a babe.
- You!
- Me?
Yeah. Where have you been
all my short life?
Forget where you've been. All I
care about is that you're here now...
...and that you'll be my bride.
- I will?
Excellent. You'll make me
the happiest caliph in all Arabia.
Oh, no.
Like, I know how to make you
a lot happier.
No way. Really?
Yeah, I mean, gee, I...
I know. How about a story?
I tell a way-cool story.
A story? Cool.
Don't worry, Scoob.
It's all part of the plan.
I'II, like, tell him a real dull story and
put him to sleep. Then we can escape.
- Story, story! Story, story!
- Coming.
Well, since you're in, like,
a romantic mood...
...how's about the romantic tale
of Aliyah-din and the magic lamp?
I am truly sorry, princess.
We had hoped you would be the one...
...but you are a delightful lady and will
make the right man an excellent wife.
Believe me. It is not you.
Well, of course it isn't me!
No one is perfect, my son.
She wasn't perfect, Father.
I mean, there was
nothing wrong with her.
- But nothing right, either.
- There was plenty right.
- Just not enough.
- I love my son, Haman.
- I want only his happiness.
- I know, my lord.
Marriage to a wise woman who loves him
will enrich his life...
...and give him joy
he cannot even dream of.
That is exactly
what I'm looking for, Father.
Look at him, alone, brooding, forlorn.
- Look at me. Do I look happy?
- No, my lord.
But happiness was within our grasp.
Oh, yes.
Love, marriage, perfect bliss,
all ours.
The princess of Serandibe had been
promised to my son upon her birth.
She was a child of exquisite beauty
and great promise.
The kingdom's future was secure until...
Yes, sire, I know.
She was gone.
- Vanished, like a shooting star.
- A great mystery.
A greater tragedy.
Now the very kingdom is at risk.
With no wife, there is no heir.
I have scoured all Arabia
for a suitable bride.
And still the wedding bells
remained silent.
My son has rejected every
eligible female in the kingdom.
My son can never be sultan
if he cannot provide an heir!
And this he cannot do
without a wife.
The prince must marry,
and there will be no more delay.
Scribe!
- Make a proclamation.
- As you wish, sire.
All nobly born females in the kingdom
are to present themselves at the palace.
Tonight!
The prince will choose one for his bride.
- But, sire...
- No buts! No exceptions!
Of course...
...not, sire.
Only, how will it be possible to notify
all the eligible ladies by tonight?
You are right.
Make it tomorrow.
Is this necessary, Your Highness?
Surely the prince will find an
appropriate young lady on his own.
But when?
Soon it will be too late.
When? Who could know?
- Eventually.
- You are right, old friend.
My son will choose
in his own good time...
...but that may be too late.
It is only Haman, my prince.
You know your father means well.
He only wants you to be happy.
So take your time
and make the right choice.
No matter how long it takes.
Wait! No, she can't hear me.
Wait! Gone...
Arise, O Lord of the Amulet.
Who disturbs the peace
of the Lord of the Amulet?
This humble and worthy servant
begs your counsel, O lord.
Again?
It is 18 years since I last
received your wise guidance.
And you dare present yourself
again so soon?
But, lord, the plan put into effect those
many years ago is now bearing fruit.
The abduction
of the princess of Serandibe...
...has reached the crisis point
you so long ago predicted.
Of course it has!
The old sultan's health is failing.
The young prince never married.
Soon the throne will be empty.
Yes. So?
This insignificant one fears his meager
magic will fail if left on its own.
Can you do nothing for yourself?
In the tomb of riches
resides the magic lamp.
- Tomb of riches?
- Of course you don't know.
Its location is revealed every three years
by the light of a full blue moon.
Whoever possesses the lamp controls
the power of the genie within.
But take care that the tomb of riches does
not become your own final resting place.
Only the pure of heart may enter...
...and leave.
- But, lord...
- I know you are not pure of heart.
- Then who...?
- Lf you will stop interrupting.
Better.
Aliyah-din can retrieve the lamp.
No other.
Tomorrow, by the light
of the full blue moon.
This happens only once every three
years and the next time is tomorrow?
Do not question the hand of fate.
And do not disturb me again.
He'll pay. They'll all pay!
I don't understand
how I can possibly help.
You...
You are the only chance we have.
There is, in a secret place,
a special lamp.
Within this lamp is the last
remaining hope for our sultan.
It has been foretold that you,
and only you...
...can retrieve this lamp.
It is a great honor you have been given,
as well as a grave responsibility.
I will do what I can.
I promise.
We have little time. Meet me tonight
by the light of the full blue moon.
Do not be late.
Our sultan's fate is in your hands.
- Look, it's him!
- Isn't he cute?
Maybe he'll pick me.
Oh, please.
And why should he pick you
when he can have me, dear?
Quiet. He'll hear you.
I'm going to be late!
Oh! Now I'm going to be really late!
What? The prince will choose a bride...
...from all the eligible ladies
of Shiraz? Tomorrow?
Do not get too excited.
He'll never choose you.
I know that.
Wait a minute. Why not?
Just look at yourself.
How can my father expect me
to marry some girl I've just met?
It's ridiculous!
Except for you.
Excuse me.
- You!
- I have to go.
- No, you don't.
- I don't?
No. Never.
Oh, I have to go.
Wait!
You're late! Where have you been?
- I'm sorry, l...
- I'm sorry too.
It's just the sultan...
Oh, it doesn't matter.
The blue moon can't reveal its secret
while it's clothed in clouds.
- What is it?
- The moon!
Down there, child, inside
the tomb of riches, is the lamp...
...and with it, your destiny.
Remember, only the purity of your soul
allows you to enter the tomb.
It is filled with
unimaginable temptations.
But take only the lamp!
Flowers! They're so lovely.
What harm can come
of picking just one?
What is taking that girl so long?
No! It can't be!
She was pure.
The Lord of the Amulet said so.
Why, you're not a flower.
I wonder if anything here
is what it seems.
The lamp!
You're a funny little lamp.
But the wazir says that you have
the power to cure the sultan.
What?
No!
The lamp. My lamp!
Gone!
Cursed girl,
you have cost me my lamp...
...but I will not be defeated.
The throne will be mine!
Haman!
Oh, what's the use?
Are you the cause of my undoing?
No. No.
I only have myself to blame.
And what is worse,
my sultan must also suffer.
And my prince.
Tomorrow he will pick a bride.
And where will I be?
I will be here.
Well, perhaps you can at least
help me see what "here" is.
"Rub me"?
What can that mean?
Hey, hey, hey!
Yeah, that was one long hibernation.
I'll bet I haven't eaten in eons.
Hey, hey, hey!
Looks like a bumper crop.
My choppers must be
out of practice.
Nothing so rare
as a bright yellow pear.
Yum!
That pear was no fair.
All these treats are a trick,
and it's not even Halloween.
Boo Boo, buddy!
Glad you could make it,
my genie-in-training-type bud.
Maybe this time,
I'll get my wisp of smoke.
Then I'll be able to fly, like you.
Yeah. With my tummy on empty,
I'm almost grounded myself, Boo Boo.
Golly, Yogi, I don't think
we're here to eat.
Hear that, tummy?
Boo Boo says no yummies.
So why are we here?
We're here to give her
three wishes.
She's our new master, Yogi.
Three wishes?
You think maybe she'll
use one for say...
...a picnic basket that we
could all, you know, share?
Kind of. Sort of.
I don't believe I've had
a good night's sleep...
...since the princess
of Serandibe was lost.
Oh, well. After tomorrow,
everything will be fine.
My son will be married.
The kingdom will be secure.
There will be purpose to life.
But I will never get to tomorrow without
a potion to help me sleep tonight.
Eye of newt and toe of frog...
...wool of bat and tongue of dog.
What drivel!
Now, this could be something.
My poor sultan...
...wasting away over
concern for your son.
Never sleeping...
...but Haman will help you.
Yes.
Haman will fix it
so that you'll never wake up.
Powerful stuff.
My sultan.
Haman, my trusted counsel.
- Once again, I must trouble you.
- Trouble? Never.
Here.
I brought something that cannot fail
to bring the peace you deserve.
- Breathe deeply.
- Oh, yes.
That's right. Just like that.
Excellent.
I'm sorry, Father. I never meant...
It's just all these women are...
I mean, I always thought
you wanted me to be happy.
That is, I know
you want me to be happy.
But if it will make you happy,
I will marry tomorrow.
I'm sure there's one woman.
Oh, Father, I promise.
No more grief.
Tomorrow, I will marry.
Father!
It's all right.
It's just a potion.
Your father is finally at peace...
...just as you will be!
Who needs a genie?
It's working!
Everything is working!
At least the important stuff
is working.
Sleep well, my prince...
...and may you find
the girl of your dreams...
...but only in your dreams.
I must content myself
with your throne.
But be assured...
...it will do!
What is your first wish, O master...?
Masteress...?
Ma'am?
- Wish?
- I don't think she gets it, Yogi.
No?
Well, let me make you comfy whilst
I give out with the explanations.
Yeah, maybe a little less comfy?
Much better! Now, then...
...you have three anything-your-
little-heart-desires-type wishes...
...and if you need any more
explanation than that...
...I can get you baba ghanouj...
...tabbouleh...
...or hummus...
...lip-smacking wara areesh...
...or finger-licking malfouf.
I can serve you breakfast,
brunch, dinner or lunch...
...or could anything be finer
than owning your own diner?
It's my task to get you
whatever you ask.
Hey, hey, hey! What are you
waiting for, your birthday?
Blow out the candles
and make like a wish.
Now, wow,
what do you think?
Pretty good deal?
- Yogi!
- Not now, Boo Boo.
Can't you see
I'm granting wishes?
But, Yogi, maybe
she doesn't want food.
But goodies are such a good wish.
Maybe for you, but how do you know
it's what she wants?
Because I'm smarter
than the average genie.
Besides, what else
could she possibly want?
Well, I don't know. Let's ask.
- Hi.
Is this your wish?
- Come on out, Yogi.
- I can't, Boo Boo.
I'm all out of ideas.
Well, why don't we ask...?
- What's your name?
- Aliyah-din.
That's a nice name.
Mine's Boo Boo.
That's Yogi.
Why don't you ask...?
Great idea, Boob!
Almost as good as if
I thought of it myself.
So, what can ol' Yogi get you?
Just name it, and it's yours.
What do you want, Ali?
What's your heart's desire?
Oh, what's the use?
I can never have it.
It's far too much.
Let us genies be the judges of that.
Well, if I could have any wish...
...I would save my poor sultan
who languishes near death.
And if I could have another wish...
...I would make myself
worthy of the prince.
But it doesn't really matter.
I'm only a simple, common girl.
And besides, the prince is probably
married by now anyway.
Not just yet.
- You mean it's possible?
- It's more than possible.
- It's a done deal!
- And that's only two wishes.
You still have one left.
Right, Boo Boo. Perhaps I can
interest you in a little snack.
Yogi!
But for me to be worthy of a prince...
...I must be a princess.
- She catches on quick.
- How do I look?
- See for yourself.
And, of course...
...what's a princess
without a princess' dowry?
How's that for rich?
Not to mention high in vitamins
and nutrients.
That's for the prince, Yogi!
I was just gonna sample it
to make sure it was fresh.
This is all so amazing.
I don't know what to say.
You don't have time to say anything
if you want to get to the prince...
...before he gets hitched...
Married, that is.
What's the matter, Ali?
Yeah! You gotta get go, go, going!
- But how?
- How?
You are looking at
the genuine article, Ali.
A-one, full-service, money-back-
guarantee-if-you're-not-satisfied genies.
Oh, thank you!
You're so wonderful!
End of the line, sugar.
A thousand and one pardons,
your honor.
Oh, what's the use?
I can't compete with
the noblest ladies of the realm.
Hey, hey, hey! Why so blue-blue...
...when you got Yogi and Boo Boo?
The prince will never even notice me.
The prince won't even seen them
with you around.
- You really think so?
- Abso-dabba-lutely.
Well, I'm still in training.
See, Ali?
It's your turn already.
It can't be!
Get going and break
the proverbial leg.
And who...
...might you be, my dear?
- Me? I'm...
- My lord!
- Scribe...
...I'm glad you are here.
You may dismiss
the rest of the candidates.
But there aren't
any more candidates.
- Good.
- You don't understand, sire.
There were more. Lots more!
They just...
...disappeared.
- Did they?
How convenient.
You may go, scribe.
I said, go!
Now, then, my dear...
...your name?
Your name!
I don't know.
What is it?
- Aliyah-din.
- Who's that?
- You!
- Really? How nice.
My name is Aliyah-din, my lord.
A lovely name
for such a lovely lady.
Thank you, sire.
I do not come empty-handed.
I have an ample dowry.
The most beautiful and gracious lady
in the kingdom...
...is all the riches
I could ever want.
Although, perhaps a simple token...
...that lamp at your side,
for instance.
Mine! Finally, mine!
No!
No longer must I hide
behind foolish disguises.
Now, I alone have the power!
Hey, hey, hey!
Are we ready for a wedding-type feast?
I guess not.
I am your master now.
You must do as I wish.
As you wish, master.
Good!
For my first wish, I would have you
make me sultan...
...with all the trappings and majesty
of the office.
As you wish, master.
Guards, seize her and throw her
in the dungeon!
Now...
...let the real wishes begin.
Oh, my prince!
What is to become of us?
Our Lord...
...rescue us from our oppressors...
...and raise for us from thee...
...one who will protect...
...and raise for us from thee
one who will help.
We will be fine, my prince.
Allah is watching.
He will guide me.
His majesty...
...Haman, sultan of Shiraz!
It has such a nice ring to it.
Now, then...
...what to do about those
other two pesky wishes?
Rise and shine, genie.
Is it an earthquake?
Oh, it's worse.
- It's you.
- Yes, it's me.
What do you need, master,
some Dramamine?
No, but I do need my second wish.
How's about a little public feast
to celebrate your sultanship?
- No!
- Not even a teensy-weensy feast?
No!
- How about toasted marshmallows?
- No!
What's going on?
Not so fast, genie-in-training.
This is where you win your wisp of smoke.
Yes. Why simply rule Shiraz
when I can rule the world?
Why not?
Here we go again.
Yep. Another power-hungry evil guy
bent on world "donimation."
Nobody's ever happy with
a kingdom, a beautiful wife...
...and all the gold they can count.
- They're all alike.
If you're through, I'd like to make
my second wish now.
Your wish is my command.
I know.
For my second wish, I want supremacy
over the entire universe!
You're sure you wouldn't want
maybe a cheese sandwich...
...and a nectarine instead?
- No!
- Aren't you even a little bit hungry?
- Hungry? Yes.
Hungry for power!
You'd think some of this hunger would
go to his stomach instead of his head.
- Just do as I wish!
- Gee, what a grouch.
Hey, hey, hey!
I wish...
I'm sorry, my prince.
I have no more wishes.
Oh, prince!
I shall return, my darling, I promise.
Finally! My power is complete!
The world turns at my whim!
Maybe now we can eat.
Now, then, about my third wish...
Gee, I hope it's gonna be a falafel
or tabbouleh.
Granting wishes isn't easy
when your stomach's always queasy.
A third wish.
What else can I possibly want
now that I have everything?
The lamp!
What do you get for the man
who has, quite literally, everything?
- A queen to share...
- I do not share anything...
...with anyone!
- Of course not.
What could I have possibly
been thinking of?
- For my third...
- And final!
...and final wish...
...I wish to live forever...
...so that I may rule the universe
throughout eternity!
- Yogi!
- What is it, my genie-in-training buddy?
Oh! Really?
- You are completely correct, Boo Boo.
- I demand my wish!
- Nope.
- No way.
You must obey! I own the lamp!
No!
Hey, hey, hey!
What's your first wish, tiny masteress?
I wish that everything was
as it should be.
My pleasure, masteress.
Guards, arrest him!
You can't do this. Put me down!
- I am your supreme ruler!
- Not anymore!
My scarf!
I've been searching for you
to return it.
I don't even know your name.
- Aliyah-din.
Aliyah-din, you are the girl of my dreams.
Say you will become my princess.
Are you sure you really want me?
How could you think anything else?
You don't understand.
Your love isn't given freely.
You see, I wished for your love.
I was bewitched the moment I saw you.
Then we both got our wishes?
We will, the moment
you consent to be mine.
Did I hear someone say marriage?
- Well, where is she?
- This is she, Father.
She is lovely, son,
but you cannot marry just anyone.
That is, you are a prince.
You must marry a woman
of noble birth...
...a wise woman who can advise you
and enrich your life.
But, Father, she will be
all those things and more.
You don't understand, son.
The succession is only assured
if you marry someone of noble birth.
I cannot condone this marriage.
What is your wish, masteress?
Genie, I wish to be a princess.
Royalty, nobility, these are things
that come from within...
...not from without.
- I'm sorry, Aliyah-din, but our love...
- What did you call her?
- Aliyah-din.
- Can it be?
Aliyah-din was the very name
of the lost princess of Serandibe...
...who was promised to you at birth.
I don't know how it is possible...
...but your Aliyah-din
is that very princess.
By royal decree...
...let the marriage proceed at once!
Genie, for my final wish,
I wish for a huge wedding!
With an equally huge picnic-type
wedding feast, I hope.
Your command is my wish.
And fulfilling all your wishes
will be my life's joy.
Hey, hey, hey, Boo Boo!
You're a full-fledged genie!
- What are you gonna do now?
- That's easy, Yogi. How about...?
I just...
I just love a happy ending.
And, like, they lived happily ever after,
like all good stories end.
Boy, that was neat.
- Okay, story's over. Wedding time.
- Right.
But I could never get married
in this old thing.
Yucky! Good thing I let the royal
dressmaker in on our plans.
Like, my thoughts exactly.
- Your majesty?
- It's you.
- It's you, all right.
- Are you sure I'm really your type?
I don't want you to be sorry
that you married me.
You're smart, fun and a babe.
Exactly my type.
- Where is that assistant?
- Coming!
- Tell another story.
- Great idea.
I mean, great idea!
Well, like, we're stuck here anyway.
How about...?
Sorry.
Maybe something a little less romantic.
Like Sinbad the Sailor.
- He's lost his mind!
- He's crazy!
- Run! Flee!
- Get out of here!
Mutineers!
Run! I will get another crew.
Nothing will stop me
from finding my treasure!
Perhaps I should place an ad
in the personals.
Can't wait to start the vacation I won.
Better get on the right boat.
But which one is right?
Left, right.
This has gotta be it.
It's on the right.
Although it is kind of small.
Small?!
Did I hear small?
Who said that?
- The captain, you son of a camel!
- Captain?
Sinbad the Sailor reporting
for vacation, captain, sir.
You may set sail, ready!
Oh, welcome aboard.
Oh, did I forget to mention?
I'm not only the captain...
...I am the cruise director too.
You will have the vacation of your life...
...or your money back.
No napping on my cruise ship!
But...
You do not want to sleep
through the fun, do you?
Fun? What fun?
Whoever catches the biggest fish wins.
Why, it feels like you have got a big one!
Do not let it get away!
Wow! Heavy! I can taste it already!
Tender, flaky and no fishy taste, either.
Got him!
Gee, he got away.
I guess you win, captain. Captain?
Ruhk's egg. Precious gems.
Golden toothbrush.
When do we play our next game, captain?
Game?! Oh, yes.
Game, game, game, game.
I know. How about a scavenger hunt?
Scavenger hunt?
Oh, boy! Oh, boy! Oh, boy! Oh, boy!
An egg?
Boy, scavenger hunts sure send you
looking for weird stuff.
Not just any egg! A Ruhk's egg!
They are rare and real big!
A big egg.
Like I said, weird stuff.
Do not talk! Look!
Aye, aye, captain!
Thar she blows! I mean, egg ahoy!
I mean, I found it.
Land ho!
First one to the egg
gets to keep it!
That is my egg!
This'll be a snap.
This isn't much of a competition.
Come on!
Shoo! Scat! Go away!
Wow! It looked so tiny
in the little spyglass.
It's much bigger in person.
It's mine! All mine!
You sure you want to eat that
all by yourself?
- It is mine, mine, mine!
- Okay, but that's a lot of cholesterol...
...for a little guy like you.
I really didn't think he could
get it down all by himself.
Captain! Oh, captain!
There you are, captain.
Mine...
Tell that to her.
It's mine! Mine! Mine!
I must find some place to hide you.
Shove off! Shove off!
- Excuse me?
- I said...
...raise the anchor
and get us out of here!
Bye. Bon voyage! Thanks for the egg!
Captain, that birdie's back.
Birdie. Do not be ridiculous.
We are miles from land.
What birdie could...?
That birdie.
The Ruhk is raining rocks on us.
Yeah, fun, huh?
What a ride!
You sure run a great
vacation cruise.
Keep a lookout.
The next items on the scavenger hunt...
...are jewels from
the stream of precious gems.
Aye, aye, your captainship, sir.
Stream of precious gems, ho!
The stream of precious gems
is a roller coaster ride?!
I love rides.
- It's marvelous.
- Get back in line.
- Move out of my way!
Get this line moving!
Sir, I'm sorry, but your son
is too short to ride.
He's got to be as tall as the parrot.
Short?! I will show you short!
There. Now I am tall enough.
Please keep your hands and arms
inside the log.
Oh, yes. Yes, yes.
Anything you say, sir.
Our hands will be too busy grabbing
diamonds, rubies and emeralds...
...to stay inside.
Remember, whoever has
the most jewels at the end wins!
And I will keep them all.
Look, but do not touch!
Many braver than you have tried
to steal the treasure within.
But no one has succeeded yet.
Hang on! Sounds like a big waterfall
coming up.
I do not worry.
They always try to scare you
on these rides.
It will just be a teeny-weeny,
paltry little...
Yippee!
Grab everything!
- Captain.
- Do not bother me!
You should be grabbing jewels.
- But, captain.
- Do not "but, captain" me.
I said...
Wow! A beautiful recreation
of the legendary Davy Jones' locker.
And the even more legendary
jeweled football.
Say "cheesy."
Touchdown!
Mine! All mine!
Hello.
Gee, it looks like a pretty dull ride.
And way too short too.
The golden toothbrush.
Prized for a 24-carat gold handle...
...and its very stiff,
deep-massaging bristles.
Land ho!
How can you read that sign, captain?
- What sign?
- See? You're too close.
Now, isn't that better?
You have found the secret path
to the golden toothbrush!
Does this mean I don't get
to build a sandcastle?
Perhaps later.
Gee, that looks like fun.
Get me down this instant!
Smile.
Perhaps not this quickly.
Help again.
You have saved me again!
Now let us get after the toothbrush.
No smooch?
After we get the toothbrush.
There's the golden toothbrush.
- First one down gets it.
- Yes, indeed.
But it is a long way down.
And there does not appear
to be any way back up either.
Well, my friend,
it looks as if this time...
...you will win.
Gee, I hope I didn't get an unfair
advantage over the captain.
Sure is dark, drafty and foreboding
in here.
And wet too.
They think of everything
on these cruises.
"M. Cyclops, Esquire."
Wow! A Cyclops too.
This is gonna be great!
Yes?
Hello. You must be here to sell
gorilla-scout cookies.
I'll have several boxes of peanut butter
banana dreams.
- I love those.
- I love them too...
...but that's not why I'm here.
- Too bad.
- Well, what are you here for?
- To see the golden toothbrush.
Down the hall, third door on the left.
Tourists.
- Nice place.
- Thanks. I like it.
Wow! These bristles are stiff!
How much time does one need
to look at a toothbrush?
I'll give you 10 seconds
and not a moment longer.
Can't wait all day, I'm a busy Cyclops.
Are you done yet?
I say, I've got tickets to Cats.
They were hard to get.
You asked for it. I'm coming in.
Gone!
Two can play this little game...
...although some of us
are a little big for games.
I admire his commitment
to hygienic excellence...
...but I am not going to give up
without a fight.
After all, it is 24-carat gold,
and the bristles are very stiff...
...for deep cleaning and a satisfying
gum massage:
You come back here
with that toothbrush!
- I just need to borrow it.
- Borrow it?
That's disgusting!
Give it over and we'll call it square.
Drat!
Come on!
I know I'm going to miss
the opening song of Cats.
Penthouse, and step on it.
Go away! That is my banana!
- Thanks, captain, sir.
- Never mind the thanks.
Where is that toothbrush?
- Mine!
- Hey, what about me?
Get your own golden toothbrush.
Gotcha!
Mine, mine, mine.
See here, I'm going to get
awfully angry...
...if you don't come back
with that toothbrush.
You have no idea what happens to me
if I don't brush after every meal.
You'll have to come down eventually.
I've got all day.
I've already missed Cats...
...and I brought a good book
to read.
Look what you have done,
you big gorilla.
Now we are trapped!
Don't worry. I've got a plan.
- What time is it?
- Time for me to get a new gorilla.
I say.
Amazing how things happen
right on cue in a cartoon, isn't it?
The island, it is sinking!
Raise the sails. Raise the sails!
I guess it's time to say goodbye.
These cheap trinkets will bring back
great memories.
My... My jewels.
My toothbrush.
It's great the way you let
the passengers win.
I had a wonderful time...
...and I'm going to recommend you
to all my friends.
Nothing. I have nothing!
My boat, my jewels,
my toothbrush.
My Ruhk egg.
Wait one minute.
I still have my Ruhk egg.
I can sell it and not only recoup
all my losses...
...but have enough money to...
Mama. Mama.
Toodle-Ioo, Donna and Gordon.
I had a marvelous time.
Let's do this again next year.
My toothbrush!
Mine!
I have my toothbrush!
I'm oral-hygienically secure.
Protected from plaque,
cavity comfy, safe from morning breath.
Mama!
Mama.
- I'm not your mama.
- Mama!
I can't be your mama because...
Because she's your mama.
Gee, that was swell.
I am one lucky dude to get you.
- Oh, sire.
- Let's scram, Shaggy.
You're everything a guy could want
and modest too.
- The perfect companion for life.
- I can't go.
Didn't you hear? I'm perfect.
- Let the wedding begin.
- How can you have a wedding without...?
Without what?
Without... Without a wedding cake.
Did someone say cake?
Yummy. Looks tasty, huh?
Like, how can I tell until I taste it?
- Wow!
- Yummy!
- It's them!
- Them who?
The ex-royal food tasters.
Like, hide!
- What's the problem?
- There's the problem.
Great. Cake!
No, you fools! The ex-royal food tasters.
- Like, hi.
- Yeah, hi.
Zoinks!
Well, this cake is just perfect.
Like, let's proceed with the wedding.
Sire, you must send these fools
to their final reward at once.
Don't worry, Scoob.
At least our last meal was good.
Gee, I don't know.
They weren't bad food tasters.
- I didn't die of food poisoning.
- You didn't eat anything either.
Well, the stories were so neat
I forgot I was hungry.
Okay, your lives are spared...
...if you stay on as royal storytellers.
- Great.
- Not so fast, Scoob.
Like, maybe we could be
royal storytellers...
...and royal food tasters.
If you two are my food tasters, I may
never eat again, and I'm still growing.
Well, at least you'll never die
of food poisoning.
Hey, there's some risks you've
just gotta take.
Say, this isn't bad.
Scooby-Dooby-Doo.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
[ENGLISH]