Reporting to you live
from Lynwood County
where a chilling scene
has been discovered by police.
The bodies of four
family members were found
inside early this morning
in what police are describing
to be a brutal homicide.
We are collaborating
with various law
enforcement agencies
on a possible connection
to a previous set
of murders in Oakwood Glen.
Dozens of miniature
cameras were found
inside the property,
hidden in household objects
such as smoke detectors,
bookshelves
and light fixtures.
These killers are
broadcasting their crimes
as a live feed.
Viewers apparently had no idea
that what they were watching
was happening in real life.
I thought that it was fake.
You just don't expect
it to be real.
I kind of feel sick
to my stomach about it,
but it's still entertaining.
It appears that these victims
were given the opportunities
to defend themselves.
This played out like
some kind of deadly game.
The violence was
kind of overwhelming...
Gruesome and...
Graphic.
But it was okay in the moment
because it was
like a horror movie.
I was rooting for them.
I really didn't want
them to die.
The whereabouts of
a fifth family member
Marissa Vasquez
are unknown tonight
as authorities continue
to search for the young
woman missing
since the horrifying incident.
Our working theory is that
this feed is being transmitted
on a time delay.
FEMALE REPORTER: These killers
are treating their broadcasts
like a Hollywood horror movie,
designed with one
chilling purpose...
...to entertain.
The question that remains
is will these killers
strike again?
And if so...
MAN:
How will they select
their victims?
JAMIE: I keep having this...
This nightmare.
It starts the same
every night.
There's, um...
There's a storm outside.
It's thunder and
lightning and...
I feel like I'm not alone.
Like someone's watching me.
MAN: Someone is watching you?
Who's watching you?
JAMIE: Her.
MAN: Your mother?
JAMIE: Well,
at first I just...
I feel her presence.
But when the lightning
flashes, I can see her.
She's laying on
the kitchen table.
And she's got
a shroud over her.
MAN: So what's happening
in Jamie's world?
JAMIE: And I can see
all these bugs,
these spiders and cockroaches,
and they're just...
I'm fine.
They're just eating
away at her.
MAN: Are you feeling scared?
No.
MAN: Those are
very scary images.
It's okay to be scared.
It's perfectly normal
to be scared.
Yeah.
MAN: Sometimes letting
yourself be vulnerable
makes you stronger.
So do you think your father
has dealt with his grief well?
JAMIE: No.
He came home one day
with this new girlfriend.
MAN: You must resent
him for that.
JAMIE: I don't resent him.
I resent her.
MAN: That's your
stepmother, Olivia.
How do you feel about Olivia?
JAMIE: She's so different
from my mom.
I barely survived the first
six months of their marriage.
Now, I gotta be stuck with her
on a whole ten-day vacation.
DJ: I told you, you should
have peed at the airport.
ADAM: I understand that.
It's not gonna be a problem.
I'm gonna take care of it.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Is there some maid you hired
I'm unaware of?
Coat on the rack,
suitcase out of the way.
Come on.
Wait, wait, wait. Steve.
JAMIE: Dad!
Let me explain.
JAMIE: You're shouting.
I'm gonna get you the money.
You have my word.
The deposit should go
through any day now.
It's not like I'm trying
to fuck you over!
I'm not trying to give you
the runaround.
Look, I'm gonna work
something out here.
OLIVIA: DJ, no food!
It's almost 11:00.
I know you can hear me.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Look, you don't have
to threaten me.
Expect a check tomorrow
afternoon. Two days at most.
Okay, fine.
Is it a healthy
snack at least?
It's gluten-free.
Really?
Hey. What?
How do you eat this?
It's delicious.
OLIVIA: Ugh!
Something smells good.
You guys have a snack
without me?
JAMIE: Uh, what happened to
the wallpaper in my room?
ADAM: Just feeling it out.
We were gonna run it by you.
Um, but you didn't.
And you just went
into my room?
ADAM: Look, I really think
you're going to like it.
OLIVIA: Look,
I understand you're mad.
Of course, we were
gonna tell you first.
We just thought that we'd
find something that you liked.
JAMIE: Funny, because
I don't remember anybody
ever having a problem
with my wallpaper before.
Right, DJ?
Yeah. Totally.
I mean,
actually, that wallpaper
is kind of creepy.
Okay.
This is really uncool.
Jamie...
You told me you were
gonna ask her before
we tested the paint.
ADAM: I was going to,
and then I remembered
how she reacted
when I asked if
I could throw out her
Harry Styles posters.
OLIVIA: This is not
helping here.
I mean,
how'd she even see it?
Hey, Josh, it's me.
I've left you like
a thousand messages
so just call me back
when you get this.
DJ!
What?
My charger,
why did you take it?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I have my own charger.
JAMIE: I don't
believe you.
Fine.
JAMIE: Wait!
So, you're not
screwing with me?
No. I'm being totally normal.
You should try it sometime.
JAMIE: Wait, Deej, wait.
I'm sorry.
Whatever.
Hey. Come on.
It's just you and me, right?
DJ: Sure.
OLIVIA: DJ,
take out the trash!
OLIVIA: Oh, my, God! Sorry.
I'm sorry.
JAMIE: Hey! Get out!
OLIVIA: Sorry.
JAMIE: Get out of here!
Cool.
You're gonna die!
Matt!
I'm sorry, dude.
You definitely frightened...
MATT: Uh, so, that
was too easy.
You were just like
a sitting duck, man.
How you doing?
DJ: I'm all right.
You survive Florida, my man?
Yeah. It was pretty boring.
Hot as hell.
I went to the beach,
went to dinner.
I'd rather be playing
Xbox, but...
Oh. It's on already?
Hell, yeah.
Okay, I'm getting my revenge.
DJ: Let's do this.
MATT: No, you can't
push it like that.
That is against the rules.
You can't do that, no!
You can't score.
DJ, I'm gonna kick your...
Hey, bro.
You staying a while?
I don't... Um...
Yeah, this...
It's kind of a long story.
Matt? It's 11:30 at night.
Wait, why didn't
you just call us at least?
I was going to call,
but Sheryl kind of
accidentally deliberately
threw my cell phone
in the toilet.
But he's gonna be out
of here in three days.
Tops. Three days tops.
Hi, Liv. How are you?
I'm good, thanks.
Thanks for asking.
OLIVIA: How you doing?
Oh, my God.
No way. You're too hot
for this guy.
This is stupid.
This just doesn't even work.
We got some pizza
in the freezer.
The two of you.
Go get some food.
Oh. Okay.
I'll set you up in the room.
Mmm.
JAMIE: Coming!
Yeah.
Hey, Killer. Hi.
Oh. Hey, there.
Now's not actually
a good time to talk.
MATT: No, no, no. No, no.
You're not getting
off that easy.
You gotta give me something.
Come on, it's me.
Catch me up.
I wanna know about
your life. Go.
Um...
Olivia's trying to
destroy my life.
Okay, first of all,
refined sugars,
that's what's
destroying your life.
Second of all,
Olivia is not scary at all.
If anything,
she's terrified of you.
Why would she be afraid of me?
'Cause you're a teenage girl.
Teenage girls are terrifying.
One look from a teenage girl
will send most men off...
You just did it.
You did the teenage girl look.
I'm terrified right now.
You see?
I just feel like...
Like I don't have a say
in anything, you know?
And it stresses me out.
MATT: It's good not to
have a say in things.
You just gotta chill.
Believe me, I know.
That's why I self-medicate.
Really?
It's for my glaucoma.
You know that.
All right, good talk, son.
You gotta get out
of this funk.
Come here.
JAMIE: Okay.
MATT: Do your homework
and eat more vegetables.
And, uh, drink
more water and exercise.
That's what
your Uncle Matt says.
It's really good.
He's my brother.
What am I supposed to do?
OLIVIA: You tuck him in.
ADAM: Hey, guys.
Look at the camera.
Look up at the
camera and smile.
JAMIE: What the...
ADAM: What do you think?
Is that a butterfly?
YOUNG JAMIE: A butterfly!
ADAM: A butterfly?
Did Mommy make
a big butterfly, too?
Great job too, Mommy.
Hey, I got your texts.
All 20,000 of them.
I was worried that on your way
home from the airport
you got trapped
under a burning car.
Can I ask you a question?
Yeah, go for it.
Do you see us
staying together?
I mean, like,
past senior year.
Whoa. Yeah.
I mean, I think so. Do you?
Yeah.
Babe, what's going on?
Nothing. I don't want
to talk about it.
Talk about what?
Babe, what's going on?
Do you think
even when people die
they could still judge you
for your mistakes?
Baby, are you talking
about your mom?
It's been six years.
All right? What would
she judge you for?
I gotta go.
Come on, I miss you,
and you're freaking me out.
Talk to me. Like,
did I do something?
Did I screw up?
Say something wrong?
No. No, it's not you.
I just...
Yeah, I gotta go.
Jame.
Does she know
I'm 35 grand deep?
No, I'd be a dead man.
Thirty five grand?
Look, don't...
Jesus, even the rich are poor.
Here, man, it sounds like
you need this more than I do.
Oh.
Oh, God, it's like
we're back in senior year.
Where'd you get
this shit anyway?
Same guy we got it
from in senior year.
No.
No, I'm not kidding, man.
Dirk, he's a lifer.
No.
All right, I'm going to arrive
around the corner. Watch out.
There's a guy right there.
What the hell?
Okay, sorry, I'm back, guys.
Oh, come on. That's bull crap.
Hey, Jame?
Yeah?
Just wanted to see
if you're okay.
Yeah, I'm okay.
Listen, I...
We shouldn't have
gone in your room
without your permission.
It was stupid of me.
I know this transition's
been rough.
And the last thing
you need is someone
invading your privacy.
All right. Good night.
JAMIE: Night, Dad.
Hey.
Five more minutes,
then the game goes off
and the teeth get brushed.
DJ: Can it be ten?
ADAM: Five.
Shit.
Maybe I've been trying
to change too much.
I'm just afraid I'm never
gonna connect with her.
Stop it.
You're just feeling
each other out.
Besides, you got lucky.
You missed the zombie years.
The piss, the shit,
the puke.
You took a shortcut to
the best parts of motherhood.
No.
What the fuck?
Jesus!
What?
DJ?
MAN:
It's started.
Two to three minutes.
Yeah, okay.
I'm in here!
Hello?
Did you hear that?
I got it.
DJ: What's going on?
OLIVIA: Don't know,
I heard something.
DJ: Okay.
JAMIE: What's going on?
ADAM: Matt,
is that you?
JAMIE: What was that sound?
Matty?
Matt?
Call the police.
Okay.
JAMIE: Dad,
what was down there?
What did you see?
What are you getting?
It's okay.
Just hang back, guys, okay?
The phones are gone.
Okay, get back in the bedroom
and lock the door. Now.
Okay. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Jamie! Jamie, come on!
Stay up here.
Listen to what your dad said.
Hello?
Matty?
Matty, if this is you,
it's not funny.
Shit.
Oh, shit.
Jesus Christ!
What the fuck?
Dad! Please
come back upstairs.
Jamie, go back upstairs.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Dad, please. Please,
come back upstairs.
ADAM: It's okay, sweetie.
Get back up there.
OLIVIA: I can't see anything.
DJ: What's going on
down there?
JAMIE: Dad...
Dad! Dad!
Adam! No!
Get off of him!
Get off of him, please!
JAMIE: Dad!
OLIVIA: Jamie, get back here!
Dad!
Come on, go, go, go!
JAMIE: We have to help him!
No, we have to help him!
OLIVIA: Jamie,
just come with us!
DJ: This way, we gotta go!
OLIVIA: Get in!
What do we do?
Lock the door. Look the door.
Help me. Come on.
Is it okay?
Oh, shit.
No! Hold it!
No!
Is he gone?
Oh, my God.
DJ: Jamie.
OLIVIA: Check under the bed!
DJ: Jamie, I'm scared.
It's gonna be okay.
No, no, I'm just scared.
OLIVIA: Where are the phones?
JAMIE: What are you doing?
OLIVIA: Where the hell
are the phones?
JAMIE: We have to help him!
We wait for the...
The phones were right here.
Where are the phones?
We gotta go downstairs,
and we have to help him!
There's somebody downstairs.
Our only priority right now
is to get out of this house.
Do you understand?
JAMIE: How are we
gonna do that?
Check the windows. See if we
can get out through that side.
We can't jump.
It's way too high.
What is that
Back away. Back, back, back.
We have to get out of here.
BOTH: Help! Help us!
Help!
Help us! Somebody help!
DJ: What is it?
Nothing, nothing.
What
Get back, get back, get back!
Oh, my God.
JAMIE: What's that?
What is that?
What is happening?
You don't understand.
It's ridiculous. It's like...
Jamie
She treats me like a child,
but yet she's closer to my age
than to my dad's.
I don't know.
She's a total gold digger.
They were watching me...
And the grossest part is,
I think my little brother
has a crush on her.
What the hell is this?
I don't know. I don't know.
You know, my dad acts like
I'm the one with the problem.
But really, he's the one
in total denial.
What is this?
He's the one that's
responsible for all this.
Is this a prank between
you and your friends?
This isn't funny, Jamie!
No, I don't know
how they got these!
How'd it get on the screen?
I don't know. He's filming me!
Sometimes...
Sometimes, I wish it was him.
Oh!
Oh, no!
It's okay.
Oh, my God.
No!
Turn it off.
It's okay. It's okay.
Turn it off! Turn it off!
Who's doing this?
JAMIE: I don't know!
DJ: Jamie, I'm scared.
Okay. Okay, look...
All right. All right,
we just stay calm.
We're gonna get
out of this house.
Okay? Just help me look
for something sharp.
Something we can
protect ourselves with.
JAMIE: There's nothing here.
I can't find anything.
OLIVIA: Come on, keep looking.
DJ: I found something.
That's good.
Just hold on to it, okay?
Come on, Jamie, here.
We'll just take
the glass, okay?
All right, listen. Come here.
Listen to me.
We're gonna walk out
of that door right now. Okay?
Just stay together.
DJ: Are you sure?
Everyone's gonna be fine,
I promise.
Just stay together, okay?
You know what,
it's gonna be fine.
It's gonna be fine. Come on.
Come on.
Help me.
Stay together.
Yeah.
OLIVIA:
Nobody's here. It's just us.
What do we do?
I don't know.
Come on, stay together.
Come on.
I hear something.
Was that you?
JAMIE: My God. What is that?
DJ: What's what?
JAMIE: I hear something.
OLIVIA: It's okay.
Keep calm.
Do you hear that?
What is that?
I hear something.
OLIVIA: Just stay together.
What?
Someone is watching us.
My cell phone.
Wait, wait, wait!
Where is it? Shit.
Okay.
Jamie
What is that?
Where is it?
No, no, don't touch that!
Don't touch that.
Olivia, someone's
planning this.
"Kill or be killed."
They want us to fight back.
OLIVIA: Careful!
It works!
What do we do?
Oh...
OLIVIA: Oh, my God!
Just stay close, all right?
DJ: What is that?
It smells like gas.
Where's Jamie?
DJ: Jamie.
Jamie, come here.
Come on. Get down, dude.
Get down.
Run. Run!
OLIVIA: Adam!
JAMIE: Dad!
DJ: Go! Go! Go!
OLIVIA: We can't get out!
We're trapped!
DJ: He's here. Run!
Go! Run!
No! No, back up!
JAMIE: Olivia!
Stay back! Get back
in the basement! Get back!
Olivia, come on,
hurry! Olivia!
Stay back!
OLIVIA: Shit, shit, shit...
Okay, let me look.
JAMIE: Oh, my God, somebody...
OLIVIA: We need to
get out of here.
JAMIE: Somebody
could be in here.
No! No!
It's locked!
We have to try and find
a way out of here.
The windows!
Okay. Okay. Okay.
No...
Oh, my God.
What are we gonna do?
Find something
to pry it open with.
OLIVIA: What
"What would she do?"
OLIVIA: Was
that your mother's?
Help me!
Damn it!
OLIVIA: It's okay. It's okay.
Hey, guys?
Do you guys hear that?
Guys, guys, do you hear that?
It's okay.
It's the police!
It's the police, guys!
What?
DJ: Hey!
Help us!
We're in the basement!
Down here! We're here!
DJ: Hey!
Downstairs in the basement!
This is the police.
We've received reports
of a disturbance...
ALL: We're down here!
We're down here!
Downstairs!
We're downstairs!
Wait.
Help us!
(INDISTINCT POLICE
CHATTER OVER RADIO)
I hear them.
DJ: Hey!
Hello! We're down here!
Help us!
We're in the basement!
OLIVIA: Down here!
Help! Help!
OFFICER: This is the police.
We've received reports
of a disturbance,
and we're searching the home.
This is the police.
We've received reports
of a disturbance,
and we're searching the home.
I don't understand.
This is the police.
We've received reports
of a disturbance...
This is the police.
We've received reports
of a disturbance...
This is the police.
We've received reports
of a disturbance...
and we're searching the home.
What is it?
Speakers.
They're screwing with us.
They wanted us
in the basement.
We're all gonna die.
Okay, listen to me,
all right?
I need you to be strong
for me. Can you do that?
Can you be strong for your
brother and for me?
DJ: Hey, guys?
I found this on the driveway.
It... it had a bow on it, too.
DJ: Did you guys hear that?
OLIVIA: What is it?
DJ: It's coming
from over here.
Oh, my God. Josh.
Go get him.
Josh.
Josh! Josh...
JAMIE:  Josh!
Hello!
JAMIE: Where's he going?
OLIVIA: Jamie.
JAMIE: Josh!
Jamie, you okay?
Jamie...
Josh, go around!
Hey, are you...
Jamie, you down there?
JAMIE: I'm here!
Jamie, what's happening?
Jamie! Jamie!
JAMIE: Josh, keep coming!
Trying to get this
stupid door open.
Are you all right?
Let's go, come on!
Josh, look behind you!
Why won't this stupid
door open? Jamie!
No!
No, Josh!
Josh!
Why are you doing this?
God damn you!
Leave us alone!
Help! Help us!
Why? Why...
Guys, there's another window.
There's another window.
Guys! Guys!
All right. All right. Come on.
Come on.
Olivia!
Wait.
It's okay.
JAMIE: Olivia, where
are you going?
Okay, listen to me.
All right. I want you
to be strong for me.
We locked ourselves in here.
They can't get in here, okay?
I'm gonna go outside
and find some help.
It's gonna be fine. It's safe.
Just wait here.
I promise, I'll come back.
Okay? I'll come back.
Olivia!
I'll come back
for you both.
I promise.
Are we gonna die?
I don't know.
Oh, my God, you're alive.
We have to...
Okay, wait, wait. Oh, God.
Get out of here.
OLIVIA: Come on.
Hurry. Hurry. Pry it off.
Run! Run!
Run! Get out!
OLIVIA: Wait! Help!
Help!
MAN: Come around back.
Hello?
Don't worry.
She made it out.
I know she did.
DJ, you can still go
to the bathroom.
Don't worry.
I'll keep a close watch.
Just go use the sink.
Okay.
DJ: Jamie?
Jamie.
Jamie,
the door's locked.
I can't get out.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Jamie!
I can't open the door.
What's happening?
Jamie! Jamie! Help!
Shit.
Who are you?
JAMIE: Fuck.
DJ: You okay?
Okay. Come on.
Jamie. Your arm.
Come here.
JAMIE: What is that?
JAMIE:
I keep having this nightmare.
It starts the same
every night.
There's a storm outside.
It's thunder and
lightning and...
Stay here.
Then I get this feeling...
That someone's watching me.
When the lightning flashes,
I can see her.
She's laying on
the kitchen table...
And she's got
a shroud over her...
And I can see all these bugs,
these spiders and cockroaches,
and they're just...
Eating away at her.
What is it?
Olivia. No.
Nothing.
It's just a mannequin.
They're just trying
to scare us.
It's my nightmare.
DJ, run!
Come on! Let's go.
It's okay. Don't look.
Come on, go.
Is he going to find us?
Yes.
Stay here.
Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
MAN:
Because it's fun for them.
Fun for who?
The people watching.
Just tell me what you want.
To cut you open
and see what's inside you.
We've been watching
you a long time.
We know your darkest
thoughts, Jamie.
We see the anger
you hold back.
For your mother. Your father.
You used that to stay alive.
And now we all want to see
how far that will take you.
There's a shock value to that
that's endlessly entertaining.
I couldn't help it.
I had to know how it ended.
Use this gift, Jamie.
The only way you're going
to survive is if you become
the darkness inside you.
Please, whoever's
watching this,
please help us!
We live at 2-1...
...Lane.
Remember when you asked me
if we were gonna die?
And I said I didn't know.
Yeah.
I do know.
The only other person who's
gonna die here tonight...
Is him.
Listen to me.
No, Jamie.
DJ, you have to trust me.
No.
It's okay. So this
is what we're gonna do.
Get the fuck out of our house.
DJ, now!
Come on, go on!
DJ!
JAMIE: Get off of me!
DJ: Jamie!
Get off of her!
Jamie!
Jamie! No!
Burn in hell, fucker!
Okay, DJ, help me. Come on!
Come on! DJ, let's go!
DJ: Come on, Jamie, come on.
We're almost there.
I can't keep going.
I don't think anyone's coming.
It's okay. Come on.
I can't do it.
All right, come on.
Come on, Jamie.
Hey! Hey!
Stop!
Come on. Hey!
Come here! No! Stop!
Please!
Get off!
DJ, look out!
No, please! Jamie!
DJ! DJ, are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Leave us alone!
Why are you doing this to us?
Why are you doing this to me?
MAN:
The rules have always
been very simple.
What is this?
MAN:
Kill or be killed.
It's your turn now, Jamie.
We're not going
to hurt your brother...
As long as you do exactly
what I tell you.
Don't listen to him, Jamie.
You will provide
the excitement
for our next family, Jamie.
You will give the audience
the reason...
...to keep watching.