Maybe I’ve never felt like this
So I just don’t understand
Maybe I’m not what you think I am
Nobody knew how to hold me
Without room for secrets to breathe
Only to pull me in tighter
So I couldn't see
Now I’m wondering I’m thinking
It’s something like a disarray
And the memories streaming
down my face
Cuz I was strewn across
your living room
But you never did
know what to do
about me and you
With all the sorry’s inside me
I just can’t muster one up
A tragic misunderstanding of love
I try so hard to be happy
Try not to ride that train
But when it finally happens
I run away
Now I’m wondering I’m thinking
It’s something like a disarray
And the memories streaming
down my face
Cuz I was strewn across
your living room
But you never did
know what to do
about me and you
Hello, Miss Winston
My usual, please. -- black
So sorry to hear about Amy.
She was your best friend, wasn't she?
Yes.
My mother says
losing your best friend
can be as hard
as losing your husband.
Have you ever been married?
Why do you ask?
My mother told me that when someone
asks you that question you just say
"why do you ask?"
-- stops me in the tracks
Lola, if you don't learn the
-- rules
then everything you write will give evidence
of a compromised education.
It will scream out
"I have no interest in excellence",
"I'm not smart",
"I'm average",
"I don't deserve a good grade
or a good job"
Now, do you want your writing
to ruin all your chances for success?
Let's go over this
one more time.
Sarah,
I've been meaning
to call you.
Lola has decided that she'd
like to try another tutor.
You understand,
sometimes our pairings are a mismatch.
Lola is lazy.
Lola wants someone
who won't challenge her,
she wants someone
who won't expect anything from her.
We just think another personality
might work better with her.
Excuse me.
Please, I'd like to have the bike
It's 50 dollars.
I told you we can't afford it.
But you promised.
I know.
We can't afford it.
Please.
Excuse me.
--
Don’t underestimate me
And tell me to behave
You got it easy baby
Don’t say "I feel the same"
You warned me to be careful
Be smart enough to wait
It’s more than I can handle
I’d like to set things straight
You called it right,
I’m in the wrong
I should be shot for thinking
I could understand
You called it right,
You knew all along
I would be shocked
I had to shake the underhand
You keep believing in the one thing
I’ll keep believing in the other
You called it right
Don’t say I’m going crazy
See I just forget my place
It’s not the fool you make me
This one seems real friendly.
- Is he house-broken?
- Absolutely.
Bless you.
Shakespeare.
House-broken?
Somebody who never speaks.
I will see you later, okay?
- Bye.
- See you.
You look so hard
For something real
But I can't hurt
And you can't feel
So run alone,
run alone, run alone
On your feet
You kick my knees
Leave me here
On your empty street
Run alone,
run alone, run alone
'Cause you're gone without a trace
leave those lies
to lay across my face
I was here
waiting for your call
Just to hear
you say nothing at all
But you're no fake,
my sweet mistake
It's a sad,
sad world you're living in
Where no one breaths
under their skin
But you pretend,
you pretend, hey yeah
That your gone
Without a trace
Leave those lies
to lay across my face
I was here
waiting for your call
Just to hear
you say nothing at all
But you're no fake,
my sweet mistake
Anything specific
bothering you today?
Yes.
One of my friends
died of cancer recently.
Another just had a heart attack.
So yes, that bothers me a lot.
--
I'm in a blue petal sky of roses, daisies...
spinning inside my mind
and as I float through the mist,
the world below me
seems so far behind.
like I can fly fly fly
nothing seems to matter
now that you're here beside me.
fly fly fly
When I'm here with you I feel alive.
And all the cars swirling by
in motion seem like
they could be paralyzed
and the light
inside me feels so bright
it's hard for me to deny
like I can fly fly fly
nothing seems to matter,
now that you're here beside me.
Do you know where the group meets?
I think it might be a Bible study group.
Sorry?
Do you know where the meeting is?
Oh, yes. I'm going myself.
Come with me.
You can just put your umbrella
right there.
Okay, come.
…that God could and would
if He was sought.
Anyone feel like sharing?
I'm Hank and I'm an alcoholic.
Come on.
As most of you know
I had my first drink when I was 13.
And ever since that time
I've liked the way alcohol
makes me feel: numb.
And I wish I was numb today.
My ex-wife is getting remarried.
I never saw that coming.
And as crazy as it sounds
and as much as we fought
I always thought
we'd get back together.
But thanks to Leo, my sponsor,
I made it through another day.
I called about 13 times
but he picked up every time.
He was a minister
before he retired.
He's a good man
and he was there for me.
So thank you, Leo.
'Cause I know
I was --.
So, you come in.
You're new,
aren't you?
I see you're feeling
exactly the way I did my first time.
But let assure
you will not regret.
- Name is Kit.
- Sarah.
Nice to meet you.
Wait!
I really didn't get the chance
to introduce myself.
I'm Darla.
This is Sarah.
It's her first time.
I could tell.
Do you have a sponsor here tonight?
A sponsor?
No, I don't.
Do you ever think of changing
your hairstyle?
Why do you ask?
Cause I think you would look
so much younger
with your hair loose
around your face.
--
makes you look 10 years older
than you really are.
I have to be going.
Listen.
I know I'm just a kid
but I've been in the program a while now
and I can help you.
Good night.
See you later, then.
And remember,
keep coming back!
Who is there?
It's Kit.
Our meeting is about to start.
I'm not going.
Yes, you are.
I won't take "no"
for an answer.
It's really not a good time.
It's never a good time
but you've got to do it.
Come on, let's go.
You don't understand.
I had a buddy who dragged me
to my first committees
and I wanna do
the same thing for you.
I'm not going.
I'm absolutely not going.
It's a misunderstanding.
We try to carry this message
to alcoholics
and to practice these principles
in all our affairs.
I lost my job,
my marriage, my kids
and my self-respect.
The only thing I gained was weight.
About 45 pounds.
A bunch of us
are going out to eat afterwards.
Do you wanna join us?
She'd love to.
So, how long have you been sober?
It's hard to say.
Do you know what,
that's okay.
Even if it's a day or two.
It takes progress.
Listen to her,
the expert.
I'm the one who
should be giving you advice.
- Because?
- Because I've done this 5 times.
Oh, that's great.
Hank, you're discouraging her.
It doesn't take 5 times.
- Isn't that right, dad?
- It's right.
- Dad?
- Yeah.
These meetings are quality time,
together.
My advice is:
take things at your own pace
and don't let anybody
pressure you.
You missed one.
-- time Kit was snorting
I came down pretty hard on him.
Those were bad times.
He looked at me like I was evil.
Sarah, I've no right to criticize him
after what I've put him through.
He was right.
Eventually I got through to him,
he got through to me
and we helped each other out.
We've been cleaning out
for two years.
And what about his mother?
She hasn't been in the picture
since he was 2.
- Thanks for walking me home.
- My pleasure.
Do you want me to come
and get you tomorrow?
That would be nice.
Okay, then.
Bye.
Put your head on my shoulder
lean a little longer
and breathe.
…to realize that my kid
is embarrassed of me.
Last week I was talking
to my ex-wife.
She told me about
a school play that he was in.
He looked to me and said:
"Dad, don't come"
"You'd have to take time off work
and it'd be too much trouble".
He was pretending to be thinking
about me but I could tell.
I could see it in his eyes.
He didn't want me there.
He knew that he'd be embarrassed
by his old man. Again.
Anyway, I guess all I can do
is keep following steps right
and keep trying.
And that's it.
- Why don't you go out?
- No.
Anyone else?
Charlie,
would you and Kit like to come
to my place for dinner tomorrow?
We'd love to.
So, what you have in mind?
Remember what you said
about my hair?
I sure do.
Would you mind if I --
It won't hurt, I promise.
You shine in my eyes
Frozen still, open wide
Come down, fill my heart
With a fire you flaunt
And I can't say a word
They would only sound absurd
Maybe you're my shooting star
Blindly falling through the dark
Burning a hole in my sky
so fierce, so bright
Maybe it's all I need,
so baby come shoot through me
Wishes won't survive on you tonight
If you stay for good
On the ground, I think you could
It's not a life that you lead
Just a path following
cause everybody else
has you aiming at yourself
- So?
- Thank you.
- You look great.
- Where is Kit?
- He couldn't make it.
- Go ahead.
- All right.
This is truly heaven.
I can't remember the last time
I had a civilized meal.
What do you mean?
I mean I don't eat like this often.
Candles and cloth-napkins...
For example, there was a time
when I used to make
a pretty good jelly from scratch.
It was an all-day affair
but then, after a while I thought:
"this is too much trouble,
I just gonna get can jelly"
And shortly after that I thought:
"heating it up is so much work".
And then I reasoned:
"if I'm not gonna heat it up
why not just eat the jelly
out of the can?"
You wouldn't eat cold jelly
out of the can.
I would and I do,
regularly.
And I think,
I'm pretty sure
if I could figure a way
to eat that jelly
without opening the can
I would do that too.
I think you'd better go now.
Why?
What's the matter?
Nothing is the matter.
It's just late.
Sure.
- It's me.
- Hi.
I couldn't bear
to have my normal breakfast this morning
It would have been an insult
to my taste buds after last night.
- What's your normal breakfast?
- Don't ask.
So how are you doing?
I'm fine. Why?
No, I mean with the "eternal struggle".
You mean the drinking?
I'm okay.
Because you really haven't indicated
where you're at.
I'm sort of about the beginning.
What about you?
Three-year anniversary --
My previous record
is two.
You know, it's funny because before
all I could think about was drinking
and now all I can think about
is not drinking.
So let me see
if I got this straight.
You prefer not to talk
about your past relationships,
you prefer not to talk
about your family
and you prefer not to talk
about where you are in the steps.
- I'm a brilliant conversationalist.
- You're a challenge.
- How about football?
- No.
Baseball?
I don't --
- Movies?
- I used to go. All the time.
That's something.
I like ping-pong.
I won a little tournament once.
So you're a ping-pong champion,
aren't you?
I -- in about 25 years
But now I've someone to work with.
I love that --.
Wouldn't you love
to fall into that every night?
Aren't you and I planning
on doing that some time?
So movies, ping-pong
and big, fancy beds with fluffy pillows.
I think we're making progress.
Sorry.
- That was fun.
- It was.
Listen, I hope that you didn't get
the wrong impression.
I think I've got the right impression.
Which is?
That you're -- in my hands.
But don't worry,
I assure I intend to exercise my
power over you with extreme responsibility.
Good-bye, Charlie.
I'll see you at the next meeting.
I finally realized that
drugs --
ruining my future,
turning off my old friends.
And quite frankly,
I've become really disgusted with myself.
I've become so self-centered.
I don't want to be like that anymore.
I want to be more like you, guys.
I wanted to help people.
So, that's what I did.
Thank you for helping me
get better.
One other thing:
my band is  --
Just kidding.
The music is free.
Anyone else?
You don't sew, do you?
You have missing a button.
I'm sure I have many buttons missing.
Do you work
or are just -- wealthy?
I work.
I just have a lot of time off.
What do you do?
I'd rather not say.
What, I can't have my privacy?
You are like a hit-man or something?
I edit books.
I've taught English
at a girls private Highschool for 12 years.
Then a friend of mine in publishing
asked if I'd be interested in editing manuscripts.
It sounded interesting.
I do it from home.
It suits me.
Any good books coming out?
I never read the books anyway.
Why not?
Well, I start with
the last sentence on the last page
and then I work backwards.
That way I can just focus
on the punctuation
and the spelling, the grammar,
not get distracted by the story.
- What?
- Nothing.
Hi, everyone.
We're gonna start -- now.
I hope you enjoy it.
No, I've never been married.
What?
You asked me before
if I'd ever been married
and I was very rude
not to have answered you.
of just being kind to me
after my friend Amy died.
No, it was stupid of me.
No, I was being stupid.
Sorry.
On the house.
Thank you.
I'm not exactly
the tie housekeeper.
No. Indeed.
Kit says it's like a work of art.
Expresses my eccentricities.
It certainly expresses something.
picture frames could
serve to a purpose.
I always thought they were
just for displaying art.
--
No, never.
why burden county's land fields
when I can just go ahead and get my own.
Very thoughtful.
Have a seat.
Anywhere.
Make yourself at home.
I'll go get you something to eat.
Just kidding.
Come on.
Voilà.
Good? Yes?
Salt? Pepper?
No. Perfect.
Charlie.
Where is he?
- How is he?
- Not good.
He's really drunk.
Threatened me to kill himself.
I've tried every --
to get through and nothing worked.
- Okay, just wait here.
- No, I'll go with you.
Stop right there.
Don't try to make me change my mind, Charlie.
Okay.
Just take it easy.
Why? I have nothing to live for.
You've got your son.
He don't need me.
He don't even want me.
better off without me
and you know it.
Hank, you love your son, don't you?
And how do you think he's gonna feel
when he has to explain to people
that his father took a gun
and blew his brains out?
Thank you for today.
We need to talk.
This is really embarrassing.
You know how hard it is
for me to open up.
- I'm strange.
- You are.
I don't mean about opening up.
I'm not strange in that way.
What are you trying to say?
I'm trying to say that I'm not going
to have sex outside the marriage.
I came to this conclusion
because
I've been through
a lot of heartache and pain in the past
and I can't go through that again.
I can't.
I promised myself I wouldn't.
I swore that the next time
I had sex with someone
we would be married.
You're kidding, right?
Okay.
Marriage would just be a --
for what is going on here.
You know that, right?
And your problem is that you are deeply
afraid about opening up to someone.
I don't really need you
to psychoanalyze me.
You have to get over this.
I don't wanna get over this.
I'm completely pathless.
I wouldn't blame you
if you didn't wanna see me again.
This is a big problem,
I know that.
Isn't it?
What do you think?
We're gonna have to get married.
It's not funny.
Let's just call tonight.
Hello.
Listen, I think we better
cool it for a while.
Because I don't wanna pressure you
into doing anything
you're uncomfortable with.
Okay.
See you.
Charlie.
These are for you.
Thank you.
Listen, I've been thinking.
It's not such a bad idea.
What?
You and me getting married.
Please, don't make fun of me.
I'm not. Look.
We go to Babys,
we get
and when you think
we -- its course we get a quick divorce.
A what?
Sarah, it's obvious
that you desperately need it.
You just have that mental blocks.
We need to find a way around that.
I've got nothing,
you've got nothing,
There's no need for a prenup.
Seriously, sooner or later
and I really hope it's sooner
I'm gonna have my way with you.
Can you think of a better solution?
That was the worse proposal
I've ever heard in my life.
I'm sorry you're so upset.
I'm not clear
on one thing though.
What exactly
are you so upset about?
You don't know
what I'm so upset about?
You can't figure it out?
Do you think it's been my life's dream
to be married by an Elvis impersonator
in some wedding chapel
filled with slot machines?
Or to plan my divorce
before the marriage has even begun?
Is that my life's dream?
Let alone getting married
to someone without feeling that --
You know what?
I have a good life. I do.
I have my work
I have my piece of mind
and I have a manuscript to edit.
Good bye.
Sarah!
Sarah, it's me, Charlie.
Come on, open up.
I thought about what you said,
I feel like an ass. Come on!
If I cause Sarah to start drinking again
I'll never forgive myself.
Since when you care
about the women you --
Sarah!
I own all the units and rent them out
so yes, I do know Sarah.
This is Memorial Hospital.
We have Sarah Winston here
and I'm trying to locate
family members.
Please, call us
if you receive this message.
Sarah.
Hi, there.
I'm fine.
Well, maybe you are but I'm not.
Whatever are you doing here?
What do you mean
what I'm doing here?
I'm taking care of you.
I'd be really angry if I died before
I had the chance to ask you something.
What?
Why you don't eat the tomato?
It says in case of emergency
I should call her sister.
I guess I should do that.
- Dad,
- What?
What's happening to you?
I don't know.
That's very sweet.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hi, Tony.
-- those cartoons?
I go in about once every other month.
-- and I also do commercials for the -- products.
Why -- tell me about it?
Because when people find out
what I do for a living
it generally changes their opinion of me.
Which is?
They start looking at me as the edgy
kind-of-guy that I am
As a tomato, yes.
I'm glad you're here.
Heading in there right now.
Where is it again?
Back left corner, bedside table.
Hang on a second.
We got it.
Yeah, this is it.
I will bring it with me when I come.
We'll see then.
- What are you gonna do?
- Nothing
Aren't you gonna call her on it?
Wouldn't do any good.
Dad, we should throw all that away.
She's gonna do that herself.
Come on.
- Are you Charlie?
- Yeah.
I'm Olivia, Sarah's sister.
- Can I talk to you for a sec?
- Yeah, sure.
I'm really glad you came.
This is my son, Kit.
- I thought you said she was dying.
- I didn't say that.
- Well, you said it was urgent.
- It was. It is.
No, it's fine.
It's just superficial stuff.
She should be out of here
in a day or two at max.
I wouldn't call a concussion
and internal bleeding superficial.
- How long you know my sister?
- --
- And what's your relationship?
- We're friends.
- Right. How did you meet?
- At an AA meeting.
What's my sister doing
at an AA meeting?
She's handling her problems.
My sister?
My sister does not have
a problem with alcohol.
Well, you're gonna have to talk
to your sister about that.
I hope you're not just another guy
trying to rip her off.
What do you mean?
I mean are you trying to
get your hands on her money?
I didn't even know she had any money.
-- you think about me
but your sister really needs you right now.
No, my sister does not need me
and I don't need her.
That¡s the beauty of our relationship.
And don't tell her I was here.
-- her recovery.
Wait!
- Can I talk to you for a moment?
- Now what for?
Cause I think you --
I came because I thought
she was about to take her last breath.
I have a feeling you're not the cold
heartless bitch you pretend to be.
Excuse me?
I thought I didn't need
my dad either.
I thought I could make it on my own.
But he means the world to me now.
We helped each other with our addictions.
We've grown really close.
Well, luckily my sister and I
don't have any addictions
so we don't really need
to grow close.
Wait a minute.
If I can help you to make peace
with your sister in any way
here is my card.
"Kit Peterson:
musician slash mechanic"
You're being quiet.
Am I?
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize that.
What are you thinking about?
Us.
What's up?
Sister. She was a piece of work.
I didn't even know she had a sister
until yesterday.
I don't really know
nothing about her.
What a nice surprise!
- What's wrong?
- Can I talk to you?
Yeah. Come in.
Considering you might be
in a very vulnerable position right now
--
I just think...
Do you know how step 9
is to go round and make a -- talk
-- those we harmed in the past?
Well, I've come here today.
This visit is about that.
But you've never harmed me before.
I see.
So you plan on harming me
in the future
so you've thought
you apologize now.
I didn't warn you now
I'll feel bad later.
It's about my dad.
My dad is a great guy,
the best guy in the world.
He was never ugly or violent
when he drunk
he never hit me or anything
He never even yelled at me.
He just disappeared.
Everything would be fine
and then he'd fall into this weird mood
I wake up one morning and find a note
"I love you but
I have to go away for a while"
"I'll come back as soon as I can"
And then he'd be gone for months.
Happened when I was a kid.
Every time it happened
I had to call my grandma to come get me.
He's on the same thing to
every woman he's ever been with.
I see.
I really think it's best
if you don't…
I mean, with the stage you¡re in.
Just don't depend on him.
Thank you for the advice, Kit.
I hope you feel better.
Welcome home.
Why haven't you tried
to kiss me today?
I wanted to be careful.
I don't want you to be careful.
Sarah, why haven't you really told me
anything about yourself?
What do you mean?
I mean
I have no idea hat happened to you
to make you the way you are.
I have no idea when you first realized
you had a problem with alcohol,
how you're handling it,
what you think about AA,
where you are in the steps,
how you feel about your family,
basic things.
I don't know everything about you either.
This is a big deal for me, Charlie.
I need to go slow.
In case you haven't noticed.
I just need time.
That's all.
You're a peculiar woman, Sarah.
I've come to terms with that,
so you take your time.
Just don't take too much time, okay?
Percy is hiding behind the tree.
We're coming to get you,
broccoli.
You'll never catch me.
I'm
about getting a ring.
What kind of a ring?
Have you lost your mind?
You saw the booze under her bed, right?
She's obviously not in a good place.
Wouldn't be good for you either.
I just got this idea
in my head.
how many times before
the big ideas you get in your head
are almost never
the right thing to do.
I'm in love with her, Kit.
Be careful, dad.
--
I want to be sure if she was being
completely honest with me.
Do you think it's a good idea
to have alcohol in the house?
What do you mean?
If you have a problem with alcohol,
Do you think it's a good idea
to have alcohol in the house?
No, I think it's a terrible idea.
So you wouldn't do that.
No.
Excuse me.
Can we have -- please?
Are you okay?
Would you mind if I didn't walk you
to your door tonight?
Who was that at the restaurant?
That was my father.
I'm dead to him
because I was a big disappointment to him.
Have you ever tried to talk to him?
Maybe if you went to him
and you were completely
open and honest
maybe you would have a change of heart.
What do you know
about being open and honest?
What about all those bottles
under your bed, Sarah?
You lied to me tonight.
You lied to my face.
--
I found it by accident
when I was looking for your address book.
I have an explanation.
I don't want to hear
any explanations.
I've been honest with you.
I've been honest with you
except on one thing.
Oh, please, Sarah.
Just go. Just get out.
Get out!
Just get out.
to accept things I cannot change
the courage to change the things I can
Is your dad home?
No. He wasn't here when I got back last night.
I'm worried about him
I'll drive.
It's not him.
Your dad took me to this
really beautiful place
on the shore once.
Maybe he might be there?
fishing
--
This is not good.
- Hi, dad.
- Hi.
Hey, Charlie.
So what are you doing here?
I think the question should be
what are you doing here.
I'm appreciating nature.
What about all of this.
That was a terrible waste of money
and glass.
I really should have recycled.
I poured it out.
Came close but coming close
doesn't count.
I really need to talk to you, Charlie.
You two talk.
Since no one is talk to me
just gonna wait in the truck.
You've right to have lost confidence in me
after what I did.
Why won't you trust me, Sarah?
I haven't had the best luck
with relationships.
My first love swept me off my feet
and then left me.
I was pregnant with his child
and I was devastated.
I lost the baby 5 months later.
After that it seems like
every man I ever trusted
found a new way to hurt me.
And after a while it started to feel
like I deserved all that pain.
That's why you drink?
That's what I wanted to explain.
I've been allowing myself
to tweed this web
and it just keeps getting worse.
What are you talking about?
I don't have a drinking problem.
I've never had.
You really got me there.
For a second I thought
you're finally opening up to me.
You don't understand.
I'm trying to tell you.
Stop, okay?
Just stop.
No, you don't understand.
I can't deal with
this crap right now.
I've had a very rough night.
--
Hello.
Olivia who?
Musician slash mechanic, right?
That's me.
I left my wallet at home --
Just died. I don't know.
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate this.
Do you know your sister
calls you
just to hear the sound of your voice
in the answering machine?
I've long
lost interest in what my sister does.
Just try and talk things out with her.
How can that happen?
I don't care about her anymore.
Hi, this is Sarah.
I just wanted to say that
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for the way
that I treated you
and sorry for the way
I've behaved with you and Roy.
I just hope that you can
forgive me
because
I miss you.
And I love you.
And I really need
my little sister right now.
So please call me.
I love you.
All right,
we probably have time
for a couple more to share.
Who would it be?
Charlie, alcoholic.
I had a rough night
but I made it.
I made it through the night,
I made it through this day
and here I am.
I was going through the big --
this afternoon
something suddenly
became very clear to me.
may not make any sense
what came clear to me
was that
we all have wounds
that will never heal.
But that's okay
as long as we help each other
to bind those wounds.
So you don't bleed to death.
But then it occurred to me
that maybe that's why
we're here on this Earth
help each other bind our wounds.
Anyone else?
Okay, then.
Meeting over.
Could I say something?
That's great.
I think it's her first time.
My name is Sarah
and I'm not an alcoholic.
And I'm not in denial.
I want to extend my apology
to all of you.
I've been dishonest with you.
I've betrayed your sympathy
and your trust,
I've betrayed your friendship
and for that I'm very sorry.
I didn't start out
intending to deceive you.
It's just that
I used to watch you
all gathered out in front
and I just wished that I could be
a part of your group.
And then one night
I saw Charlie.
And I couldn't take my eyes off of him.
I loved the way he moved,
I loved the way he smiled.
I came to that first meeting
just to meet him.
I was following my heart
for the first time in a very long time.
And then one thing
led to another
and before I knew it
I was pretending to be an alcoholic.
But I have to say
that being here has helped me
because the truth is
I am a mess of a human being.
I may not be an alcoholic
but I have problems to overcome.
Huge, scary problems.
And I've learned so much
from all of you.
I know it's a lot to ask
but if you would allow it
I would like to keep coming back.
This is a meeting for people
with serious problems.
Rules are
everyone is welcome to our open meetings.
She can keep coming back
as many times as she likes.
As often as you want.
Thank you.
Okay. Meeting closed.
You have to keep coming
'cause this wouldn't be the same
without you.
I'm so disappointed
you're not a real alcoholic.
God, grant me the serenity
to accept the things I cannot change
the courage to change
the things I can
and wisdom to know the difference.
Keep coming back!
What do we do now?
I know exactly
what we do.
We start on page 1.
And we don't worry about punctuation
or grammar or spell words
or whether or not
the margins are even,
we just get lost in our story
and we see where it takes us.
I love the sound of that.
Lola,
can I talk to you for a second?
I just wanted you to know.
I probably should
have said this before but
I think you're very smart.
Exceptionally smart.
Do you think
I could get into college?
If you commit yourself
and you work really hard
I think you could get
into an excellent college.
And if you let me
I'd really love to help you
achieve that goal.
You won't yell at me?
I promise.
This is him?
This is the killer?
Shakespeare, come.
Here's the door.
I think --
message this morning.
Let me begin by saying that
Elvis is honored
to be officiating this ceremony today.
We are gathered here to celebrate
the marriage of Charles Manning
and Sarah Winston.
Charlie,
you take this woman to be your wife?
Before we all stuffing our faces
I'd like to make a toast.
During the ceremony
I asked myself
if these two
really did belong together
So I sized them up.
Sarah is tall, intelligent, good-looking,
refined, cultured and dignified
and Charlie is
not.
But obviously offsets attract.
So I say "yes".
Yes, they do.
I'd like to make a toast as well.
Your wedding
couldn't make me happier.
I've been looking for an excuse
to move out of my dad's place for years now.
I'd also like to make a toast.
To my sister who is starting
a new life
with a new husband,
a new future
and a new group of friends.
Cheers.
Subtitles by Héctor Lahoz
I have one more surprise for you.
Close your eyes.
Turn left.
This way.
Open your eyes.
Do you like it?
I love you, Sarah.
Subtitles by Héctor Lahoz
I gave up drinking,
I gave up smoking.
I gave up thinking all the time
stone cold revoking.
The reason to my rhyme,
I wasn't joking.
If there's a phoney bone in me,
I want it broken.
If you don't know what to say
or where to begin,
turn your high light on,
turn it up, tune me out
and rub it in
Rub it in