subtitles by boxd.it/dirtgrub
don't come for me if there are mistakes
He's here.
Professor Perlman.
-Welcome, welcome.
Thank you so much.
-It's so nice to-
Oh my goodness, you're-
you're bigger than your picture!
Well I couldn't get all of me in the photo,
that's the problem.
Mrs. Perlman.
-Annella.
Oliver. Very nice to meet you,
thank you for having me in your home.
Elio!
You must be exhausted.
Ah, what gave me away?
Elio, Oliver. Oliver, Elio.
How you doing?
-Nice to meet you. Elio.
You must be exhausted!
Little bit.
-Ha ha ha! Come, come, come.
May I bring your things up to your room?
-Uh, sure, yeah.
My room?
Follow him.
You're very welcome here.
Our home is your home.
Hello!
Hey.
Oh.
My room is now your room.
I'll be next door.
We have to share the bathroom.
It's my only way out.
We're being called for dinner!
(Oliver snores)
Oh, sorry the uh...
We're being called for dinner.
Um, yeah, um, I'm probably gonna pass.
Will you make me an excuse for me
for your mom though?
Thanks man.
So this is your old room, huh?
Thanks.
Later.
Wow look at this!
Good morning professor, good morning.
-From the dead.
Was I up that long?
-It seems like it. How- how are you?
I- uh- well, rested now, thank you.
Glad, would you like some espresso?
I would love some, thank you very much.
This looks amazing.
I didn't take your seat did I?
Oh, no, no, no, it's ok, please.
Did you- did you recover from your trip?
Uh, I did, yeah. Big time, thank you.
I could show you around.
That'd be great, thank you.
Um, is there a-
is there a bank in town? I'd love to start an account while I'm here.
Sorry.
Ah, it happens to the best of us.
Yeah, well.
None of our residents have ever
had a local bank account.
Really?
-Mm.
Should I take him to ...?
I think they're closed for summer vacation.
You try uh, Crema.
Crema?
Is this your orchard?
These are Annella's trees.
-Oh, wow.
Pomegranate.
Have another egg.
No, no, no.
I know myself too well, if I have a second
I'm just gonna have a third,
and then a fourth and then you're just
gonna have to roll me out of here.
Delicious.
Darling?
Thank you.
Should I give him Anchise's bike?
What does one do around here?
Wait for the summer to end.
Yeah?
What do you do in the winter?
Wait for summer to come?
-Well,
we only come here for Christmas
and some other vacations.
Christmas? I thought you were-
I thought you were Jewish?
-and Easter as well.
Well, we are Jewish but also American, Italian,
French- somewhat a typical combination.
Besides my family you're probably the
only other Jew to set foot in this town.
I'm from a small town in New England.
I know what it's like to be the odd Jew out.
So what do you do around here?
Read books, transcribe music, swim at
the river, go out at night. I don't know.
That sounds fun.
Alright buddy, thanks for the help.
Oops, sorry. Sorry about that.
It's alright.
Alright, later!
What do you have there?
That should all be-
What is this? Uh, these are the continuation
of these archeology department.
These are archeology? Yeah, those archeology,
the rest of these should be history.
More apricot juice?
Yeah.
Here.
-Thank you.
Help yourself to some more.
The word 'apricot' comes from the Arabic.
It's like the words 'algebra', 'alchemy', 'alcohol'.
It derives from an Arabic noun combined
with the Arabic article 'al' before it.
The origin of our Italian "albicocca"...
is 'albaricoque'.
Now it's amazing that today in Israel,
in many Arab countries,
the fruit's referred to by a totally different name:
"mishmish".
I may have to disagree with you there professor.
Ah?
I'm gonna talk in etymology
so just bear with me a second.
Um, you're right in the case that most Latin words
do find their origins in Greek words, however
in the case of apricot it's a little bit
more of a complicated journey.
Ah, how so?
Ah, well here the Greek actually
takes over from the Latin.
Latin word being "praecocum" or "praecoquis"
so it's pre-cooked or pre-ripened as you know,
not to be precocious or premature.
And the Byzantines to go on,
then borrowed "praecox"
which became "praecocia"
which then became "baricoci"
which is how the Arabs got "albaricoque".
Courtesy of etymology 101.
Flying colours.
He does this every year.
... let's move here.
How do you know about this place?
Okay!
No, no, no, no, no!
Perfect timing!
What's the matter, you alright?
-Huh?
Pinch your nerve?
-I'm okay.
Here, hold this.
Trust me, I'm about to be a doctor.
Hey, hey, hey, come here.
See, that's the problem.
You're too stressed. You just gotta relax a little bit.
-I am relaxing.
Marzia? Come here for a minute.
Back me up here.
Feel that, right there? It's too tight,
right? He needs to relax.
-Oliver!
Later!
You should relax more.
Ok guys, ready?
Woo!
Ok, our ball, our ball, our ball!
Twelve serving eleven.
Mine, mine, mine, mine!
Yours, yours, yours!
I don't think he's arrogant.
Just watch, this is how he'll say goodbye to us
when the time comes with his, "later".
Meanwhile we'll have to put up with him for
six long weeks won't we, darling.
I think he's shy.
You'll grow to like him.
What if I grow to hate him?
(Elio sighs)
Elio. Play something.
You're spoiling everyone's fun.
Hey!
-Hey.
What you doing?
-Reading.
How come you're not with everyone
else down by the river?
I have an allergy.
Yeah, me too.
Maybe we have the same one.
Why don't you and I go swimming?
-Right now?
Yeah, come on!
Let's go!
Do we have to go right now?
I'll go get changed. Meet you downstairs.
-Okay.
See you downstairs.
Elio, what are you doing?
Reading my music.
-No you're not.
Thinking, then.
-Yeah?
'Bout what.
It's private.
You're not gonna tell me?
-I'm not gonna tell you.
He's not gonna tell me what he's thinking about.
-(Annella) Elio!
I guess I'll go hang out with your mom.
More apricot juice!
Good boy, thank god you're helping me.
Sounds nice.
Thought you didn't like it.
Play it again, will ya?
Follow me.
That sounds different. Did you change it? Why?
-I changed it a little bit.
I just played it the way Liszt would have
played it if he'd altered Bach's version.
Play that again.
-Play what again?
The thing you played outside.
-Oh, you want me to play the thing I played outside?
Please.
-Ah. Of course.
I can't believe you changed it again.
-Oh I changed it a little bit.
Yeah, why?
I just played it the way Busoni would have
played it if he'd altered Liszt's version.
And what is wrong with Bach, the way Bach
would have played Bach's version?
-Bach never wrote it for the guitar.
In fact, we're not even sure Bach wrote it at all.
-Forget I asked!
It's young Bach.
He dedicated it to his brother.
Hey, professor.
-Hello.
Oh, here, please. Join me.
-Thank you.
Be honest, how bad is it?
(Michael) I think your insight's...
Ciao.
-Ciao.
Elio. You sleeping?
-Hm?
I was.
-Listen to this dribble. Tell me what you think.
Wait.
-What?
Can't hear you.
For the early Greeks, Heidegger contends,
this underlying hiddenness is constitutive of the way beings are,
not only in relation to themselves but also
in relation to other entities generally.
In other words, they do not construe hiddenness merely or
primarily in terms of entities' relation to human beings.
Does that make any sense to you?
Doesn't make any sense to me.
I don't think it makes any sense to your dad either.
Maybe it did when he wrote it.
That might be the kindest thing anybody
has said to me in months.
Kind?
-Yep. Kind.
(Armie Hammer dances quite horribly)
We almost had sex last night, Marzia and me.
Why didn't you?
I don't know.
Well you know it's better to have tried than failed, right?
All I had to do was find the courage to
reach out and touch. She would have said yes.
Well, try again later.
Try what later?
I just heard from the people in Sirmione,
they say they've come up with something.
Oh! Fantastic!
Going there today.
Would you like to come along?
I would love to, thank you.
Smell this.
-Can I come too?
Uh, on the condition you remain silent.
Silent as in he has too many opinions or silent as in
not telling anybody what amazing thing you've dug up?
Well nothing has been dug up, it's what has been brought out.
Out of the water.
Dad always sits up front with Anchise to navigate.
She seems to like you a lot.
More beautiful than she was last year.
I saw her naked on a night swim once... great body.
Tryna get me to like her?
-What would be the harm in that?
Not no harm, just typically like to go
those things on my own if you don't mind.
Just don't play at being a good host.
What's going on boys?
Oliver, come.
Sit up front, be my navigator.
What? What?
Look who's here!
He's grown a bit, eh?
And this is Oliver.
Ciao!
Hey boys!
The ship went down in 1827 on the way to Isola Del Garda.
Gossip has it this statue was a gift from
Count to his lover Contralto.
There are four known sets after the Praxiteles' originals,
this fellow's at number three.
The Emperor Hadrian had a pair dug up at Tivoli, but uh,
one of the more philistine of the Farnese popes
melted them down and had them recast as
a particularly voluptuous Venus.
Who'd like to go for a swim before we head back?
Elio!
-Oliver!
Hey, hey!
-I have to go!
Goodness!
Are you going too?
-No, no. I should stay and do some work on my book.
Oh, come on!
How 'bout a drink to celebrate the day?
Okay maybe just one.
-Alright!
Marzia?
(Elio) Cosmic fragments by Heraclitus.
(Oliver) The meaning of the river flowing is not that all things
are changing so that we cannot encounter them twice
but that some things stay the same only by changing.
Hm.
Darling have you seen my Heptaméron?
Mafalda.
It's in German.
Okay.
Can't remember where we left off
but I think you'll like this one.
So, I'll translate, huh?
A handsome young knight is madly in love with a princess,
and she too is in love with him,
though she seems not to be entirely aware of it,
despite the friendship
that blossoms between them, or
perhaps because of that very friendship,
the young knight finds himself so-
so humbled and speechless,
but he's totally unable to bring up the subject of his love.
So one day he asks the princess, point blank,
"Is it better to speak, or to die?".
I'll never have the courage to ask a question like that.
I doubt that.
Hey, Eli belly.
You do know that you can always talk to us.
My mom has been reading this
16th century French romance.
She read some of it to my dad and I
the night the lights went out.
Is that about the knight that doesn't know whether to speak or die?
-Right.
So does he or doesn't he?
"Better to speak" she said.
But she's on her guard.
She senses a trap somewhere.
So does he speak?
Nope.
He fudges.
-Hm.
It figures. He's French.
I gotta go to town in a little bit to pick some things up.
-Oh, I can go I'm not doing anything today.
Why don't we go together?
-Right now?
Yeah, right now.
It is of course unless you have more
important business going on.
(ELIO MOCKS OLIVER)
Mind if I put this in your bag?
-Yes, please.
I fell. I was coming home the other day
and I scraped myself pretty badly.
Anchise insisted I apply some kind of witch's brew.
I think it helped.
Hold this for a second, will ya?
Want one?
-Sure.
Not bad, huh?
-Not bad at all.
Thought you didn't smoke.
-I don't.
So WWII, huh?
-Oh no, this is WWI.
You have to be at least 80 years old
to have known any of them.
I never even heard of the Battle of Piave.
Battle of Piave was one of the
most lethal battles of WWI.
A hundred and seventy thousand people died.
Is there anything you don't know?
I know nothing, Oliver.
Well you seem to know more than
anybody else around here.
Well if only you know how little I know
about the things that matter.
What things that matter?
You know what things.
Why are you telling me this?
'Cause I thought you should know?
Because you thought I should know?
'Cause I wanted you to know?
'Cause I wanted you to know.
Because there's no one else
I can say this to but you?
You saying what I think you're saying?
Don't go anywhere.
Stay right here.
You know I'm not going anywhere.
They mixed up all of my pages.
I'm going to have to retype this whole thing.
I'm not gonna have anything to work on after this.
This is gonna set me back a whole day.
Damnit.
Shouldn't have said anything.
Just pretend you never did.
-Oh, does that mean we're on speaking terms but not really?
Means we can't talk about those kinds of things,
'kay?
We just can't.
Hey!
Ready?
-Let's go.
Pretty much.
Oh my god.
You thirsty?
-Yeah.
That's Italy.
Come on!
This is my spot.
It's all mine.
Come here to read.
Can't tell you the number of books I've read here.
Oh my god it's freezing!
Spring is in the mountains.
The water comes straight down from there.
I like the way you say things.
Don't know why you're always
putting yourself down, though.
So you won't? I guess?
You really that afraid of what I think?
You're making things very difficult for me.
(Elio sighs)
I love this, Oliver.
(Oliver sighs)
What?
Everything.
Us, you mean?
Ah, it's not bad. It's not bad.
Better now?
No, no, no no, no, no, no, no.
We should go.
-Why?
I know myself, 'kay?
And we've been good.
We haven't done anything to be ashamed of.
And that's a good thing.
I wanna be good.
Okay?
Am I offending you?
Just don't.
I think it's starting to get infected.
Stop at the pharmacist on the way back.
-Excellent idea.
Elio?
Elio, you alright?
Sit for a second.
If you insist.
That wasn't my fault, right?
-No.
I'm a mess.
Well.
The kitchen table sure is.
Ow, where'd you learn to do that?
My bubbe used to do this for us when we were sick.
Trust me, it helps.
I used to have one of these.
Used to?
-Yeah.
How come you never wear it?
My mother says we are Jews of discretion.
Well,
I guess that works for your mother.
Funny witch.
Ow you'll fucking kill me if you do that.
Oh, I hope not.
Hey, are you leaving?
-Where's Elio?
He's inside, he had a bit of a nosebleed
during lunch so he's just resting.
Ah, really?
-Yeah.
Okay, I'll be back in a minute.
Don't go anywhere.
Traitor.
Please don't avoid me. Kills me.
Can't stand thinking you hate me.
Your silence is killing me. I'd sooner die than
know you hate me. I am such a pussy.
Way over the top.
Can't stand the silence.
I need to speak to you.
Someone have a good night last night?
Hm.
Well you must be tired then.
Or were you playing poker too?
I don't play poker.
Several hundred colour slides of our boxer and
the others like them arrived yesterday from Berlin.
We should start cataloging them.
That'll keep us busy 'till lunch I imagine.
-Sure.
Oh, beautiful aren't they?
But they're all so incredibly sensual.
Because these are more Hellenistic
during 5th century Athenian.
Most likely sculpted under the influence of Praxiteles.
"Greatest sculptor in antiquity".
(Oliver) Grow up. I'll see you at midnight.
(Elio) Grow up. I'll see you at midnight.
Muscles are firm.
Look at his stomach for example.
Not a straight body in these statues,
they're all curved.
Sometimes impossibly curved,
and so nonchalant.
Hence their ageless ambiguity.
As if they're daring you to desire them.
Don't forget, Isaac and Mounir are coming for dinner.
Also known as Sonny and Cher.
-Okay.
I'd like you to wear that shirt they gave
you for your birthday.
-No.
Darling they bought it from Miami!
-I'm sorry it's too big, it's too big.
Come on, it'd make them so happy.
-It looks ridiculous on me.
I'll try it on for Oliver. If Oliver thinks I look like
a scarecrow in it, I'm not wearing it.
Oliver?
Hey, what time you got?
It's two.
Well, later.
Later.
Mafalda.
Um, uh,
How are you?
-Hey, I'm good.
Good to see you.
-It's great to see you.
No, no, I have to go.
Have a nice evening.
-Oh, thank you.
This right here,
is the brand new china that
you guys so kindly sent to us.
Oh, it looks wonderful!
Come here Mounir, Mounir, come, come, come.
I can't put it on now they've already met me,
it'll look like a put-up job!
-Yes, you can!
Papa! Papa! It'll look like a put-up job!
-Yes-
No misbehaving tonight, no- no laughing.
When I tell you to play, you'll play.
You- you're too old not to accept people for who they are.
What's wrong with them?
What's wrong with them!
You call them Sonny and Cher behind their back?
That's what mom calls them!
-Then you accept gifts from them?
The only person that reflects badly on is you.
Is it because they're gay or because they're ridiculous.
You know as much about economics at Mounir's age
you'll be a very wise man indeed.
And a- credit to me.
Now- now, get into this you.
These are, unbelievable, I just uh-
I'm sorry I have to go to bed.
Sorry I'm so tired.
Elio. Elio.
Thank you.
-Goodnight.
Goodnight.
Do I know you?
I'm glad you came.
I'm nervous.
Like what you've done with the place.
It's nice.
You ok?
Me ok.
Can I kiss you?
-Yes please.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
This make you happy?
You're not gonna get a nosebleed on me, are ya?
I'm not gonna get a-
Off, off, off, off, off!
Just pull it.
Or I'll pull it.
Oliver.
Call me by your name and I'll call you by mine.
Elio.
Oliver.
Did we make noise?
Nothing to worry about.
I don't know, Mafalda always looks for signs.
Well she's not gonna find any.
You wore that shirt the first day you were here.
Will you give it to me when you go?
Let's go swimming.
Are you gonna hold what happened
last night against me?
No.
Elio.
Come here.
Take your trunks off.
Well that's promising.
-You're hard again.
Good.
Professor, I got your note.
Uh, thank you for reminding me.
I'm gonna go into town to
pick up those typed pages today.
So maybe this afternoon would
be a good time to-
Later.
... before you leave.
Okay.
So, later.
Later!
Oliver!
You're not sick of me yet?
No, I just- I just wanted to be with you.
I'll- I'm gonna- I'll go.
Do you know how happy I am
that we slept together?
I don't know.
Of course you don't know.
I don't want you to regret anything.
And I hate the thought that maybe
I might have messed you up or,
I don't want either of us to pay for this.
-No I- it's not like I'm gonna tell anyone you,
y- you're not gonna be like in any trouble.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Are you happy I came here?
I'd kiss you if I could.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
What did you do?
Nothing.
-No?
Oh, I see.
You've moved onto the plant kingdom already.
What's next, minerals?
I suppose you've already given up
animals, you know that's me.
I'm sick, aren't I?
I wish everybody was as sick as you.
Please don't do that.
-You wanna see something sick?
You wanna see something sick?
-Please don't do this.
Hey! Please don't do this.
Why are you doing this to me?
What are you doing? Stop, you're fucking hurting me.
-Then don't fight.
(ELIO SOBS)
Come here.
Sorry.
It's ok.
I don't want you to go.
God, we wasted so many days.
Why didn't you give me a sign?
-I did.
You didn't give me a sign.
-I did!
When did- when?
You remember when we were playing volleyball?
And I touched you
just to show you
that I liked you?
The way you reacted made me feel like I molested you.
-Sorry, I'm sorry.
No, it's fine. I just decided
I should keep my distance.
I don't know.
I come out here for hours almost every night.
I didn't know that.
That's funny, I-
I thought that...
Yeah I know what you thought.
-Stop, stop.
For Oliver, from Elio.
Elio?
I had to work.
Yeah, I don't know, I just uh-
I'm- I'm not your girl?
Oliver has to go to Bergamo for a few days.
Oh?
Research at the university.
Then he'll fly home from Linate.
Oh but what about Elio?
Maybe it could be nice for the two of them
to get away for a couple of days, no?
What do you think?
... our favourite student.
You must come back.
-You sure you're not just saying that?
Oliver.
-Thank you very much, professor.
Oh, man.
Please, please, come back soon.
-Come back? I'm just going home to pack. I'm living here!
You're welcome!
Oh, well.
Thank you guys so much.
-Ah, of course.
Oliver, Oliver.
Come back.
Come here, come here. It's been amazing. Thank you guys.
-Oh, oh.
Well,
later Perlmans.
Later! Later, later, later!
Tell Elio to call when you get there!
Oh no!
What?
Nothing.
-What!
Yes!
Woo!
Oliver!
Elio!
Woo!
Oliver!
-Elio!
Woo!
You hear that?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no! It's this-
it's this way come on!
You're missing it!
Come on!
Woo!
What'd she say?
Did you get your passport?
Fuck.
How are you?
Good.
Missed you at dinner.
So?
Welcome home.
Thanks.
Oliver enjoy the trip?
-Yeah.
Think he did.
You two had a nice friendship.
Yeah.
You're too smart not to know how rare,
how special, what you two had was.
Oliver was Oliver.
-Mm.
Oliver may be very intelligent but-
-Oh, no, no.
He was more than intelligent.
What you two had,
had everything and nothing to do with intelligence.
He was good.
You were both lucky to have
found each other because...
You too are good.
I think he was better than me.
I'm sure he'd say the same thing about you.
Yeah, he'd say the same thing.
Which flatters you both.
When you least expect it,
nature has cunning ways of finding our weakest spot.
Just...
remember I'm here.
Right now you may not want to feel anything.
Maybe you never wanted to feel anything.
And uh,
maybe it's not me you want to speak about these things but uh,
feel something you obviously did.
Look, you had a beautiful friendship,
maybe more than a friendship.
And I envy you.
My place, most parents would hope the whole thing goes away.
Pray their sons land on their feet, but...
I am not such a parent.
We rip out so much of ourselves to be cured of things faster,
that we go bankrupt by the age of 30,
and have less to offer each time we start with someone new.
But to make yourself feel nothing,
so as not to feel anything,
what a waste.
Have I spoke enough?
Then I'll say one more thing.
It'll clear the air.
I may have come close,
but I never had what you two have.
Something always...
held me back,
or stood in the way.
How you live your life is your business.
Just...
remember.
Our hearts in our bodies are given to us only once,
and...
before you know it,
your heart's worn out.
And as for your body?
There comes a point where no one looks at it.
Much less wants to come near it.
Right now,
there's sorrow...
pain...
don't kill it.
And with it, the joy you felt.
Does mom know?
I don't think she does.
I'll get it!
(Elio? You there?)
Hi!
(Hey!)
How are you?
(I'm good, I'm good. How are you?)
I'm good! They're fine.
-(How are your parents?)
(Good.)
I missed you.
(I missed you, too.)
(Very much.)
(I have some news.)
N- news?
Oh, you're getting married?
I suppose..?
(I might be getting married next spring, yeah.)
You never said anything.
(It's been off and on for two years.)
That's wonderful news.
(Do you mind?)
Oliver! Oliver!
-(Hey, hey, hey!)
Oh darling when are you coming back?
(Oh, I wish I was.)
You caught us in the process of choosing the new you for next summer.
And guess what? He's a she!
-(Oh, nice!)
Well speaking of she's,
I'm calling to tell you guys I got engaged!
Oh, wonderful!
Congratulations!
-Mazel tov!
Congratulations, Oliver!
-(Thank you, thank you.)
Listen, w-we'll leave you-
we'll- we'll let you speak to Elio.
Happy Hanukkah!
Bye, sweetheart.
They know about us.
I figured.
How?
Well, from the way your dad spoke to me.
He made me feel like I was a part of the family.
Almost like a son-in-law.
You're so lucky.
My father would have carted me off to a correctional facility.
Elio?
Elio, Elio, Elio, Elio, Elio, Elio, Elio, Elio.
Oliver.
I remember everything.
Elio.
Elio?
im gay and sad thanks for coming to my ted talk