What is this whiny crap
we're listenin' to?
Rawlins, you suck, man.
They gay bar's
across the street!
I bet she still sings
better than you!
Don't know what he's playin'.
Is that guitar in tune?
To top that,
he looks like he's 12.
He's a little boy.
He walks in here
trying to be tough
with the leather jacket
and boots.
And then he's singin'
about love.
He probably ain't even
been laid yet.
He sings like that, he won't be
gettin' laid any time soon.
LAND OF LEOPOLD
Subrip: Pix
The cards dealt to me
were rags.
All I saw in my hands
was pain and violence.
I wanted to escape
what my father did.
If I didn't...
I would end up the person
I despised the most.
Growing up,
nothing was simple.
My mom was always gone...
on the road performing.
We would talk
through letters often...
but only see her
once in a while.
I got to spend
most of my time with Dad.
Well...
you can guess
what life with him was like.
Drank himself near to death
before he grabbed that gun...
killed Mom and himself.
So I ran...
away from the world.
I tried to shut it
out of my mind,
but the images never left.
-Morning, Michael.
-Morning, Reggie.
Reggie, do you know
what time it is?
We're already short of staff
as it is.
Your tray's
on the counter there.
Yes, ma'am.
[footsteps approaching
Morning, beautiful.
Morning, Reggie.
You have my stuff?
The other stuff.
Come on, Reggie,
we made a deal.
If I find out
you're skipping your meds...
You're the best.
Kisses.
Don't get caught this time.
Can you dare imagine
what it must be like
to stand at the foot
of the great beast...
between you and the hot
flesh, only a sliver of steel?
Emphasis!
If you're going to play
in one of my productions,
professionalism,
embody it!
Closed rehearsals!
Go away!
You're disrupting
the tranquility.
Come on, Francis,
you gotta take your meds
just like everybody else, man.
Okay, everyone.
Take five.
Where's Cal?
Stepped out.
Places, class!
Objectives, obstacles,
intent, triggers.
What are they?!
Corrina!
You guys are
really quiet today.
Shut up.
Corrina, you make me so happy!
When my skies are gray!
Cal!
Get down from there!
Not until Corrina accepts me
as her soulmate!
She knows it.
It's her destiny.
Cal, just get down already,
man.
No!
He doin' the roof thing again?
He's obsessed with you.
This shit gotta end.
As far as I can remember
I was a runaway.
No home, no family...
disconnected
from the world...
drifting in and out
of trouble.
A good lawyer
and enough money
can get you out of anything.
A so-so public defender
and three dollars
in your pocket...
well...
that'll get you 12 months.
I did a year
at Northridge Penitentiary
for beatin' the grin
off that face.
Northridge proved to be
a real hellhole.
But before the State
threw me back on the streets,
they sent me
to a halfway house
in the middle of nowhere.
It was for people
who didn't fit in...
in other words, those who
are mentally unstable.
Come on down here
before I whoop your ass!
Are you serious?
Corrina!
I love you so much!
Boom!
The first person I saw
when I got there
was Cal.
Try this.
Corrina!
That's hospital property!
He wasn't what you'd call...
a big supporter of the arts.
That's it.
I'm comin' up there
and gettin' your ass, man.
Ignore him and he'll have
no one to jump for.
Hey, Reggie, it looks like
we got ourselves another one!
He looks sad...
but in a kinda cute way.
18, she's legal.
Damn.
So... have a seat here.
Dr. Warren will see you
when he's ready.
All right?
News now, Pete.
It ain't good.
We gotta move on, partner.
You're next in line.
What's the compensation?
It's like this.
The State's check isn't nearly
as sweet as an insurance claim.
I don't know how I feel
about this.
It doesn't make a damn
how you feel about it, Deece.
The State board
doesn't bargain.
What's your take?
50 percent.
That's a hefty take.
You ain't got
anything else, pal.
I'm your only ally.
Small State contractors
like you...
don't cut it anymore.
If Northridge takes
your psycho clients...
you can forget it.
I got your back...
as long as you live up
to your end of the deal.
You could be livin' high,
my old friend.
You could be livin' high.
What's it like...
to kill?
E.O.P. at Northridge
for a year...
It says that...
you're a violent type...
a convicted criminal.
Says you're prone
to running away?
I like the exercise.
Ain't nothing' wrong with that.
Yeah... but don't get
any ideas...
'cause nature
around these parts...
ain't too forgivin'
to city folk.
You know, you could've,
joined the service
and put that anger to good use.
Rejected.
They think I'm nuts.
I didn't even kill anybody.
Seriously injuring people
is your thing?
Well...
there'll be none of that
here.
Get me?
Get me?!
-Get it.
-Good.
Give me those.
Maybe you can earn 'em back.
If you follow the rules,
that is.
And those fancy sunglasses too.
Your shoes.
Any other contraband
I should know about?
That's it, Doc.
I told you not to call me that.
You're lucky to be here.
You might want to take
advantage of the opportunity
before it's too late.
Too late for what?
Your file must be signed by me
and approved by the State
before release.
You mess up here,
you go right back
to Northridge,
and you can kiss all your
rockstar dreams goodbye.
This is my rodeo...
and you're late
for group meeting.
Reggie'll show you the way.
The pen.
Nurse.
Frank, hand it over.
Are you incompetent?
Don't you see he's just
pining for attention?
-Cal, please wait...
-Nurse Verona?
This is Leopold Rawlins.
Hello, Leopold.
Please join us.
Leopold.
Leopold, why don't you introduce
yourself to the group?
Not today.
Well, it is customary
for new patients to...
Nurse Verona, is it?
Not today.
Very well.
Tomorrow you can share.
Why do we gotta bring
another queer to the group?
That's enough, Cal.
Okay, now, Mary Bell,
are you still having
the nightmare?
No, not anymore.
Good!
Positive reinforcement
through negative association.
That's what we covered
last week.
I do have a new dream, though.
Really?
It's about a bow tie
that wraps itself
around my neck...
softly...
slowly, and it tightens
until I'm on the verge
of death,
and then it loosens just enough
so that I can feel
the warm air
tease my cold lungs,
and then it tightens
back up again.
And it does this
over, and over, and over,
and over, and over,
and over again until...
until I finally wake up.
Good, improvement.
-Improvement?
-I like that last one better.
We'll open up the floor
when we finish with Mary Bell.
You need to learn how to lead.
Cal, this is your second
and last warning!
For fuck's sake!
She's making these dreams up!
My God, could you be
any more fucking dim-witted?
I'm not finished yet,
Nurse Verona.
I know.
I'm not finished yet!
-Ern.
-Yeah, Ern!
If I have to
stop this session one...
What?
You're gonna do what?
I'm not finished yet!
Go on.
I wanna fuck you
in the bathroom.
No.
-I like it on the sink.
-Shit everywhere.
That is
extremely inappropriate.
Good grief,
what is going on with...
Old hag!
I'll light your pussies
on fire.
All of 'em. They're burning
in the shit box as we speak.
Meow.
Meow. Meow.
This was the circus...
and that's how
I met Corrina.
I didn't know who she was,
but there was something
about her.
I wanted to find out more.
Being out here
in the middle of nowhere
kind of forced you
to connect with one another
and clear up your thoughts.
I started thinking more
about my family.
Seeing my parents die
at a young age
was a hard thing to shake.
All I had from my mother
was a few letters
and this photograph.
She's gorgeous.
I was gonna be a mother.
I grew up on this...
artists' commune...
and all we did all day
and all night was paint...
and time didn't exist...
and there was never
enough of it.
I can barely remember
what that feels like.
My life's always going in...
opposite directions.
What do you mean?
It's just not...
easy.
Fate's heavy on some.
When...
When Grandma found out
that I was coming...
she made this quilt
for my mom...
and it was covered
in caterpillars.
My mom used to wrap me in it...
and sing me to sleep,
and she told me...
that one day
I would do the same...
but then...
I snagged it on a tree...
and she got mad...
'cause it started to unravel.
Sometimes things, they...
they just don't fit
like they should.
"To my Leo...
I'm so proud of you.
Everyone says
you're gonna grow
into such a handsome man.
Do you like the new guitar
I sent you?
There's something new and fun
to learn every day.
The best part of life
is what we don't expect.
Music has taken me
far and wide...
sometimes, to the other side
of the world...
but remember...
even if I'm not close by...
I know that
I'm always with you.
We live our life in stages.
When one ends,
another one begins.
Change is constant...
and life is short.
Seize every moment...
every breath.
I'll be back soon,
my baby boy.
I miss you
more than words.
Love, Mom."
Baby giraffe.
Gazelle, gazelle, gazelle.
Francis was a novelty.
He liked games
and kept the morale high.
I figured...
he was in pretty deep.
How're you likin' the place
so far?
Are you thinkin' about
makin' a run for it?
Here's your pen.
Keep it.
You want to be friends?
Go get the keys
and un-cuff me.
I'm the boss.
Yeah, I heard you the
first time, you fucking loon-o.
Now go get the goddamn keys.
They left you hangin'?
Reggie, Reggie told me
to watch him.
I'm the boss.
No, Eddie, no you're not...
Make good use of yourself
and rinse this cup out for me,
would you please, Eddie?
Thanks.
Where in the hell
are you getting these blades?
I don't have it anymore.
Why are you doing this, Callum?
Why?
You know I'm gonna have to have
your room searched.
I'm fine.
Why'd they cuff you?
Look, they just cuffed me here.
All right?
I don't believe that.
Not for a second.
It was Verona.
Don't worry about staff issues.
All right?
-Mr. Deece?
-No.
So, you gonna un-cuff me
already?
I mean, this is...
This is probably illegal.
-Mr. Deece.
-Eddie, I said...
Th-there's someone
here to see you.
What can I do for you?
Why is that patient
handcuffed to the chair?
That's what I wanna know.
I'm sorry. You are...?
Catherine Windgate,
State Inspector
assigned to Milton Way.
I'm looking for
the clinical director,
Dr. Warren.
Well then, look no further.
I'm Dr. Warren.
I've been assigned
by the board to...
assess your establishment.
Very well...
Whatever you need,
I'm always here to help and...
I'm, sorry about
this little mix-up here.
Eddie, go grab the keys for me,
would you?
Okay.
Go.
Okay, Dr. Warren...
We'll be in touch.
Okay.
Take care.
I'll be damned
if I don't pass this place on.
300k is big money.
Enough to hang your hat on
for good.
Just make sure it looks
like an accident.
We'll see.
But please, you try
to stall 'em on your end.
That's more like it.
I gotta go.
Thanks, Frank.
Those bastards, they never
give me more than two.
How's the new boy toy?
You're gonna let him
get away with that?
Don't.
It's okay.
Can I help you?
If you wanted seconds...
you should've just asked.
Fuck!
Again, people?
Sir, it was the new guy,
Leopold.
He just threw a try of food
at me for no reason.
He's lying, Dr. Warren.
Why are you stickin' up
for him?
Your first day, Leopold...
and you're already
on thin ice.
Look, it was an accident.
I dropped my tray.
Maybe you do wanna go back
where you came from?
Maybe I'm headed there already.
Leopold will clean this up,
Reggie.
Busted.
Cal, you'll be joining him.
W-wait!
All right.
Clean 'em off,
then lights out,
except for those two.
And make sure they get the best cleaning
equipment we've got, all right?
I'm gonna keep my eye on 'em.
All the stunts and charades
end today.
I can tell who's real
and who's not.
Ain't no room
for faggots here...
Not on my watch.
Stay clear of Corrina.
She's mine.
She always has been.
I'll do what I want.
You think so?
Whatcha lookin' at?
Nothin'.
Fucking bitch!
You want what you want?!
Is this what you want?!
Give it to me!
What are you afraid of?!
What are you afraid...
What happened to that broom,
Rawlins?
It was an accident.
Another accident?
You two, get up to your rooms.
I saw myself in Cal.
Somewhere inside
when I was young...
without a home...
without a friend.
Deece was trying hard
for his son...
but Cal was so damaged.
My mom's letters
were the only memory
of what having a family
felt like.
"Leo... I'm missin' you.
I think about you
growing up.
I think about your music.
I loved your last letter.
I know it's tough
without me there.
I wish I could
ease your mind.
I know I'm gettin' older.
No one is around forever.
Just remember
how special you are...
to see the good in people.
Look for the beauty
in the world.
There are bad people, but...
you're not bad.
You come from a good place.
Remember...
even if I'm not
next to you...
I'm always with you.
I hope you know
I'm comin' for you soon...
like I always said.
And now...
I'm close.
Everything's going to be okay.
Love... Mom."
[distant train horn.
This is my favorite place...
my little sanctuary.
What's on your arm?
Words...
to a song.
How's it go?
Not finished yet.
I'd like to hear it
when you're done.
They're gonna be free.
I'm thinking about escaping.
Maybe tonight.
Maybe tomorrow.
Maybe next year.
Maybe tonight?
I'm all better now.
Promise this stays between us.
Milton Way is shutting down.
They're sending all of us
to Northridge.
I ain't goin' back
to Northridge
no matter what.
I know my lines.
I'm a tiger.
You know your lines.
Lines are all over you.
You should be in the...
in the zoo,
not the movie business!
Dinner in 30 minutes!
What's on the menu
tonight, garçon?
Rice stew,
same as every Monday night.
And ain't it the best rice stew
this side of sane?
You don't tell me shit.
I'm the master here.
You're the apprentice.
Hey.
Hi.
Your use of monochromatics
continues to impress, Cor-Cor.
You should hang it up
in the entrance.
Can't.
Milton Way is no more.
It's Northridge
from here on in.
Right, Leopold?
Do they have paints
at Northridge?
Okay, listen.
Promise this stays
between us three.
We got no one else to tell.
It's a prison.
No paints, no music...
That sounds like exaggeration.
Sounds like an exaggeration?
Hospitals are moving patients...
into prisons.
It's not somewhere
you wanna be.
I know where I'm headed.
Where?
Anywhere but there.
Listen...
I know these parts pretty well.
I can draft a plan.
I could've made
my own escape, no problem,
but if it meant getting closer
to Corrina...
Okay, let's do it.
I love you.
Do you love me, too?
I need to speak with Dr.
Warren, please.
Dr. Warren.
I'm sorry.
He was found decapitated.
A stripper cut his head off.
Excuse me?
I know. Tragic.
Is this some sort
of sick joke?
Have Dr. Warren
call me immediately.
It's urgent.
Beautiful day at Milton Way.
Who was that, Mary Bell?
God.
You are never to answer
this phone again, you hear me?!
Never!
God.
It's in the back.
Deece had started
selling Milton Way off
piece by piece.
The debts were
so high, though,
that it wasn't enough.
Felt that
the ship was sinkin'
but he would never
let anyone know.
Corrina would always paint
the same picture.
Sometimes of a young boy
and sometimes
of a young girl.
I guess that was her way
of imagining
what it would be like
to be a mother.
Francis had such
a childlike innocence
and imagination about him.
He had to be shutting out
his past life very well.
He refused to talk
about what got him there...
and I never asked.
At Milton Way...
the patients created
their own world.
They felt safe when they
were able to dream.
Deece had done a good job
makin' a home
for these people.
Everyone...
Ron, you too.
Good morning, troops.
Today... we're gonna go out
on a field trip.
All right?
Everybody up!
You like to get it up,
don't you, Deecey Boy?
Mary Bell, you stay here.
You look a little peaked.
Let's go!
I remember the last time
I had to take a hill like this.
Why are we out here?
Nothin' like Texas...
Nothin'.
Is that woman
gonna shut us down?
She's a member
of the State board.
They've already passed a grant
to renovate our facility.
Why don't we have pizza
and movie night tonight?
Reggie, can we move it up?
Sir, good as great.
All right.
Yes, Leopold. You wanna
share something with us?
What lies to the north
beyond the river?
What do you care?
Past the river there's
the Jenkins' farmland.
The cotton field
and corn fields...
used to be an ancient
Indian burial ground.
Before that, it was plains
full of wild buffalo.
I think he's talking about
the physical characteristics
of the land.
Well,
there's a dense forest,
and there's
the Jenkins' farmland.
Then there's another forest.
And beyond that forest?
A spring.
I didn't know
there was a spring.
What's after that?
An untamed land.
-Got a minute?
-Not now.
Rendezvous in 27 seconds.
Yeah.
I forgot about
your big concert tonight.
Shut up.
Don't blow our cover.
We're being watched.
Nobody's watching us.
Yeah?
Check out Hawkeye over there.
Easy.
No bite.
Cal seems onto us.
He has it out for you.
Anybody Corrina
takes a liking to
he automatically targets.
Hold this.
Hey.
Hi.
Operation White Tiger
is in effect.
It's now or never.
What's "White Tiger"?
No time to explain.
I'll give the green light
at dinner.
This is the spot.
Remember this spot, Leopold.
This is where the pillowcases
have to be buried.
Pillowcases?
Yeah, we need to fill them
with food at dinner.
I'll take care of the rest.
Listen...
I've collected
all the information we need.
Thanks, Corrina.
We're here,
and we need to get there.
In between are obstacles
of all sorts.
Big payoff is just
past the river
at the Jenkins farm,
but we gotta make it
past the dragon.
Dragon?
It's a hound.
Dragon.
Okay, good.
And since the drought,
we might be able to
-make the crossing here...
-Dinner time!
...without trouble,
but we gotta book it,
'cause the rains are comin'.
How do you know?
-I heard it on the radio.
-Teddy bear.
Leopold, you do the talking.
Hey, what's goin' on, guys?
Here.
just...
picking wildflowers...
They're in bloom.
Want one?
Yeah.
It's dinner time.
Everybody inside.
Yeah.
Come on, let's go.
Hey.
Hey, where's my milk?
I told Reggie
to fill it last night.
Can't sleep without my milk.
Come on.
I want warm milk, too.
Abort White Tiger.
I repeat, abort White Tiger!
I put them there.
Double-crossing us?
Look, I figured
it would save us the trouble
of finding 'em in the dark.
Improvising already.
Risky... but smart.
I found myself running
once again.
This time... with company...
a plan, and where to...
no one could really be sure.
I just knew
if we stayed behind...
it was a one-way trip
to Northridge.
The water level's
not that high.
A little muddy...
but not that bad.
I could do without the smell.
What a big crazy fucking world.
We're only here
for a nanosecond
when you think about it.
Well, I cannot believe
we're actually doing this.
We could always go back.
They wouldn't even know
we left.
-It is too late.
-No, no one is... going back.
Now is our chance to live free.
Free.
Francis...
If you could go anywhere
in the world...
where would you go?
New York.
Broadway!
Let's do it.
What about you, Corrina?
I...
I haven't figured out
that one yet.
Well...
My mother...
she was a hell of a
guitarist. She toured...
all over the world.
Told me about gettin' lost
on the streets of Berlin...
seeing the lights in Paris...
getting fat on pasta and wine
in Italy...
She was free as free can be.
I just wanna go
where my music takes me.
I could be your song.
I'm gonna have to
take a tinkle.
I'll see you guys
in a little bit.
Do you think the stars
are attached by strings...
and if we just... snip 'em,
they would...
fall to the Earth?
I like that.
Wha...
Shit! Kneel!
Jenkins' place.
We gotta go around.
No other way.
Corrina, come on!
-There he is.
-No!
Scurry.
Go, go, go, go, go!
I think he's dozing.
Stay light on your feet.
You little bastards!
Come back again,
I'll put your ass down!
Stay off of
my fuckin' property!
I thought you said
there was a hound!
-Slight miscalculation!
-God!
Blow your god damn head off!
Francis, you fucking idiot!
It was a mistake!
I-I-I...
We're getting shot at
back here!
You're gonna get us killed!
I never make a mistake!
Yes, you do!
Never!
What are you talking about?!
You know, that map of yours
almost got us killed.
Almost... but not quite.
Not quite?
Told you to make it good.
There are a lot of things wrong
in this world, Leopold...
including me.
But this map...
This map is right,
I'm sure of it.
Let me see this map.
It seems wrong.
Well, according to this map,
which is right...
we're close.
Hey, guys!
Look what I found.
And then... it hit me.
There we were...
our own little family...
living in the moment.
It felt like we were startin'
our lives from scratch.
All the bad, forgotten...
free from our past...
even for a little while.
It all seemed so perfect...
but so fragile.
Boys!
Look!
My God!
I've never seen such a place.
That's quite a drop.
Yeah.
Look at that.
Corrina, look at that.
It's beautiful.
One summer...
I don't remember where...
I was really little
and my dad lifted me up.
We went flying.
And then
the water hits you.
It felt like an eternity.
You know that feeling when...
your heart stops?
Freedom.
When I was a kid...
my mother left for good.
Where is she now?
She's gone.
I just haven't felt anything...
since my mother died.
And now?
It's different.
Corrina!
Frank, we fucked up, man!
We're gonna get you outta here.
You're gonna be okay.
We're gonna get you
out of here.
It's my fault.
A truck!
I'm sorry.
Deece...
Deece!
Hello.
Deece, it's Pete.
The State's takin' action.
Your boys are headed
to Northridge.
Listen, small hospitals
just can't cut it anymore.
When?
In the morning.
Got word today.
You can still make good.
It's the only way to get back
what's yours.
Deece?
Hey!
You listenin'?
Deece?
Hey, Deece!
Corrina!
No!
Get the fuck off me!
Cal!
No!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No! No!
Please, God!
God damn it!
No! No!
-Cal!
-No!
Wake up! No!
No! He's bleeding to death!
God damn it!
I tried to have you
in long life.
Your mother died
behind closed doors.
No witnesses.
You try to think
of her music,
but the screams
creep into your mind...
so you run...
but the pain
follows you everywhere.
Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
The lights blind you.
You lose your way,
your voice, muted.
Fuck! Fuck!
You plead with God...
just once to make it right.
You want to hit me,
don't you?
I wanna hit everything.
Fine.
Go ahead. Hit me.
Come on.
Show me what you got.
Come on, fuck me up!
Feels good, doesn't it?
If you use a crutch
too often...
it becomes a prison
of another kind.
When you first came here,
you asked me how it feels
to kill.
War has a way
of exposing demons...
deep down inside you that
you'd rather not have exposed.
But I dealt with my demons
head on...
in a room like this one.
They were all kneeling...
in a row.
Their faces will always
be with me.
I looked into their eyes...
They're still searching.
They're still hoping.
They're still asking why.
Why?
Hate...
is horribly destructive.
Hate takes over
when reason fades away.
Hate shows itself
in violence and abuse,
and the pain
of that violence and abuse
only intensifies the hate
'til all you wanna do
is strike out at something!
Everything!
I started this place
to be close to my son.
I opened my doors...
to help others
who were like Cal.
I thought...
this is a good way
to keep him close to me...
so I could protect him
from the outside world.
Well now,
I've done all I can do...
and I'm tired.
So tired.
We all need help.
Dr. Warren?
Everything okay?
Reggie...
I need you to get everyone
out of the house, now.
Deece, what...
What's goin' on?
I said now!
Everyone out!
Right away, Dr. Warren.
Give me strength, Father!
I don't wanna go like this!
Leo-Leopold, stop.
It's burning.
Everybody out now.
Get Corrina.
-Corrina?
-Leopold, get out, man.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Where's Corrina?
Leo, I'll get her.
All right?
I need you to get out
right now.
All right?
Cassandra! Sandra...
Corrina!
Corrina, open the door!
Hi.
I thought I killed you.
Who'd kill me?
Dr. Warren!
Reggie...
thanks for your service.
It's a pleasure, sir.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
-What?
-I'll be right back.
Hey!
Corrina, get down.
Get down.
Stay there.
Okay.
Yeah, let's go.
Come on.
"We all need help,"
Deece said to me...
and I knew he was right.
Milton Way went up in flames
and was never again.
After his son's death,
there wasn't much there
for him.
Maybe we were Deece's family.
We just didn't realize it.
And that's how
our journey began...
to the untamed land.
We escaped...
but that's not
what made us free.
I feel something
for the first time
in a long while.
I got this warm feelin'
in my heart...
the kind of feeling you get
after a crazy dream...
with a happy ending.
I don't wanna
let this feeling go.
When I was ready
to give up...
life wouldn't let me.
Guess it figured
I wasn't done just yet.
Destiny came knockin'...
loud.
And it all happened
right here...
on this very rock
that we breathe on.
Mama would be proud.
I'll never forget Deece,
Cal and the whole lot of them.
They will be the song
when I need to remember.