[SCREAMS]
Hi. I'm Jason Harris.
This is Joanne, my sister.
She had a neighbor, Stefan Salvatore.
He's the one who killed her
and I can prove it.
That's why I followed him
all the way from Manhattan to here.
- Welcome to the Mystic Grill.
- Hi.
I'm actually looking for
the Salvatore boarding house.
Are you sure you wanna stay there?
Why not?
Because it's the creepiest place
in Mystic Falls.
At least that's what everybody
that lives there and drinks here says.
Plus, I can ask...
...but I think it shut down
about three months ago.
What happened three months ago?
The guy that owns it, Zach Salvatore,
just kicked everybody out.
He had family coming home.
JASON: So Stefan Salvatore
has come home to his family.
Funny, because Stefan Salvatore
moves around a lot.
I did some checking.
Seventy times in the past 45 years.
Only this is Stefan Salvatore.
He's not old.
He's a vampire.
JASON:
I'm in the Salvatore boarding house.
In a vampire's bedroom.
Front door was open. Nobody's home.
At least,
nobody that can walk around in the day.
And Stefan...
...he must be in the basement,
in his coffin.
Which is good.
It'll give me time to set up
a couple surprises for him.
A few traps.
Right across from the door.
It'll be the first thing that he sees.
Garlic.
It'll soak into his clothes, make him weak.
Holy water. Purifies everything.
He keeps a journal?
Whoa.
He keeps a lot of journals.
"I saw her again today at her house.
Downtown with her friends.
At the cemetery."
I'm not letting him kill anyone else.
When he comes outside,
I'll be ready with this.
Ready and waiting.
JASON:
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. He just jumped.
Stefan Salvatore just jumped.
No. Flew.
Flew to the ground.
And what about the garlic?
The crucifix or the holy water even?
I mean, how is he even out in the sun?
Shouldn't he be up in flames?
Is this stake even going to work?
What am I doing out here?
Tracking down Dracula.
Nothing makes sense.
I know he killed my sister.
I know he's a vampire.
But if he isn't then what?
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait. What is that?
You see this rabbit?
Still wet.
Another one.
Oh, God.
It's the same.
It's exactly the same way
they found my sister.
He's still here somewhere.
I have to stop this.
The place is still empty.
Which means Stefan Salvatore
must still be out hunting.
[CLATTERING]
Hello?
He's more powerful than I thought.
And since nothing else
that I've tried has worked.
And since I don't think
I'm gonna get close enough to stab him...
...I have to be efficient.
To destroy a vampire,
you have to destroy his nest.
And the best way to do that...
...fire.
[BIRD CAWING IN DISTANCE]
Just a bird.
Wait, wait, wait.
I can't believe he saved this.
[WIND BLOWING]
[BIRD CAWS]
I didn't open that window.
[MAN CHUCKLES]
You're not Stefan Salvatore.
Why are you in his room?
MAN: Don't you know it's rude
to enter uninvited?
- Stay back.
- Heh, heh, heh.
You stay back.
You killed my sister.
You killed my sister!
[JASON GRUNTS]
[HISSES]
[JASON CHOKING AND GRUNTING]
DAMON:
Say hi to the nice people of Mystic Falls.
And now, say goodbye.