We can now confirm the mysterious freezing
conditions falling over Gotham City
are a result of an attack by supervillains
believed to be connected to the sightings
of a giant monster roaming the streets.
Scanning for target.
Target acquired.
Grandfather! No! What?
Oh, Pennyworth. I was pulling
an all-nighter but I guess I fell asleep.
Master Damian, as we've discussed
on previous occasions,
a young man must have adequate rest.
Those who wore the Robin mask
before you all...
Save the lectures, please. Like you didn't
hear about what happened last night.
Last night?
You really didn't hear? Well, don't worry.
The rest of the world has.
A guy on the street
caught it on his handheld.
I've got him, Batman.
Now that's funny.
Let's just say it's a pretty
popular clip online.
Hey, stop filming.
I do see why this has caused you
a measure of distress, Master Damian.
But the clown prince of crime has
long been Batman's greatest enemy.
It is not surprising that you
found yourself at a disadvantage
in your first encounter with him.
Disadvantage!
I accidentally leapt off a building.
If Batman hadn't been there...
I don't think he's happy with me.
I wish Red Robin was here.
It would be good to talk to someone who's
been through the Robin training before.
It is unfortunate that Master Tim's work
with his team keeps him away so much.
- But you could speak with Master Dick.
- Nightwing?
He's not really giving off
come-talk-to-me vibes right now.
Master Bruce. I have prepared tea.
Thank you, Alfred.
Studying. Good.
That's what I was trying
to tell Pennyworth.
I'm familiarizing myself
with your biggest villains.
Not good if it keeps him up all night,
if I may say.
And where have you been, sir?
On patrol. Some trouble
in the Bowery. Handled.
Hey, who is this little guy?
Oswald Cobblepot. The Penguin.
- Criminal kingpin.
- How come I haven't seen him around yet?
I sent him away for a while.
That cursed Batman.
It's all his fault. Did I deserve this?
Being stranded up here for over a year?
I just tried to make Gotham City
a more livable place for criminal...
people like me.
And the Batman always ruins everything.
I should be ruling Gotham City,
not stuck in Mr. Freeze's lab
of half-working machines.
What? I actually caught something.
Bah! Barely a minnow.
You take it, buzz.
You know, you're the only one
here I can talk to.
You understand me.
Oh, is it here?
Where did I put those things?
Oh, great. Mr. Fun is back.
What's got your thermals
in a bunch, Freeze?
Solitude. That's all that I ask for.
And yet wretched humanity
keeps intruding upon me.
Wretched humanity?
If this is your way of saying you
don't want me as a roommate anymore,
the feeling's mutual.
Just drop me off in Gotham City.
I won't take it personally.
No, not you, Penguin.
My territory has been invaded.
A new oil drilling platform
here on the ice pack?
Maybe they can get me
back to civilization.
For the 1,000th time,
you'll be much happier once
you've turned your back on humanity.
Living among them brings nothing but...
misery.
Here we go.
- What's that?
- One of my inventions.
The key to our solitude.
Our solitude? Great.
My device can transform a simple
animal like this tiny isopod,
into a monster.
Yes. We shall defend what is ours.
Come, beast!
Come on, Buzz.
We might as well see the show.
Drill coming in. Get ready for setup.
Your occupation of my land
must come to an end.
You shall return from whence you came.
Don't feign ignorance, you gadflies.
My monster.
Attack!
Now, fools, you know the consequences
of crossing Dr. Victor Fries.
Well, Mr. Freeze is crazy.
But he's always entertaining.
How could you even hope
to defend yourselves?
You are powerless.
Victor, they are roughnecks.
Obviously here to drill.
They might have...
Yeah, one of those.
Darn! How dare you defy me.
- In your face!
- Laugh while you can.
My next monster will eradicate you!
Next monster?
Victor, wait!
Leave me alone. I need to plan.
You want better monsters.
I think I can help.
How? You had better be serious, Oswald.
I have never been more serious.
However, to pull it off,
we have to return...
to Gotham City.
Is this one of your tricks?
I assure you, far from it.
What are you waiting for? To Gotham.
Yes. To Gotham.
Why so sad, Buzz? You don't think
I'd leave you behind, do you?
I need you to keep an eye
on this madman for me.
I am confident, sir, that today's
obligation to Wayne Enterprises
is present in your thoughts.
I haven't forgotten, Alfred.
The new technology showcase
at Wayne tower? That's today?
In less than 10 minutes.
Isn't that super important?
We'll never make it in time.
Yes, we will. Get in.
- Alfred, you're on logistical support.
- Of course, sir.
- When do I get to drive?
- We'll see.
- Soon?
- I hope it's soon.
- Remember,
this is going to be a Wayne Enterprises
function. So, we have to wear our costumes.
- We're already wearing our costumes.
- These are our work uniforms.
Stupid costume.
Gross! Who would eat this?
That couldn't be what it sounds like.
Hilarious, Madam Senator.
I'll definitely have to avoid that vintage.
Wow. He's so friendly.
Yeah, it freaked me out
the first time I saw it, too.
- Oh. Hi, Mr. Green Arrow.
- Watch it, Damian.
Here, it's Mr. Queen. Call me Ollie.
Sorry, Ollie. Add that to the pile
of rookie mistakes I've been making.
Yeah, go easy on yourself, kiddo.
We were all new once.
And you're training under him. That's like
jumping into the deep end of the ocean.
Bat... the boss doesn't seem
very happy with me.
Not talking much. Acting grumpy.
- Yeah.
- That's just the way he is.
Green Lantern took him
to a theme planet once.
The whole planet, one big amusement park.
I asked him how it was,
you know what he said? Enjoyable.
- That's it.
- Because he doesn't care.
Wrong. It's the opposite.
Underneath, he cares more than any of us.
He has the biggest heart of all.
That's why he has to hide it so well.
- Mr. Wayne, I presume.
- Yes. And you must be general Sam Lane.
You've done your research. I'm responsible
for the military's technology budget.
And if today's demonstration
goes as well as it's supposed to,
I'm going to make you an even richer man.
In that case,
I'm very pleased you're here, general.
Ladies and gentlemen.
If I could have your attention.
I am Dr. Kurt Langstrom,
the head of Wayne Enterprises research
and development department.
Wayne Enterprises has long produced
high tech drilling sledges
for mining in extreme conditions.
Now, welcome to the next level.
This single operator
drilling mech's plasma pincers
actually turn solid rock into lava
to safely pass through.
We designed the mech
for mining exploration and extraction.
- Alfred.
- Emergency, sir.
A break-in at Arkham Asylum.
- You mean a breakout.
- No, sir. In.
This technology could one day be used
to explore the core of the Earth,
or even other planets.
The potential is nearly endless.
Thank you for your time.
Well, Mr. Wayne.
I have to say I'm very impressed.
You could...
Mr. Wayne?
Seal off the perimeter.
Full lockdown protocols.
Get to your stations, people.
That's coming from...
Something tells me you don't have
a license to drive this thing.
No one can issue me a license,
for there is no government that holds
authority over Dr. Victor Fries.
Freeze!
Exactly.
In the name of the Gotham
Police Arkham division,
I demand you give yourselves up.
You're the best Arkham has to offer?
It's embarrassing
I've ever been kept in here.
Stay focused, Cobblepot.
You promised me what we need
is somewhere in here.
I've already spent more time among
other humans than I am comfortable with.
You won't be disappointed.
Release me. I shouldn't be in here.
That's what they all say.
What are you guys doing
trapped in that hallway?
Don't you want to be free in here like me?
Okay, freak show.
I don't deserve to be free of here.
I was going to say the same thing.
Where are the items we need?
Patience. I waited for months
in your mad scientist igloo.
You can wait a few moments more.
First on the list.
What do you two want?
Time to come with us, Bane.
Why do you want me out?
Explanations in good time.
Or we can always close you back in.
Good decision.
Chemo! We have a deal
you might be interested in.
Always impressive, Killer Croc.
This cell is vacant, you fool.
Au contraire.
Clayface, meet your new boss, Mr. Freeze.
No, you wouldn't forget little old me
in your escape plans, would you?
Because that wouldn't be funny,
if I do say so myself.
Sorry, Clown.
I already have to deal
with one lunatic on this job.
Ozzy, Ozzy, Ozzy.
You need me. I am the style.
I will put the life in your team's party.
I'd get used to your new
accommodations if I were you.
I have an absolutely awful memory, Oswald.
But this I won't forget, do you hear me?
- Why are we waiting?
- I'm scanning.
Always use caution, Robin.
Leaping into Arkham unprepared
is like going into a lion's den.
I've always loved the lion's den.
It's my favorite part of the zoo.
I'm thinking he's not great at caution.
What did I say? Checking off everything
on our shopping list was easy.
Wait. You don't expect me
to work with this snake, do you?
He sold me out to the Gotham police.
You got a score to settle?
Then let's settle it.
Gentlemen, now is not the time.
We should be on our way before Batman...
This game ends now.
Game? Trust me, we are not playing.
Really? Because I could go for a round
of pin-the-arrow-on-the-bad-guy.
Who wants to go first?
- Good work, Robin. We'll take it from here.
- Gordon? You made it to Arkham quickly.
- Kid, duck.
- You crazy?
Do it now.
- Yeah.
- This guy wasn't in my holobook.
You're learning how to be
a superhero from a book?
We're wasting time.
Great, you've trapped us in here.
You are a shortsighted little man.
Bane.
They escaped.
There are sewer tunnels underneath here.
They had a vehicle waiting. They're gone.
This wouldn't have happened if I could tell
the difference between the real Gordon
- and Clayface.
- You're still learning, kid.
I guess.
What's the big mystery?
Penguin and Freeze needed some muscle,
freed some inmates, simple as that.
On the surface it looks simple.
- You think there's a pattern here?
- The breakout wasn't random.
They skipped others to select Bane,
Chemo, Croc and Clayface.
Why them? It's not a solid team.
Bane and Croc have a known rivalry.
We don't need to know what they want.
We just need to stop them.
The key to stopping them
is outsmarting them.
Unless you have explosive arrows,
then that's the key to stopping them.
Oh, and look what I've got.
A pattern.
If this is a trick...
You will no doubt inflict
bodily injury upon me. Yes. Yes.
Your threats are de rigueur. Do not worry.
My science is no hoax.
What's that little guy's name? Appetizer?
Buzz here is my hench-bird.
Don't mind him, Buzz.
He's a mere sewer-born cretin.
Level with me, Penguin.
What are the odds this is going to work?
Victor Fries is a loony
with a monster size ego.
He's practically a hermit
and on top of it all,
he's a terrible roommate.
But he's also one other thing.
- What's that?
- A genius.
Time for the moment of truth.
Criminal history. No connection.
Known MOs. No connection.
Personality profile. No connection.
Maybe they're just recruiting
for an all-villain flag football league.
What if Penguin and Freeze didn't
pick these guys for who they are,
but instead, for what they're made of?
- Made of? What does it matter?
- Never mind. Probably nothing.
Tell me.
Well, three of them have
unusual chemical components.
Bane's venom,
the stuff that makes him strong,
Clayface's mud,
which can expand into anything,
and Chemo, well, he's basically
made of super toxic sludge.
What about Croc? He's not like the others.
No, but the strength of his constitution
would make him an ideal test subject.
Mr. Freeze is a scientist, right?
What if he's experimenting?
No offense, kid, but don't you think
that's a bit of a stretch.
- No.
- Okay. Dumb idea.
I mean, no, it's not a stretch.
- It's not?
- I was focusing on the villains' skills.
It never occurred to me to analyze
their physical composition.
Good work, Robin.
To force those kind of chemicals
to interact with one another,
there'll be tell-tale signs
in chroma-spectral scans of the area.
Got a hit. Robin, with me.
- Where to?
- Gotham Harbor.
I'll follow in a second.
In the meantime, this cup is getting low.
Indeed, sir.
It is done.
How will you know if it worked?
There's only one way to find out.
Lay it on me.
Yes. I feel it. The power.
It's time to have a little fun.
- Hey.
- It's amazing.
Hey, do superheroes get snow days?
That's a no, I guess.
Sudden weather shifts. Icy conditions.
Part of Mr. Freeze's plans, I assume.
- No doubt.
- You know, if you let me drive,
you could focus on developing
the perfect plan for fighting Freeze.
Not the time, Robin.
- You're seeing this, right?
- Like you said, Chemo's asset mutates.
Clayface's mud stretches.
Bane's venom enlarges.
But I didn't know that meant giant,
crazy monster. What do we do?
Here it comes.
Now, let's cause some chaos.
What's this? An old friend.
I should spend some time with him,
now that I've come up in the world.
- You wearing your seat belt?
- Always.
Good.
Oh, yeah? Bring it.
Hey, guys, a minute ago I was having
coffee in Paris when I saw the news.
Sorry it took me so long to get here.
What the...
There goes the Flash.
What?
Hi, Mr. Croc. Good to see you?
Goodbye for good, Batman.
It turns into a plane?
This is the coolest thing ever.
Any chance this thing also transforms
into an enormous heat lamp?
We stop the monsters,
the climate will go back to normal.
Right. Wait, monsters?
As in more than one?
Look down.
Freeze is turning
Gotham City into the arctic.
It's better than I could have ever hoped.
Soon I won't need this blasted suit
to cool me down anymore.
What did I tell you, Victor?
You were so focused on defending
your little ice cave,
you weren't thinking big.
Yes, you're right.
I have been underestimating
myself, haven't I?
Oh, yes, Victor. Look at that screen.
See all that you can accomplish.
No! Oh, my goodness.
Nightwing. Thank you.
- Oh, such a good boy.
- No problem, ma'am.
You all need to find safety indoors.
An avalanche in downtown Gotham?
Give you one guess who's behind this
and it rhymes with "sister please."
How did Mr. Freeze
get power on this scale?
Ask Batman or the new Robin
for the details.
But I, for one, never wanted
to live in a snow globe.
Oh, yeah, and then there's that.
Thanks to you, I realize
I don't have to hide from civilization.
I can turn civilization into what I want,
an ice world.
Ice world? Not everywhere, I hope.
I didn't pay for a private island
so it could freeze over.
Of course everywhere!
Now, because of you, I think big!
A new global ice age!
- He doesn't even seem to know we're here.
- Then it's time to drop the subtlety.
A barrage of missiles is subtle?
What are you doing? Isn't that
the button that turns off the jets?
- There, he noticed us.
- I think you made him mad.
You know what? Maybe I don't
want to drive this thing anymore.
Open fire!
It's not affecting him.
Smashing up the GCPD.
I knew this day would come.
Need a lift?
At least they're safe.
We would never forget you, Commissioner.
Frozen. Shining. Perfect.
A wasteland paradise.
Everything I've ever dreamed.
Cold enough to ditch the suit yet?
Yes, I think it is.
Finally free.
I am glad you are here to see
the beginning of all this, Oswald.
- You were instrumental.
- Sure. Happy to help.
But your usefulness has come to an end.
But... but we're partners.
I'm no fool, Penguin.
You wanted to return to Gotham
for one reason, to rule it.
Now that I do rule it, this makes me
your number one enemy.
Nonsense!
Perhaps, but that's not a risk
I'm willing to take.
You'll never get
the upper hand on me, Penguin.
Sorry, Victor, but I already have.
- No! No, you couldn't have.
- But I did.
The power is great.
This was worth the wait!
Nothing can stop me now!
Croc was a durable test subject.
But the others?
Do you have any idea
how unstable they are?
Do you have any idea how little I care?
And without the defenses
in your freeze suit,
there's nothing you can do to stop me.
You'll never get away with this.
Looks like he will.
Bring me the Batman.
He'll pay for putting me in exile.
And then Gotham will finally,
rightfully, belong to me.
- You bet.
- Got a score to settle first.
Hey, Nightwing.
Good to see you.
You must not be getting my texts.
- I got them.
- Oh, but...
More urgent stuff
to deal with right now, Flash.
- Can't say I expected to see that today.
- Can't say I expected to any of this today.
Come on, guys, this is Gotham.
Time to settle up, Croc.
Happy to.
Batman, it's Nightwing. It looks like
our big problem just got even bigger.
I have eyes on it, too.
We have to shut them down
before Gotham is destroyed.
- Good work, Robin.
- There you are.
What's happening to me?
Freeze's formula, it's...
He's unstable. Whatever freeze did,
Clayface can't handle it.
Here, it's the key.
- You said you wanted to drive the Batmobile.
- I kinda took that back.
I've got a plan,
but I need you to buy me time,
try to keep Clayface from destroying
the city until I get back.
- That's a pretty tall order.
- I know you can do it.
You need a ride?
- I've got one.
- Is your ride invisible?
Wait for it.
A new batcycle! Nice!
You'll have to show me
how to get the spikes to work...
He does that to everyone, doesn't he?
Even... even better!
Instead of crushing you,
now I'll burn you!
Okay, what does he usually do?
This is the ignition, right?
Can't run from me.
I don't know what I was worried about.
This is awesome!
How do you do plane mode? Plane mode now!
Oh, yeah!
Eat missiles, lava breath!
Where is he?
- Time to go to the workshop.
- Batman, it... it's not ready.
Giant monsters are loose in Gotham.
Consider this a field test.
Don't start without me.
There you are!
- What are you doing here?
- You'll see.
- The magnetometer might me miscalibrated.
- That won't be a problem.
But Batman, you don't understand.
Some of the servos are registering
at sub-optimal PSI readings.
Doctor, I've seen the specs.
I can handle it.
- Nice.
- Boot it up.
- Forget something?
- Oh, of course.
- I think that'll do.
- You ordered your own mech?
You think you're the only
billionaire in the world?
I convinced Langstrom
you might need some backup.
The Queen Industries contract helps
support research and development.
We filed a report.
Let's go.
- Welcome, Batman.
- Prepare to deploy.
Copy that. Actuator systems, nominal.
E systems, 100%. Weapon systems, online.
Wait for me.
Launch in 10, nine, eight,
seven, six, five, four,
three, two, one.
Launch!
This is one sweet ride.
Green Arrow, you're on Chemo.
Stop the freezing process.
- My pleasure.
- Langstrom, I need something else from you.
You do?
Masked freak, zero. Croc, everything.
We can now confirm the mysterious freezing
conditions falling over Gotham City
are a result of an attack
by supervillains.
Come on. That was my favorite TV!
Is that Batman?
You know, your mouth runs faster
than your brain, speedster.
Who else would that be?
What's this button do?
Oh, yeah!
- Nothing's stopping this guy.
- I've got you, boy wonder.
It's impossible to stop me in this thing.
And by impossible, obviously,
I meant totally possible.
Which one was it again?
Had it under control the whole time.
Keep Clayface from destroying the city,
Batman says. Sure, no problem.
- Robin, come in.
- Dr. Langstrom, is that you?
Yes, Batman sent me.
I'm headed your way, fast... too fast.
This vehicle travels far too fast.
Yeah, it's awesome. What have you got?
Batman has a plan for dealing
with the lava creature,
but it's only at the design stage.
Hey, Chemo.
The kids of Gotham are happy to build
snow-forts and have snowball fights in summer.
But enough is enough.
Hello, I'm talking to you.
Okay, now you're just hurting my feelings.
Let's try that again.
Which building you want, Buzz?
You can have your pick.
Who's there?
Mr. Cobblepot, you're back.
We haven't seen you for some time.
You're going to be seeing a lot
of me now. Care to know why?
Because Gotham belongs to me now.
And not even Batman
can do anything about it.
Oh, yes, meet my right-hand penguin, Buzz.
I'm naming him head of security.
Nice to meet you, boss.
Yeah, I think it's time to retire.
It will be the most powerful laser
cannon ever constructed. In theory.
Don't worry, I'm sure
we can get this thing going.
This should pull in enough amps.
Okay, that's most of the stuff.
What took so long? You've been gone
for, like, two full minutes.
Some of the things on the list
were only available in Central City.
- Excuses. Excuses.
- Here, I'll go get the rest of it.
So, Dr. Langstrom, this Cannon will be
powerful enough to cut Clayface down to size?
- Batman hopes so.
- Great! Wait, "hopes"? He doesn't know?
Well, the last time a giant lava monster
attacked Gotham was, never.
So, no, we haven't had a lot
of chances to test it out.
You think some robot's going to stop me?
Just one of your toys.
Here's another one.
I'll break your machine, Batman.
I'm going to pry open
that shell of yours, Batman,
so I can get to the soft center.
Thank you for doing
my dirty work, detective.
With Killer Croc out of the way,
I'll be able to enjoy
my dominion over Gotham.
You plan to dominate Gotham
as the Penguin's flunky?
The Penguin is a means to an end.
Looks to me like he's sitting back
and watching you do all the work.
Tell me, Batman, between Penguin and me,
who is the bigger man?
Don't forget what they say.
The bigger they are...
This day at the beach is turning out
to be no day at the beach.
Computer, are all
of these buildings evacuated?
Affirmative. No life signs detected.
- Show me which ones I own.
- Displaying now.
Good, 'cause I have great insurance.
That one needed a renovation anyway. Yeah.
You're sure it's ready to be tested?
We don't have time
to work up a better prototype.
That's a good sign.
- And that's a bad sign.
- Batman's not going to be happy.
The contrivance
wouldn't have worked anyway.
- What did you do to it?
- Nothing. The design was flawed.
It couldn't support valence co-sharing
between the bonded particles.
He's right. Should have thought of that.
No one tell Batman, okay?
Why are you here? We know it was you
who put Gotham in a deep freeze.
It was, but I was foolish.
- You're here to turn yourself in?
- No, I'm here to help.
As if. We're not getting fooled
by that old trick. Are we?
Why would you want to help us
clean up your mess?
Because it is my mess.
All I wanted was to be left alone
in my desolate land
but Penguin convinced me
to assault Gotham.
I was manipulated and then betrayed.
- I'll admit, that makes sense.
- Really?
'Cause all I'm hearing is, "I'm a bad guy.
I'm a bad guy. I'm a bad guy."
You said something about helping.
- Nice and slow.
- This is one of my arctic devices.
Coupled with your Cannon, it could be
an effective weapon against Clayface.
But what is... Oh, I see. Brilliant.
He's right, it could work.
But he'd have to help us set it up.
- Then the question is, can we trust him?
- No.
Maybe.
I better call the boss on this one.
Your mech has a back.
I bet I can break it.
Langstrom's laser's a bust, but Mr. Freeze
is here and says he can get it to work.
- Do it.
- You think you can trust him?
- Imagine being partners with the Penguin.
- I'd rather not.
Working with the Penguin
is an easy thing to regret.
Victor's whole personality
is built on guilt.
He's got enough of a conscience
to want to make amends.
Got it. Robin out.
Well, well, well.
Who knew that's all it would take?
Oh, no.
Me and my big external speaker.
Anyone ever tell you
your power is kind of gross?
Fine. How about call it a draw?
Done yet? How about now? Now?
The Flash pestering me does not
encourage my success.
So we do have something in common.
Yeah, but Flash is right.
You need to be done.
- Done in one more minute.
- Not sure you've got it.
Or we can be done now. Now's fine.
Fire!
It worked briefly,
but we need a sustained blast.
Without his freeze suit,
these temperatures could kill him.
Dr. Freeze, let me operate the cannon.
Get away from the lava.
Only I can manage the arctic device.
How much more can he take?
Your freeze suit, where is it?
I just wanted solitude.
Watch out for the acid thing!
He loves to do the acid thing.
What's happening? Hey!
Hey! I think I need that.
You cracked him?
No one's ever cracked him.
- I like what I'm hearing.
- Green Arrow, I'm trying to concentrate.
Oh, sorry. Let's see if I can help.
I think we got him.
Can I talk now? Did we win?
Mayor Cobblepot. No, Governor Cobblepot.
No, no, President Cobblepot.
No, no, Lord Cobblepot!
That has a nice ring to it.
What?
Melting?
This isn't supposed to be melting.
Where are my monsters?
What are they doing?
Here comes one now.
What?
We've stopped them all, Penguin.
It's over.
No. No. No!
Curse you, Batman. No.
Hey! You should've seen the look on you face
when we came around the corner. Priceless.
They'll be fine, once they wake up
back inside a cell in Arkham Asylum.
Almost there.
So very hot.
I found it.
- Let me help you.
- Thank you.
What's gonna happen to him?
He'll get a trial, and I imagine
he'll be back at Arkham with the others.
- He saved us.
- Yes, but I caused all this as well.
It's all right. Perhaps I can request
solitary confinement.
I might find the peace
I've been looking for.
One more.
You may have beaten me this time,
but once I'm free...
Enough!
I'll have the last laugh over all of you.
Don't forget his pet.
All right, calm down now.
What's gotten into this thing?
Remember that hole you guy's
blew out on our floor? Good news.
During labor detail,
you can help with the reconstruction.
Fantastic!
Well, well, well.
When I vowed to get even,
I had no idea it would be this soon.
What are you going to do to me, clown?
You're in that cell, and I'm in this one.
You were saying?
Not the beak!
Look, Daddy!
I'll have to replace
the forward actuators.
Clearly, new struts along the port side.
I can fix this.
Oh, no! What did he do to you?
I heard you let the new kid
drive the Batmobile.
- Yes.
- I didn't get to do that for years.
The northern lights are supposed to be great
in Finland, but they start in 20 seconds,
so, I have to leave soon.
Great working with you again, buddy.
I'm not your buddy.
What a kidder!
There's a Queen Industries building down by
the harbor that needs some reconstruction.
See you when I see you, Bats.
Batman, I know I haven't been
the new Robin for very long,
but thank you for taking me out
on this mission. I learned a lot.
Robin, I owe you. The whole city owes you.
We couldn't have done it
without your help today.
Thanks. That means a lot.
Hey, I was going to go train.
Want to come?
You can help me learn how to do those
quick getaways you're always pulling.
Okay, let's go.
Alfred, you're on watch duty.
Of course, sir.
Have you really been to a whole
planetwide amusement park?
- Yes.
- How was it?
Enjoyable.