(Man laughing)
Want to be scared?
Forget Freddy and Jason.
This is a whole
new crop of crazies
You haven't seen before.
These are movies you have to
see.
This is the only list you need.
We are counting down
50 of the scariest movies
That you've never seen.
(Female screaming)
It was the scariest
thing I had ever seen
Probably up until that point.
The whole mannequin
itself will sort of move
And then its mouth will drop
open
And just sort of scream at you.
When the creature comes,
This mutant jelly,
sausage, bear thing.
Despite the fact
that this movie
Was pulled from theaters,
Somehow it managed to spawn
four sequels.
It's like a fairy tale.
That's the greatest character
I've ever seen
in a slasher film.
There are so
many red herrings in it.
Of course everybody's wondering,
What is inside that basket?
Watch your nipples
because this baby
Likes a little more than milk.
It's in your face and
misogynistic
And it's directed by a woman!
It has some of
the best death scenes.
The whole time your
just like "No! No she's not."
"No she's not. No she's not!"
She definitely holds
his "future" in her hands.
(Laughs)
Welcome to the 50 Best
Horror Movies You've Never Seen.
A countdown of
horror's hidden gems.
We are shining the
spotlight on 50 lesser known
Yet totally amazing horror
movies that will satisfy
Even the most hard core
horror junky.
The needles in the eyeballs.
Like "Oh man."
Like your -
Really stylized, really violent.
The movie scared the crap
out of me.
It's insane.
It's terrifying.
It's pretty brilliant.
It's a very psychological
horror.
These spine chilling movies
have garnered cult followings
And critical praise and
it's time you discovered them.
So turn off the lights, lock
your doors
And get ready for a
count down like no other.
(Man screaming)
Grab some popcorn,
grab some beer, this is it.
This really are the 50 best
horror movies.
You've never seen.
You will sleep with the lights
on.
50 scary movies.
You have to see.
See this movies, they'll
scare the pants off of you.
These are the 50 Best
Horror Movies You've Never Seen.
A countdown of horror's hidden
gems.
Narrated by me, P.J. Soles.
We begin at number 50 with
Basket Case.
You at home, you
have to see Basket Case.
Oh my god, it's amazing.
It's set in New York.
It's really gritty but
it's also really creepy.
In Basket Case,
Belial is the monster
That our hero keeps in his
basket.
Hence, the Basket Case.
(Creature screams)
Finished already?
It's about a brother,
Duane, who had a conjoined twin.
Who was just a head and claws,
Just made of disgusting half
brother
But Duane loved his brother
And was totally sad that
his Dad separated them.
The father throws him
in the trash
And then our hero rescues him
And keeps him
as his pet/brother.
Belial is a little bit
on the nasty side.
One of the most charming
things about the movie
Because it predates CGI is
that it's all stop motion.
I thought that was very
cool back in the day
To move Belial, the big
lumpy appendage brother.
Had to be all stop motion and
to me it was a very cool effect.
The scene where
Belial attacks the nurse
And then jumps out the window.
Belial is sort of a mound of
just flesh with a face,
And one arm.
So to fling himself out the
window and crawl down
The side of the building
Is so creepily, blissful
That you can't help but just
love every second of it.
(Man screaming)
It's a really original idea
And it's really well executed.
I mean, you can laugh at
the stop motion animation
And think maybe it's
a little dated
But this is genuinely creepy.
It freaked me out when I was 14,
too,
Especially all the stuff about
the brother sharing everything
Including their first sexual
experiences. Eww.
It was so horribly awesome that
they made two sequels out of it.
It's my top five of movies that
I would recommend people watch
If they've never seen
horror movies before.
(Belial screaming)
Now doesn't that look
like a basket of bloody fun?
Now for number 49,
When A Stranger Calls.
If you want piss your pants
scary,
You need to watch
the first 15 minutes
Of When A Stranger Calls.
That first 15 minutes easily,
I think affected every
babysitter in America.
When A Stranger Calls is
a really fantastic little movie
From 1979, starring Carol Kane,
Colleen Dewhurst
and Charles Durning.
The first 15 minutes of the film
Follow Carol Kane as a
babysitter
Who's watching these two kids.
The babysitter's typical
girl next door, just there,
Going to do her homework, talk
on the phone with her friends
And starts getting this creepy
phone calls.
I first saw this movie
when I was 12 years old or so
And it was the scariest
thing I had ever seen
Probably up until that point,
To hear him call on the phone
and say,
"Have you checked the children?"
(Phone ringing)
Hello.
Why haven't you
checked the children?
So he keeps harassing
Carol Kane,
Asking her to check the children
And when she finally does...
Let's just say you have
to see it for yourself.
You're going to ask yourself,
did they really go there?
You have to see it
to know the answer.
Carol Kane as that babysitter
in that house,
With those phone calls
And the final moment
of that scene
Where she realizes
where the killer is
And that he's coming for her,
Is take your breath away
frightening.
The reason that
opening is so terrifying
And it stood the test of time
Is because it could actually
happen.
I thought that was
one of the best
Horror movies of the decade.
(Phone ringing)
Leave me alone!
All you baby sitters, beware.
Next up at number 48?
Silent Night, Deadly Night.
I think really bad
taste is very entertaining
And one of the films that is
the worst taste of all time
Is Silent Night, Deadly Night
Where you have Santa Claus
as a psycho.
It was only a matter of time
before somebody took Christmas
And kind of made a
horror movie out of that.
It had one of those giant
ass VHS boxes back in the 80s.
It made me feel like as a kid,
I thought I was a bad person
for watching this movie.
Silent Night, Deadly Night
is about a little boy Billy
Who sees his parents slain
by some guy
That just robbed
the convenient store
That happens to be
dressed like Santa Claus.
Even more traumatizing,
is that they sent Billy
To live with a bunch of nuns
For the remainder of his youth.
This very sinister evil nuns,
Who punish them
whenever they're bad.
The main character, Billy,
Develops a phobia of Santa
in Christmas
And also this intense sort
of thing of punishment
For anybody who does
anything wrong.
So years later
when he's forced to don
A department store
Santa outfit
And see something naughty
happen,
He snaps and becomes
this killer Santa.
Silent Night, Deadly Night has
probably one of my favorite
Kills
of the slash movie ever.
There's this two kids
that look like
They're too old to be sledding.
One of them goes down
and he's all right,
The second one comes down, Santa
Claus steps out with an axe.
(Horror sound)
(Man screaming)
You have killer Santa
in this movie,
And yet the grandfather I think
is far more upsetting
Than anything else.
Christmas Eve is the
scariest damn night of the year.
I'd be scared too,
if I were you.
It's one of the
funniest things I've ever seen.
Consider tame
by today's standards,
This chilly horror movie
Caused quite a snowstorm
when it was released in 1984.
Parents and all
these religious groups,
They were picketing the film,
They were picketing the studio,
writing letters.
It didn't create a controversy
Because it was this
horrific wholesome film.
It created it because
Santa Claus was a bad guy
And they were airing commercials
for it at like 7:00 at night
During family hour, bad idea.
People just went nuts
about the idea of something
As pure and innocent as a
character like Santa Claus
Being exploited in this way.
The movie eventually got pulled
After just a couple of weeks
release
Because just so much pressure
from all these groups.
Despite the fact that
is was this movie
That was pulled from theaters
Somehow it managed
to spawn four sequels.
Mickey Rooney was
even involved at one point,
Writing a letter to the studio.
Telling them that they should
be disgusted with themselves
For releasing this film.
Then ironically
some 5, 6 years later
Wound up in Silent Night,
Deadly Night 5
As the killer Santa Claus.
It's very disturbing,
it's cool
But there's something grubby
about it
Which only enhances
your enjoyment.
If you're in for a really
mean spirited ugly, cheese fest,
This is your thing.
Have you been good?
You'll be frozen in fear
after screening
Of Silent Night, Deadly Night,
Don't miss it!
At number 47 is every
teenager's nightmare,
The Slumber Party Massacre.
Yeah, Slumber Party Massacre,
a great 80s slasher movie.
It came out of 1982
And the funny thing about
it is directed by a woman
And written by this woman, Rita
Mae Brown, who was a feminist.
So this is going to be like the
first feminist slasher movie.
Somehow Roger
Corman gets a hold of this.
All he heard was girls,
slumber party, drill.
He decides this is going to be a
really great exploitation film.
What you end up with
is definitely not
Like a feminist parity
of a slasher film.
What you get is like a drill,
Drilling women
at a slumber party.
You've got
the group of girls,
They're having a slumber party
And then a maniacal
serial killer
Is picking them of one by one.
Brinke Stevens is a
goddess in terms of horror film.
If you want to see what led
her on the road to becoming
A scream queen,
You have to watch
Slumber Party Massacre.
You can see her star power
in this film,
And you can understand why she's
had as insane a career she has.
Slumber Party Massacre kind of
launched my career
As a scream queen
So I have a real soft spot
for it.
It came sort of at the
end of the slasher craze.
It was in the same genre as
Texas Chainsaw
Where you get some crazy
maniac with power tools
Doing terrible things
to pretty young girls.
I was surprised that
Slumber Party Massacre
Wasn't more well known.
It didn't have a Jason or
a Freddy kind of thing,
It never really got the fame
of Nightmare on Elm Street.
This movie has some of those
great, perfect slasher moments.
Like when the little sister
wants to go get a beer
Out of the fridge
And she opens it and a body -
(Horror sound)
Slumber Party Massacre has
a lot of those kind of moments
And I think that that's why
people enjoy the film so much.
In addition to the fact that
it's kind of a sisterhood movie.
It's this group of girls who
instead of breaking apart,
All kind of come together
to save each other
In the middle of this
massacre that's happening.
If you're a fan of gratuitous
nudity in slasher films
Then Slumber Party
Massacre has you covered.
There's a shower scene
at the beginning where the girls
Were like,
were talking about
Like a soccer game or something.
They're just lathering up
and passing soap around,
And it's just ridiculous.
One point in the movie,
they kill a pizza boy.
One of the girls gets hungry and
decides to take the pizza
From out from under his head.
Then she put it on his back
and eats the pizza
Off this poor dead guy.
You're not gonna
eat that dead guy's pizza!
I feel better
already, really I do.
Great, great horrible
mean-spirited scene.
Silly, fun, fluff.
I can't believe to this day
It's still sort of
one of those movies
That you know the title but
you haven't seen the movie.
Because I think people
will really be surprised
At how good and how funny
it really is
Both intentionally
and unintentionally.
All that was written and
directed by women
Which is pretty cool
For something in the
early 80s slasher genre.
You need to run out and get
a copy of this on DVD right now,
You will thank me later,
trust me.
If you like
Michael, Jason and Freddy,
You'll like the driller killer.
(Female screaming)
Now come on, that
looks like fun doesn't it?
The next movie on our
list will prove to you
That well, love hurts.
Coming in at number 46,
Valentine.
I loved Valentine
because it has
Some of the best death scenes.
Valentine was kind of an
under the radar
Kind of slasher film
That came out right
after Urban Legend
And the last Scream film
and all these other things.
So people don't really remember
it but what you have at its core
Is basically a really great
slasher movie.
It's based on
a book by Tom Savage.
The novel is incredible
And the director Jamie Blanks
Really wanted to create
something
That was true to the book
but also was
Just sort of throwback
to 1980s horror.
So he's really trying
to bring back that classic
80s slasher movie formula of
crazy killer,
Trying to kill all these girls
And stalking them and murdering
them in very clever ways.
The greatest thing
about Valentine is the script.
It's very, very well written.
It's a who-done-it
and anyone of the characters
Could be the killer.
There are so
many red herrings in it.
And throughout the course
of the movie
There's always this, "Oh I
thought it was this person"
But now I think
it's this person."
The plot centers
around these girls
That have known each
other since childhood.
There is the fat one,
the popular one,
The sexy one, the fun one.
And there's this
mysterious person
Sending them creepy
Valentines and notes.
One by one they get knocked
off and who's the killer?
Is it the cute guy,
or the other cute guy,
Or the other cute guy?
You know, you just don't know.
There's this one scene
where two of the characters
Are just sitting at home and
they get a box of chocolates,
And a card sent to them
for Valentine's Day.
So she opens up these chocolates
And she discovers
that there's maggots
Inside these chocolates
that she's eating!
(Horror sound)
You got to give it up for a
killer
That will taunt his
victims using chocolate.
Who can't have fun with that?
You've got Denise Richards as
the lead,
Bitchy, beautiful character.
She's just in this
Jacuzzi with alcohol
Lounging all fancy and the next
thing we know she gets a rose
And then she gets trapped
in the Jacuzzi.
Then he's like drilling holes
into it.
(Drilling machine)
The killer's kind of cool
because he's got this black
Kind of jacket in his cherub
kind of mask.
This cherub like mask that
really looks like an obese baby
And it's really creepy.
If you're looking for something
a little bit more like Scream
Or something a little bit
more like Urban Legend,
You've got to see Valentine.
(Horror music)
You are watching 50 Best
Horror Movies You've Never Seen.
A countdown of horror's hidden
gems.
Next up at number 45?
A baby that you won't soon
forget. Meet Grace.
Grace actually
has a lot in common
With a lot of horror films
from Japan.
Not the ghost films but
the sort of very unnerving,
Weird women going crazy
character dramas.
For me a really effective
horror movie is something
That really transcends,
And really gets on your skin
emotionally
And you cannot stop thinking
about it.
The basic premise of
the movie is that a woman,
She's been trying to
conceive for several years.
This the first time she gets to,
She gets in a horrible accident
and she doesn't lose the baby
But the baby dies.
And she makes the decision to
carry the baby to term anyway,
The dead baby, and deliver
naturally.
When she does, she asks for
a minute alone with the child
And reluctantly the midwife
agrees
And when she comes back the
baby is alive and nursing.
It's a miracle but it's not
without...
Sinister consequences.
Watch your nipples
because this baby
Likes a little more than milk.
The core idea of Grace is
to sort of create a situation
Where a woman
is doing horrific things,
That you would do in her
situation.
It's very important to me,
to not be able
To dismiss this character
as a lunatic or a kook.
She is a mother, who loves
her child as any other mother
And is just trying to
keep her child alive.
And bit by bit she's
crossing various lines
In understandable ways.
If your child is hungry
and needs something to eat
You're going to provide
something to eat
Any way you can.
(Woman in pain)
Although it is a monster
baby movie
It's not this weird,
mutant creature with fangs
That's like pulling people under
the couch and attacking them.
It's more the fact
that this woman
Has this un-dead mutant baby
Who needs to drink blood
and she sort of has
This descent into madness.
Because when the baby
starts biting her
And wanting to drink her blood
And she keeps needing more and
more blood, and fresh blood.
Then people coming
wanting to know
What's happening with the baby
And they can't see this
weird creature thing.
It's important to me to not
spoon feed you the explanation
For what's going on
with the baby.
I mean it's vampiric
and it's not alive.
But the terms
don't exactly apply.
Grace premiered
at the prestigious
Sundance Film Festival
And on its first screening
reports of fainting men emerged.
Two guys at Sundance fainted
watching this movie. Fainted!
How many people faint
anymore watching movies?
I love it that it was
exclusively men
For the little
while passing out.
I love gore,
I love horror movies.
I grew up on this stuff.
I'd like to think nothing
affects me.
Grace made my stomach
turn, I don't know why,
I can't exactly explain it.
Men are really uncomfortable
with sort of like
The female body
and their you know,
It's still
very awkward territory for men
So I just, I'm a little
bit of [unintelligible].
I don't like to punish an
audience that's irresponsible
But I do like to sort of
twist the knife a little bit.
Zombie baby
needs blood to survive.
I mean if that doesn't
make you want to see it,
I don't know what will.
It's Grace.
(Baby cries)
Ohh and you thought that all
babies were cute and innocent.
Don't miss Grace!
If you like vampire movies,
you must see the movie
At position number 44.
The cult classic, The Hunger.
The Hunger has got to be one of
The best horror features
ever made.
That movie visually is just - I
mean it's absolutely gorgeous.
The opening
ten minutes of the movie
With Bauhaus and the killing,
and then the monkey
And like it's got all
this great things,
All just jammed
in the first 10 minutes.
The Hunger is the quintessential
lesbian vampire movie.
Catherine Deneuve is so cruel,
Like she is one of
the cruelest vampires.
Who wouldn't want to be bitten
by her?
Who wouldn't want to
spend eternity with her?
She's hot! Holy shit!
A little David Bowie thrown in
And I included him
because let's face it
He's a little androgynous
anyway.
Then Susan Sarandon, I mean one
of the greatest actresses
Of our time.
Here she is, this vampire
lover and at the end she -
I can't tell you
but you got to see it!
Catherine Deneuve and
David Bowie are two vampires
And suddenly he starts having
this weird aging thing.
Where he gets old really fast,
Which I guess happens
every 100 years.
This starts to happen to David
Bowie and she picks a new lover
And it's Susan Sarandon.
Which leads to all sorts
of vampirism, violence,
And of course kinky eroticism.
Of course Sarandon
is absolutely wonderful,
Not to mention young and
beautiful in this.
It's definitely sort of a
forgotten Sarandon role.
She has this sort of remarkable
duality of vulnerable and tough.
There's a very famous love scene
Between Catherine Deneuve
and Susan Sarandon
In the middle of the film.
And it's we're seeing.
It's very bizarre,
It's just one of those films
that I think
Could only exist in the 80s.
It wouldn't happen now.
It's just bizarre and creepy
and like scene with lesbian sex,
Intercut with monkeys
killing each other.
That movie is like a
new wave, soft core, hot fest
Of lesbian vampire goodness.
There's a rumor that
David Bowie upon watching this
Has never aged.
Look at Bowie in Labyrinth and
then look at Bowie like now,
He's older but how the -
does he stay so young looking?
(Music)
David Bowie, Catherine
Deneuve, and Susan Sarandon?
Loads of bloody fun!
For the monster movie lover in
you, why not check out Prophecy
Coming in at number 43.
If you had to see one
mutant bear movie in your life
It should be the Prophecy.
Prophecy,
when it came out 1979
Was build
as the monster movie.
Stars Armand Assante
from Mambo Kings
And Talia Shire from Rocky.
Prophecy doesn't get
the credit it deserves.
It's an environmental
horror film
Long before they're making them
Is it's amazing schlocky,
late 70s killer bear movie.
In a lot of ways it's sort
of America's answer to Godzilla.
Godzilla is a by product
of nuclear testing
And Prophecy is the result
was because of mercury
And chemicals in the water
Which mutated this animal.
When the creature comes
and it is this mutant,
Jelly, sausage bear thing
Roaring around, rawr-rawr-ra.
It's so fun and endearing
and just like
"Oh my, are you kidding me?"
That you just go with it.
The bears get like huge
and mutate
And they're like running around.
They're like 20 feet tall
with like rotting skin
And just like giant - you know.
You feel bad for
the bear because it's trying
To protect its kids.
None of them are meant to
be this mutated creatures.
(Creature roaring)
One of the best parts
of Prophecy for me personally,
Is Armand Assante as an Indian.
Running around with his
bow and arrow, awesome.
The sooner the
Indian Armand Assante,
The native American going up
against the bear with his bow
That's great stuff.
(Creature roaring)
I think this movie,
coming out in 1979
Was sort of, part of that
first wave of environmentalism
That really got going
after disasters
Like Three Mile Island
and Love Canal.
Everybody was really worried
about corporate toxic waste
Getting into our water,
and getting into our food,
And turning us all into
crazy mutated freaks.
Prophecy is great,
it's underrated.
Steven King loves Prophecy,
Anybody get a copy
of Steven King's book
Where he gives five pages to it
in Danse Macabre.
When you look at Prophecy today,
Yeah it's kind of funny
and it's a little hokey.
Yeah the monster
doesn't look like
What it looks like on the poster
But once you can kind
of get passed that
It's a guy in a costume
And just watch the movie,
it works.
(Creature roaring)
(People screaming)
Who can't resist a giant
sausage salami monster?
This next movie is an
over the top genre gem
That will leave you speechless.
Coming in at number 42
is The Dentist.
I don't know about you
but Dentist give me the creeps.
We've all been to the dentist
And we all have natural anxiety
about going to the dentist.
Dentists are real people,
they're going to have bad days,
Well he has a really bad day.
Corbin Bernsen is in
it and he plays this dentist.
He kind of snaps
because his wife gets
A sweet tooth
for some other guy.
So all day long, in his office,
he's just torturing patients
That come in for their
cleanings and crowns.
(Woman screaming)
It's one of those
films where if you watch it
This-of course
it's a little far fetched
But this could happen.
Your dentist could decide to
snap one day
And just accidentally plunge the
drill half way down your throat
And cause this big bloody mess
Which your insurance probably
wouldn't cover anyway.
One critic said,
"If you've got teeth,
This film is guaranteed"
"To give you nightmares,"
and we couldn't agree more.
It's so over the top,
What this dentist does to
this people is just so crazy,
Ruthless, and bloody, and awful
That it's almost makes it
okay to watch.
You don't sit there
wanting to scrub yourself
Because you feel dirty
watching it.
You're almost like in disbelief
That you're watching
what you're watching.
You'll be covering your eyes,
You'll be doing a lot of this.
It really makes you kind
of think as you're going under
And you're in that chair
you think,
What kind of day
has my dentist had?
So it definitely, it gets
you dreading your next trip
To the dentist
even more than usual.
Watching his dentist
just flip out is so much fun.
I was hoping sequels
would come out,
Like the Construction Worker and
the Lawyer and the Librarian,
But it never happened.
There now, better?
With two sequels
to look forward to,
I suggest you start watching
immediately.
If giant rodents equate to
your idea of a good time
You will love The Food of The
Gods, coming in at number 41.
The Food of The
Gods was released in 1976
But you feel as though it could
have been released in 1956.
I mean it's definitely got
those kind of special effects.
Special effects are not what
I would call the highest quality
But in some ways that is why I
recommend it because it's fun.
It's a giant rat movie and
it was made decades after anyone
Kept making drag rat movies.
Food of The Gods is a good film
Because the animals get back
at the humans
And they grow nice and big,
it puts man and beast
At the same fighting strength.
Food of The Gods
is one of those
Environmental horror movies.
Something that's getting into
the water,
And the plants are infected
And then the animals that
eat the plants are infected
And then the animals that eat
the other animals are infected,
And they grow giant and mutate.
It's one of the big,
kick ass, killer rat movies.
The rats are being shot,
the rats are chasing a jeep.
They used real
rats in this little models
Like this little toy cars
and little toy houses
And it's so obvious.
There's this one scene where a
rooster is attacking somebody,
I can't remember who it was
but it's hysterically funny
Because it's obviously this
big paper mache rooster head
And it's kind of like someone's
throwing it at the actor
And the actor's like "Ahh,"
it's so funny.
I kind of wonder like the
actors when they signed on
I mean Ida Lupino,
an icon is stabbing
A giant rat in her kitchen
As it climbs through the window.
(Rat squeaking)
You know what, that's
kind of why you want to see it.
Because it's so cheesy fun.
I mean it's cheesy and it's bad
But the fact that
it's entertaining
And fast paced at the same time.
You can't beat it, I mean it
makes you want to run out
And get some KFC.
(Rat squeaking)
You are watching 50 Best
Horror Movies You've Never Seen.
A countdown of horror's
hidden gems.
Next up at number 40,
Motel Hell.
Motel Hell is about
the place where you check in
But you do not check out.
It is a story of a couple
that runs the motel Hello.
But when the neon sign flashes
out, it's the Motel Hell.
Oh Motel Hell, how I love the -
Let's just say best
cannibalism movie ever.
It takes all critters to
make farmer Vincent's fritters!
This people have this weird,
I guess it's a motel but
mainly it's a sausage house.
Of course their hicks because
we all know hicks are crazy.
We've learned anything from
watching horror movies,
If you don't live in the city,
You're demented and eat people
And you probably have sex with
your sister and are deformed.
Rory Calhoun is the
proprietor of this place
And his also a sausage maker.
So you can put the two together,
figure out where this is going.
Basically what all of
their guests are really for
Is not just the income for the
down payment on the hotel room
But to be buried in their
garden outback and fattened up
So that they can be cooked into
this sort of sausagy fritters
That they're famous for.
You also get to see people
planted
In the ground like cabbages
Because that, makes sense?
I think what I love
about movies like this one
Is the sense of humor.
Farmer Vincent is so proud
of the fact
That they don't use
preservatives
And then on his death bed
at the end,
The big confession
is not that he's been
Slaughtering all this people
Who come to his motel to
put them into his fritters.
It's that they did use
preservatives.
I used preservatives.
Ohh!!
You might want to look on
the back of your sausage package
To make sure you know
exactly what's in it.
Or you can just watch Motel Hell
And that will explain
everything.
Yeah, I think this horror movie
Is probably
a vegetarian's wet dream
Because you can watch it
and be like
"See, I told you!
Parts is parts!"
"You don't want
to eat that stuff."
"You don't know what's in it,"
"It could be your grandma!"
(Man screaming)
Yes folks, this movie
actually got made,
And yes, you must see it!
The next time you get lost
in your car,
You'll totally be thinking of
horror movie at number 39,
Wrong Turn.
You have to see Wrong Turn,
The whole idea
of taking a wrong turn
And ending up
in this hellish situation
Is something that I think
anybody can relate to.
We've all been lost
at some point
And this just happens to really
play up that idea really great.
It's a story about a bunch
of inbred cannibals really
That live in the woods and they
prey on people that get lost.
They're in the middle
of Virginia
And they just sort of attack
these people and eat them.
A good family movie.
These are hillbilly's from hell.
These are the kind of people
that you don't want to cross
If you're ever lost.
If you see anything
remotely looking like them,
You go the other way and run.
Wrong Turn features
a strong cast
Including Desmond Harrington,
Jeremy Sisto, and Eliza Dushku.
Eliza Dushku, I don't even
know if I said her name right
But she's hot,
it's good enough for me.
She's under a table or something
And she's watching her
friend just get cleaved.
You put yourself on those
situations and you're like,
How do I handle it
if I'm watching
My boyfriend, girlfriend, wife,
Lover, whatever
just getting hacked
And there's nothing
you could do about it.
There's this one scene where
The three surviving characters
escape
Up into this watchtower in
the middle of the woods.
Then you realize the
cannibals aren't so dumb
Because, since there's only one
way in, there's only one way out
And they're like 300 feet
in the air or something.
And the monsters,
instead of climbing up
To get them,
they set it on fire.
Oh my god.
(Horror music)
It's crazy.
So you got to see it.
Eliza Dushku in a good
bloody horror film, shit.
They should have made that
movie over and over again.
(Female crying)
(Female screams)
I guarantee you that you'll
never forget your GPS
After seeing this movie.
If telekinesis
gets you going,
Get your hands on a copy of The
Fury, coming in at number 38.
The Fury's directed
by Brian De Palma,
Who two years earlier
had made Carrie.
I think what's great
about The Fury
Is that it's got a spy
thriller element to it.
If you took a horror film
And combined it with a
summer action blockbuster
You would have The Fury.
The cast in this movie
is amazing.
You got Kirk Douglas as an
on the run government agent
Looking for his kidnapped son,
who is played by Andrew Stevens.
And you also have Amy Irving
and John Cassavetes.
Kirk Douglas' son
is a psychic
And he's kidnapped by
this government agents.
They kidnapped Andrew Stevens
because he has this power,
This telekinetic power and kind
of prime him
To work for their organization.
Basically these government
agents want to harness
The psychic powers
from Andrew Stevens
So they can use it for all their
kind of secret experiments.
So they pamper him,
they give him everything
And Andrew Stevens
becomes their puppet
Until he finds out that he
has a rival in Amy Irving
Who's younger and has
the same kind of power.
So she teams up
with Kirk Douglas
And they have to rescue
the psychic son.
Basically you've got two
people with psychic powers,
Two not just one.
Basically the Fury is
like Carrie on overdrive.
There's some fantastic
set pieces in the film.
Whenever Amy Irving goes
into a psychic fit,
Everyone around her
starts bleeding.
As you might suspect causes a
whole lot of carnage mayhem.
You can see it on her face,
Her hands are just shaking as
the power, you could feel it.
You could feel it.
There's also a huge attack
sequence
At this indoor carnival.
For the day,
it's pretty impressive.
At this point in the
movie, Andrew Stevens' character
Is kind of turned into a
psychopath.
The secret government
agency pushes him too far.
They're giving him way
too many tests,
They've taken him
away from his Dad,
Their sort of psychologically
screwing him up,
And so he gets more furious.
He just stares at
this amusement park ride
And the veins are popping out
of his head
And all of a sudden
the ride breaks,
People go flying,
screws are flying.
It's just a complete disaster.
(People screaming)
The next time you're in
an amusement park ride,
You're going to be thinking of
this scene, it's terrifying.
The camera work in this thing
is phenomenal
And it's underrated
And people just say well Brian
De Palma, well that's Carrie,
The Untouchables,
Dressed To Kill,
They mention all
of his other stuff
But that little Fury
had a big budget
And it had like all these stars.
You're going to love this movie
Because you're immersed
in that atmosphere.
You definitely got to see
it, one of the best movies.
If you like Brian De Palma's
Carrie
And you're looking for some
more telekinetic mayhem,
Then pick up a copy of The Fury.
I can make you get up.
Classic Brian De Palma,
trust me, I know.
Claiming our number 37 spot
is the cult classic,
April Fool's Day.
And I'm not joking around.
April Fool's Day
is this awesome comedy horror
That tricks you into thinking
it's one thing
And it's another
and then it's another.
April Fool's Day kind of came
late in the slasher cycle,
Came on 1986.
There was all the Friday the
13th movies coming out,
Halloween movies coming out
And then you have this fun
little campy, slasher film
Just popping out of nowhere.
It stars the 80s scream
queen, Deborah Foreman.
From valley girl, My Chauffeur,
God love you wherever
you are Deborah Foreman.
She was so cute and ridiculous
And Amy Steele was like
the tough as nails chick.
Then Amy Steele was also
in Friday the 13th part two,
So she certainly had
a genre following.
April Fool's Day enrages every
guy who loves blood and guts
And every girl who, "I like
scared but not too scared."
They love April Fool's Day!
It's such a ridiculous plot.
It's so ridiculous, it's
hard to explain in fact.
It's fun because you've
got all of this like
80s archetypal characters.
You've got the rich kid,
who has the house, Muffy.
Muffy's the real name,
I mean I figured Muffy
must stand for something.
Muffin?
Muff child, moffo,
the muffster, muffin stuff.
Muff dive.
And she invites
all of her friends
Over to this island cottage
That is huge and there's
like rooms everywhere,
And you got the jock,
you got the smart kid,
You got the rich preppy kid.
One by one they're picked off
And Amy Steele our heroine
is trying to solve mystery
And then she realize
Muffy has a twin sister.
Buffy, or so she thinks.
The plot is so thin.
Amy Steele and her boyfriend
are in the basement I think
And her boyfriend sees like
the eyes behind this painting.
Oh my god.
Amy goes and pulls
the photo off.
(Woman screaming)
That was fun.
Not to mention, what
I thought in my 10 year old mind
Was the craziest sex scene
in the history of the world.
Although it was just legs
in the air,
To me at 11, 10 whatever I
was and my mom's next to me,
It was the most uncomfortable
thing in the universe.
This movie definitely has one
Of the more memorable
twist endings
In all of slasher movie history.
I think as the audience
we were kind of like, "Huh?"
"Wait, what?"
At the end the big reveal is -
Of course we won't
reveal the ending here
But don't be foolish by
skipping this 80s classic.
Jesus!
It's so awesome,
You just get sucked right in and
before you know it,
You've sat their
for an hour and an half.
And like "Man I forgot how -
good this movie really is."
It's a lot of fun to watch.
Especially with a new girlfriend
or something like that.
Yeah, it's a little
on the softer side.
(Horror music)
All joking aside, April
Fool's Day is worth a look.
Number 36, is the salty monster
movie, Humanoids From The Deep.
Okay, listen to me, you're
going to hear about
A bunch of movies
on the special.
But if you're a 14 year old boy
And you're looking
for the real deal
It is freaking
Humanoids in The Deep!
It's sexist, it's outrageous,
It's offensive,
it's in your face
And misogynistic, and
it's directed by a woman!
Humanoids From The Deep.
Which is this kind of fun
ripoff
Of Creature
from the Black Lagoon.
Imagine if Alien, Piranha,
Creature from the Black Lagoon
Got together and then got horny,
Because that's
just what the movie is.
Takes place in
this East Coast upstate
Little small
sleepy fishing town
And they're starting to
have a shortage of salmon.
Of course this scientists
decide,
"What's a way we can figure out"
"To make the salmon more,
bigger, better?"
They start genetically
engineering these little fish.
Little did they know,
when they tried
To put this fish
in the ocean to grow
That they would
become a tasty treat
For other creatures in the deep.
Kind of
doesn't even make sense.
They also didn't know
that these little tasty treats
Must have tasted like some kind
of bacon,
Cheddar flavored pretzel
Because no female would
partake in this snack,
Only the male species
would eat this.
When you try to mess
with the fish population
Anybody whoever flunked sixth
grade science knows,
Fish like creatures from
the ocean
Sort of wash up on shore
And start raping women.
The violence is crazy,
the monsters are magnificent,
Giant beautifully designed
monsters by Rob Bottin,
Who did Total Recall and
designed Robocop.
They've got this Groucho Marx
walk and they got their -
Their really horrible sound
they make.
You know it's a rubber
suit - yeah it's pretty cool,
It's kind of creepy.
Much better than any CGI stuff
that you could see right now.
They look slimy and
real, and gross, and wet.
They're just like yeah,
you know that there's men
With costumes on them whatever
But for more than a few
minutes you believe it.
They're not human
but they want human women.
Not for killing, for mating!
(Creature roaring)
There's a scene where a
woman is attacked in a tent
And she's having sex
with a ventriloquist.
The guy who operates
Chuck Wood in Las Vegas.
They slash him to pieces
and before they can attack,
They molest her,
she runs out of the tent
And you'll notice
she's suddenly played by
A red head with breast size
About three sizes bigger
than the woman in the tent!
It's like the most fortuitous
nude scene
For no apparent reason
and it's great.
Humanoids From The Deep
is a Roger Corman movie.
Mr. Corman is legendary
in the movie business
For producing
super low budget movies
That showed tremendous returns.
Roger Corman, the king of low
budget films and making them
Huge was able to put together
this film with a low budget,
Making it look like it
was a big budget film.
The best horror films punch
you right in the comfort zone
And this one messes
with your head.
It's Creature from
the Black Lagoon
With modern day sex
and violence.
It's scary, it's creepy,
the monsters are brilliant.
First 20 minutes,
it wastes a kid,
Kills dogs,
raping women on the beach.
It's just an outrageously,
unbelievably,
Shocking, schlocky,
Great horror movie that I
absolutely love
And heartily recommend.
(Woman screaming)
(Horror music)
You are watching 50 Best
Horror Movies You've Never Seen.
A countdown
of horror's hidden gems.
Coming in at number 35, Hatchet.
This movie is great.
I love this movie.
I've told so many people
about it.
I'm a child of the
Friday the 13th generation.
I grew up on all those movies
And to me Hatchet
perfectly encapsulates
What I love about
Friday the 13ths.
If you want kills,
you got to see Hatchet.
In the past few years,
Horror have been taken over
by PG 13 movies,
Remakes, sequels, reboots,
re-imaginings, all that stuff.
Hatchet comes out and
Adam Green and his crew
Deliver this kick ass
slasher movie.
Hatchet is basically the
equivalent of a campfire story.
It kind of creates
this mythology
Around a killer
named Victor Crowley.
A group of characters
go into the woods
For this haunted swamp tour
And their boat
gets kind of capsized
And they're stuck there.
They're trying to escape while
this elephant man like killer
Is threatening to tear them
apart limb from limb literally.
Kane Hodder is probably the
most famous guy
That ever played Jason.
He's the only one that came
back to play more than one film.
This was a new icon
for him to play,
I mean Victor Crowley
is every bit as strong
And ridiculously inventive
With farming implements
as Jason was.
Adam Green wanted to
stick with the old school horror
And have blood spray
And people getting
their heads ripped in half
And crazy monster people,
and it's all practical.
Practical meaning, no
computer generated effects.
Modern horror movies are filled
with computer touch ups
But not Hatchet.
If you are just into old school,
brutal,
Viscous, nasty, slasher kills
Hatchet provides,
I think really probably
One of my favorite
slasher movie kills
In the history
of slasher movies.
I don't even want to know -
I don't even want
to give it away really
But let me just say it
involves twisting someones head
In various ways, where their jaw
sort of comes off of their head.
I mean it's pretty brilliant.
You got a head getting
ripped off,
You have arms being
completely ripped off.
There's like tendons that
are just like stretched
And you have tons of blood
spurting.
Obviously hatchets involved.
It is gory as -
in the greatest ways possible.
Now this is an actual prop
from the movie Hatchet.
I was a big supporter of
the movie when it came out
And I got a couple
of thank you's
From Adam Green the director.
This was one of them,
so it's been on my wall,
I took it down for this
but so I have the hatchet.
Secret is I think he
made about 20 of these
Because I know a couple of
other like friends of mine
That have the exact same one.
It's not a remake,
it's not a sequel,
It's not based on
a Japanese one.
Definitely the type of thing
That you should check
out with your friends
And just have a good time
and not take too seriously
Because it's a really fun
audience movie.
(Man screaming)
80s horror fans unite,
let there be Hatchet!
If creepy and quirky
get you going,
Check out our movie
at number 34, May.
May is the perfect
film that encapsulates
What it's like to be the
loner or the outsider.
May is this amazing horror
movie, directed by Lucky McKee
About a girl who essentially
goes from being
Just kind of a weird girl
Who has a fake eye, and
her only friend is a doll
To becoming a complete
psychopath.
The whole idea is that she
likes certain parts of people.
What she's doing is taking
pieces from people in her life
And putting them together
and it's kind of -
In some twisted way a bit
of a Frankenstein story.
She has a crush on this guy
and she really likes his hands
Or she meets this guy and
she really loves his arms
Because he has a cool tattoo.
She has this doll that breaks
And she kind of goes insane
after that
And decides to take all this
favorite parts
And sew them together,
As any normal girl would.
And makes her own
special best friend.
Typically in horror films,
you see the damsel in distress,
The scream queen who as a guy
we can almost safely sit back
And watch a hot girl screaming,
Yelling ultimately
get axed to death.
It's a little bit less frequent
When you say that the males
are the victims.
Angela Bettis portrays May
In a very awkward
yet sympathetic way.
She's essentially this girl that
doesn't really have a connection
With other human beings
And kind of has a crush on
the Jeremy Sisto character.
Some people
think it's kind of gross.
I love gross.
Really?
Disgust me, please.
(Female giggles)
I think one of the
most amazing things about May
Is that you identify with this
girl who's about to cut up
Her ex-girlfriend
and her ex-boyfriend
And all of these people
would make a fake person.
And I think that's amazing
That you start to identify with
her because you feel bad for her
And you feel bad because
people are mean to her
And they think she's weird
and you want her
To be able to find a friend
Even if it's a weird
Frankenstein friend.
The ending of May will
definitely leave you
With a feeling that you need to
take a shower immediately.
It's one of the most
bizarre, uncomfortable,
Creepy films I've ever seen.
It's just sort of a girl
search for her best friend,
Just kind of sad.
(Lyrics)
Do you love me now
A movie about a nut job
making a Frankenstein friend?
What else do you need for
a night of horrific fun?
Now for a a little obscure
vampire movie
At number 33, Lemora.
Lemora, a child's
tale of the supernatural.
Basically a - fairy tale.
It's about this young girl,
Really on the burgeoning
edge of womanhood.
She is roped into the clutches
Of this witchy vampire named
Lemora.
Who uses the girl's
gangster father
As bait to lure her
into the forest.
Where she would like to
have her as a companion.
The mirror is broken.
You can see how lovely
you are in my eyes.
Look.
(Horror music)
You'll feel
the lesbian instincts
More than they're showing
Which makes it weird and hot
and dark and interesting.
This movie would be
on my list of top 50 to see
Because A, it's so
beautiful just to look at.
B, it's got
the lesbian vampire angle
And if you're like me, there's
nothing wrong with that.
C, it's just creepy as hell
And it's got some
of the best vampire kills
Back when vampires were
actually evil and cool,
And they did bite people,
And they did want
to have sex with them
And they didn't sparkle.
You never really
hear Lemora mentioned.
I think Elvira probably
gave its widest audience
When she put on video and DVD.
It's amazing, it's
beautiful, it's creepy,
It's got the lesbian
vampire angle.
I mean what's not to like?
(Horror music)
Creepy and sublime,
Lemora will bite into you
And won't let go.
Looking for more
blood sucking fun?
Check out The Brides of Dracula.
Our hidden gem at number 32.
I love Hammer movies
Because they're
always so gothic
And they take place in the
Transylvanian countryside.
They have the most beautiful
actresses in them, always.
This one has no exception.
Brides of Dracula is sort
of the red headed step child
Of all the Hammer Dracula
movies.
Probably because it's the
only Dracula movie they made
Without camp Dracula.
Peter Cushing is back thank
goodness, playing Van Helsing.
But in this one you
have a creepy old estate
And of course this
beautiful young French woman
Who is traveling by
herself to the countryside
To go be a teacher
to girls school
Is intercepted and brought
to this castle.
And there is a young master
of his estate
Who's been chained up for years
Because he's a vampire.
She - silly little thing -
she let's the vampire go.
You fool, you don't
know what you've done,
You don't know what you've done!
(Horror music)
But in the nick of time
Van Helsing is there
To save the day, huzzah!
You might be noticing that not
only is Dracula
Not in this movie
But neither are his brides,
we'll explain.
Producers, I think over
the years
Have learned and failed
And learned again,
what sells a movie.
If they put Dracula in the
title, audiences will go.
What audiences
are really drawn to
Are the characters
or the actors.
It's more about this one
guy who sort of has a harem
Which is where the brides
of Dracula comes from.
His got this posse of hot chicks
that his turned into vampires.
David Peel who
plays Baron Meinster,
Somehow seems
to out camp Peter Cushing.
I don't know how he does it
but when he finally emerges
With his purple cape
and his bouffant hair
His sort of the Gary Glitter
of Dracula.
I think sometimes you just want
to have glamour Hammer.
(Horror music)
Bouffant hair,
countryside blood lust,
And gothic mansions?
Horror heaven!
Coming in at number 31 is
the hair raising Exorcist 3.
Exorcist 3 was really
a welcome movie for me
Because it made up for the
awful stench of Exorcist 2.
Exorcist 3 with George C. Scott
and Brad Dourif and Jason Miller
It's certainly
a much worldlier sequel
To the exorcist
than the Heretic was.
When this movie came out, I
don't think a lot of people
Knew it to make of it because I
think they expected
More of like the first Exorcist.
A girl with the crucifix
doing stuff to herself
And projectile vomiting.
This movie's actually more
of a psychological thriller.
Brad Dourif plays
the original killer
Who has kind of been hiding out
in the body of Father Karras
Who has gone unnamed for
the last 15, 17 years,
However long it had been
since the original film.
The priest from the first film,
he's locked away and he's crazy.
He's actually possessed.
(Doors & windows shutting)
Did you think to save
your friend the priest?
When you think about
sequels that get three's
Like Jaws 3 or Friday the
13th 3, or whatever 3 - ehh.
But this one's actually
pretty intelligent.
One thing that people
overlook about the Exorcist 3
Is that it's got a really
great sense of humor.
Father Dyer says,
"Jesus loves you,"
"Everyone else thinks
you're an asshole."
The Exorcist 3
is highly overlooked
And people do need
to check it out.
It's a very moody,
slow burn kind of film
And has some of the creepiest
nurses known to man.
It has a very powerful
atmosphere that stays with you.
It also has one of the
all time greatest scares,
In any movie ever.
One of the best shock
scenes that I have ever seen
In a movie in my life.
Probably one of the
best scares in horror ever.
That moment with the music,
everything just freaks you out.
Man did that audience
scream their heads off
And I was just as loud as
anybody else.
It's one of those scenes where
you have to check
The mirror afterwards to see if
your hair has gone white
Because it is so frightening
when it happens.
It is absolutely insane.
You see that in the theater,
remember seeing in the theater
At the summer of 1990.
The entire theater jumped and
it's very rare
You see that
in a movie theater anymore.
If you think we're going to
show you the scene,
You're crazy!
Stop the DVR, rent the movie
now and thank us later.
(People screaming)
You are watching 50 Best Horror
Movies You've Never Seen.
A countdown of
horror's hidden gems.
Up next at number 30 is the
terrifying Burnt Offerings.
Burnt Offerings is that
haunted house horror film
That came in the 70s before
the Amityville Horror.
Burnt Offerings,
That movie has a plethora of
scenery chewers to enjoy.
Oliver Reed, Burgess Meredith,
And of course the great diva
throw down,
Karen Black and Bette Davis.
Come on, you have to see this!
This family, they're sick of
being cooped up
In their city apartment
And they want to go out and
spend the summer in the country.
They find this house that's
just too good to be true.
It's this huge mansion,
just beautiful grounds.
These people move
in to this house
And it's of course owned
by Burgess Meredith
Who else would own the house
other than Burgess Meredith?
Oh I like them, Roz,
I like them.
Don't rent a house
from Burgess Meredith
That just should be a
general rule in horror.
Don't ever do that.
He can train you as a boxer but
do not rent a house from him.
Brother and sister are
renting it to them for a steel
With the only catch being that
there's an 85 year old woman
Who will be living up stairs
in her room
And only needs a tray
brought to her,
Three times a day with food.
Awesome, awesome!
When they move in to
the home the plants are dead,
The wallpaper is peeling,
the house
Is kind of cracking
and falling apart.
And things start to get a little
crazy as the summer goes on.
Karen Black is getting
a little freaky
About keeping
the silver polished.
Bette Davis, as Aunt Elizabeth,
She's getting tired
all the time.
All she wants to do is sleep.
All of the sudden the
house that's been dilapidated
And it's pretty old, whatever,
starts repairing itself.
It becomes more colorful,
the plants come back to life
And yet the characters within
the film
Are all slowly deteriorating.
When someone dies
or gets sick
The house regenerates itself.
It regenerates itself
and gets more beautiful
But it requires death
and sickness to do so.
It seems like the house
is kind of trying to kill them.
When I saw it at 7 years old,
it literally destroyed me,
Gave me nightmares.
A little boy is the only one to
kind of notice what's going on
And he's attacked by his
father in the swimming pool.
The concept that your own
father would try to kill you,
Especially to a young
child was traumatic for me.
Although Burnt Offerings
received mixed reviews,
The film won three
industry awards in 1977,
Including best director,
best actor, and best actress.
It's one of those movies that is
not afraid
To be unrelentingly grim.
There's this great running
bit
Of this evil looking chauffeur
That keeps smiling
with his sunglasses
And Oliver Reed has a nightmare
about it from when he was a kid.
This chauffeur keeps coming up
the entire time,
It's really a creepy image.
It remains one of those movies
That kind of affects you
mentally
In some way
that you can never shake.
30 years after seeing it
originally,
It still just makes me
nervous when I watch it.
(Horror music)
A murderous mansion!
Have you ever heard
of such a thing?
At number 29
is the terrifying Funhouse.
The year 1981 had I think
more horror films
Released on record
than any other year.
Every week there was an
American Werewolf in London,
A Happy Birthday To Me,
A Deadly Blessing,
And the Funhouse was right in
the middle of all of that stuff.
Funhouse was directed
by Tobe Hooper
Who did the
Texas Chainsaw Massacre,
One of the greatest
horror films ever made.
First of all Funhouse is a
great place to set a horror film
But you add this people
that run the Funhouse
And their demented, depraved,
Crazed son who's
like 8 feet tall
And wears a Frankenstein mask.
You haven't seen anything
Until you've seen Tobe
Hooper's The Funhouse.
It takes these kids who go to
the sort of ramshackle carnival
And go into the Funhouse
and find out
That it's not as much
fun as they had hoped.
The killer is sort of almost
like Texas Chainsaw Massacre 2,
Where he's abused by his father.
He's not sort of this
creature that hides
In the shadows
that you don't see,
You kind of feel
some sympathy for him.
At one point
he takes the mask off
And you get this weird
vampire mouse creature,
With his vampire teeth
that's like -
(Creature screaming)
That is not at all what I
expected under the mask,
A white haired vampire toothed,
mouse alien, albino creature?
It's a great scene.
This hulking creature is like
stalking
This poor teenagers
in this Funhouse
And at one point, she kind
of huddled against the fan
And it's rotating behind her.
He's kind of like "Oh
there's a hot chick,"
And he wants to touch her
and he's kind of like,
"Hey may I touch you?"
A deformed guy who wants
to have sex!
It's really unnerving!
The actor who portrays
him does a fantastic job
Of just having like
pathos in his eyes
And you can really relate to him
and yet still be scared of him.
(Creature screaming)
The next time you go to
a carnival or a circus
You will definitely be
thinking of the Funhouse.
Especially if you're on one of
those little rides and the cart
"Oh my god," scary!
(Horror music)
How can you resist?
Pick up a copy
of The Funhouse today.
Coming in at number 28
Is a film that might surprise
you, Halloween 3.
Halloween 3 is not like
the other Halloween movies.
There's no Michael Myers
in Halloween 3.
Where the - is Michael Myers?
Once you get passed that
and you kind of realize
That it's still a solid
little film and it is scary.
New film, horror film,
John Carpenter, Michael Myers
And you pop the tape in and
your like "Yeah, here we go!"
And then you got all these kids
With bugs coming
out of their mask.
And you're like, "All right,
where's Michael Myers?"
"Hello?"
People dump on that because
it wasn't really
A Michael Myers movie
But to me I think it's
all the better for that,
It stands out for doing
something different.
John Carpenter decided
It wasn't going to be like the
other Halloween scene.
He wanted to branch off from
the whole Michael Myers story
And then make each
Halloween movie
A new plot as things went on
With new bad guys
and new killers.
Almost turned it into
a horror anthology series
Wherever that releases new
creepy film titled Halloween.
Halloween 3 happens
to be about a mask factory
Which they're selling masks that
will kill people on Halloween
Specifically children.
You just have this really
cool, weird plot with this guy
That's essentially a horror
movie version
Of a James Bond villain.
Trying to take
over the world
But he's doing it
with killer masks
And he wants to kill
all the children.
A television commercial
played on Halloween night
Is what gives the masks
their destructive power.
At 9:00 you're
supposed to gather around
And put on your
silver shamrock mask
And watch a special presentation
Which is a doomsday device.
Which is going to trigger
a piece on your neck
That is going to make slugs
and snakes and spiders
Crawl into your head
and kill you.
You are going to be hearing
the silver shamrock jingle
Over and over again during
the course of the movie.
Da-da-da-da-da-da six more days
'til Halloween, Halloween.
Five more days
Three more days
to Halloween, Halloween.
Two more days to
Halloween, Halloween.
One more day to
Halloween, Silver Shamrock.
(Lyrics) It's four days to
Halloween, Halloween, Halloween.
Turn that down!
You will not get this thing
out of your head
For years to come,
trust me.
There's a scene about
an hour in to the movie
Where a kid and his family
sort of test out the masks
And you see exactly what these
masks can do
Which is pretty impressive.
Somehow the beam from the
TV will melt your head
And snakes and other
insects will come out of it.
It's just so mean spirited and
yet funny.
It's the key moment I think
what makes this movie so odd,
And yet so great.
My favorite element of
the film was Dan O'Herlihy
As Conal Cochran,
sort of Mr. Halloween,
Sort of a great Boogeyman.
Dan O'Herlihy is probably
one of the best horror villains
You could ever hope for.
Halloween.
The festival of Samhain,
The last great one
to place 3,000 years ago
When the hills ran red.
If you want your Halloween fix
But are totally tired
of Michael Myers,
Check out Halloween 3,
Season of the Witch.
When you go back
and look at Halloween 3,
It's a brilliant
little horror movie.
I really think
that of all the sequels
Halloween 3 has the most
Halloween spirit.
Happy Halloween.
Nothing says Halloween spirit
like an insane mask maker.
Up next at number 27, a sweet
revenge story called Hard Candy.
Hard Candy, that blew me away.
I thought that was
a really fine film.
Hard Candy is essentially
about an internet predator
That finally meets his match in
a 14 year old,
Sadistic, preteen girl.
This young girl played by
Ellen Page meets this older guy,
Played by Patrick Wilson for the
first time in this coffee shop
And they end up back at
Patrick Wilson's house
Which is very, very
inappropriate
Because she's like a young
adolescent girl
Going to this like full grown
man's house.
Like he's just so
slimy and charming and you do
Like you want to hurt him in
the manliest way possible.
What man would want
to meet a 14 year old girl
If he didn't have anything
but bad intentions.
So I guess she's going
to teach him a lesson
And that she does.
It's a role reversal movie.
He's the fly
and she's the spider
And she's just drawing him
into her web.
She's there for vengeance,
Like she is in no way
vulnerable.
She is the bad ass
in this relationship.
She is the one
that's in control.
The great thing about this
movie is its unpredictability.
Every time you think
Patrick Wilson's
Going to get the upper hand,
She turns the tables on
him every single time.
I've talked to a
lot of guys who walked out
Because a particular scene in
which Ellen Page
Is snipping off the balls
Of the male character.
She definitely holds his future
in her hands. (Laughing)
You're like watching the scene
and slinking back in your seat
A little bit more, a little
bit more, a little bit more.
The whole time you're
just like "No, no she's not,"
"No she's not, no she's not!"
Please! Please!!!!!
I love that scene so much.
Damn right, that's
right, that's what you get,
Now talk in a high voice
for the rest of your life.
Ellen Page really,
I must say pulled
A real rabbit out of her hat
With that performance.
For a girl,
it's supposed to be playing
A sadistic 14 year old.
It's really creepy
and impressive.
She's so one thing
at the beginning
And is so different
later in the film
And it's almost hard
to believe
The same actress
was playing that,
That one role.
Super scary,
Ellen Page is crazy
And you totally identify
with this super crazy girl
Who is tazing this guy
in the shower
And snipping his balls off.
It's one of the most fascinating
And interesting character
horror movies you'll ever see.
Like I think
it takes the horror genre
And kind of flips
it in a lot of ways.
You could almost see that
being a two character play.
Yeah, a couple other
characters come into it briefly
But it has that kind
of unity and intensity.
You don't get off that easy,
Jeff.
Revenge never tasted
this good as Hard Candy.
Next up, an Italian castle
with a very unwanted guest.
At number 26, Castle Freak.
Castle Freak was,
not a lot of people know,
But it was actually based on an
H.P. Lovecraft story
Called The Outsider.
This is a movie that
scared the shit out of me
When I was like 18.
Jeffrey Combs and
Barbara Crampton as this couple
Who inherit
an old castle in Italy,
Which turns out to have this
hideous monster in the basement.
They get to the castle,
everything's great honey,
We love it here
but there's a freak.
The monster is actually
this fellow named Giorgio
Who had been chained
up there since a child.
And sort of has become this
ghoulish creature
From lack of sunlight
And being beaten with
a cat and nine tails
By his psychotic mother,
And fed horrible things.
He's only ever
like lived chained
In a basement of this old
Italian castle.
Then on day his chain breaks and
he terrorizes the people
That had moved in the castle
and their blind daughter.
I remember I was watching this
with a boyfriend at that time
And I was like
"Oh my god, this movie's
Actually really terrifying."
(Woman screaming)
Then after the movie was over
he started doing this thing
Where every time he
looked at me he'd be like
"Ha-yey ba-den."
I was like, I'd be like
"Stop it, that's not funny!
It's not funny!"
And I would like get really
upset.
It is a fun
effective scary little film.
There is an action figure
that exists
And you can have your
own castle freak.
Rip off nipples or do whatever
castle freak does,
Eat cats and do all the things.
Kids out there, get your
castle freak figure.
What you see is what you get.
It's castle freak,
there's a castle,
There's a freak in the castle.
It's scary.
(Woman screaming)
You are watching 50 Best
Horror Movies You've Never Seen.
A countdown of horror's
hidden gems.
Claiming the number 25 spot,
a fright fest called Feast.
John Gulager's Feast
is one of the most
Splattery movies
you'll ever see.
It's one of those
great creature features
That has a really cool monster
But at the same time it's got
a really great sense of humor.
Ben Affleck and Matt Damon
started this thing
Called Project Greenlight
Where the TV show would detail
the production
Of a low budget film
And then at the end of the
season,
The film would come out in
theaters.
The first two time around,
the show was great,
Movies kind of sucked.
Feast comes out, the show
was great, the movie's great.
Horror fans got to sit and
watch as they made a horror film
From behind the scenes,
especially
What's creative involved.
For Dimension Films at that
time, it was really cool.
The fact that no one
really even saw the movie
Has always been a big
disappointment for me.
We designed Feast to kind of be
like old Peter Jackson movies
Or old Sam Raimi movies where
they're really stylized,
Really violent but really funny.
It's about a bunch of monsters
that attack
All this people in a bar.
The bar in the middle
of nowhere.
And then the door kicks in and
there's this guy running in
And his going like
"batten down the hatches"
And his got something
in his hand.
It's the head of one of these
guys, and it's been chopped off.
And they're relentless,
and they swoop down on this bar
And they break in and they start
attacking people left and right.
They batten down
the hatches and stuff.
Basically everybody knows,
don't stand by the window
But you think, well maybe
this guy has it down.
His got a shotgun and
he's going to save the day
And his right in the middle
of saying something like
"I'm going to save your ass."
Then he gets ripped
out the window.
I'm the guy that's
going to save your ass.
I don't even know how you
can describe
The creatures in Feast.
The creatures in Feast
are - they're horny.
The monsters have penises.
The monsters in Feast
will - you and kill you
And not always in that order.
There's a big scene where the
monster's penis
Gets stuck in the door and they
chop it off
And
it bounces down the stairs
And it's kind of almost,
seems like it's alive
And it gets squashed and it
squirts all over the camera.
We wanted to go that extra step
And have it be a little
unsavory.
That approach worked
and the Feast
Franchise cranked up
two more sequels
That served up
the same unsavory fun.
Jenny Wade in the Feast movies
Is sort of like
Ash from Evil Dead.
Over the course
of the three films,
She gets every
single bodily fluid
Tossed, gunked, everything
you could possibly do
To this poor woman
across three movies.
Basically if it's a liquid
it gets splashed
Across somebody's face.
It's just wall to wall stuff
like that,
You'll never ever know exactly
What will happen next in
a Feast movie.
Any horror fan who's getting
Into horror would love this
movie.
To me it's like the
Evil Dead 2 of this generation.
And they do the
same tricks all over again
And surprise you all over
again in Feast 2 and 3.
(Woman screaming)
It's a Feast for the senses,
isn't it?
Rent this, now!
And if you like a good dose
of humor with your horror,
Try out Slither at number 24.
And the award for best use of
an Air Supply song
In a horror movie
goes to: Slither!
Slither is an awesome movie,
I will just say that right now.
I love that movie.
The plot is, an alien
lands on earth,
Wants to take over the world
And kill everyone and eat
them, or impregnate them
And the towns folk are just
trying to stop it
From destroying
the entire world.
Of course it happens
in a small town
Because it always happens
in a small town.
Grant who's played
by Michael Rooker
Goes to investigate and
ends up being infected.
He starts to mutate into a
creature.
He goes on this meat lust
Where he's like in the
supermarket
Looking at stacks of ground
beef and just going "Meat."
Meat, meat.
It brings back
what a lot of horror films
I think have been missing in
recent time and that is humor.
A lot of people
are caught off guard
With the fact that Slither
was a horror comedy
Which at the time
was sort of taboo.
It's unfortunate that it kind
of got lost in the shuffle.
A lot of people instantly
see the slugs
And they're like "Oh I don't
like bugs."
But it really is one that not
everybody see and it's so good.
What makes this different
is the direction of James Gunn.
His execution of this story
was brilliant.
James Gunn decided,
"Look we're not going to take
ourselves seriously"
"Because this story is
ridiculous."
"So we're just going
to make a completely campy,"
And tongue and cheek,
And fun,
and yet scary and creepy.
Of all the
movies on your list,
Slither should be
at the top of your -
I haven't seen this yet
but I really should.
James Gunn? Props, man.
(Man screams)
Slither serves up
sensational slimy fun.
Love a good gore fest? Check
out Inside at number 23.
Inside is so disturbing,
It made me not want to have
a child, personally.
I hope I never get pregnant
after watching Inside.
Essentially it's a home
invasion movie
With a really - up twist.
The cool thing about Inside
Is that the title actually has
two meanings.
Obviously that's
the obvious one, inside,
She's trying to get
inside the house
But there's something else
she's trying to get inside
And I think I'll let the movie
speak for itself on that one.
You go in thinking
that it's going to be
A creepy killer kid movie
And a baby that maybe is like
Rosemary's baby or the devil
And it's really not that at all.
It turns out to be a real
cat and mouse thriller.
You take this most
seemingly simple concept
Of a woman alone in her
house on a Christmas.
Then somebody shows up.
In the middle of the night, she
gets a knock on the door
And its a woman who says,
"Oh I need to use your phone"
And then tricks her way in.
There's this one scene
where she's watching TV
And the crazy lady comes out
of the shadows from behind her.
Then it becomes this extreme,
brutal -
It's maybe one of the
goriest movies ever made.
The amount of
gore is just astounding.
I mean it's really Grand Guignol
And it brings back
the French tradition
Of the theatricality
of the gore.
Inside is about
two women battling.
When you put two men against
each other
It gets very testosterone
driven.
It's like "Oh you man up -
I can get you -"
Your dead bro - I'll kill you."
But when it's women
against each other
It gets like a mother
tiger protecting her young.
It gets very much like
"Oh this it, you're done."
When it gets
to the blood bath stuff
By the end you're almost
like numb to it
Because there's so much blood.
One of the key
scenes in this movie
Is where this woman has to
give herself a tracheotomy.
I have to say tracheotomy scenes
get me right here every time.
Inside has one
that tops them all
And it's really,
really cringe inducing.
I don't think anybody
was prepared for how gruesome
And how out there
eventually it got.
Make sure when you watch Inside
that it's the unrated version
Because the rated version
is 10 minutes shorter,
That's how gory and
gruesome this movie is.
It's a viscerally,
brutal, relentless movie.
I mean it is not
for the faint of heart
But if you want something
that is just raw hard,
It delivers the goods.
It will stick with you.
There's no ghosts,
there's no creatures,
It's two women
fighting each other
With anything
they get their hands on.
Pencils, scissors, axes,
knives and it's gruesome.
Whenever anyone asks for me to
recommend a great gore movie,
My first instinct is to
recommend Inside.
(Woman screams)
A bloody good time all
right, only for the brave.
If you're in the mood
for total creepiness,
Check out Tourist Trap
at number 22.
Tourist Trap revolves
around just that, a tourist trap
Which is sort of a roadside
attraction
That you might encounter
while driving down Route 66.
Like crashed UFO sighting,
Look at our little aliens
in little jars.
It's one of those sort of stop
here for a break and some gas
And some food and
here's the tourist trap.
It's where the tourists are
trapped into buying stuff
On the side of the road.
Tourist Trap
from the late 1970s,
It's got some creepy
mannequins in it.
Our heroes sort of
converge at this tourist trap
Which run by the incredible
Chuck Connors.
Chuck Connors
has a weird brother
And it's the brother
whose hobby
Are this mannequins
that he makes.
He puts on masks
and different hair.
Probably the scariest masks
I've seen in a horror movie.
It's kind of those
half masks which cover
Just about half your
face except your mouth.
He's killing people and
turning them into mannequins
And then dancing
with them and doing -
God, who knows
what he does with them.
To him this is normal
and this is a way to keep
The things that are - that
means something to him.
Some kids that were on the
wrong place at the wrong time,
Wind up falling victims
to a telekinetic mad man,
With a split personality.
It's really, really creepy
And actually kind
of hard to describe.
It sort of needs to be
seen to be believed.
What really sells that though
are those marvelously demented
Mannequin things
throughout the movie
That are animated by telekinesis
And their jaws drop open
and they scream.
The whole mannequin
itself will sort of move
And then it's mouth
will drop open
And just sort of scream at you.
It's just so dementedly weird.
Even the king of horror,
Stephen King,
Praised the movie in his book,
Danse Macabre.
Claiming it wields
an eerie, spooky power.
Anytime someone in this movie
Like fights back or
tries to get away,
All the mannequins start
making these weird noises.
(Screaming)
It's kind of neat and it's
really beautiful in a way.
Even though it's very creepy.
Creepy little film you know.
To this day,
I can't stand next to
A realistic looking mannequin
In a department store.
I know that that sounds
silly for a guy who's 39
But that's how effective that
movie was in terrifying me.
If you don't like mannequins
you will love Tourist Trap.
(Horror music)
(Woman screaming)
Tourist Trap is a creepy
little classic
That you'll never forget.
Now get ready for another
genre classic,
Trilogy of Terror,
next at number 21.
The Trilogy of
Terror film is so great.
It's an anthology film and
anthology films
Are made up of shorts
That are strung together
into a feature movie.
The Twilight Zone,
the Creepshow movies,
All of those
are anthology films.
Well, Trilogy of Terror
was one of the first
And it's also one of the best.
Karen Black stars in each
one of the three shorts
That are in the feature film.
Nobody ever remembers the
first two shorts, nobody.
You ask them, "Have you
seen Trilogy of Terror?"
And ask them to talk about it,
They will always talk about
that third and final story.
You really have to
hold out for the third chapter
In the Trilogy of Terror.
It's a story about
a doll coming to life,
Not just coming to life
but being
Extremely violent and murderous.
The Zuni fetish doll,
little African doll
With the long hair and a
spear, and his about yay big.
And he starts chasing
her around her apartment.
Basically the idea is that
if the necklace
That its wearing falls off,
It comes to life.
She sets this doll down
And the little chain
falls off it
Onto the coffee table.
Next thing you know,
this little warrior doll,
His got this teeth, these fangs
And he's all dressed up
as a warrior,
And he's got the spear
and he comes alive.
What I love
about this film is that
There are absolutely no
computer generated effects.
This movie didn't have any CGI.
This was a little African doll
with a spear
That was actually
animated somehow
To run around after Karen Black.
You didn't need CGI because
there was Zuni fetish doll cam.
So the camera
is at that level chasing
Her kind of nipping
at her heels,
Nipping at her ankle.
It just charges
after Karen Black.
I mean it's like
she's a piece of meat
And he's just trying
to kill her.
Any which way
that he possibly can.
He's really
viscous and very mean.
This little doll
is out of control.
There's a scene where
she throws him
Inside this little suitcase and
you think,
Well thank God
it's locked in the suitcase.
Until you see this little sword
come out and cut his way
Out of the suitcase.
And he works so hard
at everything, "Hee-hee-hee."
He's just so determined
to kill her.
And you think it sounds silly
But I'm telling you it's
a huge impact on you,
You'll never look at
little dolls the same.
Long before Chucky from Child's
Play hit the silver screen
There was the Zuni fetish doll.
(Creature screaming)
(Woman screaming)
You are watching 50 Best
Horror Movies You've Never Seen.
A countdown of horror's
hidden gems.
Up next at number 20
Is a prickly little gem
called Splinter.
Splinter is this movie that not
a lot of people have seen yet
But it's super, super creepy.
Some reason just thinking
about it, I get chills.
That thing with the spikes and
the thing -
It's just weird,
and creepy, and gross.
Splinter came to
me actually as a script.
It was originally
called Tooth and Nail.
It reminded me a lot of
all the great horror movies
I loved as kid.
The very sort of contained
siege based movies like,
Dawn of the Dead,
Alien, The Thing.
Movies where people are
trapped in a situation
And have to deal with
whatever's attacking them.
Takes place at a gas station
And these people
are stuck inside
Of the gas station
convenient store
And there's this monster outside
that is pretty relentless
And it's trying to get on in.
What is the actual creature
itself
And really there
is no creature.
There is no entity, it's
basically a substance.
If it touches you,
you sort of get infected by it.
The core of the idea
for the creature
In Splinter came from
is that it infects you
From the inside
and takes over your body
And takes control of
your skeletal structure
With no regard for how
your body normally works.
It's not a vindictive creature,
It just wants to survive
in propagated species.
As long as it has something to
eat off, it will stay alive.
Splinter features some of
the best special effects ever.
It's absolutely incredible.
There's a scene in the movie
where one of the characters
Gets infected
at the top of his hand
And they need
to remove his hands.
So, I mean how do you do that?
You cut it off but if you
don't have necessary tools,
You have to break it off.
So Splinter has one of the most
disgusting arm removal scenes
You will ever, ever, ever see.
The idea of this severed hand
running around and chasing them
Is kind of funny but It's
also just kind of terrifying.
I mean the thing is really
coming at them.
Go! Go!
I really like that scene.
It's kind of the fun break in
horror movie
That the audience really needs I
think at that point in the film.
And It's a crowd pleaser,
it's a lot of fun to watch.
Go see Splinter, okay?
Rent it, NetFlix it.
Every time you think that
you have them figured out,
It kinds of veers laughter,
veers right.
Really, really cool, really
dark, really strange.
Run.
I just love a movie that
gets under your skin, don't you?
If you're looking for bone
chilling scares
Look no further than
Session 9 at number 19.
Session 9 is about
a group of guys.
They're an asbestos
removal team.
They go and they
take this asbestos out
Of this huge abandoned
mental hospital
And they go in and they
start working on this thing.
And they're in separate wings
and it's a place
That's absolutely horrifying.
One of the guys finds
a box that says, evidence on it.
Inside this box
are all these tapes,
Prerecorded interviews of a
patient that used to live there.
I think it was patient 444
And it's all of these tapes
marked session one, session two,
Session three,
and there's nine of them.
I was watching the
movie in my bedroom one night.
My wife is asleep next to me.
In the middle of the scene where
he's listening
To those really slow tapes
and all that stuff.
My wife kind of woke up in
the middle of a nightmare
And she said, "What the
hell are you watching?"
"What is this movie?"
What happens to this crew
after listening to these tapes,
It's like this energy is
summoned inside this asylum.
It starts to sort of affect them
And they start to crack up a
little bit.
Each guy is kind of
living in his own nightmare
And the movie just absolutely
blew me away
Because they did
so much with so little.
It's got all the
atmosphere of the shining.
It's got all that, what's
around that next corner.
It's just harrowing
from beginning to end.
Everything that's scary
about Session 9 is in your head
And it's got
a great reveal ending.
With a lot of reveal endings,
they're kind of groan worthy.
The audience goes, "Oh my
god, are you kidding me?"
If you make it through the movie
and you get to that last line,
I mean, I will
never forget that.
That line is always
running through my head.
So - twisted.
I don't know anyone
that has seen this film
But every time
I bring up horror movies,
I tell people to see this movie.
You have to see it.
(Laughing)
Happy nightmares everyone.
Up next at number 18
is Ginger Snaps.
The movie, not the cookie!
There's [not] a lot
of great werewolf movies.
American Werewolf in London,
The Howling, The Wolf Man.
They kind of peak with those
And then There's kind of
nothing that comes close.
I would actually
put Ginger Snaps
In that same league with
those great werewolf films.
Ginger Snaps
is about a teenage girl
Who's a ginger who changes,
turns into a werewolf.
It's coming of age story
Except it involves teen girls
and werewolves.
It was really interesting seeing
that metaphor
For the beast inside.
You know, and like seeing this
woman confront her sexuality
Through the act
of becoming a werewolf.
That is like the greatest
movie metaphor
For female puberty ever.
It reminds me of when I was
a teenage girl
And I got my period and I turned
Into a werewolf and
I started killing teenage boys.
So here was a really
unique interesting take
About two sisters named
Bridget and Ginger.
They're kind of outcasts,
they're kind of rebels.
They stick together,
they're the best of friends
And they sort of like hate
everybody else.
They're kind of misanthropic
and living
In their own little world.
And Ginger gets bit
by a werewolf
And her little sister who
is more the main character
Sort of tries to get her
to quit killing people.
But also the main character's
name is Ginger and she snaps
But I love, I love a pun title.
These two girls are
not normal to begin with
And on top of that,
now the older one's
Turning into a werewolf.
All of a sudden boys are
attracted to her
And they want to take her out
And she doesn't
really know how to do it
Because she's always
been a weird girl
Who didn't like boys and
boys didn't like her.
And then all of the sudden
she's ovulating
And they find her
more attractive.
Ovulating meaning
she's a werewolf.
It's actually
a really sweet movie
Even though It's about a high
school girl tearing out throats
And like having six nipples
as a werewolf.
Six or eight.
I don't know, is it weird that
that still looks sexy to me?
When you talk about
transforming,
It's not like American Werewolf
in London
Where it's just like a two
minute sequence
Of her rolling on the floor
And growing fangs
and fingers growing,
And nails getting longer.
It's a slow process that
she grows like a tail,
She starts getting
a little hair.
It is really a
vicious and dark movie.
It really explores
the relationship
That these two girls have
And how far is one willing
to go to help the other
And how far can they
really trust each other
When these monstrous
elements come out in them.
It's a really amazing
way to look at that.
You're both a girl still but
you're also a beast in some ways
Once you hit puberty.
You're mauling men.
That's what happened to
me when I hit puberty.
I started mauling men in the
back of cars.
Normally It's the wolf MAN.
It's men playing werewolves,
but this is really great
Because it was seen werewolves
from a female perspective.
Any teenager growing up that's
looking for
New horror films to check out,
Ginger Snaps is definitely one
of them.
It's part of growing up when
you're dealing with all
These different sides of
yourself
That you discover as you get
older.
Hers just happens to be like
covered
In hair like the major fangs.
(Werewolf roaring)
Werewolf movies just don't
get any better than this.
If creepy religious children
spook you
Then check out Alice
Sweet Alice at number 17.
Alice Sweet Alice overall is one
of the scariest movies
I've ever seen but nobody really
remembers it
At least in the current
generation.
Alice Sweet Alice
takes place in the 60s.
It's about a mother that's
preparing her younger daughter
For her first communion
And the other sister
is jealous about this.
Besides that she's going to
start being mean to her sister.
Her own parents are
afraid of her
But there's an added
element to it
And that It's highly Catholic.
Nothing's creepier than the
creepy music
And a girl whispering.
Hail Mary full of grace the Lord
is with thee, blessed are...
And just over and over again
as the titles are rolling.
The murders
in Alice Sweet Alice
Are among the most gruesome
I have ever seen and even 30
years after the movie was made
They remain shocking.
That's a big part of the
power behind Alice Sweet Alice
Is the intensity of the kills.
The girl who plays the killer,
She puts on this sort
of clear mask.
That transparent
mask with a blue eye shadow
And a rouge around the
cheeks and the red lipstick.
And it's transparent
and you kind of see it
But you really can't see
who's behind the mask.
She's creeping through
the church
And you know that It's her
from the very beginning.
It's almost like Rhoda
in The Bad Seed
Where you know that she's bad.
This rage keeps
building up in the sister
That she ends up killing her
9 year old sister
Who's played by Brooke Shields.
Brooke Shield screams
and the mask is pulled out
And there's an even creepier
mask.
(Horror music)
(girl screams)
You don't expect to see violence
done to a child like that.
It's like, wow,
it broke some taboos.
That's when
the body count starts.
Everyone who's amongst that
little cast of characters
Is being killed off one by one.
The whole town is just so
surprised that this has happened
In this small community and It's
a search for who this killer is.
This whole movie,
every character,
Something's wrong with them.
Also worked well
as a police thriller
And mystery at the same time.
This one is the one
that is not as famous
As The Bad Seed
or Audrey Rose,
Creepy Kids, movies like that
the people have heard of.
Not many have
seen Alice Sweet Alice
But It's definitely
worth looking.
(Creepy music)
Now that little girl
makes the skin crawl.
Don't miss Alice Sweet Alice.
Next up at number 16 is a movie
you'll remember
If you're ever hospitalized,
Visiting Hours.
There was this sub
genre in the early 80s
Of news women reporters in
danger.
There are movies like
Eyes of a Stranger
And The Howling
and The Seduction,
And the list kind of goes on
and then There's Visiting Hours.
I think people were going into
it expecting another
Jason or Michael or whatever
like that and it wasn't.
It was actually
like intelligent adults
In intelligent situations.
Visiting Hours is kind
of a rip off of Halloween 2
Where you have the serial killer
who just has to get
Into that hospital
and terrorize the nurses
And patients,
and the anchor woman
Whose love interest is played by
William Shatner.
Always a plus!
In Visiting Hours, Lee
Grant plays an anchor woman
Who's very opinionated
and very strong.
For some reason we don't know
at first why
But really in theory It's
Michael Ironside
Who plays our killer.
He's got some personal
vendetta against her.
So he stalks her, injures her
in her home
And then she's
sent to the hospital
Where he stalks her more
during the visiting hours.
Unlike the other
80s horror films,
Like Michael Myers or Jason,
Michael Ironside is this
character that is out front
You know who this guy is.
This wasn't a faceless killer.
This is someone you
meet right away.
You see what he exactly
looks like right away.
You go to his apartment
and you see where he lives.
You follow him around
like he's an ordinary guy
Which actually makes it
terrifying
That this guy could be
any person on the street.
Yeah, you don't want
to run in to this guy.
He just sort of
wanders in whenever he wants.
He pretends to be a well wisher,
He even hurts, injures himself
so he has to go to the hospital.
(Glass breaking)
He mutilates his arm by
taking a bottle, smashing it,
Giving him some really bad cuts
To get him admitted
into the hospital.
Sure enough they take him in
and he's couple of rooms down.
He's in there for a few minutes
and then decides
To go
look for good old Deborah.
(Horror music)
(Woman screaming)
There's that amazing scene, he
goes after her children.
And It's just one
of those great moments
Where the little kids
are woken up
And they're at the top
of the stairs
And he's just looking at them,
Coming up with them
with a knife.
And you're thinking wow,
this movie is going
To take that turn.
(Horror music)
It's one of those great movies
that you remember
The next day when you wake up.
And you're like yes, that
movie stays with you.
(Horror music)
You are watching 50 Best
Horror Movies You've Never Seen.
A countdown of horror's
hidden gems.
Next on our list at number 15 is
the black and white masterpiece,
Repulsion.
These producers came to
Polanski and they were like,
"Can you make us a campy,
shitty, horror movie?"
He was like "Oh yes, of
course, you know, of course."
And then he proceeded to like
go completely over budget
And make this completely
insane like bizarro art movie.
Roman Polanski's Repulsion
is about sexual repression.
It's about a woman who stays
cooped up in her apartment
For too long and goes nuts.
Catherine Deneuve plays
this gorgeous young manicurist
Who is integrated with
her sister to London.
And she's the object of desire
of every man
Who sees her naturally
but she has this
Like weird frigging repression
thing going on.
She's in every frame
And she is what you're watching
the entire time.
And it's her descent
into madness
Once the sister
goes away for the weekend.
And she's begging the sister
"Please, please don't go.
"Please don't go." And you're
thinking,
"Why not?
What's the matter with you?"
And yet once the sister goes
and then the guy
That has been pursuing her
finally says,
"I'm going to
just go over to her apartment,"
And then everything goes
downhill from there.
I don't want to spoil it
for people
Who are wanting to watch it
But she does some really
terrible things
That start to happen
once this guy comes over.
In her mind I think she thinks
sex is probably
The last thing she wants to do
And she would rather die
or kill somebody
Than be subjected
to what she hears
Often times her sister
doing in the next bedroom.
It's a very
psychological horror.
Watching an environment's
transformation
Mirroring the protagonist
is fascinating for me.
For instance Carol was left in
the apartment alone
With this rabbit and she puts it
Back in the refrigerator
And then once her sister
leaves for the weekend,
For some reason she takes
it out and we think,
"Oh, she's finally going
to cook that rabbit."
"Can you eat it please or
throw it away?" but no.
She puts it on the floor
in the living room
As the scene progresses
and the days go by,
Bugs and
flies start buzzing around it
And there's always this rabbit
laying there bloody on the plate
And it's disgusting
and horrifying
And makes you very squeamish.
Many directors cite Repulsion
As being influential
on their work.
Among them Darren Aronofsky,
director of Black Swan
And Lucky McKee director of May
Which also happens to be the
number 34 movie on our list.
It would have been a film
that would have interested me
Because my father always told me
I looked like Catherine Deneuve.
So I think I wanted
to see the movie
Because Catherine Deneuve
was in it.
The best most beautifully
shot portrait of someone
Descending into madness
that I or you have ever seen.
It's still crucial viewing for
anyone who considers
Themselves horror film fan.
(Hammering sound)
What's that saying again?
Paranoia will destroy ya?
If you think hidden cameras
can't be scary, think again.
At number 14 is Alone With Her.
Alone with her is about
this guy played by Colin Hanks.
Colin was at the top
of my wish list from day one
And when I heard that he liked
the script, I was thrilled.
So we met and what was great
about working
With Colin among other things
Was that we saw the film
in the same way.
I mean he was as excited to
bend some rules as I was.
It's a voyeuristic
stalker movie.
He's kind of trying to
infiltrate the life
Of this girl that he likes.
It's kind of put together from
surveillance camera footage,
Cameras that he wears
on himself.
So you the audience gets to
kind of partake in the voyeurism
Of how he kind of
stalks this girl
And becomes a part of her life.
This movie is very,
very inventive
In a way that it uses
the camera.
It's very much a
first person perspective
We're seeing her
through his eyes.
So for example when he meets
her in the coffee shop,
It's the black and white shots
Where he's wearing on his
person.
And here you can see her looking
right into his eyes
And speaking to her.
It was nice talking to you.
Yeah, I guess
I'll see you around, huh?
Yes.
I can't wait to hear
about your taste in books.
Yeah.
He uses information as a weapon.
In other words he makes up
for whatever disadvantages
He has as a person.
Even he has no self confidence,
he doesn't know what to say
Or when to say it but he uses
An informational advantage
to compensate for that.
And he gets the information
through surveillance.
And the way that he implants
himself into her life,
There's scene where
she tells him,
"I'm going to go stay with
my parents for a few days."
And while she's gone, we see
him on his hidden cameras
Like sleeping in her room.
He sneaks into her house,
he goes so far
As to make her dog disappear.
Kill her best friend.
Break in, put glass
all over the floor
And so it's dark and she
comes home and she steps in it
And then she has to call him.
He does a really good job
being an abuser
And pretending like
he's the white knight,
And coming to save her.
It's kind of a low
budget independent film
That a lot of people didn't see
that shows how much you can do
With kind of just being creative
with cameras.
The reason Alone
With Her is on this list
Is because being stalked
like that is very real
And I'm sure it happens a
lot where people break in
And install cameras
and then slowly watch.
It's scary, it's like,
who can you trust?
The technology has
only gotten better
Since I shot the film in 2005.
These micro cameras are
everywhere
And it's really scary.
I mean I think anyone looking
to do this,
The equipment is out there
and anyone can get it.
After you watch Alone With Her,
You're kind of looking up
and like
"Hmm, where could someone
possibly put a camera?"
We were trying to do
Something different
and innovative.
It's very scary and It's
Really effective
and it draws you in
And the ending is pretty
unforgettable.
(Static sound)
If you find yourself
searching for hidden cameras
After watching Alone With
Her, I won't make fun of you.
Next at number 13 is
a gritty vampire movie
With a cowboy flare, Near Dark.
Near Dark has to be one
of my favorite movies ever.
Near Dark was
directed by Kathryn Bigelow
Who just recently won the
Oscar for The Hurt Locker.
You could see
the style in this film
Just coming a mile away
of what kind of director
She was going to
continue to become
And this movie is amazing.
It's a horror western.
So It's got like people
riding horses with cowboy hats
But It's also got vampires.
You have this kind
of cow poke kid from a farm
And he's out one night downtown
having an ice cream cone
And he sees this beautiful girl.
He's just completely
infatuated with her.
Unfortunate for him because
she's traveling around
With a band of fellow vampires
Including Lance Henriksen,
Jenette Goldstein,
The kid whose name I
can't remember but says,
"You're so ugly you make my
gums ache." My favorite line.
So this cow poke gets sucks
into this vampire clan
And he's turning into a vampire
but of course makes
The stomach turn to think about
killing other people.
And the best scene
is that bar scene
Where they're really trying to
teach him
How to go and hunt and kill.
And they lock that bar
And they just take the rednecks
down one by one.
To the patrons
they don't look like vampires.
They don't have teeth,
they don't come up that way.
They just seem like
a crazy family
And everybody in that
bar knows that
They're not getting out alive.
Even Bill Paxton doing
this really awesome role.
He's this shift kicker vampire
and they devastate the bar
And it's sudden explosive
violence.
There's a beautiful
waitress and he kills her
And he fills a pitcher
with her blood.
Basically Near Dark
to me I think
Is the ultimate boy meets girl
Then boy has to meet girl's
family for the first time.
And the terror that comes with
that, that moment when she goes,
"I'd like you to meet my dad."
He's like "Oh, okay."
But dad isn't dad, it's Lance
Henriksen, he's a bad ass.
It's Bill Paxton who basically
represents the crazy brother.
He's the crazy brother
who plays football
But he doesn't play
football in this movie.
He has spurs and he like tears
your throat out,
That't Near Dark to me.
So many vampire movies,
Oh, I'm going to rewrite
the whole book on vampires
And what they mean by that is
I'm going to rip off
Kathryn Bigelow's Near Dark.
If you really want to see where
Oscar winning director
Kathryn Bigelow came from,
You should really check out
Near Dark.
A lot of horror
fans maybe haven't seen it
Because they're like "Oh, that's
just some weird vampire film."
But It's actually like a really
well shot, beautiful looking,
Western, slash horror.
What you people want?
Just a couple moments of your
time about the same duration
As the rest of your life.
If your blood just ran
cold, that's a good sign!
Next up at number 12,
ladies and gentleman,
Meet the trouble little boy
named Joshua.
There are lots
of creepy kid movies
Like The Good Sign,
The Bad Seed.
Joshua was right up
there with them.
Sam Rockwell's
performance in this movie.
People talk about Moon and
some of his other work.
I think he should have gotten
the Oscar for this one.
He is just hilarious in
this movie and terrific.
The fact that Sam Rockwell
is in it
Is the reason you should see it.
How do you play a dad
that realizes
His son may be a murderer?
Rockwell found a way.
The mother is going
through postpartum depression
Played by Vera Farmiga
who interestingly
Did another
Bad Seed child movie
Called Orphan which is
actually really good, too.
There are so many elements
going on to this movie,
Themes going on to this movie
that are beyond
Just the fact
that the kid is kind of evil.
There's also the idea of the
modern family in New York City
Trying to keep up with this sort
of New York City Joneses.
And they're stressed and they're
dealing with this weird kid.
All the while you're kind
of wondering is this little kid,
Is he really dangerous?
You start doubting yourself.
Well, you know, I haven't
seen the kid do anything.
Maybe he's not so bad,
maybe it's the father,
Maybe he is a bad father.
Maybe the mother is just
going a little nutty.
He's put in question,
you're not sure exactly.
Is he a sociopath?
He probably is.
He just have that perfect
balance
Of creepiness but sweetness.
He has a brain of an adult
And that's what's actually
really creepy about it.
Is the fact that the lead
character, a young boy
Is talking and acting like
an adult.
I guess it's the idea of when
you see children
On the one hand,
they're supposed to be innocent.
They can operate in a
diabolical way with impunity
Because nobody wants to
assume the worst about a kid.
It's a real talent
to be able to maintain
That sort of edge-of-your-seat
underlying tension
In a film throughout,
Without anything happening.
You know, nothing bad really
happens
In the movie
but it's all so tense.
Entertainment weekly
and The Hollywood Reporter
Praised the movie and it was
also a selection
At the Sundance
film festival in 2007.
Fox Searchlight like put it out,
They're not in too many
theaters.
So I don't think a lot of people
have gotten a chance to see it.
The kid that played Joshua,
he went on to be
The little Spock in Star Trek.
There's no greater honor I think
Than to say that you're
capable of living up to Nimoy
And I think he did a
great job in that too.
It surprises me how
many people have not seen it.
How much it was ignored
because It's really well made.
And I've got to say the
last few seconds of that movie
Will make your skin crawl.
You'll watch it again and again
because it draws you in slowly
And then the last few seconds
is just sort of catapults itself
Into this other stratosphere
of horror.
That's when you realize just how
terrifying the movie is.
I think everybody in the room
will have
A different understanding of
what just happened
In that last couple
moments of the film.
It's really chilling,
kind of beautiful
And that's the end of the movie.
It's on this list for a reason.
It's just one of the
best horror movies
You've probably never seen.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing?
In Egypt when they
embalm people like Pharaohs,
They broke the nose and removed
the brain through the opening.
This movie is
the strongest argument
For birth control
you'll ever hear.
Ever heard the expression,
Don't Be Afraid of the Dark?
Coming in at number 11,
will explain why.
Don't Be Afraid of the Dark
Was a TV movie originally
in 1973
Brought to you by Lorimar.
When you first turn it on, you
think you're just
Going to watch an episode of
Mary Tyler Moore
And then it goes kind of wrong.
Kim Darby plays this woman
who has moved
Into her grandmother's
rambling old house.
Moved out of the city with her
high powered lawyer husband
And they're going to fix it
up and it's going to be great.
She's in this like middle
class boredom with her husband
And the husband's always
working,
Nobody's listening to her.
I mean even her friends are kind
of bored with their stories.
There is a locked room
in the house
That has a walled off fireplace.
Basically the openings
to the fire place
Have been all bricked up
And steel bars and basically
the message is, do not open.
The handyman is like
"Don't do it."
"Some things are better
left the way they are."
Truly all it need
is to be smashed open.
Those bricks are
cemented four deep
And reinforced with iron bars.
Some things
are better left as they are
Especially that fire place.
But no, she's got to
open the freaking fireplace!
They open the wall and
it lets out these three goblins
Who somehow have some
attachment to her.
Oh my God, they've got these
like pumpkin heads.
They have these little
slashing claws,
Black eyes, raspy mouth
And gorilla, little chimpanzee
bodies.
And they come out in the
dark and they want her soul.
Now she's got little evil troll
people running around
Saying, "Sally, we want you."
And grabbing at her dress
and tripping in,
Killing her interior decorator.
(Horror music)
You thought you were having
a bad day.
The last ten minutes of
this movie are gut wrenching.
It's as scary as any real played
in theaters film on the list.
They grab her
and they're dragging her
Down to the basement
And she's alone in the house
except for the goblins.
And she grabs this old 70s
Polaroid camera
And she was snapping flashes
And the only thing that pulls
These monsters back are the
flashes.
But there's only a
limited amount of flashes
And they're getting closer
and closer to the basement.
This movie is insidious.
People forget that Don't Be
Afraid of the Dark is a TV movie
Because it is utterly
horrifying.
(Horror music)
You are watching 50 Best
Horror Movies You've Never Seen.
A countdown of horror's
hidden gems.
Claiming our number 10 spot
is Audition.
A nasty little film
that sneaks up on you.
Audition is a horror
film by Takashi Miike
And the funny thing
about this movie
Is if you were to walk out
around the 45 minute point,
You would think you're
watching a romantic comedy.
The movie takes forever
to get to become a horror film
But that's exactly what makes
it so great.
It's about a widow.
His son's like "Dad, you
got to start dating people."
He's just not satisfied
with the women that he sees.
And he holds fake film auditions
to audition actresses
For a movie that really he
doesn't intend to shoot
But what he's really doing
is auditioning
For a new girlfriend
or a new wife.
He auditions the wrong one
and she is a little bit psycho.
It's almost setup
like a quirky dating game
And then suddenly it turns into
Like the sadistic,
endurance test.
Everything seems sweet
like It's going normal
But then she goes home
and you see
That she has a man
that she keeps alive in a bag
In the corner of her room.
I'm going to be honest
with you, this one is hardcore.
I've seen a lot of horror
movies and I can sit and eat
A piece of pepperoni
pizza during most of them.
This one got under my skin but
at the same time it's awesome
Because it has
a badass chick villain
That you just
don't even see coming
And you don't even know how
far she's going to take it!
The first time I saw it,
I'd been warned.
I'd been told, it turns on you
And then you're going to
be squirming in your seat
And even with that warning I
was still caught off guard.
It's pretty intense stuff.
She takes the needles,
they're like,
Are they acupuncture needles?
Literally, anywhere
you wouldn't want them.
When she does a "tiki-tiki-ti."
Tiki-tiki-tiki. Kiti-kit-kiti.
Tiki-tiki-tiki.
Kiti-kit-kiti. Kiti-kit-kiti.
The needles in the eyeballs.
It's like "Ohh, man."
Like you're...
There's one scene however
that cemented Audition
Into the hearts of horror fans,
The scene with the piano wire.
There's a scene where he's
tied up, she has a piano wire.
A whole bunch of people
were getting up
And walking out of the theater.
My wife and I were among
of the few to stick it out
To the bitter end.
She tortures him,
chops off his foot, right?
With piano wire.
(Male gasping in pain)
It's a great film.
(laughing)
That scene is up there
in the horror lexicon
Of crazy scenes.
I feel so horrible
for the people
Who stumbled upon this movie
Having no idea
it was a horror film.
Because when it turns
into a horror film,
It is one of the most sadistic,
nasty,
Vile, vicious, repugnant movies.
(Laughing)
Go to this audition
at your own risk.
For the vampire aficionado,
you can't beat
Let the Right One In, coming
in at number 9 on our list.
Let the Right One In a
fantastic Swedish vampire film
That came out a couple
of years ago.
Let the Right One In is not only
One of the best
vampire movies ever made.
It's just one of the best movies
that you could possibly see.
I thought that that
was the most original take
On the vampire genre
I have seen in years.
It's also sort of
a remake of My Bodyguard
Which is a classic beloved
children's film from the 80s
Except with vampires
and not for children.
It tells the story
of an awkward 12 year old kid
Who's kind of being bullied
at school
Who befriends this awkward
12 year old girl
That just moves in next door.
It just so happens
that she's a vampire.
She kind of teaches him
a little bit
About how to stand up
for himself
And vice versa
he teaches her maybe
A little bit about
her humanity.
I think he reminds her
what it was like
To be a kid
and have fun again.
That kind of bond I mean,
if you think back
To when you were 12 years old
And where your friendships
are like,
This movie captures that
perfectly.
The title itself,
It's talking about love.
When you let the right one
in, they won't hurt you.
They're both so awkward
and cute around each other
Like she smells really
bad because she's dead
And he gets over it
because he's her friend.
It's just really sweet
And then she ends up killing
people in between
And It's a really cool movie!
There are some bullies
who pick on Oscar at the school.
You can imagine
what happens to them
When his new friend gets a hold
of that.
Bodies are drained
with their blood
And they're hidden under
the ice in the frozen lakes.
It's a case where
you have a young actor,
In this case a girl.
While they appear very youthful,
There's something hauntingly
mature and old about them.
I think obviously in the case
someone's
Supposed to be a vampire,
it really worked.
It just something really
frightening
And yet alluring about this
girl.
One particular moment will
have you drowning in fear.
The spectacular scene
at the swimming pool.
It all kind of builds up
To this final scene
at the pool hall.
The bully's brother puts
Oscar's face
Submerged in the pool.
It's all done in one take.
He's actually hiding
in the pool underwater.
Air bubbles are just coming up
slowly, slowly, slowly.
Then you hear screams but
they're muffled screams
Because you're underwater
with Oscar.
And you sort of just
get glimpses of the massacre
That's sort of going on behind
And these people are being
murdered and dragged across
Like the surface of the pool.
And you're wondering
what the heck's happening?
At the peak of
the Twilight mania,
Here we have this
beautiful love story
That's also a vampire movie
Which is what Twilight
tried to be
But as far as I'm
concerned, did not succeed.
No vampire sparkle here.
We're talking about
traditional scary vampires.
The best contemporary
vampire film ever made.
It shows a sense
of bravery in film making
That I think is really
hard to find
At least in Hollywood
film making.
(Horror music)
Let the Right One In is
bone chilling vampire brilliance
And you'll thank us
for the recommendation.
Another brilliant film claims
our number
8 spot, the mind blowing,
Re-animator.
Dude, Re-animator.
I saw it the first time when
I was 14 years old, - me up.
Re-animator is your
classic mad scientist tale.
With an absolutely
iconic performance
By the very versatile and
talented
Jeffrey Combs, unforgettable.
My first horror
crush was Jeffrey Combs.
It's primarily because he's
so freaking good in the movie.
It cemented his place as a
horror icon.
It's basically about
this mad scientist, Herbert West
Who's trying to create this
Formula to bring the dead to
life.
But the problem is when they
come back, the brains have died
And they're not quite the
same as they were before.
They go on psychotic murderous
rampages.
They're mindless killing
machines,
Duh! Doesn't that always happen?
Re-animator was
directed by Stuart Gordon
And was based on an H.P.
Lovecraft story
By the same name.
Stuart Gordon now is considered
Kind of one of the masters of
horror.
Stuart Gordon has
never made a bad movie.
The movie just went further
Than anything that I've ever
seen.
They were like exploding
entrails
Like wrapping around people.
(Horror music)
It's just crazy, words can't
you really have to see it.
After watching that movie, I
had to sleep with the lights on
And with my Winnie the Pooh.
I have never been more
terrified with stuffed cats
Than when the first time
that I saw that movie
Like the sound that
comes out of this thing.
(Cat growling)
And It's just kind of like
twitching
There because the spine's broken
Like it's just, it's awesome.
And also very unforgettable
and delightful Barbara Crampton
Who's most notorious
and unforgettable scene
Gives a whole new meaning
to the term, "giving head".
If you really want to get
"ahead"
In your knowledge of horror
movies,
That's the one to go for.
All props to Stuart Gordon
for going there.
We can't say much more
about that scene on TV
But here's a "heads up": Pick
up a copy of Re-Animator.
See for yourself what
all that talk is about.
We have a feeling you'll be
forever grateful
For our recommendation.
It's the kind of movie
that you get a couple of beers,
Get your friends together and
watch it
At midnight on a Friday night.
And It's really, really sick.
So I don't know what that
says about me, but I love it.
I will be famous.
Everyone's entitled to
one good mad scientist movie.
Up next at number 7 on
our list is Wishmaster.
Wishmaster is the age old story
Of "be careful what you wish
for"
Which is actually the tag
they use on the poster.
An executive asked me to come in
Because they wanted to do a
horror movie.
When I got there they said,
"We have a great idea,
It's an evil genie movie."
He's this really evil
but very charismatic genie
Played by Andrew Divoff
who turns in
A performance that is up there
With Freddy Krueger in A
Nightmare on Elm Street.
When you get the right guy
And the horror makeup, it really
sells it.
Divoff has got a voice like a
fork in a garbage disposal
And so are these.
It doesn't matter what we write.
It even doesn't matter
what the makeup guys do,
Even though they're
brilliant and tough,
If you don't have a guy behind
the mask who will deliver,
Who will commit,
who will do it right
Then it all goes to naught,
And I thought Andrew was just
terrific.
And he plays an
evil genie called a Djinn
And he's sort of trapped inside
this little red kind of crystal.
Of course he gets out and
he starts granting wishes
And when he starts granting
wishes,
He's got a way of twisting them
a little.
Just in a way that an evil genie
Would to make you suffer
immeasurably
For your want, your desire.
Oh my god.
Am I to understand this is
not something you wish to see?
Uh-huh.
Very well.
My eyes!
One of the real
pleasures of Wishmaster,
Certainly for me and certainly
for Bob Kurtzman who direct it
Because it was like homecoming,
it was a school reunion time
Because we managed to get a lot
of great people in the cast.
We had Kane Hodder in there,
we had Tony Todd in there.
We had Ted Raimi, Reggie's
in there, Buck Flowers.
Robert of course
is in there too.
All these existing monsters were
welcoming Andrew into the fold.
We got all these people that
we loved
And we have the fans love too.
If you're looking for something
A little bit our tongue and
cheek,
A little more crafty and clever
and fun,
Then you have to see Wishmaster.
Doesn't that intrigue you?
Just a little?
Be careful what you wish
for. You have been warned!
Claustrophobia anyone?
Check out our number 6 movie,
The Descent.
I think Descent is
probably the best film I've seen
That deals with claustrophobia.
Really making you feel like
you're trapped
Along with the characters.
You feel claustrophobic,
you feel it's damp.
You feel It's wet, you
feel like wet with blood.
You just feel that real
claustrophobic feeling.
That would have been
scary enough for the whole movie
But then they add monsters
to the mix, holy shit!
We follow a group
of female spelunkers
Who decide to explore a cave
That supposedly has never
been explored before.
I've never seen four
better looking spelunking women.
They end up trapped underground
After there's this horrible
cave-in.
They're wounded, their
batteries are going down
And then you discover that
there's something else
Down there with them.
The cool thing about it is you
got this
Really claustrophobic setting.
I mean there are shots in the
film where you're just like
You want them to just spread
their arms out
Because it's like they can't.
They've got rock above them and
rock below them
In their left and the right.
And then there's the monsters.
The monsters in The Descent are
some
Of the scariest
monsters I've ever seen.
They're there for the babe
buffet
Because little by little every
single one of those females,
Dead and eaten alive.
They're very nocturnal.
They're like bats or whatever
they are.
They can't see anything at all.
Their skin is as weird like
translucent
And they just adopt this where
all they really need
Is like to make this weird like
click noises
And screams and communicate
with each other.
You only get perspective
on them
When you've got a flash of light
Because it's dark, the
whole movie is dark.
It's one of those films where
you're like
"Just turn,
turn the light on!"
One of the girls finally clearly
sees one of the creatures
But it's from a distance.
(Creature growling)
That shot has stayed
with me since I saw it.
The girls end up
turning on each other
And It's like so they're not
only fighting these monsters
But they're fighting each other.
When things start going bad,
you want to get out of the cave
But yet they're forced to keep
going deeper
And deeper into the cave.
There's an awesome sequence
where these two girls
Are stuck upside down.
And these girls are they're
like hanging from these hooks.
Crawling across the
ceiling, when they're attacked
By one of these things
that come running at them.
(Creature growling)
I saw this movie in a sold out
theater
And everyone
hit the roof.
Are you scared of
being caught in tight spaces?
Are you scared
of underground monsters?
If you're scared of either one
of those things,
It's covered in The Descent.
(Creature growling)
You are watching 50 Best
Horror Movies You've Never Seen.
A countdown of horror's
hidden gems.
And coming in at number
5? Alone in the Dark.
Alone in the Dark
is one of those
Classic 80s horror movie gems.
It's kind of a
weird hybrid of slasher
Meets home invasion,
meets mystery.
Like a lot of horror movies,
Alone in the Dark
Kind of hinges
on you buying into one thing
That doesn't really makes sense.
The premise isn't the greatest
because
It's basically an insane asylum
Where security is all run by
electricity.
This place, as soon as the
electricity goes out,
Literally every inmate
breaks lose.
Nobody thought when
the electricity goes out,
All the crazy people
can get out?
Great plan!
They get most of
them back which is great
But of course a few manage to
wreak havoc
And kill a few innocent people,
All because these guys didn't
want to buy a generator.
Alone in the Dark
was New Line Cinema's
First major motion picture
And it featured
a star-studded cast.
Another great thing
in this movie
Is they had like an amazing cast
in it.
I mean Jack Palance was in it.
Jack Palance is
bigger in life than that.
Dr. Potter!!
HappyÉ trails.
Donald Pleasence was in it.
Donald Pleasence
plays his typically nutty self
But he runs this asylum where
he sort of lets the inmates
Kind of do whatever they want.
You ever watch a Halloween movie
And think what if
Dr. Loomis ran Smith's Grove?
That's what
Alone in the Dark is.
Forget Dr. Loomis from Halloween
Where he was practical
and carried a gun.
In this one, he is as crazy
as the inmates
In the asylum he's running!
Move your hands, in front of
your face three times,
Like that.
Yes and then the
intestines will stay inside
And you won't turn to porcelain.
And you have "The Preacher"
who's Martin Landau.
Vengeance is mine
saith the Lord.
Alone in the Dark and
Friday the 13th part three
Were in production
at the same time
And both films actually have
a hockey mask.
Of course Jason's went on
to be quite more successful
But it's kind of interesting
now to look back and see
A film from the same era using
pretty much the same mask.
And there were
a couple of killers.
One of them was "The bleeder."
The only way you know
him is when he gets a nosebleed.
(Horror music)
One of the escaped
mental patients in this movie,
They call him "Fatty"
and he's like so big
That he will pick up people
by their necks
And shake them around
like ragdolls.
(Horror music)
At one point they do go into
Friday the 13th's territory.
That, actually that is one
of the key slasher movie scenes.
Basically one of the inmates
is under a bed,
The couple is going at it.
And this hand reaches out
from the bed,
And yanks him under it.
So she's screaming and scared
but she doesn't know what to do.
She doesn't want to jump off the
bed because they might get her
Also and this knife starts
shooting up through the bed.
(Woman screams)
But the studio wasn't
just going for gore,
They wanted to surprise
audiences
With a killer twist ending.
This was 1982.
It was really rare to
have like a good twist
And it usually just involved
some guy
Jumping out of something and
screaming
And the girl screaming and
people scream.
But this movie actually has a
brilliant twist,
You won't see it coming.
But it's an amazing
film, it's shot so well.
You have like A-list actors,
hamming it up
As like different kinds of
crazy.
The movie scared
the crap out of me.
(Man screaming)
Don't miss the
electrifying Alone in the Dark.
Coming in at number four is a
grim 1955 fairy tale,
The Night of the Hunter.
The Night of the
Hunter is a classic movie.
It's the only movie that
Charles Laughton ever directed
Which is a really cool
note about that movie.
I think it's a masterpiece.
Robert Mitchum is one of
these best performances.
Well I think The
Night of the Hunter is crucial
Not only for horror film fans
But for anyone who loves movies
period.
It's one of the best movies ever
made.
Robert Mitchum
plays Harry Powell
And he's a traveling preacher.
The story of the film is
Harry Powell is arrested
For vagrancy or something like
that
And he overhears
a young Peter Graves
Tell the story right before
he's going to be hanged
That he has buried a large sum
of treasure
And only his children
know where it is.
Harry Powell gets out of
prison, finds the widow
And woos her and tries
to outsmart the widow
But the children know better.
It's a modern day fairy tale,
he is the big bad wolf.
These little children
are Hansel and Gretel.
What I like most about it
is that it's like a fairy tale.
If you look at it for the
visuals alone,
You've got these two children
that are trying
To escape from this monster
and they're hiding out in barns
And they're going on a
little boat down the river,
And it's like the wicked witch.
It's very much an ethereal
fairy tale kind of a story.
It's very clearly
like a set and a stage
But the world it creates
is so consistent and real
That it succeeds in that goal
of sort of creating a world
That you can escape from.
Even though it's
completely a fantasy world.
There's that wonderful,
beautiful sequence
When they are on the boat
And she sings that
kind of creepy song
But it's really touching.
The whole thing
about going after children
I think is really
macabre and creepy.
Child performances in horror
movies can be a real trick
And this is an example of a very
successful pair
Of child actors here.
You really care
about these two kids.
I mean and they are in some
serious peril.
Just tell me,
where's the money hidden?
But that's why I
promised dad I wouldn't tell.
John doesn't matter!
Can't I get that through
your head,
You poor silly
disgusting little wretch?
This movie influenced director
John Carpenter
When he made Halloween
And after you see it,
you'll know why.
Coming in at number 3,
is a nail-biting
80s monster classic,
The Beast Within.
The best horror
movie in this whole list
Is of course The Beast Within.
The fact that I've directed it,
Has nothing to do with my
opinion.
It's sort of the
movie that would not die.
I have no idea
when I was making that film
That it would have the
life that it has had.
The Beast Within
is about this kid.
He has basically a beast
within that's going to come out
Like a cicada
and he's going to shed
His human skin
and become this beast.
There have been a number
of people over the years
Who have felt that the movie
does not make a lick of sense.
In the dialog throughout the
movie, a couple different places
There is actually
a coherent explanation
For why the whole cicada thing.
It shed a skin, like a cicada.
The life cycle of the cicada,
it's a 17 year life cycle.
That's why all the weirdness
starts happening
To my character when he is 17.
It's just awesome because you
can't wait for him
To turn into the beastÉ within.
The film offered a grungy
film style and broke new ground
With these innovative and
unprecedented special effects.
That kind of pure, gritty,
horror film
That they don't make anymore.
No CG at all, all practical
effects.
The video box that was daring
you to watch the last 30 minutes
Without running from your seat?
It's true because it is a
special effects extravaganza.
The idea was to make the
last half hour
As terrifying as possible.
The single weirdest scene
bar none
I have ever had
to do as an actor
Was in the infamous last half
hour of The Beast Within.
There was no way I was going to
have a stunt man play the beast.
No, no, no, I was the beast.
They didn't do that because
I wanted to be the -
I made that very clear that
I wanted to be the beast.
United Artists,
in their wisdom asked us
To shoot in a mental asylum
But they'd promised me that
there'd be no inmates.
They said it was a disused
hospital.
We're up there shooting this
transformation scene
For three days
and I'm going through
All these
different stages of prosthetics.
And when we
started shooting the stuff
And the tongue and the heads
exploding,
Then behind me I suddenly heard
"Huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh."
When I turned around,
there were three inmates
From the mental asylum in
nutcase gowns.
And I suddenly realize they
thought this was their worst,
This is the operation
room, this is surgery
Because we had lights like
this, lights like this.
I thought "Oh my God,
they think this is real."
These burly guys came in and
dragged them off screaming
And I've always
felt bad about this
Because I'm sure they
told all the other inmates
"We've seen the room and that's
where they cut your head off"
"And they do experiments
on you."
Guess who is a
fan of The Beast Within?
Would you believe,
Queen Latifah!
I ran in to her one
time at a magazine stand
And she said,
"You look really familiar.
Do I know you?"
I said, "Well, I'm an actor,"
And she goes "Oh,
what have you done?"
"Well, when I got
to The Beast Within,"
Her eyes went like this
and she went, "Oh my god!"
"The Beast Within!
I love that - I've seen that
movie five times!"
"My brother and I used to
hide behind the couch!"
"You scared the crap out of us!"
(Horror music)
This magazine which I have a
lot of fun and respect for,
Rue Morgue magazine out of
Canada,
They recently referred to The
Beast Within
As "a criminally underrated
genre masterpiece"
Which I thought that's
pretty cool becauseÉ I agree.
(Horror music)
Think of The Beast Within as a
twist
On a classic werewolf story,
with an entomological flair.
Earning the prestigious
number 2 spot on our list
Is the pulse pounding,
Pumpkinhead.
If you like creature movies,
you will love Pumpkinhead.
There aren't a lot of
good backwoods horror films.
Pumpkinhead is one of the best.
Basically these
kind of jerky city kids
Go out into the backwoods and
they're riding their dirt bikes.
They start racing along
and they're zooping up and down
And Lance Henriksen's son
goes chasing after his dog,
Gets in between one of the
bikes,
Gets hit in the head and killed.
(Motorbike sound)
Lance Henriksen plays Ed Harley
Who's the father
of the boy who gets hit
And he goes into
this old witch, Haggis.
When I first saw that witch,
she scared the hell out of me.
He has her resurrect a
demon that they call Pumpkinhead
That's out in this pumpkin
patch buried in the ground
To extract revenge on the people
That accidentally
killed his son.
He plays such a broken character
And you could feel his
desperation.
He just has to do this.
The only catch is every
time the demon kills somebody,
Ed Harley feels it.
As the movie progresses he
starts realizing
What he's doing is wrong,
Vengeance in his
ultimate form is wrong,
And has to kind
of try to stop it
Before Pumpkinhead kills
all the rest of the kids.
He is a mean son of a bitch.
(Man screaming)
Part of Pumpkinhead's success
I think is that
it's directed by a man
Who made monsters for a living,
Stan Winston.
I love the monster.
I mean what can I say,
it's just one
Of the all-time greatest
movie monsters.
He creates a monster
that's so memorable, so evil.
Stan Winston got what was scary.
He goes back and taps into
something very primitive
And very child-like,
what is scary?
There's no CG in this movie,
it's all very practical.
No CG, that what you saw
was right there on the set.
You can't substitute, there's
no substitute for that.
The tangibility, you can
reach out and touch it
And it can reach out
and touch you.
There's a scene
where Pumpkinhead picks her up
And he basically cuts a cross
Into her forehead
with his nails.
It's very atmospheric,
It's very creepy all around
But for some reason that
scene was very primal.
It's just a great
spooky backwoods horror film.
And it's required viewing
for any casual horror film.
(Woman screaming)
If you think Alien was scary,
you haven't seen Pumpkinhead.
The time has come to
announce our number 1 movie
On our list of 50 Movies
You've Never Seen!
Ladies and gentleman,
behold! Black Christmas!
This movie started the
entire slasher genre
And continues to send icy chills
down the spines of horror fans
That discover it
year after year.
Black Christmas
is number 1 on the list
And there's a reason for that.
It was the first slasher film
and it's basically
About this sorority house where
they're being menaced
By some obscene phone caller.
The first time I saw Black
Christmas, I was in high school
And it scared
the shit out of me.
Bob Clark was a very,
very underrated director.
He directed another classic
film called A Christmas Story
Which is the polar opposite
of what Black Christmas was.
It's all very Christmasy feeling
And yet there's this evil
that's lurking outside.
People, they might lump it in
With like Silent Night,
Deadly Night
And it's nothing like that.
It's a really dark ugly movie
Set on the happiest time
of the year.
I love it for that reason.
I love the use of
this Christmas atmosphere
Which normally is supposed to be
something comforting
And jolly and so forth
And kind of just turning
it on its head.
The movie opens with a
point-of-view shot
Of these two hands crawling
Up the trellis
on the side of this house.
What this guy does is he makes
his way to top of the window
To the attic and
he lets himself inside
And he sort of camps out there.
What he ends up doing
is making phone calls
Down to the girls that live
in this sorority house.
I mean the telephone
calls are just so terrifying.
The phone calls will
make your hair on your body
Completely stand on end.
This killer could have just
been this crazy man on the phone
But what Bob Clark does
is he layers the voices.
It's almost like there's three
voices talking at the same time.
What he does in doing
that is so chilling.
(Man laughing)
The filthiness, the
sleaziness of the phone calls
From this perverted phone
stalker.
You're surprised that at the
time that the film was made
That it would have gotten away
with it
Because it's just so perverse.
It's more of a
detective movie in a way.
There's a lot of creepy scenes
in it
But it's really
about the characters.
Margot Kidder
like steals the show
As like kind of the lush house,
house sister.
She's like boozing it up all
the time and talks like a sailor
And she's hysterical.
Like she has this
really great line
Where she's sitting there
with a cigarette
And some guy
is calling on the phone.
She's like "Oh, put this,
put your",
And rub it in a light socket!"
Why don't you go find
a wall socket
And stick your tongue in it,
That will give you a charge!
You should just get all your
friends together
On Christmas Eve
and watch Black Christmas.
And you know, screw the Santa
Claus claymation shit.
Just watch Black Christmas
and get really drunk
And laugh at everything
Margot Kidder says
Because that's
the greatest character
I've ever seen in
a slasher film.
Although Margot Kidder
provides the comic relief,
It's only to protect you
from some
Of the scariest movie moments
of all time.
There's this great scene in the
film where one of the girls
In the beginning is supposed to
be heading home.
So she's up in her room and she
hears her cat meowing
Over in the closet and there's
this,
You know, point of view shot
behind the plastic
So you know that something
is probably there.
She gets closer and closer and
all of the sudden
The plastic like leaps out.
(Creature roaring)
The 1978 film Halloween
is clearly the benchmark film
That ushered in modern horror.
Without Halloween you
wouldn't have Freddy Krueger,
You wouldn't have
Jason Voorhees,
You wouldn't have Scream,
you wouldn't have Chucky.
It ushered in that
franchisable kind of horror.
Well, what people don't realize
Is that the director
of Halloween
Was friends of the director
of Black Christmas,
And Black Christmas did what
Halloween did
Four years before, in 1974.
And it really created
the template
That all those other movie,
Everybody thinks it's Halloween
that created
The template
for that kind of thing.
In fact it created
two templates,
Not only the point of view
of the killer,
Seeing things through
the killer's eyes
And hearing the breathing and
doing that device,
But also
the killer is in the house.
The caller is in the house.
The calls are coming
from the house!
Jess, get out!
Well, several other movies
wound up doing riffs
On that one as well,
When A Stranger Calls?
Etcetera, etcetera.
Black Christmas did it first!
You know, and credit,
where credit is due!
If you're wondering
why the killer
Is stalking the sorority girls,
you're out of luck.
Director Bob Clark only
dangles sporadic clues
Which causes attention to
escalate.
You never find out who
the crazy guy is or what he did.
You never find out what
did Billy do with the baby.
Who is Agnes? I don't know.
You don't see the killer.
What you see are fleeting
glimpses of him.
You see a shadow,
you see a door closing.
You see an eyeball
in a crack of a door.
The killer is so menacing...
without you seeing him.
It's never revealed
exactly who the killer is.
You never really did
a good look at him
And I think that's actually
the fear of the unknown
Is what makes this film so
effective.
Let your imagination
fill in the blanks
And most of the time our
imaginations are much more
Terrifying than anything you can
put up on the screen.
Black Christmas is one
of my favorite horror movies.
I'm going to say it's
a masterpiece.
I'm going to just say
it's a masterpiece
And even Elvis loved it.
He used to watch it
on Christmas.
It's one of the scariest movies
And if you haven't seen it,
shame on you.
Go out and rent it
right now.
Stop this DVD.
Go rent it,
you can watch this later.
Black Christmas to me
is the highest standard
Of slasher films.
There's just so many classic
horror movie moments
In Black Christmas
That have been imitated
time and again.
Black Christmas just doesn't
receive
The credit that it deserves.
I personally can see
Why that would be the
number 1 movie on your list.
Talk about influential, wow.
It just set a major
ball rolling, didn't it?
(Man screaming)
(Female screaming)
I'm P.J. Soles and it's
been an immense pleasure
Introducing you to 50
classic horror films
That I know you'll love.
These movies totally helped
shake the horror genre
And they continue to draw
critical praise
And cult followings,
So start exploring!
Many of the movies are available
As special editions
with deleted scenes.
Thank you for watching!
(Music)