[Music playing]
[INDISCERNIBLE CHATTER AND
LAUGHTER]
[Grunting]
Oh, excuse me.
Another county heard from.
How about a little drink, Mimsy?
Mimi, much obligated, I'm sure.
Oh, my pleasure.
Back in a flash.
Oh, why don't you, uh,
make yourself comfortable?
Okey doke.
[Laughter]
Say, nice digs.
SENATOR OVERSTREET: Oh,
well, it comes with the job.
Not bad.
You know, I never actually
done it with a senator before.
SENATOR OVERSTREET:
Yeah, my wife
Boasts about the same thing.
Your wife?
Oh, not to worry.
She's back in
Washington running MOP,
Mother's outraged
over prostitution.
[Laughter]
You're kidding me!
Your wife's one of those cows?
Why, I always say
it's nobody's business
What goes on between two
condescending adults.
SENATOR OVERSTREET:
Condescending, I like that.
You know, you are wise
beyond your years, Mimsy.
Mimi.
Yeah, well, I read a lot.
I like that.
You know, I really
do... yeah, I really
Admire career women, ahh.
Mimsy?
Mimsy!
How about a little
filibustering?
[Gasps] Oh, sweet baby Judas.
You don't waste
any time, do you?
[Grunts] [growls] Wait for me!
[Grunts] Oh, this
woman is a machine!
[Screams]
Wrong, senator.
She's no machine,
just a fragile human.
And the damn things
break so easy.
Cy... borgs!
Very good, senator.
Cyborgs!
And you don't like
cyborgs, do you?
No, you're wrong.
You don't understand!
I understand more
than you think.
But I voted against
Project Cancel.
I'm a friend of
the cyborg lobby.
Looks like your date
has expired, senator.
Don't despair.
We brought a spare.
Meet Razor.
[Grunts]
[Snarls]
[Laughs]
So you wanted to get
fucked tonight, senator?
Well, you are definitely fucked.
[Screaming]
[Laughs]
[Dance music playing]
[Indiscernible chatter]
OK, OK, OK, OK, OK.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Heads or tails?
[Sighs] Man, you're the
one that digs this shit.
Why should I have to pay?
Come on, man, heads or tails?
I don't want to go in here?
Look, who's going to be...
All right!
Heads.
All right.
[Grunts] I'll take the quarter.
[Dance music playing]
I've gotta hit the
john, so why don't
You find us a couple of seats?
Be in the bathroom, man.
Sure, take your time.
Wouldn't want you
to hurt yourself.
JIM: Yeah, right.
You know your money is
no good in here, McCord.
Thanks, Jay.
By the way, have you
seen Blue around?
She's out in back, getting
read to go out next.
Catch any bad guys lately?
Yeah.
Weaver and I were
down in Central.
We caught these two punks raping
a business woman in an alley.
They injected her with heroin.
She didn't even know
what was happening.
JAY: How is she?
She's fine.
She's in stable
condition in a hospital.
Ah, that's good to hear.
Those punks will be
out in the street
Again soon, the jails being
so overcrowded and all.
Oh, they're not in jail.
JAY: Yeah.
Well, where are there?
They opened up on us.
Does that answer your question?
You looking for something, man?
Well, yeah, I'm trying
to find the john.
Well, use the one downstairs.
I must have passed it.
Is there something else?
Take it easy.
I'm gone.
[Woman laughing]
And now ladies and
gentlemen, our special treat
Of the evening, Blue!
[Cheering and applause]
[Music playing]
Hi, can I get you
something to drink?
Piss off, bitch.
Fuck you, faggot.
I'll show you, faggot!
Don't concern yourself
with the bitch, brother.
You know we have work to do.
[Music playing]
[Cheering and applause]
[Sighs] Hey, babe.
You looked great
up there tonight.
Thanks, honey.
I'm always extra good when
you're here to inspire me.
Yeah.
Me and the 30
other guys in here.
Come on.
Chill up, McCord.
You know very well this job is
just a way to pay my tuition.
Oh, come on, Blue.
Don't hand me that.
When you're up there
taking off your clothes
In front of a room full
of men, don't tell me
You don't enjoy it.
Yeah, I enjoy it,
but my school is
Still the most important thing.
And besides, Brent, no one
ever touches me except you
As you know damn well.
Hey, no need to remind
me what a lucky guy I am.
I already know.
So did you notice
the two borgies
Who came in a little white ago?
You mean the ones
in the corner?
So what?
Just a couple of cyborgs.
Yeah, well, there's something
suspicious about 'em.
You know, Brent, sometimes
I just don't figure you.
You've got to be
one of the least
Paranoid men I know except
when it comes to cyborgs.
Yeah, well, all borgies
give me the creeps.
But those two are
especially creepy.
Hey, Weave.
Say, hot stuff.
You knocked them
dead again tonight.
Thanks, sugar.
What'd you say to McCord
to make him so serious?
It's not me.
He doesn't like the
looks of those two.
Uh, borgies.
Jesus, you too?
BRENT: I don't know, I just
have a bad feeling about them.
Well, maybe there's
a connection,
But something's
going on backstage.
What do you mean?
JIM: Well, there's two
gorillas back there in suits,
By Maria's dressing room.
And my guess is is that she's
entertaining some pretty
Heavy gentleman caller.
So, that's not unusual?
BRENT: What?
BLUE: Well, some of the goods
taken some business from time
To time with some
well-to-do types,
You know, military head,
politician, senator maybe.
So a couple of borgies just
happen to show up tonight?
Why?
Hey, where'd they go?
Come on!
Let's come up through backstage.
Blue, get behind the bar.
[Gunshots]
[Screaming]
See you later, cop.
[Gunshots]
Weave, you OK?
Yeah, they got me, pal.
But they didn't get me good.
Well, I don't know
why you rushed me.
We're here and the meeting
doesn't start for 40 minutes
Yet.
I apologize, sir.
I had a few points I'd like
to go over with you before we
Meet with general Braddock.
You know he hates
to be kept waiting.
Braddock can take a flying...
Uh, where's my briefcase?
Um, it's right here, sir.
Get any more word on
Senator Overstreet's murder?
[Sighs] Well,
Braddock seems think
It's linked to the
Project Blackhawk problem.
Well, I figured that much out.
I was against that project
right from the start.
So was Overstreet.
Dammit, I hate dealing
with the military.
General Braddock seems think
we can still make it work, sir.
General Braddock
is full of shit.
That project was mishandled
right from the start.
He gave his man Peck
too much leeway.
Now it's totally out of control.
You're trying to say
we can't regain control?
I'm saying there's only one
thing we can do with it now,
And that's shut it down.
Close down Blackhawk?
But we've put millions into it.
Wipe it out.
Leave no trace.
Make it look like it
never existed at all.
Listen, if we can't do
that, and do it now,
Then we at all better get
the hell out of the country
And fast.
[Gunshots]
Hey, Veena.
Don't they ever let you go home?
Well, fellows, if
it wasn't for you,
I probably would be home by now.
Well, just doing my job, Veena.
And making my tougher.
So, what do we have here?
What we have is possibly
a very sticky situation.
Come, let me show you
what I have found.
We have two cyborgs.
This one is almost
totally reinforced
With a titanium steel alloy
throughout his midsection.
He's virtually indestructible.
He was killed with a bullet
penetrating the heart.
She had much more
humanity than the other.
A shot to the throat
[inaudible] to kill her,
Connecting the link
up to the brain.
What is all that,
um, white stuff?
I believe it's a
preservative of some kind,
Possibly a substrate for blood.
Do you have any idea where
these cyborgs are from?
It is my speculation that it
is government property, probably
Army or something like that.
What makes you so sure?
I may only be a
coroner, but I know
The difference between
commercial work
And fighting machines.
These two are specifically
built for combat,
And they have a
high pain tolerance
And can withstand
any temperature.
Are these two unique?
Their circuitry and
programming is very complex.
I'm sure there's more from
where these came from.
Well, we better get going.
BRENT: Um, look, if you,
uh, find out anything else,
Give us a call at the office.
Sure.
Major Wright, gentlemen.
Have a seat.
So, uh, what can I do for you?
Well, you're familiar
with a massacre
At Sharkey's last night?
Yes, I saw it on television.
Yes, well, it seems that
two cyborgs strolled in there
And blew the place apart
for no apparent reason.
But what has that got
to do with the Army?
The coroner report states
it was a government model
With very sophisticated parts.
All of our soldiers are humans.
The government
doesn't build robots.
[Knocking]
Come in.
Here's that design on that
Blackhawk 2000 for the colonel.
Uh, not now, Sam.
I'm busy.
Oh.
Sorry.
So where was I?
Oh yes, yes, yes.
I understand the marines
are experimenting
With some cybernetic tanks
or something of that nature.
I'm afraid that's all
I can tell you, sorry.
Now, if you gentlemen
will excuse me.
What's the Blackhawk 2000?
I'm sorry, this classified
Army information.
Now, if you gentlemen
would excuse me,
I have some work to do.
Thank you.
Of course.
Hold up.
You guys the police?
Yeah.
Show me your badges.
All right, look.
I know what's going on.
I can tell you
about the cyborgs.
I help make them.
Do you know why they
attacked a club last night?
Look, not here.
There's this alleyway off
of Hollywood and Vine.
We know the place.
Meet me there tonight at 11:45.
I'll answer your questions then.
Make sure no one follows you.
Gotcha.
No, I hear you loud
and clear, general.
Yeah.
No, no, don't worry.
It won't happen again.
You've got my word on it.
Goodbye.
Nice tie.
You know who that was on
the phone just now, boys?
General Braddock
over at the Pentagon.
Seems like your
little visits you
Made to [inaudible]
made some pretty
Big waves with those boys.
I'd like to know what the
hell you think you're doing.
Well, we can, uh,
explain that, captain.
Go on.
I'd like to hear it.
Well, Weaver and I, we have
stumbled onto something big.
I, uh, think the
Army is involved
With some way with the
Overstreet assassination
And Sharkey's last night.
And the Quay
assassination as well.
Go on.
Well, we checked and found
that the two dead cyborgs
At Sharkey's were
government-issued,
The kind that were being
turned on back in the '90s.
You guys are out of your
fucking minds, you know that?
BRENT: It's true, sir.
And we think the Army is
trying to cover it up.
When we left Major
Wright's we ran
Into a possible
information source,
And he said that something
covert was going on.
So we've arranged a
meeting with him later.
So who is this
reliable source, huh?
JIM: You know we can't
reveal that until we're
Sure of our information.
All right.
And you have a meeting
set up with this guy.
Yes, sir.
For tonight.
Forget it.
What?
I said forget it.
Cancel the meeting.
Do not show up for that.
You hear me?
Are you crazy?
We can't do that.
[Stammers] What he means
is, you can't be serious?
I can.
And I am.
Captain, two United
States senators have
Been assassinated, murdered.
Look, I know all
about that, McCord.
But you know what that means?
It means you two have got
to find their murders, see?
Only.
Leave the Army out of it.
[Sighs] I can't believe
I've hearing this shit.
Just stay away from
the Army, McCord.
And forget about that
meeting, you got it?
That's a direct order.
You boys are excused.
Hey, sugar.
Are you lookin' for some action?
Yeah.
Party's at our place.
Look, I'm just meeting
someone here, so, uh.
Oh, come on now.
Lizzy feels like getting
her knees dirty for you.
Mmm.
What do you say? [Inaudible].
Look, I'm really
not interested.
Oh, we won't hurt you.
Maybe just a little.
Yeah.
We don't bite unless, uh,
it's what you're into.
Yeah, maybe some other time.
Thank you.
Well, honey, you ain't
gonna find a better girl
No where on this block.
Mhmm.
What she said.
Yeah.
He'll be back.
Huh.
Hey.
I didn't say anything, I swear.
[Gunshots]
Search him.
Freeze, [inaudible].
[Gunshots]
[Grunts]
Oh, Brent.
[Breathes heavily] Brent.
We have to take
it easy, brother.
Yeah, help's coming.
I got you.
[Inaudible].
Don't try to talk,
man. [Inaudible].
We'll have you
fixed up in no time.
[Inaudible].
[Crying]
They won't kill you.
[Sirens]
COLONEL PECK: Report Hair.
Captain Hair, reporting, sir.
Target Sam Ames is dead.
Are you sure?
Oh, I'm real sure.
Also dusted one of those
two cops I told you about.
Only one.
I had a little trouble, sir.
What kind of trouble
was that, Captain Hair?
It was that second cop.
He's like no other human
I've ever gone up against.
He killed Lead Eye.
You're telling me that,
uh, that one cop took you?
It was no ordinary
cop, Colonel.
Fighting him was... well, it
was like fighting another borg.
Another borg?
What is it you're saying?
What I'm trying to say,
sir, is that he was good.
He could've the man that dusted
Deep Throat and Ratchet Jaw
At the club.
What did he look like?
Well, he was six foot, had
black hair, blue eyes, a
Crooked nose, and a wide mouth.
Crooked nose, blue eyes.
McCord.
Sir?
[Chuckles] After all
this time, finally.
Finding McCord.
What are you saying, sir?
You... you know this guy?
Know him?
Captain Hair, [laughs] you
might say he's like my brother.
McCord.
You bastard!
[Laughs]
[Buzzes lips] How
did you get in here?
Why did those bastard machines
of yours kill my partner?
I've got nothing to say to you.
Hell, well I have
something to say to you.
So listen up.
First, I'm going to find
those clowns of yours
And cancel every one
of their fucking asses.
Then I'm gonna gather
enough evidence
On you to have you court
marshaled and put in jail
Where you belong.
Look, I'm sorry for what
happened to your friend
And whatever happened to you.
But you're getting into
this matter much too deeply.
There are other people
involved, professional people
Know what they're doing.
I think you're full of shit!
And I think we've
talked enough.
It's time for you to leave.
[Breathes heavily]
You're finished, Frank.
[Sighs]
I gave you an explicit order
not to go to that meeting,
And you deliberately disobeyed
that order, didn't you, McCord?
You also told me to
find the murderer.
That's...
Look, I don't want
to hear that, McCord.
Where do you get off, huh?
Where do you get off taking
matters into your own hands?
What gives you the right to
disobey a direct order, huh?
And go above the law?
Captain, we were
on to something.
Oh, Jesus.
I don't want to hear
that again, McCord.
anything from you
Right now, not word one.
I've got a man down out there.
And you know why?
Because he disobeyed
an order, McCord.
And you... you're as responsible
for that man's murder
As the guy as who
pulled that trigger.
Don't you think I know that?
Weaver was my partner.
How do you think I feel?
If he were here right now, he'd
tell you we were onto something
Big, something that
involved the Army.
And we both knew it.
I don't want to hear it.
Something really
rotten is going down.
And nobody is doing
anything about it.
They killed my partner.
I'm gonna bust their asses
if I have to blast my way
Into the Pentagon to do it.
You're not gonna
fuck with the Army.
I ought to bust your
ass except that I
Got a shortage of good men.
Yeah?
Fuck your shortage.
I quit.
What're you gonna do, huh?
Take to the streets?
Let me tell ya.
You wouldn't last two days
out there without this badge
To protect you.
Out there?
Why, you'd just be another
hot-headed punk with a gun.
And sooner or later,
McCord, I'd have
To come out and cancel you.
Don't make me do that.
Jesus Christ.
This isn't the '90s, you know?
I wish it was.
McCord, this whole country
is this close... this close...
To busting right at the seams.
And you know what's
holding it together?
Two things, two things.
The Army and us.
So we take care of the murderers
and the... and the pimps,
And the punks, and the whores.
If there's something rotten
in the political system,
Well, the Army
takes care of that.
And one thing we don't do,
we don't fuck with the Army.
Well, yeah?
Well, who's policing the Army?
You're on thin ice, McCord.
And you know what
I want you to do?
I want you to go home
and get some rest.
Take a couple days off and
you come back and see me.
I will give you
your new assignment.
My what?
As of right now,
you're off this case.
You can't do that to me!
Watch me.
Do I make myself clear?
Yes, sir.
I'll see you in two days
You couldn't do
it, not this way.
What's wrong with
how I'm doing it?
Because, baby, what you're
planning to do isn't justice.
It's revenge.
BRENT: That's right, it is.
They murdered my
partner, my best friend.
What do you expect me to
do, slap them on the wrist
And make them stand
in the corner?
BLUE: What about me?
What happens to me if you go
off and you get yourself killed?
I'm not the one that's
gonna die tonight.
Oh, Brent.
Please don't be stupid.
What do you want from me?
Can't you see that something
is very, very wrong?
[Inaudible] hasn't been bought
off or at least scared off.
Now there's no one
else left but me.
Can't you see that?
And what if you die?
Huh?
What happens then?
You knew the risk when
you fell for a cop.
[Sighs] Brent.
Please don't go, baby.
Please don't go.
Please, baby.
You're still gonna
go, aren't you?
I have to, baby.
Then I'm going too.
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
It's gonna be dangerous.
I mean it, Brent.
You're gonna need help now.
So I'll be your partner.
Blue, you've got to get real.
This is gonna be dangerous.
That's right.
You could get killed.
And I'm not going to
live without you, McCord.
If we go, we go together.
You realize what you're
getting yourself into?
Yes.
All right, let's go.
Ah ha.
Pay dirt.
You found something?
Well, not something.
Everything.
What is it?
Some birth records of some
are least favorite cyborgs.
Let me see.
"Severely wounded while
attempting escape."
Son of a bitch.
Seems that my pale
friend here was, uh,
A prisoner at Leavenworth
prior to picking
Up some much needed new parts.
Lovely.
"Convicted murderer
and pederast.
Shot before a firing squad."
Some more lovable types here.
Brent.
What is that?
What's the matter?
Oh.
It's not true!
Oh my god.
"Lieutenant Brent C.
McCord was stationed
At the American
embassy in Beirut."
Lieutenant, huh?
[Inaudible]
"When he was seriously
wounded in a terrorist bombing.
He later died"... my god...
"while undergoing " Uh.
"Cybernetic transformation
and memory block authorized
By Major Collin Wright."
Come on, Brent.
We've got to get out of here.
Come on.
Come on!
[Gunshots]
What the hell did you do to him?
Shut up.
Well, it doesn't look as if
he'll be much trouble now.
Let's get him out of
here on the double.
[Inaudible].
Don't take him out
of here so fast.
I'd give a closer look
at these intruders.
There's nothing to worry
about here, Colonel.
We have the situation
well in hand.
All right, let's go.
Let's get them out of here.
Major.
I said wait.
Wait.
Guh.
[Laughs] [inaudible]
good work, Major.
See, I don't care what you
do with the rest of them.
I want this one in my
office in five minutes.
I'm sorry, Colonel,
but I can't do that.
You can't what?
Major, perhaps you, uh... you
forget to whom you're speaking.
No, sir, but this is
Project Rogue business.
As you know, we
have our procedures.
Uh huh.
Well, perhaps I could
phrase it another way.
I'm sure you're cognizant
of the chain of command.
I'm a colonel.
You're a major.
This colonel has given
this major a direct order,
Which will be obeyed.
This man will be in my
office in five minutes.
With all due respect,
sir, as officer
In charge of Project Rogue,
I take my orders only
From General Braddock.
Have a nice evening, Major.
Glad that's over with.
What should we do with
these two now, Major?
Take them back to the base?
No, I don't think that's
a good idea right now.
I know a better
place to put them.
Yes, sir?
Call Professor Mancini.
Tell him to meet
us at this address.
Tell him I need him immediately.
Yes, sir.
Where you taking us?
MAJOR WRIGHT: To some
place where we can talk.
To jail?
MAJOR WRIGHT: Oh no.
It's a place better.
To your house.
Good, you're awake.
Wha... wha... where am I?
We're in your own bed.
Just relax a minute while
I go and get someone.
[Groans] Ow.
[Groans]
Well, McCord, how
are you feeling?
Where's Blue?
She's perfectly all right.
You'll be seeing here soon.
But how do you feel?
How do you think I feel?
I would think you have
a lot of questions.
BRENT: Oh?
Whatever will give
you that idea?
I mean, just because I find
out I'm some kind of cyborg
And that I... I've been living
a lie for the past few years?
Whatever would give you the
idea that I have questions?
PROFESSOR MANCINI:
OK, easy McCord.
Oh, fuck you.
MAJOR WRIGHT: All
right, let's calm.
No, no.
Fuck you too.
What the hell gives you
the right to do this to me?
You were about to die?
Well, you should've
let me die then.
McCord, I can understand
how you must feel.
But I'm not going to stand here
and argue the morality of it.
What's done is done.
When that car bomb in
Beirut took you out,
There wasn't enough... left
of you to put together.
You were a dying man... no
family, no attachments.
And we needed a subject.
A subject?
Yes, a subject.
And you were the perfect choice.
OK, so that said, I'm...
I'm not a man anymore.
I'm just an experiment?
A robot?
You are not a robot.
You just have a few new parts.
Professor Mancini, you tell.
This is Professor Mancini.
He headed the research project
that developed this technology.
Oh really?
So I should... I
should call you Daddy.
Look, I'm not here to win
your approval, Mr. McCord.
Oh, then why the hell
are you here, then?
To check up on your experiment?
PROFESSOR MANCINI:
Let's face facts here.
You were an experiment,
McCord, like it or not.
We built you practically
from the ground up.
We erased certain
memories pertaining
To your time in the service.
We even returned you
back into society.
So yes, you were an experiment,
a very successful one,
I might add.
So all this time on the
force, all these years,
You've been watching me?
We never have lost track of
you, if that's what you mean.
Don't worry, though,
you've had your privacy.
Oh, thanks.
Come on, McCord.
Snap out of it.
It's not as bad as all that.
You've got some new parts
that are 100 times stronger
Than the originals,
but you're still
A man in the ways that count.
So I'm new and improved?
So why tell me all this?
Why not just erase my memory?
Because we need
your help, McCord.
Have you ever heard
the term, "cybernator"?
Sure, isn't that one of
those hologram movies?
MAJOR WRIGHT: No, it's the
name of the secret government
Project that was
involved in creating
Military cyborg assassins.
The only glitch was that once
they created the cyborgs,
They found out that they
couldn't control them.
They had to terminate
the whole project.
All borgs were to be erased.
Right, so?
So the cyborgs found out.
And they went
underground for 10 years.
We lost all trace of them.
Now over the last
year and a half,
They've begun to resurface
as assassins, the function
For which they were created.
Only now we've
become the target.
At last count, they
had assassinated
A total of 12 military
leaders and politicians.
So you've got a problem?
Why call on me?
Because you are
our ace in the hole.
That's why we put
you with the police.
In the eight months this
bunch has been on the loose,
We tracked them down and
fought the five times.
We lost every time.
You, on the other hand, have
gone up against them twice
And beat them both times.
And now you want me
to clean up your mess.
Is that it?
MAJOR WRIGHT: I sure makes
you the logical choice.
Well, what if I don't want to?
MAJOR WRIGHT: That's
not a request, son.
That's an order.
You're still in the army.
PROFESSOR MANCINI: You
have the advantage.
The other cyborgs
you've seen are
Part of an older technology
developed during the Falcon
Project of the 1990s.
Except for a few touches that
are still military secrets,
Most of the
technology in cyborgs
Is available in the
commercial marketplace.
You, on the other hand,
are a Blackhawk class.
Your cybermechanics
are all internally
Contained, no external parts.
Plus your speed and agility
are several times that
Of the earlier models.
And now you want me to go up
against your other experiments,
Is that it?
Well, what if I don't
want to play cybernator?
There must be others
like me, right?
There is one other Blackhawk
class cyborg in existence.
Why the hell don't you go
get him to ice those guys?
For military reasons,
I can't tell you more.
Oh great, just fucking great.
PROFESSOR MANCINI: He's
not your equal in any case.
He was created first,
actually, the prototype
Of the Blackhawk series.
By the time we got to
you, we had improved
The model significantly.
BRENT: Really, really?
Well, how come that doesn't
make me feel any better then?
MAJOR WRIGHT: Those are
the facts, Mr. McCord.
What's your answer?
Will you help us?
Do... do I have any choice?
MAJOR WRIGHT: Not really.
All right, what about Blue?
What'll happen to her?
She's quite all
right at the moment.
And what does that mean?
Where's Blue?
I want to see her.
MAJOR WRIGHT: You'll
see her, McCord, just as
Soon as we finish our business.
I'm not doing nothing
till I've seen Blue.
MAJOR WRIGHT:
Understand one thing,
McCord, what you think of us and
our work isn't important to me.
But stopping those rogue cyborgs
is absolutely imperative.
We need you to do that.
And Blue stays with
us until you do.
Or you're dead.
Think about that.
We'll be right in the next room.
So, they patched
you up pretty well.
On my outsides, maybe.
I'm still burning
on the inside, Blue.
I feel like my bed is on fire.
I need to latch onto
something, someone.
I feel the same way, Brent.
I'm with you.
So what do we do now, McCord?
Are you with me, then?
I'll always be with you, baby.
They want me to track
down the other cyborgs.
They're holding
you as insurance.
Me?
But isn't that what you
were after, to get Peck?
But that was different.
Then it was my idea.
And that was before all this.
You saying you've
changed your mind?
No, no.
It's not that.
It's just that I don't
like the way they work.
At first they
turned me into this,
And... then they blackmail me
into doing their dirty work.
So?
I just don't like it, Blue.
I don't like it.
So what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna do exactly
what they want me to do.
Then, um, I'm
coming back for ya.
We're gonna go away some
place where we can be alone.
Just you and me.
I'm waiting right
here for you, Brent.
That you can count on.
[Sighs]
Well, McCord, what
have you decided?
I want your guarantee
that Blue will be OK.
Nothing will happen to her.
You have my word.
And I want her here
where I can call
And talk to her at any time.
Forget it, McCord.
She goes into high security.
Get this straight, Wright.
You need me to do this job.
If I decide not to...
We kill Blue.
Yeah, well, you could kill
Blue and you can kill me.
But that still won't
solve your rogue problem.
I want her here,
Wright, or no deal.
All right, all right,
we'll do it your way.
All right.
What about equipment?
I have plenty of my own.
I just need a couple
things from you.
MAJOR WRIGHT: Name it.
First, I need that weapon
you used on me last night.
MAJOR WRIGHT:
Absolutely, McCord.
That's a good choice.
That was developed especially
to use with rogues.
In fact, we call it
the rogue killer.
Yeah.
It's funny you haven't come up
with a way to track them yet.
We had, almost.
Sam Ames was developing
the prototype.
Unfortunately, he was killed
in the alley where you had
Your fight with the cybernator.
I could only assume
that they got it.
Dammit.
Yeah, that's too bad.
Well, we'll just have
to do without it.
They must have a
secret base operation.
Whatever it is, I find it.
[Cartridge shells falling]
MAJOR WRIGHT: About how long
do you think you'll need?
I'll say two or three
days at the most.
You're pretty
confident, aren't you?
What makes you think
it'll be so easy?
You just keep up your
end of the bargain.
I'll be calling here tonight.
Where will you be?
I'll let you know.
Maybe.
[Music playing]
Cyborg scum.
No, no, no, big metal man.
Tonight only love, only passion.
Cyborg scum, got the
passion of a toaster.
Some of my best
friends are toasters.
You fuck.
[Gunshot]
Oh, humans bleed good.
Humans bleed real good.
[Music playing]
[Beeping]
Keep to yourself. [Inaudible].
Keep to yourself.
Wha... watch the...
The ba... [inaudible].
They can walk through rock.
What?
Who?
Who walks through walks?
They can, that's who.
They... they can
walk through rocks.
Look, here.
I'll show you something pretty.
I got pretty things... wires.
Wires are good...
Yeah, pretty wires.
To have.
Yeah.
They're good to
have, but you can't
Tou... no, don't touch them.
They're mine.
And you could bleed.
Humans they bleed good.
[Laughs] Humans bleed real good.
Humans bleed real good.
[Beeping]
[Screaming]
[Mechanical sounds]
[Beeping]
[Laser gunshots]
Well, look what
followed me home.
Lose your hardware, McCord.
Now.
[Grunting]
[Groaning]
McCord.
McCord, I understand
you're looking for me.
Here I am.
[Gunshot]
Are you really supposed to be
the mighty Blackhawk model?
[Chuckles] [inaudible] over me.
McCord, let's quit
playing games.
You know you've already lost.
You might as well come out.
So you're the one?
COLONEL PECK: Yes.
'Tis I, Colonel Elton C. Peck.
[Chuckles] At your service.
I'm here to finish
you off, Peck,
And I'm not leaving until I do.
Would you spare the tired
words, please, McCord?
Don't you know you're
talking to your brother?
You're not my brother.
It really is a shame.
I feel sorry, McCord.
The Army hires you to
do... do their dirty work
And their killing,
and they don't even
Tell you who you are.
You're not my fucking brother!
Oh.
You're not my brother.
Perhaps I made a mistake.
Maybe you're my executioner.
And if you are that, execute me.
[Gunshot]
As I said, McCord,
highly, highly overrated.
Highly overrated.
[Gunshots]
You might as well
give up, McCord.
Stop cowering like so
measly human being.
[Inaudible] beneath the
cyborg of your caliber.
[Gun clicking]
You know you were
built to replace me.
My god.
Can you have some
pride in yourself?
Come on, McCord!
McCord.
You have no weapons
left and nowhere to go.
[Gunshot]
You think you could kill me?
[Inaudible].
You see, McCord, I... I used
the funds from the Blackhawk
Project to slowly build my body,
cybernetically, limb by... limb
My limb and organ by organ.
[Inaudible] McCord.
You're fighting
on the wrong side.
Why do you think
you are [inaudible]?
Look, it's in your
[inaudible] way.
You're doing the
killing for them.
If I were to kill
you, I'd kill you now.
You think they would care?
No.
They wouldn't care, McCord.
You see, see all
they want you to do
Is accomplish your mission,
which is to destroy me.
[Inaudible] and Elton C.
Peck, the one that got away.
And if you were to kill
me, how long do you
Think you would live, McCord?
[Explosion]
[Chuckles]
That was not a nice thing
you did, little brother.
You don't understand.
You see, they're afraid of us.
Listen, McCord,
they... they think
The Blackhawk Project was a
mistake, was an embarrassment.
They never, ever meant to create
a cyborg superior to them.
Why do you think we went rogue?
McCord, they're afraid of us.
All they want to
do is terminate us.
But that's not going to happen.
I'm going to kill them all.
But McCord, you must go first.
[Cries] [groans] [inaudible]!
[Cries]
You know, you're really
starting to get on my nerves.
What, are you bucking
for a section eight?
Very funny.
I just don't like
it when somebody
Else is pulling the strings.
Look, what are you
talking about here?
We've got McCord
by the short hairs.
Look, all that bluster
and bravado on the phone
Just proves it.
He's pissed because he
know he's got no choice.
Think so, huh?
Absolutely.
Then why do I feel as if we've
got him where he wants us?
[Glass shattering]
[Coughs] Tear gas.
[Music playing]