CHILDREN? E from the beginning of time
Dreaming of exciting,
Breakneck adventures ?? municipalities.
These are exciting for children
A sometimes breakneck
FOR ADULTS.
TAK? ALSO ON THIS STORY ...
Starring
CLIFFORD
Play? E
Screenplay
Re? Ia
EDUCATIONAL DOM for boys
FOR? Not yet a ?,
In the old? ASU.
IN 2050th
Ricardo and obviously you better.
Pleased to meet you.
? Hi, the? e Cliff.
?? Hello, Victor. Fanta.
What's with that Roger?
You napodili from here?
I hope not, son.
?? s but evil.
You're not exactly a saint,
when you're in? el'm Victor. Do not forget.
This is true.
Bye, guys.
Zacchaeus was a small, small men ?.
Little, little mo? It was.
He climbed on ...
Who ...
Who me? E ...
O If Clifford.
? What Works ?, Roger?
Be? I ??
? Who, me? Yes.
Why? Just lost my equilibrium? It is
I? istil window.
Did you? Istil a cent? Who?
Roger!
My heart. It hurts.
Oh, no. ? Look who's back.
? Let me go. ? What challenge? I?
Well, well.
After a few very? I wish,
some adults still re? e not.
Mr. Prune the last? I said,
I'll be in time? both from Ljubljana team
then he said that I can not be.
? That's why you blew up the gym?
Yeah. ?? Although your parents? i
g. Prunu say
it should not be? Play
contact? ports?
My old? I do not allow no? Anything,
what are you doing? I wish.
Other guys are very angry at you,
Roger.
I do not care what they think.
Why then was? I ??
What's your IQ, son?
? 185th
The real genius you are.
My is 190.
Wait, I forgot.
Is My 195th
After Why, I forgot.
My almost 200th
But this is not essential.
It is essential
that people like you and me,
They do a lot? code
when the? feel very silent? not.
You are not like me.
And why? As I grew up?
It is true that I have changed,
but when I was your age ...
I'll tell you my story,
when I was your age.
The star? I am traveling
on the island of Hawaii.
The weather is a lot better? E, Steffen.
Us continue to take-off.
Landing in the water.
Would I stop moving my arm?
I would like to sleep.
Sorry, gd ?. A friendly old lady,
but I do not know about? em talk.
Mogo If you dreamed about va? I
youth in the circus. ?? s one written,
However CALL? em stewardess.
A little rude from the wicked old woman
that is rampant in this key? nico, is not it?
Ladies and gentlemen, it? Ez ten minutes
We will of Los Angeles.
The sky is clear, therefore, should
be the way to Honolulu without this? av.
Damn, Clifford.
Why did you wake me? ? Steffen you.
Why did not you let him sleep?
Now that you're awake,
these few questions? al, o? ka mine.
When we land in Los Angeles,
we can go immediately into the world of the dinosaurs?
How many times do I have? E to say,
to fly straight to Honolulu?
How is this possible? Well, the? Ka?
? What? ? My birthday is
and we're so close to the Council of dinosaurs,
but so far ?. ? Not for? Enjaj me.
Birthday you had half a year ago.
? Clifford, the? I is the Service? Benem ...
At SLU? Benem trip.
It's not the holidays.
Could I stop for five seconds
by the Council of the dinosaurs? Would you?
When? Temper makes me ?.
? O? Ka will hit the big stroke
and then will speak like that.
? Come? Em to ...? Clifford!
Could a little stop? ? As the pike? E ?,
loving woman who gave birth to me.
You can usually master ?? em on? E?
Probably the single? It is very brave and wise.
Most likely, the
dimple in his chin.
Also, a return to a more? Erje.
? As re? E ?, the? A.
Oh, my God.
Captain, a young man? a? wish.
What's your name, son?
? Clifford.
Have you most? Ej? I master
in this? irnem world.
Thank you, Clifford. ? Could
possible? e arrived in Los Angeles,
that really started in the World of dinosaurs? ? In Los
Angeles could be landed only
If you should land in an emergency.
? As re? Ete, my captain.
Somewhere quiet here.
Where is Clifford?
Shut down the engines. ? Sorry,
I do not know why Steffen did it.
Are you ZME? Alo, sir?
Steffen, MD? I.
I got control of the airplane.
I ask for an emergency landing.
Roger, let 43rd
Harbor can track the 23rd
What an incredible story.
? This is the? E ?, not?
To die is not? On. Flights had
land, you get what you want.
But I risked? Life couple
hundreds of people. ? But there was no one ?.
But they may be.
? But they were not. ? A ...
? A wonderful story about? e,
but now I have to go. ? Okay, bye.
The story? Ele for? Ela, son.
? Sorry, the? E.
It? S okay.
Sit down and be comfortable installed.
Peppermint?
No, thank you.
It should be noted how
that day happened before.
Ve? ...
Yeah.
I'll save it for later.
I had an uncle,
that his name was Martin.
He was a famous architect.
He dreamed of two aspects.
The hotel is build transit system
the then city of Los Angeles
and at the wedding to go with Sarah,
the love of his? life.
Sarah was teacher
in kindergarten company where he worked,
and she is very loved.
Even Zaro? One was.
? Hi. Thus,? One of you.
? You like that? One.
Very good mood here. And why?
? Surprise. I'll tell you later.
No, now.
? No. ? Come on.
Enthusiasm? One will ?. This
It will surprise your? life.
We here?
? Here we are.
I'm excited. No? Hernias.
? I do not. ? No? Hernias.
What is it? ? Are you happy ??
Yeah. ? Hello.
Super will. ? Good.
? Good. ? Good.
Please don? Hernias.
? I do not. ? Good. ? Good.
Good.
Look.
Are you stunned?
? What do I look?
Hi? O. I bought it.
? So in May? Keno?
You said,
you begin? mal? ico.
It is not incredible? Minimalist? On it,
a quietly intense.
No, sweetheart?
? It is very warm.
But there was little of that? AVIC.
Sarah was a? Child wanted,
but it seemed that Martin
no hurry. ? Martin?
How many bedrooms the house? A?
? One, sweetheart.
One bedroom, sweetie.
A look at the view and the sea.
I think there is the island of Catalina.
There are quite steep.
Honey? ? I can not believe
I'm back to let.
What's wrong? ? I can not wedding to go
with you. As my first mo? FIG.
Neither he did not want children. ? Who says
that they no? em? ? There is no need to re? I.
It is clear as day.
? O? Em talk ??
About this home for males with one bedroom.
Where to sleep a child?
You? E heard? Ala
the word evil? analogue bed?
You? E heard? Al the word idiot?
? The first? sli? im. ? You fool!
Ho? E? say hi to? but not suitable
for children? No, it is complete.
Where are the kids, he loves?
Play the pe? Ina. ? Are you serious?
Children obo? Engagement. ? Like this
I have not seen them.
The number of foreign children.
It seems to me to have it? Ak.
You never said that? not waiting.
? Obo? Get him. ? What's his name?
Mason? Clifford.
Mali Clifford.
How old is he? ? Finally, I
seen in baptism. Probably the single? It has grown.
Grown? Yeah. About ten years old.
My brother and I have too little contact,
I know that Clifford
something special.
Where is that little by? Ast?
? Julien, please.
Again, did you not?
They will not even let you on the plane,
So tomorrow I will miss convention
So I lost on the thousands of e Dollars
payment method of speaking. He understands me ??
It is understood ?, what ...
Where did you get this walkman?
Did you steal it? ? No. ? Oh, my God.
Where the final but that your madness? ? Dal
to me he is a nice old priest.
La? E ?. ? No. ? Our in the? Father
la? e? with ease. As there'd let
Small beast. How can
This re? ete so adorable child?
I'm really? Al him. XXL.
How many donuts you in the ass?
Julien, calm down. Your heart.
? O? I come.
Oh, my God! Theodora.
What should I do? On the plane I need.
? O? I, o? I, o? I.
What is it? ? Excellent? I have no idea. In Los
Angeles' lives Uncle Martin, is not it?
Mogo? E could really started to see him and
World of dinosaurs, but you two to Hawaii.
Sarah?
? Martin? Yeah?
Martin, Julien on the phone.
Your brother.
Your brother Julien. Yeah. ? I know,
to this? For some years I did not call,
rather these could blame
If it decided? il, but no decision? i.
The fierce dilemma I have.
I need a huge favor.
I can not believe it. Abutting it.
? The World of dinosaurs go.
I said that I am waiting for a lucrative speech
and that Clifford on an airplane and left.
The World of dinosaurs.
? Almost she seemed happy.
I'm Martin Daniels. When? I el
by not waiting for Clifford. ? Document? Yeah.
OK. Behind the? Iva.
Contact with me. ? Thank you.
Clifford?
How sr? Henna. Please.
I love Uncle MARTINA
Clifford?
? Do not deny me.
Uncle Martin?
Yeah.
I will not hold? Eval.
Auction her uncle Martin? Yeah?
? Come on now, in the Council of the dinosaurs?
Now it is closed, it is 22:30,
I'll tell you a secret.
I have to? Living viewed free entry there,
because I created Stra? Care Larry.
You're him?
I'm Larry, stra's not Rex,
stra? I'm a dinosaur,
but do not be afraid of my sharp teeth
and roaring possible? Care.
Then are you some kind of hero.
? Let's go get your luggage. ? It is.
Someone stole my dog ​​Sneakers.
? Calm down. ? They stole my dog.
The flight 791 is unloaded?
Yeah.
Missed? Amo mountain bike,
radio, surfboard
and big, brown dog.
Many of the luggage ?.
? Excuse me. O? And he is afraid of burglars,
so we travel with all things.
? Even with a dog?
Sneakers? E could not
leave home. ? Of course not.
Sarah will be so happy. He said
I told her how much it means to me ?.
As the first? I'll see you.
? Not really. I was at your baptism.
Dru? Yl we got a good thing? One part of the day.
I very admire.
Uncle Martin.
? Good.
Now you can drop ?.
? Doke. ? Doke.
Sarah obo? U is dogs.
Come on, Sneakers. Come on.
Come on.
Come on, Sneakers.
Please, get out of the car.
Face it, Sarah.
Sama will? to death. Old maid.
Faked be? enthusiasm? learning
above the luck of others.
Others, however this will pomilovali.
Not that Sarah Davis?
How he did grow old.
Banish all their strong points and
the dry? like an old plum contract, which ...
Sarah!
Steffen is to blame.
Ashamed of themselves and their on? I.
What? Sarah!
? Martin? ? Are you okay?
Frightened? Il me. How ugly
potegav ?? ina. ? What? Potegav on ?? ina?
Your stupid dinosaur
Shower.
It was Clifford.
? Who the hell is this?
My right? Ak.
I was telling you about it.
Your not? Ak here?
? He called me brother Julien.
He flew to Hawaii and asked me,
that for a week keep an eye on him.
I gladly agreed.
? wonderful children.
Come on, you guys know.
? It is.
? Hi. ?? Hi, uncle. Served
I have friends? and a snack.
No? for it. ? Martin?
? Clifford, this is Sarah Davis.
? Hi.
?? Hi, gd ?. Sarah Davis.
What a beautiful room pla ?? You have.
If it wearing someone else,
would not even approximately? no so good.
Thank you. What a nice compliment.
? It is not pure like this? En, such as I have described?
I love you, my Uncle Martin. ? I
but you, Clinton. ? Clifford. Yeah.
Look how similar we are.
Apparently true.
Avoid bankruptcy uncle,
that we several times saw Clifford.
Of course. Now we have to uncle
Martin sleep. ? Usually I'm furious,
If anybody so ku? tra,
but not, if I am called.
Not something special?
? It is true. ? Come on, dear? Ek.
You can no ?, mistress.
? You can no ?.
Let's go, Clifford.
And you can no? you. ? You can no ?,
dear Sarah. Pleasant dreams? I wish.
Let the rainbow ...
? Come on, me? Ko. We have to sleep.
Lakes? Anke as a second home? Ini
imitate motion? animals.
Since they are? Animals left
enter in your environment,
It exists between each other
spo? esteem. The dance is called ...
It's time to shut down.
Spat.
Steffnu this seemed very cruel.
? Tell him,
that is two in the morning
and that we have to get up very early,
as we go into the world of dinosaurs.
Most? Ej? I uncle
in this? irnem the world you are.
Thank you. ? You can no ?, Clifford.
? You can no ?, Uncle Martin.
You can no ?, Clifford.
You would not lie to me, do not you?
If I could, I would be very angry.
I do not know what I would do.
? No, I would not have lied to you.
In bed.
Pleasant, enjoyable.
Uncle Martin,? Ho ring is this?
? Where did this on? El? ? In the locker. ? Come on.
Yes. ? It is very valuable.
Babi? And wedding ring.
From my grandparents?
Yeah.
Not after all my
such as yours?
What would you like to say? ? I would like to
Wedding il with gd ?. Davis and gave it to her.
Very sweet but very unrealistic.
? The ring, however, ho? Em.
Do not give it to you. Give it to me.
? But that shimmers.
Also considers it in? E ?.
This will ring a Sarah? I gave.
How exciting.
I'll be wearing rings down the aisle?
We'll see.
Laughing, right?
? Hi, Martin, Clifford.
?? Hi, gd ?. Sarah Davis.
I did not know that you are u? Iteljica.
? e would like to bring you an apple.
How nice and thoughtful of you.
? Today I ride in the World of dinosaurs.
Then I have a meeting with Ellis.
The deadline is fast bli? A.
Everything will be fine,
great ideas have ?.
Come on, Clifford. ? A little strange is,
that this nursery open? e half a year,
g. Ellis us not in? El look
even once. ? It enemy? S children.
Very? And very strange is? Iv? Care
me work. If I talk prohibited slowly,
of? not tleskati with your fingers.
? What? En disgusting ?.
Similar? Ala I was? The same? Womanizer
and that is obsessed with himself.
Apparently wears a wig. ? Come on. ? It is true.
? The carpet bear? It really is disgusting ?.
? Hi, Martin. How are you, Mr. Ellis?
? Thank you in? El. We do not know it.
This is Sarah Davis.
? Sarah Davis, of course. I know.
I am proud that we can
thanks for your? e? wonderful job.
Thank you.
How nice. ? It?
No? I do not mean he knows? such as welfare
child in? our employees ...
At the end of the meeting?
This is my right? Ak Clifford.
Say hello to my? Ef, g. Ellis.
How light? Texting. ? Hi, son? ek.
? Good morning, Mr. Ellis.
This is the most? Ej? A wig, what
I've ever seen. ? This is not a wig.
You yourself said it. You said it
carpet. ? You understand me wrong.
I never said,
to wear a wig, sir. ? Good.
What are you watching ?? Not wig.
? I know. ? Neither the carpet.
Forget about it.
Yeah.
A lot of the work we waiting for, is not it?
You can later CALL? Em?
? Of course. Me?
No, her. ? My Zaro? Enka?
? I'd love to talk with you.
Of course.
Okay. Goodbye, sir.
How about? Fascinating.
The whole model was to be transformed
in two days?
? railway line is to be moved.
3 km. That is all.
It is impossible? E? Railways to? La
then this is? no? ez Sepulveda Dam.
This is not good.
Will? ? e? esa remembered.
For a few days, shut in,
drink a lot of coffee ...
As a pro us?
As always lead to victory.
Are you okay? ? No.
? Good. ? You are right, Mr. Ellis.
If you are a visitor, register
? card number of the visitor.
Clifford?
? Hi, Uncle Martin.
Let's go now to the Council of the dinosaurs?
Clifford. I have bad news.
Now I can not drive. ? Turn
back road to the Council? s past.
Fuck you'll.
? Well so be it.
Hold me, Steffen to me la? Is.
?'re Holding on too to be wanton you!
What is it?
?? Chocolate. I urgently need it.
Good God!
Good for? What little.
I'll be right back.
Do not breathe. After the Why.
Good.
Children, the next stop:
World of dinosaurs. Who just waiting for?
O? I, p ?? e I.
? Come on.
You do not have chocolates? ? Out
I was. ? I need chocolate!
Well, I can be in the refrigerator? E
If half Easter bunny care? ka.
Give a bunny? Ka.
Thanks to this, we all have to wait,
Little prick.
Clifford?
Where did you get this clothing? Yl? ? One boy
I sold my dinozavrsko dress.
What is wrong with you?
You UEL? An? What goes ??
I'm really? Al.
? Where's my son?
When he last saw it? Tel
the money he received on page ?? u.
You pervert!
My ear!
? Where is it?
Mom, I'm here.
? Kevin.
You're fine.
What the hell is that?
What meeting? E with chocolate? ? What meeting? E
with chocolate? What meeting? E with chocolate?
Naughty you, Clifford.
I do not know what to say.
I was shocked.
Those old? E could have a stroke.
If this is? lie,
this can be closed.
And wasted? As.
I have a bunch of work, young people ?.
Throughout Los Angeles
Ana? a on my public transport.
? ef me breathing down the neck.
What? To the embarrassment of Mr. Ellis.
Do anyone know? do not say,
He has a nice wig.
I said that the most? Ej? A,
I have ever seen. It was a compliment.
He says he does not wear wigs.
And there is no tribute,
If someone re? e ?,
He has a nice wig. ? I'm not,
I say most? ej? o.
This is something else.
Whence therefore learn? on wigs?
? Since wearing my me being a professor.
Sometimes you can break
playing with her. ? Leave you,
to play with his wig?
? Frisbee.
Also on? A u? Iteljica art
you borrow,
but for other reasons.
Let's forget this wig.
I have to be punished.
World of Dinosaurs is off.
? I do not understand.
I have a bomb for you: Here I am main
and? the mayor can not? override.
As a wise man of the world
probably the single? Know ?, that is terrible,
that? s boy breaks? promise
and therefore punishable ?.
The boy was not responsible
for their next actions.
This is similar? I as a threat? Tion,
but they do not like,
so will it be? until the end of the day
in your room. Drive.
Drive.
Not the? Fair, Steffen.
The promise is a broken one,
I have punished me.
Not the? Fair.
It's never the? Fair.
The World of dinosaurs go,
However, the re? e, which ho? e.
Please? ?? Hi, I am.
How was the Council of the dinosaurs?
The decisive? I had to go. Ellis
my investments? il a bunch of changes to the model.
UBO? Ec. Clifford is probably the single?
pure crushed. No, it's okay.
In the kitchen doing popcorn.
Cover the pot, Cliffie.
Kli? Em in respect tonight.
? Tonight? ? The anniversary of my parents? S.
Did you forget? ? Of course not.
This could If I would not miss.
Good. At 19h it. Hardly? AKAM,
that star? i know Clifford.
I'll see you.
? Bye. ? Bye.
Did you hear? Al, Steffen?
Lack of time for boys dream
but enough of time for supper.
I have to be punished. World of Dinosaurs
Void. ? It would be a mistake.
I have a bomb for you: Here I am main
and? the mayor can not? override.
Steffen,
you Uncle Martin? e ??
Menu also.
Martin Daniels on the phone.
I have a bomb.
How huge hi? A.
? living in the hotel,
Uncle Martin?
You did not know? Angry because of penalties, do not you?
? Of course not, Uncle Martin.
Why would you just been?
O? I, be nice to Martin,
my sake. ?? If I need to, honey.
If still do not understand how that
? man of his age? e not married? en.
? Hi, sweetheart. ?? Hi, honey.
See, Martin is in? El.
? congratulate, sir. congratulations
anniversary and? s many years of marriage.
This is not Martin? Ak Clifford.
? Look at him, hm? Ka. Clifford, is not it?
Yeah.
? Will ?, What ?, Cliff when he grows up?
Dinosaur.
Are you the dinosaurs? E ?, gd ?. Sarah?
? Obo? Catch them.
Would glass pun? A, Clifford?
? Very much.
Martin, bloody mary? ? Thank you.
? Ultra-h? Er, sir.
Thank you to let me know.
? Probably the single? u? iva ?, which can be.
Why gd ?. Sarah?
? Because you finished? No little uncle.
Oh, Uncle Martin.
Horror Uncle Martin.
? Sarah. ? Hi, sweetheart.
How will it be? Ansko looks ?.
This dress I? E always been in? E ?.
Nova is Julia.
? Oh, of course.
They'll present Raweejnija.
I do not understand a word ...? I'll be there.
Doke.
Clifford, where you saw Sarah?
?? la meet a Raweejnija.
He took her a lady,
which looks like this.
Why have some of that face?
? This is the re? E litfing face.
What is litfing face?
No blood? I.
? Excuse me. Here's your drink? A.
Martin.
? Ms. Davis.
I knew that? in? el. Parker
He says that you try? al spread all over,
but I know that's not true. Yes No
to the? on el vajino 35th anniversary?
Is this Clifford? Yeah, I think I
really I do. ? I am Sarah's mother Anabel.
Then you most? I? Man
in this? irnem world.
How beautiful children.
Wait. Wait. Yes.
Wait!
Uncle Martin to you on this happy
opportunities? rad spoken of toast.
How nice.
Parker, Sarah, gather all.
Sarah Martin is toast.
Come on, quickly.
Thus. ? Toast.
? Let's raise glasses.
First, the? Ast Parker Davis
family patriarch amounts of Davis,
If 35 years of age engages in devotional mo? u
and very loving emu on the? father.
Very we love you, sir.
? Cheers.
Next.
It will not? toast
If Sarah Mom?
Damn, Daniels,
Continue? e.
You all right, Martin?
Allow
I want to talk with you? ak.
Va? A sauce of peppers
It is the star of entertainment.
Punished? me because you're not really started in the World
dinosaurs. ? O? Em talk ?? ? O? Em?
Something you planted in the beverages on.
? In beverages on? Yeah! Language'm jealous.
Is it not? No?
? No.
No, but it was
when I toast Parker Davis.
We love you, sir,
then ...
All they said: What? En clown.
Then he led the pun? U.
? ogo in baseball look,
then he strikes.
Watching it should ?. ? ogo see.
These? When will remember
all of this.
So ...
Do you understand?
Yeah.
Supper roof? Show.
? Ve Dinner.
How to la? One guy I am.
Clifford, he goes? wash your hands?
Okay.
Good-bye, Captain.
I could have told me,
If I had? You? Not collapse?
? i? no evil.
Tomorrow inviting me in San Francisco, where
It will open a new kindergarten. ? What did I say?
Yeah. Just for one night ?. ? By Ellis
will it be? overnight? contract in San Francisco?
My? Ef is, I can not just be dismissed.
What is with you tonight?
Clifford, what the ?? ? Borrowed
would your zadevico lip.
I have dry lips. ? People can not?
browse? epics and does not give you,
this is hygiene? no. ? Very well, uncle
Martin. ? Va? E pickles, sir.
Handsome? A thanks,
kind sir.
How polite young man? FIG.
? He said,
that although this is sometimes too much? worry
fully believes in you.
Mogo? E? E driven me
in San Francisco, if I leave.
No transfer ?, If I'm in a good mood,
they do not. ? Of course I stand.
Forget it.
? Hi.
?? Hi.
What is it ??
? Martin, how do you not? En.
Do so.
Martin, go to the bathroom
and DELETE? i.
Pages ?? e is on the second floor,
Mrs.
Martin Daniels?
Yeah.
Can I sleep with you,
gd ?. Sarah?
Quickly come, sir? On.
Terrible mistake doing.
On the anniversary we are. Zaro? I'm the one ...
Zaro? En am gd ?. Davis. ? Martin?
? Excuse me, ladies and gentlemen,
We are police officers. Without fear. Sir?
podtaknjenja suspected bombs.
What? No! I work for the city!
On the? Plan to transit system
for all of Los Angeles!
Terrible mistake doing.
? I would not say, ma'am.
I warned her.
After the Why.
? Uncle Martin! No!
In the name of everything holy,
Help your uncle!
INNOCENCE? One is! INNOCENCE? En.
Mission accomplished, my friend.
Easier? Mixing work and tell us,
Where is the bomb.
I like someone,
who would? mayor planted the bomb?
With these hot o lu? I
We want to force a confession.
Sorry.
Now, is not it? I do not see anything.
This is ...
More? E? ? I will not complicate.
Carry? E with it.
Because you wanted to catch you.
You called us. ? What?
Here Martin Daniels. At the moment I'm not
at home, I have a bomb for? mayor.
Do we hear? Imo.
No, this is my secretary.
This is potegav ?? ina. It is not necessary,
to believe me. CALL? Ite me home.
Here you go.
Speaker is included? En.
? Hi, Clifford here. I do not know where
Uncle Martin, but you hinted ...
Clifford? I'm sorry,
I'm not scared of this hotel? go.
Good morning, gd ?. Sarah.
Dressed one of you a special opportunity? Community.
Do not tell me I'm wrong.
? Thank you.
I did not hear? Ala up.
? I awake? E of 5h.
I do not sleep as much as you? Man
possible? s thought. ? Have a look at? El breakfast?
? Hi, prisoner in? el.
? Martin, so I was worried.
Thebes?
Here it is. Are you okay, Clifford? How
It was in prison, my uncle Martin?
Did you know
some? not many bastards?
What happened? ? But I
If talking about Larry Gould?
Yes. ? ?? And King potegav.
All set me up.
I can not believe it.
? I do not.
We? Re after, watch how? flakes e.
This small and its flakes.
What happened? ? He has recorded on my answering machine
and talk with me
and they are edited. When I clip
sli? al, I thought that I am? a.
How sick. ? It? S not all.
The cop who arrested me,
as Larry's cousin.
? This is not even a little bit? No.
I too did not see,
but then I thought
and really started to laugh.
The funny thing.
? For the crazy? Nico they are.
It is true.
How I was relieved.
Clifford, I did not say,
that everything will be okay?
Yeah, but those gentlemen we do not? E ?,
gd ?. Sarah.
La? Nivci are and everyone knows,
to la? nivce finally caught.
It is true that little motherfucker.
See you tomorrow.
Get some sleep, Martin looks? Exhausted.
Work me waiting.
I'm sorry I called this? Yl result
trip to Ellis. ? Do not worry, honey.
The hotel will Wemberton. The apartment
CALL me? i at any time. ? Apart? Yeah.
Bye, Clifford. Make sure Uncle
will not be back in it? s when I get back.
How funny.
? Bye. ? Bye.
Bye. ? Bye.
In the car.
They let me
v var ?? ini.
Similar? I ?? No?
Yeah.
Evil? FAMILY record I have.
He knows ?, what will it be? have you?
One-way ticket to the star? Em.
Not after? SEND me back to the old? Em,
hate? lie to me. ? Not like me.
Stop play. ? I do not play.
I'll admit, but not the star? Em.
Gd ?. I told Sarah that I
? Minko planted me, although I did not.
Its about? If you did it.
Hotel this is a shame.
He said that limited jerk.
? Sarah on? E said to me, asshole?
Limited asshole. ? And he said to me
in the pocket planted? Minko? Yeah.
Why?
? Because I hate? I. I do not know why.
He believes in what he? S ?. ? Sarah on? E
I also? ynyl beverages about, is not it?
That I do not know. ? Do not know ??
? No. ? The concepts of who ?, who else is?
I suspect the waiter. Only the suspect.
I suspect someone else.
Le whom?
If the? I said,
which I think will ?,
no? em go? ati,
because of Sarah Davis loves.
That would not do,
Although in all these relationships? ave.
I do not think ?,
it was me?
Uncle Martin ...
? Stop it.
In prison I was naked investigated
and Pony? or!
I know.
I'm sorry, I'm the one filmed.
Sorry, Uncle Martin.
Why do I do it?
I think I know why.
Since I was a little mad,
because you did not ride in the World
dinosaurs. Why are you so crazy about him,
that is what sick?
Obsessed with him.
As the only place where you can
boy like me luck one.
Business? Aj me! Shut up a minute!
Business? Aj! Shut up!
We will be? listened to?
Yeah. ? Good.
Do not touch me with dinosaurs.
Leave him there,
something I want to tell you.
When I ...
When we were little ...
Touch him, I'll kill you.
Steffen ho? E to be here. ? Get it here!
I tore off his head!
Give it to me!
Almighty? God no, boy.
Business? Aj me. I would like to make a couple
I told me to help you.
I would like to tell you what happened
me when I stage ?? al in Chicago.
Right? There was a big party is not ??
Park named Riverview.
He is about? E ever mentioned? Yeah. ? Thought
I was only there could Wed? en,
the? e but he never takes you there.
And one day ...
It was torn down,
before I ever visited.
Now I understand.
? Really? Yeah.
You ever get la? It is
My Uncle Martin?
Neither does.
Business? Aj me. I have a suggestion.
Go to your room and write? S recognition,
which I will carry to the police,
and I will not send
Back to the old? em,
Sarah could tell that we were most? A
friend. ? We're. ? Silent.
If me
Only strange sight?
or do? anything? udnega,
well at least? the thing ...
Again, this work ?. Only for
Flash behavior? a? as? love? that guy?
Watch me as? Man. No ERA? I? He knows?
than a few seconds, right? See normally.
If the? screwing around with me,
will it be? fly to star? em.
It is understood ??
? I understand that I love you.
Put me down.
Steffen is in? El back.
Give it to me!
Asks to leave him, is the only
pre? lived in the family? ini. ? Go.
No? Em by. Take it.
Go and write? S recognition.
Okay.
Soon there will be
anyone knows? in the family? ini.
I've got 20 hours.
I managed to,
If you do not panic.
Clifford, come to lunch.
Clifford?
So I was disappointed aral to go
on the train at 13:45 in San Francisco,
that poi ?? em gd ?. Sarah. I love you
with all his boy sr trades.
Clifford.
Heated? AN CHILDREN
My God, what have I done?
Clifford!
Clifford! Clifford!
Have you seen this boy?
No, sir.
? No.
San Francisco,
open your Golden Gate,
Do not let anyone before them.
San Francisco, here's your bum,
when he settles down to be.
Everywhere? E and I was with you
is the most beautiful? e, you're right for me.
You little?
STATION SAN FRANCISCO
Sleeping carriages
San Francisco.
Please? ? Who is this?
? Brian. Who are you?
? hi ho? a is it? ? From the small,
which has a? h. I think Clifford.
Clifford is there?
No, the last was in the garden
and waving the pinata. He said,
that it may be with him? ur,
If we drive in the World of dinosaurs.
Ga poi ?? em? ? Will I? E i.
Where? ? The planes ?? e? E soon
but stop at the hotel Wemberton.
Forget the hotel, let's go
as at airports ?? e. What am I going?
Wait, stop. Here I go out.
? You will? E override.
It's not just me,
but on the whole enterprise.
I'll help you.
I saw you looking at ?.
Thus. Grip is.
This is the? E ??
? I have no words. She is very beautiful.
What is it?
? No ?.
Just glad I did.
That's what I thought to be ?.
I'll go, if I port.
? It is. ? As soon as I get back. ? It is.
Allow.
What is it ?? Why Spy?
for me? ? What about the necklace?
I do not put on,
but the whole enterprise,
and I did not intend is held by? ati.
How are you child? S.
Clifford could have been watching you.
? I prefer varu? S,
who are not related to Satan.
? O? Em talk ?? Where is Clifford?
Do not worry about it. Wed? One is, it gives him that?
tonne of sugar and a book about Hitler.
O? Em talk ??
? By inviting me in San Francisco.
Why would you do that?
? To be able to host a party.
About Hitler knows? is not it? anything. I think
on Clifford. The intriguing? Ast is.
View ??
Therefore, we can not wedding to go.
So to speak
even on their own son.
All you just played, is not it?
Special bond by Clifford
and loving uncle ego.
Lagan you.
Such a? No smell at given ?.
? Excuse me, sweetheart.
You can be? E seen
Grey? s Scotland? February? ? No.
Pity you,
it will? He died a lonely old man.
I pity you.
Think ?,
that you will not? grow old?
I think I Lagan,
old and lonely?
Page, disgusting ?. Yes.
I think I broke a rib.
?? s more? I'm going to, if not stop.
Don.
These stupid necklace at all
I do not think is held by? ati. ? No? ? No.
You think I do not know what's going to
romantic down several erjicami and gifts?
Is it in? Ito me?
Not be? No, shut up!
? I'll help you. ? No!
Thanks, but no thanks.
Ljubica. If thoughts ?,
that it will be your medium? olsko
sanctimoniousness discouraged
It is wrong ?.
? Oh, my God!
My God, it's true.
Come back.
? No.
Put it back on his head.
? No. ? No!
Mind your own business.
Weasel small.
Clifford!
? Uncle Martin!
I'm so glad you're here.
? el'm on the train,
then someone touched my
Specific work. When I returned,
here were motorcyclists,
which I was tied.
They told me,
what they do on their engines.
Some of the stories were entertaining,
some horror.
? Hi, Clifford here. I do not know where
Uncle Martin, but you hinted ...
Hello? ? Clifford?
? Gd ?. Sarah Davis?
How are you?
? Not so good. And why?
As Uncle Martin me? A.
Long it has been since he came back,
However, the behavior? like a fool.
I know what you thinking ?. Too? work.
Tomorrow flew the first airplane.
I love you, gd ?. Sarah Davis.
? I love you too, Clifford.
Sometimes I? S afraid of himself.
What? En balm on my? I.
Gd ?. Sarah Davis, my lips
dry, because I was all well? tied up.
UBO? Ec small,
What do you do? ? I do not know.
I prefer the question? Aj, who was tied up,
the motorcyclists and the specific part!
Away from him.
? The bomb had threatened him, not Larry!
O? Em talks?
Why has such a face?
Help? Use ?.
? He needs it! On!
As you take him, but I will not blame me,
when his head? not turn!
Get ready
the green vomit!
Oh, my God.
My cassette.
Where is my cassette model?
How it is? El?
So I do not like.
? we live in an era of traffic stopper? tion.
On the? A projection of 2000 ka? E,
that the average speed on ...? is late?
for an hour. This fool business? Am? S ...
What is he watching ??
? No ?. ? Good.
You made changes to the model?
? Of course.
You did not shave. All journalists
herein. It looks like? like shit.
You like Willie Nelson.
I see.
Ladies and gentlemen,
of man, which led to? Planning
the entire project Mag Trans.
Mr. Martin Daniels.
Come on, Marty. Come on.
Come on, obo? Exchange gains.
Poka? I fuck them.
Thank you.
I just want to say that ...
Careful!
? I congratulate, Clifford.
Ingenious.
Who is responsible for this?
I.
? ?? En forgiveness.
Clear.
? And Willie Nelson obo? Engagement.
Lobo I underestimated.
What do we do now, Clifford?
What do we do now?
I'm Larry, stra's not Rex,
stra? I'm a dinosaur ...
But do not be afraid of my sharp teeth
and roaring possible? Care.
I love children and they me ...
? Shut up!
Look at him, Clifford.
World of dinosaurs.
Now, are you lucky? En? ? Wed? Ed? S boy
in this? irnem world, Uncle UEL? anec.
I ZME? Anec?
Because you're forced to Joppa? U.
When he dressed show you,
will it be? I need much more? Jega.
How funny.
ENTRANCE FOR EMPLOYEES
? Hi, Mitchell.
?? Hi, Mr. Daniels.
Tale mal? Ek is crazy about dinosaurs.
I would like a little tour.
I accept full responsibility.
? All right, sir.
Stra? Care Larry little lights,
please. ? It is.
LARRY, STRA? NO REX
Jump and inside, Clifford.
Are you happy ??
Yeah, I've always? Wanted.
But I've always? Wanted
to plan transit system.
You now know? is not it?
Is this your desire: what happened?
We'll see yours? Desire,
when the? vlakcu to take ten hours.
? Ten? If more I will? e ?.
Then we'll see,
how it will be after 100 hours.
? Hi, I'm Terry pterodactyl.
If I were you, I would really started back.
Larry was a terrible mood.
At? Emu world last? Asenot faring best and ...
Oops, earthquake!
Re? I before it's too late!
Ions? I!
Re? I! If term? e, which is zataval
to Larry, no pre? lived.
How did great.
Use of a laser.
Only in this way can pre? Live ?.
Sre? A, DOWN? To me.
Steffen, we did it.
We killed the giant.
Bravo! Do not forget to visit
in the? ego bar with frozen yogurt.
Larry stra? En rex,
stra? a dinosaur is,
but do not be afraid of his teeth
and roaring possible? Care.
Kids and they like to have him,
Although large? jaw has.
It was stra? No? Yeah, but fun.
For how long ?, thought that? sitting,
because I kidnapped me,
Uncle Most Wanted?
Life is? O. Let's go a little faster.
Yeah!
It was stra? No?
? Not at all.
Think ?, to first child
gd ?. Sarah and g. Martin Ellis name?
How sr? Henna.
He knows ?, what? You really should not set
on hiperhitrost, but what I can not.
Here we go.
Oops!
? Hi,
I pterodactyl Terry ...
On the help ?!
Uncle Martin, re? I am!
Uncle Martin?
? Straight? Ljujem.
Please, I'm scared!
? Me, however, what will happen, if these things? Im.
Mogo? S I? Love? Humanity do me a favor,
If I let this dinosaur after? re.
Who knows,
some? horrors will not? cause il.
What
If you come into the hands of plutonium?
I made the most? Ej? O Atomic
a bomb on it? irnem world.
Uncle Martin!
Hold my hand!
Help me, please.
? Dr? I.
Come on.
Sorry.
No, no? Em this hug.
Who'd ever wanted to hug?
? I really? Al.
When? Grief is? Love? When? Ustvo,
You're not? love? that guy,
but a machine for uni DIGIT,
by all with time
begin to hate? go.
Let's go.
If such thoughts ?,
why should we? el with you?
And do not go. Sam decisions? I.
The first? the? life
I was very confused.
I thought I did not care,
Uncle Martin what he thinks of me,
but I was wrong.
His words devastated me.
And I thought,
I'm so clever.
? ele then I realized,
that? s ruin? all
standing in the way of your dreams,
you end up alone and without dreams.
Will this happen to me?
You do?
Yes.
Many're too smart for that.
Throw.
You uncle ever forgive me?
? I begged him.
I sent him
He knows? as 287 made? yl.
All I got back unopened.
Advances ?, Lofty.
What happened to his
girl? ? Gd ?. Sarah Davis.
One day,
like a bolt from the blue,
as we have rules in those sometimes,
she called me.
She is best? Ej? O pro? It
in this? irnem world.
Uncle Martin has forgiven me.
It's dobrotno act
I changed? life.
Thank you on? E.
? Not at all, Roger.
O? E?
Were you but something special.
What you should do,
that you should move.
But I will not. ? Why do not you, son?
? I want you to love me.
How will it be? to achieve this, Roger?
? I'll write 287 place? Il.
See you next week, the? E.
? Bye.
Mission accomplished,
old friend.
Translation and adaptation:
Nina Breznik
Technical working on:
Translation Studio Milenko Babi?