Sync by Caradecuica
Happy birthday, son.
Happy birthday.
Cake before dinner?
Well, it's your
brother's big day,
let's let him decide.
Then I decide on... cake!
Cake it is.
Really?
Sure.
Yeah. I don't suppose it'll
kill you just this once.
Okay, blow out the candles
before we burn
the house down.
How many are there?
Why don't you count 'em?
8, 9, 10.
10 years old and one
to grow on, 11.
That's right.
10 years old.
And one to grow on.
Wake up. Wake up.
Do exactly as I say.
Alex, Alex...
Alex, Alex!
Come on.
Do exactly as I say.
Okay, here we go.
Here, take your robe.
Come on.
Get the door.
In the truck.
Go on.
Stay back!
Leave us alone!
Boys, stay in the truck.
You don't want
to do this.
Look... it's not you.
Stop!
Don't do this!
Check.
Can't do it.
Mate.
Fucked again!
Without even the courtesy
of a reach around.
It's been a business doing
pleasure with you, my friend.
Who's next?
Come on, girls,
don't be shy.
What about you, sugar?
Hope you have some change in
your pocket for a metrocard.
Come on.
You two girls
have fun, now.
I'm gonna go find me some
respect somewhere else.
Come on.
See you.
Hit the timer.
Well, that sucked.
It's game over.
Forget it.
Harry Jellenik.
Alex Borden.
You okay?
Yeah, yeah.
It's a migraine,
i guess.
Well, you keep at it,
young Alex.
Good-bye, Alex.
Hey! Don't do that!
Why do you do that?
My dream.
It tried to get
me in my dream.
I hurt him so he's
too weak to come after us.
You've seen them, too?
I don't want to talk
about it. Okay?
If dad finds out this
is happening again,
he'll send us away
from each other.
Do you want
that to happen? Huh?
Thought so.
Then keep
your mouth shut.
Promise?
Promise.
We need to stick
together. Okay?
As long as I'm here, I won't let
anything happen to you, Alex.
HELLOOO?
Alex.
Jason?
How did you get in?
Your door is wide open.
I thought
somebody broke in.
I expected to find some lunatic
raping your lifeless corpse.
Yes. Yeah. That would be
what you'd think.
What are you doing here?
This is where I live.
No. This is where
you house-sit.
I brought these back.
Stacy's in the car. Smoke?
No?... 'Course not.
What's that?
It's "secrets of modern chess
strategy advances since NIMZOWITSCH."
You hate chess.
I know.
So...?
So, I don't know.
Something like, something
like happened today.
I got home and I'm flipping
through every book in the house.
And, here...
Take this one. This is
a real page Turner.
I read it an hour ago.
You finished it an hour ago?
No, no. I read it
an hour ago.
Yeah...
Yikes!
When do the Klausners
get back?
In the fall.
Who vacations in Rwanda?
I don't know,
but it beats
unemployment.
Would you stop touching
the things, please?
I don't think you can call
house-sitting employment.
Alex, with a brain like yours,
you should have a job
with NASA or, you know,
one of those companies that
hires really smart people.
Yeah.
Headache?
Yeah, it's...
Do me a favor.
Lay off the speed reading.
I gotta go. Stacy's waiting.
I'll see you later, okay?
Alex?
Oh, god.
Wake up, man.
Alex! Alex!
Ira, right now,
medically, he's fine.
The curvature is completely
unbroken, inside and out.
Look, if I'm reading
this correctly,
this kid uses more of his frontal lobe
for cognitive activity than anybody
who has ever been charted.
You can't release him,
sweetheart.
No, this chart alone is worth tens
of thousands in study grants.
What choice do I have?
I have no basis
for keeping him.
I suppose a postmortem analysis
is out of the question.
Is that supposed
to be funny, ira?
Hey, buddy,
what you got there?
My head
is killing me.
Well, that's inaccurate
and quite impossible.
What I don't doubt
is that you've had
a mild to mildly
severe head trauma.
So what I need to do is give
you a cognitive assessment.
Then I'll poke a few holes
in your skull.
Holes?
Metaphorically speaking,
of course.
We'll start off with
the easy first test.
Okay?
Okay.
Okay. Look very
carefully at this chart.
Try to remember as much as
you can about what you see.
Alright. How many of the
pictures can you remember?
In alphabetical order-
apple, ball, cat, dog,
egg, fire truck,
grasshopper, hat,
ice cream cone, jump rope,
kangaroo, light bulb...
Well, that's fine.
What was that?
Why don't you tell me?
Calculate the following-a plane
flying the 3,458 mile distance
from New York City to London
has a 50-mile-an-hour tail wind.
The plane's point of no
return is 1,489 miles.
Give or take
a hundred yards.
I didn't even
finish the question.
Well, in layman's terms...
You're getting smarter.
The part of your brain
that you use for cognition,
it's just off the charts.
When we ran the test, it
showed your brain's activity.
Other than the blackouts, you
seem to be in perfect health.
None of this
solves my problem.
What if it
happens again?
Do you have any idea
what you could do,
if you harnessed even a fraction
of your intellectual potential?
Do I even care about
that right now?
God, you sound like that geeky
friend of yours, Doctor, uh...
Dr. Gold.
Yeah. You know, and
i don't like his idea
of "postmortem
analysis."
It's not that
kind of hospital.
Don't tell me the thought
didn't cross his mind.
I heard him.
You heard him
during the scan?
I heard a lot of stuff.
Alex.
Look, it's a long shot,
but I have a colleague
who's doing some research
that might help you.
It's worth a try.
Right now, I might
try anything.
I think this is the place.
Hey, we'll keep you
in our prayers. Okay?
Hey, you want us
to wait for you?
No, than ks.
It's alright.
Sure?
Yeah.
Take care of yourself.
God bless.
Alex Borden? I'm Dr. Murphy.
I don't know
how much Denise-
Dr. bell-has told
you about my book.
She just said that
i should see you.
She must have told you i
don't have insurance.
It's not about money.
You let me document your
progress with these sessions,
anonymously, of course, and
I'll treat you free of charge.
What's this book
you're writing?
It's a study of people who,
in simple terms,
have found the switch that turns on
the dormant portions of their brains.
We're documenting the ways
in which it affects them.
Migraines, night terrors,
spontaneous knowledge,
visions...
Some people even swear
they hear voices.
Well, some people
are crazy.
Do th ese symptoms
sound familiar to you?
Can you help me or not?
Alex, if even half
of what Denise has told me
about you is accurate,
you're unlike anyone I've ever studied.
Your case would
take priority.
Just promise, you'll
make the pain go away.
Whatever it takes,
i promise I'll try.
I've been doing it ever since
i was a little kid, I guess.
Lie down, focus on
a point above...
Clear my head of all the stuff
crashing around inside.
And I just...
Go somewhere.
It's all I ever wanted,
was to go away.
And I found out
how to do it.
Why didn't you tell
anyone back then?
Who could I trust
besides my brother?
And that'll do it
for me today, gentlemen.
One more game?
I'll make it quick
and painless for you.
Is that right?
Hey!
I've been waiting
almost two hours
to win my money back.
Wait your turn, kid.
And what makes you think today
is going to be any different?
Bitch.
Harry!
You really want
that game, huh?
How... how do you
live with these?
You paint what you know.
So... people, like...
Buy these things?
Beer?
Yeah.
You gonna stand
there all day?
Or are we gonna
play some chess?
I don't usually have
strangers up in my studio.
Hit the timer.
You know you're
never gonna beat me.
I'll beat you.
Maybe not today,
but I will beat you.
That's mate.
Oh! That really,
really sucks.
You know, in the future,
you may want to consider
castling your king, because it
tends to prolong the game.
Yeah.
What are those for?
My nutritionist told me they thought
they'd put hair on my chest.
And, uh... what do you
think about that?
I think he's full of shit.
Have a good day.
Okay...
Oh... sorry.
I come back.
That's al-it's okay,
it's okay. Go ahead.
Thank you.
Okay.
Jason! Stacy!
You there?
Dr. Ira Gold
was found mutilated.
In our last session
you mentioned
that something
strange happened
in the ambulance
on the way to the hospital.
You want to
tell me about it?
It's hard to explain.
I remember them, like,
trying to save me.
I was out cold,
but I could hear them.
And somehow...
See them.
I could smell what Charlie
had eaten for lunch.
Charlie?
The ems guy.
I don't know how I know that,
but I know that's his name.
Go on.
I could see Alice...
The ambulance driver,
behind CHARLIE'S back.
She kept a bag of weed
under the passenger
seat for when
things on the shift
got intense.
Isn't it possible that because
of your accident, just maybe...
What?
I dreamed it? No.
Call the hospital if you want,
ask what their names were.
Or, better yet, go down
there, roll a joint.
Maybe share some
with Dr. gold.
Oh, wait, he's dead.
Tell me when to stop.
Stop.
Ask me what's
in the book.
Go ahead.
Ask me.
"A survey of
702 clubs found-"
"that almost 70% met in saloons or
neighborhood halls that sold liquor."
Ask me another one.
Jesus.
Well, look who
the wind blew in.
You had to come looking
for him, didn't you?
Free country.
Next time you want to play
Harry, you go through us.
Where is he?
He's probably home
counting his money.
He's probably at the empire
luncheonette on Avenue b.
Thanks.
Believe me...
You're not welcome.
You can play us next time.
Deal.
Ooh! What else have you
been doing with that hand?
Ah, chess is good.
What shall we eat tonight?
Hmm, where are
you taking Sammy?
Someone did well
for himself today.
You could, too.
If you'd stop drinking
all your profits.
Hmm, yeah.
Fuck you!
You know I'd be out of sorts
without my, ah, medicine.
Your medicine. Right.
Ah, it won't take me
but a moment.
Do you mind if we, ah...
Stop off at the bath room?
You have to pee again?
How ever did you guess?
Sure.
I hate it
when that happens!
Lloyd?
You made me piss myself!
I'm gonna
slap you so hard!
Lloyd?
OHHH! Please!
Hey, Sammy!
What you doing in there?
Sammy?
Shit.
Now I gotta go.
Tanked after
only a few drinks.
Are you sure it
isn't something you ate?
Or maybe someone?
Okay.
So it ain't funny.
You aren't still mad
at me, are you?
I mean about the money.
Come on, Sammy.
I won that fair
and square.
That's the way
it's done.
Sammy?
You could have stayed here if
you needed a place to sleep.
What did this...
This beast do?
My god!
Alex, you...
You wouldn't hurt
yourself, would you?
Fuck you!
Alex! Wait!
You came to me
for help,
but I can only help you
if you're honest with me.
I never lied to you. Never.
The police have been met
with another grizzly surprise,
in the predawn darkness. This
time on the upper West Side.
Connie Sanchez
has the latest. Connie?
That's right, Brian.
Detectives have no leads
yet in a double homicide
that shattered
this quiet West Side
neighborhood
late last night.
New York residents Lloyd
Carter and Sammy chung
were found brutally stabbed
directly behind me,
in a public restroom, right here
at the 79th street boat basin.
Their bodies found shortly before
sunrise by a maintenance man.
You know, we, we,
we came, you know,
and all of a sudden, there was
cops all over the place...
I killed them.
Alex, you didn't kill anybody.
Things from my dreams...
They're not
in my dreams anymore.
You know, we've had
our ups and downs with bums...
Alex!
Leave me alone.
It's Alex, man.
It's not a good time.
It's important, man.
I gotta see you.
Are you okay?
Two good friends
are dead.
How do you think I am?
Sit down.
How much have
you had to drink?
You came here to play
chess, didn't you?
So let's play.
Maybe... maybe when
you feel better.
Better?
I haven't felt better.
And I haven't
played better
now that I stopped
taking this shit!
Check!
And check-fucking-mate!
Okay.
Okay, we'll play! Just...
It's not every day your friends
get butchered by some beast.
What did you just say?
Nothing.
Something I heard
on the news.
I have something
to tell you.
White moves first.
So, seeing that
you're white...
I do believe that
pleasure is all yours.
You know...
Ev, ev, ev, ever since
Nimzowitsch developed the,
the flexible dynamic approach
to the queen's pawn,
the chess world
has been polarized
as to what white's
response should be.
I would put the rubinstein
variation into play.
Good for you.
A little late for
the catalan opening.
You need to focus
on your middle game.
Who's been whispering
into your ears?
You don't want to know.
See? Never underestimate the
Cambridge Springs defense.
That's what Karpov did.
That's how Kasparov
kicked his ass in '85.
Check.
Well, we'll
see about that.
Check.
Mate.
The Borden sacrifice.
I haven't lost a chess game
in almost three years.
So, here's to the
Rubinstein variation.
And the Borden sacrifice.
You gonna,
you gonna be okay?
I told you.
Never better.
Here, drink up!
Uh... thanks.
I'll, I'll pass.
Do you want to play
like a man?
You drink like a man.
Tell me about
your paintings.
You wanna play another
- Tell me about your fucking paintings!
Do you really want
to know what I know?!
I scare you, don't I?!
We play!
Again!
I can't emphasize
this enough.
It's a very
serious matter.
Giving up your rights as legal
guardian of the children is permanent.
Irrevocable.
Once I place them
in a foster home,
the new parents can
adopt the children.
They can change their names,
and even move out of state.
And once that happens, it's next
to impossible to get them back.
I urge you
to think it over.
I don't need
more time to think.
I want you
to take th em now.
The sooner, the better.
I have the papers here.
If you'll
take them and...
Read th em over.
It's done.
Oh... and there's
another thing.
I want you to listen
to me very carefully.
What the fuck!
Whoa, whoa.
What's the matter
with you, man?
Don't do that.
Okay, sorry.
The other night, there
were reports of a peeper.
A what?
A fucking peeper.
I thought you might
be the perv.
Can I come in?
Okay. Sure.
Things from hell
are after me.
I know that sounds,
that sounds, whatever.
But, I... I can't
call the doctors
because they'll put me
in a straightjacket.
I can't...
I can't sleep because there's like
a fucking monster in my closet.
And I have
this headache.
Because I know things, I know,
i know a million things,
that I, I have no idea
how I know them.
I'm mastering
the game of chess...
I'm reading cervantes.
I know these things.
I know you guys
fucked an hour ago.
Your brother doesn't
know that you talked
your father into
changing his will.
What the fuck are
you talking about?
And you.
You say that...
You say that you're
true to Jason.
But when you wanted
a raise at work,
you flashed your
supervisor your tits.
Jason, that's not true.
Yes, it is.
You even let
him feel you up.
Okay. You need to leave.
Now.
Okay.
Yeah.
I didn't think you
could help me.
Is there anything I can
do for you, son?
I'm... I'm Alex.
Reverend Hartman.
You look lost.
You know, you're not
the first young man
with a dazed expression...
Who wanders in here
in dead of night.
There are things
that are after me.
Hurting
people around me.
Who is after you?
Things you find
in shadows.
They're not pretty.
They're never pretty.
When do you see them?
Night, mostly.
Welcome to the club.
What else, Alex?
I, ah, I see things and
i see these
memories of my past that
never happened to me.
Or at least
i don't think so.
It sounds like you're
really in big trouble, Alex.
So what do we do?
You're sure you want to be helped?
Yes.
That's all I want.
I'll be right back.
Our substance
independence group
meets every Tuesday
and Thursday evening.
It's very discreet.
No one has to know.
Lam...
I am not an addict!
What I'm telling you
is real!
People are dying!
Really?
You believe that?
Yes. That's what I keep
trying to tell you.
Why doesn't anyone
believe me?
I believe you, Alex.
But, important is,
what you believe.
I don't know what to believe anymore.
I don't know who to believe.
That is why I'm here.
So you say you're
plagued by evil.
Yes.
More and more.
Evil, Alex, is merely
the absence of good.
As for me, it's the proof
of good, the test of good.
There are two opposing forces,
locked in mortal combat
fighting for eternity.
What are they
fighting for?
They're fighting
for you, Alex.
For your intellect, humanity,
what you might call your soul.
You know, you have
to be very careful.
The devil can be
a very tricky one.
So, what do
i do? I pray?
Here.
Alex. A good start.
Oh, my god.
You're bleeding.
We have to leave
here right now.
Leave? Why?
Listen to me!
You have to leave here right
now or you're going to die.
Why leave?
Alex!
We are already here, Alex!
Alex, my son.
What's happened to you?
You okay?
Alex, you had nothing
to do with those murders.
You can't blame yourself
for what happens around you.
You can only be
responsible for yourself.
Bull fucking shit!
My brain is growing.
I wish I didn't
have to do this,
because I don't think
it's in your best interest.
But maybe you need to hear
it from someone else.
Then you'll believe me.
What is this?
I know someone
who wrote an article
for the "annals
of abnormal psychology."
He used to be a rather
respected metaphysician.
Over time, his theories began
to get Wilder and Wilder.
Towards the end, we thought
they were pure fantasy.
He was finally blacklisted by
most conventional practitioners.
How is this going
to help me?
By proving to you once and
for all what you aren't.
Yes?
Um, Dr. Karen
Murphy sent me.
You know.
You are seeing them?
You believe me?
Believe?
Is not empirical term, please,
do come in, quickly!
They have finally
come true.
Yes?
I...
I don't, I don't-
killings are happening
all around you,
violent killings of much
blood, much suffering. Yes?
I am Pavlovsky.
Boris Pavlovsky.
I first find out about them
at institute in Moscow.
A subject was also a "link."
Like you.
That is what we call them.
A link from world we know
to world we cannot imagine.
What are they?
Who can say?
They are not from this
plane of existence.
But only people like you,
"links" you can see them.
What do they want?
I'm not sure.
No one has ever
survived an encounter.
Link I studied is dead.
If they're so powerful,
then why haven't they
killed me already?
They are scared
of your power.
I, I don't
have any power.
Ah, but you do.
But they never stop.
Never sleep.
Where you go, they smell
you on other people.
Everything you touch,
everyone you touch-
that is how they
are following you.
Yeah, but...
It's me.
It's my fault.
Is not fault.
Is destiny. Yours.
The gloves.
The gloves. That's why you
wouldn't shake my hands.
Even now, I am in danger
with you in my house.
There are others
like me?
Once were plenty.
Now, no more.
At institute...
Soviet institute
of metaphysical science,
we study many links.
Isolate th em.
Tap into brains.
Learn that they use part
of brain other humans cannot.
Know things
other humans do not.
One link is like genius.
Two links, three links
together, like weapon.
Psychic laser.
Make the ministry
of defense very happy.
I... I'm going
to throw up.
Other link...
One who is giving
you power...
Is who?
I, I don't, I don't know,
i, I don't know who that...
Visions are new to you?
Link is someone you
are recently meeting.
That is when visions
are growing strongest.
Yes.
Yes. Oh, yes.
I know who it is.
What can we do
to stop this?
Tell me what
that means!
You'll know soon enough.
Look what you did.
You brought evil
into this house!
Evil has many faces.
Evil!
Come on, hey...
We're gonna play a game,
we're gonna,
we're gonna play a game.
We're gonna play a game.
Come get me.
We're gonna,
we're gonna play.
Play... play...
Look,
it's not you. Stop.
Stay back!
You leave us alone.
Don't do this! Now!
We have to stick
together, okay?
As long as I'm here, I won't let
anything happen to you, Alex.
Giving up your rights of
the children is permanent.
My dream, they
tried to get me in my dream.
You've seen them, too?
I've got you.
I got...
I got you!
Harry Jellenik.
Alex Borden.
Wanna play a game?
Let's play a game.
I got you! I got you!
Harry?
I want you to listen
to me very carefully.
Whatever you do, you
keep these boys apart.
Separate. Do not place
them in the same home.
But it's customary-
I don't care.
I know what's best for them
and the people around them.
Do you understand?
I got you! I got you!
What the hell is going on?
You know what time it is?
Jesus Christ!
You have to get out of here.
Slow down.
Listen to me.
You have to
get out of here.
Alex, you're scaring me.
What is it, man?
It's them.
Who the fuck is them?
Alex?
What are you doing, man?
Hey.
Alex? Is that you?
What's going on?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Calm the fuck down!
Alex. Put that thing down.
You're going to hurt somebody.
Alex.
Listen to me.
Drop the knife.
Number 2405
west 71st street.
We need some help here.
You've gotta come right now.
We need some help. You need
to get here right now.
What the fuck!?
What are you doing?
Whoa!
I can't.
They won't...
They won't understand
what's happened...
I don't understand
what's happening.
Why don't you tell us?
I can't stop it.
I can't stop it!
Stop us.
Kill us.
You okay, Alex?
Do you want to die?
Like your mother?
Like your brother?
Fucking back up!
Whoa! Hey!
Alex, put the knife down.
Put the fucking knife down.
Come on, knock it off.
Come on, man.
Stay there.
Back up.
Put the knife down!
Back up!
Come on!
Come on, we're your friends!
Back up!
Alex, calm down. Alex,
you need to get some help.
Back up!
Come on,
this is ridiculous.
Put the knife down!
I'm not going to do
anything to you!
I'm not asking you again! Who are you?!
Who are you?!
Back up!
Calm down, kid, you
don't want to do this.
It's not them!
See?! It's not them!
Drop it.
Drop the knife.
Drop it!
Oh, my god.
It's not them.
Listen to me!
It's not them,
it's not them!
It's not them!
Motherfucker!
Stop! Stop! Aah!
If we only knew something.
Anything about what's
going on in his head.
We were starting
to make progress.
Karen...
we don't know what to do.
We're not even
sure what he is.
Do you mind if I spend
a little longer with him?
Be my guest.
You may be the only
friend he has left.
There's a coma
blue in the south ward.
...please notify...
It's okay, baby.
Everything's gonna be okay.
No more pain...
No more troubles.
You have to be
careful, Alex.
Evil can be a very tricky one.
Sync by Caradecuica