(TRAIN WHISTLING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
CONDUCTOR: River City
Junction. River City,
next station stop!
River City next! Board!
It's them big new department
stores back East.
They let folks buy
anything on credit!
If I don't give credit,
I'm gonna lose customers!
You're crazy with the heat.
Credit is no good
for a notion salesman.
Why not?
What's the matter with credit?
It's old-fashioned.
Charlie,
you're an anvil salesman,
your firm give credit?
No, sir!
Nor anybody else.
♪ Cash for the merchandise
cash for the button-hooks
♪ Cash for the cotton goods
cash for the hard goods
♪ Cash for the soft goods
cash for the fancy goods
♪ Cash for the noggins and
the piggins and the firkins
♪ Cash for the hogshead
cask, and demijohn
♪ Cash for the crackers
and the pickles
and the fly-paper
♪ Look, whadayatalk,
whadayatalk, whadayatalk
whadayatalk, whadayatalk?
♪ Wheredayagitit?
♪ Whadayatalk?
♪ You can talk, you can talk
you can bicker, you can talk
♪ You can bicker bicker
bicker, you can talk
you can talk
♪ You can talk, talk, talk
talk, bicker, bicker, bicker
♪ You can talk
all you wanna but
it's different than it was
♪ No it ain't, no it ain't
but you gotta know
the territory
(CLINKING SPOON)
(TRAIN WHISTLING)
♪ Why it's the Model T Ford
made the trouble
made the people wanna go
♪ Wanna git, wanna git
wanna git up and go
♪ Seven, eight, nine,
ten, twelve, fourteen,
twenty-two
♪ Twenty-three miles
to the county seat
SALESMAN 1:
♪ Yes, sir
Yes, sir
SALESMAN 3:
♪ Who's gonna patronize
♪ A little bitty two-by-four
kinda store anymore?
♪ Whatdayatalk,
whatdayatalk?
♪ Wheredyagitit?
♪ It's not the Model T at all
Take a gander at the store
♪ At the modern store
At the present-day store
♪ At the present-day
modern departmentalized
grocery store
♪ Whadayatalk, whadayatalk
whadayatalk, whadayatalk
whadayatalk?
♪ Wheredyagitit?
♪ Whadayatalk, whadayatalk
whadayatalk?
♪ Wheredayagitit?
♪ You can talk
you can bicker
you can talk, you can bicker
♪ You can talk, talk, talk
talk, bicker, bicker, bicker
♪ You can talk
all you wanna but
it's different than it was
♪ No it ain't
but you gotta
know the territory
♪ Why, it's the Uneeda
biscuit made the trouble
♪ Uneeda, Uneeda,
put the crackers in a package
in a package
♪ The Uneeda biscuit in an
air-tight sanitary package
♪ Made the cracker barrel
obsolete, obsolete
♪ Obsolete, obsolete
obsolete
SALESMAN 4:  ♪ Cracker barrel
went out the window with
the Mail Pouch cut plug
♪ Chawin' by the stove
Changed the approach
♪ Of a travelin' salesman
Made it pretty hard
♪ No it didn't, no it didn't
but you gotta know
the territory
♪ Gone, gone
♪ Gone with the hogshead
cask, and demijohn
♪ Gone with the sugar barrel
pickle barrel, milk pan
♪ Gone with the tub
and the pail and the tierce
♪ Ever meet a fellow by
the name a'Hill?
♪ Hill?
♪ Hill!
ALL:  ♪ No!
♪ Just a minute, just a
minute, just a minute
SALESMAN 4:  ♪ Never heard
a' any salesman Hill.
♪ Now, he doesn't know
the territory
♪ Doesn't know the territory?
♪ What's the fella's line?
♪ Never worries
'bout his line
'bout his line?
♪ Or the cracker barrel
bein' obsolete
♪ Or the Uneeda biscuit in
an air-tight sanitary package
or the Model T Ford
CHARLIE:  ♪ Just a minute
just a minute, just a minute
SALESMAN 5:  ♪ Never worries
'bout his line
SALESMAN 2:  ♪ Never worries
'bout his line?
♪ Or a doggone thing
He's just a bang beat
bell-ringin' big haul
♪ Great go, neck-or-nothin'
rip-roarin'
♪ Ever-time-a-bull's eye
salesman, that's Professor
Harold Hill, Harold Hill
♪ Tell us, what's his line?
What's his line?
♪ He's a fake
and he doesn't know
the territory
♪ Look, whadayatalk
whadayatalk, whadayatalk
whadayatalk?
♪ He's a music man
♪ He's a what?
and he sells clarinets
♪ To the kids in the town
with the big trombones
♪ And the ratatat drums
and the big brass bass
big brass bass
♪ And the piccolo
the piccolo
♪ Uniforms too, with the shiny
gold braid on the coat
♪ And a big red stripe
running...
♪ Well, I don't know
much about bands
♪ But I do know you can't
make a livin' sellin' big
trombones. No, sir
♪ Mandolin picks, perhaps, and
here and there a jews-harp
♪ No, the fella sells bands
Boys' bands
♪ I don't know how he does it
♪ But he lives
like a king
♪ And he dallies
and he gathers
and he plucks and he shines
♪ And when the man dances
certainly, boys, what else?
♪ The piper pays him
Yes, sir
♪ Yes, sir
♪ When the man dances,
certainly, boys, what else?
The piper pays him
ALL:  ♪ Yes, sir
Yes, sir
♪ But he doesn't know
the territory! ♪
(TRAIN BRAKING)
CONDUCTOR: River City!
River City!
We've crossed the state
line into Iowa.
River City,
population 2,212.
Cigarettes illegal
in this state. Board!
All right, if you're
all through, I'll tell you
about Harold Hill!
You really know Harold Hill?
Never saw him in my life,
but I know this much,
he's giving every one
of us a black eye!
After he's worked a town over,
the very next salesman
automatically gets tarred
and feathered,
rode out to the
city limits on a rail.
(LAUGHING)
You think that's funny?
Well, wait till it
happens to you!
The hair never grows back.
But why should he get
rode out 'a town on a rail?
Because in order to sell band
instruments, and uniforms,
and instruction booklets,
he has to guarantee
to teach them kids to play.
Well?
And form them kids
into a band, with
himself as the leader!
SALESMAN 5:
What's wrong with that?
CHARLIE: He don't know
one note from another,
that's what's wrong with that!
He can't tell a bass drum
from a pipe organ!
I'll catch up with
that swindlin' two-bit
thimble rigger,
and when I do I'm gonna
squeal on him so loud.
Pardon.
Yeah.
Sure would like to be
around when you catch up
with that fella.
Me, too.
Well, it won't be
on this trip. Not in Iowa.
Even the great Professor Hill
wouldn't try to sell to them
neck-bowed Hawkeyes
out here, huh?
(ALL LAUGHING)
CONDUCTOR: All aboard.
Gentlemen, you intrigue me.
I think I'll have
to give Iowa a try.
I don't believe
I caught your name.
Don't believe I threw it!
Harold Hill.
That's him!
It's you! You're him,
you're Harold Hill!
You're Harold Hill.
That's him, fellows.
That's him. That's the fellow!
That's the fellow
we were just talking about!
That's... Right...
That's Harold Hill!
I won't forget
your face, Hill!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Good day!
Got a hotel in this town?
Yeah, it's not in town.
Can you tell me where it is?
Straight through town,
turn right, come to the fork,
go on from there.
Left or right?
Doesn't matter to me.
Thanks, anyway.
♪ Oh, there's nothing halfway
about the Iowa way
♪ To treat you when
we treat you
♪ Which we may not
do at all
♪ There's an Iowa kinda
special chip-on-the-shoulder
♪ Attitude we've never
been without
♪ That we recall
♪ We can be cold
as our falling thermometer
in December
♪ If you ask
about our weather in July
♪ And we're so by-God
stubborn we can stand
touchin' noses
♪ For a week at a
time and never see
eye-to-eye
♪ But what the heck
you're welcome
join us at the picnic
♪ You can have your
fill of all the food
you bring yourself
♪ You really ought to
give Iowa a try
♪ Provided you are contrary ♪
Good afternoon, Mayor Shinn.
Good afternoon,
Mayor Shinn.
It is, if you wanna
go 'round in your
drawers all day.
...and there I was in
Madison Hospital and
nobody come to see me.
Cousin Will never come,
and Aunt Bertha never come.
Aunt Bertha's dead.
Ah, she wouldn't
have come anyway.
♪ We can be cold as a falling
thermometer in December
♪ If you ask about
our weather in July
♪ And we're so by-God stubborn
we can stand touchin' noses
♪ For a week at a time
and never see eye-to-eye
♪ But we'll give you our shirt
♪ And a back to go with it
♪ If your crop should
happen to die
♪ So what the heck
you're welcome
glad to have you with us
♪ Even though we may not
ever mention it again
(CAMERA CLICKS)
♪ You really
ought to give Iowa
♪ Hawkeye, Iowa, Dubuque,
Des Moines, Davenport,
Marshalltown,
♪ Mason City, Keokuk,
Ames, Clear Lake
♪ Ought to give Iowa a try ♪
You really ought
to give Iowa a try.
GIRL: It's not fair.
She started it.
I'd like a room near a bath,
please. Facing the back.
Gregory!
Marcellus!
Why, you old son of a gun!
Shh!
But, Greg...
Hill's the name.
Professor Harold Hill.
But Greg, what are
you doing here?
Why didn't you let me
know you was coming?
I didn't know I was myself.
Besides, how could I know
you'd end up in a little
tank town like this?
Well.
You were a
pretty big slicker
when you were in
business with me.
Too many close shaves
hawking for you.
Besides, I got me a nice
comfortable girl.
Ethel Toffelmier,
my boss's niece.
Gone legitimate, huh?
I always knew you'd
come to no good.
So, what's the new pitch?
Oh, you're not back in
the band business!
I heard you was
in steam automobiles.
I was.
What happened?
Somebody actually
invented one.
No!
So, uh, give me the lowdown
around here, Marce.
Oh, you'll never get anywhere
in the band business with
these stubborn Iowans, Greg.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
Besides we got this
stuck-up music teacher
who'll expose you
before you get
your grip unpacked.
Male or female?
The music teacher?
She's a librarian.
Female.
Perfect!
That's what I wanted
to hear.
If she passes by,
point her out to me.
I will.
This your best room?
(CHUCKLES) Afraid so.
How you gonna start
the pitch?
Same old way. Keep that
music teacher off balance,
and my next step will
be to get your town out of
the serious trouble it's in.
River City isn't in
any trouble.
Then I'll have to
create some.
I've got to create
a desperate need
for a boys' band.
You remember. Now what's
new around here, Marce?
What can I use?
MARCE: Hmm, let's see.
Nothin'.
Except the billiard parlor's
just put in a new pool table.
They never had a pool
table here before?
No, only billiards.
That'll do.
I'll see you downstairs
in a little while, Marce,
and you can
show me around.
And don't forget,
music teacher.
Music teacher.
(BELL DINGING)
(BILLIARD BALLS CRASHING)
Ha! There it is.
Remember.
Excuse me, sir.
Is this your store?
Yep.
Well, either you are closing
your eyes to a situation
you do not wish to acknowledge
or you are not aware of
the caliber of disaster
indicated by the presence
of a pool table
in your community.
♪ Well, you got trouble
my friend
♪ Right here, I say trouble
right here in River City
♪ Why sure,
I'm a billiard player
certainly mighty proud to say
♪ I'm always mighty proud
to say it
♪ I consider that the hours
I spend with a cue
in my hand are golden
♪ Help you cultivate
horse sense and a
cool head and a keen eye
♪ 'J'ever take and try to give
an iron-clad leave to yourself
♪ From a three-rail
billiard shot?
♪ But just as I say
it takes judgment,
brains, and maturity
♪ To score in a balkline game
♪ I say that any boob
can take 'n' shove
a ball in a pocket
♪ And I call that sloth
the first big step
♪ On the road to
the depths of degrada...
♪ I say first medicinal wine
from a teaspoon
♪ Then beer from a bottle
♪ And the next thing you know
your son is playin'
♪ For money in
a pinch-back suit
♪ List'nin' to some
big out-a-town Jasper
♪ Hearin' him tell about
horse race gamblin'
♪ Not a wholesome
trottin' race
No!
♪ But a race where they
set down right on a horse!
♪ Like to see some
stuck-up jockey boy
settin' on Dan Patch?
♪ Make your blood boil?
Well, I should say
♪ Now friends
lemme tell you what I mean
♪ You got one, two, three,
four, five, six
♪ Pockets in a table!
Pockets that mark
the difference
♪ Between a gentleman
and the bum, with a capital B
♪ And that rhymes with P
and that stands for pool
♪ And all week long
your River City youth'll
be frittern away
♪ I say your young men'll
be frittern
♪ Frittern away
their noon-time, suppertime,
chore time, too
♪ Get the ball in the pocket
never mind gittin
dandelions pulled
♪ Or the screen door patched
or the beefsteak pounded
♪ Never mind pumpin' any water
'til your parents are caught
♪ With the cistern empty
on a Saturday night
and that's trouble
♪ Oh, yes, you got lots
and lots a' trouble
♪ I'm thinkin' of the kids
in the knickerbockers
shirt-tailed young-ones
♪ Peekin' in the pool
hall winda after school
♪ You got trouble, folks
right here in River City
♪ Trouble with a capital T
and that rhymes with P
♪ And that stands for pool
♪ Now, I know all you folks
are the right kind a' parents
♪ I'm gonna be perfectly frank
♪ Would you like to know
what kinda conversation
♪ Goes on while they're
loafin' around that hall?
♪ They'll be tryin' out Bevo
tryin' out Cubebs
tryin' out Tailor-Mades
♪ Like cigarette fiends!
♪ And braggin' all about
how they're gonna cover up a
tell-tale breath with Sen-Sen
♪ One fine night
♪ They leave the pool hall
headin' for the dance
at the armory
♪ Libertine men and
scarlet women and ragtime
♪ Shameless music
that'll grab your son
your daughter with the arms
♪ Of the jungle animal
instinct mass'steria!
♪ Friends, the idle brain
is the devil's playground
Trouble!
♪ Oh, we got trouble
♪ Right here in River City!
♪ With a capital T
and that rhymes with P
and that stands for pool
♪ That stands for pool
♪ We surely got trouble
♪ Right here in River City!
♪ Right here!
♪ Gotta figure out a way
t'keep the young ones
moral after school!
♪ Our children's children
gonna have trouble
(HORSE NEIGHING)
Mothers of River City,
heed the warning
before it's too late.
ALL: (CHANTING REPEATEDLY)
Trouble!
Watch for the telltale signs
of corruption.
The moment your son
leaves the house,
does he rebuckle his
knickerbockers below the knee?
Is there a nicotine stain
on his index finger?
A dime novel hidden in
the corncrib?
Is he memorizing jokes out
of  Captain Billy's Whiz Bang?
Are certain words creeping
into his conversation?
Words like "swell"
and "so is your old man."
Well, if so, my friends,
you got trouble.
ALL:
♪ Oh we got trouble
♪ Right here in River City!
♪ With a capital T and
that rhymes with P
♪ And that stands for pool
♪ That stands for pool!
♪ We surely got trouble!
♪ Right here in River City!
♪ Right here!
♪ Remember the Maine,
Plymouth Rock,
and the Golden Rule!
♪ Our children's children
gonna have trouble!
♪ Oh, we got trouble
We're in terrible
terrible trouble
♪ That game with the
fifteen numbered balls
is the devil's tool!
♪ Devil's tool!
♪ Ah, we got trouble!
Trouble! Trouble!
♪ Oh, yes, we got trouble
here we got
big, big trouble
♪ With a T
♪ With a capital T
♪ You gotta rhyme it with P!
♪ That rhymes with P!
♪ That stands for pool!
♪ We got trouble
Right here in River City
♪ That stands for pool!
♪ Our children's children
are gonna have trouble
♪ Right here in River City
♪ With a capital T
that rhymes with P
♪ And that stands for pool!
♪ We surely got trouble
trouble, trouble!
Right here in River City!
♪ Right here!
Gotta figure out a way
♪ To keep the young ones
moral after school ♪
Did you drop your...
No!
Didn't we meet in...
I will only be in
town a short while,
I'll...
Good!
(PIANO PLAYING)
(HUMMING)
MRS. PAROO: Oh!
Is that you, daughter?
MARIAN: Yes, Mama.
Keep on, Amaryllis.
I'll be there in a minute.
Fine, dear.
Now your exercises.
Yes, ma'am.
Hello, Mama.
I don't remember
the library bein' open
this late last summer.
It was, Mama,
you just don't recall.
Mama, a man with a suitcase
has been following me
all over town.
Oh! Who?
I don't know.
I've never seen him before.
Did he say anything?
He tried.
Did you say anything?
Mama, of course not.
Now, don't dawdle, Amaryllis.
♪ Sol do la re ti mi
♪ A little slower and please
keep the fingers curved
♪ As nice and high
as you possibly can ♪
Don't get faster, dear.
If you don't mind
my saying so,
it wouldn't have hurt you
to find out
what the gentleman wanted.
I know what
the gentleman wanted.
What, dear?
You'll find it in Balzac.
Excuse me for livin'
but I've never read it.
♪ Neither has anyone else
in this town
♪ There you go again
with that same old comment
♪ About the low-mentality
of River City people
♪ And takin' it all
too much to heart
♪ Now, Mama, as long as
the Madison Public Library
♪ Was entrusted to me for
the purpose of improving
River City's cultural level
♪ I can't help my concern
that the ladies of River City
♪ Keep ignoring all my counsel
and advice
♪ But darling
when a woman has a husband
♪ And you've got none
Ugh!
♪ Why should she take advice
from you
♪ Even if you can quote Balzac
and Shakespeare and all them
other highfalutin' Greeks
♪ Mama, if you don't mind
my sayin' so
♪ You have a bad
habit of changing
every subject
♪ Now I haven't changed
the subject. I was talkin'
about that stranger
♪ What stranger?
♪ With the suitcase who may be
your very last chance!
♪ Mama! Do you think that
I'd allow a common masher
Now really, Mama!
♪ I have my standards
where men are concerned
and I have no intention
♪ I know all about your
standards and if you
don't mind my sayin' so
♪ There's not a man alive
who could hope to measure up
♪ To that blend of Paul Bunyan
Saint Pat, and Noah Webster
♪ You've concocted
for yourself outta
your Irish imagination
♪ Your Iowa stubbornness and
your library fulla' books ♪
Well, if that isn't
the best I've ever heard!
Thank you.
Can I have a drink
too, please?
May I have...
May I have a drink, please?
Yes, dear.
(DOG BARKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Winthrop. It's after dark.
Is that a way to
greet your mother,
I'd like to know?
Hello.
Well, that won't do at all.
I'll have a kiss
if you please.
One for your sister, too.
Hello, Winthrop.
I'm having a party
on Saturday.
Will you please come?
I would especially
like it very much
if you'd come, Winthrop.
MRS. PAROO: Well, Winthrop?
Amaryllis asked you
to her party.
Are you goin' or aren't ya?
No.
No, what?
No, thank you.
You know the little
girl's name.
He won't say Amaryllis
because of the "S",
because of his lisp.
Yeah, we know all about
his lisp, Amaryllis.
Well, Winthrop?
I'll bet he won't say it.
No, thank you, Amaryllis.
(AMARYLLIS GIGGLING)
Winthrop, honey!
Why does he get so
mad at people
just because he lisps?
Not only because he lisps.
That's just part of it,
Amaryllis.
What's the other part?
Never mind, dear.
It's just that he never
talks very much.
Not even to you
and your mother?
No, dear. We all have
to be a little patient.
I'm patient. Even though
he doesn't ever talk to me.
But I talk to him.
Every night, I say goodnight
to him on the evening star.
"Goodnight, my Winthrop.
Sleep tight."
(AMARYLLIS SOBS)
Oh, there, darling, don't cry.
You have lots of time.
If not Winthrop,
there'll be someone else.
Never! I'll end up
an old maid like you.
I'm sorry, Miss Marian.
Can I play my
cross-hand piece?
May I play...
May I play my
cross-hand piece?
You may.
See, without a sweetheart you
have no one to say goodnight
to on the evening star.
I know, Amaryllis.
For the time being,
just say, "Goodnight, my..."
Someone.
You can put the name in
when the right someone
comes along.
It's better than nothing.
Yes, it is.
Now you can play your
cross-hand piece.
Now I may play my
♪ Goodnight, my someone
♪ Goodnight, my love
♪ Sleep tight, my someone
♪ Sleep tight, my love
♪ Our star is shining
♪ Its brightest light
♪ For goodnight, my love
♪ For goodnight
♪ Sweet dreams be yours, dear
♪ If dreams there be
♪ Sweet dreams to carry
you close to me
♪ I wish they may
♪ And I wish they might
♪ Now goodnight, my
someone, goodnight
♪ True love can be whispered
♪ From heart to heart
♪ When lovers are parted
♪ They say
♪ But I must depend
on a wish
♪ And a star
♪ As long as my heart
♪ Doesn't know who you are
♪ Sweet dreams
♪ Be yours, dear
if dreams there be
♪ Sweet dreams to carry
♪ You close to me
♪ I wish they may
♪ And I wish they might
♪ Now, goodnight
my someone
♪ Goodnight
♪ Goodnight ♪
(RAIN POURING)
♪ Thy banners make
tyranny tremble
♪ When borne by
♪ The red, white, and blue
the red, white, and blue
♪ When borne by
♪ Thy banners make
tyranny tremble
♪ When borne by
the red, white, and blue ♪
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
I'm sure we're all
grateful to my wife,
Eulalie Mackechnie Shinn,
for leading the singing.
Bravo, Eulalie, bravo!
And to Jacey Squires for
his fine stereoptican slides.
Thank you.
And to Ethel Toffelmeier,
our fine player-piano
player piano.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
As Mayor of River City,
I welcome you River Citizians
to the Flag Day exercises
set up for the indoors
here in Madison Gymnasium
account a'the weather.
(AUDIENCE CHUCKLING)
Four score...
(FLAPPING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(DISPERSED LAUGHTER)
Shoo! Shoo!
Ah, the newly selected
elected members of
the School Board
will now present
a patriotic tableau.
Read it.
Read the note.
The note.
Oh.
The members of the School
Board will not present
a patriotic tableau.
Some disagreement
about costumes, I suppose.
Instead the Wa-Tan-Ye
girls of the local
wigwam of Heeawatha
will present a spectacle,
my wife...
In which my wife,
Eulalie Mackechnie Shinn,
will take a leading part.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Yeah! Got some matches?
Right here.
Wa-Tan-Ye!
GIRLS: Wa-Tan-Ye!
I will now count to 20
in Indian tongue!
Een, teen,
(BANGING DRUM)
tuther, feather, fip!
(EXPLOSION)
(SCREAMING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
I'm shot, George!
Eulalie!
Who shot me? Help me!
Bring in the curtain!
(EULALIE SCREAMING)
Who set off that cracker?
GIRL: I know who did it.
Tommy Djilas did it.
Yes, it was Tommy Djilas.
Tommy Djilas,
I wouldn't leave if I was you.
MAYOR: I'm happy to say
Mrs. Shinn will recover.
No thanks to a certain
young ruffian who is
a disgrace to our city.
Four score and seven year...
"The Flag Day Fireworks
Spectacle, Last Days
of Pompy-eye will take place
"providing the rain
stops by 9:30.
"It'll be out to Madison
Picnic Park in the far meadow,
"cross the crick from
the Pest House."
MAN: How come it's raining?
Didn't the  Gazette
predict fair?
Sure did, that's why we
prepared for a storm.
The  Gazette is accurate
most a'the time and you
know it, Jacey.
You wouldn't last very long
in the bankin' business bein'
accur't most a'the time.
What are you talkin' about?
MAYOR: Order here! Order!
Order! Order!
Will you fellas stop
bicker'n in public?
All in the world that
I'm sayin' is...
Never mind!
Four score...
We heard there's
a pool table in town!
(CROWD CLAMORING)
Now just a minute here...
Well, is it a pool
table or isn't it?
Will you allow me to
get on with the exercises?
We don't want any more
exercises till we get this
pool-table matter settled!
ALL: Yeah!
Protect our children.
Resist sin and corruption.
ALL: Yeah!
Smite that devil and keep
our young boys pure.
ALL: Yeah!
Friends, may I have your
attention, please?
Attention, please.
♪ I can deal with this trouble
friends, with a wave
of my hand, this very hand
♪ Please observe me
if you will
I'm professor Harold Hill
♪ And I'm here to organize
the River City Boys Band!
♪ Burrrr
♪ Oh, think, my friends
how could any pool table
♪ Ever hope to compete
with a gold trombone?
♪ Raaaa-baaaa, ra-da-da-da-da
daaaa-daaaa
♪ Remember, my friends
what a handful of trumpet
players did to the famous
♪ Fabled walls of Jericho!
♪ Oh, billiard parlor walls
come a tumbling down!
♪ Oh, a band'll do it,
my friends
Oh, yes!
♪ I mean a boys band
Do you hear me?
♪ I say River City's gotta
have a boys band and
I mean she needs it today
♪ Well, Professor
Harold Hill's on hand
and River City's
♪ Gonna have her boys band
as sure as the Lord made
little green apples
♪ And that band's gonna
be in uniform!
♪ Johnny, Willy, Teddy, Fred!
And you'll see the glitter
of crashing cymbals
♪ You'll hear the thunder
of rolling drums
The shimmer of trumpets
♪ Tan-ta-rah!
♪ And you'll feel something
akin to the electric thrill
I once enjoyed
♪ When Gilmore,
Liberatti, Pat Conway,
the Great Creatore,
♪ W. C. Handy and
John Philip Sousa
♪ All came to town on that
very same historic day
♪ Seventy-six trombones
led the big parade
♪ With a hundred and
ten cornets close at hand
♪ And they were followed
by rows and rows of
the finest virtuosos
♪ The cream of every
famous band
♪ Seventy-six trombones
caught the morning sun
♪ With a hundred and ten
cornets right behind
♪ There were more than
a thousand reeds
springing up like weeds
♪ There were horns
of every shape and kind
♪ There were copper bottom
tympani in horse platoons
♪ Thundering, thundering
all along the way
♪ Double bell euphoniums
and big bassoons
♪ Each bassoon having
his big fat say
♪ There were fifty mounted
cannon in the battery
♪ Thundering, thundering
louder than before
♪ Clarinets of every size and
trumpeters who'd improvise
♪ A full octave higher
than the score
♪ Seventy-six trombones
hit the counterpoint
♪ While a hundred and
ten cornets blazed away
♪ To the rhythm of
harch-harch-harch
all the kids began to march
♪ And they're marching
still right today! ♪
(BANGING)
(WHISTLING)
(BEATING TABLE)
♪ Seventy six trombones hit
the counterpoint
♪ While a hundred and
ten cornets blazed away
♪ To the rhythm of
harch-harch-harch
♪ All the kids began to march
and they're marching still
♪ Right today ♪
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
That man is a spellbinder.
Men, this calls for
emergency action.
I haven't seen Iowa people
get so excited
since the night Frank Gotch
and Strangular Lewis
lay on the mat
for three and half hours
without moving a muscle!
Never mind!
I want that man's credentials.
There he is!
Oh!
Very good.
That will be five
dollars earnest money.
Thank you very, very much.
Let me see your hands.
Piccolo player.
How's that sound?
CONSTABLE: Grab that hoodlum!
He almost blew up Mrs. Shinn!
HAROLD: It'll be five
dollars, earnest money.
(GASPING)
CONSTABLE: Hurry, Sheriff,
after him.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Thanks, Professor.
Have to make an
example of him.
Ringleader, you know.
What he does, the gang does.
Lemme go.
You a' wild kid, ya.
Hanging around
my oldest girl.
His father is one a' them
day laborers south a' town.
You wild kid, ya.
Taggin' down Main Street after
my oldest girl last Sunday.
I wasn't either taggin'.
Don't you counterdict me.
We'uz just walkin' together,
Jeely Kly.
You watch your phraseology!
I know what you'uz doin',
my little Gracie seen ya.
Now you stay away
from my oldest girl
or you'll hear from me 'til
who laid the rails!
Hill! I'll talk to you Monday
morning about this band thing,
over at City Hall.
10:00 sharp.
I want that spellbinder's
credentials.
Constable, I'll be
responsible for the boy.
Oh, you don't know this
kid, Professor, he's tough,
and he's got his
gang waitin' outside.
Oh, I'll be careful.
Tommy, I'd like to talk
to you about the band.
Aw, gee, Professor,
that's for the little kids.
I'm not talking about you
playing in the band.
I'll bet you're mechanically
minded, aren't you?
Ever do anything
with perpetual motion?
Ah, yeah. Nearly had it
a couple times.
You did?
Then you're my man!
Do you realize that nobody
has ever invented
a music-holder for
a marching piccolo player?
No place to
hang the music.
Jeely Kly! Wonder where
I could get some wire from?
Look in your cellar,
that's where people
usually keep wire.
Oh, Tommy!
Yes, sir?
Now, constable, I'll show you
how to break up a gang.
Oh, miss.
Oh, young lady!
What's your name?
Zaneeta. I didn't have
any idea you was
beckoning to me. Ye Gods.
Do you know Tommy Djilas?
Well, I...
Tommy, this is Zaneeta.
Escort the young lady home,
by way of the
ice cream parlor.
Yes, sir. Do I hafta?
Ya hafta.
Yes, sir.
Ye Gods!
Professor, you're a pretty
bright young fellow.
But you made a couple
mistakes, though.
Oh?
The Mayor happens to own
the billiard parlor and
that new pool table.
Oh! What was
the other mistake?
That Zaneeta.
She's the Mayor's oldest girl.
Just a minute, Professor Hill,
we're on the School Board,
and we'd like
to have your credentials.
Academic certificates.
Nothing of the kind!
We need letters and papers!
Make him put up a bond!
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute,
what am I hearing?
Gentlemen, follow me.
Say
♪ Ice cream ♪
Ice cream.
But I don't sing
if that's what
you're gettin' at.
All right, all right,
talk then.
♪ Down here! ♪
Ice cream.
♪ Talk slow! ♪
♪ Ice cream ♪
You see? Singing is only
sustained talking.
♪ Now you
♪ Ice cream
♪ Now you, right here
Now you, sir!
♪ Ice cream ♪
I didn't know
we could do that.
From now on,
you'll never see one of those
men without the other three.
Oh, Professor, you're wrong!
Everyone knows they've
hated each other since
kindergarten! Ye Gods!
(SINGING A CAPPELLA)
♪ Ice cream
Ice cream
♪ How can there be...
♪ Any...
♪ Sin in sincere
♪ Where is the good
in goodbye...
♪ In goodbye
♪ Your apprehensions
confuse me, my dear
Like I said, you'll never
see one of those men
without the other three.
♪ Puzzle and mystify
♪ Mystify tell me
what can be fair
♪ In farewell, dear
♪ While one single
star shines
♪ Above
♪ How can there
be any sin
♪ In sincere?
♪ Aren't we sincerely
♪ In love
♪ Oh, we're in love ♪
How do you do?
I don't suppose you live
alone, or anything?
No!
I've got some wonderful
caramels over't the hotel
if you'd...
Mr. Hill!
Professor Hill.
Professor of what?
At what college do they give
a degree for annoying women
on the street
like a Saturday night rowdy
at a public dance hall?
Well, I wouldn't know
about that.
I'm a conservatory man myself.
Gary, Indiana, Gold Medal
Class of aught-five.
Even should that happen
to be true,
does that give you the
right to follow me around
wherever I go?
Another thing, Mr. Hill,
I'm not as easily
mesmerized or hoodwinked
as some people in this town
and I think it only fair
to warn you
that I have a shelf full
of reference books
in my library
which may very well
give me some interesting
information about you.
Hey, Greg!
Hi, Marcellus.
Don't call me Greg.
So how'd you make out
with the music teacher?
Ate out of my hand
the minute I tipped my hat.
She did? Oh, boy,
did you cut a swath today.
For a minute
even I thought
you knew somethin'
about leadin' a band.
Just like when you
used to imitate
that band-concert
fellow in Joplin.
Yeah.
Ah, kid stuff.
I'm in rare form these days.
Just keep your eyes on me
for the next three weeks.
Three weeks?
It only used to take ten days
for the instruments to arrive.
Still does. But it takes
three weeks for the uniforms.
Oh, no, Greg.
You haven't added uniforms?
Uniforms and
instruction books.
Instruction books?
But, you can't pass yourself
off as a music professor.
I mean not for
any three weeks.
Marce.
But you don't know
one note from another.
I have a revolutionary
new method called
the "Think System"
where you don't bother
with notes.
But in three weeks...
Why that's the Fourth
of July sociable.
The people will want
to hear music.
You'll have to
lead a band.
When the uniforms arrive
they forget all that,
at least long enough
for me to collect and leave.
Oh, this is a refined
operation, Marce,
and I've got it timed
right down to the last wave
of the brakeman's hand
on the last train
out 'a town.
And now,
Mr. Washburn...
If you'll excuse me.
Gonna line yourself up
a little canoodlin', huh?
Uh, well...
Say, I could fix you up
with Ethel's sister.
Lovely girl,
teaches Sunday School.
Oh, no.
♪ No wide-eyed, eager
wholesome, innocent
Sunday School teacher for me
♪ That kinda girl
spins webs no spider ever...
♪ Listen, boy...
♪ A girl who trades
on all that purity
♪ Merely wants to trade
my independence
for her security
♪ The only affirmative
she will file
♪ Refers to marching
down the aisle
♪ No golden, glorious,
gleaming, pristine goddess
♪ No, sir
♪ For no Diana
do I play faun
♪ I can tell you that
right now
♪ I snarl and I hiss
♪ How can ignorance
be compared to bliss
♪ I spark, I fizz
♪ For the lady
who knows what time it is
♪ I cheer, I rave
♪ For the virtue
I'm too late to save
♪ The sadder-but-wiser
girl for me
Ooh, wow.
♪ No bright-eyed blushing
breathless baby doll baby
♪ No, sir, that kinda
child ties knots
♪ No sailor ever knew
♪ I prefer to take a chance
♪ On a more adult romance
♪ No dewy young miss
who keeps resisting
♪ All the time
she keeps insisting
♪ No wide-eyed, wholesome
innocent female
♪ No, sir
♪ Why she's the fisherman
I'm the fish, you see
♪ Plop! I flinch, I shy
♪ When the lass
with the delicate air goes by
♪ I smile, I grin
♪ When the gal with
a touch of sin walks in
♪ I hope, I pray
♪ For Hester to win
just one more "A"
♪ The sadder-but-wiser girl's
the girl for me
♪ The sadder-but-wiser girl
for me ♪
MRS. SQUIRES:
Ooh, don't you love it?
It's the latest from Chicago.
MAUD: Kansas City.
MAUD: Needs a feather.
MRS. SQUIRES: Maybe two.
MRS. SQUIRES: Oh, my goodness,
it's Professor Hill.
(WOMEN SHRIEKING
IN EXCITEMENT)
Oh, Professor.
Won't you please give us
your opinion on these hats?
Now, what's the latest
fashion in Chicago?
Are feathers
de rigueur or passe?
Passe.
Oh, well, I don't consider
myself an expert.
Oh, Professor Hill.
We're all agog.
Simply agog!
On the qui vive.
Everyone's so excited
about the band.
I'm Ethel Toffelmeier,
the pianola girl?
Oh, you're Ethel Toff...
That hat, it's scrumptious.
(ALL GIGGLING)
I'm Mrs. Dunlop,
and this is Mrs. Squires,
and Mrs. Hix
and of course you've met
Eulalie Mackechnie Shinn,
our Mayor's wife?
Oh, Eulalie,
isn't this exciting?
Oh, I couldn't say.
I could not say.
Oh, no. I could not say
at this time.
My husband will wish
to investigate, I'm sure.
So naturally,
I'm reticent.
Yes, I'm reticent.
Of course, Mrs. Shinn,
I understand.
But you see,
part of my music plans
include a committee
on the dance and...
Wait...
Now wait, do that again,
Mrs. Shinn.
Your foot, the way
you raised it just now.
Well, I have a bunion there
that bothers me.
Oh, what grace.
Oh.
What natural flow
of rhythm.
Oh.
What expression of line
and movement.
Oh, you must accept
the chairmanship
of the Ladies Auxiliary
for the Classic Dance.
Mustn't she, ladies?
WOMEN: Oh, yes!
You must.
Oh, every move you make,
Mrs. Shinn,
bespeaks Delsarte.
(GASPING)
Oh, the way
you move your hands...
Oh, I...
Yes, yes
and turn your head.
Oh, Mrs. Shinn,
I would give a year's pay
to see you dance
the  Shipoopi
at the Fourth of July
sociable.
The  Shipoopi?
All the rage
in New York and Paris.
(GASPING)
Oh, oh, Mrs. Shinn,
you can't refuse.
Not someone with
your natural ability.
Say yes.
Well...
Eulalie Mackechnie Shinn.
Well... I... That is...
Dancing.
Well...
Then you'll accept
the chairmanship?
Yes, indeed.
(ALL SHRIEKING)
And to my committee,
I would like to say
to all of...
Uh, thank you.
Thank you.
Oh.
And about the young lady
who works at the library?
Miss Paroo,
I think it is.
ALL: Ooh!
Mmm.
She plays the piano.
Oh, she plays...
Yes, she plays.
Pick-pick!
And not just the piano,
oh, no!
Isn't that right,
ladies?
Talk a little,
talk a little.
♪ Pick a little
talk a little, pick
a little, talk a little
♪ Cheep cheep cheep
talk a lot, pick a little more
♪ Pick a little
talk a little
pick a little, talk a little
♪ Cheep cheep cheep
talk a lot, pick a little more
♪ Pick a little
talk a little
pick a little, talk a little
♪ Cheep cheep cheep
talk a lot, pick a little more
♪ Pick a little
talk a little
pick a little, talk a little
♪ Cheep cheep cheep cheep
cheep cheep cheep cheep
Professor, her kind of woman
doesn't belong
on any committee.
Of course, I shouldn't
tell you this,
but she advocates
dirty books.
Dirty books?
Chaucer.
Rabelais!
Balzac.
♪ Cheep cheep cheep cheep
cheep cheep cheep cheep
And the worst thing is,
well, of course,
I shouldn't tell you this...
I'll tell.
The man lived on my street,
let me tell.
Stop!
(SINGING STOPS)
I'll tell.
She made brazen
overtures to a man
who never had a friend
in this town
'til she came here.
Old Miser Madison.
Miser Madison?
Madison Gymnasium?
Madison Picnic Park?
Madison Hospital?
That Miser Madison?
Exactly. Who did he think
he was anyway?
I should say. Showoff.
Gave the town
the library too, didn't he?
Well, that's just it.
When he died he left
the library building
to the city...
But he left
all the books to her.
She was seen going
and coming from his place.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yes!
That woman made
brazen overtures...
(LADIES RESUME SINGING)
...with a gilt-edge guarantee.
She had a golden glint
in her eye,
and a silver voice
with a counterfeit ring.
Just melt her down
and you'll reveal
a lump of lead
as cold as steel here,
where a woman's heart
should be.
♪ He left River City
the library building
♪ But he left
all the books to her
♪ Chaucer
♪ Rabelais
♪ Balzac
♪ Cheep cheep cheep cheep
cheep cheep cheep cheep
♪ Pick a little
talk a little
pick a little, talk a little
Just a minute here.
We need to see
your credentials.
Yes, of course.
I have just what you want
over at the hotel.
Come with me.
Goodnight, ladies.
♪ Cheep cheep cheep cheep
cheep cheep cheep cheep
♪ Goodnight, ladies
♪ We're going to leave you now
♪ Farewell, ladies
(CONTINUE SINGING)
♪ We're going to leave you now
♪ Cheep cheep cheep cheep
cheep cheep cheep cheep
♪ Pick a little
talk a little, cheep ♪
Oh!
(WHISTLING)
(DOG BARKING)
(RINGS DOORBELL)
Just a minute here.
Are you soliciting?
You haven't got
a license.
Why no,
Mayor Shinn, I...
I collect doorbells
and this particular sample
has an unusual
tone quality that...
Flattery will not
avail you, sir.
Soliciting is statutory
in this county,
malfeasance
without a permit.
Why haven't you been
down to City Hall
with your references?
Must have just
missed you. I...
Oh, Mr. Mayor,
your hand...
What? What?
Oh, no, that spread
of the little finger.
It's hereditary.
Oh, it is...
What does that mean?
That means that
your son's little finger
is perfectly situated
to operate the spit valve
on a B-flat flugelhorn.
Is that good?
Good?
It means that America
has at last produced an artist
who can flugel
the Minute Waltz
in 50 seconds.
How do I get
one of those horns?
Sign right here,
Mr. Mayor.
That'll be $17,
import fee.
Yes, sir.
Just think, I could'a
missed this whole...
(DOG BARKING)
I haven't got any son!
You're unscrypulous,
flew-by-night...
You unflypulous...
You be down at City Hall
with your by-God papers
at 3:00.
You mean this afternoon?
I couldn't make myself
any plainer
if I'se a Quaker
on his day off.
(GIGGLING AND
INDISTINCT TALKING)
Shh!
(GASPING)
It's all right.
I know everything
and it doesn't make
any difference.
What are you
talking about?
You were probably
very young.
Anyone can
make a mistake.
What?
No apologies,
no explanations, please.
I'm only in town
a short time and...
The sadder-but-wiser
girl for me.
Will you please
make your selection
and leave?
I have.
Well, what do you want
to take out?
The librarian.
Quiet, please.
(WHISPERS)
The librarian.
You're not listening,
Marian.
Look!
♪ Marian... ♪
Marbles. Six steelies,
eight aggies,
a dozen peewees
and one big glassie,
with an American Flag
in the middle.
I think I'll drop 'em.
No!
Shh!
♪ Madam Librarian
Oh!
♪ What can I do, my dear
to catch your ear?
♪ I love you madly, madly
Madam Librarian, Marian
♪ Heaven help us
if the library caught on fire
♪ And the Volunteer
Hose Brigademen
♪ Had to whisper the news
to Marian...
♪ Madam Librarian!
♪ What can I say, my dear
to make it clear
♪ I need you badly, badly
Madam Librarian, Marian
♪ If I stumbled and I busted
my what-you-may-call-it
♪ I could lie
on your floor unnoticed
♪ 'Til my body
had turned to carrion
♪ Madam Librarian
♪ Now in the moonlight
a man could sing it
♪ In the moonlight
♪ And a fellow would know
that his darling
♪ Had heard ev'ry word
of his song
♪ With the moonlight
helping along
♪ But when I try in here
to tell you, dear
♪ I love you madly, madly
Madam Librarian, Marian
Shh!
♪ It's a long lost cause
I can never win
♪ For the civilized world
accepts as unforgivable sin
♪ Any talking out loud
with any librarian
♪ Such as Marian
♪ Madam Librarian
(GIRLS SHRIEKING
IN EXCITEMENT)
(WHISTLES)
(GASPS)
(GIGGLES)
Ah.
♪ But when I try in here
to tell you, dear
♪ I love you madly, madly
Madam Librarian, Marian
♪ It's a long, lost cause
I can never win
♪ For the civilized world
accepts as unforgivable sin
♪ Any talking out loud
with any librarian
♪ Such as Marian
♪ Madam Librarian ♪
No!
(ALL SHUSHING)
Mrs. Paroo, do you realize
you have the facial
characteristics of
a cornet virtuoso?
I don't know if I understand
you entirely, Professor.
If your boy has that
same firm chin,
those splendid
cheek muscles, by George.
Oh, not that he could
ever be really great,
you understand.
Oh, is that so?
And in the name
of Saint Bridget,
why not?
Well, you see,
all the really great
cornet players
were Irish.
O'Clark, O'Mendez,
O'Klein.
But Professor,
we are Irish.
No.
Yes.
No!
(LAUGHS)
Well, that clinches it.
That clinches it.
Sign here, Mrs. Paroo.
Your boy was born
to play the cornet.
Oh!
Fine, fine.
That'll be $7
earnest money,
with nothing more due
till the first installment
payable at the opening
of band practice.
Thank you.
Oh, and of course,
I'll need the boy's
measurements
for his band uniform.
His uniform!
(BOY SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
I got ya.
Hello, son.
Certainly, certainly
his uniform.
And there won't be
a penny due until delivery,
just in time for
the Fourth of July,
which gives him
three weeks to enjoy,
to anticipate, to imagine,
at no cost whatever.
Never allow
the demands of tomorrow
to interfere
with the pleasures
and excitements of today.
Would it have a, a...
A stripe? A stripe.
Certainly, my boy.
A wide red stripe
on each side.
What do you think
of that?
(DOG BARKING)
You'll have to excuse
Winthrop, Professor.
We can't get him to say
three words a day, even to us.
And if you can get him
to play in the band,
you'll have St. Michael's
own way with you.
If anybody can do it,
I'll bet you can.
Out of a crowd,
I'll pick you
for a hod-carrying,
clay pipe smokin',
shamrock wearin',
harp playin',
Mavorneen-pinchin',
Tara's hall
minstrel-singin' Irishman.
Be-gob and be-jabbers.
Where are ye from,
me boy?
Gary, Indiana.
I knew it! Gary...
Where did you say?
Gary, Indiana.
♪ Gary, Indiana, Gary, Indiana
Gary, Indiana
♪ Let me say it
once again
♪ Gary, Indiana, Gary, Indiana
Gary, Indiana
♪ That's the town
that knew me when
♪ If you'd like to have
a logical explanation
♪ How I happened
on this elegant syncopation
♪ I will say without
a moment of hesitation
♪ There is just one place
that can light my face
♪ Gary, Indiana
♪ Gary, Indiana,
not Louisiana, Paris
France, New York, or Rome
♪ But Gary, Indiana
♪ Gary, Indiana
♪ Gary, Indiana,
my home sweet home ♪
In fact, Gary Conservatory
was my alma mater.
Was she now?
(DOOR OPENS)
Oh, why, yes.
Gold Medal Class
of aught-five.
Oh!
Ooh!
Howdado, Miss Paroo.
Howdado, Mr. Hill.
Oh, of course. Paroo.
I thought the name
sounded familiar.
He wants to put Winthrop
in the band.
We're not interested, Mama.
But Marian,
the boy might have
his father's musical gift.
He does have
me jaw, you know.
Oh, your husband
musical?
Well, I'd like
to have a talk with him.
I'm sure
that we could...
Do you burst in
on everyone's home
like this?
Prying into
personal affairs?
We're not interested.
Marian!
Well, that's one for
and one against.
Now why not let
the boy's father decide?
The boy's father is dead.
Anything else?
Oh, I'm sorry.
But that's all the more
reason that your brother
should have
something like this.
My brother
is an eight-year-old
problem child
who can't understand
why our father was taken away.
Would you care
to explain it to him?
He's been brooding
about it for two years.
As to your musical tricks,
why don't you go into business
with some nice carnival man
who sells gold-painted watches
and glass-diamond rings?
Musical tricks?
Well, Miss Paroo,
I hardly...
I get the feeling
she likes the idea.
Oh, a little cautious perhaps,
but I admire that in a woman.
Keep me alive
and I'll be back
later in the week.
Oh!
(DOG BARKING)
One moment,
Professor Hill.
About the boy's
measurements,
I make all his clothes,
sleeve 21, waist 18,
crotch 14.
Fine! Fine,
that's all I need.
Now, I must get back
to the hotel.
Professor, I do hope
you'll excuse Marian.
She's not really...
Oh, please. Don't worry
about a thing.
I'm sure that at heart
she's as lovely as yourself.
Good day to ya,
Widow Paroo.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(HUMMING)
Has he gone?
He has.
And I hope
not forever.
Darlin', don't you ever think
about your future?
Gary, Indiana,
Conservation Class
of aught-five.
Now darlin'...
Now Mama,
surely a girl's future
doesn't depend
on encouraging
every fast-talking,
self-centered,
woman-chasing, traveling man
who comes to town.
And the fact that
he claims his commodity
is music does not,
in this particular case,
impress me.
All right, darlin',
all right.
Only it's a well-known
principle
that if you keep
the flint in one drawer
and the steel in another,
you'll never strike
much of a fire.
Mama!
Winthrop!
Winthrop! I know
you're out there.
(SIGHS) Winthrop.
Please go to the post office
and ask Miss Grubb if a
package has arrived for me.
It's a book, the  Indiana State
Educational Journal
1901-1910.
Do I hafta?
You won't have to
talk to anyone.
I've written it all down.
Thanks, Win.
What are you up to?
What do you need
with another book?
I have a feeling
this book may poke
some large holes
in the Professor's claims.
Well, I give up.
At your age,
if you don't mind my askin',
what kinda white knight
do you expect to come
ridin' along?
Well, I'm not waiting
for Luther Greiner
who backs me into
the Ancient History shelf
every time he comes
into the library.
Oh, he does?
♪ All I want is a plain man
♪ A modest man, a quiet man
♪ A straightforward
and honest man
And not Ed Gammidge
and that buggy of his
with the removable
back seat.
But I'm not waiting
for a man in shining
white armor either.
♪ My white knight
♪ Not a Lancelot
♪ Nor an angel with wings
♪ Just someone to love me
♪ Who is not ashamed
of a few nice things
♪ My white knight
♪ What my heart would say
if it only knew how
♪ Please, dear Venus
♪ Show me now
♪ All I want is a plain man
♪ All I want is a modest man
♪ A quiet man, a gentle man
♪ A straightforward
and honest man
♪ To sit with me in a cottage
♪ Somewhere in
the state of Iowa
♪ And I would like him to be
♪ More int'rested in me
♪ Than he is in himself
♪ And more interested in us
♪ Than in me
♪ And if occasionally
he'd ponder
♪ What makes Shakespeare
and Beethoven great
♪ Him I could love 'til I die
♪ My white knight
♪ Not a Lancelot
♪ Nor an angel with wings
♪ Just someone to love me
♪ Who is not ashamed
of a few nice things
♪ My white knight
♪ Let me walk with him
while the others ride by
♪ Walk and love him
♪ 'Til I die
♪ 'Til I die ♪
Hey, Zaneeta.
Tommy, Mom and Papa
are on their way to the bank.
They could come
in here any minute.
Ye Gods!
All right, then meet me
after supper.
I can't.
It's Epworth League night.
Meet you where?
The footbridge.
You see? Isn't that just
what I said?
Last time the lumberyard
and now the footbridge.
Then where will you
meet me after that?
In the Black Hole of Calcutta?
Ye Gods.
I only wanna show you
my invention.
What invention?
My music holder
for a marching
piccolo player.
It still has a couple
of minor flaws.
See, when you keep it
tight enough
to hold the music steady,
you cut off the circulation
and you can't wiggle
your fingers.
Meanwhile,
you could go blind.
Shh! It's Miss Paroo.
Miss Paroo.
Oh, I'll be right
with you.
MARIAN: Oh, yes. That's
a very good book.
(TELEGRAPH BEEPING)
♪ Oh-ho, the Wells Fargo wagon
is a-comin' down the street
♪ Oh, please, let it be for me
♪ Oh-ho, the Wells Fargo wagon
is a-comin' down the street
♪ I wish, I wish I knew
what it could be
♪ I got a box of maple sugar
on my birthday
♪ In March I got
a grey mackinaw
♪ And once I got some
grapefruit from Tampa
♪ Montgomery Ward sent me
a bathtub and a crosscut saw
♪ Oh-ho, the Wells Fargo wagon
is a-comin' now
♪ Is it a prepaid surprise
or C.O.D.
♪ It could be curtains
♪ Or dishes
♪ Or a double boiler
♪ Or it could be...
♪ Yes, it could be
♪ Yes, you're right,
it surely could be
♪ Somethin' special
♪ Somethin' very,
very special now
♪ Just for me ♪
Mayor Shinn,
I've found some
very interesting
information
in this book
about Professor Hill's
alma mater.
His who?
His university.
I know all about that.
In fact, that's the only thing
I can ever
get out of him.
Gary Conservatory,
class of aught-five.
Yes, well, if you'll just
take time to read a little bit
about the Conservatory
I don't think you'll
have to look much further.
It's on page...
Papa!
The Wells Fargo Wagon's
just comin' up from the depot.
I know, dearie!
It could be
the band instruments!
The band instruments! Ha!
Excuse us.
♪ Oh-ho, the Wells Fargo wagon
is a-comin' down the street
♪ Oh, don't let him
pass my door
♪ Oh-ho, the Wells Fargo wagon
is a-comin' down the street
♪ I wish I knew
what he was comin' for
♪ I got some salmon
from Seattle last September
♪ And I expect
a new rockin' chair
♪ I hope I get my raisins
from Fresno
♪ The D.A.R. have sent
a cannon for the
courthouse square.
♪ Oh-ho, the Wells Fargo wagon
is a-comin' now
♪ I don't know
how I can ever wait to see
♪ It could be something
for someone
♪ Who is no relation
but it could be
♪ Yes, it could be,
yes, you're right
♪ It surely could be
♪ Something special
♪ Something very
very special now
♪ Just for me
Oh, there it is.
ALL:
♪ Oh-ho, you Wells Fargo wagon
keep a-comin'
keep a'comin'
♪ Oh-ho, you Wells Fargo wagon
♪ Don't you dare
to make a stop
♪ Until you stop for me ♪
(CHEERING)
Yay!
It's the band instruments!
Here you are, Winthrop.
My cornet!
Gee, thanks, Professor!
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Sister! Sister!
Isn't this the most
scrumptious
solid gold thing
you ever saw?
I never thought
I'd ever see
anything so scrumptious
as this scrumptious
solid gold thing.
Oh, Sister, Sister!
HILL: Men!
You'll all be given individual
instruction in due course.
Until then stay
off the streets.
Get acquainted
with your instruments,
and think about
the  Minuet in G.
♪ La de da de da
de da de da
♪ La de da, la de da ♪
I better hear some
by-God tootin' out'a them
horns in pretty short order
or I'll see you
in front of the grand jury
over at the County Seat.
Now, Miss Paroo,
about that book...
EULALIE: Come, George.
Tempus fugits.
You watch
your phraseology.
George, I only...
Now, get along
if you want to.
I need to get something
from the librarian.
But George, the bank
will be closing.
Miss Paroo, the book.
Yes, of course.
The Ladies Dance Committee
meets Tuesdays
at the High School.
They're rehearsing
for the Fourth of July
sociable.
I know they'd like
you to be there.
They would?
Very much.
You'll come,
won't you?
♪ La de da de
da de da de da
♪ La de da
That's it, men.
♪ La de da de
da de da de da
Don't stop.
♪ La de da de
da de da de da
♪ La de da de da
de da de da
♪ La de da ♪
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
EULALIE: Lovely, ladies,
lovely and turn.
Take the body with you.
Uh, lovely.
Now let's have a go
at our Grecian Urns.
Positions.
One Grecian urn...
And a fountain.
Position.
Oh!
Trickle, trickle, trickle,
trickle, trickle, trickle,
trickle, trickle, trickle.
Smile, girls, smile.
(SIGHING) Lovely, ladies,
lovely.
I predict that
our Delsarte display
will be the highlight
of the Fourth of July
Ice Cream Sociable.
(SQUEALING IN EXCITEMENT)
♪ It's you in the sunrise
♪ It's you in my cup
And remember, ladies
don't make me tell you again,
always keep your faces
to the audience.
(MEN SINGING)
♪ It's you
All the way into town
EULALIE: And thank you,
Miss Paroo,
for your excellent
accompaniment.
Splendid!
(APPLAUDING)
Oh, thank you.
Yes, thank you.
Shouldn't you be
dancing with them?
I'm really much happier
at the piano.
But you do dance,
don't ya?
I really have
to get home.
♪ It's you on my pillow
in all of my dreams
♪ 'Til once more
the morning breaks through
♪ What words could be saner
♪ Or truer or plainer
than it's you
♪ It's you
♪ Yes, it's you
♪ Oh, yes, it's you
♪ It's you in the sunrise
♪ It's you in my cup
♪ It's you all the way
into town
♪ It's your sweet
"Hello, dear"
♪ That sets, that sets me up
♪ And it's your,
your "Got to go, dear"
♪ That gets,
that gets me down ♪
Take your hands
off my daughter!
Papa!
You wild kid, ya!
Mr. Shinn, your honor.
Your daughter and I
are goin' steady
behind your back.
Why you!
Well, we'd rather do it
in front a'your back but...
Do what?
Well...
Never mind.
(GASPS)
I'm going to warn
you once more.
If I ever catch you
touching my daughter,
I'll by-God horsewhip you
'til Hell won't have it again.
But, George!
Not one poop
out'a you, madam!
He means peep.
Yes!
And now get off
the school property.
I got as much right
to be here as anybody.
How do you get
any right around here?
Aiding and abetting
the swindling activities
of this spellbinding
cymbal salesman?
Now, Mr. Mayor,
if you please...
I'll settle your hash
as soon as I get
these premises
offa' my oldest girl.
All right, all right,
but in the meantime
I want you to know
that I'm vouching
for Tommy Djilas.
This boy's got the confidence
of every kid in town.
You'll be standing in line
waiting to shake his hand
by the time our band
plays its first concert.
By the time your band
plays its first concert,
the individual members'll
have to foregather
in wheelchairs
on account of the broken legs
they'll get from tripping
over their beards.
You know what I see
written all over you?
Reform school!
Papa, please.
It's Capulets like you make
blood in the market place.
Ye Gods.
You watch your phraseology,
young woman.
You go home
and stay in your room.
I'll tell you something,
my fine young feathered...
My feathered young...
Never mind!
And you, get out of here,
you wild kid, ya.
All right, all right,
Tommy, let me buy you
a sarsaparilla.
I hate you.
Eulalie!
Now George, I only...
You tend to your dance.
But...
Oh!
MAYOR:
I'll handle this my way.
Mr. Mayor, you are
not being fair.
Now, you stay out
of this, Miss Paroo.
And by the way,
thanks for nothin'.
I've read that book
you gave me
from cover to cover
for a whole week now,
and didn't find a thing.
Oliver!
Jacey! Olin! Ewart!
I want that man's references
and I want 'em tonight!
Don't let him
out'a your sight.
He's slipprier'n a
Mississippi sturgeon!
Do you mean you want us
to get his credentials?
Get his papers
or get him in jail!
I couldn't make myself
any clearer
if I was a button-hook
in the well water.
Come on. Let's go.
Okay.
Thank you.
Now you enjoy yourself.
Excuse me.
Hello, Miss Marian.
Thanks for the sarsaparilla,
Professor, and the talk.
Miss Marian.
Professor Hill,
I think Mayor Shinn
has behaved abominably,
and I just wanted to say
it was wonderful of you
coming to Tommy's defense
back there.
Oh, that was nothing.
Oh, yes it was.
Oh, no, no.
A man can't dodge
the issue
every time a little
personal risk is involved.
What does
the poet say?
"A coward dies
a thousand deaths,
"the brave man only
"500."
Unfortunately, of course,
the Mayor was already
pretty mad at me
on account of
his billiard parlor.
Now...
Oh, I suppose
a recommendation
from a musical authority
such as yourself
would help but...
I couldn't think of asking you
to do a thing like that.
Why not?
You mean, you would?
I'd be glad to.
I just wish I was
a little more informed.
I've been wanting
to talk to you
about Winthrop's cornet.
His cornet?
Mother-of-pearl keys.
Oh, I'm sure it's fine.
It's just that
he never touches it.
Oh, the first week or so,
he made a few experimental,
uh, blats,
I guess you'd say?
Yes, yes, blats.
And he sings the  Minuet in G
almost constantly.
♪ La de da de
da de da de da
La de da ♪
But he never touches
the cornet.
Yes, well...
He says you told him
it wasn't necessary.
Well...
He tells me about some
"Think System."
If he thinks
the  Minuet in G,
he won't have to bother
with the notes.
Now, Professor...
Miss Marian,
the Think System
is a revolutionary method,
I'll admit.
But, so was Galileo's
conception of the Heavens,
Columbus' conception
of the egg,
uh, globe,
Bach's conception
of the Well-Tempered
Clavichord. Hmm?
Hmm.
Oh, now I cannot discuss
these things here in public,
but if you'll
allow me to call.
When may I call?
Why, any night
this week.
♪ Pick a little,
talk a little,
pick a little, talk a little
♪ Cheep, cheep, cheep, cheep,
talk a lot, pick a little
Oh, Miss Paroo, please join
our Delsarte Committee.
You were so dear today
dancing with Professor Hill.
♪ Cheep, cheep, cheep, cheep
cheep, cheep, cheep, cheep
♪ You dance like
a fairy princess
♪ With a moonbeam
for your floor
♪ You had a golden shimmer
in your hair
♪ And silver shoes
for all to see
♪ We know that
you will soon unfold
♪ A forgiving heart
of purest gold
♪ Here, where
a woman's heart should be
♪ Cheep, cheep, cheep, cheep
cheep, cheep, cheep, cheep
♪ Fairy princess
♪ Moonbeam floor
♪ Golden shimmer
♪ Silver shoes
♪ Now unfold
♪ Heart of gold
♪ Here, where a woman's
heart should be
♪ Cheep, cheep, cheep, cheep
cheep, cheep, cheep, cheep
♪ The Professor told us
to read those books
♪ And we simply
adored them all
♪ Chaucer
♪ Rabelais
♪ Balzac
♪ Cheep cheep cheep cheep
cheep cheep cheep cheep
♪ Pick a little
talk a little, cheep ♪
ALL: Mmm!
Sorry, Professor,
but we got our orders.
We've all been deputized.
Oh! Oh, well,
congratulations.
Uh, let's see now,
you know all week long
I've been trying
to give you fellows
my references
and credentials,
but you always seem to get
off the subject somehow.
Now I have just what
you need up in my room.
Take me a second.
Sorry. 'Fraid we'll have
to go along with you.
Yes, yes, well, let's see
if I have my key.
What is this?
Oh!
Oh, it's a testimonial
from Madame Rini.
The only female
bassoon player ever
to appear on
the Redpath Circuit.
Her stage name, of course,
actually, she was from Moline,
Lida Rose Quackenbush.
Could I see that
for a minute?
Oh, you'll never forget
the name, Lida Rose,
just like the song.
♪ Lida Rose
I'm home again, Rose
♪ To get the...
♪ Sun back in the sky
♪ Lida Rose
I'm home again, Rose
♪ About a thousand kisses shy
♪ Ding dong ding
♪ I can hear
the chapel bell chime
♪ Ding dong ding
♪ At the least suggestion
♪ I'll pop the question
♪ Lida Rose
I'm home again, Rose
♪ Without a sweetheart
to my name
♪ Lida Rose
now everyone knows
♪ That I am hoping
you're the same
♪ So here is my love song
♪ Not fancy or fine
♪ Lida Rose
oh, won't you be mine
♪ Lida Rose, oh, Lida Rose
Oh, Lida Rose ♪
♪ Dream of now
♪ Dream of then
♪ Dream of a love song
♪ That might have been
♪ Do I love you?
♪ Oh, yes, I love you
♪ And I'll bravely tell you
♪ But only when
we dream again
♪ Sweet and low
♪ How sweet that memory
♪ How long ago
♪ Forever?
♪ Oh, yes, forever
♪ Will I ever tell you?
♪ Ah, no
♪ Lida Rose, oh
Lida Rose, oh
♪ Dream of...
♪ Lida Rose, oh...
♪ Now
♪ I'm home
again, Rose
♪ Dream of then
♪ Dream of a love song
♪ Lida Rose
I'm home again, Rose
♪ About a thousand
kisses shy
♪ That might have been
♪ Do I love you?
♪ Ding dong ding
♪ Oh, yes, I love you
♪ I can hear the
chapel bell chime
♪ And I'll bravely tell you
♪ Ding dong ding
♪ But only when we
♪ At the least suggestion
♪ Dream again
♪ I'll pop the question
♪ Sweet and low
♪ Lida Rose
I'm home again, Rose
♪ Without a sweetheart
to my name
♪ Sweet and low
♪ How sweet that mem'ry
♪ Lida Rose, now
everyone knows that
♪ How long ago
♪ I am hoping
you're the same
♪ Forever?
♪ So here is my love song
♪ Oh, yes, forever
♪ Not fancy or fine
♪ Will I ever tell you
♪ Lida Rose, oh,
won't you be mine?
♪ Or no
♪ Lida Rose, oh,
Lida Rose, oh,
♪ Lida Rose ♪
Seems like we just took down
the flags for Flag Day,
and now we're starting to put
them up again for
the Fourth of July.
I'm starting to see
red, white, and blue spots
before my eyes!
(CHUCKLES) You say that
every year, Mama,
but you always
volunteer to sew.
Well, it's funny how
things get to be
a habit with people.
You think a person
might change, but they don't.
might let herself go,
might speak her heart,
but she don't.
Might tell a fellow
how she's longing,
but she don't.
Mama!
Will you ever tell him?
Won't you ever tell him?
Ah, fiddlesticks, just open
your mouth, my girl,
let it come out.
Now Mama...
Now nuthin'.
If he ever comes
to call again,
you see him alone
and if you haven't
the gumption to tell him
how you feel...
Tell him?
Well, there's nothing wrong
with a ladylike hint.
(DOG BARKING)
Winthrop,
where've you been?
Fishing.
Fishing!
With Harold.
You mean Professor Hill?
Mmm-hmm.
And look, I still
have some worms left.
Ew! Oh, what's that?
A lucky rabbit's foot,
he gave it to me.
Did you have
a good time?
Scrumptious. Look, Mom!
Ugh!
Scrumptious.
What did you talk about?
Stuff.
What stuff?
He told me all about
his hometown, Gary, Indiana.
He said he'd
take me there someday.
And he taught me
a song, which hardly
has any 's's' in it.
♪ Gary, Indiana
Gary, Indiana
♪ Let me say it once again
♪ Gary, Indiana
Gary, Indiana, Gary, Indiana
♪ That's the town
that knew me when
♪ If you'd like to have
a logical explanation
♪ How I happened
on this elegant syncopation
♪ I will say without
a moment of hesitation
♪ There is just one place
that can light my face...
♪ Gary, Indiana
♪ Not Louisiana, Paris
France, New York or Rome
♪ But Gary, Indiana
♪ Gary, Indiana
Gary, Indiana
My home sweet home ♪
I'll be back in a minute.
I have to show Amaryllis
my new live frog.
Oh, you're not going
to the Fourth of July
sociable in those clothes!
You make sure you're
back in time to
have a bath!
Okay.
♪ La de da de da
de da de da
♪ La de da
♪ La de da da de
da de da de da ♪
Oh, leave the dishes,
Mama, I'll do them.
Aren't you gonna change
for the sociable?
There's plenty of time.
Come on, Shadow. Come on.
MAN: River City!
River City, station stop.
River City!
Say there, old timer,
you know where I can
find Elm Street?
Yeah.
Criminee!
Yes?
Is this the Shinn residence?
Oh, the Shinn home
is on East Elm.
This is West Elm.
Aw, criminee, I...
See you're the piano teacher
here in town.
Yes.
My name's Cowell,
Charlie Cowell,
anvil salesman.
Oh!
I guess you know all about
this Hill fellow, formin'
a boys' band here in town.
Yes.
Well, you don't need
to worry about
him no more.
I got the goods
on him in spades.
Swindlin' two-bit
thimble rigger.
That's why I gotta
go see Shinn.
But...
Mr. Cowell, wait! Please!
Ah, sorry, miss, the number
eight only makes
15-minute water stop.
Ooh, I wish it was
20, though.
Sure would like to concentrate
five minutes more
on you, girly girl.
But just now I'm out
to protect the good name
of the travelin' fraternity
from that swindler.
Please, Mr. Cowell,
you are making
a big mistake.
Mistake! Mistake my
old lady's corset cover!
That fella's been
the raspberry seed in my
wisdom tooth just long enough.
He spoiled Illinois for me,
he's not gonna spoil Iowa!
What kind of music
teacher are you, you
don't see through him?
He's no more Professor than...
Oh, I know all about that.
Band leaders are
always called Professor.
It's a harmless deception.
He's a fine director
and his scholastic...
Now just a minute.
Fine director?
Have you heard even one
note a'music from any band?
No, but...
But nothin', girly girl!
He's never formed
a band in his life!
And he never will!
If you'll just listen
to me for a minute.
Oh, I'd like to. I'd like
to do a lot more than that,
if I had the time,
'cause I sure got
the inclination.
But I gotta get back
on that train and
deliver this dynamite
to somebody on the way
to the depot.
Bye, girly girl.
I'll see you
next time through.
You'll never make
that train at the depot.
You'll have to catch it
at the crossing.
No, sir. I've got to
leave word.
And I can see you ain't
the one to leave it with.
Just a minute,
Mr. Cowell, you...
You don't know me yet.
Is that an invitation?
I never met a man
who sells anvils.
That's something, well...
Uh, quite different.
Takes a real salesman,
I can tell you that much.
Anvils have a limited
appeal, you know...
I... What am I doin'?
If I miss that train,
I'm fired!
I gotta leave word
about that fellow Hill!
Leave word with me.
Not on your tintype.
How do I know you'd even
deliver these letters?
Try me.
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
There's your train,
you better run for it!
You double-dealing little...
Who do you think
you're protecting?
That guy's got
a different girl in
every county in Illinois,
and he's taken away
from every one of 'em!
And that's
102 counties!
That's not counting the little
piano teachers like you
that he cozies up to,
just to keep their
mouths shut!
Neither one of you's
heard the last of me,
girly girl!
(MRS. PAROO EXCLAIMS)
Oh, my goodness,
I just remembered, I've got
some jelly on the stove!
There's no jelly
on the stove, Mama.
Well, I'll just put some on.
You just come up here and set.
Shall we "set"
as your mother said?
What are you doing here?
You asked me to call.
Did I? I didn't
mean anything.
No, no, I wasn't
suggesting that your
invitation inferred anything,
but academic enlightenment,
the Think System.
I've been by your house
to try to explain it to you
a time or two this week,
but there always seemed
to be people around.
Mostly ladies, I thought.
Yes, Mrs. Squires
and several of the ladies.
I'm glad. Wouldn't want
anybody beating my time.
Well, it's evidently
not the convenient time.
Professor Hill!
Is it true that you've
had 100...
What I'm trying
to say is...
Yes?
Is it really true that
you've developed a...
A Think System?
Absolutely.
It's really very simple,
as simple as whistling.
No one has to show
you how to use
your lips in whistling.
You only have to
think a tune to have
it come out clearly...
Here.
Now just try
this yourself, before
you ask any questions.
I take your word.
(SIGHS)
Would you like to sit down?
Are all music teachers
as dense as I am?
All music teachers?
I daresay you meet dozens...
Even a hundred.
Well, I...
Have they all been
fascinated as I have with...
The Think System?
Some more, some less.
One young lady thought up
the same system
before I got to her town.
She showed me
a few refinements.
I see.
Have I said something wrong?
Please don't let me
keep you, Professor Hill.
You must have many more
important things to do
than explain the
Think System to me.
Can't think of one.
And I must be
very dull company for
a man of your experience.
Now, say, where'd you get
an idea like that?
One hears rumors
of traveling salesmen.
What have you heard?
Oh, nothing, nothing about you
personally, just generally.
What have you heard generally?
Just that,
but of course, it stands to
reason that disappointment
and jealousy can lead to,
to, I mean,
take you for instance,
your attention to,
to, to customers
and, and, and well, teachers,
might easily be
misinterpreted, mightn't they?
I mean, now honestly,
mightn't they?
Why?
And, so you say,
if another
salesman or someone
were jealous,
I mean...
Well, they could be
downright lies, couldn't they?
What could?
Rumors and things.
Why, of course.
It just proves that you
can't believe everything
you hear, doesn't it?
I mean...
If you just
discuss things.
Miss Marian, I would be
delighted to discuss anything
in the world with you.
But couldn't we do
it sitting down?
You do sit?
Your knees
bend and all.
We could sit
on the porch steps.
We could also sit
on the large hollow log
over't the footbridge.
Oh, I couldn't think of it.
I've never been
to the footbridge
with a man in my life.
Just to talk.
I just can't, please,
some other time.
Maybe tomorrow.
My dear little librarian,
pile up enough tomorrows
and you'll find
you've collected nothing
but a lot of empty yesterdays.
I don't know about you,
but I'd like to make today
worth remembering.
So would I.
Footbridge. In one hour.
One hour.
(EXCLAIMS)
Mama! Mama!
What?
I just told Professor Hill
I'd meet him at the
footbridge in an hour.
Glory be and the saints
be praised. It works!
What does?
I've been usin'
the Think System
on you from the parlor!
ZANEETA: Professor Hill!
We need you for
the  Shipoopi!
I've been looking
everywhere! Come on!
Zaneeta,
I'll be along shortly.
No, we've got to hurry!
Everybody's waiting,
and there's gonna
be fireworks.
Ye Gods, you don't
want to miss them!
(ALL CHEERING)
All right, I'll give it a try!
Found him!
What? What am I
supposed to do?
We got her!
Yay!
All right, watch out!
Step back!
♪ Now a woman who'll kiss
on the very first date
is usually a hussy
♪ And a woman who'll kiss
on the second time out
is anything but fussy
♪ But a woman who'll wait
'til the third time around
♪ Head in the clouds
feet on the ground...
♪ She's the girl
he's glad he's found
♪ She's his Shipoopi!
♪ Shipoopi!
Shipoopi! Shipoopi!
♪ The girl who's hard to get!
♪ Shipoopi!
Shipoopi! Shipoopi!
♪ But you can
win her yet
♪ Walk her once just
to raise the curtain
♪ Then you walk around twice
and you make for certain
♪ Once more
in the flower garden
♪ She will never get
sore if you beg her pardon
♪ Do re mi
fa sol la si do
♪ Si la sol fa mi re do
♪ Squeeze her once
when she isn't lookin'
♪ If you get a
squeeze back
that's fancy cookin'
♪ Once more for
a pepper-upper
♪ She will never get sore
on her way to supper
♪ Do re mi fa sol
la si do si do
♪ Now, little ol' Sal
was a no-gal
as anyone could see
♪ Lookit her now,
she's a go-gal
who only goes for me
♪ Squeeze her once
when she isn't lookin'
♪ If you get a squeeze back
that's fancy cookin'
♪ Once more for
a pepper-upper
♪ She will never get sore
on her way to supper
♪ Do re mi fa so la si do
si do
♪ Shipoopi! Shipoopi!
Shipoopi!
♪ The girl who's hard to get
♪ Shipoopi! Shipoopi!
Shipoopi!
♪ But you can win her yet
Whoa!
GIRL: Come on,
we wanna sing.
All right, stand back.
(APPLAUDING)
Aw!
Hey!
(GASPING) Oh, my God.
(CROWD LAUGHING)
(CHUCKLING)
Oh!
♪ Shipoopi! Shipoopi!
Shipoopi!
♪ The girl who's hard to get
♪ Shipoopi! Shipoopi!
Shipoopi!
♪ But you can win her yet
♪ You can win her yet
♪ Shipoopi! ♪
(ALL GASPING)
(INDISTINCT VOICES)
The footbridge.
Five minutes.
Miss Marian, you're late.
I came right here.
No, I meant
that you were about,
well, I'd say
about 26 years late.
Took you all this time
to get to the footbridge
with a fella.
If you wanna know the truth,
it almost took longer.
Oh?
Halfway here,
I nearly turned back.
I suppose
I'm not the first to find it
easier to think clearly
when not under the spell
of your salesmanship.
Now, Miss Marian,
surely you don't think
I've been
selling you anything.
No. No,
you've given me something.
That's why
I decided to come.
Why I don't recall
giving you anything.
Oh yes, you have.
Something beautiful.
That's why I came.
I'm glad.
Please don't be afraid that
I'll expect too much more.
One can't expect a traveling
salesman to stay put.
I know there have been
many ports of call
and there will be many more.
But that's no reason
for me not to be grateful
for what you will have
left behind for me.
Marian, I...
♪ There were bells
on the hill
♪ But I never
heard them ringing
♪ No, I never
heard them at all
♪ Till there was you
♪ There were birds in the sky
♪ But I never
saw them winging
♪ No, I never saw them at all
♪ Till there was you
♪ And there was music
♪ And there were
wonderful roses
♪ They tell me,
in sweet fragrant meadows
♪ Of dawn and dew
♪ There was love all around
♪ But I never
heard it singing, no
♪ I never heard it at all
♪ Till there was you
♪ There was love all around
♪ But I never heard it
♪ Singing
♪ No, I never heard it all
♪ Till there was you ♪
Marian, there are
a lot of things
you don't know about me.
MARCE: Psst! Hey, Greg!
Excuse me,
I was expecting a cable
from Hector Berlioz.
This could be it.
Huh.
(TRAIN WHISTLING IN DISTANCE)
What?
Who's the salesman here?
Looks like she's selling
and you're buying.
I have to keep her
off balance, don't I?
I told you that.
Well, she's so far
off balance now,
you can't tell her
from a catboat
in a hurricane.
Listen, the band uniforms
just came in on the train.
Tommy helped me collect.
Here's most of the dough.
The people are gonna be
screaming for music now,
so you gotta get out
of here.
What time's
the freight go?
9:40 from the junction.
Well, it isn't even
8:30 yet.
Look, you wanna
turtle-wurtle around here
and get yourself
caught up in a bunny-trap,
you go right ahead.
Don't worry, Marce.
I'll meet you at the hotel
in plenty of time.
Your commission.
Oh!
Now, I'll go
collect mine.
(LAUGHS)
Never a peaceful moment
in the music business.
(MARIAN CHUCKLES)
Now then, uh,
where were we?
You were about to tell me
what I don't know about you.
Yeah, well, we don't have
to go into all that
just now, do we?
No, we don't, or ever,
for that matter, Harold.
The librarian hasn't
felt much like
doing research lately,
but she did plenty
when you first came here.
Oh, about what?
About Professor
Harold Hill,
Gary Conservatory
of Music,
Gold Medal
Class of aught-five.
Harold, there wasn't any
Gary Conservatory
in aught-five.
Why there certainly was.
Because the town
wasn't even built
until aught-six.
You knew all the time?
I tore this page out
of the Indiana Journal.
It was originally intended
to use against you,
but now I give it to you
with all of my heart.
But if you knew,
why didn't you...
(GASPS)
Why you little...
(WHISTLING)
♪ While a hundred and ten
cornets played the air
♪ Then I modestly
took my place
♪ As the one and only bass
♪ And I oom-pahed
up and down the square
♪ Goodnight, my someone
♪ Goodnight, my love
♪ With a hundred and ten
cornets right behind
♪ Our star is shining
♪ Its brightest light
♪ There were horns
of every shape and...
♪ Sweet dreams be yours, dear
♪ If dreams there be
♪ While a hundred and ten
cornets played the air
♪ I wish I may
♪ And I wish I might
♪ Now goodnight, my someone
♪ Goodnight
♪ Goodnight ♪
One Grecian urn!
Two Grecian urns.
Oh, that's good.
And a fountain.
Ah! Trickle, trickle, trickle,
trickle, trickle,
trickle, trickle, trickle.
Stop. Stop, stop, stop. Stop!
Listen to this man!
He has something very
important to tell all of us.
You gullible,
green-grass goats!
Can't you get it
through your head
that you're being
swindled out'a your eye teeth
right now, this very minute?
There's a burglar
in the bedroom
while you're fiddling
in the parlor!
I'm talking about Harold Hill.
(CROWD GASPS)
Road agent. Highwayman.
Pickpocket.
Pickpocket?
CHARLIE: Same thing, oh-ho!
Oh-ho, same thing.
He's had his hand
in your wallet, mister.
And yours, madam.
And yours, little lady.
Ever since the first
moment he came
to this town!
Why there is more documented
evidence than you'll
ever have time to read!
There isn't any band,
there never
has been any band,
will be any band!
Winthrop!
And unless you track
this man down,
right now, like a mad dog,
there won't be any
Harold Hill either!
Because, he'll be on
the next train outta town.
(CROWD GASPING
AND TALKING)
Now you believe me.
So, what are we
waiting for?
I want my money back!
Money back? I want his hide!
After him.
And when you find him,
bring him
to the schoolhouse.
After him!
I don't believe any
of those things he said
about the Professor.
Try the low road!
Look by the creek!
This is America.
A man is innocent
until proven guilty.
Don't you quote
the constitutional
to me, you young pup.
That fellow doesn't have
an  e plurbis unum
to stand on!
Try the mill!
Back at the privy!
Follow me.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Outta my way.
(GASPING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(PANTING) You gotta
get out of here, Greg.
There's an anvil salesman
blew you outta the water.
Uh-oh!
Everyone in town
wants a piece of ya.
Hurry!
Here, go out the back.
See you
around the pond.
Good luck!
(CROWD SHOUTING)
MAN: Upstairs!
This way!
Winthrop! What is it?
What's wrong?
(SOBBING) I hate him!
I hate him!
Who?
The Professor.
What happened?
He's a liar.
Winthrop, tell me
what happened.
MRS. PAROO: Marian! I can't
find your brother!
He's up here!
Mother, what happened?
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
MRS. PAROO: Winthrop,
open this door, this second.
MARIAN: He's probably
out the window again, Mama.
(DOG BARKING)
MAN: Check down
by the banks!
Marian, let me in.
Just for a minute.
You can't stay.
You have to get out.
Please go!
Please, Harold,
they're even
talking about
tar and feathers.
Marian, I had to see you.
I was writing you a letter.
It's all right.
Don't you know that?
You don't owe me a word.
Not a word.
Now, please, hurry.
I hate you!
Winthrop!
I hate you, you liar.
Wait a minute here, son.
WINTHROP: I'm not
your son! Leave me go!
Not till I talk to you
for a minute.
I won't listen!
You wouldn't tell
the truth anyway.
I would, too.
Would not.
Would too!
Tell you anything
you wanna know.
Can you lead a band?
No.
Are you a big liar?
Yes.
Are you a dirty
rotten crook?
Yes.
Now, leave me go,
you big liar!
What's the matter?
You wanted
the truth, didn't you?
Now I'm bigger'n you
and you're gonna stand here
and get it all,
so you might as well
quit wiggling.
Now, there's two things
you're entitled to know.
One, you're a wonderful kid.
I thought so from the first.
That's why
I wanted you in the band,
just so you'd stop
mopin' around
feeling sorry
for yourself.
What band?
I always think
there's a band, kid.
What's the other thing,
I'm entitled to know?
Well, actually the other thing
isn't any your business
now that I think of it.
I wish you'd never come
to River City!
No, you don't, Winthrop.
Sister, you believe him?
I believe everything
he ever said.
But he promised us.
I know what
he promised us.
And it all happened
just like he said.
The lights and the flags
and the colors
and the cymbals.
WINTHROP: Where's all that?
In the way every kid
in this town
walked around here
the last three weeks,
and looked and acted.
Especially you!
And the parents, too.
Does Mama wish
he'd never come
to River City?
No.
WINTHROP: Well you do,
don't you?
No, Winthrop, I don't.
Now go, please, Harold.
Go on, Professor, hurry up.
I can't go, Winthrop.
Why not?
For the first time in
my life, I got my foot
caught in the door.
♪ There was love
all around
♪ But I never
heard it singing
♪ No I never heard
it at all
♪ Till there was you ♪
MARCE: Greg!
Greg, they're here.
Get out!
Get out any way you can!
Go on, Professor.
Do as he says.
Sorry, Marce.
Let's go.
MAYOR: As soon as I spoke
to Charlie Cowell,
it was oblivious to me that
something had to be done.
Which is why I interrupted
the program when I did.
Rest assured,
this snake
in our bosom
would have been
misapprehended
by this time.
Yes! And always remember,
fellow River Citizians,
I can only remind you,
that I did everything
in my power to prevent
this dire happening
from happening.
What have you done
to get our money back?
That Professor collected
nearly three hundred dollars
for uniforms, just last night.
We haven't seen
any uniforms yet.
He's slippery. I told you.
I haven't seen my boy
since just after supper.
He's a kidnapper.
Fine situation here.
Virtue has triumphed.
The sword of retribution
has cut down
Professor Harold Hill!
And if there are those,
as I have heard,
who are melting tar
and collecting feathers,
I will not say them nay.
Well, I think there
ought to be some
of you who could forget
our everlasting Iowa
stubborn chip-on-the-shoulder
arrogance long enough
to remember River City
before Harold Hill arrived.
Do you remember?
Well, do you?
Surely some of you
ought to be grateful to him
for what he has
brought to River City
and if so, I should think
you would want to admit it.
You're wasting
a great deal
of time here.
If there's a person
in this hall who doesn't think
this man Hill should be
tarred and feathered,
let him stand up.
Come on.
MAN: Go ahead, stand up.
Eulalie, sit down.
And the rest of you,
standin' there like a coat
of Shropshire sheep,
have you people
forgotten how you bought
expensive uniforms,
technical instruction books
and high-priced
band instruments?
Have you forgotten
the clear understanding
and warrantee
that your children
would be taught
to play in a band?
Well, where's the band?
Where's the band?
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
Think, men, think.
One, two...
(BAND PLAYING OFF KEY)
That's my Barney!
That tuba's my Barney!
Just look at him.
He's so wonderful.
Thank you.
Linus, play to me, son,
play to me!
MAN: (SHOUTING)
That the way, Steve.
That's Eddie's coronet.
Davey, my Davey.
MAN: That's my Garrett.
(BLOWS)
Mrs. Paroo, that's Winthrop.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(BELL RINGS)