♪ ♪
I don't have anything
stuck in my teeth, do I?
Let me see. Nope, all clear.
Honey, you look so handsome.
She's going to have a great
time with you tonight.
You'll see.
Oh, and I want a
picture of you two.
- Mom, no.
- Oh, come on, please.
Just one.
Okay, uh, but you promised
you'd let me walk to
the door by myself.
I know, I know. I'll be
right here in the car.
- Okay.
- Waiting. Okay.
Hi, Annie.
Harold, you're so dressed up.
Are you trying to
make me look bad?
That was a joke.
This is for you.
Thanks. It's beautiful.
So are you ready to go?
Yeah, I told everybody to meet
us out in front of the gym.
Uh, everybody?
I invited a bunch of
friends to come with us.
I thought it'd be fun if
we went as a big group.
Don't you think?
Yeah.
Okay, you two. Move in together.
Move in.
Smile, Harold.
So the software we
set you up with
will issue all of your invoices.
It keeps everything organized,
so when tax time
comes, it's a snap.
Saves time for me
and money for you.
Um, where do I enter
that information?
Right, Claire has volunteered
to be my billing department.
Well, I can walk you
through it if you want.
You just have to
remember to enter
all your setup expenses
because they're all deductible.
Will do. Thank you.
Sure.
These are beautiful.
Are they all the
same photographer?
Uh, yes. They are.
Actually, it's me.
Really?
Well, listen. We really
appreciate your help.
- Thank you, Harold.
- Yeah.
Yes.
Uh, Steve and I were thinking,
we're having a party next
Saturday for Megan's birthday.
I'm a big girl. I'm turning six.
Oh, wow.
And we're just having
some friends over,
but we'd love you to join
us if you're not busy.
Yeah, thanks. I'll drop by.
Great. Great.
Um, my sister Annie is in town,
you two were in the same
high-school class together,
weren't you?
Yeah. Yeah, I remember Annie.
Um, how is she doing?
You can find out for yourself.
Uh, Saturday. 2:00.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, thanks again.
Yes, yes.
I'll talk to him
about it right now.
And then I'll put
her name and number
right in front our boy,
and I'll watch him score.
Bye, hon.
- Who's going to score?
- You are.
So when's our next
round of golf?
Do you really think we
should keep playing?
We have to be the
worst golfers ever.
We quit by the sixth
hole or lunchtime,
whichever comes first.
We should come up with
a new sport like...
Miniature golf or bowling.
Ooh, bowling. I like bowling.
Guess who just walked in?
And she saw me.
You should go talk to her.
This isn't the first time
that she smiled at you.
- She likes you.
- I don't think so.
See, there you go, hiding
under a rock again.
Look, you know as well as I do,
every time I ask a woman
out, it ends in disaster.
Thank you.
Why do you think that is?
I don't know.
But it's always the same
whether I'm set up by friends,
or internet dating, or
matchmaking services.
Nothing works.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Maybe it's not the
meeting-people part
that you have a problem with.
Let's be honest.
Socializing is not
your strong point.
Yeah, the whole thing
is just so frustrating.
Have you ever heard
of a dating coach?
A what?
A dating coach.
Denise and I saw it on
TV the other night.
They're kind of like a
private teacher you hire
to teach you how to date.
Dating coach.
Is there really such a thing?
Yeah.
And I found someone
in the city for you.
She's got a bunch of clients,
and a lot of people
are trying it.
Willy, come on.
I mean, this is
just embarrassing.
I couldn't do it. It's...
it's too weird.
So I've never been to a
dating coach before.
My friend Willy, the
guy who called,
thought you might be
able to help me out.
Well, that's why I'm here.
To help people stop
making mistakes
in the modern dating world and
attract their perfect mate.
Oh, great.
Um, how do we get started?
Well, what we need to
do is schedule you
for a series of intensive
one-on-one sessions.
During this time, I
am going to mold you.
I'm going to teach you
the skills you will use
to attract and hold onto
that special someone.
Wow. How many
sessions do we have?
Well, we have a number of
packages to choose from.
I recommend you go with
our Diamond package.
It's the longest and
most intensive.
Wow, it's expensive.
Cost should be no
obstacle when it comes
to your future
happiness, Harold.
And don't worry,
we have payment plans and
accept all major credit cards.
And just a little paperwork
for you to sign.
I think, um, I just...
I should take some time
to think this over.
You made it.
Hey, here you go.
Thanks for having me.
Oh, this is so sweet.
Come on in. Everyone's
through here.
Smile, Harold.
Annie, look who's here.
Harold, you remember Annie?
Sure. Hi.
Hi. Hi.
It's so great to see you again
after all these years.
Yeah.
Harold...
- White.
Of course.
How have you been?
Fine, thanks. How have you been?
Ah. Ah, you know.
Living the high life,
hanging in there.
All that good stuff.
Yeah.
So can I get you a
drink or something?
- Yeah, that would be great.
- Okay.
And then after college,
I move the whopping-hours
drive away to the city.
I've always loved the city.
And then I started
my own business.
I'm an event planner,
like, I put parties together.
You know, decorating
everything and organizing.
- Did you do all of this?
- Yeah, I did.
It's amazing what you can do
with some scraps of fabric
and, you know, a hot glue
gun and some colored paper.
Wow. You're really talented.
Thank you.
Although it's been a
really tough line of work
to break into.
Anyway, enough about me.
What about you?
Claire said you're helping
Steve set up his body shop?
Uh, yeah.
I'm sorry. And what
is it you do again?
I run my own accounting firm
and do some consulting.
- Small business, mostly.
- Yeah.
I'm also a photographer,
but that's really just
on the side, you know.
No, that's great. Good for you.
You know, on the
way over here...
I was thinking about
that dance we went to.
What... what dance is this?
In freshmen year of high
school, homecoming.
I couldn't drive, so
my mother took us.
Do you remember?
She took that picture
of us together.
Of course.
Yeah. Oh, right.
We had such a good time.
Didn't we?
Yeah.
Good night, birthday girl.
Sweet dreams.
She went out like a light.
Thank you for everything.
The party looked fantastic.
Everybody said so.
So I talked to your friend
Harold like you asked me to.
I was just worried he'd
be left alone all day.
He's a nice guy, right?
Eh, kind of blah, but
yeah, he's nice.
You promise you aren't
trying to set me up, right?
No.
Besides, you're going out
with that Brad or Brian...
Brady.
And no, that was
like, five guys ago.
So who are you dating this week?
Uh, well, no one yet,
but hey, at least I've worked my
ways through the "B" s, right?
- Mm.
- No, I'm actually...
I just got a lot on
my plate right now.
Speaking of which,
I kind of need to
ask you a favor.
Remember how I said I'd be ready
to move out of here next week?
Yeah.
Well, turns out, um,
trying to find a job
and a place to live in the
city, it's been really tough.
Everything is so expensive.
And I'm wondering how you'd feel
if I could just stay for
a little bit longer.
Please.
Oh, Annie,
you've been here
for four months.
Yeah.
Time flies when
you're having fun?
What happened to getting a job?
I've been looking all over.
There's no openings for
event planners anywhere.
Why don't you do something else?
You know, just for a little
while, pay the bills.
Oh, uh, yeah. Sure, um,
I'll just... I'll get a day job.
Okay.
And in the meantime, I
can baby-sit Megan,
and I-I can do your decorating,
and I'll even do your windows.
You know, you need a backup plan
for this career of yours.
Annie, you're not a kid anymore.
Well, hello, stranger.
It's been a while, huh?
Let me guess, table
for one, right?
Please.
Follow me.
Here, sire.
And okay, so the specials today
are meatloaf and roast chicken.
If I were you,
I'd go with the roast chicken.
Thank you.
Someone will be right with you.
Here's your menu right here.
You gotta be kidding me.
Hi.
You work here?
Yeah. Sure do.
Just started here today.
And I gotta say, so
far, not so good.
My car broke down this morning
on my first day of work,
wouldn't you know?
Thank you.
That's... that's tough.
Sorry to hear that.
Thank you.
And now my shift
ends in an hour,
and I have no way
of getting home.
Do you believe this?
This is my crazy life.
Hi, welcome.
There's no one who
can pick you up?
No, you know, Steve's
working late,
and Claire's with
Megan somewhere,
but it's fine.
You know, something
will work out.
It's... it literally
cannot get any worse.
You know, I am not
going to say that.
That's bad karma.
I'm just going to
take that back.
Uh...
What can I get you to drink?
- Uh, coffee, please.
- Coming right up.
You know, if...
You really need a ride home,
I can take you.
Thank you.
Harold, that's very...
That's very sweet of you.
But I just... I couldn't
ask you to do that.
Right.
Could I?
Thank you.
Someone's girlfriend
trained them well.
I don't have a girlfriend.
Not really good at that.
Come on, you can't be that bad.
I'm so bad, my best
friend had to get me
to see a... Specialist.
Specialist for...
A dating coach.
Really?
A dating coach? How did that go?
Uh, it was a disaster.
She was more interested
in making a sale.
Kind of made me feel
like a lost cause.
Nobody's a lost cause, Harold.
I should get going.
Okay.
Well, thanks again for the ride.
Sure.
I'll see you later, okay?
Okay.
How'd you get home?
Harold dropped me off.
Poor guy.
And I thought I had problems.
Ugh.
What a day.
If I were into bubble baths,
this would be the
time to take one.
Do you have a minute?
Okay, look, I know I
need to pay Steven back
for fixing and towing my car,
and I will have the money to him
right after I get
my next paycheck.
And the one after that...
And the one after that.
Why don't you sit down?
Aw.
- Is this about my dirty room?
- No.
- My dishes in the sink?
Borrowing your dress
without asking?
No.
That's all I know about.
What have you got on me?
Annie, your staying here...
I don't think it's a
good idea anymore.
What?
I've been giving this
a lot of thought,
and frankly, I feel like I'm
helping you escape reality.
Of course not.
I escape reality all on my own.
Pew.
Sorry.
Claire. Look, I'm sorry.
I know I'm a pain,
but I promise you,
this is not going to be forever.
I just need to buy myself
a little bit of time.
Sometimes things don't work out
the way we want them to.
It's not always about
getting a free ride.
What's that supposed to mean?
At some point, we all
have to grow up.
You need to move out and
get your own place.
Even your own family
won't bail you out?
So much for "blood is
thicker than water," right?
Sorry. I mean, you
could stay with me,
but my place is, like,
as big as your shoe.
Oh, thank you,
but now I have to
find another job.
And it has to be
something flexible
so that I can keep this one.
- How am I supposed to do that?
- I don't know.
Maybe you can try to
win big at Vegas.
You could.
My friend won $60 at blackjack,
and she met Siegfried.
No kidding.
What is happening to my life?
Oh, honey. It'll be okay.
Really, I mean,
things will be good.
You know what they say.
You know, "if at first
you don't succeed..."
"If life gives you lemons..."
"A bird in the..."
They say something...
Oh, I know what they say.
They say that if you want a job,
you have to go to
people you know.
You should ask around.
I don't even know anyone
around here anymore.
- Oh?
- Except for Harold.
Hmm.
Wait a minute. Harold.
Who's Harold?
You know, one of your regulars.
He was here the other
night, drove me home.
Oh, Harold. Table seven Harold.
He needs help dating.
He needs help breathing.
He needs a drink.
Really, he's very stiff, Harold.
I could help him.
Yeah, he was talking about
needing a dating coach.
He could just hire
me to do that.
- Really?
- Absolutely!
Listen, I have dated
all over the place.
I have got years of experience.
Oh, that sounds
great on a resume.
"I have dated hundreds
of thousands of guys,
and I'm still alone."
I'd hire you.
It's perfect.
♪ ♪
It's open.
Hi.
Thanks for seeing me. I
know I'm a little early.
Yeah... no. Come on in.
Okay, I'm just going
to skip the small talk
and get right to the point.
Remember when you drove
me home the other day,
you mentioned how that
dating coach thing
didn't really work out?
Yeah, I kind of wish I
hadn't brought that up.
Actually, I'm glad you did
because I'm wondering how
you would feel about
giving it another shot.
Um...
About working with
somebody different,
somebody who's really good.
Me.
- You?
- Mm-hmm.
Seriously?
No, listen, I know it
sounds a little crazy,
but I really think I can help
you out in this department.
Have you ever done
anything like this before?
Uh, not exactly, no,
but I've done a lot of research,
I have tons of
real-world experience,
and I'm cheaper than
a professional.
Which brings me to my
next subject of payment.
Here's what I figured
would be reasonable.
Uh, how many classes or lessons
are you thinking about?
Um, eight. Yes, eight.
Eight really great,
really great dating
class lessons.
Um...
Am I asking for too much?
No, it's... It's not
about the money.
That's right. That's right.
It's not about the money. No.
It's about all the
great dates out there.
It's about Harold White
and the great, fun
times ahead of him.
Um, I don't know.
Please.
I really think we'd
make a great team.
And if this doesn't work out,
we can just walk away,
no questions asked.
Come on.
What have you got to lose?
Yes.
Let's give it a try.
I mean, I'm really glad we
can do business together.
When would you like to start?
- Uh, well...
- How about Tuesday night?
I don't work the late shift.
Tuesday. Um, 7:00...
7:30 sharp.
Deal?
Deal.
♪ ♪
Tonight's the beginning
of the new you.
Are you ready?
I guess so.
Ah, well, I was hoping for
a little more excitement,
but not to worry.
We'll work on it.
Whoa. Great place you got here.
♪ I'll never forget
how my heart ♪
And nice music.
Yeah, I'm kind of into
this kind of stuff.
I see.
Wow.
I guess you could
say my collection
has gotten a little out of hand.
Perry Como, Nat King Cole,
Ella Fitzgerald.
These are all old love songs.
Yeah, I like the
slower vintage stuff.
Harold, it's an omen.
- What is?
- This music.
It's so romantic.
It's time to become one
of the few, the proud,
a heartbreaker.
This is great.
Okay, stand right there.
- Okay.
- Now, first things first.
You start dating long before
you say word one to a woman.
- Really?
- Really.
Hmm.
They key ingredient
to successful dating
is self-confidence.
I should be seeing lots
of confidence in you.
And right now, I'm not.
Yeah.
Okay, Harold, if you're going
to be my lump of clay,
I need you to be a
little less of a lump.
Okay?
Okay.
I want you to look
at your reflection
and tell me some of
your finer qualities.
Uh...
Okay, tell me one of
your finer qualities.
Um...
Just hang on for a second.
I'm thinking.
♪ The first night we met ♪
Harold, you're scaring me here.
Come on, what do you see
when you look at yourself?
I see the guy who stayed home
every Friday night
doing his homework.
What? What are you
talking about?
Harold, that was
a long time ago.
Your awkward years are over.
Yeah, but I don't think
I've changed all that much.
- Are you serious?
- Uh-huh.
Wow. That's crazy.
Yeah.
You know, I think this
whole dating-coach thing
- was a bad idea, so I'm gonna...
- Nonsense.
Being attractive
starts with having a positive
attitude about yourself.
Look at your reflection,
and let me hear you say,
"I look good."
Come on, say it. "I look good."
Let me hear you.
I look good.
Louder, and like you
mean it, please.
You know, this is embarrassing.
Nobody is even around.
- I look good.
- With confidence!
I look good.
Okay. That's better.
Harold...
Nobody is going to
notice you in this world
unless you feel like you're
worth being noticed.
You've got to get
rid of this idea
that you look like
you did back then.
It's not what anyone else sees.
Trust me.
How do we do that?
By bringing out the best in you.
Of course, that means
our first lesson
is going to take a few more
sessions than I thought.
Mm-hmm.
And uh,
how much more is that
going to cost me?
You know what,
it's on the house.
Yeah, let's just call it
some free, extra credit.
I am committed to this cause,
and we are in this together.
Yeah?
Okay.
♪ ♪
Focus. Keep it up.
You've got ten more.
What's one thing you like
about the way you look?
Go.
I don't know.
Think. Come on, think.
Your smile... You've
got a great smile.
All those years of
braces paid off.
Say it. "I've got
a great smile."
I do?
Harold. Come on!
Ten more, let's go.
Let's go.
I'm earning every penny.
You didn't think it'd
be easy, did you?
Maybe not easy, but
not this hard.
I know. I mean,
he's cute, right?
He has potential.
I hope so.
Well, you know, I like him.
He's a good tipper, and his
hair smells like detergent.
- Okay, careful.
- Whoa.
- Aah...
Oh!
Now say, "I look good."
I look good.
All right.
All right, tell me five things
you like about yourself.
Go.
- Uh, I'm loyal.
- Uh-huh.
Considerate, hard worker,
and I like getting
into better shape
now that the soreness
is wearing off.
That's four.
You're going to make
me say it, aren't you?
Come on, let's hear it.
And I've got a nice smile.
Better.
Good. Let's go.
Ah, you kidding me?
Sorry I'm late.
Don't worry, you
haven't missed much.
I can't putt to save my life.
What happened?
Oh, I ran into traffic
on the way over.
No, no. Not that.
I mean, your look and...
And your clothes.
And everything.
I started working
with a dating coach.
Why, is that...
Does it look okay?
Dude,
women are going to
be all over you.
Really?
I told you a dating coach
was the way to go.
That place I suggested...
It worked.
No, uh, I found someone
else actually.
I don't know who they are,
but they definitely know
what they're doing.
And they teach golf too.
You know, her
name's Annie Hayes.
I actually went to
high school with her.
And she's a dating coach.
No, she's a party planner
working as a waitress.
It's, um, kind of
hard to explain.
Basically, she needed a job.
Okay, how well do
you know this lady?
Um, not all that well.
We went a high-school
dance together.
It was a long time ago.
Okay, let me see if
I've got this straight.
You hired someone
from high school,
a woman you barely even know
to teach you how to date,
and she's someone who
normally plans parties
for a living?
Yeah.
Pretty much.
♪ La da da da da da da ♪
♪ ♪
Hey, you made it.
You look great.
Thanks.
I went ahead and
got you something.
Oh, what is it?
A cranbertini.
Ah, thanks.
So... Excuse me.
Why are we having
our lesson here?
I thought it'd be
good to, you know,
just throw you right
into the shark tank.
I mean, surely
you've noticed girls
you've wanted to ask out.
Uh, there's this woman
I always see at the coffee shop
my friend and I go to,
but I've never actually met her.
Hmm.
All right, you need to learn
how to break the ice.
Start a conversation with
someone you don't know.
I'm just going to
warn you right now,
I'm, uh, awful at this.
Okay, don't worry about it.
It... it just takes practice.
I'm going to give
you a few pointers.
Okay, don't use
cheesy pickup lines.
Just don't do it. It
always goes over badly.
Right.
And mostly just be yourself.
What do you mean?
Oh, wow. Uh, okay.
Well, when you see someone
you want to meet,
you just go up to them, and
you say something like,
"hi, I'm Harold.
I wanted to introduce myself.
What's your name?"
It's that easy.
Easy? It's not easy for me.
Hmm...
Okay, see that blonde
at the end of the bar?
That's potential
date number one.
Batter up.
Come on.
Yeah. You can do it.
Take a sip. All right.
Hi. I'm Harold.
Uh, I wanted to
introduce myself.
What's your name?
I'm Amy.
Well, it's um...
Nice to meet you, Amy.
You too.
Oh, my god.
What was that?
Harold, I didn't think I
needed to tell you this,
but after the introduction,
you got to follow it
up with something.
You know, "you look
great tonight."
Do you come here often?"
You make some conversation.
And then of course,
you ask her out.
So remember, it's
one, two, three.
You introduce yourself.
You make some conversation.
You ask her out.
Got it?
I told you, I'm not
very good at this.
Confidence.
You'll get there.
Um, I do think that maybe
we need to throw in
a little more extra credit.
Yeah.
Now, say something to her,
but be sincere about it.
Show her you've really paid
attention to her, yeah?
How about...
You have beautiful eyes.
Good.
That... that felt real.
How are you guys this morning?
Well. You?
Are you going to be here
for dinner tonight?
Nope. Working late.
I thought you worked
the day shift.
For job number one.
- There's a job number two?
- Long story.
Do you need help
finding a place?
Uh, no, thank you. I
can do it myself.
I got to go.
I bet she hasn't even
started looking.
So why is it so important that
Annie move out right now?
Don't you think you're being
a little hard on her?
Steve, she can't just have
a free ride all the time.
I don't get it.
You're more than willing
to help me set my shop up.
Why are you so tough
on your sister?
I'm not. You don't understand.
You sure it's not payback time?
For what?
For resenting her for being
the baby of the family
while you had to be the more
responsible older sister?
It's not that at all.
Really?
All right.
Think about it.
Annie, I'd like to introduce
you to Willy Taylor.
Willy, this is Annie
Hayes, my dating coach.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
I got to say, you're
doing a bang-up job
with my friend here.
Ah, he's doing a great
job all on his own.
I'm just here for moral support.
So when do we expect
our target to show up?
- Is that her?
- Right on time.
I can do this, I can do this.
- I can do this, right?
- Of course you can.
Just remember what
we worked on, okay?
You know what you're
going to say,
so just relax.
Now make your move.
It's time to shine.
All right.
All right, here I go.
Hi.
Are you okay?
I just wanted to
introduce myself.
I'm Harold. Harold White.
Julie. Julie Owens.
Nice to meet you.
I've seen you here before.
I've seen you too. I
love the new haircut.
And that color... It
looks great on you.
Oh, thanks.
Yeah, you always look
so, um, stylish.
Thank you.
So, um, what did you order?
I usually kind of play it safe and...
plain old coffee.
I've tried almost everything.
I like to switch it up.
Keeps things interesting.
Well, I like that.
Sounds, um, adventurous.
Listen.
Hmm?
Do you want to get
together sometime?
Yeah. I'd love that.
My number's on the back.
Call me.
Nice meeting you, Harold.
Yeah, it's nice meeting you...
Julie.
That looked promising.
So what happened?
Oh, nice!
Whoo!
You scored. I knew
you could do it.
I got to call Denise.
She's going to go crazy.
You just went from
being on the bench
to being the star quarterback.
Never thought I'd see the day.
Yeah. You and me both.
My advice is to make plans
to meet Julie for drinks.
It's great because
it's a public place,
and she'll feel more comfortable
since she doesn't
really know you.
Also, it's a short
time commitment,
so if things go south, you
don't have to stay long.
That's a good idea.
This also means
you get to advance
to the next level.
Time to tackle the
art of conversation.
Another one of my weak points.
Okay, let's start
with the basics.
Listening and asking questions.
They go hand in hand.
When you ask a question,
it automatically gives
you more to talk about.
And when a man
listens to a woman
and remembers what she says,
in the world of
relationships, it's golden.
Trust me on this.
Got it.
Okay, so Kim here is
going to play your date.
Oh. I'm good at dating.
Good.
Now, let's say you
guys just met,
- you sat down at the bar.
- Okay.
You got your drinks,
and now it's time
to start talking.
Okay.
So Harold, you start things off.
Um...
Hi. Uh...
What are your... What
are your career goals?
Career goals?
Suddenly, I'm, like,
at a job interview
with the inquisition.
I don't want to...
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Harold, not so
formal, all right?
Try for something a
little more relaxed.
Okay. Right, right. Um...
Right.
You, um, you look nice tonight.
Oh, thank you, Harold.
I don't even have any makeup on.
Just the lip gloss.
I just came from the gym.
Thank you.
Uh, what do you do for a living?
Oh, I am an actress. Yeah.
Well, um, I'm a waitress by
day and actress by night.
All right, well, right now, I'm
a waitress by day and night,
but I'm auditioning and
getting lots of call-backs,
thank you for asking.
Uh, what do you
like to do for fun?
Oh, for fun? Good question.
I, um, I collect teeth.
Different animals' teeth.
You know, they've already
passed on, and I love teeth.
And I raise iguanas,
which I love.
Mm-hmm.
I make, uh, art out
of pie filling,
which is fun.
And um, I'm a wench.
I love jousting.
I have... I'm the champion
jouster at the medieval fair.
No judgment.
Um, it's not going to be
this hard with Julie.
Cheers.
Oh, cheers.
- Mmm.
So, um, what do you
do for a living?
I'm a sales rep in real estate.
I've been doing it
almost ten years now,
and I love it.
That's interesting.
And how did you get
into that line of work?
A friend of my dad's
is in the business.
It's what I always
wanted to get into,
so after college, I went
and worked with him.
That's great.
And, um, what do you
like to do for fun?
Oh, where to start?
I love traveling,
which I do a lot of.
I just got back from
Brazil, which was amazing.
Love fashion, love movies.
Do you like movies?
Yeah, sure.
What about horror flicks?
I love monster movies.
Yeah, I don't get to
see too many of them,
but you know.
Well, hey, you know.
Something just opened
downtown at that theater.
It looks really scary.
We should go see it.
Ooh, doesn't look
too scary, does it?
Well, I hope it's scary.
Rah!
So we're going to a
movie Friday night.
Hey. Good stuff.
Look at you, racking
up those dates.
How did the conversation go?
Pretty good, I think.
It doesn't take much
to get her talking.
She's really, uh, open about
the things she likes to do.
Good.
Okay, so now it's time
for you to do the same.
Which brings us to our
next order of business.
If you really want to
get close to somebody,
you need to start sharing.
You mean, like, talking
about my background,
that kind of thing?
Well, yeah, but more than that.
You know, getting
close to somebody
means talking about the
things that matter to you.
Like, what are you
passionate about?
What do you love?
What moves you?
Those are the things you
want to share with her.
Okay, but, uh...
Yeah? But what?
No, I'm just...
I'm afraid I might
disappoint, you know?
I think I might be
kind of boring.
Harold, that is so not true.
The right person is going to
love you for who you are.
Trust me.
There's just one problem though.
What?
Who are you?
I mean, I know you have
great taste in music,
but what are you
passionate about?
You took all these photographs?
Yup.
Printed them, too.
I had no idea.
There's something so exciting
to me about preserving
a perfect moment,
you know, to hang onto
something beautiful
that never fades nor goes away.
Does that sound corny?
No. Not at all.
I just...
I wouldn't have guessed you
for the creative type.
You just keep on getting
more and more interesting.
Mmm. It's delicious.
Really?
Well, I tried to
make it healthy.
You sure it's good?
It's incredible.
Harold, I had no idea you
were such a good cook.
- Well.
- Okay.
All of this plays
into your favor.
Let's recap, shall we?
All right, you like
candlelit dinners.
Uh-huh.
- Gorgeous photographs.
- Yeah.
Your favorite movie
is Casablanca,
and we're not even counting
the love songs yet.
Need I go on?
Oh, um, does that
seem a little bland?
No way.
Harold, you're like this
old-fashioned romantic.
Most women think guys
like you are extinct.
Or never existed.
You know, at least
outside a romance novel.
You think so?
Oh, I know so.
Harold, for your next date,
I want you to share
this side of yourself.
Tell her about something
you love doing,
and do something with
her that's romantic.
I promise you, you're
not going to regret it.
All right.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Plenty more of that.
- Mmm.
Good.
I loved that part when
he popped up behind her
with that big knife.
How freaky was that?
I, um, closed my eyes
through that part.
And then the chase scene
through the woods...
Wasn't that scary?
Actually, I closed my eyes
through that part too.
I think I'm going to have
nightmares all week.
Yeah, me too.
It was great, wasn't it?
Yeah.
They have really good
double chocolate cake here.
Do you like chocolate?
Love it, I'm addicted.
Well, we could share
a piece if you want.
How could I refuse?
Thanks for the movie.
Thank you for dessert.
Look, I really had fun tonight.
Me too.
You're a great guy, Harold.
Good night.
Okay, so two fries, two burgers.
Cheese on yours, no cheese.
You want fries, you
want mashed potatoes.
Do you want coleslaw too or...
- Yeah, we'll do some coleslaw.
- Great, you're here.
I need to talk to
you for a second.
I... uh, Harold, what
are you doing here?
- I thought you had a date.
- No, I did.
- Can I just see you?
- Sure.
Sorry, excuse us.
- Is everything okay?
- Better than okay.
I had to come by
and say thank you.
You were so right about
everything you taught me.
Being myself and
asking questions
and just sharing who I am.
I did exactly what you
told me, and it was like
we were really connecting.
Do you know she even
kissed me good night?
- That's so great.
- I know.
I just... I feel different.
Everything is gonna be
different from now on
all because of you.
Ah, thank you.
Yeah.
So we're still on for
Wednesday, right?
- Yeah, for sure.
- Okay.
Good, so... I'll see you then.
- Okay, I'll see you.
- Bye.
And... and great work.
Really great.
Wow.
Denise, if you don't
hear from me by noon,
I want you to call a paramedic.
Bye, sweetheart.
This is all your
fault, you know?
- What is?
- This.
Making me do all this.
Ever since you
started working out,
all I've been
hearing at home is,
"why don't you get in
shape like Harold is?"
And "why don't you ask Harold
to bring you with him"
the next time he works out?"
Yeah, but it feels
great, doesn't it?
Great? This isn't great.
Great is sitting at
home on my couch,
watching the game,
drinking beers,
and eating chips.
Come on, we got to
keep up the pace,
we only got another mile to go.
What? Shoot me now.
You know, I was
thinking about maybe
trying to cook for Julie.
Maybe a candlelight
dinner or something.
Who are you?
Preparing candlelight dinners?
I definitely don't
recognize you anymore.
I don't recognize me either.
I got to tell you, feels great.
This isn't great.
I've never seen Harold
like that before.
He's, like, this whole new man.
I almost didn't
recognize the guy.
I know, from what
I've seen, like,
you've done a great
transformation.
It's like you have a
gift for this, really.
I mean, if word gets out, like,
you could be famous,
really, you really could.
You could have, like,
your face on the side
of, like, bus benches
or a reality show...
If they offer you a series, can
I please, please play you?
It almost sounded like
he didn't need me
anymore though.
But that... That can't be right.
Right?
He needs me, he needs me.
For sure.
Are you more worried about
losing your dating coach gig
or the fact that this guy
is now off the market?
What do you mean?
You like him, don't you?
- I... of course not.
- Yes.
That is crazy, no.
- You do.
- I do not.
Your mouth just had
a little quiver.
It never... Has never done that.
No, it's professional, we're
working together, that's it.
- Really?
- Really.
- Yes.
All right, just checking.
Although I have to say,
since you've worked on him,
he has gotten kind of hot.
I'm just saying.
♪ Annie and Harold,
sitting in a tree ♪
♪ K-I-S-S-I-N-G ♪
Try this.
What is it?
It's delicious.
- Pineapple.
- Pomegranate.
- And raspberry.
- And coconut.
So tell me, what am
I learning today?
Well, I was thinking,
you're at that stage
where it's not super serious,
but you want it to go that way.
So now might be a
good time for you
to do something nice for her
or make her feel special.
I love that. What do
you have in mind?
All right, well, forget
expensive, all right?
It shouldn't be
anything too big.
You don't want to scare her off.
So I don't know,
just something small
to show her you really care.
Oh, you know what?
I have an idea.
- You do?
- Yeah.
See, Julie's always
talking about wanting
to spend time in the city.
I could take her somewhere
nice for dinner.
Unless you think
that's too much.
No, no, that could work.
Gotta think about where
I could take her.
It's gotta be really romantic.
I could... I could probably
recommend a place.
Oh, great, let me
know what it is.
I'll make reservations.
You know, I actually...
I haven't been there in so long.
I'm thinking, maybe we should
go there first and check it out
just to make sure
it's the right spot.
Yeah, that sounds great.
♪ ♪
I'm thinking, before dinner,
you guys could go for
a nice, long walk,
watch the sun set.
I like that idea, it's,
um, it's romantic.
And good for the appetite.
You know, this place is perfect.
Julie's gonna love it.
I'm suddenly wondering
why I don't
come into the city more often.
Harold... I can't believe
I just heard you say that.
That doesn't sound like
the Harold I know.
Well, that's thanks to you.
- Oh, before I forget.
- Yeah.
Here is your last payment.
So... that homecoming
dance we went to...
Yeah.
We danced together.
No.
No?
Are you sure?
You invited a bunch
of your friends
to meet us at the dance.
I didn't really fit
in with that group.
When I finally got the nerve up
to ask you to dance,
I was too late.
Matt Schneider had
gotten to you first.
Couldn't get up the
courage to ask you again.
Matt Schneider?
You remember that?
Kind of thing tends
to stay with you.
Sometimes longer than
people think it should.
That's not why you
remember the dance, is it?
I didn't make you
feel that way, did I?
I'm really sorry, I...
I promise you, I... I
never meant to do that.
I was 15, it was just me
trying to have a good time.
Yeah.
It wasn't supposed to
make you feel bad.
Well, hey, if it makes
you feel any better,
you're doing a lot better
in life than I am.
I have no career and
no relationship.
Come on, Annie.
I mean, you're the prettiest
girl from our high school.
I know you're gonna
meet somebody.
I've seen your work.
It's only a matter of time
before somebody hires you.
You just have to
believe in yourself.
I know I do.
Wait a second.
Did you just give
me my own advice?
I think you did.
Yeah.
Very good.
What about Billie Holiday?
Oh, I love it.
Have you heard her
version of Misty?
Amazing.
Although first place
for that song
still belongs to Johnny Mathis.
What about Tony Bennett?
Classic. Definitely
in my top ten.
Uh-huh.
Do you like Dean Martin?
You're Nobody Till
Somebody Loves You.
Mm, it's one of my favorites.
You know, some people
would say we're sappy
or born in the wrong era for
listening to that kind of music.
Who cares?
It's the best stuff on earth.
I know.
This... This could very well be
my first choice for the song.
The song?
Yeah, you know, the one
that becomes our song
when you find the
right somebody.
When you share a
song with somebody.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, I've always liked
that idea too.
Did you just get in?
Yeah.
Just a little while ago.
Been putting in some
late nights, you...
You look tired.
Annie?
Hmm?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Okay, don't stay up too late.
Listen, I wanted to tell you...
I know I haven't been the
best sister in the world.
Moving in here and not
really pulling my weight.
I just... Things haven't really
worked out the way that I
wanted them to, you know?
I never thought life
would be this hard.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
I just wanted you to know that.
Thanks.
And I also wanted to tell you
what a great job I
think you're doing,
being a great mom and
having a great family.
You've got a lot to be proud of.
I appreciate that.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night.
Annie, yeah, it's open, come in.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Oh, wow.
These are new, aren't they?
Yeah. What do you think?
I think they're amazing.
They belong in a museum.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
Man, this is beautiful.
Thanks.
Uh, are you ready
to get started?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
So today we're gonna work on
one of the most important
parts of dating.
Getting close,
becoming intimate,
you know, getting to first base.
Yeah.
This could be the most important
lesson in dating ever.
Agreed.
So how do you recommend
I make a move?
Well, first of all,
wait until you guys
are close together.
Uh-huh.
After you've been talking awhile
or when you're saying good
night at the end of the date.
So, um, like this?
Yeah, good.
Now, the most important thing
is to be natural about it.
You know, don't do the old "guy
gotta stretch my arm" routine.
Stay away from tacky.
Yep.
And...
And use your eyes.
- My eyes.
- Mm-hmm.
Look at a girl when
she's talking to you.
And if she's looking
at you the same way,
she's giving you
the green light.
Like this?
Mm-hmm.
Then what?
And then you just
lean in slowly.
Yeah.
And then you just...
How was that?
It was great.
I mean, I mean, you
did all right.
How do... How do
you feel about it?
Okay.
Just okay?
Well, shouldn't I feel okay?
No, no, you should be okay.
Definitely be okay.
Um, I'm just thinking
though that we should
probably run through
this a few more times.
Just to make sure you're
comfortable with everything.
Yeah, I mean,
that's a good idea.
- Sure.
- Good.
So...
I'm ready whenever you are.
Um, so you were
pretty quiet tonight.
What do you think
of the restaurant?
It's nice.
I just wish we could have
done more, you know?
Seen a show or maybe
check out some clubs.
There's just so much
to do in the city.
Well, um, maybe next time.
Can I get your chair?
It was nice though.
Thanks, Harold.
Sure.
You know, um...
People say I'm not
such a bad cook.
Maybe next time we can
have dinner at my house.
That sounds good.
Whoo, closing time.
Here we go.
Hello?
- Hmm?
- Anybody there?
You've been in a daze all night
with that, like, gooey
look on your face.
You okay?
Who is he, and does
he have a friend
that looks like Ben Affleck?
No, I'm just thinking
about Harold.
You know, he's just not who
I thought he was at all.
I mean, he's this
amazing photographer.
And he's smart and
romantic and...
And it's funny, like,
all this time,
I just thought he was a nobody.
That makes me a horrible
person, doesn't it?
Nope, Annie, it
makes you someone
who obviously has the
hots for this guy.
Kim, he's dating someone.
And she's beautiful and
successful, and I'm...
You're beautiful,
and you love him.
Just admit it.
I cannot like him. He's taken.
And that was not my point.
What was your point?
I don't know, I just...
I didn't realize what
a great guy he is.
All right, whatever you say.
I'm out of here.
Whatever you're cooking
smells incredible.
We're gonna be ready to
eat in about ten minutes.
My special Risotto.
Harold, you don't happen to know
any event planners, do you?
A good friend of mine
is putting together
a big fundraiser in the city.
Are you serious?
- She said they're desperate.
- I know someone great.
She and I went to
high school together.
Can you get me her number?
Yeah, of course, no problem.
Thank you.
So where are we going tonight?
Uh, what do you mean?
You mentioned dancing.
Oh, right, yeah, no, I
thought we'd pick out
some records from my
collection and dance here.
I got lots of Sinatra.
You like Sinatra?
I guess I misunderstood.
I thought you meant we'd be
going out for the dancing part.
No, I just kind of planned
a quiet evening in.
What do you think?
Anything I can do to
change your mind?
I'm not really into
the old stuff.
It reminds me of what
my parents listened to.
Sure, yeah, okay.
Great.
There's a new bar that
just opened downtown
I've been dying to check it out.
I heard they have a great band.
I'll see what time
the show starts.
Megan, here is a hot chocolate
with whipped cream.
Thank you.
And a coffee for
you, young lady.
Harold.
You're not gonna believe this.
- I... I got the job.
- Whoa.
I am officially employed
as a party planner.
And it's in the city.
You're welcome.
Thank you for this too.
So, um, how did your date go?
Did slow dancing sweep
her off her feet?
Not exactly.
She, uh, really wasn't up
for a quiet evening in.
She always wants to go out
and do something...
Something fast and furious.
Ah, well, believe it or not,
this is actually a good thing.
You're starting to see
each other's differences.
Which brings us to
our next topic.
The subject of give and take.
Compromise is essential to
making any relationship work.
So what do you suggest I do?
Well, since you gave
on the dancing bit,
I say switch it around.
Invite her to do something
you really want to do.
- You think?
- Yeah.
If you want to be someone,
you find ways to compromise.
And who wouldn't want to
spend time with you, Harold?
I think that's the nicest thing
anybody's ever said to me.
Hold still for a second.
No.
No, stop.
No way, I never pass
up a beautiful photo.
Okay, that's enough.
That's good, that's good.
You know what, I'm taking photos
out by the lake tomorrow,
you want to come along?
Why?
No reason, I just...
I like your company.
Okay.
I'll pick you up at 5:00 then.
Wait, in the morning?
Whew.
Do you always get up this
early to take pictures?
Well, I have to.
The light is perfect
this time of day.
It's magic hour, you know?
Magic hour?
Yeah, um, well, it's
soft, you know?
Everything has this
nice, beautiful...
Like, a golden look about it.
It only happens at
sunrise and sunset.
Mm.
You want to take a look?
- Go ahead.
- Yeah.
Oh, wow.
That's pretty.
I feel free out here, you know?
- Does that sound weird?
- No, not at all.
I love being out here this
time of day, it's like...
Well, it's like the whole
world is just waking up.
Yeah.
So this event I'm planning...
It's a fundraiser to
preserve our parks.
Well, that's a great cause.
It is, yeah.
And what I'm thinking
is we could feature
your gorgeous landscapes.
No, come on, think about it.
You know, photos everywhere
of what we're trying to save?
And you'd get some free
advertising out of it.
You interested?
- Are you kidding?
- No.
Yeah, of course I'm in.
How great.
All right.
I love this.
We definitely have
to use this one.
Oh, are you sure
it's good enough?
Absolutely.
It's beautiful.
Don't question my good taste.
Sorry, my mistake.
You can really see that
look of magic hour
you were talking about.
Somebody was paying attention.
It's like, um...
A picture out of a fairy
tale or something,
where it's all soft and glowing.
- Come here.
- What?
- Why?
You mean...?
- No.
- Please?
No, no.
Julie doesn't like
this kind of music.
I don't have anybody
to dance with.
And Matt Schneider isn't around
to steal you away from me.
I can't believe you're
guilt-tripping me.
Mm-hmm.
You're never gonna let
me forget that, are you?
Probably not.
Come on, dance with me.
♪ What went wrong ♪
Well, I guess I do owe you one.
♪ ♪
♪ We lost each other
in every way ♪
♪ Sometimes we're blinded,
don't you know? ♪
So after that dance
we went to...
Mm-hmm.
You dropped me off and
walked me to the door
and kissed me good night.
No.
- No?
- No.
Um, you sat in the front
seat with my mother.
When we dropped you off,
you waved good-bye.
And that was it.
I think that was the last
time we spoke in high school.
♪ Suspecting all along ♪
♪ That something was so wrong ♪
Are you sure you didn't
walk me to the door?
Yes.
♪ But the memories ♪
♪ They won't let me ♪
♪ I've got a bad case,
don't you know? ♪
So you and Denise should have
a good refund this year.
Just increase the deductions
on your paychecks.
You got it.
Hey, how are things
going with Julie?
Oh, they're going great.
Good.
Hey, what are you working on?
A new landscape?
No, it's just a
work in progress...
Ah, pictures of people.
The man is breaking new ground.
This isn't Julie.
Does somebody have a
crush on his coach?
- I don't.
- Mm-hmm.
You should go work on
your taxes, don't you...
And to celebrate...
- Whoa.
- Ta-da!
Uh, what is that?
Uh, I don't know, it
was all we had left
when I closed up last night.
Banana cream, I think.
Not bad.
And what's the candle for?
Well, I wanted to
add some flair.
I know it's a birthday
candle, but who cares?
We're celebrating
your graduation.
Go, blow it out.
There's still one more
lesson though, right?
True, but first a toast.
It's official,
you're a heartthrob.
And one of the
nicest guys I know.
I hope Julie knows how
lucky she is to have you.
But most of all, here's
to your happiness
because you deserve it.
Do I get to say a few words?
By all means.
A toast, back to you.
I learned from the best.
And I also got to
spend a lot time
with the prettiest
girl in high school,
who I always had a crush on.
You did?
I did.
Huh.
Okay, final lesson.
And this is probably the
most important thing
I will ever teach you.
I call it my golden rule.
Okay.
There's not a lot to it.
It's just something you
should always remember.
When in doubt, trust your gut.
Follow your heart.
And always, always be honest...
With yourself and with
the person you're with.
Oh, uh... Aah!
It's so wet and muddy.
Are we there yet?
Here it is.
This is it?
There's not, like, a
beach or something?
No, I told you it was a
little more rustic than that.
Oh, great, my shoes are ruined.
I just bought them.
Are you almost finished?
Have you taken everything
you need to take?
The light isn't
really what I want.
This was supposed to be
an early morning trip.
Well, the party ran
late last night.
I didn't get to bed
till 2:00 this morning.
I overslept.
What's wrong?
Nothing, just not gonna
get anything I can use.
Great, does that mean
we can leave now?
Yeah.
Okay.
You just have the best
laugh in the world.
Aww.
- I gotta get going.
- Yeah.
Thank you so much
for stopping in.
It was great to see you, Matt.
Yeah, I'll see you soon.
- Bye.
- You're the best, Annie.
She is the best.
Nice to meet you, handsome Matt.
Take care.
- Kim.
- Oh, yeah.
Is that guy's name Matt?
Yeah, yeah, that's Matt.
Did you get his last name?
I forget his last name.
He's a high-school
friend of Annie's.
Is it Matt Schneider?
Yes, Matt Schneider.
You okay?
Hey, Harold.
Hi, I didn't know you were here.
Why didn't you say hi?
Uh, you were busy. I
didn't want to interrupt.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah, you okay?
Yeah.
Um, I found an
apartment in the city.
I'm gonna be moving there.
When?
Pretty much right away.
Mm. Well...
Great it's all coming
together for you.
Seems like all your dreams
are coming true, huh?
Yeah.
I owe you big-time, Harold.
It's Julie.
Oh, take it, yeah.
Hello.
Okay.
I'll see you then.
- Sorry.
- It's fine.
Um, I just wanted to...
What?
I just was gonna
say, um, thank you
for helping me get that job.
You deserve it.
How was your last shift?
Great.
Sounds like it.
I'm moving out tomorrow.
I thought you were
leaving on Saturday.
No, my apartment's
ready in the city,
and there's no reason
for me to stay.
The sooner, the better, right?
You could stay if you want.
What?
I thought you wanted
me to move out.
Wasn't that the whole point?
No, I...
It's... it's really hard to
stand out in this family
when the kid sister is you.
What?
I guess I've always
resented that.
Uh, have you been drinking?
Because if not, maybe now's
not a bad time to start.
I'm serious. You
were the baby...
The pretty one that got to
go out and have a good time.
But I had to make
a good example,
so I just did what I was told.
Okay, first of all, you're nuts.
Second of all, I was
the one who couldn't
measure up to you.
Do you know how
many times I heard,
"why can't you be
more like Claire?"
When we were growing up?
- No, you did not.
- I did so.
Mom and dad worshipped
you, and you know it.
- I don't think so.
- Well, I know so.
And I'm right.
You're wrong, forever
and infinity, so there.
I am so proud of you.
You are so brave.
Going out there and
living your dreams.
Doing all the things I never
had the courage to do.
And I think you are a
huge success in life.
Having a home, a family,
all the things that
really matter.
So we both want
what the other has.
We're quite the pair.
I guess so.
I'm really sorry for making
things hard for you.
I'm sorry too.
I really look up to you.
I always have.
I want you to know that.
Will you teach me how not
to be a loser in life?
Baby, you are not a loser.
You're brilliant at
everything you do.
And I want you know, I have
always thought that about you.
Really?
Yes, really.
What's wrong?
Nothing, nothing.
Just the man of my
dreams is already taken.
- Hi.
Thanks for coming.
Do you want to get something?
No, no, I'm fine.
Julie, there's something
I wanted to t...
Before you do, there's
something I need to say first.
- This can't wait, I...
- No.
Really, please.
I've been thinking about
a lot of things...
About us.
And I just think that we're
two very different people,
which is why I think we should
stop seeing each other.
Are you saying you don't
want to see my anymore?
I hope you understand.
I think it's for the best.
No, that's great.
I mean, it's not
great, I'm just...
I'm glad that we're
on the same page.
I guess so.
Look, Julie, I want to thank
you for being honest.
Because I really think
that's the best way.
Yeah.
You take care.
Good-bye, Harold.
Take that picture, and put
it in the corner over there.
Thank you.
Are you the Annie Hayes
responsible for putting
all this together?
Um, that depends,
do you like it?
I love it.
- Then I'm Annie Hayes.
- And I'm Malcolm Winters.
Hi.
This is amazing.
My hobby is photography.
But whoever did these
is a true artist.
His name's Harold White.
Listen, my company's having
its Diamond Jubilee.
I'd like to talk to you
about it, here's my card.
Give my office a call next
week and set something up.
I will, thank you.
That's great.
You're staying for the party?
Oh, I wouldn't miss it.
And I can introduce you to
my photographer friend.
I love his work. See you later.
Okay.
Great job.
Thank you.
Harold, why aren't
you in the city?
Doesn't the party start at 7:00?
I just wanted to leave
this for Annie.
For you to give her the
next time you see her.
Can I see?
Mommy, look, it's me and Annie.
I also, um, wrote a letter
explaining to Annie why I
wouldn't be there tonight.
I don't understand why you're
not going to the party.
You got Annie the job, your
photos are on display.
Well, there's only so many times
I can let myself be
rejected by Annie.
What are you talking about?
I had a bad experience a
bunch of a years ago.
Annie and Matt Schneider
were a big part of it,
and I don't want to go
through that again.
I'm sorry, I'm...
I'm confused here.
Me too.
Matt Schneider
really likes Annie.
She seems to like him too.
You really don't get it.
Annie likes you.
Annie told mommy that you
were the man of her dreams.
She did? She said that?
Those were her exact words,
except she thought
you were taken.
You can still make it.
Before I turn the evening
over to dancing,
I'd like to thank our donors.
For all of you who have been
admiring the impressive
images around the room,
I'd like to introduce
the photographer.
Is Harold White in the room?
Mr. White?
Hi, I'm Harold.
Mr. White has offered to
donate all the proceeds
from the sale of his photographs
to help us save our parklands.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you, everyone.
Uh, I need to thank
someone special.
She's the person who put
this whole party together.
She's a woman of many talents.
And, uh, I'm living
proof of that.
Her name is Annie Hayes.
Annie and I knew each other
a little in high school,
but recently, I've
had the chance
to get to know her much better.
She's taught me a
lot about who I am,
who I want to be.
I don't know how I'm ever
gonna thank her for everything.
Annie, I like my life so
much more with you in it.
I'd like to keep it that way.
Oh, and, uh, I agree with you.
I think this would make
an excellent choice
for the song.
♪ I wanna be loved ♪
♪ With inspiration ♪
What do you think?
Can this be our song?
I think you've got
great taste in music.
♪ Hold me tight ♪
♪ I wanna be kissed ♪
♪ Until I tingle ♪
♪ I wanna be loved ♪