I met the two great loves
of my life
when I was 10.
One was the girl
next door.
The other...
a mail order bride...
so to speak.
Two love stories that
changed my life forever.
Papa! Mail.
Huh.
This is your wife.
I have a wife?
You will.
This is Sharmila.
When you are 22,
you will marry her.
But, I don't
love her.
Love-shmove.
Here.
Go get the milk
for mommy.
Yes, we were now in America.
But as you can see,
my father held on to
some of his Indian ways.
The Karma Kid
has his ears on.
Huh?
Hurry up,
Smith!
Lickety lick!
It's "lickety split!"
That was the girl next door.
Her name was Amy.
How doing,
Mr. Wilson?
My father told me,
if you want to get
along with Americans,
you should always ask them,
"How doing?"
How doing,
Swanson family?
As for me,
I just wanted to be
a good old American boy.
And yes,
my name is Smith.
You see, my father
believed,
to pursue
the American Dream,
you had to have
an all-American name.
But what my father
didn't know,
was that "Smith"
was a very
common American...
last name.
I studied hard
to be American.
Every Thursday,
I watched "Happy Days."
My favorite movie was
"Saturday Night Fever."
And...
I longed to eat
all-American food.
So it was time
to be a man.
Time to take a bite
of the American Dream.
♪ Well you can tell
by the way I use my walk ♪
♪ I'm a woman's man
no time to talk ♪
♪ Music loud
and women warm ♪
♪ I've been kicked around
Since I was born ♪
♪ And now it's all... ♪
What was I thinking?
I was a vegetarian.
There were a few
cowboys in this town.
Some of them did not care
for this little Indian boy.
Nice bag,
Pocahontas.
I'm not that
kind of Indian.
Well the only good
Indian's a dead Indian.
And Billy MacNamara
was one of them.
Get him, boys!
You boys tryin' to get
yourselves killed?
No, sir.
We're just...
p-playing.
Well, you better go
play somewhere else.
Yes, sir.
You're, uh,
Captain Mack's boy?
Yes, sir.
Well, I'd rather not have
to tell your daddy
what you've been up to.
We ain't up to
nothin', sir.
Well, good.
Let's keep it that way.
Have a nice day, boys.
But there was one cowboy
that made up for
all the others.
Butch Brunner.
The Lone Ranger.
And I wanted
to be his Tonto.
Come here, boy.
You know how much
this would cost
in that stupid
grocery store?
Um...
Two dollars!
Conversion, please.
Uh, 125 rupees.
Exactly.
That's too much!
Cost me only pennies.
You have to
be smart, Smith.
Wait.
Come and see your
Jack-o'-ladder.
"Jack-o'-lantern."
Here is
your pumpkin.
It's supposed
to be big.
We have a couple
of months.
It will grow big.
Bigger than your head.
And, orange?
A red marker
fixes it.
Red and yellow
make orange.
But pumpkins are
supposed to be round.
Round-shmound.
You will use whatever
I give you.
Here, take
these to mami.
Damn, kids.
In India you take
whatever you get.
No questions.
And don't forget
your shoes.
Yes, papa.
Just because we live
in this country
does not mean we have
to become heathens.
Smith!
I'm sorry I ate animal.
I'll never do it again.
One.
It was the dreaded
Uthak-baithak.
I'm sorry I ate animal.
I'll never do it again.
Two.
Punishment reserved for
the worst of transgressions.
I'm sorry I ate animal.
I'll never do it again.
Three.
It was not a violent
punishment,
but a humiliating one.
I'll never do it again.
Spanking would've been
a blessing in comparison.
I'll never do it again.
Five.
The mere mention
of Uthak-baithak
could bring
tears to my eyes.
I'm sorry I ate animal.
I'll never do it again.
Six.
You eat chicken again,
you will be banished,
straight to India.
Understood?
I'm sorry I ate animal.
I'll never do it again.
Seven.
Papa, it's enough.
No, he needs
to finish.
You will do
all ten.
You understand,
chicken boy?
I'm sorry I ate animal.
I'll never do it again.
Eight.
What's going on, Papa?
Never you mind.
Come, help me in
the kitchen, Asha.
But, mami, I have
to study with Betsy.
Go help, mami.
Asha.
Keep going.
I'm sorry I ate animal.
I'll never do it again.
Okay, that's enough.
Go to your room
and study.
Wait.
Where's the milk change?
I'm sorry I spent
the milk change on chicken.
I'll never do it again.
One.
The term "human anatomy"
comprises a consideration
of the various structures
which make up
the human organism.
In a restricted sense,
it deals merely with the parts
which form the fully
developed individual,
and which can be rendered
evident to the naked eye,
by various methods
of dissection.
In addition to deciding
who I would marry,
my father had decided
my profession, too.
I was to be a doctor.
Specifically,
a neurologist.
Fortunately, there were
certain distractions.
And I wasn't the only one
who was roused by them.
Every neighborhood
has that one family
that marches to
its own drumbeat.
In our neighborhood,
it was the Brunner's.
They were the
talk of the town.
The subject of rumors
at Bible study.
The gossip at
the local hair salon.
Like lions in
the Serengeti...
They were beasts to
be admired, and feared.
But more than admired them,
I loved them.
In fact, I thanked them.
Were it not for their moments
of unbridled lawn sex,
I would not have Amy.
My first love.
Hmm.
There she was,
a touch of Heaven
a mere 30 yards from me,
yet a Heaven
unreachable.
A distance I was
unable to cross.
I still remember the first
time she spoke to me.
Wanna be
my partner?
Would I?
Are you kidding?
Huh?
Which in Hindi
means "yes."
Is everybody partnered up?
Okay.
And, five, six,
seven, eight.
♪ My baby moves
at midnight night ♪
♪ Goes right until
the dawn ♪
♪ My woman takes
me higher ♪
♪ My woman keeps... ♪
What are you staring at,
pervert?
You should talk to her instead
of being a Peeping Tom.
Oh, god.
Smith, come here.
Do I smell
like curry?
Yes.
This smell
is impossible!
I thought Patrick
likes Indian food?
Shh!
I'm studying
with Betsy.
You remember that, and I
won't go telling mami and papa
about your little
sick habit.
Smith, you want to get
along around here?
Rule one: don't go telling
mami and papa everything.
They'll never
understand, anyway.
Ah! There were rules.
I had no idea.
I need to rid
of this smell.
I resolved to pay
closer attention.
Nalini, this
is good news.
The Ramesh Bhai is
offering 250,000 rupees
for Sharmila.
That's...
Five thousand dollars.
Not bad for
our chicken boy.
We can put it
towards the gas bill,
finally get some
heat in here.
It's so cold
at night, papa.
Put on another sweater
if you're so cold.
You're so conjoos.
Just put the heat on.
I'll light
the fire.
Let me just enjoy
my chai first.
She's beautiful.
They look
lovely together.
Mami!
How many times must
I remind you to remind me
that the chai is hot?
Papa, I brought
you a saucer, now.
Oh.
As my parents debated
my matrimonial value,
my sister was about to
get away with murder.
Papa will never let
you go before supper.
Learn from
the master.
Bye!
See?
Told you.
She's not
having supper?
Well, Betsy, no?
Who is Betsy?
Uh...
Papa,
we're a family.
We should have
dinner together.
Like in India,
on the table.
Bye!
Stop.
Come in here.
Where are
you going?
Ah...
outside?
Nothing doing.
Go back to your studies.
But my eyes hurt.
Come here, Patel.
Come now.
Go set
the table, okay?
Hm? We're gonna eat
in a few minutes.
You don't want his eyes
to get worse, do you?
Here, now.
Ruko.
Thank you, Patel.
It hasn't been
easy for Smith.
He has no friends here.
Everyone makes fun of him.
At least in India he had
someone to play with.
I never hear
the boy complain.
We're much
happier in India.
I had Lata.
I didn't my own dishes,
I didn't wash my own clothes.
I never cleaned
my own toilet.
Here, no Lata,
no servant, no nothing.
I'm doing it all.
Be patient, mami.
When we go back, we will
live like rajas and ranis.
We will live the American
Dream, in India.
I don't want to
live like a queen, papa.
I just want
someone to talk to.
You don't even let me
invite that Avon lady in.
She's no friend.
Besides, you have
the make up.
And the Wilson's, when they
brought us an apple pie,
I could have returned the favor
with a spinach paneer.
But you said "no."
The Wilson's.
They come to my house and tell
me that my gods are worthless.
That only that
the Jesus saves.
Still nice
people, papa.
Give them the spinach
paneer and you'll see
a cross burning in our
vegetable garden.
Besides, none of us
liked the apple pie.
I liked the apple pie.
Oy, chup!
See that?
Today it's the apple pie,
tomorrow it's the Jesus.
I swear I will send that
boy back to India,
he keeps it up.
More talk of banishment.
Smith!
Get the axe.
The axe?
The axe.
Yes, go get
the axe.
It seemed like
a harsh punishment
for merely
liking apple pie.
The Wilson's.
Good.
Keep practicing.
So this Halloween thing
is coming up again.
Yes, can I go
this year?
Maybe you would like
to go as a doctor.
A neurosurgeon.
It pays to specialize.
Yes...
or, maybe Darth Vader?
Doctor Vader?
Does he specialize?
Um...
kind of.
And just our luck,
it falls on Diwali this year.
Definition, Diwali.
The festival of lights.
Our new Year.
Good.
Well, let's see what
mami can put together.
Go ahead, keep chopping.
Chop chop.
So, what do you think
of these all-American
metal grilling contests?
It's not a contest,
it's a barbecue.
I know barbecue.
I'm just saying, do you think
we should have one on Sunday?
Sunday's no good.
Everyone will
be in church.
Ah, forget it, then.
The Brunners never
go to church.
The Brunners, huh?
Okay.
Get the wood inside.
Patel, where is
your papa?
His tea's
getting so cold.
Hm?
It is done.
What is done?
The Brunners are
coming over Sunday
for a metal
grilling barbecue.
You invited them?
Of course
I invited them.
But when the square bricks
start coming
through the windows...
...don't blame me.
What...
what will I make?
Oh, I could make them
apple pie, or maybe the corn,
uh, Patel,
what-what do they eat?
Uh, hot dogs, hamburgers...
Uh-huh?
Nonsense.
We will cook vegetables
on the grill.
The onions, the eggplants,
the chili pepper.
All from our
home-grown garden.
They will love it.
Papa, uh, I think we should
really give them something
that they will eat,
or something
that they will like.
When you go to Rome,
you do what the Italians do.
It was Sunday.
Sweet Sunday.
And the Brunners
would soon arrive
for a metal
grilling contest.
While my mother was in
the kitchen, trying to
figure out how to prepare
vegetables for grilling...
My father was in the backyard
adding a little more charcoal
to that old grill.
And my sister, she was
priming herself
for another study
session with the Betsy.
It was Sunday,
and the Brunners...
the sweet Brunners...
were only a half
an hour away.
What's cookin'?
Or not.
Dad, it's customary
to ring the doorbell
and wait for them to open
the door for you.
Oh, honey, it's fine.
We're guests.
Hello?
Anybody home?
Papa!
Papa, who are they?
They're here
already?
You see, I warned you
about these people.
Welcome.
Welcome to my home.
Hey, buddy.
Good to see ya again.
So is it two
o'clock already?
Oh, no, it's just...
we wanted to come over early
and help you guys out.
Brought a couple beers.
Uh-huh.
So who are these
pretty ladies?
This is my wife
and daughter.
Who's who?
I'm Nalini.
Melanie.
Nalini.
Melanie... I dated
a Melanie once.
I'm Asha.
This is my daughter,
and this is my wife.
Smith!
Come in here!
I can see why you keep this
beauty locked up, Oscar.
Bhaaskar.
Basker?
Butchy.
I'm sorry, this, uh...
This is my sweetheart
here, Nancy.
Oh, he is
too cute.
Hi, it is so nice
to meet you guys.
It's nice to
finally meet you.
How are you?
We brought you
apple pie.
No.
Yes.
Too much trouble.
Yes, yes, of course.
I mean, you just
have to bake it.
But it's like
two hours at 350.
Just in time for dessert.
And our little
angel, Amy.
Amy,
get in here.
May I come in Mr. and Mrs. Bhatnagar?
Come in, honey.
Come on.
Come in right here.
This is Amy.
Hello.
My son.
Oh!
Hey, buddy.
You know Amy,
right?
Yeah, we're both in
Mrs. Reynold's class.
Oh.
You got a whole church
goin' on here.
Looks like
Little Boy Blue.
Dad, it's Krishna.
He's a Hindu god.
That's right!
Very good.
Huh.
Is this little
cutie pie you?
Oh, that is Sharmila.
Smith's wife
when he turns 22.
I wanted to tell her
it wasn't true.
That if she wanted to,
I would marry her
right now.
And this is
Asha's husband,
when she turns 18.
So, let us
go grilling!
Let's do it.
Uh, show me around.
What do you think?
So, uh, what are
we eatin' here?
The vegetables.
Oh, and Nalini
made rice.
And delicious naan.
Grilled vegetables, huh?
Never thought to do that.
So, what's naan,
like a chicken
or a beef
or somethin'?
It's a bread.
We are vegetarian.
Huh...
Well, we are definitely
not vegetarian.
How could you
know that?
I'd like to eat
a vegetarian meal.
Well, today's your
lucky day, sweetheart.
But me
and your mom...
we got, uh,
certain needs.
I'll be back,
Oscar.
That's a barbeque,
buddy.
That meat
is done.
No, uh, uh, uh.
I got it.
We're almost
done here.
Ooh, that is good.
I'm off to study.
Bye.
See ya later.
Say hello to the Betsy.
Smell it.
Let's eat!
Ah, look at
that, huh.
Thank you.
Oh, dear.
So, O-Oscar,
what made you wanna
come to the U.S.
of A. anyway?
Well, it's always been
my dream to work in America.
As a CPA.
Huh. Uh, th-that's
like a doctor?
A certified public
accountant.
Ah.
Oh.
Melanie,
do you have a job?
Why should she?
I make a base
salary of $32,698.
What?
Plus the overtime.
No!
Butchy, baby, you are
in the wrong business.
Hm.
How much
do you make?
Well, I'm... You know,
I'm... about that.
It's... No, it is
not that much.
But we do manage
to get by. We're good.
Yeah, I'm savin' up,
uh... you know,
I wanna open
my own garage...
Mm-hmm.
...like a-like a car
garage, you know?
It's not a reliable
business.
We've got the Japanese
making cars now,
that never break down.
So what do you expect?
There you go
again, sweetie.
I mean, I've been thinking
about maybe getting a job.
Well, what you need is
a job that has a future.
Smith here is going
to be a neurosurgeon.
Why a neurosurgeon?
Because it pays
to specialize.
Hmm.
Oh, my God,
that is so cute.
Right, but h-h-how do you
know he's gonna end up
doin' what you
want him to do?
Because if you are
a good obedient boy,
you do exactly what your
father tells you to do.
Exactly.
Huh.
Okay.
What you need to
do is ask yourself,
what is your
specific skill set?
Oh.
What talents
do you possess?
Ooh.
Okay, skill set.
I like that.
You know I've got
talents, honey.
Skill set, yeah.
Yeah.
In the bedroom.
That's my skill set.
It's true.
Oh, honey .
Uh... all right,
here we go.
Oscar, look at that.
Uh huh.
That's for you, sweetheart.
Thank you, my darlin'.
Thank you so much.
You want me to
take your plate?
Okay, she's good.
All right, kids,
before we eat,
who wants to
play a game?
Uh, me.
Me, too!
All right, this is
a very serious game, okay?
It's called, uh,
Don't You Dare Laugh.
Uh-uh.
So we all look at each
other real serious,
and-and the first person
who laughs, loses.
Ready?
One, two,
three, go.
Right here, Oscar.
Right here.
Ahhh!
I couldn't...
You laughed.
It was Sunday.
Sweet Sunday.
And while my neighbors
were at church,
trying to
reach Heaven,
Heaven came to
my own back yard,
and reached out to me.
♪ Sugar Pie Honey Bunch
You know that I love you ♪
♪ I can't help myself ♪
♪ I love you
and nobody else ♪
♪ In and out my life
in and out my life ♪
♪ You come and you go ♪
♪ you come and you go ♪
♪ Leaving just your
picture behind ♪
♪ And I've kissed it
a thousand times ♪
♪ When you snap
your finger ♪
♪ or wink your eye
I come a-running to you ♪
♪ I'm tied to your
apron strings ♪
♪ And there's nothing
that I can do ♪
I had fun today.
Me, too.
See ya at school.
Yeah, see ya.
Bye.
Hey, daddy.
Hey, sweetheart.
Smith, what are
you doin'?
How doing, Butch?
Come on in here.
Wow.
Really cool motorcycle.
Thank you, buddy.
It says "Indian."
I am Indian.
Yep.
Wait.
What is that?
This?
That's like
a good luck bell.
It keeps all the evil spirits
away when you're ridin'.
I think every
bike needs one.
Really?
Even mine?
Sure.
Cool.
Yep.
Smith, come on!
Time to make
the table!
I have to go.
Your motorcycle
is really cool.
I wish I had
a bike like yours.
Bye, Butch.
See ya later.
I cannot understand
why this mortgage
is not a priority to you.
Why the charge card bill
is not a priority.
I know what you're get...
I'm not-I'm not
sellin' my bike.
What costs this much?
I'm not gonna talk
about that anymore.
I'm not sellin' my bike.
Okay, fine.
Keep it.
Keep your toys.
That's fantastic.
But how am I supposed to
pay for our kid's shoes?
She doesn't even have
shoes that fit, Butch.
I gotta send
her to school.
Mom?
Yeah, baby.
What's for dinner?
Something special,
sweetheart.
Something your, uh, mom's
been preparin' all day.
It's called
a TV Dinner.
Be ready in five
minutes, baby.
Yeah, five minutes,
'cause it's a damn TV Dinner.
God, I don't wanna be
this person, Butch.
You just...
you push and you push,
and it's excuse
after excuse.
It's not just me.
How am I supposed to afford
anything at
the grocery store?
I'm a joke at
the grocery store!
I'm the lady clippin'
every coupon...
Yep.
...buyin' cheap TV Dinners
'cause that's
all I can afford.
My parents are
at it again.
Amy...
get inside, please.
Your mother needs you.
But dad, I wanna
go with you.
Smith.
Promise me you'll take care
of my little girl, all right.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
I'm...
It's okay.
Just-just promise me
that you'll never
leave us until you
go to marry that girl.
I promise.
Don't worry.
He'll be back soon.
Yep.
I'm gonna go inside.
Okay.
Bye, Smith.
Bye.
Love-shmove.
Who needs it?
She's pretty, no?
I have a surprise
for you.
What is it?
It's a surprise from papa.
Is this my costume?
It's your very own,
home-grown...
Jack-o-landon.
Mami, that's
not a pumpkin.
I know.
I'm sorry, Patel.
Is my costume ready?
Getting there.
Coming along.
I need it by morning.
It's all in the note.
Don't worry, Patel.
Be ready by the morning.
Who am I going to be?
It's a surprise.
Mami, can I have
a real pumpkin?
We'll see.
Mmm.
Come on, go wash
up for supper.
Just the two
of us tonight.
Where's papa?
Papa is...
working overtime,
and Asha is studying.
With the Betsy.
Hmm?
Yeah?
Go.
Go wash up.
♪ Don't break the heart ♪
♪ That loves you so ♪
For better or worse,
we were quickly becoming
a typical American family.
♪ Handle it with care ♪
♪ Don't break the heart ♪
♪ that needs you ♪
♪ Darling please be fair ♪
I had promised Amy
that her father
would return home.
Now, I had to make
that happened.
For the first time
in my life,
on my very own,
I prayed.
I turned to Ganesh,
the remover of obstacles,
the god of safe journeys.
And I asked that he
bring Butch home safely
from his present travels.
Wake up, doofus.
Go to bed.
I had the best night, Smith.
I was charming
and wonderful.
Do you like it here?
I love America.
The boys are so handsome.
Not as handsome as
my little brother, but...
Can you keep a secret?
This was serious.
You know,
Patrick and I...
we're in love.
Very serious.
With my sister
already paired
with a suitable
boy in India,
the punishment
would surely be...
banishment.
He's smart, and charming.
He thinks I'm beautiful.
When we first
saw each other,
we just knew.
You just know.
Whoo!
Oh.
Your hero's home.
Bet he's wasted.
I sold my bike!
To a guy with
some money.
Yeah.
Honey, I'm home.
Yep.
Wasted.
Butchy.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Great!
Got a little
somethin' for ya.
Where's your bike?
A big wad of these.
Here you go.
What did you do?
I sold it.
I sold my bike.
'Cause I love you.
I didn't want
you to do it.
Ah, it's all right,
I'll get another one.
Smith!
Butch sold his bike, buddy!
Gone!
You're the only
Indian I got now.
Ha.
Go to bed.
Thank you, Lord Ganesh.
Thank you.
Good night.
Where is mami?
"Where is mami?"
Just sit down.
Your silly costume broke
the sewing machine needle.
And she's out
trying to fix it.
But I need it
for school.
Chup.
Eat your breakfast.
Mami will bring it
to school for you.
Asha!
Breakfast!
I work the overtime,
and this is what
I have to show for it.
How doing?
Um, it's very important.
I need a sewing needle.
It's, uh...
Read the sign, lady.
We don't open for
another ten minutes.
Um, okay.
But it's-it's for today,
uh, sewing a, uh,
Halloween costume.
Please?
One needle.
Come on!
Bye, papa!
Remember I won't
be home for supper!
I know, I know.
Studying with the Betsy.
Hey, where's your costume?
Whoo!
Come on, get in the car.
I'm already late.
I'll ride my bike.
No you won't.
Ah!
All right, okay,
Let's finish up with
the Jack-o-lanterns.
And now is your last chance
to check your costumes.
I hope your mama gets here
before the costume contest.
In future,
make sure your mama
reads the notes
that we send home.
And if she needs help
understanding them,
she can always call me.
Okay?
There were many things
my mother, with her master's
degree in English Lit
did not understand.
But English was
not one of them.
Damn stupid needle.
Okay.
Now, who is
going to win...
this genuine light saber
that I got off
Obi-Wan Kenobi. Hm?
Well, let
the voting commence.
Cindy, you go first.
Okay.
Now who votes
for Cindy?
Steven, stand.
Come on.
Who votes for
the Swanson boys?
Okay. Billy.
Good job.
How many votes
for Billy?
Amy.
How many votes
for Amy?
Okay.
Has everybody gone?
Oh, Smith, sweetie,
that's okay.
You can stay seated.
No, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
I vote for Smith.
Billy, that's not funny,
he doesn't have a costume.
That's the best little
Indian boy costume
I've ever seen.
I mean, who else
votes for Smith?
Come on.
He's not that kind
of Indian, stupid.
All right.
Amy and Smith,
sittin' in a tree.
K-I-S-S-I-N-G!
Billy!
First comes love,
then comes marriage...
Thank you.
Smith, wait up.
Slow down.
Can I walk with you?
It's a free country.
Hey, watch.
Oh, boy.
I could smell
the Johnson & Johnson
rising up from her hair.
Oh, sorry.
Oh, no.
That's okay.
Um, what happened
to your costume?
My mom was supposed
to bring it.
I guess she forgot.
Yeah, I made my own
costume 'cause I knew
my parents would forget
to buy me one.
Hey, if your mom never
makes your costume,
then we can make one up.
We could be like
the two hobos or something.
My dad's got a bunch
of extra suits.
I mean,
if you wanna go
trick-or-treating with me.
Okay.
You got a date.
Come over as
soon as possible
so we can hit
a lot of houses.
Okay.
Bye.
See ya later.
Okay.
K-I-S-S-I-N-G.
Indeed.
Mami!
I'm in the kitchen!
Papa said you were going to
bring my costume to school.
So sorry, beta.
I tried
But the needle broke.
Twice.
So no costume?
I finished it.
Finally.
Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait!
It's a Diwali present!
Diwali present?
But it's Halloween.
You can have it
after dinner.
And after our tea.
Come on, why don't you
finish your homework quickly,
before papa comes home
and doesn't let you out.
Oh, yes!
Just my luck.
Diwali fell on
Halloween this year.
So much to do.
So little time.
Slow down.
You can not rush God's
invitation to our home.
You must invite each god,
one at a time.
One at a time?
For the first time
in my life,
I saw the advantage
in believing in...
one god.
I'm done.
Can I go put my costume on
and go trick-or-treating?
You're going
to eat first,
then you're going to put
up the lights for Diwali.
Can you do that?
Or you can stay home.
Mami!
The trick-or-treaters
are here!
I need my costume!
I hope you like it.
Enjoy, Patel.
Mami, come.
The game is
about to begin.
Papa, let's give the children
real treats this year, no?
Nonsense!
There's nothing more
real than money!
Ah, mami,
they're almost here!
Come!
Trick-or-treat!
What do we have here?
Mami, what do
you call this?
No wait, don't tell me.
Count Dracula!
No, no, no,
that's not it.
Uh...
shoot, it escapes me.
You, of course,
are guitar player.
But do you know how to
play the sitar, huh?
And you are
a punching man.
Can we just have
our candy, mister?
Okay.
Okay, these
are real coins.
Try and grab as much
as you can with one hand.
Shoot!
It's a trick!
That's right.
Trick-or-treat.
You got tricked.
Here's candy.
Are you Indian?
Why, yes I am.
Then where are your
feathers, chief?
Oh, that is a very
original joke.
Uh, dude,
it's Halloween.
Not Christmas.
What a dick.
We have to
go back home.
I know, papa.
Mami!
Coming, Patel.
Papa, please
give the candy.
Please be nice to
the children this year.
I don't want to spend
all my day tomorrow
cleaning the soap and
the eggs off the windows.
Coming, Patel.
Boo!
Butch.
What's with the Christmas
lights, buddy?
It's Diwali.
Tamale?
Diwali.
The festival of lights.
Very good.
So where's that
boy of yours?
He's supposed to go
trick-or-treatin'
with this little tramp.
Oh, come in.
Boo!
You got me.
Smith.
Come on.
So, what do you think?
Oh, terrific, mami.
This is a better
than a surgeon.
I am not going
out like this.
What the hell is that?
He's Ganesh.
Ah, another one of
them Hindi gods.
A Hindu.
Hindi is the language,
Hindu is the religion.
Yeah, I know.
He's the god
of journeys
and the remover
of all obstacles.
I think he's beautiful.
My gratitude to you,
Lord Ganesh.
All right, well,
you kids go have some fun,
and Smith,
promise you'll, uh,
protect this
little girl
from all those witches
and goblins and whatnot.
I promise!
I'll be fine.
Bye, beta.
Don't worry, your daughter
is in good hands.
Yes, all four of them.
Get it?
That was a joke, because
Ganesh has four hands,
and what Nalini was
trying to say is that,
if your daughter is with
my son who is Ganesh,
she's got four arms
protecting her.
♪ Sugar ♪
Okay, um...
Okay, okay.
♪ You are my candy girl and
you got me wanting you ♪
Trick or treat.
Oh, a hobo...
And an elephant?
Not very scary.
♪ You are my
candy girl ♪
♪ and you got me
wanting you ♪
Trick or treat.
My, what do
we have here?
You must be a bum,
and you are, uh,
what's his name?
Dumbo the elephant.
Here you go.
♪ I just can't believe the one
to love this feeling to ♪
♪ I just can't
believe it's true ♪
Thanks, lady.
♪ Oh Sugar ♪
Smith, don't
sweat it.
We'll get you
chocolate.
Yeah.
♪ You are
my candy girl ♪
♪ and you got me
wanting you ♪
♪ Oh honey ♪
Well, bless
your hearts.
What have we here?
Well, you're that
Charlie Chaplin fella.
Oh, yes,
the tramp.
Very good, honey.
And this one is from
that cartoon movie.
Well, Dumbo didn't
have four arms.
He's Ganesh,
a Hindu god.
There's only God,
and don't you
forget it.
Have you children
repented your sins?
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ Pour a little sugar
on me baby ♪
Here.
These will help you
children more than candy.
♪ Oh yeah ♪
Remember,
only Jesus saves.
♪ Pour a little sugar
on me baby ♪
I'm not answering
the door again tonight.
Well, turn off
the lights.
All right.
♪ Pour a little sugar
on me honey
♪ Aw sugar ♪
♪ Honey honey ♪
This isn't working.
Nobody gets
who I am.
I'm not scary.
I look
like Dumbo.
Can't even see
in these things.
Smith, tonight is not
about the costumes.
It's about
the candy.
And we've only
got eight pieces,
not including
the religious stuff.
We can't go home unless
we have at least 50.
I think you
look divine.
Get it?
Oh...
Very funny.
Good one.
Hey.
It's the graveyard.
You know you can't
go through these things
without holding
your breath.
Hmm?
You don't want a dead soul
getting inside you, right?
There could be a mass murderer
living inside you,
and you wouldn't
even know.
Okay.
Let's go through.
Hold your breath
and count to three.
One,
two,
three!
Oh!
Hey, Amy.
Who's the elephant boy?
Leave him alone.
He's my cousin.
You don't look like you're
from around these parts.
No.
I'm from In...
Uh...
Run!
Go get 'em, boys.
And there I was,
in quite
the predicament.
I started praying
to Lord Ganesh
to remove all obstacles
from Amy's path
and the danger
from mine.
Smith, shut up.
That's right,
elephant boy!
Yee-haw!
Go.
Trick or treat,
Pocahontas!
Go! Yee-haw!
Boy.
Hope Stan
didn't hurt her.
Gimme the bow.
Billy, you sure you
want to do this?
Shut up, Steve.
Excuse me?
Could you
let me go, please?
I need to
find my friend.
She'll be dead
in a few minutes.
It's all your fault.
Put the bow
down, boy.
I'm outta here.
Butch,
is that you?
That's right, buddy.
Where's Amy?
I think she, uh...
Right here.
Billy, this
is my dad.
Uh, hello, sir.
What are you doing
there, cowboy?
I was just playing.
So why were
you being mean?
Amy's the only girl
who's ever nice to me.
Now her and Smith
are hanging out.
She doesn't
like me anymore.
Huh.
Well, here's the thing
about girls, Billy.
You're gonna have
a much better chance
at being friends
with them
if you aren't trying
to beat 'em up.
You understand me?
Yes, sir.
All right, you
know what to do.
Sorry, guys.
See you at school.
I had failed Butch.
I had not protected
his daughter.
It was a night
I wanted to forget.
Y'ello!
Anybody home?
Rise and shine!
How doing, Butch?
How doing?
Looking good, Bhaask.
I gotta get me
a pair of those.
Oh.
So, what
is happening?
I was gonna go
hunt some big game.
Thought I'd take
little Smith with me.
You know,
could be fun.
Toughen him up
a little bit.
Big game,
yeah, sure.
Toughen him up.
Smith, come!
Uh, no, I don't think...
No, no,
it's okay, mami.
The boy needs
to toughen up.
Hey, buddy.
Do you want to go play
the big game with the Butch?
Oh, yes.
Good, then go
get ready.
Oh.
No, it's okay.
Wear somethin'
warm, buddy!
Oh, yes.
So what's
for breakfast?
♪ A young cowboy
named Billy Joe ♪
♪ grew restless
on the farm ♪
♪ The boy filled
with wanderlust ♪
♪ who really
meant no harm ♪
♪ He changed his clothes
and shined his boots ♪
♪ and combed his
dark hair down ♪
♪ And his mother cried
as he walked out ♪
Here you go.
♪ Don't take your
guns to town son ♪
♪ Leave your guns
at home Bill ♪
♪ Don't take your
guns to town ♪
♪ He laughed and kissed
his mom and said ♪
♪ Your Billy Joe's
a man ♪
♪ I can shoot as quick
and straight as anybody can ♪
♪ But I wouldn't shoot
without a cause ♪
♪ I'd gun
nobody down ♪
♪ But she cried again
as he rode away ♪
♪ Don't take your
guns to town son ♪
♪ Leave your guns
at home Bill ♪
Look at this,
Smith.
Fresh tracks.
A doe and a buck.
What is a doe?
It's a deer.
Come on, let's find
a place to hole up.
And never put your
finger on the trigger
until you're about
to shoot, you get it?
Hmm, okay.
All right, right now
we're on safety.
Okay.
Another thing is,
never run with a loaded gun.
It's dangerous
and stupid.
Is that clear?
Yes, Butch.
All right, get your
gun out here.
All right.
Let's see what
happens, huh?
♪ Don't take your
guns to town son ♪
♪ Leave your guns
at home Bill ♪
♪ Don't take your
guns to town ♪
You see anything?
No, but when they
come, watch out!
Blam, blam!
Blam, blam, bam!
Hey, whoa, watch...
Hey, hey.
Hey, Smith, no.
It ain't
"blam, blam," buddy.
Uh-uh.
Hunting is
a sacred thing.
This is real.
Look at the, uh,
American Indian.
When he kills
an animal, he...
he bends down
in front of it
and thanks it for giving its
life for him and his people.
You know?
And he-he says
prayers for it.
Then he uses every
bit of that animal,
every bone
and tendon,
every bit of
meat and fur.
Nothing gets wasted.
You understand that?
Yes, Butch.
Surprised your dad
let you go hunting.
Actually,
I don't think my father
understands big game hunting.
Hmm.
Big game...
hunting...
Nalini!
Oh, my god.
Butch.
Yeah, buddy.
Is it okay to
hunt squirrel?
Sure, you can
hunt squirrel.
What'd you
shoot at?
A squirrel.
Did you get him?
I don't know.
Let's go check it out.
Just keep looking at the map,
and see anything that
shows "hunting ground."
Big game,
look for it.
Why are you
looking outside?
What is big game?
I am looking outside.
You look at
the map, please.
Wow, Smith.
That's some shootin'.
It's alive.
Maybe we can take
the bullet out.
No, the bullet
went clear through.
This guy's
a goner.
What have
I done?
Can we do
the prayer?
Yeah, we can, uh,
we can do the prayer.
Uh...
great spirit,
mother Earth, father sky,
uh... sister tree,
brother leaves.
Before you all,
we wanna thank
this squirrel,
this generous squirrel
for giving his life
so that we may
live and learn.
Smith, repeat after me.
Squirrel, we thank you.
It is done.
I had killed an animal
without being provoked,
but Butch...
had cleansed my soul.
All right, let's
pack it up, huh?
And now we're lost.
Where the hell are we?
I tried to
tell you twice,
but you wouldn't
listen to me.
If it's important,
you must speak up.
I tried.
Now our son might kill
something or someone.
All right, buddy,
let's get home
and cook up that
squirrel, huh?
You mean like eat it?
Yeah, I mean eat it.
But, I... But...
Shh, shh, shh.
Look, look.
You see that?
Stay here, don't move.
Butch!
Ow, son of a... That hurts.
But you told me not to
run with a loaded gun.
Just drive, Smith.
Yeah, this is Red Hawk.
Uh, got a man down,
a little hunting accident.
We're heading West
on I-47.
I think we
just passed 213.
Keep an eye out for a blue
and white Dodge truck...
with a...
with a little Indian
fella behind the wheel.
Gonna need an ambulance.
Dammit, Smith!
Watch the road, buddy.
Smith?
Take care, you know.
We'll call an ambulance.
Hang in there,
Red Hawk, Over.
Copy that.
You heard him, Smith.
You got two miles to
keep us on the road.
There's probably gonna
be some cops there, too.
Whatever they
ask you, just...
plead the fifth.
Plead the fifth, yes.
Wait, Butch,
what is the fifth?
Butch, Butch,
what's the fifth?
Butch?
Smith!
Mami, Papa!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt, papa?
Huh, are you hurt, beta?
Are you injured, son?
What-what is...
Oh, ew.
Did you kill that?
Answer the policeman, Smith.
Uh, I...
plead the fifth.
All right, good work.
Did you shoot
Butch Brunner?
I plead the fifth.
Make a note, Dick.
He pleads the fifth to
shooting Butch Brunner.
Okay, we got that, son.
You know, personally,
I-I would have
plead the second.
You do what you
feel is right.
Yeah, pleading the second
would have been
the way to go, kid.
Definitely.
Now...
what about this?
I plead the fifth?
He can't plead the fifth
on a squirrel, can he?
Uh, no, on a possum
you can plead the first,
but only if you haven't
already plead the fifth,
and he's already
plead the fifth.
Which negates
all of your rights
to plead the first.
You're in a heck of
a pickle here, Smith.
What can I plead that
will cover everything?
Oh...
I... Can he plead insanity?
Squash, squid, squirrel.
How old are you, son?
Ten.
Ten?
Why didn't you tell
us you were ten?
He can't plead the
fifth until he's 13.
Right!
I thought because of his
extensive knowledge of the fifth
that he would
be at least 13.
Me, too, but he's ten.
Hmm.
I'm sorry, Smitty.
You can't plead the fifth.
What can I plead?
How's Brunner?
He's gonna live.
You get a statement?
Yeah.
Said the kid's a hero.
Saved his life.
You hear that, Smitty?
You're off the hook.
So, off the record...
why don't you tell us
what really happened.
And so I did.
It was a relief to hear
that Butch was okay,
and he called me a hero,
and it was good to tell
the policemen my story.
It was a story I was sure my
parents would not appreciate,
but these men thought it
very interesting,
and for some reason,
very funny.
The story caused
a bit of a stir,
and was published
in the local paper,
along with a photo
of my family.
Okay, everybody,
say, "How doing?"
How doing?
We quickly became
the talk of the town.
And being an election year,
the article caught the attention
of some politicians.
I am honored to bestow
the key to the city
to Smith Butt Naked.
Bhatnagar.
Oh, uh, Mr. Smith.
Let's give him a round
of applause, shall we?
Before I knew it,
I was telling
my story on TV,
and believe it or not,
I was invited to The White House
to meet the president
of the United States.
I was no longer
just an Indian.
I...
was a Bee Gee.
It was the pinnacle of
my American boyhood.
Ah, the maharaja
has finally returned.
Good.
Go change and come
help me in the garden.
Jesus Christ.
What did you say?
Nothing, papa.
You think you are
a superstar now, huh?
Gallivanting all
over the town.
But you're no local
hero around here.
You want to come in,
into your father's house?
Show your respect.
Ah!
Jeetay Raho.
It was good to receive
my father's blessings...
but sadly, the blessings
did not quite reach...
the Brunners.
Oh, man.
Honey, we gonna
talk about it.
Are we gonna talk,
or argue?
This isn't fun, Butch.
It's not fun.
All right?
I just have to know...
how I'm supposed
to pay the mortgage.
I already told you,
I... My...
I can't work!
When my leg heals.
My mother can help.
I don't want your
damn mom's help.
Just let her.
I mean, what's wrong
with that?
I can't...
I can't do that.
I can't let her help.
When my leg heals,
I'm gonna...
do what I do,
and I'm gonna fix it.
I promise.
No, you're not.
Smith?
And then...
I have to tell
you something.
The worst thing
imaginable happened.
Amy told me she and her
mother were moving far away...
to another school,
to live with
their grandmother.
And dummy that I was,
I got mad at her.
From that moment on...
Smith!
I decided I wasn't going
to see her anymore.
Bye, daddy.
Bye, sweetheart.
Come here.
I'll see you soon, okay?
I wished I had not
gone hunting that day.
I wished everything could
go back to the way it was...
before hunting,
before fame.
Before I had ruined...
the Brunners' lives.
Hello?
...the various stages of
its intrauterine development,
from the fertilized ovum...
Doofus.
Amy's on the phone.
Hello?
Hi, Smith.
It's Amy.
Hi.
Sorry I didn't say
goodbye to you.
It's okay.
Um, how's school?
Okay.
Are you coming back?
No.
Oh.
I'm running away, Smith.
I wanted to say
goodbye to you.
Where are you going?
To New York.
I can't stay here...
It's smells like mothballs,
and my-my grandma
can't cook, and...
I think that...
That my parents
are splitting up.
I'm sorry.
Smith.
Yes?
I miss you.
I miss you, too.
I wish you were here,
my Ganesh.
I wish I was
there, too.
My grandma's coming.
I have to go.
Bye.
New York?
What was I thinking?
Why didn't I try
and stop her?
She was calling me to
save her, and I said...
nothing?
You scared me.
Where's Smith?
He's in his room.
Tell him it's time
to chop the wood.
I'll go get him.
Smith?
Smith!
His bike's not here.
Let's go look for him.
Get in the car.
Papa, they couldn't be far.
He could be, come on.
Let's get in the car.
My Ganesh.
I knew you'd come.
At your service.
I have to catch
the 9:55 bus.
The 9:55 bus?
But what about
money, food?
I packed a bunch
of sandwiches,
and I borrowed some money
from my grandma.
I'll pay her back
once I land on my feet.
Amy, I don't
want you to go.
It's too dangerous.
I can't protect you
if you're in New York.
But...
I don't like it here.
I know, Amy, but...
I don't want to lose
my best friend.
I thought I'd give you
a ride home, cowboy.
Okay, thank you.
Were you planning on
writing when you got there?
Any idea where you
two were going?
Smith wasn't going anywhere.
He just came over
here to stop me.
Hmm.
You're just all by
your lonesome, huh?
You sure are brave.
Actually...
I've decided to stay.
I'm happy to hear that.
Looks like Smith is, too.
Why don't you get
back inside
before we all
catch cold, huh?
Bye, Smith.
Bye, Amy.
Bye, dad.
Bye, sweetie.
Let's go.
Why would he run away?
It makes no sense.
You're the one
that got upset with him
for being a local hero.
You don't think
he has any feelings?
If you ask me,
he has too many
damn feelings.
Where are we going, papa?
It's the park,
where kids go to play.
What are you looking at?
Move!
Move out of the way.
So many damn kids.
What are they
playing at night?
How the hell do I know?
Someone must have
seen him.
He's the local damn hero.
You check over there.
Be careful, papa.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
How doing?
I'm looking for
a young boy,
Smith Bhatnagar.
Bhatnag?
I've never heard of him.
Yeah, you know,
man, Smith.
He's the kid that saved
the dude that shot himself.
Yes!
Oh, yeah.
That was cool.
Is Smith here?
That's what
I'm asking you.
Oh...
Oh.
Well, I don't know, dude.
Yeah, we just got here.
Nalini!
Thank you.
No, nothing, nothing.
Let's check these people.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for a little...
I will never again lie
about where I'm going
and with whom.
Two.
Never, ever.
We ought to send
you back to India.
Shame on you.
I will not.
I will never again lie
about where I'm going
and with whom.
Three.
Butch, what do
I tell my parents?
Just tell 'em the truth.
I bet your dad will think
you're a real stud.
Really?
Sure.
Running after girls,
saving their lives?
You're like a knight
in shining armor.
Thanks, Butch.
Smith, I got you something.
Whoa.
For my bike?
Yep.
Thanks, Butch.
Listen, buddy, don't sweat it.
You're still a kid.
The best is yet to come.
All right?
Hmm.
Let's go.
I will never again lie
about where I'm going
and with whom.
Twenty.
Mami, what is happening?
Never you mind.
And you will never see
that boy again, ever.
And wipe that nonsense
off your face.
India will definitely
shape you up.
So where the hell
were you?
Amy decided
to run away, so...
I had to try
and stop her.
I rode to her grandmother's
house and told her not to go.
She decided to stay.
Telling the truth felt so good,
I decided to
let it all out.
I love her.
You rode all the way
across town on your bike
to chase after a woman?
What is wrong with you?
What is wrong
with our children?
Whores, all of them.
Rule one... never tell
mami and papa everything.
How could I have forgotten?
Go to your room.
We'll deal with you
in the morning.
My poor sister...
in love and about
to be banished.
I wondered if her
heart would ever mend.
What would I do
without my sister?
That night, my parents
called India,
an expensive
and rare event.
They stayed up very late
talking to the family,
and deciding
my sister's fate.
Our hopes for you,
our dreams for you,
they have all
been destroyed.
What suitable Indian boy
will marry you now?
You've been enjoyed.
Okay, mami, we keep
this in the house.
But from now on,
it is decided.
You will go to school,
and that is it.
No more extra-circular
activities.
You want to study
with someone?
Mami and I will need
to meet her first,
and she will need to
study in our house,
but no more studying
with the Betsy.
And as for you...
Go ahead, mami,
show him the picture.
Patel, this is
your daddy and baba.
You remember my parents?
He was three when
we moved to Pune, papa.
I know that.
You are going to
live with them...
in Lucknow.
But-but...
that's in India.
Yes.
Best thing for you, Patel.
Why?
Because he needs to go back
and remember the things
that you so easily forgot.
Respect, honor, virtue.
When will you
come see me?
Don't worry, Smith,
we'll all be
together again...
in just a few years.
I never did get to watch
my sister bloom
into the beautiful
woman she became.
But she continued
to love Patrick,
even more than before.
As for Amy, well...
she lingered on my mind
for some time to come,
a heaven,
half a world away.
My family never did move
back to India to rejoin me.
They told me how lucky
I was to have escaped,
to grow up to be
a respectable boy in India.
I went to med school
and became a doctor,
specializing in neurology,
like my father expected.
At 22, I married Sharmila,
as I was told I would.
What no one
told me was that...
I would fall madly
in love with my wife.
This was
a wonderful surprise.
I bought a large house for her,
and for a little while,
we lived like
rajas and ranis.
I'd like to say we lived
happily ever after, but...
life has a mind
of its own.
Over the years,
my mother would send me
letters on a cassette.
She kept me connected to
the place I left behind.
My mother's voice
made me feel at ease.
Especially as
I mourned for Sharmila.
♪ And bigger
than me and you ♪
Hi, beta, it's mami.
I hope you're feeling...
♪ In the form of an
evergreen cassette ♪
♪ And I played it
in the morning ♪
♪ Till after the sun
would set ♪
♪ See mother I believe ♪
♪ That half of everything
I hear is true ♪
♪ Between you and me ♪
♪ I believe
the anecdote's true ♪
So I moved back to a place
where I knew I would
find love again.
♪ In the veranda
in the midnight heat ♪
♪ Cousins and I would
wait for the rains ♪
♪ Singing songs about ♪
♪ America ♪
♪ And then the first
drops came ♪
♪ So don't worry ♪
♪ Even though you were ♪
♪ oceans and continents away ♪
♪ I heard evergreen hits ♪
♪ Lullabies ♪
And it was wonderful.
♪ And everything
you had to say ♪
♪ See mother I believe ♪
♪ That half of everything
I hear is true ♪
♪ Between you and me ♪
Wonderful to be back
in the embrace of family...
young and old...
and new.
♪ If time time
could be bent ♪
♪ with the drop of a tear ♪
♪ You'd see it rain in
our house for a year ♪
♪ This is the sound of
the beating you'd hear ♪
♪ All the tapes
we've taped over ♪
♪ all of our hopes
and our fears ♪
♪ The open veranda's been
flooding for years ♪
♪ I always hoped that
I'd see you here ♪
Whoa.
Smith?
You won't believe it.
I shot a 98.
You shot a what?
The golf!
I broke 100.
Now is 98 good
in the golf?
Good?
It's excellent.
Great, papa.
I'm very happy for you.
You're finally back home.
Come on, hurry up.
We have to go to Namata's
kid's birthday party.
I'm coming.
So many damn
birthday parties.
Ah, I see you found
your old bike.
You saved it
all these years?
Oh yes, just for you.
Don't be ridiculous.
It's for Asha's kids!
Oh, boy, okay.
Come on, papa.
I'm coming.
Smith?
How doing, Butch?
Look at you, buddy,
all grown up.
Wow.
See, uh, you still
got your old bike.
I see that you
got yours back.
Yeah, yeah, took a while,
but she came home.
Cool.
My father tells me you have
your own service station now?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And, uh, you became, uh,
that doctor your dad
wanted you to be.
Yeah.
And the brain surgeon who
couldn't save his wife.
Yeah, I was, uh, sorry to
hear about that, buddy.
How's Amy?
You asking, uh,
or you asking?
Both.
She's good.
She's, uh, got a kid.
Teaching fourth grade.
Living over at her
grandmother's house.
And no, she's not married.
You probably remember how to
get over there, don't you?
I'm sure I can
figure it out.
Good to see you, buddy.
Yeah.
Come by anytime.
Sure thing.
Bye, Butch.
♪
♪ Sugar pie honey bunch ♪
♪ You know that I love you ♪
♪ I can't help myself ♪
♪ I love you
and nobody else ♪
♪ In and out my life ♪
♪ You come and you go ♪
♪ Come and you go ♪
♪ Leaving just
your picture behind ♪
♪ And I kissed it
a thousand times ♪
♪ When you snap your fingers
or wink your eye ♪
♪ I come a running to you ♪
♪ I'm tied to your
apron strings ♪
♪ And there's nothing
I can do ♪
♪ Can't help myself ♪
♪ No I can't help myself ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Sugar pie honey bunch ♪
♪ I'm weaker than
a man should be ♪
♪ I can't help myself ♪
♪ I'm a fool
in love you see ♪
♪ Want to tell you
I don't love you ♪
♪ Tell you that
we're through ♪
♪ And I've tried ♪
♪ But every time
I see your face ♪
♪ I get up all
choked up inside ♪
♪ When I call your name ♪
♪ Girl it starts the flame ♪
♪ burning in my heart ♪
♪ Tearin' it all apart ♪
♪ No matter how I try ♪
♪ My love I cannot hide ♪
♪ Sugar pie honey bunch ♪
♪ You now that
I'm weak for you ♪
♪ I can't help myself ♪
♪ I love you
and nobody else ♪
♪ Sugar pie honey bunch ♪
♪ I'll do anything
you ask me to ♪
♪ I can't help myself ♪
♪ I want you
and nobody else ♪
♪ Sugar pie honey bunch ♪
♪ You know that I love you ♪
♪ I can't help myself ♪
♪ No I can't help myself ♪
♪ Sugar pie honey bunch ♪