Uploaded to OS by: xXSwesubsXx
Translated by: 90399bc
National day of mourning in the Philipines,
after 44 police commanders were killed,
in the line of duty when an anti-terror
operation went wrong.
-
PUNJAB PROVINCE
50 miles north of Lahore, PAKISTAN
Philipine authorities now say the toll in yesterday's
hotel bombing has risen to 146 dead and 231 wounded
It is the most devastating terrorist attack in Asia,
in 10 years. And the worst ever, in Manila.
While no organization has taken
responsibility for the blast,
Western intelligence sources have identified
chemical traces that are the hallmark of
the infamous arms-dealer, Aarmir Barkawi
International security experts say that the Barkawi
family is now instigating violence in remote capitals
To foster instability, and thus fuel
massive arms sales around the globe.
- Kamran
- Raza
Did Philippine Intelligence track you?
Father,
- You did well,
- Thank you.
We need to discuss Major General Rahmad.
It's your sister's wedding.
I'm sorry, this can't wait.
I think your ISI officer was compromised.
Kamran, all Pakistani intelligence
officers are compromised.
One of our Afghani friends discovered
a German BND agent in his circle.
And?
That particular general won't be very
useful to us anymore. He's been eliminated.
Thought you might want to know.
Don't forget his family.
Vengeance must always be profound,
and absolute.
Very happy.
"BARKAWI on SITE"
#lol  #selfie_stick
-
CREECH Air Force Base,
NEVADA
confirmation from MI-6 ground missile.
You're free to execute.
Hell of a a presidential race, sir
Everyday the same damn joke.
Seriously?
- What the hell your made of?
- Bourbon, and poor choices.
Pick a name yet?
Well, we were thinking Benjamin
if it was a boy.
- Really?
- Hell, no!!
If it's a girl, maybe.
Voight,
- Voight, you want to run over him for me?
- Believe me, sir. We've tried.
Baby,
babe.
What?
A little problem in the nursery.
Alright, so six cameras, right?
One, two, three, four, five, six.
- Why is that too much?
- Yeah, maybe.
Yeah, it's too much.
and I thought that.
They're baby gifts from the guys.
- I'll take them down.
- All we need ..
- Is one baby monitor.
- One baby monitor, right.
Okay,
- And a kevlar mattress.
- and a kevlar mattress..
Come here,
- Unhand me.
- Never
Guess who just got the next week off.
Oh, don't toy with me, young man,
cause there will be consequences.
We're finishing this nursery.
I can't believe it's taking me this long.
Paint samples.
- What?
- Yeah.
Oh, I gotta show you this amazing paint.
- Can I get a shower first?
- Not yet.
-
-- Kanye West‘s new album Life of Pablo
is now available on torrents --
-
--Yeah, UFC 196 too, McGregor finally shut
his big mouth.  STOCKTON Slap! --
Sir, Speaker of the House is waiting,
and the Senate Majority Leader
would like five of your time.
Ahh, hhmm, I'll take him first.
When is Trumbull getting back?
The Vice-President has
three more days of vacation
and insinuated considerable violence
if he heard my voice before then.
Never get between that man and a fish.
- Sir, I got your son on video-chat.
- Excellent.
He had his first date last night.
Mr. President,
you need to take this, sir.
Sir, Speaker of the House?
You need to take this now, sir.
This is the President.
Okay, thank you.
Sources confirmed that
British Prime Minister James Wilson
has died while sleeping in his residence
at 10 Downey Street.
He is believed to have
suffered a heart attack.
Possibly, from complications
after the surgical procedure
to repair his knee a day earlier.
An autopsy has been scheduled
within the next 48 hours.
To determine the actual cause of death.
It's the White House.
It's okay. My mom can come over.
LONDON
-
70 Whitehall
Cabinet Office (UK)
-
The Joint Committee on Security (UK)
take place this Thursday,
the 9th, 4:00 PM, at St. Paul's.
-
Minister of the Interior
Rose Kenter
world leaders, with the lone
exception of the Russian president,
Well, no love lost there.
-
Head of Scotland Yard
Kevin Hazard
private services in St. James's Palace
the morning of
-
Chief Of Counter-intelligence: MI5
John Lancaster
.. Jordan, Saudi Prince Moochrin,
Yes, it's a logistical nightmare.
But let's make sure this runs
without a hitch.
Questions?
And what special requests did
the [ ?? ] circus demand so far?
Dallas Cowboys cheerleaders,
part of the [ ?? ] possibly?
That's a request I can get with [ ?? ]
I'm partial to the Kardashians, myself.
As apparently is Her Majesty.
19 special requests from
12 different countries.
We denied all of them.
Any issues or special concern
with our current assessment?
We all know about he 350 or
so British nationals who
have traveled back and forth
to Syria in the past year,
As we've seen before in Iraq,
and Afghanistan.
Of rising concern is the handful
we believe to be former military.
- Is any of this actionable?
- No.
Very well ..
then we send off our dear friend James,
with dignity.
Give him a ceremony he deserved.
Sir,
- Are you ready for us?
- Yeah, come on in.
Take a seat.
Head of the Secret Service
Lynn Jacobs
What are you guys so damn nervous about?
The Brits are world-class.
We all know their reputation.
But still,
These are the trips I hate.
Last minute, out of the country,
no time to plan.
Are you sure I can't talk you out of this?
Lynn, it's a state funeral.
They're our oldest, strongest ally.
Alright.  I spent half the night
on the line with our advance team.
Metropolitan Police will secure the parameter
of the funeral around St. Paul's Cathedral.
Air Force One will land at
Stansted Airport (London)
On the ground, it's all Mike.
Touch down. Then a 12-minute chopper
ride to Somerset House.
From there we take an armoured vehicle escort
down Sweet Street .. to the Cathedral
You don't seem thrilled.
The British have their hands full.
It's a cluster-fuck .. sir.
Well,
Forty different countries,
with 40 different security teams.
Minimal flexibility on approach routes.
funeral seating, egress.
- Can we make it work?
- Mike?
I always do, sir.
Good.
I know it's not great timing for you, but ..
It's what I do.
Thank you sir.
- There's my man.
- Mr. Vice-President,
- How was your vacation, sir?
- Son,
Do you have any idea, the joy a man feels
pulling a 70-lb king macarel out of the
waters around Jekyll Island?
- No, sir, I don't.
- That makes two of us.
And I'll have to wait till next year to find out.
But, thanks for asking.
- It's beautiful.
- There you go.
- It's pretty.
- I love these things.
Don't worry about a thing, we'll be fine.
- Doris, can we have a minute?
- Sure.
- Oh you meant Leah? right.
- Very funny, Doris.
She tells me not to worry.
It's only three days.
- Yeah,
- And I'm not due for two weeks.
- Walking away, it's not so easy this time.
Hey, I got this.
You go and you do what you have to do, and
we'll be right here when you get back.
Okay? Here, say bye bye to Daddy.
Bye, bye Daddy.
- Bell tolls
- Yeah.
I love you
You better.
Behave.
- Ah, here you go.
- Thank you.
You've been [ ?? ]  hiding lately.
You've been busy nesting?
- Something like that.
- Mm, hmm.
Your idea of nesting being, bullet-proofing
the walls of the nursery?
Now, that is actually a great idea.
Yes,
I'll do it.
Well, that only took two weeks.
Hm, mmm. That's no small thing being a god-mother.
I didn't take your asking lightly.
Oh, I know. You think you can handle it?
Well, I'm competent, brilliant,
[??] beautiful, and really [??] an omelet.
- Really honored.
- Thank you, Lynn.
- Big day ahead?
- Correction, make a day. [??]
Morning.
Thank you.
-
CONTROL ROOM / COMMAND CENTER
Gentlemen, ladies,
Today I need your undivided best.
The most important people in
the world are in our care.
So muck in, and get it right.
Good morning, London.
Stansted Airport
20 miles north of London
:::: 14:30 ::::
Southpaw has landed.
- Agent Banning, John Lancaster, Intel MI-5
- Hey, John.
- Bit early, aren't you?
- Yep.
- We're moving up our schedule.
- I see.
The fewer people know the President's
exact movements, the better.
- Why wasn't I told?
- Nobody was,
that's how you keep it a surprise.
We'll thanks for the help.
-
St. Paul's Cathedral
:::: 15:00 ::::
With security at unprecedented levels,
in anticipation of the funeral,
set to begin just an hour from now
this isn't just the gathering
of the world's most powerful leaders.
It is the most protected event on earth.
Marine Force One, Two, and Three on
final approach to Somerset House.
Marine One cleared for landing.
-
BUCKINGHAM PALACE
German Chancellor
Agnes Bruckner
Clyde, it's okay.
Thank you
Yeah, I understand.
-
Canadian Prime Minister
Robert Bowman
Yeah, I promise.
Everything is going to be fine
- Important matters of state?
That was daughter No 2,
She didn't pass her driving test.
Guess whose fault it is?
-
Japanese Prime Minister
Tsutomu Nakushima
Is it much further?
We're almost there, sir.
I'm sorry but as expected ...
and security measures are very strict.
-
WESMINSTER ABBEY
:::: 15:15 ::::
-
Italian Prime Minister
Antonio Gusto
It's time, Mr. President
The cars are ready?
I hope not too ready!
I say wait 10 minutes?
At least
Southpaw has arrived at destination.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Bugs the shit out of me.
Thank you.
- Sir
- Major Clicker [??]
Thank you very much for your [??].
[ ?? ]
Sorry.
- You know, the funny thing is James always
hated funerals. -- Yeah, don't we all.
Get down!
Move!
- Alright, back to the car.
- Okay.
We've been compromised.
Two in the front.
[??] what you can. [??] on me now!
You okay? -- Yeah,
-- Stay with me, we'll get you out of here.
Duck!
[ ?? ]
Oh, Jesus.  There's been a massive
attack at the Cathedral.
[ ?? ]
- Get me [??]
- Yes sir.
- Where's Emergency Response?
- On their way.
- Voight, where the fuck are you?
- Almost there.
- You okay sir?
- Keep you head down.
Get inside!
Let's go!
Let's get to the chopper.
Dean Court. Black Land Rover.
- I don't believe it. They overran everything.
- Not everything.
Looking for hot extract. Marine One for Southpaw.
Fuck. Calls are down.
Alright, here we go.
- Voight.  - Yo.
-- Ram this guy next to me.
- Copy that.
- Hold him.
Now!
Voight, front brakes now!
Drive.
- Keep pressure on the wound.
- Voight!   fight!  fight!
He's dead, Lynn.
Get down, sir.
Lynn, take that wheel.
Bike on your left.
Not really where you want to be right now.
- Fuck you!
- - Fuck me?
Fuck YOU.
We're almost there sir.
Go, sir, go.
Five world leaders are confirmed dead.
Along with hundreds of innocent civilians
in an attack that has decimated most of the
known landmarks in the British capital.
-
SANA'A
Republic Of YEMEN, (Arab)
Clarkson and Asher are alive.
All the rest are dead.
And I thought it was too much to hope for.
We just changed the world.
Blind be the Sultan.
Fate is smiled on us.
-
CENTRAL LONDON
Railway system
- [??] General ...
- Good evening
We've asked the residents of London
to stay indoors for their own safekeeping,
While the situation remains fluid.
But let there be no doubt,
that every relevant police authority and counter-terrorism
unit is actively at work regaining control of our streets.
And within hours we will secure our city.
-
Breaking News
LONDON ATTACK UK
Jesus, it's not connecting.
- How bad is it?
- It's pretty goddamn bad, sir.
- All lines of communication have been
compromised, both civilian and military. -- Shit.
We've tasked satellites and drones
to get eyes on, but so far nothing.
Sir, the drone is on station.
We have visuals incoming.
Secretary of Defense
Ruth MacMillan
-
National Security Agency / NSA
Deputy Director, Ray Monroe
We have a Quick Reaction Force?
Sicily, two hours out.  -- Speed them up.
And get a line to Downing Street,
and Emergency Command.
Satellite is up.
Marine One is airborne. Southpaw is evaced.
Marine One with Southpaw onboard, airborn.
Prepare Air Force One for departure. Copy.
Copy. Air Force One prepped and ready to go.
It was a trap.
That's an understatement.
Holy shit.  It's one thing to plan
for this. Another to live it.
Alright, well, we're good now.
- It'll be okay.
- Yeah.
We'll be on secure ground in 10 minutes, okay?
There was no chatter on this. None.
Something of this magnitude, it took
years to plan. And we're in a daze.
It's a fucken bloodbath.
- How did they do this, Mike?
- They only have to get it right once.
Today, they got it right way more than that.
- Mayday, mayday, mayday.
- Marine Three is down.
Roof-top three O'clock, you see him?
[ ?? ]
- We're being pinged.
- Stingers.
Deploying flares.
Okay, Stinger gone.
Stinger at three O'clock.
- Marine One out of flares.
- Marine Two, out of flares.
- Marine Two, prepare for sacrificing.
- Copy.
Marine Two is down.
It's a lock on.
Mr. President we're going to take a hit.
Brace for impact.
Our families, remotely from the sky.
Your time .. is over.
We're bringing the war, to you.
Make no mistake.
This is the day,
when your world changes forever.
- Jesus. -- This is all over social media too.
Everybody in the world has seen this.
Aamir Bakawi.
Number six on the 10 list.
This man is responsible for
more deaths than the Plague.
Sells arms to every failed state in the world.
Has a vast array of connections,
terrorists, mercenaries, corporations,
- Mr. Vice-President, it's Barkawi.
- Put him through.
Thought you might take my call.
You understand if I make it difficult to track.
You have me at somewhat of a loss.
I thought you would've learned a lesson
by now, about crawling out of your hole.
- I've never lifted a finger against you.
- You arm those who have.
I sold triggers, Mr. Trumbull.
Just like you.
What do you want?
Your President.
You can end this right now.
- Just hand him over.
- That's not going to happen.
Then every death from this moment
forward, will be on your head.
Barkawi, sells arms to dummy companies.
Some of them probably in London.
Find a connection to him.
He's probably been planning this for
years. Everybody makes a mistake.
We have to find him before
he finds the President.
Let's get to it.
- Mike is a bully?
- Yeah.
Not exactly standard police issue.
Really?
Oh, my god.
- I've never seen a man suffocate before.
- I didn't have a knife.
Got  more ammunition than
the entire US Army.
How can they pull something like this off.
Gots to be somebody on the inside.
Yeah, looks like it.
These aren't you typical hill-trained
hillbillies. These guys are pros.
- We should go for the Embassy.
- They'll be expecting that.
There's a MI-6 safehouse near here.
I have a contact there.
We go there, we get geared up, and get an extraction.
- Do you trust them? -- Yeah.
The fact is, every single one of these guys
is a terrorist asshole. Until proven otherwise.
The only person you trust right now,
is me, okay?
Come on, let's go.
- Gotta get underground.
- These guys are everywhere.
Let's go.
Stay here. I'll be back.
Raza ..
Raza
Here ..
We can do easy, or the hard way.
Raza. Answer me, brother.
Raza's not feeling too well at the moment.
He's a little bit fucked up.
Hey, you. What's this dick guy's name?
- This is Kamra. Who is this?
- Hey, Cameron. [sic]
- My name is Mike Banning.
- You are the one with the President.
Bingo. So why don't you boys pack up your shit and head
back to Fuckeninstan or wherever it is you're from.
You should've let us kill him quickly.
Because now, we're going to kill him slowly.
And stream it live. For the whole world to see.
Can you hear me, Mr. President?
- Tell him,
- Yeah, he can hear you.
And here's something I want you hear first.
That's the sound of your brother dying. Yeah.
Not much of a talker, that one.
But I bet one of your men will.
I'll see you soon, Cameron [sic]
- Was that really necessary?
- No.
The Brits are compromised.
The police for sure.
Who do you trust?
We can also assume all communications
are compromised.
Anything that isn't secured,
could get into the wrong hands, sir.
- And Banning would know that too.
- So how could he even reach out for help?
There, freeze that. Sir,
- Is Banning left-handed?
- No, right-handed.
Okay, well, the President doesn't move
without a drone or satellite over his head.
- Banning knows that.
- That's his left hand.
- Southpaw .. six.
- Shorthand for MI-6.
Look for any MI-6 location in that are.
- Yes, sir.
- Alright, Banning.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- [ ?? ] , bad choice.
- Hah,
Sit down, take deep breaths.
How many you think died?
I don't know .. A lot.
All those innocent people.
Dead ... Because of me.
No. Not because of you. Because of them.
They tried to kill you, sir.
And they killed all these people, just
to make everyone else more afraid.
Well, fuck that.
Fuck them.
Mike ..
You don't let them take me.
- I'm not going to.
- You need to do it.
If it comes to it.  If it's going south.
If it comes to it, I want you to kill me.
That' an order.
I will not be prosecuted for propaganda.
As my son and the American people see me on
fucken YouTube for the rest of their lives.
.. Okay.
- Vice President Trumbull is among us, sir.
- Inspector.
I'm afraid our .. news isn't promising.
Our dearly departed Prime Minister
James Wilson was assassinated.
Poison in his anesthesia, and his doctor's
body found dumped about an hour ago.
State funeral ..
Must-attend event for western leaders.
Each one a target.
Goddamn.
And we walked right into it.
And all dead. By your men and ours.
What's happening on the ground?
The terrorists have killed 19 first-
responders. We've another 30 unaccounted for.
They're impersonating us. Our people
are walking right into ambushes.
Say the word and we go in.
But make no mistake.  We risk turning
London into another Fallujah.
That's the last thing we need.
The President in the middle of an urban battle.
Or the citizens of London.
Or you're just as likely to take out
half the Metropolitan Police Force,
Unless you can tell me how you can tell the
difference between the good guys and the bad guys.
- We're have to stand down our Emergency Services.
- Surrender London?
He's right.
Take out all legitimate personnel.
Anyone that remains .. is a terrorist.
Look, the sooner we end this,
The more chance there is of stopping
London becoming a complete warzone.
Well, how do we get the
word out to our people?
[??] system.
We [??] sound that, people know to
stay secure in their place, then ...
You have the military sweep in.
door-to-door, if necessary.
Clear these bastards out.
- Good evening.
- Is Auntie M in?
Put that away.
- Are you who I think you are?
- Unfortunately
What a pleasure this is, two handsome men
visiting me on such a lovely evening.
- Long time, Jackson. -- Eh, not long enough.
-- Mr. President.
Sir,
- Jaqueline, MI-6 finest.  Don't fuck with her.
- Hello.
The phones are down.  That said,
It did allow us to pick up this..
Mr. President, Banning ..
I hope this finds you well.
Mike, we got your message.
And I'm sure you don't know
who you can trust,
and all prior authentications
may be compromised.
So .. I offer you this,
Do you have any idea the joy a man experiences pulling a
70-lb King Mackerel out of the waters around Jekyll Island?
That's him.
a Delta Team has been clandestinely inserted.
By now they should en route to your position.
They'll take you to the US Embassy, where an armored
convoy stands by to get you out of SAM range.
- And on to a military train.
- Thank god.
- Let's get us out of here.
- Alright, sir.  So who's behind all this?
Aamir Bakawi.
Bakawi provides armaments.
He's a fucken criminal.
Shielded by governments.
Mike, there was a drone strike, to get him.
Two years ago, authorized by the G8.
So we took a shot.
He survived
We didn't know his family was there.
His daughter was killed.
Well, he certainly got his revenge.
- Civilians?
- Well, they're not being targeted specifically, but ..
- Collateral damage?
- Yeah, quite a lot, I'm afraid.
[??] targeting. No official support from
any countries Barkawi shows, but..
Didn't have any problems finding the creeps today,
United Nations all with blood on their hands. [??]
- Who's on the inside? There's gotta be somebody.
- Yeah, you're right.
They've infiltrated our CCTV system.
And they've copied the Wi-Fi network. [??]
- Yeah, but who?
- I don't know.
Mike ..
if you hadn't move our schedule up.
- Here you go sir, get this in you.
- Thanks.
- I don't know about you, but I'm thirsty as fuck.
- Yeah.
- How're you doing?
- I was thinking about my son.
He sends me these jokes every day.
It's kind of our, our thing.
A little off-color.
His mother wouldn't approve.
I tell you something Mike, These little
messages I get from him everyday,
They mean everything, you'll see.
Most important thing, never criticize.
Always encourage.
You just want them to be passionate.
That's what I always tell my son.
Find something you care about, and care deeply.
That and the Golden Rule.
Treat others as you like to be treated.
- That's it?
- Yeah, basically.
What about all the other stuff.
Sleeping, eating, electrical outlets,
diapers, stairs, and ...
That stuff takes care of itself.
- Really?
- No, hah ha, you'll figure it out.
Okay, your dates have arrived.
That's under construction.
No one lives or works there.
- That's why this is particularly interesting.
- I had my NSA analysts take a peek at the power usage ..
Through the roof the last three weeks.
pretty odd, considering no one
lives or works there.
Central London.
Right under our bloody noses.
Tell the SAS that we're going
to make a house call.
Mike,
[??] to your right.
Left.
There's no way to dress this up, sir.
It isn't good.
Could be worse. Could be [??]
Atta boy.  Don't stop for anyone.
- Are we clear?
- Yeah, ha hah. We fucken made it.
Ha ha, we did.
Where is he?
Where the fuck?  Where is he?
Were did they take him?
[??] UNINTELLIGIBLE [??]
Back off, take it easy, take it easy!
You've gotta be Banning.
(introduces himself),
Captain Tutu, SAS [??]
President Asher has just been taken.
And these assholes intend
to publicly execute him.
We know, at 8:00 PM.
It's all over the internet.
- We'll take care of that.  Move out!
- Hey, hey, wait.
[??] you come this with me.
How many times you've saved this man's ass?
Now, I'm going to go get him.
And you can kill me,
Or you can come with me.
But I ain't going to go any other way.
After you.
- CCTV is back up.
- What did you do?
Disable the authorization code
that shut down the CCTV system.
[??]
Wait ..
What authorization code?
:::: 19:50 ::::
You should be thankful.
How many men get to experience
their death witnessed by billions .. live?
You are going to go down in history.
I'm not the only that's going
to die today, Kamran.
- Post Command.
- Banning.
Mike Banning? Chief Inspector Hazard,
Scotland Yard. Hold your position.
- Our military will be on your location in 20 minutes.
- No sir.
- The President's going to be dead in 10.
- You don't understand,
We have NSA imagery of where you're going.
It's their base of operations.
There are nealy a 100 terrorists in there.
Yeah, well.
They should have brought more men.
- Things are ready to get sporty.
- Just watch your balls.
Will do.
RPG!
[??]
Yeah, they kill the President
the second we try it.
Alright call Fox Command .. [??] the utilities here.. [??]
[??]
- The generator? -- Yeah
- Let's pull out the plug. -- Yeah.
- What happened?
- The power supply was just cut.
Get the emergency generators up.
Come on!
Banning, this is what we got.
This is a three-story building..
The entry point is here.  There are
two stairwells. One here, and one here.
We believe the President is being held
in this room, on the second floor.
Hold your position. I need you to hit
this building with everything you got.
- You got it.
- Keep them busy. I'll sneak inside.
Take that. Do not press that
button till I tell you.
- Are you fucken crazy?
- Yeah. Wish me luck.
:::: 19:55 ::::
They are almost here.
Why don't you just kill him now?
No!
The whole world needs to see this.
Hear that, Kamran?
That's the sound of inevitability.
I am going to kill you live. But that doesn't
mean you can't suffer privately first.
Look at me!
I held my sister as she died in my arms.
You're the monsters, Mr. President.
It won't justify your insanity
to make you better about yourself.
Shoot him!
:::: 19:57 ::::
Almost, waiting for
the internet connection.
Technology, only as good as
the dumbshits that are using it.
- How long?
- Seconds.
- We are live now.
- Okay.
Say hello to the world, Mr. President.
:::: 20:00 ::::
Any last words, Mr. President?
I do solemnly swear, that I will faithfully execute
the office of the President of the United States.
Son of a bitch.
.. the United States.
And to the best of my ability
preserve, protect, and defend ..
Oh, my god.
I'm not watching this.
You know what you guys don't get:
We're not a fucken [??],
we're not a fucken flag,
we're not just one man...
And assholes like you, have been trying
to kill us for a long fucken time..
But you know what,
A thousand years from now..
We'll still fucken be here.
Mike! Grenade!
- What took you so long?
- Sorry, I had a couple of errands to run.
Shit, does this fucker ever die?
Alright, we gotta get out of here,
You good?
Go! Move, move, move!
Mike!  Come on!
I'm out.
I'm out too.
Come in!  We're trapped!
I repeat we are trapped.
- Blow it!
Are you insane?  I can't [??] ..
You know that.
We're not gonna get out of here
unless you do!
Huxley! Now, godammit!
Go, go, go!
Banning, Banning, call me.
- Has anyone find any sign?
- Nothing, over.
Well, okay. Stay sharp. Keep looking.
[??]
No sign of the President yet.
- Fox Command?
- Find them?
The President is alive.
I have to tell you.
I fucken hate funerals.
Sir, I got you, Mr. President.
- Is that all they got?
- Yeah, it looks like it.
Lieutenant,
this could be missing link .. to Barkawi
Okay, I'll get this to my folks,
right away.
Next time I tell you to blow it,
.. just blow it.
- Good job, Lieutenant.
- You too, Banning.
Safe journey home.
If that's possible for you.
Next time, you want to leave town after betraying
your country, how about you steal a car,
[??] you can get for the vehicle.
Perhaps you can [??] GPS.
Because that just takes all the fun out of it.
You forgot to delete you access logs.
You authorization code is there,
bright as day.
The security cameras
showing you logging on.
Get on the floor.
Do I have to tell you, this is the most
dangerous time since the Great War.
We're cutting budgets while
the barbarians are at the gate.
The system's failing us, Jax, it's broken.
You know it as well as I do.
- Things have to change
- So you think you would teach us all a lesson?
That and 20 Million Euros.
Come with me, Jax.
Get on the fucken floor.
Don't ..
Don't.
Get on the floor.
Get on the floor, John.
Get on the fucken floor!
[Two gun shots, DOUBLE TAP.]
Sir?
phone call for you.
Kamran?
Mr. Barkawi?
I thought you'd take my call.
You see this war ..
this war has just started.
You think it's over?
I dedicating my life to your end.
This war will not end.
Maybe you should look out your window.
[ JET FIGHTER RADIO-CHATTER ]
[ CLEAR TO PROCEED ]
[ GROUND ASSETS CONFIRMED.
TARGET CLEAR OF CIVILIAN PERSONS ]
Two weeks after the devastating
attacks on the British capital,
A new government has been installed,
and the city, has begun to rebuild.
In the words of Prime Minister Clarkson:
"London may have fallen, but it has
always endured, and will rise again."
So Daddy is going to take some
more time off, isn't that cool?
Yeah, maybe it's the new me.
He says he reckons I've earned a few
days off. Thanks to you, little one.
I wonder what you're going to
be passionate about, Matt?
- (LETTER)
[LETTER]  Subject: RESIGNATION    Dear Sir:
With great sadness I inform officially
Far too many people died for no good reason.
There are those that who will say
that this would never have happened
if we would just mind our own business.
- (LETTER)
[LETTER] resign of the US Secret Service,
an honor and privilege
But the worst option, is to do nothing.
Finally,
We owe to our children, and to their
children, to engage in the world.
-
/DELETE?/  --   /SAVE?/   --   /SEND?/
(BUTTONS)
-
[ DELETE ]
(BUTTONS)