Prison Heat
Student trip over.
I'm ready for the real fun.
What do you mean?
- So naive, Bonnie.
I have a great idea.
Let's go to Turkey.
Only
the other side of the border.
Yeah, let's do it.
I do not think that's a good idea.
- Do not you have fun?
OK, I will.
My parents would die if they knew I was going
in Turkey.
Will die when
learn what you do in Turkey.
Bonnie, you coming?
Okay, okay, I will.
Propose a toast: To Istanbul!
I'm tired of school nonsense.
Need to relax a little.
Sing us a song, Michelle?
- Are you serious?
Well, just take the guitar.
- Play something.
Sing girls.
It will pillows charts.
- And how!
Soon you will reach the border?
- I think so.
Get ready for a great trip.
A Turkish guys  beautiful you are?
- Prepare passports girls.
Pull to the side out of her car.
- Yes.
Your passports please.
Is this you?
- I lost 14 kg.
Nice is .
- Do not you dare to flirt.
He does not speak English.
Hello. Welcome to Turkey.
Where are you from?
- From the United States.
Americans? Very nice.
And where are you going?
- Tell him to throw away...
On a school trip we are.
- Four?
Other left.
- What is your name?
Colleen Dorothy.
I - mentor.
My name is Nadir.
I am a senior officer here.
Your car?
- No, hired in January
Where?
- Thessaloniki.
Come with me, please.
- I'm coming with you...
You stay here.
What do you know about that?
- What is it?
Cocaine  Miss Dorothy cocaine.
- It's not ours.
Must have been
previously in the car.
For me you idiot?
- I'm telling you the truth!
'll See about that. Come on.
What are you doing?
Let me out!
Where our water
bastards?
Saladin Bey send you fresh meat.
Do not forget about your friends.
Surely, surely.
Saladin Bey told me to undress.
Why is this?
You can hide drugs.
I have to search it thoroughly.
I want to call the embassy.
- Located in Istanbul.
I want to contact them.
We are American citizens.
We have rights.
From now on you have only those rights
that I give you. You have to search you.
If you touch it with your finger...
Wait!
Better do what he says
.
Stand in line, please.
Off your clothes.
Bra too.
Immediately remove any clothing.
Undress!
Can I help?
Now check
hiding something, which is not visible.
What was that?
Failed  excursion.
- I did not want to go with you.
Now we are not listening to Bonnie.
Calm. I'll think of something.
You can sit there.
Hi, I'm - May.
Beds are available.
Lie  there?
I - Colleen, and that her Audrey Michelle.
- Hi.
This is my pet.
Full of lice. And you will be the same after
days.
Spent many wet winters.
What is this?
- Turn off the lights at 22:00.
I can not believe it.
Did you sleep well?
- Ate me alive.
Why have you left the earrings?
I do not know.
Maybe because they are small.
Why keep us here?
I want to go home.
Nobody knows where we are.
- Leave tales. Will not help.
See how hungry look.
- What kind of nonsense?
I wish one of us.
Demonstration is over, come on.
Where were you?
- Late.
I hope Pakiz still
will give us milk.
Pakiz exception
just because your first day here.
No longer be late.
This is a powder. If you want real,
whisper in my ear.
What did he mean?
If you want something to be delivered,
cigarettes, coffee, drugs, or soap...
... Turn to Pakiz.
Just ready money.
It - God Is, or what?
- Prisoner sentenced to life.
Sale lot.
- They permit this...?!
Saladin.
It gets most of the profits.
Did it something like a mini boss.
No trust her.
I have to do something.
I think our friend from the bathroom
has already made his choice.
Awesome. But not enough.
Coming.
Do you want coffee?
What is your problem?
I'll kill you!
Uber them.
Who is in charge here?
- You.
Do not forget.
You... then in my office.
All. Spread out.
Will be even more if
brightened Sheikh.
It's okay.
Personally checked them.
All  aware.
Almost ready.
We should be careful, make sure
no one knows where they are.
Trust me.
You, you tell her you.
Follow me.
No! No!
Let me out!
Yes.
Come on, come on.
Seat. Is everything okay?
- Yes.
Do you like my bag?
- Very nice.
Skin is soft as a woman's breast.
Feel January
Miss Dorothy, drug smuggling -
is a very serious accusation.
Did not know
that car was drugs.
This court will decide.
This will be fair.
And when?
I do not know.
Court crowded.
Can I call you?
Nobody knows we're here.
You can write letters.
Pakiz will send them.
What about the lawyer?
- When the time comes.
And you call this justice?
- Do not try my patience.
Really? When it's my time?
You can return
with friends.
Miss Dorothy?
Your friend  considered a guide.
Keep them in the right direction.
Otherwise,
'll deal with you. Is that clear?
And remember, Miss Dorothy,
that my door is always open for you.
Move!
Thank you. Until recently.
- Next time will be better.
Follow them.
Can we call someone?
- No. We can write letters.
Letters? I think I'll stay
for a very long time here.
This is not so bad.
- What else but write.
We can not even call
the American Embassy.
Michelle is right.
It is important to think positively.
Right?
- Exactly.
- Yes, of course.
Let's write everything we know.
- And what will pay for postage?
They took all my money.
- Wait a minute.
What is she doing there?
- I'll find out.
I think you'll get
few stamps.
Enter.
How many letters.
- These are the cards.
For our friends who saw
what a beautiful place we live.
Joker.
- Simply send Pakiz.
Let Sultan got my little daughter,
if not let them in the afternoon.
Let your husband ran off with another woman,
if not send them in the afternoon.
He already escaped.
- Who would have doubted.
Here it is!
- Catch it!
Many are quick!
May, let me help you.
No, thank you.
- But you do not feel good.
As it is, without need to wash my
.
Are you sure?
- Yes.
I'll go with you.
- It's all right. Bonnie Michelle her there.
This soap smells.
Once was white.
- What is "white"?
Like the color of your ass.
What do you want?
- Bonnie knows what.
We can make it mild or harsh.
I think you have to be rude.
What are you doing?
Away!
She started!
- She tried to rape her!
I am not guilty.
- Shut up!
Who is in charge here,
Miss Burns?
Who is the principal?
Stop!
For you there God?
Here I am God.
In isolation.
- What? Let me out!
Colleen...
- Where are you taking me?
Okay?
and eat.
There are many worm.
No, thank you.
Are you sure
that said "insulator"?
May, what is it?
- Cell horror.
My fault.
- Bonnie, no one will fault, shut up.
Okay?
- It's just a cough.
'll Hurt for a while.
- A little.
How can we help Colleen?
- Not at all, we can only wait.
Pigs.
- Hey, you!
I?
You... come with me.
Now!
Bonnie !
- Keep working.
Come here.
Seat.
Are you afraid of me?
No sense.
I want to be your friend.
You have a very innocent face. And it
a problem in a place like this.
I do not know.
You, of course, regret
that make trouble.
Colleen tells me not to worry about it.
Yes, because of you, she died in solitary.
Must be kidding.
However...
... I can release tomorrow
if...
Do not worry,
I keep my promises.
Let me out!
Do not you want to call someone?
- We just wrote letters.
Throw them in the trash.
- I do not understand?
Now listen to me carefully.
Taken me a year ago
the same border as you.
Since then here?
- I've been here a month.
Saladin  sell me the trader who holds
brothel.
This is the brand of Saladin.
And you will do the same.
What?
At 30 am
and I look 60.
'll Fuck in all holes.
After months will be filled with
diseases.
If after six months you die,
will kill you, it will find new.
Lord. What to do?
- Escape.
Can kill you, but it's better than
to stay here.
Someone is coming.
Remember what I told you.
- Sure.
Susan. My name is Susan Allen.
I just want to remember me.
- I will not forget.
How nice to see you!
What was there?
I was with a woman who told me
...
... get away from here
as soon as possible.
Colleen  I want to go home.
Seems that it is so far.
What happened to you?
- Nothing.
Tell me.
Where are you going?
- With the new girlfriend.
How touching.
- Leave us alone!
And you better sleep with your eyes open
.
No need.
I feel you stink.
I'm tired of harassing us!
When you know a knife that she threw away?
- Yes.
Let's see how good it is.
Where are you going?
- To see Elena.
Ask her what she wants.
- What do you want?
A personal matter.
- More personal.
You have two minutes.
- Is it private?
Well?
- Stay away from my friends.
And  came here to tell me this?
- Protect your interests.
What do you mean by that?
- I have relations to Bonnie.
General.
- You mean...
I'd rather show you.
- What do you Think?
Once you taking a shower at night?
- This would be convincing.
Hot water her slippery foam.
I'll be in the bathroom at midnight.
My fault.
- Lord, Bonnie, stop.
True.
- Elena will bother us.
I can not bear it.
- I have a bad feeling about this.
You've always had bad Audrey.
- It's a gift.
If you think  bad,
it happens. You're ready.
What do you think?
- I have to work.
So, you decided to join?
- Yes. Give me the soap.
Nice.
Wait. Now it's my turn.
Very sharp,
and I am very nervous.
Do not pull her not yell.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
I'll ask a few questions.
Nodded "Yes" or
back to "No".
If you start shaking your head a lot,
then she'll slit your throat.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
Thou her your girlfriend lesbian
will leave us alone. Right?
And  no longer worry
none of us. Right?
Doing
will gut you.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
When he touched me, I felt like
vomit.
I want to
feel the same way.
Eat it  so
if it was chocolate.
Eat! Suck!
Can I help?
Now clean it from inside.
May, you better're familiar with these
who sell them in the brothel.
Hey, Pakiz why Elena
did not come to breakfast?
Usually fails.
She said her stomach hurt.
I heard that it moves away from the toilet.
- Really? - Yes.
Tell me about this merchant, May.
What do others say?
- They do not know anything.
I do not know.
- Really?
Or are you afraid to talk?
Where are you going, Bonnie?
- In the bathroom.
I'm coming with you.
- No. Stay here, please.
Miss Child?
I'm glad you came.
Unbuttoned shirt.
- No.
Please. I do not want.
Take off, please.
- No.
Unbuttoned shirt.
Strip.
Slow.
Do it slowly.
Sit, May.
Pakiz!
Do not worry. Pretends
to be absent from work.
Pretending you?
Gotta get her to the infirmary.
No need.
I just want to lay down.
Marcy, take January
- OK.
Give me your hand.
Ready ? One, two, three! Case.
Easy.
Do not worry about it.
I will not die from this.
Can not bathe now.
- My friend is inside.
'll Bathe later.
Very soon, you will be justified.
Bonnie  specialties of Saladin.
What do you mean, Pakiz?
- Do not you know?
Well blather. Right?
- You.
Girlfriend fuck with him.
- What?
Why do you think they release from solitary
?
What? Get out!
- You've got a lot of work!
Everything will be fine.
Tried to commit suicide.
If I had not gone...
okay, honey?
There are no grounds for December
commit suicide.
Do you need help?
- Alone we can do.
Son of a bitch.
Come on, Bonnie.
If you do not run in the near future,
Bonnie die.
If your cellmate was right,
then us will be the same.
Gotta get out of here.
- Yes, but how?
I think I may die.
I want to talk to Colleen.
- I will come.
We'll take you to the infirmary.
- No. I prefer to die here.
This is the key to the cell.
I keep it for many years.
Dreaming of escape,
but it was just a dream.
Take advantage .
Take the girls here.
I want to rest.
Fighting for his life
to die in prison.
She was not alone.
We were with her.
Bonnie, what is it?
I wanted to go for her.
Do not say that.
Need to get into his office.
How do you do it?
Invent something.
Leaving. Will meet with the mediator.
- OK.
Did it?
- Enough to tie this beast.
I hope that tomorrow will be
in Thessaloniki.
I think it will work.
- I'll find out.
I'm ready.
- Go.
Where are you going?
- We want to leave them in place.
Old vomited on the floor,
and must be cleaned.
Look who's here.
Come on, honey.
Want?
- Yes.
Come to us.
You're such a big boy.
- I - a little child.
Car keys!
Child wants milk.
- Well, my mom would give milk.
What are you doing. Silly boy.
I have to tie.
Spank him good.
Naughty boy.
Should go.
- Wait. To play more.
What your man! Maybe tomorrow.
- Will do as you say. Bye.
Guards at the gate of her parking
can bribe.
But car keys
in office Saladin.
Our personal matters too.
Can reveal the truth about this place.
Too dangerous to go there.
- I've already been.
You will not enter. He'll let me.
- What?
I'm going with him.
While he fucks me,
you will attack.
Lord, Bonnie...
- We have no choice.
Colleen.
- How did it go?
Mediator told me that now wants
$ 100 200 it when out.
We do not have any money.
I have only $ 10.
What do we do?
- I'll find the money.
How?
- From our friend Pakiz.
So what happened?
- I'll be waiting for me at 14:30.
So far so good.
Give me the knife her napkin.
I'll find the money.
What are you doing, Colleen?
- Monthly.
Call security.
Security?
Look. Came to her.
Monthly. Do you understand?
- What?
Need it "pads".
- Yeah, "pads".
Pakiz. Faster!
Not permitted Pakiz.
Go money.
Enough?
- Yes.
Plan "B" work.
Give me your hairpin.
Can you open it?
- It's in my genes.
My uncle was a mechanic.
- Hurry. Pakiz come.
One second.
Done!
See there, I from that country.
Not very messy.
No need to know that we were here.
Look!
It is stupefying.
Got money?
- Yes, very much. One more thing.
Gun ?
In jail?
Did not you say that your uncle was also a gunsmith?
- My father taught me to use a weapon.
What do we do?
Give the rope!
Hey, it's your turn.
- I'm sorry, honey.
What is it?
Zamechta or what?
Yes. I have a dream, an idea.
For what?
- Forget it.
What do we do now?
If you run, we will issue.
You have to kill her.
- You must be joking.
We have no choice.
Although... what did you do with sleeping pills?
Choose. Or will drink pills
or I'll kill you.
'll Drink pills? Excellent.
Lord! Fainted!
What are you doing?
- So does my dog's vet.
Will now sleep until Tuesday.
Thanks for the watch.
Almost 14:30. We have half an hour,
to bribe one of the guards.
Ready?
- Yes.
Ready .
- Let's do it.
He's waiting.
We will come in a few minutes.
Be careful.
Log.
Mr. Child, late.
Waiting for you, come.
This is my friend, Achim.
It is Beirut.
Nice to meet you.
- Sit.
Do you want a glass of whiskey?
- No, thank you.
Miss Child, I want to show you something.
I found this in his office.
It belongs to your girlfriends.
What have conceived,
tell me about it.
Nothing to say?
Let's see.
How are soft.
As my purse.
Do you want this?
Then speak.
- I have nothing to say!
Yours.
Go to  tricks.
- I hope that the same guard.
We will be here.
This is another guard.
- Do not stop.
Where are you going?
- Open, it will show.
Do not resist.
- Stop!
You took me for a fool?
Answer! Now!
Shut up, fat boy.
How do you know?
- I know all what's going on.
Need my help.
Do not pull or
get a ticket to heaven.
We have to hurry.
Do not sleep.
What's taking so long?
Open your mouth, asshole.
Close his mouth!
God's ways are mysterious.
To get out.
What the hell?
- She saved our lives!
Colleen, I also want her to
out of here. Trust me.
Well, it's time to kick someone's ass
.
Damn!
- Take care of them.
Give the rope!
Release me!
- Glad you're alive.
Run, run!
Lord shall not escape.
Tie him until he woke up.
- We're out of pills.
I will cut his throat.
- Do not kill him.
Who is this?
- Vendor. He came to take us.
Clock Pakiz behind!
- Guard waiting.
Get out.
- A tight tie.
Come on, Helen!
I should kill you.
Clear.
Colleen forgot something. I'll catch up.
- Bonnie, where...
. I'll wait.
- I'll be late!
Go. Wait for me in the car.
Here's the keys.
Some like soft bags.
I personally like portfolios.
- Not...
How are you?
- Six.
said it would be five.
- We have the money.
Wait.
Wait here.
Do not kill me!
- Give me back my money.
Let's go.
Too late!
My God!
We need to find out.
They remained there, and we are here.
No way.
- It's our only chance.
Help me.
- Come on.
I can not come.
What do we do now?
- I need to remove it.
Do you know how to use it?
- Yes.
Cover me, but shoot only
if necessary.
Guard kill them!
- No, no.
Where is Elena?
- Dead.
Why come back?
- He had lost it.
So back because the earrings?
- Yes, its a few more little things.
Bend over!
We are free!
Did it!