TONI (VOICEOVER):
Louisiana's always
been known for its good old
boy background politics.
I just never thought I'd
get tangled up in it.
Those press buzzard's
gotten more attention
than a two-headed dog.
I started out in Shreveport,
Louisiana, living
in a row of houses that
all looked the same.
It was across the street
from the rail road,
because Daddy worked for the
Kansas City Southern Railways.
After momma died, daddy
and my new step momma
began to take it out on me.
So I left.
I was only 12.
Aunt Emma took me
in for a spell 'til.
Charlotte's became my new home.
I knew the one thing I had
going for me was my looks.
I came in through the back
door as Annie B. McQuiston.
But when I left in '39, it
was through the front door
as Toni Jo Henry.
[lively chatter]
Miss Charlotte ran the
place, better known
as Charlotte's, the finest
brothel in Shreveport.
Miss Charlotte charmed
lawyers and the police
in her back pocket by offering
her services for free.
I never did learn
to play that piano,
but I sure loved
the sound of it.
I dreamt for hours of a
better life, a different life.
I heard you lost
another fight cowboy.
Yeah?
Mm.
Well, you should
see the other guy.
Mm.
Besides, it's worth it if the
loser's purse gets me here.
TONI (VOICEOVER): Every
little girl dreams
of her knight in shining armor.
And I was no different.
I just don't want to mess
up that pretty face of yours.
Ladies, it's criminal.
But I have got to
get some sleep.
Goodnight.
Goodnight cowboy.
Maybe I'll come cheer for
you on Saturday afternoon.
You think Miss Charlotte
will give us the time off?
No.
Don't you never
mind him, Toni Jo.
You sure know how to make
a man feel like a man.
Mr. Dupre is waiting for you.
Just keep him happy.
I just need to freshen up.
Yeah, sure.
[gasp]
Ah!
[grunt]
Oh!
Ah!
Oh.
So how long have
you been fighting?
Since I was born.
Six older brothers, you get
plenty of sparring partners.
That's a premium
right hook you got.
One of the many tricks I
learned from the old man.
Great role model.
Yeah.
I had one of those too.
Well, I better get back.
Miss Charlotte will
be looking for me.
I'd like to see you again.
Well, you know where
Miss Charlotte's is.
I meant away from there.
Like where?
What do you want?
Just some dinner together.
Seems like you're looking for
someone a little more polished.
Well, who ain't?
But this point, I'd settle
or just a good looking cowboy
dude.
Lookie here, lookie here.
Hey now, I'm a paying customer.
Put that down Toni Jo!
Put it down.
I'll fix you up Mr. Johnston.
Ain't no hog tie.
Well, all right.
[inaudible]?
Come over here.
[giggling]
(WHISPERING) Why don't
we go on upstairs?
[laughing]
[music playing]
[cheering]
You did good up there.
COWBOY: Tonight at least.
Usually, I end up with a
face full of hamburger.
[laughing]
Where's Toni Jo?
Oh, she's upstairs.
And she's alone cowboy.
You sure have been taken up
all Toni Jo's time lately.
And I pay for it, don't I?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Don't!
I need that.
You're a lying drug addict.
Please!
What's it going to be?
Me or this dope
monkey on your bed?
But I need it.
I need it!
You choose.
You don't understand!
I need it!
Ah!
I can't!
No!
Give it to me.
Give it.
Give it to me!
Ah!
Last chance.
You choose.
[crying]
You don't have to
do it on your own.
[crying]
Get away from me!
No!
I want momma!
Your momma's dead.
She can't help you
now, lazy brat.
Oh, where are you going?
Huh?
"Sorry!"
(MOCKINGLY) I'm sorry.
That's about the first
damn thing you said right.
Clean up this Pigs-TY!
No!
Come back here!
Don't let me [inaudible]!
Come back!
Come back here!
No!
I'm not going back
in there again!
Don't go acting all
innocent with me.
You're going to
service these men.
Come on!
(CRYING) I don't
have to listen to you!
Do like the good book says,
honor thy father and mother.
And I'm your momma now
little miss big mouth,
so you listen to me.
Now get!
You're doing great.
You're through the worst of it.
Oh, I'm just so sorry your
momma went and died on you.
I'll be real good.
I'll clean the house real good,
and I'll fix my own dinner.
Is Bertha treating
you right darling?
Those men smell
[inaudible] Emma.
Please don't make
me go back home!
Oh, it's all right child.
You just say your prayers.
You'll see.
It's going to be OK.
Just sleep now.
(WHISPERING) Shh.
Sleep baby.
Just sleep.
Slow down honey.
You're going to
make yourself sick.
Ain't nothing in
the world that's
going to stop me from
eating right now.
[laughing]
Except maybe that.
Let's do something
really crazy.
Like what?
Let's get hitched.
What?
COWBOY: I want to do
right by you, Mrs. Henry.
Toni Jo Henry.
It has a nice ring to it.
Wait 'til the girl's here.
They're going to be so jealous.
And you're never going to set
foot in Miss Charlotte's again.
You hear me?
Cowboy, don't be so silly.
There could never
be anyone but you.
All right.
Bring it in.
I don't have to tell you
boys how important this here
fight is.
The winners gets to go to
Beaumont for a whole series
of fights with the big boys.
Now, I want a clean, fair fight.
Got it?
All right.
Get in your corners.
Let's do it.
[bell]
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
I can't believe
we're going to Texas!
I'm not so sure
that's a good thing.
Well, you don't have a hair
on your ass if you don't go.
[laughs]
Eh, thing is I got in a
little trouble in Texas.
What's all the trouble?
COWBOY: No big deal really.
It happened so
long ago, probably
nobody even remembers it.
Besides, we need the money.
TONI: Let's just hope no
one remembers it, dumb ass.
I guess the honeymoon's over.
Well, I don't recall
ever having one.
You OK?
Well then, Texas
will be our honeymoon.
I'll make sure it's
worth the Wait.
Well, ain't you a
sight for sore eyes.
When'd they let you out?
Which time?
Ain't you going to introduce me?
This is my Wife, Toni Jo.
Toni Jo, this is Arkie.
What kind of a name is Arkie?
I never thought
I'd see you ever
settle down with just one gal.
Well, it just goes
to show you, I guess.
Now listen, friend, I'll keep
your bride company tomorrow
while you fight,
give her a shoulder
to cry on when you lose.
Eh... never could take a joke.
[laughing]
It seems to me I got your ass
out of more than a few scrapes.
Sure you did.
Claude ever tell you
about that time...
Shut up Arkie.
Yeah.
Too bad about Buck.
Let's go [inaudible].
See you around Arkie.
All's I'm saying is
Bonnie and Clyde should
have been treated that way.
Got a light?
The Bonnie and Clyde?
Ah... you knew them?
The very ones, little lady.
You never told her
about the Barrows?
We've come here to check
out the competition,
not shoot the breeze.
No, I've got something
I've got to do anyway.
I'll see you around cowboy.
By the way, no hard feelings
about screwing me over
on that last job, huh?
[laughing]
[bell]
Oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Uh.
[grunting]
Oh!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
That's it!
[cheering]
There's my girl.
Come here baby.
Let's get out of here.
Cowboy Henry?
Hey!
Get your hands off of him!
He won that fight
fair and square!
It's all right baby.
We'll work this out, and I'll
be back before you know it.
Sure.
We'll work it all out.
B but, but you can't take him.
It's our honeymoon.
You kill a policeman
in Texas, you either
swing or die in prison.
Will the defendant please rise.
Since you've been found
guilty of manslaughter,
you're hereby sentenced
to 50 years hard labor
at the Hudsville
State Penitentiary.
[gasp]
Bailiff, remove the prisoner.
Don't worry baby, I'm
going to get you an appeal.
I won't let you
down, I promise.
Just don't do anything stupid.
I love you cowboy!
COWBOY: I love you too Toni Jo!
That was a right
fine cheese grit.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
You gonna eat them taters?
Hard to know when
you'll eat next.
Can we just talk
about the plan?
Mm.
How much money do you have?
They didn't pay him for
his last fight, bastards.
ARKIE: That don't seem fair.
$50.
That's not bad.
TONI: What about you?
I ain't got a pot
to piss in right now,
but that's getting
ready to change.
Great.
Did you and cowboy really
run with Bonnie and Clyde?
Well, now, I was the
one who introduced cowboy
to Buck Barrow when We
was all in Huntsville.
When we got out,
pulled a couple bank
jobs to get Buck
some money so he'd
catch up with his brother Clyde.
How many banks?
I don't remember.
Hm.
Come here.
You know, me and you
could rob a bank.
There's a bank, this
little town, Harrell,
Arkansas nearabouts
where I grew up.
How do we get to
Harrell, Arkansas?
We'll get us a car.
Get a car?
Actually, you'll get us a car.
But leave it up to me.
I'll be in charge of the gun.
You can be the getaway driver,
just like Bonnie did for Clyde.
I don't know nothing about guns
and never learned how to drive.
I'll learn you.
It ain't that hard.
I think I know somebody
who can help with the guns.
This'll just take a second.
Oh, we got us plenty of guns.
Damn bastard only gave
us bullets for one gun.
Hey!
Well, it seems to
me we only need one.
Yeah.
Still need a car.
Let's Walk the highway.
Come on.
You be nice to this guy.
I'll hide in the bushes.
I'll be right there.
TONI: OK.
JP: You shouldn't be out
here all alone young lady.
Dangerous.
Where you headed?
Actually, my brother and I
are on our way to Arkansas.
Where you headed?
Well, I was
delivering this new car
to a friend of mine who lives
over in Jennings, Louisiana.
I generally don't like to
travel on the lord's clay, but...
Well, that's part way.
What do you say?
[sighs]
Well, I suppose I could take
you all as far as Jennings.
Hop on in.
Thank you!
[inaudible] right,
right nice of you mister.
Don't forget your bags sis.
Oh, thank you.
You're welcome.
TONI: You got everything?
Yeah.
ARKIE: All right.
TONI: Yeah?
ARKIE: Yeah.
Let's go.
JP: It's a beautiful
day, isn't it?
TONI: Sure is.
ARKIE: Sure is.
No rain.
So what's your name?
My name's Joseph P. Galloway.
Friends call me JP.
Well, it's nice to meet you JP.
My name is...
My name is Clyde.
It's nice to meet you Clyde.
[coughs]
So what's your line JP?
I own a car dealership
back in Houston.
Ain't you the lucky one?
No ma'am.
That lord has shown his smiling
face on me and my family.
That's real nice.
Yes ma'am.
We're blessed.
No ma'am.
I don't think you'll
find much way out here.
It's a...
Perfect.
Just take it easy.
Pull over to the
side of the road.
Mister, I don't
want any trouble, OK?
Well, maybe too
late for that JP.
Just pull on over JP.
JP: Yes sir.
ARKIE: Get out.
Come on, let's go.
Empty out your pockets
right up there.
Come on!
Go.
Come on.
Let's go.
You can have the money.
Just take it.
OK?
Take it.
This is what you've got?
Yes.
I don't travel with much money.
Shut up.
Take that watch off too.
Hey sis?
Open the turtle back.
Maybe there's money in there.
What?
The the trunk.
Just open it!
Come on.
Well, how am I supposed
to know that Arkie?
I already told
you, I don't drive!
Mmister, I won't say
anything, I promise!
I promise, I won't say anything!
Really.
That's swell.
All right.
Come on.
Just please don't kill me.
Come on!
Come on POPS!
Please just don't kill me!
Get in there!
Get!
Double time!
Ah!
Sorry JP.
JP: Ah!
What'd you go and do that for?
He didn't step it up
in the first place,
he wouldn't have gotten
his hands smashed.
Come on, let's go!
Come on!
Let's go!
Hey, pipe down back there.
[sighs]
OK.
We can't take him to Arkansas.
He's making too much
noise back here.
Find a spot alongside the road.
I don't remember kidnapping
being part of the plan.
Things change sweetie pie.
You have to learn
to use your noggin.
What's eating you?
Cool off, will you?
JP (IN TRUNK): Oh.
Nice car, huh?
Bet you wish you could drive it.
JP (IN TRUNK): Oh.
Listen.
Don't touch me.
You through in with me.
We're partners.
At least 'til the bank job.
So you ought to
make the best of it.
You want to free
cowboy, don't you?
JP (IN TRUNK): Oh.
Driving doesn't
look all that hard.
Maybe I could be
the getaway driver.
That's your ticket.
JP (IN TRUNK): [moaning]
Ah!
Now, come on.
Get out of there.
Come on!
Oh.
[grunting]
How's your hands JP?
Lulu's going to
be worried sick.
Be OK.
All right.
Take your clothes off.
Wha what'd you say?
What'd he say?
You heard me.
Now.
Come on!
Ah.
It'll slow him down.
I don't want him running for
help soon as we drive off.
[grunting]
You two know you could end
up in a penitentiary for this,
don't you?
Listen mister, you'd better
shut up and do what he says.
Come on!
Let's go!
[inaudible], take the gun.
Keep it trained on him.
Son, think about
what you're doing.
Don't kill me.
ARKIE: Get up.
I, I said get up.
Toni Jo, come on.
TONI: What are you doing?
JP: I'm praying for myself
and for your eternal soul.
TONI: I don't need
your stinking prayers.
ARKIE: Toni Jo, give me the gun.
[gun shot]
Have you read this?
Where'd they find the body?
Over in [inaudible] rice
farm behind a haystack.
Poor guy's totally nude.
Did Clemet file a report?
Not his final report.
There's more.
There was a leak
to the newspaper
that the guy was brutally
tortured with a pair of pliers
before he was slain,
sexually mutilated.
Jeez.
Did she confess?
She clammed up at the inquest.
One look at the jury
and the spectator,
she refused to answer any
of Clement's questions.
But she was indicted?
She give up her accomplice?
She refers to him as
the little yellow rat.
We're arranging for her
to go to Beaumont to visit
with her husband, Cowboy Henry.
So she's receiving
special treatment?
In exchange for the name.
Her husband's serving time at
Huntsville for manslaughter,
killing a former policeman.
Nice couple.
I don't like this whole business
of them getting together.
That's the only Way
she would cooperate.
Let's keep this whole
mess under wraps.
Have you appointed
counsel for her yet?
Yep.
Those two young tax attorneys.
[laughing]
I messed up real
good this time.
(WHISPERING) I really messed up.
Give up Arkie.
It's your only chance.
Our only chance.
They want me to
look at some books.
Give them what they want sugar.
What's Arkie's real name?
I don't know.
He just went by so many names,
we always called him Arkie.
I love you cowboy.
(WHISPERING) I love you too.
[crying]
Calloway was a
close friend of mine.
I want the death penalty.
I understand and agree.
I've arranged for
Calloway's widow and daughter
to be here for the trial.
Make sure you prep him
well before Wednesday.
I want the jury's sympathy.
Oh, they're as anxious to
see these two swing as we are.
Miss Henry?
Your lawyers are
here to see you.
That no good yellow rat.
Figures.
Arkie put all the blame on me.
Miss Henry, [inaudible]
about a court to defend you.
May we have a
moment of your time?
My name is Clement Moss.
This is...
Norman Ander...
Norman Anderson.
May we call you Annie?
I don't go by that sissy
name in your report.
[inaudible].
It's Toni Jo.
Let me get y'all
a couple of chairs.
Thank you.
[inaudible].
Well, don't worry.
I don't bite.
I just use pliers.
Let's make something real
clear from the get go.
These newspapers
are full of crap.
There was no torture.
Y'all just holler when uh,
your business is done here.
Yes sir.
Will do.
So what number am I?
S excuse me?
Well, how many murder
cases have y'all tried?
Well, actually, this
is our very first one.
First one.
CLEMENT: We filed a
motion with the judge
to be withdrawn from the case.
We're tax attorneys.
(WHISPERING) Tax attorneys?
He denied our motion.
It couldn't have come
for a worse time for us.
I mean...
He's finishing up this
year's tax returns.
NORMAN:... both our returns.
Well, I wasn't
actually planning
on filing a tax
return this year,
so I guess I won't be
needing your services.
We can understand your concern
and hesitation about us,
but we want to
assure you, we will
do everything possible
to get you a fair trial.
NORMAN: Yes.
Fair trial?
Sure.
Well, so let's have it.
What have y'all come
up with for my defense?
Oh.
Um, sorry, just... uh, OK.
Um, first We have to
pick the right jury.
And then we have to...
Yeah, right.
Read the papers.
They have me swinging before
the trial even begins.
Norman and I brought that to
the attention of the court.
We asked the judge to
change the location
of the venue of the trial,
because of all the...
Because of the press.
But it was denied.
Well, it looks like I'm
screwed every which way.
[laughs]
Not entirely.
Our motion to have your case
severed from [inaudible]
Was granted.
S... severed means your
trials will be separated.
That's a good thing.
That's very good.
It's good.
We we need uh,
information about your past.
Yes, we want to establish
a, your background.
I don't need people
feeling all sorry for me.
Well, actually, you do.
It's part of your defense.
I ain't airing out my dirty
laundry for them holy rollers.
Some of those
holy rollers might
have sympathy for you
because of your history
and actually be against
the death penalty.
A fat chance.
That's her.
Miss Galloway, would
you make a statement
concerning Mrs. Henry's trial
which opens here tomorrow?
Naturally, everyone must know
how I feel about the matter.
REPORTER: Ma'am?
Ma'am?
Mr. Copeland, Mr. Copeland.
Can I get a statement
from your Mr. Copeland?
We, referring to Mrs.
Galloway and her daughter,
will insist upon
the death penalty
for both the man and the woman.
And I cannot see or understand
how a jury could assess
anything other than
the death penalty.
You could quote me on that.
REPORTER: Give a quote here sir?
Ma'am?
[whispered chatter]
Understand Pete,
you make a call.
I'm just, what I'm
saying is you have to...
Order in my courtroom.
Proceed with jury selection.
Ah, Mr. Albert Stokes.
Mr Stokes, I'd like to ask
you that if you were satisfied
beyond any reasonable doubt
that the defendant is guilty,
could you vote for
the death penalty?
Yes sir, I could.
PROSECUTOR: The state
accepts this juror.
Um, Mr. Stokes?
[clears throat]
Uh, Mr. Stokes,
if you're accepted
as a defendant in this case,
uh, uh, as a juror in this case,
and if, if the jury
should determine
that the defendant
was guilty of murder,
would you be able to
give uh, consideration...
Your honor, would you kindly
direct my learned colleague
to speak up?
The people of the great
state of Louisiana
would like to hear
what he has to say.
Mr. Anderson, speak up.
Yes sir... (LOUDER)
Yes sir, your honor.
Wo... would you be able to give
consideration to a verdict
other than capital punishment.
That is to say,
life imprisonment?
Yes sir.
Would the opinion that you
have formed uh, accounts
or discussions, you may have had
about the case with, you know,
with you know, the mailman,
the milkman, the vegetable man,
or, or, you know, the boys
at the hardware store,
or church people
say, or you know,
whoever the...
whoever really would
have a conversation
about the case with you
with that case, the
discussions about it,
uh, easily affect your views?
Does the opinion that you
form easily effect your views?
It would.
[coughs]
Thank you.
Look, your honor,
the defense asks
that this juror be excused.
I see no reason why Mr Stokes
cannot serve as a juror.
He is accepted.
Next?
Your honor, I object.
Overruled.
Pay him no attention.
Oh, never mind.
The state is satisfied
with the jury.
Oh, your honor?
The defense is not satis...
Your honor, I object.
On what grounds?
[inaudible], I'd like to
introduce the Texas enterprise
and late Charles American press.
But your honor, in
these news... thank you.
In these newspapers, Mr.
Copeland and Miss Galloway
have made remarks
indicating that they
will settle for nothing
less than a hanging verdict.
(WHISPERING) And
if they are allowed
to sit directly in
front of the jury,
it is with the sole purpose
of arousing sympathy.
I therefore request they be
moved to outside the rail.
Overruled.
They're fine where they are.
Take a seat Mr. Anderson.
Mr. Paterson, are
you ready to begin?
I am your honor.
I would like to court
to recognize and admit
before this court assistant
prosecutor, JP Copeland,
a Houston attorney, retained
by the widow and daughter
of the murdered Galloway.
Objection, your honor, on
the grounds that this Texas
lawyer's not qualified
before the Louisiana bar,
nor is he an elector of
the parish and state,
and therefore, cannot serve as
a special prosecutor in state
court in Louisiana.
JUDGE: Overruled.
Your honor, the defense...
[inaudible], I said
I've already ruled
on your objection,
and it's overruled.
File a bill of exception.
Mr. Copeland will be allowed to
serve as a special prosecutor
during this trial.
Bailiff?
Swear him in.
Your boys, they didn't
do such a bad job,
considering your case is
moving right along quick.
Quick to the gallows.
Now, you don't know that.
I know plenty.
Is the state ready to
call its first witness?
My name is Fred Arnold, and
I'm a professional photographer.
Did you take this picture and
develop it to the present state
that it's in now?
Yes sir.
This is the photograph
that I took.
The state now
offers in evidence
this photograph,
identified as exhibit A.
Ob objection to the reception
of the photograph in evidence,
reason that it is unnecessary
to introduce in that its only
effect would be to inflame
and prejudice the minds
of the jurors.
That if the state wishes
to establish death,
the testimony of the
coroner should suffice.
Overruled.
The jury can see the photograph.
No further question.
My name is Dr. E. L. Clement.
I've been the [inaudible] Parish
corner for the past 25 years.
Did you examine the body and
determine the cause of death?
Yes.
Mr. Joseph Galloway died
instantly from a gunshot wound
to the head fired by
a 32 caliber pistol.
Were there any other
wounds or injuries?
I object, uh, as to relevance.
Any other wounds to the
body did not cause death.
Overruled.
Dr. Clement's an expert.
I'll allow the question.
There was a severe laceration
of the hand, clean to the bone.
[gasps]
Order in the courtroom.
How did the defendant
appear at the inquest?
She was totally unresponsive.
She offered no testimony,
like she didn't even care.
Objection.
Your honor, speculative.
I mean, how could he
possibly know how she felt?
Sustained.
The jury will disregard the
last statement by this witness.
Thank you.
That's all Dr. Clement.
Does the defense
have any questions?
Dr. Clement?
Other than a cut to
Mr. Calloway's hand,
was there any other
evidence suggesting torture?
No sir.
[gasps]
Quiet.
This is my courtroom,
and I'll have quiet.
Thank you sir.
No further questions.
Dr. Clement, you may step down.
Call your next witness.
Sheriff Reid, When
was the first time
you encountered the defendant?
We took custody of
her own Saturday,
February the 17th from
Captain George McQuiston.
And what happened next?
Well, at that point, Trooper
Fremont Lebleiu and myself
escorted her on a
search for the body.
At first, I thought she
was blowing smoke up at us,
but uh, she said she'd
take us to the body.
So we went looking.
You sure there's
a body out here?
I told you, we left his body
in one of these here fields.
You think you'd be a
little more interested.
Well, why don't you tell
me why on God's green earth
you'd come out
here to shoot a man
and leave him in here to rot?
We needed his car.
Who's we?
I'm no stool pigeon.
Even if he is a
little yellow rat.
That's all fine
and good Miss Henry,
but there's been no report
of a missing persons.
And you can run a good
dog where there ain't
no rabbits who'll run him out.
Now, I have about run out.
We're going to hitch this
wagon back to the house.
[gasp]
This is it!
That's it!
Right there!
(MUTTERING) This woman
is nuttier than squirrel
droppings.
(WHISPERING) Told you.
Lebleiu, we're going to need
the coroner out here, pronto.
Turn around, Miss Henry.
You're under the
arrest for murder.
Is this the gun you received
from Trooper Lebleiu, allegedly
used by Mrs. Henry?
That is the gun.
And was the bullet retrieved
from the deceased, Mr.
Galloway, fired from this gun?
Ballistics report verified
that that was the gun used
to kill JP Galloway.
Your honor, we entered
this as exhibit B,
and we have no
further questions.
JUDGE: The defense may
cross examine this witness.
Sheriff Reid, did
you escort Mrs. Henry
to the Beaumont Penitentiary?
Yes, I did.
CLEMENT: For what purpose?
Well, We wanted to find
out who her accomplice was.
That was the only way she was
going to cooperate with us.
And isn't it true that on the
return trip to Lake Charles,
Miss Henry made a
statement to you regarding
the death of JP Galloway?
On the way back
from Beaumont, she
said that she did
not fire the shot.
No further questions.
Redirect, your honor.
Sheriff Reid, was
this the first time
that Mrs. Henry had
declared her innocence?
That was the very first
she'd said on that.
No further
questions your honor.
Call your next witness.
The state calls George
McQuiston to the stand.
George McQuiston, will
you please take the stand?
Sheriff Reid?
Yes sir.
Issue a bench warrant for the
arrest of George McQuiston.
SHERIFF REID: Will
do your honor.
JUDGE: Quiet.
Call your next witness.
PROSECUTOR: State your
name please for the court.
Mrs. Emma Holt.
PROSECUTOR: And what is your
relationship to the accused?
I'm Annie B's...
uh, Toni Jo's aunt.
I've always been known to
her as Auntie Beatrice.
PROSECUTOR: Thank you Mrs. Holt,
but just answer the question.
And when was the last
time you saw your niece
before she showed up
unexpectedly at your home?
I hadn't seen my
niece for four years
until the night she
came to my house.
I could see that she
was very nervous.
And I could tell
something was wrong.
I just wished George was there.
PROSECUTOR: Please Mrs. Holt,
tell the court who George is.
George McQuiston is
my brother, and he's
captain of the state police.
We're all very proud of him.
He's nothing like Annie's
pa, the way he'd...
PROSECUTOR: Please Mrs. Holt.
Just answer the question.
I'm sorry.
But you have to
understand, Annie B.
Had to leave home when
she was only 1 2 years old.
I taught the baby how to sew.
I was like her momma.
PROSECUTOR: Your honor, I'd
like to request a recess
but reserve the right
to further question
this witness at a future time.
Granted.
Witness must step down.
Court will recess and resume
tomorrow morning at 9 AM.
Got to get a
better [inaudible].
Files are all over the place.
Did you and do you have
a close relationship...
I'd like to recall Mrs.
Emma Holt to the stand.
You were telling us yesterday
that you had not heard
from Mrs. Henry in four years?
Yes sir.
And what happened when
she did contact you?
Well, it was the
middle of the night.
Tell me dear, what's wrong?
I've gone and done
something terrible Aunt Emma.
Lord have mercy child.
What has that no good husband
of yours gone and done?
Is it cowboy you call him?
You don't understand.
I shot a man in the heart.
[gasps]
[sobbing]
Oh.
Oh child, no.
[crying]
I'll give your
Uncle George a call.
He'll know what to do.
Shh.
And she told you, I shot a man?
Yes.
But I'm not sure if that's
what she meant to say.
She was in a state of shock.
Mrs. Holt, is this the gun
that Tony Jo Henry showed you?
It could be.
I don't know guns that much.
Is this the gun you gave
to the police officers?
Objection.
The witness said
she wasn't sure.
Overruled.
The weapon's already been
established as the gun
the police confiscated
from the old home.
You then called your
brother, George McQuiston?
Yes.
PROSECUTOR: And what
did you tell him?
I told him to come
as soon as he could,
that Annie B. Was in trouble.
PROSECUTOR: And
your brother came?
He came with two
policemen to get Annie B.
Mrs. Holt, do you know
where your brother is?
No sir.
No further questions.
JUDGE: Does the defense
have any questions?
Yes, your honor.
[clears throat]
Mrs. Holt... did you and do
you have a close relationship
with your niece?
Yes.
I raised her a spell.
And what was her
childhood like?
Objection.
I fail to see the relevance
of this case your honor.
Your honor, We will
show you the relevance
by demonstrating the conditions
of Miss Henry's childhood.
Allowed, overruled.
How old was Annie B... also
known as Toni Jo Henry...
when she came to live with you?
AUNT EMMA: She was almost 12.
CLEMENT: And where was this
11-year-old girl's momma?
Her momma passed on to the
good Lord when she was 10.
TB ate her up.
My brother and his
pa, he made her
get a job at the macaroni
factory in Treeport.
So she was forced
to leave school.
And how long was she at
the macaroni factory?
'Til right before she
came to stay with me.
The factory fired her
when they found out
about her momma dying
at the TB and all.
Mrs. Holt... was Tony
Jo's father kind to her?
No.
He let that no good whiskey
turn him into a mean man.
He didn't used to be so mean.
Mrs. Holt... did Toni
Jo's father, your brother,
ever hit her?
Poor little thing.
She always had
bruises on her body.
Objection.
Cause for speculation,
your honor.
Children do fall down
and they get bruises.
JUDGE: Sustained.
Mrs. Holt, you
testified earlier
that you told Toni Jo
that you would help her
if she told you what happened.
Is that correct?
Yes.
I wanted to help you baby.
Please address your comments
to the court Mrs. Holt.
Did Toni Jo confess to
you after you told her
you'd help her?
I think so.
She just looked so hopeless.
So lost.
Mrs. Holt, you stated earlier
that your niece, Toni Jo Henry,
told you she shot
a man in the heart.
Is that correct?
Yes.
You're sure she
said, in the heart?
Not the head?
Yes sir.
That's all then.
Thank you for your testimony.
JUDGE: You may step
down Miss Holt.
Prosecution rests your honor.
The defense may call
its first witness.
BAILIFF: Do you swear to tell
the truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the
truth, so help you god?
I do.
BAILIFF: Please be seated.
Who's your husband?
Claude D. Henry.
You and your husband devoted?
Yes sir.
CLEMENT: He been in any trouble?
And what was his trouble?
TONI: Murder.
Was he charged with
killing someone?
TONI: Yes sir.
CLEMENT: Was he
convicted of this crime?
TONI: Yes sir.
Where'd you meet Mr. Galloway?
About one or 1/2 mile
this side of Orange, Texas.
Did you and Finnon
Burkes both have guns?
Yes sir.
Were both the guns loaded?
No sir, only one.
Well, who had that gun?
Finnon Burkes.
So Burkes had the
only loaded gun?
Yes sir.
Come on.
Tell the jury what happened.
After We got in the car,
Arkie pulled out his gun
and told him to stop the car.
Go on.
Well, Arkie said that he'd
better get in the turtle back.
And he slammed that
hood down so hard.
Well, it cut up that
fellow's hand real bad.
CLEMENT: Who drove?
Arkie.
I never learned how to drive.
So Burkes drove the car?
TONI: Yes sir.
Go on.
Well, Arkie drove
for awhile and stopped
by the side of a dirt road
on account of all the noise
that Callaway was making.
He uh, made him get
out of the turtle back
and take his clothes off.
There was some conversation.
I, I don't remember
what it was about.
I picked up the clothes,
and Mr. Galloway
went behind the haystack
and kneeled down.
He said, don't you
know you're going to go
to the penitentiary for this?
And I told him, he'd better
think where he would go.
And I started back
towards the car.
[gun shot]
[gasp]
(WHISPERING) What'd you do?
I shot him in the heart.
Through the heart?
Yeah.
Sounded like a punctured tire.
What happened after
you left the rice field?
First, we stopped down the
road and burned his clothes.
And then Arkie drove us to
a little town in Arkansas
where we was going
to rob a bank.
CLEMENT: Did you?
No.
CLEMENT: You didn't rob a bank?
There was no bank.
I thought you said that
there was a bank in this here
town that we could hold up.
There used to be.
How was I supposed
to know it dried up?
Well, now what
are we going to do?
Find another one.
Well, it better be soon!
We hardly have any money left.
ARKIE: Yeah?
Well, get me something
to drink with that money.
Not not Arkie.
We've got to keep
our wits about us.
ARKIE: Ha.
After a day like today,
Toni, [inaudible].
Well, you got his watch.
Why don't you use that?
ARKIE: Don't give me no lip.
You'd better not make me
look for it sweetheart.
Oh.
Well, I used the money
to buy a bus to ticket
back to Shreveport.
And I Walked to Aunt
Emma's from there.
Would your Aunt Emma
testify about your childhood?
Could you describe what it was
like growing up in your home?
Objection, irrelevance.
The facts of Mrs.
Henry's past have
been presented to this court.
And nothing new can come
from this testimony other
than to elicit
sympathy from the jury.
Your honor, we believe
the firsthand account
bears listening to,
because the defendant was
a child of misfortune and
a victim of circumstances.
I can see no additional
relevant information coming
from this line of questioning.
Objection sustained.
Your honor...
Don't try my patience Mr. Moss.
The objection is sustained.
Now, move on.
No further questions.
You changed your story
about who shot the man
after you saw your husband.
Yes.
Mrs. Henry, you say you're
devoted to your husband,
because he cured
you of a drug habit.
Yes.
Then you're no
longer an addict?
No.
Well, that's
wonderful Mrs. Henry.
Congratulations.
That's all your honor.
You may step down Mrs. Henry.
Does the defense have
any more questions?
No your honor.
The defense rests.
The court is recessed
into 9 AM tomorrow
morning, when We will
begin closing arguments.
This glass of water represents
the lives of two women.
Their lives were as
clean as this water.
This ink is the
slayer's bullet which
brought gloom and
heartbreak to the very souls
in this widow and her daughter.
You have a responsibility
to the state of Louisiana
to protect it from
people like Mrs. Henry.
Do the right thing.
Death is the only verdict
and just punishment.
GENTLEMAN: Hang her.
COURTROOM OBSERVER: Yes.
JUDGE: That's enough.
I'll have the next
person arrested.
It is our belief based
on the evidence presented
that our client should
not be found guilty
as charged, which in this case,
means sentencing her to death.
The direct testimony of who
shot Mr. Galloway establishes it
was not Mrs. Henry who pulled
the trigger, but Finnon Burkes.
It was Burkes who secured
the murder weapon,
and it was Burkes who
drove the stolen car.
There is no proof beyond
a reasonable doubt
that Mrs. Henry actually
shot JP Calloway... only
circumstantial evidence.
Gentlemen at the jury, you
cannot sentence a woman to hang
by the neck until dead based
on circumstantial evidence.
Now, in a few minutes,
the judge will issue you
possible verdicts in this case.
We respectfully,
respectfully ask
that you return a verdict
other than guilty as charged
and spare the life
of Toni Jo Henry.
Well, that's it.
Gentlemen of the
jury, we've given you
the necessary elements to
prove the crime of murder.
Further, gentlemen, if you find
that from the evidence provided
in this case that this
defendant conspired with another
or others to commit a felony,
and that during the course
of that conspiracy, one
of the conspirators,
not the defendant,
actually pulled the trigger
that shot JP Galloway,
then the defendant
is just as guilty under
the law as though she
had pulled the trigger herself.
Court will be in recess
while the jury deliberates.
JUDGE: Will the
defendant please rise?
Has the jury reached a verdict?
We have your honor.
We find the defendant
guilty as charged.
[gasps]
JUDGE: Quiet in the courtroom.
Bailiff, please reman Mrs.
Henry back to her cell.
TONI: She was the only
witness, some... someone who
unsuccessfully sought to
have her tell something
of her past life as
an abused young girl
and as a prostitute
and a drug addict
as influencing factors in
the crime of which she stood
accused.
Seems real fair, don't it?
But you boys are
asking for an appeal.
And that's good.
She actually ask for me?
She asked to speak to a priest?
Well, not in so many words.
What words did she use?
I don't force myself
or my face on anyone.
But that's why you're
the perfect person
to talk with her father.
Father Richard.
I don't know what to say to her.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Listen to this.
Mr Copland's participation in
the trial cannot be said to be
favorable to the prosecution
as he stated before the trial
in the public press that he was
employed by the deceased family
to demand only a
capital verdict.
And a high court
senior shouldn't
have been allowed to testify
about your childhood.
Yeah.
And they didn't like the fact
that your so-called confessions
weren't free and voluntary.
It helped your uncle
wasn't to be found.
Moss told me that the
authorities are trying
to get him to turn himself in.
That can help me.
Yeah.
Well, maybe at the next trial.
But we'll be ready for him.
Wait.
(WHISPERING) Thank you so
much for coming [inaudible].
Toni Jo, this is the priest
I've been telling you about.
This is Father Richard.
Well, it's nice to
meet you Father Richard.
I never really talked
to a priest before.
Well then, I hope I
don't disappoint you.
I'd offer you a place to sit,
but uh, we'd kind of full here.
No, we've got to be on
our way, so take ours.
Nice to meet you
Father Richard.
I'm Clement Moss.
Clement.
This is my partner,
Norman Anderson.
Norman.
Well, I didn't intend
to scare you fellas off.
Oh, don't worry Father.
They don't scare that easy.
I gotta get home.
Really looking forward
to finally having a home
cooked meal.
Have a nice visit.
Bring me back some leftovers.
Food stinks around here.
[laughs]
Well, I guess you're waiting
to hear my sob story.
I never really been
that big on confession.
Truthfully, neither have I.
You ain't a typical
priest, are you?
Typical has never
been a goal of mine.
Good.
Because I don't
really go for them
firing brimstone preachers.
Thank you.
To quench the fire?
I would just like
to be your friend.
But I'm a criminal.
Some people thought
Jesus was a criminal too.
Right.
Just don't try any of that
converting stuff on me.
I had enough religion
to last me a lifetime,
no matter how short it may be.
How can you befriend
a woman like that?
She murdered a
man in cold blood.
Well, you must know more
than the courts then.
Because they're in the process
of trying to figure that out.
What I do know is that
cold hearted woman needs
to pay for what she's done.
You are not
describing the woman
I have come to know
these past few months.
You expect me to swallow that?
No.
If I can arrange it, would
you like the opportunity
to speak with that cold
hearted woman face to face?
You bet.
Wait here.
I've never met a person
accused of murder.
So while I've covered the
trial of Annie Beatrice Henry,
since the beginning, I was
reluctant to actually meet
her face to face.
Yellow bellied is more like it.
You know, I smiled
at that fellow twice.
I'd say a lot of
talent's gone to waste.
He couldn't believe
your cell was unlocked.
He was shaking in his boots.
Toni Jo, as she
refers to herself,
has been in jail for six months.
She's currently awaiting
her second trial.
I found her to be very pleasant,
unlike her image thus far.
She maintains her innocence
and firing the bullet,
but she does take responsibility
for her part in the crime.
Mrs. Henry claims she's not
unlike any other woman in love
with her husband,
and that's what drove
her to make some bad decisions.
Toni Jo joked about her
need for a sewing machine
to make some new clothes when
I commented on her appearance
and how much coverage
it's getting.
It's difficult for
this reluctant reporter
to believe that this
woman deserves to die.
Punishment, yes.
Death, no.
Coral, I've got an idea.
Does that old sewing machine
downstairs still work?
Oh, no, no, no.
Over there.
Be careful with that.
Holy smoke.
It's a good thing we
had that other cell
to put all this stuff in, huh?
[gasps]
(WHISPERING) [inaudible].
[laughs]
It's about time them
press buzzards started
turning around public opinion.
One Gibbs.
Let's not get carried away.
How are they just one?
She says it's for... she said
it's for you to buy material
to sew some new clothes.
I'd like to write you.
And in my next
letter, I will include
funds for your legal expenses.
How much does that make?
Well, all told, I
ain't exactly sure.
But this Week,
it's at least $40.
No skimming Gibbs.
[MUSIC BILLIE HOLIDAY,
"SOLITUDE"]
[gasp]
You're not wearing
that in court.
Oh boy.
Wait 'til my papa
gets a load of this.
Or better yet, Wait 'til Mr.
Copeland lays his eyes on me.
I need a full length
mirror in here.
Copeland can't try
this case again,
but the district attorney,
Patterson, remains the same.
Oh, and no new judge.
We'll face Hood again.
You boys are just
full of good news.
Mm, mm, mm.
Any which way you shoot
yourself in the foot,
you wear that thing.
Yeah.
And you wear that thing
in court, the press
will have a field day.
Oh, let them.
What's the difference?
Be smart Toni Jo.
Because Patterson's smart.
Yeah.
[inaudible] want
the right to have.
Finnon Burkes as a witness.
And Judge Hood is not
allowed to our objections
to Burkes's testimony.
Well, like I said,
what's the difference?
Get a load of this.
It's from Burkes.
Basically, he's offered to
take full blame for the murder
if Toni Jo will help
him escape from jail.
Let me see that.
This is perfect.
This is just what we need.
[sighs]
It's about time
I caught a brake.
God is good.
We have a month to
prepare for any objections
to his admission.
No sir, not this month.
Better uh, better get
over to the church.
Yeah.
Looks like we're going to war.
I'm a get home.
I'll take this with me.
I'll call the judge and see
how this affects our court date.
See you later Toni Jo.
See you Toni Jo.
TONI (VOICEOVER): Dear
love, my lawyers think
my trial will take place
the first part of next year,
what with the war and all.
I just wish you
could come see me.
My place looks real good.
Father Richard's
been here a lot.
He's starting to
make sense to me.
But don't Worry.
I'm not ready to become
a nun yet, ha, ha.
Wish me luck on the next trial.
I love you, Toni Jo.
Prosecution may call
its next witness.
State your name and
occupation for the record.
My name is George
McQuiston, and I'm currently
on leave from Louisiana
State Police, where
I hold the rank of captain.
Mr. McQuiston, has anybody told
you not come to this courtroom?
No sir.
Has anybody tried
to prevent you
from coming to this courtroom?
No sir.
Then I hereby find you
in contempt of court.
And immediately following your
testimony, you will be arrested
and remanded to the
custody of Sheriff Reid.
Is that understood?
Yes your honor.
Mr. McQuiston,
you did not testify
at Mrs. Henry's first trial.
Is that correct?
That is correct.
Would you like to tell us why?
Well, Annie B. Is my
niece, and um, she's
had a pretty hard life.
Isn't it your duty as a
representative of the state
police to testify to the
truth of a criminal matter,
even if the person
is a relative?
Yes sir.
It's Why I turned myself in.
You heard your sister, Mrs.
Holt, testify in this trial
that she called you about
the defendant, Mrs. Henry.
Yes sir.
PROSECUTOR: Could you tell
the court what happens
when you arrived at her house?
Well, Emma was, she was upset.
And um, I told her to sit tight
and that I'd be there directly.
Annie B., I want you to tell
me exactly what happened.
It's like I didn't know what
I was doing, like I was crazed.
Listen, I want to help you out.
And I'm going to,
but you're going
to have to tell me the truth.
We needed his car.
We was going to rob
a bank for the money.
You then handed her
over to Sheriff Reid?
MR. MCQUISTON: Yes sir.
No further questions.
Mr. McQuiston, I'm interested
in exactly what you promised
your niece in return for her...
PROSECUTOR: Objection.
Sustained.
Your honor, I believe
George McQuiston has already
testified that he'd help her.
The objection is
sustained Mr. Moss.
Sit down.
O K.
Why'd Miss Henry tell you
she shot Mr. Galloway?
MR. MCQUISTON: Because
she wanted his car.
No, that's not what I mean.
I mean, Why do you think she
was so willing to discuss
this with you?
I couldn't say.
Wasn't it because you and your
sister promised her you'd help
her?
Objection.
Your honor...
Sustained.
There'll be no further questions
regarding what may or may not
have been promised
to the defendant.
Does that mean you have
no further questions
for the Witness?
Well, obviously, if every time
I try to ask a question you
forbid it...
Watch it Mr. Anderson, or I'll
hold you in contempt of court,
and you'll find yourself
spending the night in jail.
No further
questions your honor.
Next witness.
The state calls Horace
Finnon Burkes to the stand.
[chatter]
JUDGE: I will have
order in this courtroom,
or I will clear the courtroom.
Stand up please.
Raise your right hand.
Put the other on the bible.
Do you swear to tell the
whole truth, and nothing
but the truth, so help you god?
ARKIE: I do.
BAILIFF: Have a seat.
PROSECUTOR: State your
name for the record.
ARKIE: Horace Finnon Burkes.
You also go by the name Arkie?
Yeah.
My friends call me Arkie.
I don't mean Yorkie.
[laughter]
Mr. Burkes, you've
already been sentenced
to die for the murder
of Joseph P. Galloway.
Is that correct?
Yes sir.
So you have nothing to gain
by your testimony here today?
Objection your honor.
Overruled.
You may answer the question.
No sir.
Nothing to gain.
Tell us what happened when you
got picked up by Mr. Galloway.
Well, We did hitchhike.
We were given a ride
by Mr. Galloway.
Toni Jo had the only
gun with bullets.
She wanted to put him in the
turtle back to keep him quiet.
That's... that's a lie!
Counsel, if you can't keep
your client quiet, I will.
Continue, Mr. Burkes.
I did slam his hand
in the turtleback,
but it was an accident.
Go on.
After we were
driving for a while,
Toni Jo wanted me to
pull off the road because
of his hollerin' on
account of his cut hand.
PROSECUTOR: You
pulled off the road?
Yep.
And she wanted him to strip.
Son of a bitch is lying.
I will not have any further
antics from the defendant.
Is that clear?
Yes your honor.
PROSECUTOR: Continue.
After he undressed, we walked
him behind these rice stacks.
Toni Jo told me to take his
clothes back to the car.
[gun shot]
Toni Jo, what'd you do?
Just shut up Arkie.
It's none of your damn business.
Get back to the car.
Did you kill him Toni Jo?
Pick up the clothes.
Come on!
Pick up the clothes!
Let's go!
You killed him Toni Jo!
Why?
TONI: Shut up Arkie!
PROSECUTOR: Where
did you drive to?
I told her we should go
to Arkansas to rob a bank.
What happened?
Bank was gone.
[laughing]
She was sore.
[crowd laughing]
I knew there was no bank there.
I just wanted to get as
close to my home as I could.
So what did you do next?
I told her we'd find a
place to hide out for a bit
and then go on to another town.
TONI: I thought we said
there was a bank we
could rob in this town.
ARKIE: There used to be.
How was I to know
it was dried up?
Well, now what
are we going to do?
We'll find another one.
Well, thanks to you, we don't
hardly have any money left.
Yeah.
L... I'm going to
get me something
to drink with that money.
Not now Arkie.
We've got to think.
I think we need
bullets for the guns.
I should go out and get some.
That's the first good idea
you've had in a long time.
Where's that fella's money?
Here.
Trade that for bullets.
Arkie.
Don't double cross me.
PROSECUTOR: So you were
afraid for your life?
I was afraid she'd do me like
she did that Mr. Galloway.
No further
questions your honor.
The defense may
question the witness.
Well, I could certainly
see how such a big man
will be intimidated by such
an imposing accomplice.
Objection.
I apologize.
I apologize, I
apologize, I apologize.
I withdraw the comment.
Watch the sarcasm Mr. Anderson.
Yes your honor.
Arkie, after you were
convicted and sentenced
to death for killing
Mr. Galloway,
weren't you hoping
for another trial?
Yes.
But it was denied.
Arkie, did you recently
send Miss Henry a letter?
PROSECUTOR: Objection.
Your honor, this letter
was sent to Miss Henry
by Mr. Burkes, and I feel
it is relevant to this case.
Let me see the
letter Mr. Anderson.
I'll allow it.
Objection overruled.
Thank you.
Arkie, did you recently
send Miss Henry
a letter promising her that you
would shoulder the entire blame
for the killing if
she would help you
with a possible jailbreak?
I just wanted to
see what she'd say.
CLEMENT: Just to be
clear, is that a yes?
Yes.
Isn't it true Arkie that you
did in fact fire a fatal shot
to Mr. Galloway?
No sir.
CLEMENT: You know
how to fire a gun?
Yeah sir.
I was in the army.
Oh, you were in the army?
They teach you how
to fire a weapon?
Yes sir.
Wasn't it the business
of the United States army
to teach all their good
soldiers to fire their weapons
accurately?
They Try-
- Is that a yes?
Yes.
So after you were
instructed in how
to fire your weapon with
deadly accuracy, isn't it true
you deserted the army
of the United States?
Yes.
But I was going
to turn myself in.
Yeah, I'm sure.
It was a yes, wasn't it?
Yes.
Weren't you
convicted and served
time in Huntsville, Texas
for armed robbery Arkie?
Yes sir.
Thank you.
No further questions your honor.
Uh, your honor,
I'd like to redirect
a question to the witness.
Go ahead Mr. Patterson.
What was your purpose
in writing to Mrs. Henry?
I knew she'd lie about
who fired the gun.
I figured she'd have a better
chance getting off, being
a good looking woman and all.
Then she could help me escape.
Another well thought out plan.
Thank you Mr. Burkes.
No more questions.
Your honor, the
prosecution rests.
The jury's back.
We need y'all back
in the courtroom.
[inaudible] an hour.
Is it good or bad?
What's with the bag?
The archdiocese send you with
a poisonous snake for my cell?
The orders are orders you know.
It needs to be quicker.
You ready?
OK.
[gasp]
Oh my god!
What a sweet little boy you are!
Well then, you'd
better look again.
[gasp]
Oh.
Well, then I'll, I'll
call you Jezebel in honor
of you and your religion.
But I'll go by Bell.
Mhm.
Aw.
Oh.
It's been a long
time since someone's
done something so nice for me.
And I'm glad I could.
You restored my faith.
Well, I have been waiting
a while to hear those words.
In mankind Father, not god.
Don't you know?
That is how God loves you,
through people like me.
So that's how he's shown his
love for me for the first 20
years of my life?
Through all the wonderful people
who have guided, and nurtured,
and loved me?
Nothing goes unnoticed,
and that includes you,
and the injustices in your life.
He's just waiting for
you to reach out to him.
He'll do the rest.
Remember when I brought
that reporter fellow here,
and you nearly cussed
out a man of the cloth?
Don't you just hate
"I told you" so's?
[laughs]
No.
You received I don't
know, more than $120.
So far.
Well, that's not very
specific for an accountant.
Besides, not all of them
letters have been sugar.
Some people know the Lord's
compassion, and some don't.
What are you
working on Toni Jo?
My execution dress.
They're talking about
an electric chair.
I'm having a hard
time facing her.
May I read you something?
No more bad news, please.
This is a bit of good news.
The teachers of the law brought
in a woman caught in adultery.
They made her stand
before the group
and said to Jesus,
teacher, this woman
was caught in the
act of adultery.
In the law, Moses commanded
us to stone such women.
Jesus bent down and
started to write
on the ground with his finger.
When they kept on
questioning him,
he straightened up and said
to them, if any one of you
is without sin, let him be the
first to throw a stone at her.
Again, he stooped down
and wrote on the ground
that this, those who
heard, began to go away.
Jesus straightened up and asked
her, woman, where are they?
Has no one condemned you?
No one sir, she said.
Than neither do I condemn
you, declared Jesus.
Go now and leave
your life of sin.
What was he writing
on the ground?
No one really knows.
The holy roller's
killed some, right?
Mercy is hard to come by.
Jesus was wrongfully charged
and wrongfully put to death.
And still, he is willing
to die for our offenses.
Only he can give
you what you need.
Stop right there cowboy.
The bastards owe
us a phone call.
I'm working on
another plan baby.
So this is the good part.
It'll be a long time before
you see those pearly gates.
They can't do this to you.
Anyways, you'll always
be my pearl in the rough.
[laughs]
I think he means
diamond in the rough.
Well, either way, he
got the rough part of it.
We'll see what I can do
about that phone call.
(WHISPERS) Thank you.
O K.
Well, what questions do
you have for me this week?
O K.
Well, the last thing I
have is the vast mysteries
of the universe
should only confirm
our belief and the
certainty of its creator.
I thought we'd
moved on from that.
Don't want to talk
about Darwin, eh father?
Absolutely.
God gave you a mind
to question, and that
is how you obtain true faith.
So you think I
need to get dunked?
We don't dunk.
We sprinkle.
And yes.
O K.
Well, let's do it quick then
before I change my mind.
It's not like taking
castor oil Toni Jo.
It's, it's an opportunity
for a new life.
I do believe father.
I need to believe.
Help me.
Do you think they'll let you
out here for about an hour
tomorrow?
[music playing - hymn]
No more trial misgate.
No more robbing banks, and
no more hurting people baby.
TONI (ON PHONE):
(WHISPERING) Please be good.
I can't listen to this.
You know I can't
stand to hear you cry.
But I sure as hell can't
accept not seeing you again.
It was my last
request to talk to you,
so please tell me
what I need to hear.
O K.
TONI (ON PHONE): I was selfish.
I always felt so alone.
[inaudible] did to you cowboy.
And I always hoped that there
was a god running the show.
And I just wished
maybe I could, just
maybe I could still just
one more act with you.
Just one little act.
Put your faith in god.
Live a law-abiding life.
I'll be good sweetheart.
And you never, whatever
you do, you never
walk out that back door again.
You behave like a man and
make your momma and me proud.
And you always walk
out that front door.
You hear me love?
(WHISPERING) Well,
I've got to go now.
I love you forever.
I love you too Toni Jo.
[sobbing]
Father?
Would you step out for a minute?
Why?
Why... why's he got to leave?
It's only for a couple
of minutes Toni Jo.
He can come back.
TONI: (SCREAMING) No!
[inaudible]
[crying]
That was not right!
It was supposed to be hanging!
Father, I need
you back in there.
They're going to cut off all
her hair for the cap mask.
TONI: Get away from me!
(WHISPERING) on god.
TONI: Father Richard!
[crying]
I want my other father.
It's all I have left,
and they want to take it.
It's all I have left.
Oh god.
Toni Jo.
Annie B. Look at me.
You are more than your hair.
You are more than your looks.
And you are braver than
anyone in this room.
You have been such a bright
and colorful spot in my life.
And because you're a bright and
colorful person, you're unique,
and you have worth.
And no one can
take that from you.
You can do this.
You can do this, because
I won't leave your side,
not even for one minute
before you leave this world
for the glory that awaits you.
Then can I have my hair back?
(WHISPERING) Of course.
What would an angel be
without her glorious hair?
[sniffling]
He stays.
No problem.
FATHER RICHARD: You just
close your eyes and listen
to my words, words of truth.
Humble yourselves therefore,
under God's mighty hand
so that he may lift
you up in due time.
Cast all your anxiety on him,
because he cares for you.
What benefit did you
reap at that time
when you were slaves
to sin for the things
that you are now ashamed of?
Those things result in death.
But thanks be to God, you
have been set free from sin,
and have become slaves to God.
The benefit you reap
leads to holiness.
And the result is eternal life.
Bless the Lord with all my soul.
Bless his holy [inaudible].
Bless the lord with all my soul.
Forget not all he has given.
Bless [inaudible] and
all that is within.
Bless the lord,
[inaudible], who redeem
in thy love and [inaudible].
And the saying that is
written will come true.
Death has been
swallowed up in victory.
Where, o death, is your victory?
Where, o death, is
your [inaudible]?
The sting of death is sin, and
the power of sin is the law.
The Lord is my shepherd,
I shall not Want.
He maketh me to lie
down in green pastures,
he leadeth me beside
the still waters.
He restoreth my soul.
He leadeth me in the paths of
righteousness for his namesake.
Yea, though I Walk through the
valley of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil,
for thou art with me.
Thy rod and thy staff,
they comfort me.
Thou preparest a table
before me in the presence
of mine enemies.
Thou annointest
my head with oil.
My cup runneth over.
Surely, goodness and
mercy shall follow
me all the days of my life.
And I will dwell in the
house of the Lord forever.
Father?
I know what Jesus was
writing in the sand.
He was writing my name, Annie
Beatrice McQuiston
or Toni Jo Henry.
I guess it took him so
long for all the bad things
I'd done in my life.
And I had too many names.
(WHISPERING) That's
right Toni Jo.
And it says pardoned
next to all of them.
You sure Jesus will
take the rap for me?
Guaranteed.
Any last words?
[electrocution sounds]