(baby crying)
(chopping and cracking sounds)
(ominous music)
Katie: So you'd leave the
store for some big shot?
Drew: He's not
just some bigshot.
I mean Lance Bryant
happens to be
one of the stores
biggest customers.
The place wouldn't
exist without him.
Katie: Right.
Drew: And he's also one of the
most successful guys in town.
You know, he made the
"Forty under 40" list.
Katie: Yeah.
Katie: I know, but, okay.
Drew: Twice Katie.
Nobody does that.
Katie: That sounds very
impressive, it does.
Katie: But I mean you've been
working towards something
and I just don't know
that it's necessarily
the smartest thing to just
pick up and start over.
Drew: I don't think
you understand.
The guy is super loaded.
I'll probably get paid at least
triple what I'm making now.
It's not starting over.
Katie: Okay, but
what will the job be?
I mean, what does he even do?
Drew: What does he even do?
What does it even matter?
Katie: Oh God.
Drew: Okay, the
man sweats success.
Ever read his book?
Katie: No.
Drew: Well, there you go.
Katie: Have you read his book?
Drew: I've read the
first chapter of it.
Katie: Well, there you go.
Drew: Well, I've
read pieces of it.
I've read more than you have.
Katie: I just wonder
if you'd actually,
you know, if you're going
to be happier doing it.
Drew: Yeah.
Katie: Really?
Drew: I mean, I'm
nearly 30 Katie.
I can't be shoving
diningroom tables
into hatchbacks for
the rest of my life.
Katie: Hmm.
Drew: I got to strike now.
Strike that hot iron.
Mr. Clayton: Drew. Drew
DeLaney. I need you out back.
Drew: I got five more
minutes Mr. Clayton.
(sighs) See what I'm
dealing with here?
Got to get out of this place.
Katie: The grass
is always greener.
Mr. Clayton, he's been
good to you. Okay?
Drew: No, Mr. Clayton can
eat a hot bowl of dicks,
is what I think.
Katie: Wow.
Lance: That right there.
That mother fuckin'
shit right there
is what pisses me off
more than anything else.
You can't just come to me
to my place of residence.
My mother fuckin' doorstep
and expect a handout.
A free fuckin' handout
that will not benefit me
in any way, shape, or
mother fuckin' form.
Drew: Uh, so did you end
up buying the cookies?
Lance: What the?
It's not about whether or not
I bought the cookies or didn't.
It's about these mother
fuckers are success suckers.
Didn't you read my book?
Drew: Well, I ...
Lance: Goddamn man.
Chapter two, paragraph six.
Yes, those who refuse
to work for success
are bloodsucking leaches,
leaches who will
success suck you dry
unless you annihilate them.
Drew: Oh yeah, annihilation.
Lance: Yeah.
Drew: Got it Mr. Bryant.
Lance: Dammit Drew.
Just call me Lance.
Drew: Yeah Lance.
Lance: Now in summation.
If those little
bitches come calling
and asking for handouts
while you're here
house-sitting you
have the green light
to use this on their asses.
Drew: Uh, we're still talking
about girl scouts. Right?
Lance: Yeah. This
may be air-powered,
but let me tell you something.
This can put a hole the
size of a grapefruit
through a squirrel
from 90 yards away.
Lance: Uh-huh
Lance: Watch yourself.
Drew: Oh.
Lance: Huh! Bam!
Lance: Drew.
Lance: Let's take a walk.
Lance: All right.
Don't let Mr. Baldwin get down
there by the horse stables.
All right. If he gets to dig in.
It will be a horrible mess.
Drew: You got horses?
That's fantastic.
I've never actually seen a
horse live in person before.
I've always kind of wanted to.
I've seen them in movies.
Lance: Stables.
You hear me say anything
about owning a damn horse?
Lance: Oh shit! I almost forgot.
Okay, so something, uh, well,
someone may be arriving
before I get back.
Special arrangement.
International arrangement.
Which could bring about
some unfortunate
misunderstandings
if not handled with a
clear and focused mind.
You feel me?
Drew: Uh, I'm not sure I follow.
Lance: Don't sweat it.
Lance: You, just toss her
into my master bedroom
if she comes before I get back.
That's it. You feel me?
Drew: Oh yeah.
Drew: I feel you.
Lance: All right.
See you do good
and you are going
to earn yourself
a spot in the big leagues.
All right? Ha-ha.
A lot of great things
going on at Team Lance.
Huh? Great things.
(rap music)
(opens door - beeper goes off)
(beeper off)
Drew: Anyone here? Lance?
(lyrics) Hells
yeah, mother fucker,
Fresh up in this big hatch.
Drew: Oh, uh, who, who are you?
Marta: I'm Marta.
Mr. Lance tells you
coming to watch his house
and to take care of his doggie.
Drew: Yeah, yeah,
that's right, that's -
Marta: I'll be in
and out all weekend
cleaning Mr. Lance home,
but please, do no
mess up nothing! Hmm?
Drew: Mr. Baldwin, I presume.
(lyrics) You make
me feel like a dog
You got me on your leash
Drew: Here you go Mr. Baldwin.
(lyrics) You make
a grown man pant
You make a grown man dance
Drew: Time to eat Mr.
Baldwin. Eat it. Come on.
(lyrics) You got
me on all fours
On my hands and knees
Just take me for a walk
Drew: Look. It's delicious.
(lyrics) Get me off of my feet
You make me feel like a dog
(instrumental music)
You make me feel like a frog
Like a prince [unintelligible]
You make a grown man wild
You make a grown man a child
You make me feel something new
I could learn from you
Just give me all your mind
(Spanish speaking shows on
TV - Marta pounding mat)
News reporter: Gracias Juan.
Although local and federal
law enforcements won't
offer up many details
on the investigation
they do say that
this human trafficking ring
may involve over 35 countries.
Agent Eddie Granger:
What we're looking at
is as an exploitation
scandal, uh, that is
more complex and
more sadistic, um,
than any that we've
encountered here
in the United States of
America on U.S. soil.
Um, so the citizens ...
(Doorbell rings)
which we hold dear, we
are working diligently -
Kamal: Excuse me sir.
So sorry to bother you on
this glorious day, but -
Drew: Kamal? Drew DeLaney.
Emily Dickinson High?
Mr. Martineau's history class?
Come on man! We made
that Vietnam video.
Kamal: Yeah, Drew. Right?
Drew: Yeah.
Kamal: Yeah, I'm sorry.
I guess I didn't recognize you
with a shirt and the
tie, it's corporate.
Um, you've done pretty
well for yourself.
Drew: Oh! This house?
Actually it belongs
to Lance Bryant.
Kamal: Who is that?
Drew: You don't know
who Lance Bryant is?
Kamal: (nods no)
Drew: Anyway, if nothing
goes wrong while I'm here
he's going to give me a job.
Kamal: Really.
Kamal: Nice. House
sitting full time?
Drew: Uh, no, probably
more like, you know,
being his trusted
right hand man.
Kamal: Right hand man?
Kamal: Oh, I get
it. Right hand man.
Drew: No. You've
grown up so much.
Kamal: Right hand
man you're gonna ...
Drew: Don't, no, just don't.
Kamal: He's a powerful man.
Kamal: Powerful men need a hand.
Drew: How do you like it?
Drew: You like it.
Kamal: You got speed, speed.
Drew: How does that feel?
Drew: Job training. Right?
You're training from
a right hand man now.
Kamal: What are you digging for?
Delivery Guy: Now don't
stop on my account.
Love that shit!
You're lucky I'm
working. Especially you.
Anyway, who lives here?
Drew: I do. I mean
for the time being.
Delivery Guy: I
need a signature.
Drew: Sure. Yep.
Uh, so you, I guess
you could put it, uh,
right in here if you want.
Delivery Guy: Nah!
That's where it stops.
I don't haul shit.
(ominous music)
Drew: Hey man.
Hey you mind maybe giving
me a hand with this?
We just got to carry it,
carry it around back.
Just take about five minutes.
Kamal: I don't know.
I still got a lot
of houses to hit.
Drew: Yeah, sure. I
totally understand.
Come back later maybe.
Swing back around. Yeah.
Kamal: Um, good luck with
the house sitting though.
Drew: Yeah, should
be, should be fun.
Kamal: Yeah.
Drew: It was cool
seeing you man.
Kamal: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Drew: It's been a long time.
Kamal: Cool. Good luck.
Drew: Thanks man. You too.
Drew: 10 speeds?
Drew: 21. Wow. Do you
use, like, all of them?
Drew: Oh my gosh man.
Kamal: Yeah.
Drew: So what's in the case?
(chop)
Drew: Whoa!
Kamal: SlicePro is top
of the line cutlery.
Won the Bronze at the
Homemakers Expo in '98,
then again in '02.
The shits legit.
Drew: It seems very sharp.
Kamal: So how much should
I put you down for?
The extended chefs arsenal?
Perhaps the nuclear
family traditional set?
Hey, either way.
I'll throw in a pair of scissors
that can cut through a penny.
On the house.
Drew: Thanks man, but I just,
I just can't really afford
any right now, you know.
Maybe if I get this
job I can totally -
Kamal: Playing hard ball, huh?
All right. How about this?
I'll throw in the fish
that you've been looking at
that opens bottles.
Huh? Life of the party here.
I work on 100%
commission, you know.
Drew: Hey why don't you,
why don't you hang
out for a while man?
I've got this huge place
all to myself, you know,
we could grab a drink,
reminisce about the old days.
Kamal: Nah, I better not man.
Drew: Come on Kam.
It will be fun.
Kamal: It's Kamal,
and I think I'm good.
Drew: Yeah. Yeah,
okay, yeah. Sorry man.
(dog steps)
Kamal: Was that a thong?
Drew: Yeah.
(ominous music)
Drew: The door was open man.
Drew: Mr. Baldwin.
Look at this mess man.
Drew: Do you leave the
door open? He told me -
Kamal: Holy shit!
Drew: What?
Kamal: I think there's
someone in there.
Drew: What are
you talking about?
(ominous music)
Drew: Holy shit.
Kamal: Are you fucking with me?
Drew: No, I though you
were fucking with me man.
Kamal: Why would
I fuck with you?
Drew: I was going to
ask you the same thing.
Kamal: Someone is
fucking with us.
Drew: Someone is
Kamal: Why the fuck
would a dead chick
get delivered
here. Right? Right?
I mean this is Lance
Bryant's house. Yeah?
Drew: Yeah.
Kamal: And there's no
way that a dead chick
would get delivered here.
Drew: No.
Drew: It doesn't make sense.
Kamal: It doesn't
make any sense at all.
Drew: There's no way
it's a dead chick.
Drew: It's a dead chick.
Drew: Who do you think she is?
Kamal: You want to check
her for ID be my guest.
Drew: Lance told me
to keep an eye out
for something, something
that might raise eyebrows.
Kamal: Consider my
eyebrows fucking raised.
Drew: He figured
a woman was coming
to stay with him,
but he was so vague.
You know he called
it, he called it
an international arrangement.
Kamal: Sounds like a
mail order bride to me.
Drew: Is that what this is?
Kamal: How long do
you know this guy?
Drew: Uh, I mean he
comes into the store
like, once a month, you know,
to buy a bunch of stuff.
Kamal: So not very
well then. Huh?
Drew: Well I mean
we usually chit-chat
while I load things
into his car.
Kamal: Chit-chat. Jesus.
Drew: Well, it's longer
than a chit-chat.
Drew: It's like
conversations, we talk.
Kamal: It's a chit-chat man.
It's a chit-chat.
You chit-chat with this
guy and you don't know him.
Drew: It's like once a month
I talk to him for awhile.
Kamal: Yeah-yeah.
So you don't know him that well
and it's quite
possible that he could
be into some weird fucking shit.
Drew: No, Lance
Bryant is a legit guy.
Kamal: Yeah.
Drew: There's got to be a
reasonable explanation for this.
Drew: (sighs) Oh my God.
What are we going to do?
Kamal: We? Sorry man,
but this is your problem.
I got to get back to work.
Drew: Wait! You got
to help me with this.
We're friends.
Kamal: (laughs) Sure man.
Look, call the fucking police.
Let them sort it out, okay.
Drew: If I call the police
than Lance will get arrested.
Okay, no, he told
me to handle this
with a clear, focused
head is what he said.
If I screw this
up there's no way
I'm going aboard Team Lance.
You got to help me.
It's Team Lance Kamal.
(doorbell rings)
(Knocking)
(Doorbell rings)
Spencer: Hello.
Spencer: Hi.
Spencer: Hi. I'm here to see
Lance Bryant, if I might.
Drew: Lance isn't
home at the moment.
Spencer: Who are you?
Drew: We're his friends.
We're friends of Lance's.
Spencer: Friends?
Friends of Lance?
Drew: Yeah.
Spencer: You're both
friends of Lance Bryant?
Drew: Yeah. We're kind
of busy at the moment
so if you don't mind
maybe coming back later.
We're going to head back.
Spencer: Excuse me, excuse
me, excuse me, gentlemen,
but this is a
neighborhood watch zone.
And I happen to be
Lance's neighbor
so maybe it's
appropriate for me to let
the authorities know
you're inside of his house.
Kamal: Please by all means.
Drew: No, no, no.
(Knocking)
Drew: It's not, it's
not necessary, okay.
Look, we're just ... Lance,
Lance is on vacation.
Okay? And he asked me
to look after his place
until he gets back, that's all.
Neighbor: Well he never told me
anything about house sitters,
so you can imagine how -
Kamal: I'm not house
sitting, for the record.
Drew: I totally understand.
Spencer: Okay. Record.
Spencer: Okay. Well
I'm Spencer Shaw.
I live right down the street,
as I mentioned earlier,
so if you need anything
while you're here
just give me a jingle.
Drew: Great.
Drew: Oh doctor.
Spencer: That's
right. MD and PhD.
Spencer: I did them both.
Drew: Great. Good for
you. Congratulations.
That's a lot of work.
Spencer: Oh, and the mail. Yes.
I came to give Lance his mail
because unfortunately it gets
delivered to me by mistake.
We have dunderheads
running our postal service
here in the local area.
So there's not a
day that pretty much
doesn't go by where
there's postcards
or some periodicals of some kind
that gets mistakenly -
Kamal and Spencer: (Laugh)
Drew: Thank you for doing that.
That's so nice Dr. Shaw.
Thank you. It was
nice meeting you.
We'll see you around
the neighborhood
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Spencer: Oh, and by the way.
Just follow the exact sequence
that's on the card
that I gave you
number wise and my
phone will ring.
Drew: Wonderful.
Thank you. (sighs)
Drew: Oh man. We
got to move fast.
That guy is totally onto us.
Kamal: Us?
Kamal: Are you crazy?
This is all you.
Drew: What? He saw
you, too, Kamal.
Drew: So in his mind you're just
as connected to this as I am.
Kamal: Connected to what?
Drew. This.
Kamal: We didn't kill her.
We didn't box her
up and ship her.
We had nothing to do with this.
Think about it.
If we never would
have looked in the box
we never would
have known. Right?
Drew: Yeah.
Kamal: The best thing we can
do is pretend nothing happened.
Drew: Exactly. Yeah, Yeah.
We need to cover this up
and make a pact to go silent.
Kamal: What?
Drew: We seal the box back up.
Pretend like we saw nothing.
You know, just like you said.
Kamal: I didn't say that.
Drew: It's perfect.
You know, this way
Lance will never know
that I know and then
I still get the job.
Yeah. We just need
to find some tape.
(ominous music)
Drew: We need to figure
out another plan.
Kamal: No. I need to leave
and you need to call the cops.
Drew: I can't screw
Lance over like that.
Kamal: What if Lance isn't
as legit a guy as you think.
I mean, think about it.
Why does he pick you?
Some furniture store
clerk to watch his house.
And why on the weekend when he's
expecting something important
does he decide to get
up and leave town?
Drew: You're not
seriously suggesting
that I'm part of some?
Kamal: Conspiracy?
Kamal: I don't know,
but it's hard to ignore
the fucking facts.
Drew: Oh hang on. Hang on.
There are three basic
principles to success.
Okay, okay, okay.
Number one. Reason.
Number two. Focus. Nmber three
Kamal: Go fuck yourself.
Drew: Effort. Okay?
We follow Lance Bryant's
book and we'll be fine.
Drew: Number one. Reason.
Make an informed choice.
It's not how to use your
mother fucking time.
It's how to use it the best
mother fucking way possible.
Drew: Yeah? Okay. Okay.
So based on our situation
we need to go get a
new box for her. Yeah?
It's crazy, we're already
a third of the way done.
Kamal: Have you even
read that book man?
Drew: Okay. Let's
do it. I'll drive.
Shit! Hey Marta.
Marta: Mr. Drew I
clean master suite now.
Drew: Actually can you
clean it later? Maybe?
Just a little bit later.
Like maybe in two hours.
Marta: No, Mr. Lance
will not be happy
if I don't clean
master suite now.
Drew: Right now. I get that
and you can totally clean it.
Just not, just not
right now, you know,
so maybe you can go
clean something else
for a while and then come back.
Marta: I must clean now.
Marta: No-no. It's not
on your time. Okay?
Marta: (speaking in Spanish)
Drew: I don't speak
Spanish Marta.
That's not the [unintelligible]
Five minutes?
Can you go clean something
else for a while?
And then come ...
Kamal: It's cool.
We're finished.
Drew: Uh yeah. We're finished.
Marta: (mumbles in Spanish)
Drew: What the fuck
[unintelligible]
Kamal: Follow me.
Marta: (grumbling in Spanish)
Kamal: I had to act fast.
I'm thinking we should find
a better place for her.
Somewhere out of the sun.
Drew: Yeah.
Kamal: Don't you want to
know how I got her out here?
Drew: No.
(Music)
Girl Scouts: Wanna
buy some cookies?
Drew: What did you
say little girls?
Girl Scouts: Wanna
buy some cookies?
Drew: Uh, sure,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'd love to buy some cookies.
Um, wow. Okay, great, um,
I'll take them all. So that's -
Okay. So here you go.
That's for you. Okay thank you.
Great. Uh, thank you.
Kamal: Experiment in college.
I didn't get two.
(garage door closes)
(Marta thumping mat)
Kamal: How long do
we have to wait?
Drew: Until she's gone, I guess.
Kamal: Well then, I'm
going to have a beer.
Kamal: Not even a little
something to take the edge off?
(thumping)
Drew: I've got work to do man.
Kamal: I think we've
earned one drink.
(thumping)
Drew: Yeah okay. This is it.
(Rock music)
(somber music)
Drew: Kamal? Kamal?
Drew: (alarm goes off)
(beeping - alarm squealing)
(alarm stops - phone ringing)
Kamal's voice: You've
reached Kamal with SlicePro!
Leave a message. (Beep)
Drew: Yeah. Hi Kamal. It's Drew.
Drew DeLaney. Do
you remember me?
Uh, you were here at
Lance Bryant's house.
Yeah, you were going to help me
with an extremely
unfortunate situation
we found ourselves in.
You remember that?
Uh, well, I just wanted to call
and say thanks for nothing.
Yeah. I'm not sure
if you've heard,
but, friends don't ditch
friends. (doorbell ringing)
Not how it works.
(doorbell ringing)
So, good luck with your
crappy job (knocking)
selling crappy knives to crappy
people (doorbell ringing)
that I'm sure I'll be stuck
doing something equally crappy
since you left me high
and dry with this.
Uh, hope to never see
you around again Ass.
Okay, best wishes, Bye.
(doorbell ringing)
Drew: Uh!
Barry: Mr. Bryant?
Drew: Uh, well I'm ...
Barry: Vault Home Security.
Drew: Uh, great.
Look, I think I ...
Barry: Is everything
all right in there?
Your panic alarm was triggered.
Drew: Yeah, and everything
is fine. Thank you.
Barry: Mind if I take
a quick poke around?
Drew: Well yes, it's not
really the best time.
You know, it's fine.
I mean, I'm pretty sure
I set it off myself,
so nothing to worry about.
Barry: Quite possible sir,
but better safe than sorry.
That's the Vault
Home Security motto.
Drew: I understand
it's your job,
but this is completely
unnecessary.
Barry: Unnecessary?
The sudden power loss
55 and a half seconds
after the alarm was
triggered suggests
that the intruder cut
the power from your home.
Now, this is your
home. Correct sir?
Drew: That's what I've
been trying to tell you.
Barry: Now you
wouldn't want your home
invaded and you BTK'd
while you slept.
Would you?
Drew: BTK'd?
Barry: Bind, Torture, Kill.
Now is that what you want sir?
Because if that is what you want
then I'll pack up my
stuff and I'll go.
Didn't think so.
Now, if you'll let me continue
until everything is clear
I'll be out of your hair
in no time. (trips) Sheez!
(garage door opening)
Drew: I think everything
is fine really.
Barry: Shhh.
They like to hide in garages.
Drew: Who likes to
hide in garages?
Barry: I don't want to impart
that dark knowledge onto you.
Unless you never
want to sleep again.
(ominous music)
Barry: Holy shoot!
Is this yours sir?
Drew: Listen man
it's a long story.
Barry: If this is yours,
then I'd like to
shake your hand.
I tell you I'm a
sucker for these
old vintage photo booths.
When I said sucker I mean
"obsessive freak." (laughs)
Yeah, Jerry and I, we always
say if we win the lotto
we're going to go on a
road trip and we're going
to find 50 of these from every
state in God's good nation.
Drew: Sounds cool,
yeah. Who's Jerry?
Barry: Jerry? My brother.
You know, he works
the nightshift.
Drew: Of course, yeah.
Barry: Oh come on. You've
got to have seen Jerry.
People say we look a lot
alike, which we don't.
I'm easier on the eyes. (laughs)
Yeah, it's always been
a dream, you know.
To have 50 of these
lovely ladies.
Clean them up, you know,
make them something real nice.
Drew: Yeah, got to have dreams.
Barry: Oh yeah.
Say, you're looking
to sell this baby?
Drew: NO! NO!
Barry: Geez louise!
Yeah, I get it. It's a beaut.
No reason to sell,
but no reason to yell.
Yeah. Could use a
little scrub though.
Drew: Yeah.
Drew: What? Oh yeah, those
are just some friends
that's consensual
everyone's kind of
[unintelligible] before
handabout the parameters
of [unintelligible]
Barry: All right sir.
The garage appears to be clear.
Drew: Good, uh, great, uh,
so thank you for securing it.
Barry: It's my job
and I know you might feel safe,
but remember if a sick
psycho wants to get inside
he can if he really wants to.
(trips) (laughs) Whoa!
That was a close one.
I tell you, sir, if I had a
dime for every time I (falls)
Drew: Shit man!
Oh God. You okay?
(sighs) You just got the
wind knocked out of you
that makes you kind of -
(leaking sound - ominous music)
Drew: Oh! Oh! Oh! No!
(phone ringing)
Kamal's voice: You've
reached Kamal with SlicePro.
Leave a message. (Beep)
Drew: Hey again, Kamal.
Sorry to bother you,
but listen we have
a problem here.
Um, rather a second problem.
Um, actually the first
one is completely missing,
you know, so maybe
we only have one
to deal with now, that
would be good. Right?
Or maybe not. Um,
anyway I'm not, uh,
not really sure what to do here
so just call me back
please. Oh my God!
(ominous music)
(dog bell tinkling)
(footsteps)
(ominous music)
Allan: Lance Bryant?
Drew: Whoa! (coughs) Holy shit.
It is a pleasure to
make your acquaintance.
Drew: Yeah, that's great, uh,
but I'm not, I'm not Lance.
Allan: You're not Lance Bryant?
Drew: No.
Allan: This is what
you're telling me.
Drew: Look, this, this
is Lance, this picture
it's the guy with
the horse head on.
I'm pretty sure
that's his torso.
I don't why the
(breathing heavy) yeah.
My name is Drew.
I'm just kind of
taking care of things
while he's out of town.
Allan: You haven't seen or heard
anything about, uh,
a girl. Have you?
Drew: Uh?
Allan: A young girl who
may or may not have been
here in one form or another.
Drew: Wait a
second. Who are you?
And why, why are you here?
Allan: Who I am
is not important.
How I got in here is
even less important.
What is important is
that a very important man
is looking for his very
important granddaughter
who he believes Lance Bryant
has been in contact with.
Drew: Well, um, yeah I don't,
I don't know anything
about a granddaughter.
Allan: If she, or Lance Bryant,
come by while you're here
this very important
man that I speak of
would see to it that
you're handsomely rewarded.
If you would provide him
with helpful information.
Use this to do so.
Drew: Plateau Pines
Retirement Community.
Allan: He will make you an offer
you will not excuse, refuse.
He will make you an offer
you will not refuse.
Vik: Well?
Allan: Your granddaughter
isn't in there.
Lance Bryant isn't in there.
Vik: What do you mean?
Lance Bryant wasn't in there?
Allan: Some other guy was,
Drew something. He said
Lance Bryant is out of town.
This is Lance Bryant.
Vik: I hate to think what that
deviant would do
with my Katrina.
All right, all right,
we'll, we'll wait.
We'll sit here and
wait for my Katrina
or for that sick son
of a bitch to show up.
Even if it takes all night.
Allan: Boss, I got to have
the fun bus back by three.
Vik: Oh all right, all right,
Jesus Christ let's take it back.
We'll come back after
dark. All right?
Let's get moving.
Traffic is going to be a cunt.
(drives away)
Kamal: Drew! Drew! I'm back.
Kamal: What the fuck?
Why did you put her in there?
Drew: I wish I had. It
would make more sense.
(dog barking)
Kamal: I guess it
could be worse.
(open shed door - ominous music)
Kamal: Should have
thought of this sooner.
We should call the cops.
Drew: Are you crazy?
Did you see the guy in the shed?
Kamal: Yeah, and that
was an accident. Right?
Drew: Yeah.
Kamal: Then what's the problem?
Drew: You know maybe
if you were here
instead of out selling knives
on your little bicycle
you might have
seen what happened.
Kamal: Well, take it easy man.
I was trying to
solve the problem
that we discussed last night
or were you too blacked
out to remember?
Drew: No, I had like four beers.
I wasn't blacked out.
Kamal: Four beers, right.
Drew: Yeah four beers.
Kamal: Uh-hum, you
had four more beers
and then you had
four more beers.
Drew: Nope.
Kamal: And then you
had all those shots
to go with each and
every one of those beers.
Drew: I think, I think,
I think I remember.
(phone ringing)
Kamal: Yep. Uh yeah.
Yes sir. Uh, one second.
Drew: Hello.
Spencer: Drew. Who
the fuck was that?
Drew: Uh, hey Mr. Bryant, Lance.
It was, it was no one.
Lance: What the fuck
you mean? No one?
Don't fuck with me.
Who the fuck is in my house?
Drew: It's no big deal,
just some door-to-door
knife salesman.
Kamal: Junior sales associate.
Spence: You know what?
Go get the pellet gun
and shoot that bitch.
Drew: I don't know Lance.
He seems like a
good guy, you know.
Lance: Of course he
seems like a good guy.
Bitch probably works
on 100% commission.
Get the pellet gun
and shoot his ass.
Drew: You know what?
I think he's actually leaving.
Um, so yeah, I wouldn't
want to waste a pellet.
So nothing to worry about.
Spencer: No, no, no,
it's not all good.
Success suckers need
to learn a lesson.
Shoot him. Damn it!
Shoot his ass now Drew.
Drew: (shoots Kamal)
Spencer: There
you go. Good work!
Now listen. That hot little
package come for me yet?
Drew: Uh, no.
Spencer: Damn.
Might have slipped by
with everything else
that shows up at the house.
Drew: No, no. I'm pretty sure
we would have noticed
something that special.
Spencer: We? Who the fuck is we?
Drew: Uh, me and Mr.
Baldwin, you know.
The only two people here.
Spencer: Mr. Baldwin
is not a person Drew.
Drew: Yes sir. Mr.
Baldwin is not a person.
Spencer: Listen, you just
keep your eye out. OK?
And if she shows up
you just toss her
in the master suite.
Hell, for that matter,
even in the garage is fine.
Ha, you know, she can't
complain. (laughs)
Anyway, I am about to go
and get my wine tasting on Drew.
I will talk to you tomorrow.
(ominous music)
Drew: What the fuck
are we going to do?
Kamal: Lucky you didn't
break the skin asshole.
Drew: We need to
[unintelligible]
Kamal: I need to pull
up my ass out of here
before you shoot me again
you fucking lunatic.
Pretty good. Huh?
Lance doesn't know what the
original box looks like.
She could have come in
these styrofoam coolers
just as easily as
the cardboard box.
Drew: Okay, there's no way she's
fitting in one of these things.
Kamal: Yeah, but
she'll fit in both.
I know you weren't impressed
by my SlicePro demonstration,
but trust me the
blades are legit.
By my calculations
it will take, like,
5 to 10 minutes to
completely slice her body.
Drew: Okay, Okay, Okay.
I get it. I get it.
Yeah, and that's exactly
what we shouldn't do.
Kamal: Why not?
If we don't do something
we're the ones who are
going to be fucked.
Drew: No Lance, Lance
won't let that happen.
Not if we, not if we
take care of this,
like, rationale and
civilized human beings.
Not like this.
Kamal: Drew, Lance doesn't
give a fuck about you.
Drew: Okay, Okay.
Number two. Focus.
Okay. Aim for
something specific.
Impatience is the forerunner
of mother fuckin' failure.
(closes book)
Drew: These coolers
are an impatient move.
Okay? So, so we'll get
her back into the garage
and together we'll go find
something that actually works.
Kamal: I'm telling you man.
A box that size that
isn't already filled
with a refrigerator
or a water heater
is impossible to find.
Drew: You probably didn't check
a furniture store. Did you?
I'm not saying it's
your fault, or anything,
it's just, it just
takes a certain mindset
to achieve success.
Kamal: What the fuck is
that supposed to mean?
Drew: Well it means
like back in school,
for example, you
know, you typically
settled for the easiest
way out of things.
You know, I mean,
you transferred.
Things got difficult
and you transferred
and I'm not saying
it's your fault.
It's just, it's just
the way you're wired.
Kamal: The way I'm wired?
What about you man?
What about you jumping
ship on your fucking job?
You don't fucking
get it. Do you?
Fuck you man.
This is your fucking problem.
Drew: Seriously? Oh my God.
(Music)
(car doors shut)
(footsteps)
(knocking)
(Music)
Drew: (grunting)
Katie: DREW!
(Music)
Katie: Drew!
Drew: (sighs)
[unintelligible] (sighs)
(Music)
Katie: What the fuck?
(plunk)
(shuts car door - squish)
(knocking)
Kamal: Oh hey, you're a ...
Spencer: Spencer Shaw.
Spencer: That's right.
We met earlier.
Spencer: Yes, and you're
one of the young gentlemen
that's house sitting for Lance.
Is that right?
Kamal: Oh no. I'm
not house sitting.
I'm never house
sitting over there.
Spencer: That's right,
of course, of course.
Then it was your friend
that's watching his place?
Kamal: Look, Drew
is not my friend.
Spencer: Really? I wasn't
under that impression.
I thought the two of
you were peas in a pod.
Kamal: No, we never were.
Spence: Well then,
what brings you by ...
Kamal: Kamal.
Spencer: Kamal. Excellent name.
Kamal with a K. Uh,
[unintelligible] yes,
Those who tribal
among the mountains
see themselves
within themselves.
What brings you by
Kamal? A box. (laughs)
Drew: What the fuck
am I going to do?
(phone ringing)
Drew: (breathing heavy)
Katie: So, you'll
invite other girls
to this swanky ass
pad you're watching,
but not your own
girlfriend. Huh?
Drew: What are
you talking about?
Katie: Who the fuck is she dude?
Drew: Who's who?
Katie: The geisha
slutty anorexic slut
who's probably still strung out
on your goddamn couch.
Drew: Anorexic geisha slut?
Katie: You know what I mean.
I thought that we
were good, you know,
were on the good path.
Drew: Listen, can we, can we
just talk about this later?
It's just I'm in the middle
of fixing something major
right now and I could
lose out on much more
than the job if I don't
figure it out quickly.
Katie: No, that's fine. You go.
No-no, you just go, you
go and you do this shit,
okay and you just,
you get the job.
You, you know, you'll
just have, you'll have
plenty of time to
devote to Lance
without me inconveniencing you.
Drew: Can we maybe
talk about this
when you're not drunk?
Katie: Fuck you. Fuck
you fuckin' Drew, you -
Drew: (sighs)
Drew: Where the hell
is he getting this?
Agent Granger:
[unintelligible] corsets.
Sorry. Did I startle you?
Seemed like I
startled you there.
Nobody was answering
the front door
so I just thought I'd
come around the side gate.
I hope that's okay Mr. Bryant.
Drew: I'm not Lance Bryant.
How many times do I
have to tell you people?
Agent Granger: How
many of us people
have been by here already?
Drew: Wait. Who,
who are you exactly?
Agent Granger:
Exactly? Edwin Granger.
Immigration and Customs.
Mr. Bryant on the premises?
Drew: Well, uh, Lance,
Mr. Bryant, is out,
out of town that is.
Agent Granger: Umm,
(claps) there it is.
How convenient. For
him, not for me.
Drew: Is he in some
kind of trouble?
Agent Granger: Has he mentioned
anything about a young woman?
Drew: Uh, no.
Spencer: Very impressive Kamal.
Very impressive indeed.
Kamal: Yeah, SlicePro
does not fuck around.
Spence: No, it does
not fuck around.
It's not fucking around
in my hand. Is it?
Kamal and Spencer: (laughing)
Spencer: That feels
so good. (chop)
So tell me.
What is it that you and Drew
Kamal: What?
I'm just curious. I have
a curious bone in me.
Two young men in that house.
All that luxury at
your fingertips.
All the opulence.
Kamal: You know, I can throw in
a pair of scissors that
can cut through a penny.
Spence: (chop) You've
done it again Kamal.
I'll take it. All the
knives and the case.
Kamal: No shit.
Spencer: But before we settle up
I'm going to need to medicate.
Kamal: Medicate?
Drew: Human trafficking.
Agent Granger: Yeah, but
not your run of the mill
hop on the pick-up over the
border kind of bullshit either.
We're talking ... I
can't get into details,
but I'm just going
to tell you this
it's a global
trafficking organization
that specializes in
sexual exploitation.
Are you familiar
with sex slavery?
Drew: You mean like
mail order brides?
Agent Granger: No, I don't
mean mail order brides.
Mail order brides they enter
that stuff in by choice.
Companies like ForeignFlames.com
are actually sanctioned.
They got sponsors.
They got a website
and a web master.
I'm talking about women,
children, and men,
men like you and me having sex
against our free will.
You and I in a room
performing Caesar salad
on the side add the chicken.
If you know what I mean?
That's a position.
That's an elicit position
that's very common now
and has been since 1997.
Drew: No way. Not,
not, not Lance.
No, he's a pillar
of the community.
You know, on the "Forty
under 40" list, twice.
Agent Granger: Huh!
Fifth grade merit badge.
Ninth grade, I put a salamander
into a microwave oven.
People change.
Spencer: Are you
enjoying my robe?
Kamal: It's quite nice.
Spencer: Please partake.
Kamal: No, I probably shouldn't.
Spencer: You probably should.
It's grade A Kamal.
It's very medicinal.
You see as a professor at
a top tier medical school
I'm awarding certain,
um, best to say this,
benefits, no, no, boons rather
that other people like
yourself aren't accustomed to.
So please, please partake.
Allow me. Yes, very good Kamal.
That's it. Now
it's working well.
Very good yes.
Kamal: (coughs)
Spencer: Very good.
[unintelligible]
Now, where were we?
Oh, I remember.
You were telling me
what you were doing
over at the house.
Kamal: Was I?
Spencer: Yes, you were.
Spencer: Yes you were.
You see from my place very
difficult for me to see,
but I thought, I
thought possibly
that you might have
had company over there.
Kamal: Company?
Spencer: Yes company.
That's right.
Tick-tock you're fine.
Company. That's right.
You see I have a poor
vantage point from my place.
But I thought possibly,
just possibly you might
have had a young woman
over at the house.
Kamal: (feels sick)
Spencer: Oh-oh,
oh-oh, all right now.
Drew: What is this?
Agent Granger: That
was a wire transfer
from Lance's account to
an account in the Ukraine.
And you know what the
Ukraine's chief exports are?
Weapons grade plutonium and
hot white pasty Euro ass.
Drew: Looks, looks
like a lot of figures.
Agent Granger: Yeah, yeah,
people with a lot of figures
tend to do a lot of
questionable things.
Look, I'm not saying that
Lance is involved directly
I'm just saying that somebody
very close to him may be.
What's the old saying go? Hmm?
Good friend help you move,
great friend help you
move a body. Exactly.
He's a powerful man.
He's got a lot of pull.
You have him call me
when he gets back. OK?
By the way, um, do
you have anybody
who can stay with you
while you're here?
You know, if Lance is involved
with what we think
he is involved with,
there is no telling
who might turn up here.
You know, like a good
friend you can trust?
Drew: Yeah, I don't, I
don't really have anyone.
Agent Granger: Yeah,
I didn't think so.
Spencer: (claps hands)
Look, I'm prying.
I shouldn't be prying.
Kamal: You shouldn't be prying.
Spencer: No, I
shouldn't be prying,
but I do want to remind you
this whole area here
everything here,
this is a neighborhood, hey,
this is a neighborhood
watch zone.
Kamal: Huh! You're the neighbor?
Spencer: I'm the
neighbor. (laughs)
Look at me the
big neighbor here.
I'm the neighbor
and I want to know
who she was and how she ended up
on your doorstep?
Now I'm not saying that
she came there for you.
I'm not even saying
that you knew
that she came in the
first place. Uh-hum.
It's clear to me that Drew
is the one that's in charge.
Kamal: Drew's an asshole.
Spencer: Yes he is.
Kamal: Mother fucker.
Spencer: Mother fucker.
Kamal: Mother fucker
is one cold bastard.
Spencer: One cold bastard.
What are you saying Kamal?
Are you saying that Drew
is capable of cold,
unspeakable acts?
Kamal: Shit yeah.
The guy is heartless.
Nothing is good enough for him.
Nobody is worthy of
being in his presence.
Spencer: Hmm, a cowboy.
You're saying
there's a little bit
of a cowboy in him.
Are you telling me that
the basic fundamental principles
of life don't apply to him?
Kamal: Principles?
Spencer: Principles.
Kamal: I could go on
about the principles.
Spencer: Go on about
the principles.
Look at you. You're distraught.
There's a war raging
inside of you right now.
You've got to battle it.
[unintelligible] teaches
us that in our inner self
that there is a
war, a raging battle
we need to free ourselves.
Free yourself.
What were you doing
in the house Kamal?
Yes, the battle.
Kamal: War
Spencer: Yes, tell me
what you were doing
inside of the house, Kamal?
Yes, Kamal, yes.
Kamal: I got to puke.
Spencer: Not on my robe.
(footsteps)
(Music)
Drew: OW!
(knocking)
Spencer: Kamal, how
are you feeling?
I have a fine, fine cup of
Earl Grey with your name on it.
Kamal (hisses)
Drew: (blinded and stumbles)
(ominous music)
Drew: Marta. Oh,
Marta. Oh my God.
Oh, not you too. Marta
(crying hysterically)
Marta: I don't
know what happened.
[unintelligible] Please
don't tell Mr. Lance.
My children, I
have many children.
I promise Mr. Lance not
to sleep no more at work,
but my children.
I have many children.
I get sleepy. Please.
Drew: (Sighs)
Everybody, everybody
around me is just dropping,
you know, Marta, they're
just dropping like flies
like everyone I'm
close to they're just,
they're just leaving
me and I saw you
and I thought what -
I'm so fucked right now Marta.
Everything is completely
falling apart.
Everything I've tried
it just fucks up,
you know, I'm so fucked.
I'm such a fuck. (crying)
Marta: It's going
to be okay Mr. Drew.
It's going to be
okay. Get up. Get up.
Drew: I'm too much
of a fuck. (crying)
Marta: Sometimes you
must break things apart
in order to put
it back together.
I must do sometimes
with the toilet
when it clogs up with crap.
Drew: The crap? Huh? What?
Marta: Yeah today. I
have to clog it up.
Drew: Oh.
Marta: It's okay, it's okay.
You gonna be okay.
Drew: It's okay Marta.
I'm good. I'm good.
(Music - birds singing)
Kamal: Hey man.
It's pretty fascinating. Huh?
Kamal: Yeah, "War Maiden."
Spencer: Huh?
Kamal: The name of the
movie we shot in school.
It was "Apocalypse Now"
meets "Breakfast Club,"
is how we pitched it.
Drew: That's right.
(laughs) Man.
Kamal: The death
scene off the roof?
Classic.
Drew: Yeah, I saw scars
from those homemade squibs.
It sucks you left man.
Could have made a
ton more of those.
Kamal: Do you even know
why I transferred Drew?
You remember when
you and your friends
fucked with my family.
Chris Arnold, Bobbie
Barnes, Brett Kendle.
I know you were with them.
Drew: I was 15.
Kamal: We were best friends.
Do you even know what it's
like to be stabbed in the back?
Drew: I'm sorry man. I am.
If I had known how much
that, that hurt you
I, I would have ...
Kamal: Yeah.
Drew: Those guys were a
bunch of fucking dicks man.
I don't know why I
hung out with them.
I, I'm sure they've all
gained about 100 pounds.
Kumal: Yeah, 150 pounds.
Drew: Yeah, probably
still all hanging out.
Kamal: Probably.
Drew: Probably still
going to the high school
football games on
Saturdays [unintelligible]
Kamal: (laughs) (sighs)
Drew: Look man I
think you actually
might be right about Lance.
He's just, it's just
nothing adds up,
you know, him leaving
town and all these
random people stopping by.
This whole thing has
gotten so out of control.
Kamal: Yeah, but it's
your dream job man.
Drew: There's other
jobs, you know.
The point is a job
with Lance isn't going
to mean anything if I
end up going to jail.
Kamal: So what are you saying?
Drew: I'm saying let's do it.
Your way this time.
Kamal: Sure?
Drew: Yeah, I, I can't
do it without you.
Kamal: So the third and final
principle of success is effort.
No one gets nowhere
without 120% effort.
Take the the biggest
and best shots possible.
Go big or go the fuck home.
Drew: Just tell
me how to proceed.
Kamal: First off, I'm going to
need you to prep the stables.
Drew: Prep it for what?
Kamal: Blood Drew.
The're going to
be a lot of blood.
While you're doing that
I'll be prepping the tools.
We're going to need the
best to pull this off.
SlicePro. Like I
said, the shits legit.
(sharpening knives)
(Music)
Kamal: We'll need to burn
everything that isn't flesh.
Anything physical that can
connect back to them we burn.
Drew: [unintelligible] we
chopped up we can't burn those.
Kamal: Got to
dispose of it here.
Drew: How?
(Music)
(ominous music)
Kamal: You can do this man.
Just let the blades do the work.
(thump from knife)
Dead Girl: Screams
Kamal: Did you hear me?
Just let the blades do the work.
Drew: Yeah, yeah. Let
the blades do the work.
(ominous music - chopping)
(ominous music)
Spencer: Uh!
Vik: Uh, we don't know
what's going on inside there.
Here, we better go in heavy.
Allan: Heavy?
Vik: Heavy.
When are you going to understand
the fucking' lingo Allan?
This isn't Shakespeare.
You want me to say weaponry?
(chopping and hammering)
Kamal: Dude, everything okay?
Drew: Yeah, yeah,
everything's fine.
Kamal: I hate to bring you down,
but we got a problem.
Mr. Baldwin won't eat.
Drew: What?
Kamal: Yeah and he's being
a real picky bitch about it too.
Drew: Oh wait. I think
I know what to do.
(Sighs) Fuck. (Sighs)
Mmmm. You don't know what
you're missing Mr. Baldwin.
It's so good Mr. Baldwin.
You don't know what
you're missing man.
(gagging) That's
great. Right Kamal?
Kamal: Uh.
Drew: (gagging) So good.
Kamal: Oh, Mmmm, Oh
yeah, I've never had
such divine human before.
Drew: Mmmm, so tender, juicy.
You should try it
Mr. Baldwin. Come on.
Mr. Baldwin: (Eating)
Drew: There you
go. Good, good boy.
Oh thank God. Oh fuck.
Kamal: It's so nice in my hands.
Drew: Dude you can stop.
He's eating, he's
eating, come on.
Drew: Okay, so we'll
have a drink while
Mr. Baldwin is eating.
Clean up anything left
and then call it a day.
(ominous music)
Katrina: Lance? Lance Bryant?
I here to make wife.
Drew: Oh.
Katrina: (Ukrainian) Katrina.
Drew: Can you, can you
give us a second? Please.
Just one second. Yeah.
What? Please, just
back up a little bit.
Um, just move, yeah just.
Kamal: We're not
talking about you.
Drew: Nope. Thank
you. What the fuck?
Kamal: If that's Lance's girl
who the fuck did we chop up?
Drew: I don't know man.
I should have called the
police to start with.
What the fuck was I thinking?
Kamal: What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm the one who wanted
to call the police.
You're the one
obsessed with this job.
Drew: I just wanted to box
her back up the way she was.
You're the one who
wanted to fuckin'
Now we dismembered her
body for no reason.
Kamal: Two actually.
Drew: Two bodies.
We're so fucked.
Kamal: No it's okay. We're okay.
Drew: How are we okay?
Kamal: We took care
of one girl. Right?
Drew: And the security guard.
Kamal: Any evidence is gone.
Drew: Yeah-yeah.
Kamal: And now
Lance's girl showed up
so we're golden.
Drew: How are we golden?
Kamal: We're clear man.
We never bring up the bodies.
Drew: Of course not.
Kamal: Lance gets his girl
and nobody goes to jail.
Everybody wins.
Drew: Yeah,
everybody wins, yeah.
Kamal: Now let's get back to her
before she dies of boredom
and we have to chop her up too.
Kamal: Twosome?
Kamal: Ready?
Drew and Kamal: Hi.
Katrina: Hello.
Drew: We have been
expecting you. Yeah?
Kamal: Yeah.
Katrina: Lance?
Drew and Kamal:
No, no, not Lance.
Katrina: Knwet?
Katrina: Lance?
Kamal: No, I'm not Lance either.
I really want to
be, but I'm not.
Drew: Um, oh, oh,
actually that's Lance.
Um, the man in the picture.
Katrina: Lance?
Drew: In the woods,
yep, that's Lance.
Kamal: Tak.
Drew: So Lance will
be here tomorrow.
Um, so you'll stay
the night here
and then tomorrow
you'll see Lance.
Kamal: You look thirsty sweetie.
You want some vodka?
Katrina: Vodka?
Katrina: Oh, tak.
Drew: Yeah, yeah.
Drew: Yeah, that's a great idea.
Um, so he, he's going
to take you to the bar
in the kitchen
and get you some -
Kamal: Vodka.
Katrina: Vodka? Lance?
Drew: No, he, Kamal will
and then I'll
carry your suitcase
down to the master suite.
Kamal: Yes. Oh, right
this way my lady.
Please we go.
We can talk about Gorbachev.
Drew: Nice to meet you Katrina.
Kamal: Oh, what is that red
spot on Gorbachev's head?
(Knocking and doorbell ringing)
Drew: Hi.
Woman: You live here?
Drew: No actually.
I'm just looking after the
place for the guy that does.
Woman: Okay. How
long you been here?
Drew: I guess this will
be my second night.
Woman: So you were
here yesterday?
Drew: Can I help
you with something?
Woman: These look familiar
you son of a bitch?
They're dollars.
Drew: Yeah.
Drew: Yeah, I see that
they're dollar bills.
Woman: Yeah.
Drew: Three of them.
Woman: These are the
exact dollar bills
that you used to
swindle my scouts
out of four boxes of thin mints.
Uh-huh, yeah, remembering now?
Four boxes that are
three-fifty each.
Drew: Huh! You're right.
I think you're right.
I'm sorry. I probably
miscounted. It was -
Woman: You think you can rip
off my girls, huh? (punches)
You think just
'cause they're girls
you can just ... your bad ass
can get a discount on some
cookies. (punches three times)
Yeah, uh-huh, somebody
order a pizza?
[unintelligible] on top of it.
Drew: Listen lady
it was a busy day.
I'm sorry. I wasn't thinking.
Woman: Yeah I appreciate
you calling me a lady.
I appreciate that, okay,
but you know what?
You weren't thinking.
You weren't thinking
that those troops
also had an amateur mixed
martial artist as a leader.
Woman: Throw down.
Drew: I didn't know that.
Drew: I didn't know
that. I'm sorry.
I haven't opened the
cookies yet. Okay?
I'm [unintelligible] for
you. There's three boxes.
You can take them with you.
Woman: You think I
want those cookies?
Look at me. Look at
me in the eyeballs.
I don't want your
fucking cookies.
Not after you had your
little hands over them
your little baby hands.
Did you ever work
a day in your life?
Those thin mints used
to have dazzle in them
now they got your little
baby hands on them.
Drew: Okay.
Woman: Your man juice.
Drew: Okay, okay, what
do you want from me then?
Woman: You know what I want?
Woman: I want you to pay
me back [unintelligible]
for those cookies
that you stole. Okay?
Yeah. Full reimbursement.
Plus you're going
to reimburse me
for the mileage
that it took for me
to drive my SUV all the way over
to this well-heeled
neighborhood.
Drew: That's not a problem.
Woman: Oh good. Good.
Shake your head yes.
Drew: My wallet is over there.
You can take whatever you want.
Woman: Good, good.
Drew: Then please leave.
Woman: I got a date
tonight with a guy.
Drew: Just take
the whole wallet.
Woman: All right, all right.
Woman: I got [unintelligible]
for that pussy.
Drew: Actually on second thought
you can go fuck yourself
and fuck your cookies too.
Because they taste like shit.
Woman: Oh, okay.
Woman: Okay, yeah, yeah.
Drew: Now listen. Turn around.
Drew: Walk out that door.
Woman: Okay, which way do I go?
Drew: Out the door. Okay?
Drew: Okay, you got it? (falls)
Woman: Yeah, I got it.
Woman: Yeah, you're saying
something about my cookies?
Drew: (grunting)
Vik: What the fuck
is going on here?
That, that, that piece of
shit you're stepping on
sister he belongs to me.
Woman:This piece of
shit owes me money.
Vik: He owes me a
lot more than that.
Woman: Yeah, well you're going
to have to wait in line gramps.
Vik: Uh, but I don't
like waiting in lines.
Now look, hon, I got to
ask this, this asshole
some questions about
my granddaughter.
Then you can have what's left.
Drew: Look man.
I don't know anything about
your granddaughter. OK?
I'm just the house sitter.
Vik: Oh, you're going
to lie to me now.
Vik: Fuck, I want to
know how you assholes
got possession of
my granddaughter.
Kamal: I already told
Jubakka over here
she showed up on her
own like 20 minutes ago
you fucking idiots.
Alan: Watch your mouth Gandhi.
Vik: Allan take it easy.
Agent Granger: All right.
Everyone freeze. DIC.
The house sitter
is coming with me.
Woman: Oh, what did
he do to screw you up?
Agent Granger: Does
it concern you?
I'm here for him
and Lance Bryant.
Katrina: Lance?
Vik: Look, look, look,
I don't know who you.
I don't know what you want,
but I need a little time
to have some conversation
with these two jerks here about,
about my granddaughter
and then you can do
whatever you want with them.
Agent Granger: Holy shit.
You're Victor Koslav.
aka Big Vik Koslav,
aka Big Bad Wolf Koslav
aka Wolf Face.
Vik: Yeah, yeah, yeah,
you heard about me. Huh?
Agent Granger: Yeah, thought you
were out of this game years ago.
Vik: I'm staging a comeback now,
but first I want
to get some answers
from these two idiots.
Agent Granger: Actually
Vik, you know what?
You're coming with me, too.
Vik: I don't think so.
Allan: Officer, we will make
you an offer you cannot refuse.
Vik: Allan.
Agent Granger: Let the girl go
and tell your man
to lower his weapon.
Vik: I can't go with you
because that was one of
my plans for a comeback.
Agent Granger:
Actually, you know what?
You're coming with me.
Everybody is going with me
into a big, fucking,
happy van downtown.
We're going to sort it all
out with [unintelligible]
What the?
Security Officer Jerry: Hey sir.
Agent Granger: Hey, hey.
Security Officer
Jerry: Who's to say
you even have jurisdiction
in these parts?
Agent Granger: I'm with
the federal government.
I have jurisdiction
in every part.
Security Officer Jerry:
Every suit tells me that.
Vik: Who the hell are you?
Security Officer Jerry:
Jerry, Vault Home Security.
Barry, my brother, he's
been missing all day.
While people don't say
we look a lot alike,
but we do we're
easy on the eyes.
Have any of you seen my brother?
Agent Granger: Tell you what.
How about you help me
wrangle these people. OK?
Then we can look for Jerry.
Security Officer Jerry: Barry.
Agent Granger: Have you
checked [unintelligible]
Security Officer Jerry:
Do you have a warrant?
Agent Granger: No.
Security Officer Jerry: Yeah,
you don't have a warrant.
All right. Since you
don't have a warrant
I'm going to have to ask you
to vacate Lance Bryant's house.
Marta: Mr. Lance no home now.
Vik: Who are you?
Marta: I clean your
room now Mr. Drew.
Oh, I clean later.
Agent Granger: That's
a good idea Miss.
We clean later.
Woman: Thought you
learned your lesson?
Drew: Fuck.
Agent Granger: Hey ma'am, I
need you to hold it right there.
Woman: Maybe I should
grab it myself.
And fuck off your
nut bag with it.
You know what?
Take you dick and shove it up
where your mom fuckin' put it.
Agent Granger:
Don't do that ma'am.
Ma'am do not touch that. MA'AM!
(gunshots)
Kamal: What the fuck was that?
Drew: I don't know man.
Kamal: Are you okay?
Drew: Yeah, fine. Are you?
Kamal: Yeah.
Kamal: Is it still
considered a Mexican shootout
if there aren't any
Mexicans involved?
Drew: What?
Kamal: I guess Marta
was here for a second.
Drew: (breathing heavy)
Agent Granger: You
guys want to tell me
what the fuck that was about?
Drew: Honestly, I have no idea.
Everyone showed up
at the same time
looking for someone
else and I don't know.
Agent Granger: Well the girl
she's with Lance. Right?
I mean she's here
with the sex ring
the whole time he's
involved in all that.
Drew: No, she was
here by choice.
I'm pretty sure.
She gave me this.
Agent Granger: Look, I'm
going to need a statement. OK?
I need you to come down
and make a statement
because if what you say is true
it would really help
in clearing Lance -
Drew: Behind you.
Agent Granger: (shoots Vik)
Drew: Oh, oh,
Agent Granger: You know what?
Fuck the statement.
Drew: Yeah, fuck the statement.
Agent Granger: I don't
need a statement.
Agent Granger: Yeah
because we're going to have
to take the fuckers off of
Lance right now so just -
Drew: (breathing heavily)
we'll just forget
about the statement.
Agent Granger: Yeah I know.
Kamal: You'll take
care of them, too.
Agent Granger: What?
Kamal: The bodies?
You'll take care
of the bodies too.
Agent Granger: Do I look
like a fucking warlock?
(Music)
Drew: All right.
Should probably start
prepping the stables.
Those bodies aren't going
to dismember themselves.
Kamal: Five more minutes.
Let's try and appreciate this
shit for five more minutes.
Drew: Yeah, you're
right. Five more minutes.
Spencer: Two-faced bastards.
Drew: Oh!
Spencer: Listen Kamal.
I thought you and
I were friends.
I thought you and I created
a special relationship.
Until I found this.
Uh-hum. I knew you were
keeping her from me.
I just knew it.
Kamal: We thought
she was Lances.
Believe me.
We totally would have gotten her
the fuck out of here if
we knew she was yours.
Trust me.
Drew: Yeah.
Spencer: Just because something
is delivered to you by mistake
that doesn't give you
the right to open it up.
Now Kamal knows
that I'm a professor
that's accustomed
to certain boons
or benefits rather
that aren't awarded to
other people easily.
One such is my
exclusive membership
to a harvested organ
exchange program.
Drew: A harvested what?
Spencer: Yeah, it may
not be 100% legal,
but raw cadavers are
prime for research.
And this woman died
of natural causes.
I assure you.
Then she donated
herself to science.
But she also cost
20 thousand dollars.
So gentlemen, please tell me
that you have her
well refrigerated.
Drew: Oh.
Kamal: Yeah, about that.
Spencer: What?
Drew: Well we really did it
with the best intentions.
Spencer: You did what?
Kamal: We chopped her up.
Drew: Fed her to Mr. Baldwin.
Spencer: You're telling
me you destroyed her.
You destroyed her. (sighs)
Guys you owe me 20 grand.
Drew: Oh.
Kamal: We don't have
that kind of money.
Spencer: Fine. Let's get
Lance to help you get it.
I'm sure he will
once I explain to him
what irresponsible house
guests you've been.
Kamal: Spencer you can't.
Drew would lose everything
if Lance ever found out.
Spencer: I don't give a shit.
Drew: Actually Kamal, I
think I have a solution.
Spencer: I don't
have time to waste.
Drew: Yeah, I think
you're going to be happy.
Will this do?
Spencer: Absolutely. Absolutely.
Guys you have no idea the
work I can do with these.
Come on in. (kisses them)
Come on in you guys.
You guys. Okay, I
got to get them home.
Get them on ice ASAP.
(Music - birds singing)
Kamal: Sure you don't
need me to stay?
Drew: Oh no, it's
cool man, okay.
I think I can probably
handle it from here.
Thanks Kamal.
Kamal: Kam.
Drew: Good seeing you man.
Kamal: You too man.
Kamal: You did it.
Kamal: (sighs) It's time
for me to sell these knives.
Drew: (chuckles)
I know you will.
Kamal: Yeah, talk soon.
Drew: Yeah.
Kamal: [unintelligible]
Drew: Oh! No!
Drew: I know it
all sounds crazy,
impossible even,
and if I were you
I'd have a hard time
believing it myself.
But I've changed from
this whole experience.
I really have.
At one time in my
life, back home maybe,
you could say I was
only a caterpillar
and on my journey
here I was in a cocoon
and I now I can confidently
say the cocoon has hatched.
I am now a butterfly.
A beautiful and fully
developed butterfly
that's ready to fly
and at the end of the day
I need [unintelligible]
so thank you Lance.
Your kind generosity
is what allowed me
to escape my sad,
unfulfilled existence,
one previously
destined for solitude,
a collision course, if you will,
threatened by peril and torture.
It's because of
you that my world
is suddenly wide open
with opportunity,
opportunity and freedom,
freedom from the
chains that bind me.
Like 911, I will never forget,
never forget what
you have done for me.
I know it isn't much,
but please in my
[unintelligible] accept my bag,
and the contents
within as a token
of my appreciation.
I feel like even
though they're not me
they'll be able to
adequately comfort you
while I explore this country
as I was meant to explore it.
Farewell for now Lance.
You'll forever be in my heart.
Love always, Katrina.
Spencer: Fuck.
Drew: You know I hate to say it,
but it's probably for the best
you weren't here
when she stopped by.
Spencer: You said she was
here for five minutes. Huh?
Drew: Yeah, yeah,
just long enough
to give me the letter
and the suitcase.
Spencer: Just hope she
finds whatever it is
she's looking for.
Drew: Yeah.
Spencer: Why don't you
come on by tomorrow?
We'll talk about what it is
you're going to do
for me full-time.
Because Team Lance
could use a reliable
mother fucker like you Drew.
Drew: (sighs) Thank
you Mr. Bryant.
Uh, I really
appreciate that, I do.
Uh, but I think I'm
going to ride it out
at the furniture store a
while longer, you know.
Spencer: You're not
even curious about what
you would be doing or what
Team Lance is all about.
Drew: I've got a pretty
good thing going right now.
I don't need to jump ship
for another one quite yet.
Spencer: Okay Drew.
You're all right.
I mean you're a
reasonable mother fucker.
Hear what I'm saying?
(Music)