Hey!
[Glass breaks]
[Line unwinding]
You stink!
[Crowd cheers]
Kill him!
Ohh.
You bum!
1...
2...
3...
Hit him!
Kill him!
Aah!
5...
6...
All right. Time's up.
You're killing him.
Ooh.
All right.
Ahhh.
Ahh. dinner.
Sure put up
a big fight
for such
a little guy.
Hey, don't give me
that sad look.
All right.
[Splash]
Don't tell any
of your friends
i did that.
Don't let me catch you
out here again.
What a sucker!
I see you still got
that killer instinct.
How'd you find me,
Burt?
I'm in the security
business now.
It's my job.
O.k., o.K., your mom
told me, all right?
I'm glad you're so
thrilled to see me
after all
these years.
Do you mind
if I make myself
comfortable
on this
filthy crate?
Suit yourself.
Look, I just
got a call
from a major,
major new client
looking for a bodyguard.
I thought of you first.
Forget it.
I'm not a bodyguard.
I'm a wrestler, o.K.?
Hey, wait, wa--
I am a wrestler.
I managed you
for 15 years.
Remember?
Or did you get
head-slammed
too many times?
Listen to me.
You'll make
some big bucks,
and it'll get you
out of the ring.
Forget it, Burt.
Still having
those nightmares?
Yeah, sometimes.
So why'd
you pick me?
'Cause I love you
like a son...
And nobody else
will work for me.
So what
did you do now?
Man, it's crazy.
You bounce a few checks,
and right away
you're a deadbeat.
Remember the time
in Reno
when the hotel
locked up our clothes
and I had to sneak
down the fire escape
in a towel?
Yeah! we had some
fun times then,
didn't we?
Nope.
I got a bum leg
since I took
a bullet
for some big
lunkhead.
Hey, wait. It was
meant for you,
wasn't it?
O.k.,
i owe you my life.
I still ain't
taking the gig.
Sure, you'd help
some slimy fish,
but the guy that
saved your life--
that's gratitude
for you.
Just forget it.
Let me explain
how it works.
Ahh.
Want to know my secret?
I cook it in the can.
Mmm.
Out of the can
and into the man.
How long's it been
since you ate?
Just a week.
Here.
Tell you what...
Fill in the amount
and pay me back
when you can.
I don't want
your damn charity.
I need a job,
not a handout.
If I get this gig,
I'm back in business.
One thing I still got,
my self-respect.
I ain't going to beg.
Yeah.
Although it always
worked before...
Hey, Sean, brother,
please, man.
Oh, man, you know
i hate that.
Help me. Help me.
Come on.
All right. All right.
I'll take the job.
Oh, man, this is
such an emotional moment.
So what else
you got to eat?
* I just wanna
go fishin' *
* in the deep blue sea *
* 'cause
i need a change *
* from my reality *
* this world
will beat you down *
* beat you
with a stick *
* you want
an ice cream pop *
* they give you
a boot to lick *
* I need some time *
* to sort out
all this mess *
* I gotta be
rough and ready *
* when they put me
to the test *
* call his bluff *
* baby, gonna
call your bluff *
* rough stuff *
* it's comin'... **
good morning,
Mr. Mason.
Morning, Jane.
Lose the gum,
thank you.
Uh, yes,
Mr. Mason.
Penny?
I found a typo
on page 649,
second paragraph,
fourth word in.
Frank,
where's the bodyguard?
He'll be here
in a second, sir,
and don't worry.
Security is
on full alert for any
suspicious intruders.
All units--
potential intruder,
main gate.
Roger. we copy.
Where do you
think you're going?
I'm looking
for Mr. Mason.
Is that so?
Get off the bike.
What for?
Just do it,
butthead!
Forget it.
Are you deaf
or just plain stupid?
I've got a low tolerance
for gorillas in
rent-a-cop suits.
Gorillas, huh?
Shouldn't
have done that.
Aah!
Hey, you!
This is the bodyguard?
A terrible mistake, sir.
I'll get rid of him
immediately.
Wrong. he's incredible.
Obviously a real pro.
So where's
Mason's office?
I bet you've been
a bodyguard for a long time.
You don't know
how long.
Here, I want
to show you something.
Aah!
Got him!
That's our new
head of security.
The man who hired you.
Oh, uh,
see who hit you?
[Telephone rings]
You o.K.?
This is Alex Mason.
Ah, Mr. Mason.
You've received
my message?
Yeah.
now who are you?
Oh, just your
average psychotic
criminal genius.
I desire
your new computer chip--
the one for
the peacefinder.
I told you
it's not for sale.
Everything's for sale.
The question is only
at what price.
You have 24 hours
to reconsider.
And do take care
of your lovely children.
[Click]
Should we call
the police?
Damn right.
This man
assaulted me!
Quiet. no police!
If word gets out about
this peacefinder project,
we'll have
every crackpot
after us.
What's the peacefinder
project?
I'm sorry.
That's top-secret.
I'm putting my life
on the line.
Tell me, or I'm gone.
Well, nice meeting you.
O.k., Sean, o.K.,
but you've got to
keep this strictly
confidential.
Know anything
about chips?
I'm a nacho cheese man
myself.
I was referring
to silicon chips.
He doesn't know
anything about chips, sir.
He's only the bodyguard.
I know a microchip
is a wafer
of the chemical element
silicon
serving as
a semiconductor
under which a series
of electrical circuits
are printed.
Very good.
Did you know
that the chip itself
costs only pennies?
But the information
on this one
is worth millions.
It's the only one
in existence.
You invented it?
No. I have
a company to run.
I was an inventor,
though.
I started this place
in my garage.
Come on.
This is a model
of the peacefinder.
With our chip,
this can shoot down
any missile fired
by any country.
Cool.
It'll make
people think twice
before they start
another war.
Real cool.
Yeah.
Come on. I will
tell you about
your assignment.
[Makes blastoff noise]
Armstrong!
Coming.
So I'm supposed
to guard the chip?
Not exactly.
You're supposed
to guard my kids.
Are you crazy?
I hate kids.
The children
have a nanny.
You just protect them.
I'll find someone else,
sir.
Obviously, he's
not up for it.
I didn't say
i couldn't do it...
I mean, as long as
they got a nanny.
Ah! aah!
Aah! ah!
Get down.
What the hell
was that?
Aah!
Alex! Kate!
What happened
to miss Parker?
Miss kopalski.
Miss Parker
was last week.
Remember?
the stairs?
Oh, right.
The broken leg.
Legs.
Miss kopalski
had a short circuit
in her blow dryer.
This is
very bad.
Now the agency
won't send any
more nannies.
Say what?
That's why you
brought home
Frankenstein.
Alex!
Is there a phone
i could use?
It's in there.
[Dogs bark]
You're afraid
they're smarter than you?
Babysitting was not
part of our deal.
The security guy
hates my guts.
Hey, sure, fine.
I guess you gave it
a real effort, right?
Do me one last favor.
Go turn off
the gas in my oven.
Why can't you?
Because my head's
going to be in it!
O.k., man,
cool out.
Just get me
a replacement,
understand?
What? I can't hear you.
Something's wrong
with this phone.
Must be the phone company
disconnecting my service.
Or maybe I'm dying
from starvation!
Nice shot.
What do you mean,
nice?
I was aiming
for your wrist.
What are you doing
in my kitchen?
I'm Sean Armstrong,
bodyguard for the kids.
Ha! Mr. nanny!
Hey, why not?
I been here four years,
seen dozens of them
come and go.
But none big as you.
Smarter maybe,
better-looking
for sure,
but none as big.
Here. make yourself
useful.
Top shelf, lurch.
You survived.
I'm tough.
I raised my own four kids
by myself.
What are you doing?
This is like
the roach motel.
The nannies check in...
But they don't
check out. Yeah.
That's not
so many names.
Ha!
Oh.
I can handle
myself.
Ooh.
I hope your blue cross
is paid up.
[Whistles]
Kids...
They're just...
[Alex]
Sean, dinner!
Here, piggy, piggy,
piggy, piggy.
Sooey!
Kids.
[Splash]
Just when we get rid
of the last nanny,
he brings home
a bodyguard.
Yeah.
Ooh. nice touch.
Butter. can't
live without it.
Watch the trip wire.
All right, now, kids,
I'm not pointing
any fingers,
but I don't want anything
to happen to Sean.
What could
possibly happen?
Cute.
[Crash]
Sounds like
he's in a hurry.
Evening.
Are you all right?
Never better.
[Glass crunches]
See, daddy? It's not
so bad eating with us.
Of course not, Princess.
All right.
Yeah!
yeah!
[Pager beeps]
Dad, you're beeping.
Incoming fax.
Go ahead. Eat up
while you still
got teeth.
Oh, no.
This is all wrong.
We'll have to
take a rain check
on the ice cream.
We'll call
your secretary
for an appointment!
Come on, Kate.
I'm not hungry
anymore.
What's going on here?
Just your typical
all-American
dysfunctional family.
Where's the mom?
Passed away
two years back.
It's been downhill
ever since.
Here. next time
I'll just serve it
in a bucket.
I don't think
you like me, frank.
Oh, come on, Mr. thanatos,
what's not to like?
Then how do you explain
that bodyguard?
Oh, him. Uh...See,
he works for
this jerk, Burt?
Burt only hires
losers,
and that's why
i called him.
You should know
losers, frank.
I will let no man
stop me from
obtaining that chip!
Especially you.
Please, sir...
I know where he
keeps the chip. Huh?
And I got this
great plan. See--
wrong!
[Bell chimes]
I make the plans.
Now tell me
everything you know.
[Heavy metal music blares]
Ahem. excuse me,
Mr. Mason?
I'm PR--I'm very
busy right now, Sean.
I was just wondering,
when does
the new nanny arrive?
Oh, uh, yes,
well, it seems
we may have to look
out of state,
but I'll make it up
to you in salary.
Forget the salary.
Just get the nanny.
I'm going to
check the grounds,
then hit the rack.
[Rock music plays]
Yeah! some peace
and quiet.
[Rip]
I hate kids.
* I don't wanna
go to school *
* why do I have
to go to school? *
you're not
wearing your hat.
Forget it.
I'm not the chauffeur.
Really? well,
let's analyze this.
We're sitting
in the back,
you're driving,
we tell you
where to go,
you get paid
to drive there,
we own the car.
Yep. you're
a chauffeur,
all right.
Now put
the hat on!
* don't wanna
go to school *
or I'll scream.
Scream all you want.
No way I'm wearing
that thing.
Aah!
Drop us off
on the corner.
Hey, this is
my old school.
You trying to
tell me you go
to public school?
Ooh, he can read!
Our father thinks
it builds character,
but when he finds out
you used to go here...
Hey, stop!
What are you doing?
It's hard enough
fitting in
without everybody
knowing we have
a rolls Royce.
What do you mean?
Alex has no friends.
Like I'm so surprised.
[Teacher]
class? class!
I told you
to make him leave.
I'm not leaving.
Quiet.
I'm in charge here.
If you're in charge,
how come nobody
listens to you?
[Children laughing]
That's it!
Both of you
to the principal's
office.
Man, some things
never change.
* I don't wanna
go to school *
* there's only principals
at school *
hey, it's still here.
I said I'm not
talking to you.
"S-a"?
Sean...armstrong?
None other.
Thanks for not
talking to me.
Pretty fancy.
Must have took an hour.
Are you kidding?
For that kind of detail?
Try seven years
with a paper clip.
Spent a lot of time
on the bench, huh?
Kate Mason,
are you here again?
She's with me.
Oh. you.
Sean Armstrong,
class of '64.
Armstrong--not Sean
"king of detention"
Armstrong?
Well, it's always nice
to have alumni visit...
Run along now, Katie.
What a lovely child.
Who are you kidding?
You're supposed
to open our door.
I think we're
getting to him.
I can't believe this is
the same Sean Armstrong
I traveled
this great country with.
A man of strength
and courage
who defeated every vile,
vulgar opponent
he ever faced.
Now this fearless
giant is cowering
because of two little
innocent children!
You want to
spend your life
getting your brains
kicked in and
having nightmares,
suit yourself.
But ex-wrestlers
aren't exactly
in demand.
I mean, who else
is gonna offer you
a career?
Electromagnetic.
Radio-controlled.
Wanna see?
O.k., step back.
O.K., ready?
Crank up that dial.
Whoa!
You're so smart.
And so, so bad.
Hey, aren't you going
to pump some iron?
Later.
What's all this crud?
It's the nineties!
I'll program it.
Get on the seat.
What do you weigh?
293.
I'll get your feet.
Somehow I don't like
it when you're nice.
When haven't
we been nice?
Start pedaling
when you're ready.
Bye, Sean.
Have a nice workout.
Bye.
So what'd you
program it for?
Oh, just 20 minutes.
At 90 miles an hour!
Hey!
Somebody stop this thing!
Aah!
Whew!
Not a bad workout.
Whoo!
Better do
a light one today.
Boy, he's strong.
We can fix that.
I'm out of shape.
Ohh!
You know, sometimes
you're so immature.
Huh?
It's only low voltage.
It can't kill him.
Then crank it up.
Aah!
How was your shower?
Stimulating.
Ow!
ow!
Oops. sorry.
Don't you think
we've done enough?
Not till he leaves.
I don't think
he's going to leave.
I kind of like him.
He's not a goody-goody
like those nannies.
I got to admit,
he's one tough mother.
I can't take
it anymore.
Then go ahead...Quit.
So what if people
call you a panty-waist,
a candy-ass wuss?
Who's going
to know I quit?
When I get through
spreading the word?
Everybody, puckerbutt.
Congratulations, you have
made the hall of shame.
No, you got to stay
for the kids.
They'll do anything to
drive me out of here.
But you've lasted!
You can make the difference.
This family needs a change.
Maybe it's you.
You think so?
No, not really.
But, hey,
it's worth a shot.
So get tough.
Hang in there.
Suck it up.
I've been
sucking it up.
Here.
have some more.
Thanks.
Wow. imagine what he
could do to your head.
[Door closes]
Alex? Kate? I'm home.
We're in the gym, dad!
Wait till he
sees what we did.
Hi.
What happened?
We destroyed the bike,
wrecked the room,
and almost killed Sean.
Yeah! are you
going to punish us?
This is a new approach.
Well, what for?
Sean's fine,
and there's nothing here
that can't be fixed.
I got to make some calls.
What?
Case closed.
Now excuse me.
Excuse me,
Mr. Mason.
You're not going
to do anything?
No time to discuss
this, Sean.
And you wonder why
your kids are a mess.
You can't say that.
You don't know what it's
like raising kids alone.
I feel sorry you lost
your wife, man,
but if you can't give
these kids what they
need, get rid of them.
I guess he really
doesn't care about us.
[Muffled shouts]
O.k.
All right.
Here we go. O.K.
Come on, baby.
5...9, 8, 7.
Holy...
It's o.K. I'll
just clear this.
No problem.
No problema.
4, 5, 6, uh...
9, 8, 7.
That's the one.
Oh, jeez. Clear.
It's o.K.
Damn it! He's changed
the combination.
This is becoming
tiresome, frank.
I'll do it
again.
I'm beginning
to get a headache.
Aah, aah, ahh,
aah, aah!
Ow! jeez!
Wolfgang.
Stupid!
Very stupid!
Now I'm getting
a migraine!
Do not worry,
herr thanatos.
It's empty,
frank.
Why am I not
surprised?
Uh, he--he--he--
he must have
taken it with him.
This was not my idea--
your plan, sir.
[Alarm rings]
Great. now the cops
are going to be here.
You, with the vest,
can you give me a little
love pat right here?
With pleasure.
No, no, Wolfie,
it's o.K.
Oh, my head!
The pressure!
Ahh, ahh...
The pressure. The pressure.
[School bell rings]
Mason, where
you going?
We were looking
for you.
Gee. is it 3:00
already?
Shut up, dweeb.
Alex, we missed you
this morning.
Didn't you hear us
calling?
Oh, was that you guys?
Hand it over.
I spent my money
on lunch!
Ow!
Mason, Mason.
You weren't
straight with us.
That'll cost you
50 bucks.
Then we can be
friends again.
I hate bullies.
You'll only
make it worse.
How often
does this happen?
Just once a day.
What a wimp.
You said it.
Don't say a word.
He's very sensitive.
Hey, weenie, want Sean
to kick their butts?
Shut up!
See? I told you
he's sensitive.
Alex, I saw what
happened back there.
Mind your
own business!
I can show you how
to defend yourself.
Can it,
Mr. babysitter!
I don't want
your stupid help!
Frank...
I'm glad you're
out of the hospital.
[Mumbling]
So, who were they?
Did you get
a look at them?
[Mumbling]
Did you?
Obviously,
they're after the chip.
I'll have to move up
the Washington trip tonight.
I'll leave tonight.
Oh, what?
"I'll...
"Make...
Arrangements."
Oh, thank you, frank.
Thank you.
[Moans]
I'm--I'm--I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I hope you feel better.
Wait.
You didn't have
to be so mean.
First you heat them up,
then you cool them down.
Just what are you up to?
Oh, nothing much,
just 50 gallons of
fd&c red dye number 2.
Oh, Alex, not
the pit of blood.
Naturally.
what's the big deal?
It's just maybe
we've done enough,
that's all.
And he's really
not that bad.
All nannies are bad.
It's in
the job description.
He's not a nanny.
Look, I'll make
a deal with you.
If he survives
the pit of blood,
I'll call a truce.
Well...promise?
Promise. but
I'll need your help.
Deal?
Come on.
Let's throw
the compost heap
in this time.
I'll get the seaweed.
Ohh!
What'd you do that for?
For making a mess,
porky!
You could've just
asked me to clean it up.
Sure, but where's
the fun in that?
[Kate]
help, Sean! Help me!
Ignore it.
I wouldn't lift a finger
to help those brats.
[Kate]
help, Sean!
I can't swim!
Oh, my god!
Sucker.
I'm coming!
Hold on!
Oh, no, you don't!
You little bast--
one bolt less,
and I'd have
miscalculated his
inertial torque.
But genius prevailed.
Now all he needs is
two horns, a pitchfork,
and a tail.
That...
Is...it!
Aah!
See ya.
That's it!
I've had it!
From now on, you're
going to act right,
'cause
i ain't leaving!
Told you so.
Shut up! I don't
care for your tone!
Sit down!
You--you don't have
to go ballistic!
Yes, I do!
No more games
or tricks!
You'll sit till i
tell you to get up!
Sit down!
[Sproing]
ohh!
Oops. trip wire.
Aah!
And the flour.
I mean it!
Night, Harry.
Are you o.K.?
What happened?
Nothing i
couldn't handle.
I see.
Anyway, I'm glad
you're still here,
especially after
our talk last night.
I'm doing my job.
Good. there was
a break-in at the plant.
I want to double security
for 48 hours while
I'm out of town.
O.k.
I'll call my boss.
Fine.
where are the kids?
Hi, Alex.
Hi, Kate.
We're being punished.
I can see that.
What did you do?
I got mad.
Well, I mean,
it's all right
if they hate you
because you're
not their father.
As long as you're fair,
they'll respect you.
I know my kids.
They don't
respect anybody.
O.k., you can get up.
Oh, thank you, sir.
Thank you, sir.
I guess I was wrong.
Oh, yes,
thank you, sir.
Your immenseness.
Mr. Sean Armstrong,
sir, king among men.
God among mortals.
Créme de la créme.
What? so you couldn't
handle it by yourself, huh?
Get off!
Give...me...
the phone!
What? nothing, nothing.
Come on!
Never felt better.
Just a little
interference on the line.
See you tomorrow.
Get out of here!
Take it! Take it!
* everybody say
bad, bad, bad *
* is how you gotta be *
* to face this crazy,
mixed-up world like *
* you're supposed to be... *
are you going
to be in here long?
Yep. plenty
of room for two.
* don't have to be rude *
* don't have to be crude *
* all you really
got to have *
* is attitude,
attitude... *
you know, uh,
most people lift
the weights.
I knew that.
Yeah.
Look, if you're getting
ready for a fight,
all you need is attitude,
not muscles.
That's easy
for you to say
when you're the
size of a redwood.
Hey, I was a big kid,
but I got whupped
every day.
My old man never taught me
to take care of myself.
How'd you get them to
stop beating on you?
I graduated.
Oh.
Then this little guy Burt
taught me attitude.
And the rest is history.
O.k. teach me.
Please.
Feet apart.
Weight forward.
No. try again.
You're too tight.
Remember--
loose, but ready.
O.k. loose,
but ready.
Got it.
Attaboy.
No. somebody swings,
you're dead.
Drop your hands
by your side,
relax
your shoulders.
I just feel
a little awkward.
I know,
but nobody else will.
Remember...
You're bad!
I'm bad.
Yeah.
I'm bad!
I'm super bad!
I'm badacious!
All right!
Yeah!
Bad!
* attitude, dude **
wait a minute.
Where are you going?
* in my bed *
* about to sleep *
* I had a dream... *
[sobbing]
* some kids dream
of fortune and fame *
* some kids dream... **
daddy?
It's just me.
I can't sleep.
Do whatever you
did last night.
I couldn't sleep then,
either.
You must have
slept sometime.
Yeah.
Sure.
When my mommy was here...
Before she went to heaven.
Oh.
You know...
I lost my dad
when I was a kid.
But I don't think
he went to heaven.
You mean he went to...
Oh.
Mommy used
to sing me a song.
Could you sing it to me?
I don't know
those kind of songs.
I could teach it
to you.
* speed, Bonnie boat *
* like a bird
on the wing *
* "onward,"
the sailors cry *
* carry the lad *
* who was born
to be king *
[Snoring]
* over the sea to Skye **
hey, wake up!
I'm awake.
Then sing.
I got
a terrible voice.
Sing!
All right.
But I got to
sing my own song.
* twinkle, twinkle *
* little star *
* how I wonder
what you are *
* up above
the world so high *
* like a diamond
in the sky *
* twinkle, twinkle *
* little star *
* how I wonder
what you are *
[doorbell chimes]
* up above the world
so high... **
frank, what are
you doing here?
[Mumbling]
"Extra security."
Good, good.
Is Harry in the limo?
[Mumbling]
"Harry is sick."
You know, that's odd.
Usually, Harry
calls me himself.
[Mumbling]
Oh, your anticipation
is impressive.
"Blew his lunch
in the garage."
O.k. I'll get my bags.
[Humming]
It worked.
You have to kiss Dolly.
I don't kiss dollies.
You're going
to wake me up!
Don't tell anybody
i did that.
Dolly likes you.
Would you take care
of her for the night?
No way.
What?
All right.
* every night *
* as I lay here sleeping *
* dream dad **
Sean.
Uh...let me
see the doll.
What, you want
to kiss her, too?
What?
Oh, you mean for Kate.
It sure wasn't for me.
Sean, I didn't get
a chance to say goodbye,
so could you tell
the children I love them?
Why don't you tell them?
You mean right now?
You got something
more important to do?
Yes, as a matter
of fact, i--
no, I don't.
Good.
but don't forget,
this may be
where it starts,
but it ain't
where it ends.
[Knock on door]
[Door opens]
Sean, I was thinking
we could--
oh, hi, dad.
What are you doing here?
I'm saying good night.
Is that so surprising?
Well, frankly, yes.
Gee, my old workplace
looks great with your
inventions on it.
You know,
i really miss it.
I can't make up
for the past,
but I'm going to change,
Alex. I promise.
I can help
if you just listen
to me once in a while.
O.k.?
I love you, Alex.
I love you, too.
Mr. Mason?
Sorry to bother you,
but I'm supposed to take
care of Dolly tonight.
Well, take very
good care of her.
You bet.
Yeah.
Sean...
Thanks for everything.
Katie?
I love you, Katie.
Again.
I've never
stopped loving you.
I love you, daddy.
He missed the turn
to the airport. Driver!
Sit back.
Enjoy the ride.
Herr thanatos
has planned a full
evening for you.
Thanatos? is--is that
the sicko who's been--
oh, god.
Oh, frank! Frank!
Don't just sit there. Frank!
Frank!
[Mumbling]
"I work for Mr. thanatos."
How could you do that?
Money? you fool!
He'll get rid of you
the moment you've
outlived your usefulness!
"Ha!"
[Mumbling]
Aah!
[Pounding on door]
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm coming.
[Pounding louder]
I said I was coming.
[Pounding]
Oh!
Mama!
How would you like
that cane up your nose?
Sean!
Hey, Burt.
Hey, great to see you,
too, old buddy.
Hey, give me 20 bucks
for the cabbie, quick.
Hey.
Keep the change.
Gee...a whole quarter.
A quarter!
Give me that.
This ain't Christmas.
Ha ha!
So, who's the babe?
Corinne,
meet my pal Burt.
Ooh,
the dynamic duo--
wimpy and gimpy.
She's in
a good mood today.
Who's this?
Alex, Kate.
Burt Wilson.
Ah, the brats.
You're too old
for a bodyguard.
You're too little to have
such a big mouth.
I hope you're giving us
a golden-age discount,
gramps.
Kids,
show some respect.
Burt saved my life.
That's right.
Took a bullet right here
for this guy,
nicked an artery.
You should've seen
the blood pumping out.
Kaploom! kaploom! Kaploom!
Nearly hit the ceiling.
Eww!cool!
A long time ago,
this creep named
Tommy thanatos,
he tried to get
me and Burt
to rig a prestigious
sporting event.
The world
series?
Close. anyway,
me and Burt refused.
Thanatos lost
a lot of money.
And then
after the event...
Ahh. nice match, champ.
Now we can pay the hotel
and get your clothes back.
You sure know how
to take the glow
off winning.
I ordered you
to throw that match.
You've cost me money.
Big money!
Bigger than your hair?
We don't throw
matches.
That's right.
If you was soaked
in gasoline,
we might throw matches--
the flaming kind.
With that furball
on your head,
you'd make
one hell of a torch.
First you defy me,
then you mock my hair?
You're dead!
Look out!
Aah!
Get him!
Get out of my way!
Ohh! stop!
He's mine!
I'll cut you
down to size!
Whaaa!
[Sean]
must have hit him
pretty hard.
He landed headfirst in
the hotel swimming pool
next door.
Must have made
a killer splash.
No. the pool was empty.
It would've killed him,
but his hair cushioned
the fall.
At least he got
a metal plate
in the slammer.
Wow. you really did
save his life.
What can you
do now, pappy?
What can I do now?
Ha!
Hyah!
O.k. he'll do.
I'll take you
to class.
No way. I want to see
Alex get whupped.
Alex, did Sean share
his invincible psych-out
technique with you?
Yeah.
Forget it.
Us little guys
need backup.
Primitive, but effective.
Like me and Sean.
Thanks, but I'm fine.
I know. I know.
Too bloody.
You want something
more subtle. Blackjack!
One good bop. His brain's
all over the sidewalk.
No, really.
I'm fine.
Too messy, I know.
O.K.
How about a little mace
in the face, huh?
They'll be puking.
No.
All right. Last resort.
Classic lead pipe.
Good for one-on-one
or as a weapon
of mass destruction.
Thanks, Burt,
but I'm covered.
O.k. suit yourself.
Hey...richie rich
got smart.
Figures we'll be
nicer if we don't
have to chase him.
Right, Alexander?
Wrong!
What?
you heard me!
No more money!
I guess we'll have to
leave you alone then.
No hard feelings.
Give me your wallet, twerp.
That's not fair.
He's got to do it
on his own.
Did mommy put this
on a string
so Alex wouldn't
lose any more money?
Don't talk
about my mother!
What are you
going to do?
Let's get out of here!
The sides even
this time?
Yes, sir.
Excellent!
90 seconds,
herr thanatos.
Oh, all right.
Raise him.
[Sputtering]
Oh, I do enjoy
a good round of torture
as much
as the next fellow.
I truly do.
But time is pressing.
The chip, Mr. Mason,
i must have it.
I have spent
years of my life
on that peacefinder.
I'm not about
to turn it over
to some psycho!
Oh, let's not engage
in name-calling.
I am just
a businessman...
Like you.
My work is my life.
Of course...
Some days are
more satisfying
than others.
Let's cut to the chase.
Everyone has a price.
Name yours.
Forget it!
Oh, my mistake.
I thought you were
a reasonable man.
But no, you won't
even negotiate.
So I'll name
your price.
Alex Jr. and Kate.
You pig! You pig!
You pig!
Judging by your response,
I should've done this
a long time ago.
Do you want one lump
or two?
There's nothing in there.
It's called pretend.
Well, then,
I'll take two.
Now you've spilled it.
I'm really sorry.
I'm nothing
but a big klutz.
Always have been.
All the other kids
made fun of me.
You don't have
to be that way.
I could teach you.
Really?
Sure.
But you got to do
everything I say.
Try again.
Thumb and forefinger.
And get that pinkie up!
Well! mmm!
Ha ha ha!
Hey, hey.
A little of this.
That is an insult
to the chef.
Maybe the chef
needs a little spice.
Maybe you'd like
a ketchup bottle
down your throat.
The sexual energy
is so thick in here,
I could cut it
with a knife.
Maybe I'm too young
for this conversation.
That's a smart boy.
Reminds me of me
when I was a kid.
Except he's smart,
rich, and good-looking.
True. but I still
got time. Huh?
Mm-hmm.
No ponytails.
Just trust me
on this.
You should've seen
the flames shoot out
of that sucker.
And I used to think
all you einsteins
were weenies.
It's fairly basic.
Whoa!
what have we here?
An electrified toilet seat.
Sheer brilliance.
It's nothing. Really.
But it does complement
the poison Ivy
toilet paper.
Oh, ho ho. And you say
you aren't a genius?
Ha ha ha.
Why don't you guys
carry guns?
I lost my license.
Can't you get it back?
Once you shoot the examiner
in the foot,
it gets a lot tougher.
Any two-bit weenie
can carry a gun.
That don't make you tough.
Tough is taking on a fight
you can't win.
Tough is getting
kicked in the head
and asking for more.
Tough is a 300-pound man
in tights.
[Nutcracker suite plays]
Keep the back straight.
Make the arms
a bow.
Now bend.
Burt.
Lovely to see you.
You look positively
effervescent.
May I offer you tea?
Perhaps a watercress
sandwich?
Knock it off!
Get out of that thing!
Oh! you mean
my leotard?
Ah...the ballet.
It enhances grace.
I'm a changed man.
Aah!
Hey! put me down,
you klutz!
I'm not a klutz anymore.
Oh!
[Glass breaking]
He's not as far along
as I thought.
Darn! I jetéd
when I should've pliéd.
I used to share
a hotel room with you?
[Explosion]
Don't move!
Take cover!
Oops!
Hah! look at
the big girlie-man.
What do you want,
scuzzbucket?
We have come to play
with the children.
Over my dead body.
Make that two dead bodies.
First one to move
gets a facelift.
Ohh!
You dirtbag!
Why, you miserable--
shut up!
And now it is my turn,
ja?
Hit the alarm.
Here! take my wallet!
There's 10 grand.
[Speaking Japanese]
Auf wiedersehen.
Help us!
Aah! Aah!
Help!
aah!
Somebody help us!
Help!
let me down!
Quiet, children!
Your well-being rests
in my hands now.
Any more noise,
just shoot them.
What about him?
[Siren]
Business
before pleasure.
Daddy!
dad!
Kate! Alex!
Did they hurt you?
[Thanatos]
not yet!
[Mason]
you bastard!
Doodyhead!
Scumsucker!
Burt?
Burt Wilson?
What a delightful bonus.
Thanatos!
i should've known.
Who else
would kidnap
little children?
Thanatos?
So that's what happened
to his head.
Cool!
Who's that?
That's Sean's friend
Burt.
Sean Armstrong?
My, my...Imagine--
revenge and
ill-gotten wealth
all in one night.
I'm positively tingling.
So who goes first?
Don't you touch them.
You can have the chip,
but first you've got
to let them go.
You're hardly
in a position
to negotiate.
However...
Once I have it,
you and your family
may leave.
But not Burt!
He cost me my hair.
I had beautiful hair.
Thick...
Lustrous...
Manageable hair.
You are going
to die a slow
and agonizing death.
You ever consider going
to an auto-parts store
and getting a bumper guard
for that chrome?
Why, you!
Kidnapping children,
hitting an old man...
You really come up
in the world.
Shut up! I'm getting
a headache!
Don't wig out!
I couldn't hair y--aah!
Shut up!
Now,
where is it?
Before I change
my mind!
Well, it's right--
it's right
in Sean's room!
Alex.you rat.
I think there's hope
for this family yet.
[Police radio]
Roger, unit 32.
[Telephone rings]
Do you mind?
Yeah. could be
a ransom call.
Then fetch
your lieutenant.
I am the lieutenant.
God save us all.
Hello. Mason residence.
All right.
Hold on.
It's for you.
Alex.
Go ahead. It's me.
Lieutenant! want
a nice, fresh doughnut?
The toilet seat?
We hid the chip inside,
on my workbench,
next to my wallet.
Bring it
to the 3rd street dock.
You have to come alone.
It's thanatos!
Alex!
Very stupid!
You take a swan dive
into an empty pool,
and I'm stupid?
I'm so proud of you.
Oh, how touching.
Like the family
i never had
and...never wanted!
Wolfgang,
tie them up.
Wait!
no!
No!
no!no!
I'm going after them.
How? you're just
a wrestler.
What? who told you?
I saw you wrestle
trick McGraw last year.
Why didn't you
say something?
Because I was desperate
for those kids.
And I had a gut feeling
about you.
I got to go.
I've got no choice.
You bring
that family back safe,
or you will have
to answer to me.
You might as well bring
that scroungy, bullheaded
old gasbag back, too.
I'll go get them.
Cover me.
I'm going out
Alex's window.
Lieutenant!
Let me tell you
what happened.
Now, they broke
in here...
[Motorcycle approaches]
What's he doing?
What's going on?
I ought to
blow you away.
Sorry. got to get
those brakes checked.
Get up.
Easy. all I'm carrying
is a wallet.
[Wolfgang]
base to scarab-1.
What is your location?
[Engine starts]
Why do you not answer?
Aah!
O.k.,
captain scumbucket.
Where am I going?
Blow it out your--aah!
North!
Knew you'd see it
my way.
As soon as we have
the chip,
kill them all.
You lied.
So sue me.
Which way?
That way.
How many
number 53 markers
are there
in biscayne bay?
One, obviously.
Then why did we
pass it twice?
Uhh.
I'll kill you for that.
May I borrow
your keys?
Huh?
Waah!
Adios.
Hey!
Bingo.
They're coming in.
The anticipation
is almost too much to bear.
So is your breath.
Now we know
who's the first to die.
They should be here
by now.
Hey! what?
Aah!
Base to scarab-1.
What is taking so long?
[Static]
Why do you
not answer?
Come in.
[Thanatos]
i won't tolerate
ineptitude.
Keep trying.
Come in.
Ach, there must be
something wrong.
Freeze!
My, my,
I expected a more
dramatic entrance
from a man
who wrestled
at the west Memphis
pork pavilion.
Hey, we won
in west Memphis.
But not tonight.
Hyah!
Aah!
Hurry! untie us!
Just shoot
them both.
Grrr!
Aah!
Grraaahh!
Unlike you, Armstrong,
I never lose.
Ha ha ha ha!
Now your friends
can watch you die.
Ugh!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
No!
[Kate]
save him!
Get him, dad!
Help him!
Dad!
Aah!
I hate you!
Let him--
let him go!
Let him go!
Aah!
You shouldn't
have done that.
Why not?
'Cause you shouldn't
have hit a kid.
Uhh!
Alex, the button.
Swine!
Aah!
[Speaking German]
Hang out, Wolfie, baby.
One move, and I will
destroy the chip.
There's no chip in there,
dorkbrain.
You lied.
So sue me!
Grrr!
Alex, duck!
You screwed up
my hair.
Now it's payback time.
I will not be denied
my pleasure.
He's going
to kill him.
Do something, daddy.
A transformer!
We can generate
electricity.
Intense!
a superconducting
magnetic beam!
Like we did to
miss Callahan?
What?
The nanny
with the braces.
Hit it!
Aah!
[Crowd cheers]
Uhh!
Now you die.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
No more.
It's not working,
dad!
We need a conductor!
Come on, son,
hurry!
Quick! quick!
Quick!
Grab that end!
Need a hand?
O.k., lift it up.
Grrr!
Hit the deck!
Aah!
Whoa!
Whoa! whoa!
Stop this thing!
Whoa!
This beats
the 4th of July.
He's toast.
Aah!
Aah! aah! Aah!
[Kate]
wow!
Man really
blew his top.
So where's
the stupid chip?
Kate has it.
Do not.
Yes, you do, honey,
right here
in your Dolly.
Sure about this?
I don't need her
anymore.
You're a brave man.
You're the brave one.
Raising kids is
the toughest gig I know.
Ahem.
Hey, Burt, thanks
for getting me
out of the ring.
I'm going to
need a partner
around here.
Thanks, but
i haven't had
a vacation since...
Since I met you.
Vacation?
if you need me,
I can get out of
this monkey suit
real quick.
How far can you get
on two broken legs?
Quit mothering me.
I love you guys.
We love you, too.
See you soon.
Maybe sooner
than you think.
Bye, Sean.
Hey, you're
going to--
we're going to
make him stay.
* rough stuff *
* rough stuff,
rough stuff *
aah!
* when this job
is over *
* I'm gonna
settle down *
* I'll find a little shack *
* by the railroad track *
* on the outskirts
of town *
* I'll plant
a little garden *
* and watch
the flowers grow *
* I'll tell this crazy,
mixed-up world *
* I just don't
want to know *
* but if trouble
comes a-knockin' *
* like it did before *
* I'll take that pest *
* let him sit
in my nest *
* and put his head
right through the door *
* rough stuff *
* baby, gonna
call your bluff *
* rough stuff *
* the tough
get goin' *
* when the goin'
gets rough *
* rough stuff *
* it won't be over
till you had enough *
* rough stuff *
* you ain't nothin'
but a powder puff *
* rough stuff *
* rough stuff,
rough stuff *
* rough stuff *
* no average psychotic
criminal genius *
* makes a monkey
out of me *
* 'cause I got stuff
when it gets rough *
* that you don't
want to see *
* you know
i am a lover *
* but, baby,
that ain't all *
* I'm a wild tiger *
* when my back's
against the wall *
* you think
that you're a hunter *
* and I will be
your game *
* but your game
is lost *
* you gotta
pay the cost *
* I'm one cat
you can't change *
* rough stuff *
* baby, gonna call
your bluff *
* rough stuff *
* the tough
get goin' *
* when the goin'
gets rough *
* rough stuff *
* it won't be over
till you had enough *
* rough stuff *
* you ain't nothin'
but a powder puff *
* rough stuff *
* rough stuff,
rough stuff *
* rough stuff *
* I just wanna
go fishin' *
* in the deep
blue sea *
* 'cause I need a change
from my reality *
* this world
will beat you down *
* beat you
with a stick *
* you want
an ice cream pop *
* they give you
a boot to lick *
* I need some time *
* to sort out
all this mess *
* I gotta be rough
and ready *
* when they put me
to the test *
* rough stuff *
* baby, gonna call
your bluff *
* rough stuff *
* the tough
get goin' *
* when the goin'
gets rough *
* rough stuff *
* it won't be over
till you had enough *
* rough stuff *
* you ain't nothin'
but a powder puff *
* rough stuff *
* oh *
* ohh *
* rough stuff *
* ow *
* ooh *
* rough stuff *
* ohh *
* ouch *
* rough stuff *
* ohh *
* ow *
* rough stuff *
* rough stuff,
rough stuff *
* rough stuff **
captioning made possible
by new line home video
captioning performed by
the national captioning
institute, inc.
Captions copyright 1993
new line cinema corporation
public performance of captions
prohibited without permission of
national captioning institute