Subtitles by explosiveskull
[wind blowing]
[wood creaking]
[handbrake creaks]
[chain rattles]
Hey.
Hi.
Where is she?
In the shed,
all day.
Dan...
Sorry.
Is she quiet?
She's okay.
[moos]
[softly]
Ey, ey, ey.
Girl, let me in.
[moos]
(Dan)
Easy, girl!
Whoa, easy, girl,
easy now.
Her water's broken?
No.
[snarl]
[she gasps]
Ah!
[cow moos]
[she shouts]
Fuck! Fuck!
(Dan)
Orla!
Fuck! Ohh!
What happened?
It's okay.
I'll get you
something.
No, it's okay.
Sure?
Yeah, it's all right.
[moos]
You can't
park here.
We're not
bothering anyone.
I'm not askin', all right?
I'm tellin'.
Now go back
to the main road,
and don't 'cause me
any trouble. All right?
Please, we're not
staying long.
And we're not
on your land.
Fuckin'
knackers...
Be outta here
by tomorrow.
[car engine starts]
Maybe go...
They'd be lookin'
by now. We stay.
A day or two. 'Till they
stop watchin' the roads.
You're not sorry,
are you, Jamie?
No!
No...
Those people in the Caravan,
you can't have that, Dan.
They need to go.
Tomorrow,
I've told them.
I've explained
all this.
It's just a matter of
commercial confidentiality.
Which we're
paying you for.
For what you're paying, it
can't be much of a secret.
How's the cow?
Nothing yet.
John wants to check
her quickly.
There's no need
for you to...
(John)
Back a bit.
[Orla sighs]
Try and go lower.
There's no need to talk
to him like an eejit...
Why can't you pay
on time?
Well I have to process the money
carefully, you know that.
I'm not sure he was
the best candidate.
He was the only fuckin'
candidate, thanks to me,
and you haven't
paid me either.
[sighs]
See the head?
I think it's okay.
Something nipped
my hand, John.
Muscle pressure
from the cow,
maybe compressed it against the bone.
Who knows.
I felt something,
John.
I felt it snapping
at me.
Those last safety checks,
everything was okay?
Yes.
All of them?
Maybe we should
terminate it.
That calf looks normal,
doesn't it?
It's okay, then.
Everything okay?
(Orla)
He says so.
Is that what you think?
I'm just the vet.
Screwing him,
are you, Orla?
It's none of your
business, Dan.
Why?
I thought...
I thought you could change.
I mean, you should...
[clatters dishes]
Well...
Let me know the minute
she starts to go.
Nobody's coming,
Jamie.
Come to bed.
[distant mooing]
[mooing]
(Dan)
Jesus!
Okay.
Easy now.
I'm just going to have
a look at you, okay.
[Dan strains]
Whoa! Whoa!
[clicking]
Shit!
[mooing]
Jamie get up! Jamie get up.
Look!
[mumbles]
What?
(Jamie)
Wait by the stairs.
[pants]
Turn off the torch.
Now I told you,
we're not movin'.
Listen, I need
your help.
You want my help?
I have a cow,
she's...
Why would I want
to help you?
What happened
to you?
This is no problem
here, okay?
The cow's in trouble,
she's calvin'.
I can't get the fuckin'
thing out of her!
Ah, fuck it!
[whispering]
Fuck. Fuck you.
I thought they
found us.
Yeah. Me, too.
[panting]
He's in trouble,
Jamie.
So?
What?
Be careful, Jamie.
Okay?
Lock the door
after me.
[moos]
Christ,
that's unreal.
[whispering]
Quiet!
Vet should've
been here.
That's a good idea, you should
get him here. He'll sort it out.
We have no time. I got to get a
move on, we could loose them both.
Come on in.
You going to help
or not?
Yeah, why not.
Good man.
(Dan, shouting)
Whoa, girl! Whoa! Whoa!
[cow moos]
Move under!
Whoa, girl!
Whoa, easy!
Easy...
She's going.
[both strain]
[pants]
Good girl...
That's it.
Good girl.
Okay. We need to get this back
up here and turn it around.
Okay.
Christ, she's tight!
This is nuts. I've never
had it this difficult.
[pants]
Here we go.
Yeah.
[both strain]
Oh, that's it.
[cow moos]
Ah! Nngh!
[exhales]
[both strain]
[snap]
It's all right, girl,
you're okay.
Okay. You're okay,
Nngh!
[moos]
[Dan strains]
Oh, oh, oh.
It's moving!
Guide the legs
over that rung!
Drop the hitch,
I got it.
It's not breathing.
What?
Mind yourself.
[Dan strains]
Grab the head!
That's it!
It's breathing.
[chuckles]
I don't know about it.
What?
There's something wrong.
[straining]
[crack]
Oww!!! Shit!
Fuck! Oww!
[panting]
Where's your phone?
No! I have no phone!
Here! Here! Use this!
Rip this up, use it
as a bandage!
There's water
in that kettle!
Get that bowl!
Okay.
All right.
This is going
to hurt ya'.
[straining]
Nnngh!
Ah!
[splashing]
Jamie?
Hello?
Jesus, Jamie!
Don't do that!
That calfs
not right.
You need to kill it. Put
it out of it's misery.
You can't do that...
It's only born already.
Look, ah...
What's your names?
This is Mary.
I'm Jamie.
Name's Dan.
You need someone to
look at your hand.
Oh, I'm all right. I'm okay.
You should, uh...
You should head off now. I'll
see about a doctor tomorrow.
Come on.
Come on!
Listen.
Stay as long as you like. Okay?
You'll have no more
trouble from me.
(Mary)
Thanks.
I thought that
something...
Something what?
Something what, Mary?
Thought you'd
run off on me.
No. No, we're all
right, me and you.
That calf...?
It's over. It's done.
And nobody's
coming for us.
I need to be able to get
you on the phone, Dan,
you can manage
that now, surely.
I told you they
haven't paid me yet.
Jesus, what did
you do to yourself?
The calf bit
my finger.
The calf?
I've had to separate
it from it's mother.
It bites her.
(Orla)
Jesus.
I can see how
it got your finger.
John, we got to shut it
all down. It's gone wrong.
John... Fuck!
Orla, what's
going on here?
[moos]
Shit!
[shot]
[cow moos]
Christ's sake Orla!
(Orla) Look at it! It
jammed, all right!
For Christ's sake!
Nngh!
What's keepin' ya!
Finish her off!
[moos]
[calf brays]
(Dan) Easy, girl! Easy!
[Orla pants]
Oh, come on!
Hold her!
Easy! Easy!
[moos, huffs]
[calf brays]
[mooing]
Orla!
Aaah!
[Dan and Orla pant]
Orla, wait!
[shot]
[splash]
Dan...
Get the calf...
[click]
Hold it.
[cocks]
[brays softly]
It's all right.
Give it a minute.
It's going.
Get away from it.
What's wrong?
I'm not sure.
I need to clarify
some things.
It's not good.
[strains]
Hold the leg up will ya'?
This will be messy.
[strains]
[tearing]
(Orla)
Shit.
(Dan)
What is it?
Looks like LOS. Large
Offspring Syndrome.
The organs
grow too large.
You see the lungs
and the heart?
Caused by?
It's a genetic
abnormality.
It happens in cases of embryo transfer.
Like in these tests.
You expected this?
I didn't. It's not
my experiment.
I'm just the vet, I'm working
for him, that's all.
That's all.
Liver...
Kidneys...
What are they?
It's a fetus, Dan.
The calf
was pregnant.
Fuck, this is
unbelievable.
They're completely
malformed.
The bone structure
has gone haywire.
Skeleton's on
the outside.
What the fuck
has he done?
They could never
have lived.
[both gasp loudly]
What have you done?
John wanted to make
a genetic modification
to create
more fertile calves.
Ones that would grow quicker
and be fertile younger.
Well, that's fuckin'
young to be pregnant!
Something's
gone wrong!
Don't look at me
like that, Dan.
You took the money, you're
fuckin' involved, too!
What now?
Don't let anyone near that cow. Lock
the door and keep away from it.
The same for the cow
in the winter shed.
Keep the other
animals well away.
There could be danger
of infection.
What?!
Just a possibility.
Infection!
What infection?!
I'm not sure yet!
You sit tight until
I get back here tomorrow.
Orla.
[engine starts]
Orla!
(Dan)
[mooing]
Now...
Do you want me to feed
those other cows or not?
'Cause you look like you're
going to puke there, mister.
All right, you'll find the feed,
in the shed, over by the silage.
Give them some water
while you're at it.
And, uh, you'll find
you'll need those.
Thanks.
All right. Thanks.
It looks clean enough. I'll put
some more disinfectant on it.
Might sting a bit.
You should go
to the hospital.
No, thanks, I have to wait for the vet.
I'll go back with her.
Have you always
lived here?
Yeah, I took over
for my old man.
What about your
own family?
There's six of us.
I'm the second.
Three brothers,
two sisters.
It's close.
Close family.
And, uh, how does it go
with the traveler boy?
Do they like him?
Are you popular
with his crowd?
You're, uh, just in the
way of a romantic break.
Down a lane
on a bog farm.
If my brothers find us,
they'll kill him.
[water dripping]
[footsteps approaching]
[mooing]
[water pouring]
[footsteps splashing]
[metallic thud]
[screams]
(Dan)
I don't know.
You're right.
She's cut bad.
I'm tellin' ya. I don't know
what the fuck it was...
Oh, shit!
Fuck, Mary!
Mary!
(Dan)
Hey, Tom.
Dan Reily.
The very man.
That your van
on the verge?
(Mary)
It is.
A word, Dan,
if you please.
(Tom) The knackers giving
you trouble, yeah?
Oh, no, no, Tom.
All right, Dan, but you be careful now.
You hear me?
That's all
right, Tom.
I said they could
stay a night or two.
It's your funeral, Dan,
you know how it goes.
Sure... what is there to
steal around here, Tom?
It's a hard time,
all right.
I hear that new fellow at the
bank's taking you all the way.
He's a right fecker
by all accounts.
Aye, he is.
You can't be messing around
with these boys, Dan.
They mean business. They'll have
you out, quick as you like,
they'll be 'round with
a sheaf of court orders
to bar you from
your own land.
Was there something
in particular, Tom?
All right, Dan, just a bit
of advice, that's all.
I wanted to ask you if you
knew that Orla Buckley's car
is a mile up that lane
near O'Dwyer's Cross.
Orla?
It's a hell of a mess,
and we can't find her.
What do you mean
you can't find her?
She didn't turn up
for work today.
She was out here
last night,
she was lookin'
after a calf...
she...
she went back.
What time was it
you said she left?
I don't know.
It was late.
Fine. If you see her,
let me know.
You staying long?
Couple of days.
How many are you?
Me, me Daddy,
and me sister.
There's a halting
site in Kilmartin.
It's all right, Tom, okay. I said
they could stay a night or two.
I'd think of moving on there soon.
Maybe today. Maybe now.
Good luck, Daniel.
That Tom...
[engine starts]
What should we do?
I locked this
last night.
Orla?
Christ...
She came back?
She came back in the night
without telling me.
Don't go any closer!
We should leave it, the vet
said it could be infected.
(Mary)
Burn it.
Get rid of it.
[car approaching]
(John)
Dan?
Where's the cow?
She didn't look too
good when she left.
Like what?
I don't know, like she had
a fever or something.
What's the
story here.
They're only staying tonight.
They'll be gone in the morning.
[many clicks]
(John)
Don't come in.
Oh, my God!
I'll stay here and
check it all out.
Go. Go.
(John)
That's too fast...
[troubled breathing]
[panting]
(Mary) Jamie... can you
slow down a bit...
Hang on.
[zips]
What's wrong
with you, Jamie?
Sorry. Don't know...
Jamie.
It's my foot.
You're burnin' up.
What's that smell?
I don't know.
We're on a farm, Jamie.
It's very strong.
Just ignore it... Okay?
Just ignore it.
[Mary shrieks]
Aaah!!!
[screams] Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Jesus.
There's nothing
there.
(Jamie)
We're going.
(John) No. No one's
leaving just yet.
Yeah, right.
I know what
it was.
(John)
In the womb,
the calf gestated spontaneously.
It was pregnant.
Some problem,
something went wrong.
Somehow it was
defective.
It was carrying these
creatures. Six of them.
One, two, three,
four, five...
I think Orla
missed one.
It's still alive.
You knew about this?
Not everything.
Come on.
You don't get it.
If the missing one
gets off the farm,
thousands of cows will give birth
to millions of these monsters.
It will be
unstoppable.
You can not leave. I'm going to
have to quarantine the farm.
(Jamie)
Would you slow down?
(John)
Oh, my dear God...
It must be here.
Where's the other
cow and calf?
She's in there.
I shut her up.
That was
where Jamie...
What?
You got bitten.
Bitten?
You got bitten?
[loud bawl]
[splash]
What was that?
Jesus!
Come on.
[mooing]
How deep
does it go?
(Dan) Down there by
the end, by the wall,
I'd say around
four or five feet.
If something is in
there, it's trapped.
It would have to
come past us.
Just wait, okay. I think
we can scare it out.
[engine stops]
[engine sputters]
Dan! Get yourself
out of there!
Oh, shit! Shit!
See anything?
(Jamie) No! But, Dan,
would you hurry up!
Be careful.
Shit!
[shouting]
Oh, my God!
Oh, no!!!
No! No! No! Orla!
[sobs]
No! No! No!
[sobbing]
[straining]
What the fuck...
Ohh...
Ahh...
Oh.
In the North Sea, if they
recover a drowned body...
they're cautious
because sometimes...
It's eaten most
of her intestines.
(Jamie) It... The fuckin'
thing, you mean.
Yeah. Give me a hand.
Give me a hand!
It's gone.
The creature, it must have attacked her.
Got inside her clothes.
She tired to
get away.
Somehow, she ended up
in the pit, drowned.
But in the slurry, the body
grows cold, so it moves on.
Looking for
a new host.
Here.
What is that?
This rate of cellular
growth is off the scale.
There are human cells
mixed up with it.
Orla's cells.
[inhales]
Why you doing that?
Shut up!
Shut the fuck up!
That's impossible.
My cells... it's
corrupting them.
The creature,
it can infect humans.
It's the bite.
We have to stop it
getting off the farm.
It could infect
everyone.
People wouldn't know
they've been infected.
But their offspring...
children... Mutated...
Deformed like
those things.
It could wipe out
an entire generation.
Your foot.
Show me, Jamie.
No... Please...
[sobs]
Stay away from me.
No, Jamie.
We're going. Now!
Calm down.
You cannot leave yet.
Show me your foot.
No.
You stay away
from me!
I could help you.
No!
Mary and me,
we're going now!
Mary!
[struggling]
[John strains]
[thump]
[clank]
Fuck you!
[clang]
[pants]
No! You cannot leave!
[click]
[thud]
I feel bad.
Of course you do, Dan.
No.
I mean there's
something wrong.
Something wrong.
[distant thud]
What was that?
Where's Jamie?
Stay back.
Stay back!
It climbs inside
of them.
It's like a parasite.
[brays]
It hides inside
the cows, growing.
It ate it's way
out again.
We have to find it.
It's growing
too fast.
We have to stop it.
What about
the other subject?
Where's your last cow!
(Mary) I'm gonna go get Jamie.
It's in the shed.
Oh, God.
(John) It has to be in this one.
(Dan)
No!
It has given birth already.
We have to find the calf.
These aren't animals
to you, are they?!
They're just test subjects!
Numbers!
Like your fuckin'
lab rats!
Orla's dead!
You've killed my farm!
You hear me!
You're fucking evil!
(Dan) I'm going to
get the Police!
This stops now,
do you hear me!
[click]
You can not leave.
I was wrong.
It does
infect humans!
John...
Oh, God,
Jamie!
[gasps, screams]
[splash]
[pants]
(John)
Shh.
Why?
[click]
[sobs]
What did you
do to him?!
[growling]
Dan!
He killed Jamie, Dan.
He killed Jamie.
Where is he?
(Dan)
Ugh.
It must be here.
[thud, splash]
[hissing]
Dan!
[brays]
[growling]
[braying]
[creaking]
Jesus, Dan,
you can't.
I'll do it.
Are you sure?
Okay.
Up close.
Yeah. Yeah.
[Mary coughs]
[distant braying]
[whispers]
Mary?
[gasp]
[thudding]
[moo]
Mary!
Ngh! Ngh! Ngh!
[thudding]
[soft growling]
[Mary shrieks]
[sobs, shrieks]
(Dan)
Mary!
(Mary)
Dan! Dan!!!
[braying]
[cries]
(Mary)
Ah! Oh, my God!
(Dan)
Mary!
[whispers]
Dan.
Help me.
[braying]
[loud braying]
[Mary shouts]
[growls]
[engine starts]
(Dan)
Fuckin' work!
[sobs]
[growls]
Work!
[engine starts]
Help me!
[screams]
Come on!
[loud clank]
[Mary sobs]
[Dan's distant shouts]
[clank]
[Mary strains]
[machinery working]
[whispers]
Mary.
Come here.
[brays]
(Dan, shouting)
Come on!
[clank]
[growls]
[gasps]
[Dan yells]
Get out!!! Go!!!
Aaah! Aaah!
[screaming]
Get out!!!
[growling]
[straining]
Aaah!
[panting]
[braying]
Ngh! Ngh!
Yah!
[strains]
[keys clink]
[weakly]
I can't...
...leave the farm.
There.
Can you see
the head?
It's fine.
Do you want to know?
It's a girl.
A fine, healthy
looking girl.
So you have no need
to worry any longer.
[machinery beeps]
You have a perfectly
normal baby.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
[Jim Ford sings
I'm Going To Make You Love Me]