Turn right.
Smile for the birdie.
Your first time?
Yeah, mm-hmm.
And you're innocent,
right?
No, I'm absolutely
100% guilty.
Empty all your pockets.
What's the blue money?
Deutschmarks. Keep 'em.
Sit down.
I'll find you a cell.
Don't go anywhere.
Roy, got something nice
for a guy in evening wear?
(phone rings)
(woman) Hello,
Brighton Precinct.
Oh, this?
It's my wedding night.
Oh, no,
I didn't kill my wife.
What happened
really wasn't her fault,
and it certainly
wasn't my fault.
If the Justice Department
had just done its job,
I wouldn't have had
to do it for them.
No, I mean, look at me,
I mean...
I'm not the criminal type.
Far from it.
In fact,
I'm a very law-abiding,
non-violent person
living a peaceful,
quiet life.
I like to think of myself
as someone who always tries
to do the right thing,
even with my garbage.
I volunteer my Sunday to help
the visually impaired.
Is that a fact?
Kid, I got
a gift here for ya.
And far from being
a deadbeat dad,
I gladly support
and even lavish gifts...
Awesome!
on my ex-wife and stepson.
(cries)
Plus, rather than being
a threat to the community,
I'm sure I'm considered
an outstanding neighbor.
(all) Trick or treat!
My first customers.
Early bird gets
all the worms, right?
Well, in this case, candy.
(boy) Thank you.
Oh, boy, do you know
the way to a kid's heart.
(man) Oh, more candy?
Goodness gracious!
Oh, how generous!
Excuse me.
Here, hold my lantern.
There, I want to thank you
for your kindness.
Oh, it's my pleasure.
Listen, please,
stop back anytime.
Auf wiedersehen.
Happy Halloween.
(kids) Thank you!
(all)  Trick or treat,
smell my feet...
(horn sounds)
However, no matter
how honorably we try
to conduct our own lives,
there are others
on this planet
whose behavior
we can't control.
People do awful things
sometimes.
Well, a lot of times,
and, I, like most
of you, I'm sure,
have this perverse fascination
with other people's
bad behavior.
In fact,
evil is my hobby.
Well, more than
a hobby, really.
It's my profession.
Is it just me,
or do many of you also
feel the world is becoming
a more and more
hostile place?
It's no surprise, right?
Because every day,
all around us,
we see examples
of unethical behavior,
abuses of power,
outrageous injustices,
heartless acts of cruelty
that attack our conscience
and, well, repulse
our sense of fairness.
So, we can recognize
when behavior is bad,
but how do we know
when we're being good?
Respect for the law
is essential.
What laws? Apartheid laws?
Abortion laws? "He" laws?
And laws are subject
to change,
but what is moral has been
and always will be.
Morality is forever.
Even on weekends?
(laughter)
The golden rule really works,
but only if everybody
in the world abides by it.
(Jack) Impossible.
Hey, if you're not part
of the solution, you're
part of the problem.
That's a good point.
OK, a guy named Plenides,
an obscure Greek statesman--
Don't even bother
to look him up.
He's only available
on parchment.
Plenides was the first man
to question the practice
of pedophilia.
Now, today, of course,
child molestation
is considered a heinous
and unspeakable crime,
but back in 400 BC,
it was legal,
it was the will
of the people,
and it didn't even break
a commandment.
There's "Thou shalt not covet
thy neighbor's wife."
It doesn't say anything
about thy neighbor's kids.
Well, one day,
Plenides stood up
and he raised
the moral issue
of whether
it was right or wrong.
Plenides said,
"To live a moral life,
"you must do more
than required
and less than allowed."
What happened to Plenides?
He was wrestled to the floor
and stabbed by every member
of the Senate.
(laughter)
So much for speaking up, huh?
Ironically,
the night I first got sucked in
to committing my crime
began on a high note.
You see, I'd been looking
for a new woman in my life,
and as luck would have it,
I was really cookin' that set.
(man) Yeah!
(crowd hoots and hollers)
(announcer) Let's hear it
for the Braxton Quartet.
Remember, every Thursday is
Amateur Night at Dixie's.
It makes it a lot easier
when someone likes you first.
That way they have to come up
with an opening line.
Your high hats
were very crisp tonight.
Oh, you think so?
Yes, really, you play
so well for an amateur.
(sighs)
That didn't
come out right, you know.
Please, it's the nicest
compliment I've gotten.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I could swear
some of your riffs
on "Pick Yourself Up"
sounded familiar.
That's right.
I steal from all
the great drummers.
Oh, well, even the stuff
in between sounded great.
So how come you know
so much about drumming?
Well, my father was
a jazz percussionist
in the '50s, so...
Really? Who with?
Oh, different groups.
Herbie Mann, Kai Winding,
Charlie Mingus.
Charlie Mingus?
Well, I'm Jack Lambert.
Oh, hi.
Can I buy you a drink...?
Oh, Gail.
Gail?
Yeah.
Oh, my date.
Friend.
He's a date friend.
I have to go anyway.
I got a big day tomorrow.
Tonsillectomy first thing
in the morning, so...
I hope you'll be all right.
Oh, I'll be fine.
I perform plenty of 'em.
Oh, doctor.
Yes.
Another time, perhaps?
Well, I jam here
every Thursday.
Great.
Come back.
I will.
(radio announcer)
Gulf War Disease Syndrome
is now being passed on
to the next generation.
And in local news, wanted
Nazi war criminal Karl Luger,
the notorious "Beast"
of Berkau death camp,
where 700,000 people died,
was found living
in the greater Boston area.
Sports and weather
after this.
(Jack) Now if that evening
had ended at the club,
it would have been
a great night,
but it didn't
and it wasn't.
Trouble was lurking
around the corner.
Well, actually,
right next door.
(tape rewinds)
(woman) It's Liz.
Guess what.
They made your kid brother
a partner,
the youngest in the history
of the firm,
so Marty's having people over
Sunday afternoon.
(groans)
I know you're not crazy
about our crowd,
but please
make an appearance.
See you there.
(beep)
(man) Mr. Lambert,
this is Special Agent
Tom Roland of the FBI.
Please contact me
right away at 555-0694.
Thank you.
(dials)
(woman)
You have reached the Federal
Bureau of Investigation.
Our business hours
are 9am to 5pm
Monday through Friday.
Your call is important to us,
so please, contact us--
(hangs up)
The call from the FBI
didn't throw me,
because I hadn't done
anything wrong.
I assumed they were
after a different,
more sinister Lambert.
I finally made the connection
when I saw a familiar face
in the paper.
(TV reporter)
...and was Commandant
of the infamous
Berkau concentration camp.
A member
of the dreaded Waffen SS,
Luger was reputed
to be the most brutal
of Hitler's killers,
and was nicknamed
The Beast of Berkau.
Luger spent the next
13 years as a fugitive,
hiding out in South America,
where he lived comfortably,
raising a daughter.
His daughter spoke to CNN
from her home
in nearby Watertown.
My father was a corporal,
a cook during the war,
a good man
in terrible times,
not a Nazi murderer.
He is completely innocent
of these false charges.
(reporters shouting)
End of statement.
Neighbors expressed
shock and disbelief.
We support Max, no matter
what the circumstances.
He's been my neighbor
for many years.
He was never a Nazi to me,
but if Max did
all those things
that they're saying he did,
it's despicable,
and he's a horrible,
disgusting man.
But if he didn't,
he's a great guy.
(Shaw) Luger entered
the United States
from Ecuador in 1959
under the false identity
of Max Mueller,
where he spent
the next 30 years
a resident of Brighton,
Massachusetts.
That's my house!
It's him!
Now I remember.
(radio announcer)
It's a tie ballgame, 1-1...
Good morning,
kind neighbor.
(turns radio off)
Yes, hello.
Hello!
I wonder if I might
bother you for an easy favor.
Sure.
Ah.
You see how your tree grows
over onto my property?
That didn't used
to be a problem,
but now I have put in
a stone patio,
and these little--this looks
like a little plum here--
What do you call this?
What is it?
Oh, yes, sir,
it's a mulberry.
A mulberry? Oh, well,
that's your problem, see,
it's your mulberries,
because they fall down
and they crack open
and ooze out and they leave
this purple stain.
Here, you see?
Now, I can-- look, I can get
this stain off of my fingers,
but I can't get it
off the stones, you see?
What do you think
we should do about it, hmm?
Well, if you want to cut
the tree on your side of
the fence, feel free to do so.
That's good,
that's very good.
Danke. Thank you.
Ah, sure.
(Shaw) He was tried in absentia
by a Latvian court,
found guilty of crimes
against humanity
and sentenced to death.
Although Mueller says
he is innocent,
all claims of mistaken identity
have been ruled out.
The FBI and forensic
experts worldwide
have concluded
that the two photos are
of the same man--Karl Luger,
The Beast of Berkau.
I'm Bernard Shaw,
CNN, Washington.
It was hard to believe
I shared a mulberry tree
with the most brutal
of Hitler's killers,
but the evidence
was overwhelmingly conclusive.
(reporters chattering)
And then again, there were
those obvious signs
that he could be
a mass murderer.
He was quiet, polite
and kind to children.
...and that would be
a really lovely place.
You know, he could be
playing outside--
Hi, Liz.
You made it!
Mm-hmm.
Good!
Hello.
Marty around
anywhere?
Oh, somewhere.
Everybody wants
a piece of him today.
There he is.
I'd been there
one month before--
(Jack) Marty, congratulations!
Jack!
Well, I guess I'll
catch up with him later.
Oh, there's some vegetarian
pupus over by the swing.
Mmm, gotta see those.
(man) With the heliport,
I can make it to the cape
in 20 minutes.
Champagne?
Actually,
we have two heliports--
one in the office downtown
and one on the factory
in Brighton.
Brighton?
What did I just hear
happened in Brighton?
(man) Anyway,
the big expense
is the pilot.
His insurance rates
are astronomical.
They found a Nazi war criminal
living in Brighton.
I read about that.
I fact, you know,
he's my neighbor.
He lives directly
in back of me.
Really?
Where in Brighton
do you live?
Near the monument.
Do you know him?
What's he like?
Well, I only met him
a couple of times briefly.
He seemed affable.
Of course, I didn't know
I was staring right into
the face of evil.
I know the area--
single-family homes,
good schools.
But he's a model citizen
all these years.
He's mended his ways.
I say leave him be.
I agree. I mean,
let bygones be bygones.
That's easy for you to say
if they're not your bygones.
But what gives you the right
to forgive injustices that
happened to someone else?
Only the victims
have that right,
and they sentenced Luger
to death 50 years ago.
Hmm.
Interesting take.
Are you thinking
of moving?
Wh-Why? I don't know.
I'm Joel Wayne
with Century 21.
I'd love to list you.
I see.
Why are you leaving
so soon?
I got to go home and change.
I take someone shopping
on Sundays.
More volunteer work?
You're turning into
Brother Teresa.
Hey, congratulations.
Ahh.
You're a gifted tax attorney
and you deserve your name
on the door.
Yeah, it's down by the doorknob,
but who knows for how long, huh?
You're getting
what you always wanted,
even as a kid--
money and power.
A lot of people have
money and power now.
I want what
the big boys have.
Yeah, what's that?
I want to be feared.
(groans)
Come here.
Find another ambition,
Marty, please.
Nice party. Thanks.
Drive safe.
When I arrived home
later that day,
there was a commotion
at Luger's house.
I thought
he was being arrested
and sent back to Latvia
to face a firing squad.
Instead,
he was having a party.
I really had no business
in going over there,
but I knew it would be
the last chance I'd ever have
to be in the company of a truly
certifiably evil man.
It was just too tantalizing
an offer to pass up.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm Simon Brownell.
I will be going to bat
in the courtroom for Max,
and now you're asking
what you can do.
All right, give as much
as you can afford
for Max's defense fund.
It's tax deductible.
Write your congressman,
call the media--
let them know that
you are outraged
by these actions,
and I promise you
our government
will not send
this innocent man
to face death in Latvia!
(clears throat)
I'm going to need your help.
This is going to be
a long and costly
legal battle, but--
but with a little luck,
Max will be your neighbor
for another 20 years.
(dog barking)
(man) Absolutely.
(man #2) Yes.
Thank you, Mr...?
Most of you have
known me for years,
some of you
even longer, hmm?
You have been in my home,
I have been in yours.
We have borrowed
each other's things.
You know me.
You know that I could not
possibly be some Nazi beast.
You know I could never
hurt a fly.
You know me.
(applause)
(dog barks)
It was a lousy party,
and like the boy
right after he stepped
out of the plastic bubble,
I felt contaminated,
dirty.
After we pee pee,
what do we do?
(boys) Wash our hands.
And then what?
(boys) Dry them.
On what?
(both) On the towel.
Not on your trousers.
(both) We know.
(water running)
(Jack) There's someone
in here, just a sec.
(woman) Hello?
(knocks on door)
There's someone in here.
Just a second, please.
Next time, do not wait
till the last minute.
Be quick.
Excuse me,
I am Inga Mueller,
my father's daughter.
Who are you?
Jack, a neighbor.
I live on the other side
of the back fence.
Excuse me.
Please forgive my directness,
but you are unfamiliar to me.
I thought you might be
with the FBI or the press.
They crawl over us like bugs
and make our lives
a living hell.
I know.
The FBI interviewed me.
What did--
what did you tell them?
Everything I know--
nothing.
Thank you. We are
very pleased that so many
of you showed up today.
They say that Mr. Brownell
is one of the top immigration
lawyers in the country.
Have you heard of him?
I think so.
He may have handled
the John Lennon case.
The Beatle?
Mm-hmm.
Anyway, he feels
we have a strong case,
that after so many years,
evidence is lost,
witnesses die,
or their memories
can be faulted.
OK, so long.
Don't leave!
Does my father know
that you are here?
Come, say hello.
Father, look who is here.
What?
The house in back, Dad.
(growls, barks)
Ach, ja!
That's the mulberry man.
Ja!
Oh, isn't it nice?
Oh! Schatzi, no,
he is a friend.
No, Schatzi, no.
No, no, Schatzi, don't.
Schatzi, no.
Don't do that.
No, Schatzi, stop.
Nein!
Nein, Schatzi!
Nein, Schatzi.
Nein. Now sit.
I said don't do that
to the nice man.
OK. You don't know me
so well as the others,
so I'm especially pleased
to see you here.
May God bless you.
Excuse me.
I've got to be going.
Apple cider?
My father made it himself.
No, I've got to get home.
Do you have family waiting?
No, I've got to grade
some papers for school.
A teacher?
Mm-hmm.
Well then, in that case,
you are excused.
Thank you.
A splendid man.
Max is the real victim
in this case.
You know,
Max never misses
a Patriots game.
In the first place,
there are no war criminals
'cause there was no Holocaust.
Everyone knows
it never happened.
Have you read this?
Read what?
There are new facts
in here that prove--
Excuse me.
I couldn't help
overhearing,
but did you just say
the Holocaust never
happened?
It was a hoax perpetrated
by Zionists.
The real truth
is all in here.
Let me ask you
this question--
did World War II
happen?
Of course it did.
What are you
talking about?
How do you know?
You weren't there.
How do you actually
know it took place?
My father served in it.
He told me.
OK, so we have an eyewitness
who lived through the war.
You've probably seen
old film footage
of Germans shooting
at American soldiers?
And maybe old
TV documentaries of Hitler?
It's the same with
the Holocaust. There are
thousands of eyewitnesses.
Guys, American soldiers
like your dad, who liberated
the camps, for God's sake.
That fact of the matter is
that both events took place
in the same time
at the same place,
so why believe one
and not the other?
Whose side are you on?
There's no sides
in this issue.
There are to me, buddy,
and you're not on it!
Did you just touch me?
Yeah, I'll touch you again!
That's right!
Who are you touchin'?
I'm touchin' you!
You don't deserve
to be an American!
(punching)
(Jack) Ow! Oh!
(PA) Dr. Evans, Radiology.
(Jack) The last time
I lost a fight was
in the sixth grade,
and I just stopped
thinking about it last year.
And this one wasn't going
to go away so fast, either.
(PA) Mr. and Mrs. Miller
to Admitting.
Take my gunshot,
will you?
Sure.
Jo, can I get
the chart on the guy
with the face thing and--
Thank you.
Comin' through.
Jack? It is you.
It's your groupie, hmm?
Gail, hi. How are you?
A little better
than you, I bet.
How'd you do this, Jack?
Car accident?
No, a fight.
Hmm. From the looks
of that hand, I'd hate
to see the other guy.
Yeah.
But then I started
to think, you know,
what would've happened to me
in Germany under the Nazis?
An intellectual, an academic.
All you had to be
was Jewish, Catholic,
gay, Communist, handicapped,
Gypsy or "other"
and you're
automatically exterminated.
And you say
nothing's going to happen
to this terrible man?
Well, Luger's already
in his 70s.
Case'll be tied up
in courts for years.
He'll probably live out
the rest of his life
next door to me.
Let it go, Jack.
Keep your hand still.
You fought the good fight,
literally.
I didn't hit anybody.
He st--
(hyperventilating)
Keep your hand still.
OK, relax,
slow and deep breaths.
Slow and deep--
(breathing slows)
OK, you're OK.
If this ever happens again,
blow into a paper bag
and breathe back
your own oxygen.
Jesus, what was that?
Just your body telling
your mind
to change the subject.
Keep your hand still.
Well, nothing's broken,
but the ribs
are badly bruised,
so you're gonna have
general body trauma
for the next few days.
(grunts)
Let me help you up here.
I'll get a bandage
on that hand.
All right, I'm gonna
give you something for the pain
that you can take at home.
Thank you.
OK.
You're getting
the royal treatment, Jack.
I'm going
to bandage you myself.
Oh, wow, that's great.
Sit right there.
OK. You're doin' OK.
My main concern
was that hand.
You're not going to drum
for a while, I'm sorry,
but it should heal
completely.
Good.
So, Jack, tell me...
Are you...?
Well, go ahead.
Are you married?
No.
Do you live with anyone?
Unh-unh, just me.
I live alone.
OK, well, then,
what I need you to do is
soak this hand in warm water
and epsom salt
2 to 3 times a day
for about 15 minutes,
and then at the end
of the night, pack it in ice
for about 20 minutes.
OK.
It's important.
I'll do it.
But...
(PA) Code blue, OR-4.
If I might ask...
Code blue, Dr. Holland.
what is your--
Oh, I'm sorry,
I got to take that.
I'll send a nurse in
to take care of this.
Your personal situation?
It's like this every night.
Oh.
Except next Wednesday.
Can I help you
out of here?
Yeah, thanks.
Keep the change.
Every single fiber
of my body ached
except for my heart.
So I decided
to turn my attention
to thoughts of love
and just ignore
my neighbor from hell.
(Max's voice) "Dear Professor,
I was terribly saddened
"to hear about your beating.
"Those ignorant hooligans
only serve to further ruin
my reputation.
"I deeply appreciate
your support,
"and please know
you have mine, too.
Your friend,
Max Mueller."
(Inga's voice)
"P.S. The cabbage soup
will speed your recovery.
Also your friend,
Inga Mueller."
I don't need
your Nazi soup.
(dog barking)
(car door closes)
(Max) Schatzi,
stay in the house.
(singing)
You know how they say
you can't find love,
it finds you?
Well, it's the same
with hate.
It just takes someone
to push your buttons,
and seeing Luger alive
and kicking was pushing mine.
He'd been sentenced to death
50 years ago
and he still wasn't dead.
It was time to speak up.
Hi, Kim.
Hi.
Airmail,
special delivery.
Letters to
your congressmen, huh?
I hope it's about
those damn leaf blowers.
Let me tell you something.
They're nothing!
(radio host)
Hello, you're on the air.
(Jack) I'd like to get back
to that Luger case.
I'm gonna need you
to turn your radio down.
(feedback)
(feedback stops)
Yes, I'm calling
about the Karl Luger case.
OK, we covered that
last hour.
And so you figure
that an hour is sufficient
to cover one of history's
greatest injustices
and one that continues
to this day as we speak?
Whoa, there are a lot
of problems in the world,
and to be fair, we give
the same weight to each one.
In fact, this hour,
we're covering
older married men
obsessed with teenagers.
So now you're comparing
the engineered extermination
of an entire race of people
to aberrant sexuality?
(dial tone)
Hello?
Assholes!
(Max) My friend,
my friend.
(man) Don't worry about
a thing, all right?
(man #2) Good night, Max.
I sensed I was headed
for trouble
when I began spending hours
in my attic watching Luger,
in the morning
at his apple tree
and at night during
those damned fundraisers.
My God, I'd been obsessed
with women before,
but never with a man.
And I walk over to her,
and I'm trying to relax her
and calm her down
and I said, "I like your hair."
And she has a Southern accent,
and she says, "My hair makes me
closer to Jesus."
It looked like she'd gone
to an ice cream store
to get her hair done.
Three scoops.
So anyway, I bring her...
Oh, Jack! Oh, honey!
(moaning)
Uh-oh.
I'm sorry, I don't know
what's wrong with me tonight!
It's OK. It happens.
Not to me.
Well, thanks.
I needed to hear that.
Oh, Gail, it's not you.
I know it.
Jack, I'm
the only one here.
Was I too aggressive?
Is that it?
Sometimes
I have a habit of--
You know, I like somebody
and I show it.
No, it's got nothing
to do with you, believe me.
It really doesn't.
I don't know, Jack.
Sometimes it's hard for me
to tell what you're feeling.
Not tonight--that was
just one of those things.
But other times,
when we've been out together,
it's like you're not there.
I know,
but there's a really
good reason for that,
and that is because
I feel so comfortable
when I'm with you
that I feel
I don't have to be there.
It's a good thing?
Yeah, it's the freedom
to be alone
without being lonely.
Oh, yes, like being
with a friend.
You're driving cross-country,
neither of you saying a word,
hours goin' by,
lost in your own thoughts.
Exactly.
So I'm a friend?
Yes.
Great.
No.
My feelings are
far more than friendly
for you, Gail.
I mean, come on, I-I--
I'm crazy about you.
You've come into my life.
You're just a golden thing.
I know.
(moaning)
Jack! Ohh...
Uh-oh.
I'm sure it's not you.
It's rage, Professor Lambert,
anger at an unfair world
which is indifferent
to your just demands
and expectations.
Over a lifetime, to survive
these constant disappointments,
people make a deal
with their feelings,
as if reason
could deny them a way.
But the rage,
the rage lives inside you,
screaming for expression.
Unresolved with no outlet,
it attacks within,
first as self-loathing
at your helplessness
and ineffectuality,
leading to a sense of weakness
that leaves you limp,
and eventually you sink
into a state of despair
and hopelessness.
And as your will
and your spirit weakens,
so does your body.
Vulnerable,
you fall victim
to tumors,
cerebral hemorrhages,
strokes, other forms
of premature death.
(bell rings)
We have to stop here now.
What happens next?
We talk.
How many years
depends on you.
Well, now, listen,
in the meantime,
I need something.
I can't sleep and I'm shaky,
and sometimes I feel like
I'm losing control.
That's good.
You're in too much control.
You live in your head,
you intellectualize
everything.
You need to deal
with things more viscerally.
I want you
to act out your feelings
so we can examine them.
All right.
The goal of therapy
is to find out
who you really are
and change that.
But first, let's
find you an opening.
Isn't there
some kind of pill
you can recommend?
I'm the best pill,
Professor Lambert.
I want to see you
six days a week.
Good.
But I can't.
How's every other Thursday
at 3:15?
All right.
See you then.
Yeah.
Thursday, Thursday,
every other--Oh. Oh.
Have a nice day.
Thank you.
Professor Lambert.
Oh, I see you've
recovered nicely
from your beating.
That's good,
that's very good.
And you needn't worry
about any more
ugly disturbances
in the neighborhood, eh?
I'm going to South America.
What, on vacation?
Permanently.
My lawyer's
arranging the details.
I'm going to emigrate
back to Ecuador
where they accept me
as I am.
Ah, so, auf wiedersehen.
Wait, is this official?
Oh, ja.
Ja, I leave in ten days.
Jesus!
See, I could stay.
I could stay and I could
fight for my innocence,
but the media
and those Zionists...
They hound me.
They hound me always.
If you pour two pounds
of manure on somebody,
you could say
they stink, ja?
Ja.
Take care of yourself,
good care.
Don't let the bastards
get you down.
But this is wrong!
Yeah, I agree,
but at least down there
they will let me
live in peace.
Ja, so...
auf wiedersehen.
(muttering)
I don't believe this.
I can't believe it.
The guy's gonna walk.
(TV announcer)
From the nation's capital,
The McLaughlin Group,
an unrehearsed program
presenting inside opinions
and forecasts
on major issues of the day.
Here's the moderator
John McLaughlin.
Issue one:
getting away with murder.
You said it.
Nazi Karl Luger is
getting away with mass murder.
You bet he is!
How is this possible, Morton?
Just luck, I guess, John.
Oh, shut up! Luck!
Technically, it's because
Ecuador has no extradition
treaty with Latvia.
And if the US avoids
a very embarrassing
prosecution of Mueller,
what's wrong with that?
Mueller? His name's Luger!
The man's name is Luger.
The issue here is justice.
Right.
There's no statute of
limitations for crimes
against humanity
and there shouldn't be.
Right!
(McLaughlin) OK, exit question.
On an outrage scale of 0-10,
rate the world's outrage
regarding Luger.
Ten, baby. Ten!
(Morton) Zilch, zero.
Come on! Kiss my
gray rimpled ass,
all right?!
The answer is a minus one.
See what the boys
in the back room will have
And tell them
that I'll have the same
Just see what the boys
in the back room will have
And tell--give them
the poison they name
And when I die,
don't waste my money
On flowers
And my picture
(squirrel chattering)
Ah, my little friend
is back.
You like my apples, eh?
(speaking German)
That did it.
When I saw Luger cane
that innocent little
squirrel, I snapped.
I knew he couldn't be allowed
to live out his life in peace
on some sunny
South American beach.
Throw the ball.
He's open!
Throw it to him!
Yeah!
(announcer speaking
Spanish on TV)
OK, right 88!
You don't kill 700,000 people
and get away with it,
not in Mr. Lambert's
neighborhood.
Oddly enough, I had no problem
with it morally.
He deserved to die,
so killing him was
the right thing to do,
but planning the murder
was a bitch.
See, since I practically
lived at the scene
of the crime,
I needed to concoct an alibi
that would place me miles
from home on the night
of the murder.
So the obvious weapon
had to be cyanide.
See, it was quick, clean,
and allowed me to be away
at the exact time of death.
And best of all, I knew
precisely where to get some
under the table.
Doug.
Hey, Jack.
How long does it usually take
for the poison to work?
Eight, ten seconds,
depending on the size
of the rat.
The rat?
A little smaller than me.
Hey, hey, Jack, Jack.
Don't ever, ever tell anyone
I gave this to you.
I could be in big trouble.
I will not be breathing
a word of this to anyone.
It'll be our little secret.
I was amazed at how once
I had decided to take action,
everything fell into place.
I knew the who,
what, where, why
and how I would commit
the murder.
The only question
left hanging...
(Max talking)
...was when.
No, bring it to me.
(Inga) Hello? Yoo-hoo!
(knocking on door)
Professor Lambert!
Who's that?
Yoo-hoo!
Professor Lambert,
yoo-hoo!
Excuse me.
Excuse me, excuse me!
Mrs. Mueller--
Mueller, right?
May I help you?
Inga.
And please forgive me
for entering your home
without permission,
but did you know
your door was wide open?
Yeah, I was in a hurry
before and I forgot
to close it.
You bowl also.
Just a beginner.
May I?
Sure.
It is very heavy. Ohh!
Yeah, it's heavy.
But you know your arm.
I need a lighter one, of course.
I am just a woman.
So...
So your house--
just as I expected.
Oh, what a lovely hobby.
Oh, African trinkets,
Italian movies,
American jazz--
an international man.
Needless to say,
I didn't want this woman
snooping around my house.
What was she doing here?
What did she want?
And look at these books.
Books, rows and rows of books.
Books everywhere.
I have difficulty
reading myself.
I have a wandering eye,
but it is hardly noticeable.
Look.
Well, I-I-I wouldn't--
No, no,
look straight at me,
now quickly look
to the left.
Oh, well...
I never noticed
your eyes before.
You were wearing glasses
last time we met.
Yes, I generally wear glasses.
Sometimes I wear contacts,
but I don't really
like contacts.
A shame. You have
compelling eyes.
Thanks a lot.
Was there something you...?
As you know, my father
is being forced to leave
the country.
Yes. That hasn't changed,
has it?
No, he is leaving
next week.
That's what I thought.
And we are throwing a little
goodbye party for him
at his house on Sunday
for all the friends,
neighbors and supporters
like yourself.
Are you free?
Sunday day
or Sunday night?
In the evening only,
starting at seven.
Seven till when,
do you think?
Not past 11. After all,
it is a school night,
professor.
Yeah.
Well, I'm glad
you stopped by.
It was very thoughtful of you
to think of me,
and thank you
for inviting me.
I think it's something
I'd probably like to do.
So then,
I will see you there?
Ah, no, I have
a family function
of my own that night.
Oh.
Family.
I like that.
Sunday.
The night of the murder,
I was double-booked.
First I had to take Gail
to a birthday dinner for Marty.
Everybody seemed to be
having a good time,
so I don't think
anyone noticed
that I had other things
on my mind.
I tried to act normal,
because it was very important
that nothing I did
seemed out of
the ordinary that night.
(car horn blaring)
Well, that was a rush.
I'm sorry, honey.
I've got a lot
of things to do tonight.
Tonight?
It's already 10:00.
I know, but I'm preparing
a new lecture for tomorrow.
I thought I'd see
a film on the subject
and stay at a motel
on route 10,
kind of save myself
the commute, work on it
in the morning.
I like that you're
so dedicated to your work.
Love you.
Love you, too.
I'll get my own door.
There it is.
Call me.
(spits)
(chuckles)
(dog panting)
Easy there, Schatzi.
Stay right there.
(barking)
Get away from the fence.
(barks)
Easy, easy.
Oh...
That's right,
I'm a friend.
Jerry.
Hi, how you
doing tonight?
(both gasp)
Oh my God, Jerry!
(tires screech)
Oh, no!
(car horn blaring)
Oh!
He's gone.
He's back!
Sorry, folks.
(horn sounds)
Sink, damn it. Sink.
Come on.
There you go.
(Max humming)
Ooh, my beauty.
Donde est
la tienda de frutos?
Donde est la ti--?
Ach, ich habe das vergessen.
Ach.
Goddamned Justice Department.
(Max humming)
Ahh...
(humming)
(continues humming)
Hey!
(grunting)
Miss!
Miss! Miss!
Hold your horses.
May I help you?
Yes, I'm curious.
Did you make this
coffee yourself?
Yes, what's
wrong with it?
Nothing.
It's the greatest coffee
I've ever had.
I thought you must've liked it.
You drank close to 20 cups.
Hi, I'm Jack Lambert.
I teach at Braxton College.
Hi, I'm Patti.
I drank so much
of your great coffee,
I kind of lost
all track of time.
How long
have I been sitting here?
I think you came in
sometime after three.
No, it was 2:30,
and it's 6:30 now,
so I've been sitting here
for over four hours.
Would you like
your check now, Mr. Lambo?
Lambert! I teach
at Braxton, remember?
Maybe it is time
for your check.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to snap.
You should've stuck
with the decaf, darlin'.
Here's your check, Lambo.
Thanks.
Forget the tip.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
(man) It's 12:00.
Get up.
Thank you.
Come on, come on,
where's the news?
Oh, one of these.
Hi.
Excuse me,
can you change the channel
on the TV for me please?
I wanna see if there's
a certain story on.
The one about that Nazi
from Brighton?
Yes. What, he's dead?
Yep, he killed himself.
No. Wasn't he murdered?
Not what I heard.
Huh?
...by lacing his ritual
morning apple juice
with cyanide.
Police saw no evidence
of foul play,
and Luger's death
has officially been
ruled a suicide.
(female reporter)
Oddly, Luger took his life
just days before he was
to emigrate to Ecuador...
What?!
but his daughter told reporters
he was despondent
over allegations linking him
to Nazi war crimes.
(male reporter)
Obviously, Heather,
this story is far from over,
and let me remind our viewers
that there will be
an in-depth report,
"Suicide Among Accused Nazis,"
on the news at nine.
This has been a New England
Cable News special report.
We now...
Satisfied, friend?
Why wasn't I satisfied?
He was dead,
and I was off the hook.
Hell, the police didn't even
think there'd been a murder.
(woman)
I'm glad he's dead.
So what was bothering me?
I hate those damn Nazis.
I wish they would all
kill themselves.
(horn sounds)
That was it.
History would record
that Luger took his own life.
Unh-unh. No way.
He wasn't good enough
for suicide.
I had to let the world know
that he was punished
for his crime...
without taking any credit,
of course.
I mean, getting caught
was not part of my plan.
So to set the record
straight,
I knocked off a quick note
to the police.
(man) "Luger did not
take his own life.
"His death was a punishment,
not a choice.
"Luger was sentenced to death
by a Latvian court.
"Society has an obligation
to carry out the sentence.
"When legal means
failed to serve,
it became a moral issue..."
Wait, there's more.
There were other apples
injected with cyanide, too.
The lab boys figured that
they were contaminated
the previous evening.
The coroner, he found
a massive amount of poison
in the victim's system,
and he estimates
the time of death
around 6am.
Jesus, what if
we've got an individual
who decides to kill everybody
who deserves to die?
It'll make a lot of people
in this country very nervous.
This crime scene's a mess.
Look at all these
footprints and debris.
What the hell's this?
That's sauerkraut.
They had a get-together
that night at the house.
We're workin'
on a guest list.
OK, OK,
what do we got?
We got a literate letter,
we got a revenge killing
by poison
with the most
likely suspect
a party guest.
Sounds like a case
for "Hercules Parrot."
Who?
"Allowing Luger
the gift of life
that he denied others
"is a greater evil
than his murder,
"so killing Luger
became the moral imperative.
Sincerely..."
Obviously, it's unsigned.
(man) Questions?
(Stanley) We have no answers.
I don't know about
right or wrong,
but all I know,
what is right
is that he's dead.
(channels changing)
(woman) ...the rise
of vigilantism in
the United States.
However, the results
of our CNN public opinion poll
show a significant 75%
approve of his actions.
That approval rating
is even higher
than the one
for Bernhard Goetz.
Wow.
(psychiatrist)
So how are you
feeling physically?
(Jack) Good. Powerful.
Any anxiety?
None at all.
What brought on this
miraculous change?
Did someone put you
on Prozac?
Nope, I'm the best pill.
I remember last time
you were helpless
as a kitten--
tortured and impotent,
begging for medication,
obsessed with that
Nazi neighbor of yours
who was murdered recently.
Any thoughts about that?
Do you tape these sessions?
No.
Whatever I say to you
remains between us, right?
Like these are
privileged conversations,
like with a lawyer
or doctor?
I am a doctor, and, yes,
all of our conversations
are completely confidential
by state law.
Really?
Yes.
No matter what I tell you
about myself or what I've done?
That's right.
The only exception is
if you inform me
that you're about
to commit a crime,
I'm obligated to inform
the police or alert
the intended victim.
However, if you tell me
about something
that's already happened,
I can only advise you.
That's the way it is.
(bell rings)
(both) We have to stop
here now.
It was the happiest
I can ever remember being.
Oh, I felt a twinge
of remorse,
but I truly believed
the world was a better place
for my having done it,
and in all other respects,
I was back in the saddle.
(moaning)
(rhythm)
Jack-don't-stop!
Don't-stop!
(in rhythm)
Don't-worry-I-can't!
A Danish philosopher
once said...
(speaks Danish)
Loosely translated
it means,
"What goes up..."
and you know the rest.
It has dual bands--
AM/FM--
it's got Mega Bass
for enhanced
playback quality
and two-speed function
record and playback.
It's also voice-activated,
comes with
a separate microphone,
and check this out--
it can take your temperature.
1, 2, 3...
and, see?
99.9. I'm feverish.
I must smell a sale coming.
Jeez, that is fantastic.
My  fianc's a doctor.
She'd love one of these.
Here, take this slip
and give it to one
of the cash registers,
and they will give you
the merchandise.
Thank you very much.
Thanks.
I need
some headphones, too.
Those are on sale this week.
They're from Europe.
For a startling development
in the Karl Luger killing,
this is a WCHB
special report.
(Inga) If it weren't for you,
my father would be alive today.
You encouraged a crazy person
to commit a vicious act
of violence.
You are irresponsible liars.
We told you all along my father
was not that Nazi beast,
but, no,
you would not listen.
Now you will know the facts.
Max Mueller was
a simple and decent man,
and now he will be
remembered as one.
Shame on you.
Shame on you, all of you!
Shame on you!
Go do something useful!
And so, in Brighton,
a bizarre case
of mistaken identity.
The man murdered
for being Karl Luger,
The Beast of Berkau,
has now been
positively identified
as Corporal Max Mueller,
a lowly cook
in the German army.
Mueller's wartime file
was among documents...
No.
found in
an East German archive.
No!
Justice Department officials
in Washington now say...
I see you're interested
in our televisions.
No!
...the dead man
is Max Mueller,
not Karl Luger.
(Shaw) Israeli officials
concur with the findings.
No!
There's no doubt whatsoever
in our minds.
We are completely satisfied
that the dead man
is not Karl Luger.
(Jack groans)
The whereabouts of
the real Luger remain unknown,
and the "Sincere Slayer,"
whoever he is,
can now live
with the knowledge
that he has taken the life
of an innocent, sickly old man.
He probably never harmed
anyone in his life.
I thought of killing myself,
but that would only continue
the cycle of violence.
I know I just can't go on
as if nothing happened.
I took an innocent life,
and I have to atone for that,
I want to!
Whatever it takes!
Why don't you
turn yourself in
to the police?
Are you out of your mind?
I mean, you know,
if the police caught me
for killing Luger, so be it,
but I'm not gonna go to jail
for killing the wrong man.
I'd go down as one
of the biggest idiots
in history.
My name would be
a punch line!
Besides, what good
can I do in jail?
That's not the answer.
So, what is the answer,
professor?
I'll punish myself.
(man) Right this way. We have
a beautiful table for you.
Sit down.
Thank you.
We have
no specials today,
but you look
through the menu.
I'll be right back, OK?
The lady not show up?
Maybe she can't
find you here.
Why don't you sit inside
with the others?
No, I asked for this table.
I want to sit at this table.
She'll be here.
You wanna order
some appetizer?
I don't think we're gonna
get to eat, thank you.
Oh, to drink only
you must sit at the bar.
OK, I promise
I'll order something.
Here she is.
Just, please,
leave the water
and leave us alone,
will you?
Hi, honey.
Sorry I'm late.
Gail--
Jack, this table,
all by ourselves,
very romantic.
Gail--
Oh, what a day.
I told my mother.
She's thrilled
and horrified.
"You're gonna marry a man
you've known such a short time?"
I said, "Mom, you knew
Dad, what, five days
when you got married?
It lasted 37 years.
37 miserable years,
but anyway--
Gail!
What?
I can't come
to our wedding.
I have to be
someplace else that day.
And where would that be?
A funeral.
Oh, Jack, I'm sorry.
Whose?
A neighbor's.
Another death
in your neighborhood?
The same one.
The Nazi?
He wasn't a Nazi.
He wasn't in
the Einsatz group.
He was a chef, a cook
in the goddamn Wehrmacht,
for--
A case
of mistaken identity.
That's very bizarre.
Anyway, now they gotta
rebury him as himself.
The whole thing's
affected me very deeply.
Well, I understand,
so send some flowers
or a basket of fruit.
I have to be there.
OK, we have
no specials today.
I'm not eating.
Me, either.
Oh, but you promised!
Ay-yi!
What's going on, Jack?
Look, you don't know me.
I'm no good.
I mean, you are--
you're better off
without me, Gail.
Oh, God.
I am so sorry to hurt you.
You are a wonderful, loving,
kind, decent person--
So what's wrong?
I'm unworthy of you.
I don't deserve you.
Why, Jack?
What's happened?
I can't tell you.
What do you mean,
you can't tell me?
I wish I could.
Of course you can tell me.
You can tell me anything.
Not this.
Not what?
What's going on?!
You're not gonna tell me?
No.
Jack, please talk to me...
because once I get up
from this table and walk
out the door,
you'll never see me again.
I can't tell you.
Breaking up with Gail
was excruciatingly painful,
but it wasn't nearly enough.
I still felt I owed
a tremendous debt
to my victim's family.
And so we say goodbye
to our dear
departed brother Max,
a man of love
who was felled by hate.
(Inga) You are very kind.
(woman) God bless you.
Thank you.
(woman #2) We love you,
my dear.
Thank you.
So sorry about Max.
(camera shutter clicking)
I feel so bad
about everything.
Thank you.
Listen, if I can be
of any help...
Thank you.
...in any way.
Thank you very much.
Anything.
Thank you.
I'll call you.
(man) First, they didn't
want to get involved,
then they supported
the Nazi's murder,
then when they find out
the guy's not a Nazi,
they come forward.
It's good we have such
concerned citizens.
You sure it was that
Sunday night you saw the guy?
Yes, it was the night of
our daughter's anniversary.
Uh-huh, and you saw
the guy's face?
He looked right at me,
and said, "Hi, how you doing?"
Real friendly like.
So you could identify him
if you saw him again?
No, no.
"No, no"? Why not?
Well, his face was
all covered in black.
All you could see
were the eyes
and his lips and teeth
when he smiled.
Like a minstrel?
No, a terrorist.
He was wearing
a ski mask?
What kind of a car
was he driving--
foreign or American?
American.
Japanese, I think.
He thinks it was a Toyota,
but it was taller
than a Toyota.
(Inga) My life has been
totally uprooted.
I am lost
without my father.
He did everything for us.
Inga Mueller needed
a shoulder to cry on,
and I was the perfect choice,
because I totally agreed
with everything she said.
Murderers don't realize,
it's not just
the victims that die.
They kill
the loved ones, too.
And this "Sincere" madman--
he is no front-page
TV movie hero,
he is a menace to people.
He should never have
another decent meal.
Over the next few weeks,
I devoted a lot of time
to Inga and the twins,
doing whatever I could
to help ease the pain
all of us were feeling.
(woman) Schatzi Mueller?
I'm Schatzi's mother.
Your dog is ready.
The tests
were negative.
It was just
depression.
Here's
your bill.
Thank you.
(gasps) Oh, my God.
Ohh.
Hey, what's wrong?
You OK?
I do not know
how I will make it.
The funerals
took all of my savings.
My father's life insurance
is tied up in probate
because of the circumstances
of his death.
How can I raise
two growing children?
How will I ever pay
for their college?
Frankly, I am stumped.
(door opens)
(dog barking)
(boys) Hi, Schatzi.
Hi, Schatzi.
You look great.
Schatzi.
(Jack) Give all my money
to Inga Mueller,
but she mustn't know
that it came from me.
(Marty) Let me
get this straight.
You're talking about
your CDs, your IRAs,
your insurance policies,
everything?
Yeah, leave enough
for my stepson's
higher education
and a funeral plot for me,
then give all the rest to her.
Why?
Look, just convert it
to cash,
put it in a blind trust
for her and her children.
No, if you put something
in a blind trust,
you can't get to it, ever.
But I don't want it.
I want her to have it.
What if later on
you change your mind,
and you don't
want her to have it?
I'll never
change my mind!
(baby cries)
I'm sorry, Liz.
Look, bro, you're in love,
and that's wonderful,
but this isn't
the way to show it.
This is crazy!
Listen, Marty,
if you're not gonna
do this for me,
I'll just find
someone who will.
Jack, come on inside
the house.
I swear you are
one of a kind.
They broke the mold
when they made you.
Let's hope so.
Hi, sweetie.
(police radio chattering)
(man) Look at this.
Come here, come here.
Look, look.
You got scuff marks
here on this side.
Any scuff marks there?
(man #2) There's a lot
of 'em over here.
Over here
and over here.
There's a bunch
of 'em.
May I help you?
Yes, we're with
the "Sincere Slayer"
task force.
You mind if we
ask a few questions,
Professor Lambert?
No, not at all.
I don't know much,
just what I've read about
in the newspaper,
seen on television,
just like every
normal, average,
everyday citizen.
Who lives
on the other side?
That's where Mueller lived.
So it's just a hop,
skip and a jump
over and back?
I wouldn't--
You own a blue Volvo,
don't you, Professor?
Uh, yes. Why?
As coincidence would have it,
Professor Lambert,
a man wearing a black ski mask
was seen driving a blue Volvo
in the vicinity
on the night of the murder.
We vacuumed around
Mueller's apple tree,
and found these...
from a black ski mask,
which places the guy
in the Volvo...
at the murder scene.
Well, I imagine there are
thousands of blue Volvos
out there.
There's 238 in Mass,
26 in the greater
Boston area,
three in the city
of Brighton,
and yours--
right next door.
My Volvo and I
weren't at home
or anywhere near the vicinity
at the time of the murder.
What time was the murder?
Whenever you guys said
the guy in the black ski mask
was seen driving around.
I didn't say.
It doesn't really matter,
because I was gone
the entire night.
Do you mind telling us
where you were all night?
Certainly.
...and after the movies,
I spent a few hours
at a diner near the campus.
There's the stub
from the movie--
stub and a receipt.
Keeping a scrapbook?
No--taxes.
It was work related.
Also, uh, there was
a-a waitress there
who served a terrific
cup of coffee.
In fact, she probably
signed the guest chit.
Yes.
"Thank you...
Patti."
Thanks for your time.
It was just a hunch.
That bit with
the apple was great.
He'll come around.
Excuse me?
What do you mean "hunch"?
A hunch about me,
based on what?
I mean,
that is ridiculous.
What motive would I have
to kill the man?
You attended Mueller's
last funeral, didn't you?
So what?
You show a little
compassion for people
and it's twisted around
to mean something else?
I happen to be
a very compassionate person.
In fact, I am known
for my compassion.
Which could mean that
a compassionate person,
like yourself,
sympathetic to the cause
of the Holocaust survivors,
might, seeking revenge,
kill the Nazi.
Then when you discovered
you killed an innocent person,
overcome by guilt,
you attend his funeral.
Nonsense.
They knew, and they knew
I knew they knew.
What I didn't know
was what to do about it.
(man on TV) Here's something
that's really sweet
for your sweetheart.
The sweetheart clock.
It's got very accurate
quartz movement,
and it's battery operated,
so it's very reliable.
Guys, if you're
in the dog house,
what a great way
to redeem yourself.
If you want your wife
or girlfriend to think
you're a little angel again,
maybe this will
help her remember.
Oh--do you mind?
Jack...
Here, this is for you.
What is it?
Read the card.
Oh, out loud, please.
"Dear Jack, your friendship
and kindness have helped me
through the most difficult--"
Ooh, slow down.
"...the most difficult
period of my life.
"I will forever treasure
the time we spent together.
"My children and I think
of you as part of our family.
"Please accept this small
token of our appreciation.
Fondly, Inga."
I thought of you
the moment I saw it.
It's you, isn't it?
Oh, it's...
Thank you.
It is a memento,
should we never
meet again.
Never meet again?
I don't understand.
I know. Let me explain.
You know I have not been happy
these past few months.
There are so many
bad memories here.
I have thought I might
move to Germany. Hmm?
I phoned my relatives.
They all encouraged me to come.
They say it is a good
clean place to work
and raise a family.
There are many opportunities
in the new Europe
for someone like me.
So, what do you think?
I am such a little girl
when it comes to making
big decisions.
It's a good idea.
It sounds like something
I'd like to do myself.
Thank you.
I am going to miss
relying on you.
Not if I came along.
What are you saying?
Well, you know,
frankly I'm kind of sick
of living here, too,
here in Brighton,
where I've been
ever since I got my PhD.
And I've always wanted
to live in Europe.
But what about your
teaching career?
Well, ethics is
an international subject.
There's an American
university in Heidelberg.
I'll learn German,
whatever.
Jack. Jack.
Are you saying that...
you like me that much?
Inga, please have
a seat here
and just listen
very carefully.
You said that I was
part of your family.
Well, I like being part
of your family,
and it's something
I'd like to continue doing.
That would be wonderful.
So it's settled.
Well, great.
Wait a minute.
Jack, you are not
talking about us
living together?
Oh, God, no!
No, I mean,
that never entered my mind
for a moment, that thought.
Good.
I am old-fashioned.
Well...
I would be honored
to marry you.
(waltz music)
Please don't think
I married Inga
just because the police
were on my tail.
I still needed to be punished,
and I threw the book at me.
I gave myself life,
and I was determined
to serve my sentence
with whatever dignity,
grace and charm I had left.
(laughs)
(humming)
Ooh!
(boy) Mommy, there's
a shuffleboard tournament
in the morning
that we want to play.
(boy #2) We wanna play
some videogames, Mom.
Please leave us
some money.
(Inga) Good night.
I will.
It's important.
I will, I will.
Good night.
Don't forget to walk Schatzi
before you say your prayers.
(both) Good night, Mom.
(Schatzi barks)
The children love you.
They are so happy.
Schatzi, however,
is still a little moody.
I'm sure Schatzi
will be fine,
once he sees
the Rhine!
And I love
my wedding presents.
Yes, I can see,
you wore them all at once.
Thank you.
I like the way
you phrase things, Jack.
I think you
are hilarious.
Really?
I don't ever remember
you laughing at any
of my remarks.
Oh, often later,
when I am alone,
I will chuckle out loud
over something you have said.
Why not just chuckle
when I say it?
I am guarded
with people, Jack,
but when I am by myself,
I am very outgoing.
Maybe sometime I can be
with you when you're alone.
You remind me of my father.
He was also very funny.
(chokes)
More champagne?
Oh, no, one glass
is enough for me.
I'm already
a little too giddy.
(clears throat)
Well...
So...
(groaning)
Eee, yeah...
Ahh...
Mm.
Well.
Whoa.
Whoa!
Was good, ja?
Mm.
You?
I don't like having sex.
It gets better with time.
No.
No, I have
never liked it.
Maybe I should have
told you first.
You might have
mentioned it,
but it really
doesn't matter.
Ah. Oh, good.
I honestly thought with you
it would be different...
because you are so giving.
I will do it for you,
of course,
whenever you want.
It is my duty.
Please, Inga, try not
to think about it.
Don't even worry
about it, all right?
I'll see you
in the morning.
OK.
Good deal.
(horn blows)
Can I get you
a washcloth?
No, thanks.
Remember, Jack, when you
told me you wanted to share
all my burdens in life?
Uh-huh.
I have always wanted
to share my life
with a man.
My husband was a macho man
who would not listen.
Not like you.
But I feel I can share
anything with you.
Can I tell you
my secrets, darling?
Uh, in the morning, dear.
My father was
The Beast of Berkau.
Say that again.
My father was Karl Luger...
not Max Mueller.
That--that's impossible,
because the war files
prove that--
No, no, no.
Oh, no, listen.
That file was
a forgery, a fake.
My father was
in SS Intelligence
and could do these things.
Late in the war,
to protect himself,
he created a file
for a Max Mueller
but using his own
photo identification
and dental records.
And so he became
Max Mueller.
This file was lost
during my father's escape.
We kept hoping
it would be found.
It popped up finally,
but too late.
So let me get this straight.
What you're telling me
is that the man
who was poisoned to death
was really Karl Luger.
Yes.
So you're the daughter
of The Beast of Berkau.
Yes.
And I'm his son-in-law.
Believe me, I know what
you are going through.
Jack?
Could you not--
Just for a second.
You are the only other
person in the world
who knows.
Promise me, you will
tell no one, no one.
What, are you kidding?
Oh, no, I'm telling everyone!
I will deny it.
I told you
what it was like for us
when my father
was exposed as a Nazi!
Could you please just--
To the world,
my father was Max Mueller!
I am Inga Mueller.
Please wait.
I'm thinking.
I would deny it, Jack,
to my dying breath for
the sake of the twins.
Fuck the twins!
I knew I should
never have told you.
Of course,
you'd love to go on
perpetuating this fraud
for your own self--
Inga, there are
other families, Inga.
Yours is not
the only family
in the world.
There are millions of other
families involved in this,
families who deserve
to know the truth.
Don't you care
about them at all?
Don't people have any feelings
for each other at all,
for God's sake?!
Stop it!
You frighten me
when you talk this way.
You sound like
that "Sincere" madman.
I am that madman.
What are you saying?
Is true?
It had nothing
to do with you.
This is true?
Listen, listen.
Please, it was
beyond my control.
Oh, my God, no.
Sometimes you're compelled
to do something.
You have a feeling
of what's wrong,
and you feel
you can set it right.
Wait, wait...
You kill the father...
Inga, please.
and then you
fornicate the daughter?
No, no!
Ohh, what kind
of animal are you?
It wasn't that way.
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Oh, God, help me! Help me!
Help me, please, God.
Somebody call the police!
Police!
(sirens wailing)
Jack?
Marty!
Jack!
Is this true
that you killed a man?
Yes, but I killed
the right man.
I don't think
that's a defense
in this country.
No, look, they say here
I killed a man named
Max Mueller.
I didn't.
I killed Karl Luger,
the Nazi war criminal.
That's the heart
of my defense!
Wait. Mueller.
Is this any relation
to the lady you gave
all that money to?
You mean my wife.
Yes.
Now, she is gonna be
a key witness,
probably for both sides,
if that's possible.
I need to know,
is that possible?
And what's
a hostile witness?
I'll walk you through
the arraignment,
but then you're gonna need
a criminal attorney,
a good one.
OK, thanks, Marty.
Come here.
I'm with you on this, Jack.
You can always count
on family.
We may piss you off,
we may screw with you
on business,
but we never condemn.
Good. See you in court.
OK. Marty,
I got a plan.
What?
No plea bargains,
no deals.
I think
that's their plan.
We can make a case,
but we need more
physical evidence.
Get us an indictment.
We'll get you everything
you need.
He's our man.
Yeah, I know.
Docket number 1175-D.
The State vs Jack Lambert,
felony count,
first degree murder.
How do you plead?
Your Honor,
could I approach
the bench, please?
Get me a trial.
Hi.
I haven't been
in a courtroom since
college, Your Honor.
I'm a tax attorney now,
but the defendant's
my brother.
Interesting.
Are you prepared
to enter a plea, Counselor?
Absolutely,
but I'm wondering
if you could refresh me
on what my options
are here.
Certainly.
Guilty or not guilty.
Fair enough,
but couldn't I also
ask for a dismissal
of all charges?
You can ask.
The State recommends
that no bail be granted.
The suspect was apprehended
fleeing the country.
What? Fleeing!
He was on his honeymoon,
Your Honor.
So, I'll get my day in court,
and the truth will come out.
But even though
I committed a crime,
I solved one, too.
Hey, you know, that might
reduce my sentence.
How did you come
to arrest this man?
He confessed the murder
to his wife.
Wait a minute.
A wife cannot testify
against her husband,
I do know that.
No, you don't,
Counselor.
A wife cannot be forced
to testify, but she may
do so willingly.
I don't see her statement.
She recanted, Your Honor,
said she was under
a lot of stress,
was hysterical,
and wasn't sure
of what she heard,
but we have a hunch
she was telling the truth.
Maybe she didn't want
the trauma of a trial,
but the defendant was already
the number one suspect.
There's an overwhelming amount
of circumstantial evidence.
I think I'm ready to make
a determination in this case.
Why don't you two return
to your places?
Nice how this thing formed
a complete moral circle.
Luger paid for his crimes,
and I'll pay for mine.
I am reluctant to accept
a plea in this case.
The State may wish
to characterize its evidence
as circumstantial.
I find it merely coincidental.
There is no eyewitness
or any other
corroborating evidence
placing the suspect
at the scene.
This case is dismissed.
Enjoy your honeymoon,
Professor Lambert.
Dismissed? What does
that mean, dismissed?
What's going on?
Um...you're free.
What, on bail?
No, you're out, period.
Jack, weren't you listening?
The judge just dismissed
the case.
What do you mean? Why?
They didn't have any evidence.
And when your wife refused
to testify--
She's not gonna
want to testify.
You have to force her.
What have you done?
Cheer up, kid.
You got away with murder.
Stop saying that.
Where are they going?
Shut up and let's
get out of here.
No, Marty, everybody, wait!
No, wait! Wait.
Please--please, there's more.
Don't you want
to know the truth?
You call this justice?!
I went directly
from court to bed,
took a leave
of absence from school
and just laid around thinking,
and I came to one conclusion--
I'm glad I got away with it.
I'm a very lucky man.
Anyway, I received
an annulment notice from Inga
postmarked Duesseldorf,
and surprisingly,
I got a letter from Gail.
She'd heard about the case,
put two and two together,
and wanted to know the truth.
So I confessed everything.
She was put off at first,
but then she felt
kind of flattered
that I thought the worst thing
I could do to myself
was give her up.
She agreed to see me again,
and we caught up on stuff.
I explained that
after what I'd done,
I didn't really
think I was pure enough
to teach ethics anymore,
so I'd entered law school.