[ Applause ]
[ Man ]
BROTHERS AND SISTERS.
BROTHERS AND SISTERS,
PLEASE, PLEASE.
I WANNA ASK A QUESTION.
DO THEY ALLOW DRUG DEALERS
AND GUN DEALERS TO SELL
THEIR WARES...
IN FRONT OF SCHOOLYARDS
IN A RICH NEIGHBORHOOD ?
[ Congregation ] NO.
THEY DON'T, DO THEY ?
WELL, HOW COME THEY TURN
A BLIND EYE TO IT DOWN HERE ?
DO WE HAVE
GUN-MANUFACTURING PLANTS
IN THIS SO-CALLED HOOD OF OURS ?
THEN, HOW DO ALL THESE GUNS
END UP DOWN HERE ?
[ Congregation Chattering ]
DO WE HAVE POPPY FIELDS
IN THE POOR COMMUNITIES
ACROSS AMERICA ?
DO WE GROW POPPY FIELDS ?
DO WE HAVE POPPY FIELDS ?
THEN, HOW DOES ALL THIS DOPE
GET HERE ?
WE GO TO JAIL FOR IT
EVERY DAY.
WE GO TO JAIL FOR IT,
BROTHERS AND SISTERS,
EVERY DAY, DON'T WE ?
BUT WHO BRINGS IT IN ?
WHO IMPORTS IT ?
WHO MAKES THE BIG MONEY ?
WHO MAKES THE BIG MONEY, HUH ?
[ Man ]
THEY MAKE IT.
WELL, LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
LOGISTICALLY, WE ALL KNOW...
YOU CAN'T GET THIS MUCH DRUGS
AND GUNS INTO THE POOR
COMMUNITIES...
WITHOUT THE COOPERATION
OF SOME AUTHORITIES,
SOME POLICE OFFICIALS
AND, OF COURSE, THE MAFIA.
NOW, BROTHER PAYNE IS NOT SAYING
THAT EVERY POLICEMAN...
OR EVERY ELECTED OFFICIAL
IS ON THE TAKE.
I'M NOT SAYING THAT.
BUT SOMEONE IS MAKIN'
SOME BIG MONEY SOMEWHERE,
AND IT'S NOT US.
IT SEEMS TO ME THAT SOMEBODY
OUT THERE WANTS US MEDICATED
AND GETTING HIGH...
AND NOT VOTING AND SHOOTING
EACH OTHER IN THE STREETS.
THAT'S JUST WHAT
OUR YOUNG PEOPLE ARE DOING--
YELLOW, BLACK, RED, BROWN.
AREN'T WE DOING THAT ?
EVERY POOR COMMUNITY IN AMERICA.
ARE THE POLICE GONNA STOP IT ?
[ Woman ]
YOU KNOW THEY AIN'T.
IS THE GOVERNMENT STOPPIN' IT ?
IS THE MAFIA GONNA STOP IT ?
NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT WE GOTTA DO,
BROTHERS AND SISTERS ?
LOOK IN THE MIRROR.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE LORD HELPS THEM
THAT HELPS THEMSELVES.
LOOK IN THE MIRROR.
[ Man ]
PREACH, BROTHER.
IT'S WITH A HEAVY HEART
THAT I INFORM YOU...
THAT WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO CLOSE
THIS CHURCH.
[ Congregation Reacts ]
I'M SORRY, BROTHERS AND SISTERS.
PLEASE, PLEASE.
NO, NO, NO !
SIT DOWN. WE'RE GONNA
HAVE TO TAKE THIS STRUGGLE
TO A NEW LEVEL.
THERE COMES A TIME
WHEN YOU REALIZE...
YOU CAN NO LONGER
JUST PRAY YOUR WAY TO FREEDOM.
THIS IS GOD'S WILL THAT WE ACT,
THAT WE DO SOMETHING.
[ Bell Tolling ]
[ Tolling Continues ]
[ Speaking Spanish ]
DIOS MIO.
WHERE ?
PERU.
SMALL VILLAGE
ON THE BOLIVIAN BORDER.
CASUALTIES ?
A HUNDRED PERCENT, SIR.
IT'S AS IF THE PLACE
WAS NEVER THERE.
SHIT !
THERE'S NOT A WHOLE HELL OF
A LOT WE COULD HAVE DONE, SIR.
THE SPACE GUARD SYSTEM
ISN'T FULLY OPERATIONAL YET.
EVEN IF IT WERE, THE THRESHOLD
FOR EARLY DETECTION IS ONLY
ONE KILOMETER LARGER.
THIS IMPACT WAS ONLY 18 METERS
IN DIAMETER, SIR.
IT ISN'T THE 18-METER OBJECT
THAT CONCERNS ME, COLONEL.
IT'S THE 23-KILOMETER OBJECT
THAT'S SIX DAYS BEHIND IT.
TWENTY-THREE KILOMETERS ?
THAT'S 13, 14 MILES.
14.03, TO BE EXACT.
THE BAD NEWS IS, THE COMET
THAT TOOK OUT THE DINOSAURS
WAS ONLY SIX.
[ Phone Ringing ]
[ Ringing Continues ]
TYRELL. HEY, MOM.
NO, I'M UP. I'M UP.
[ Alarm Beeping ]
[ Alarm Stops ]
NOTHING, NOTHING.
THAT'S JUST THE ALARM CLOCK.
NO, I'M UP.
I TOLD YOU. YEAH.
MOM, YOU DON'T HAVE TO SING.
A SIMPLE "HAPPY BIRTHDAY"
WILL DO.
UH, YEAH. UH-HUH.
SO, UH--
[ Short Whistle ]
YEAH, SO, UH, LIKE AS IN
HAS JEFF PROPOSED TO ME YET ?
NO, HE HASN'T. BUT HE'S GOING
UP TO SAN FRANCISCO TONIGHT,
AND I'M GONNA GO WITH HIM.
SO MAYBE-- I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE HE'S GOT SOMETHING
PLANNED. I DON'T KNOW.
OH ! OW !
SORRY, MOM.
DROPPED THE PHONE.
UH !
[ Phone Dialing ]
WHAT WERE YOU SAYING ?
OH, YEAH. RIGHT.
WHY BUY THE COW WHEN HE'S
GETTING THE MILK FOR FREE ?
[ Phone Beeps ]
OH, THAT'S MY OTHER LINE.
GOTTA GO, MOM.
IT'S PROBABLY WORK.
I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER. BYE.
[ Phone Beeps ]
YOU ARE A DEAD MAN.
HEY, POLICE BRUTALITY.
YOU KNOW, I HAPPEN TO KNOW
A VERY GOOD LAWYER.
I'M NOT THE POLICE.
AND I KNOW
A REALLY GOOD LAWYER TOO.
OH, REALLY ?
MM-HMM, AND MY LAWYER'S
GONNA KICK YOUR LAWYER'S ASS.
YEAH, THEN MAYBE
WE SHOULD SETTLE OUT OF COURT.
HMM ? YEAH.
FIVE WEEKS AGO,
COT KOMAKOFF II...
VANISHED COMPLETELY
AS IT CROSSED THE ASTEROID BELT.
WE NOW KNOW THAT IT COLLIDED
WITH AN ASTEROID,
SENDING SEVERAL FRAGMENTS
ON AN EARTH-CROSSING TRAJECTORY.
I THINK THE IMPLICATIONS
OF SUCH AN IMPACT
ARE MORE THAN EVIDENT...
TO EVERYONE HERE.
ALL RIGHT.
I WANT TO PUT A BLACK DRAPE
OVER THIS WHOLE THING.
THE STATEMENT TO THE PRESS...
WILL BE THIS:
A DERELICT RUSSIAN SPY SATELLITE
CRASHED TO EARTH IN THE ANDES.
THEY'LL DENY IT, OF COURSE,
BUT IT'LL BUY US SOME TIME.
COLONEL KELLER,
THE PROTOTYPE
OF THE THOR DEVICE IS STILL AT
WHITE SANDS, IS THAT CORRECT ?
YES, SIR,
BUT THERE IS THE PROBLEM
OF THE ARMING SEQUENCE CODES.
DR. CORBETT
IS STILL BEING UNCOOPERATIVE.
WELL, YOU PICK UP DR. CORBETT,
AND YOU GET HIS ASS OVER THERE.
- YES, SIR.
- THE THOR PROJECT WAS KILLED,
WELL OVER TWO YEARS AGO.
I'M AWARE OF THAT, DICK.
I WANT THOR GOOD TO GO
IN 24 HOURS.
RIGHT AWAY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, BILL ?
LINEBACKER IS SITTING
AT THE CAPE, READY TO GO.
I'M AWARE OF THAT TOO.
ARE YOU ALSO AWARE...
THAT CONGRESS APPROVED IT,
NOT THOR, AS THE DESIGNATED
SYSTEM FOR THIS MISSION ?
LINEBACKER WAS DESIGNED
AND AUTHORIZED...
FOR AN OBJECT DIAMETER
OF FIVE MILES OR LESS.
THE RULES HAVE CHANGED.
THOR IS GOING UP FIRST.
THOR IS A DEAD ISSUE.
ANTIMATTER TECHNOLOGY
HAS BEEN COMPLETELY DISCREDITED
AS A VIABLE WEAPONS SYSTEM.
NO ONE KNOWS THAT BETTER THAN
YOU, BUT WE NEED ANOTHER OPTION,
AND THAT'S WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
- THE PRESIDENT'S
GONNA BACK ME ON THIS.
- DO WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO, DICK.
- YOU CAN'T JUST--
- THE DISCUSSION IS OVER, DICK.
THAT'S IT.
SIR, YOU'RE TAKING
A BIG RISK HERE.
NOW, DON'T YOU START.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BACK ME UP
EVEN IF I'M WRONG.
IS IT WORTH YOUR CAREER, SIR ?
DOUG, FROM WHAT THAT
SON OF A BITCH JUST SAID,
MY CAREER AND YOURS
ARE GONNA LAST ABOUT FOUR DAYS,
IF WE DON'T STOP THAT THING.
IT'S A TIME FOR RISK.
[ Man ]
OKAY, UM, THEN YOU WORKED
FOR THE GOVERNMENT FOR A WHILE.
WHAT WAS THAT LIKE ?
IT SUCKED.
[ Laughs ]
OKAY.
THAT'S A GREAT ANSWER.
MY READERS WILL LOVE THAT.
YEAH, SURE THEY WILL.
ALL THREE OF 'EM.
EXCUSE ME.
ARE YOU DR. CORBETT ?
YEAH.
I'M SORRY TO BOTHER YOU, BUT
I JUST GOT TRANSFERRED TO YOU...
AS FACULTY ADVISOR,
AND I HAD SOME QUESTIONS.
WELL, YOU MUST HAVE DONE
SOMETHING REALLY HORRIBLE
TO GET TRANSFERRED TO ME.
BUT I'M ALL YOURS.
HEY, WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO THIS
LATER, ALL RIGHT ?
NO. JUST A COUPLE OF MORE
QUESTIONS, AND I SWEAR TO GOD
I'LL BE OUT OF YOUR HAIR.
YOU SHOULDN'T TAKE
THE LORD'S NAME IN VAIN.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE TAKE A WALK
UP TO MY OFFICE, HUH ?
SURE.
[ Man ]
DR. DAVID CORBETT ?
MAY I SPEAK WITH YOU,
PLEASE ?
WELL, YOU'RE SPEAKING
TO ME NOW, AREN'T YOU ?
I'M FRANK PETERSON,
DEFENSE INTELLIGENCE AGENCY.
YOU NEED TO COME WITH US.
I DON'T NEED TO DO ANYTHING
OF THE KIND.
YOU GUYS FIRED ME,
REMEMBER ?
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THAT.
I DO HAVE MY ORDERS, THOUGH.
FUCK YOU.
I'M AUTHORIZED TO PLACE YOU
UNDER ARREST IN THE EVENT YOUR
COOPERATION ISN'T VOLUNTARY.
NOW... IF YOU DON'T MIND--
[ Scoffs ]
[ Corbett ]
SO WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT ?
NATIONAL SECURITY MATTER.
OH, FOR CHRIST'S SAKES,
WOULD YOU CUT THE SPOOK BULLSHIT
AND TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON ?
AFRAID I DON'T HAVE
THAT INFORMATION.
AH. WELL, IS THERE ANY
INFORMATION THAT YOU DO HAVE ?
NO, SIR.
[ Car Doors Close ]
[ Engine Starts ]
WATCH YOUR HEAD, PLEASE.
[ Shutter Clicking ]
[ Agents Shouting, Indistinct ]
[ Screaming ]
GET OUT.
[ Shutter Clicks ]
[ Tires Screech ]
[ Clicking Continues ]
GET IN !
GET IN THE BACK.
GET US OUT OF HERE,
BROTHER CLARENCE.
[ Tires Screeching ]
[ Gasping ]
WHO ARE YOU ?
A SIMPLE MAN OF GOD, DOC.
THAT'S ALL.
WE GOT COMPANY !
I SEE THAT.
THAT'S UNFORTUNATE.
[ Siren Wailing ]
RACHEL, KEEP AN EYE
ON OUR FRIEND HERE.
- ALL RIGHT, DOC.
- WHAT ?
- THIS WON'T HURT.
NO, NO !
OH, GOD !
[ Whimpers ]
GOD.
[ Siren Continues ]
THIS IS CAR 17.
SUSPECTS ARE PROCEEDING NORTH
ON THE FIRE ACCESS ROAD.
WE'RE GONNA TRY
AND CUT THEM OFF.
OTHER UNITS ARE IN PURSUIT.
READY BACK HERE, CLARENCE.
I THINK THEY LOST INTEREST.
[ Siren Wailing ]
NOT THEIR FRIENDS !
I'M GONNA NEED
A LITTLE HELP HERE.
NO PROBLEM.
HE'S GOT A GRENADE LAUNCHER !
TAKE US HOME.
[ Cell Door Opens, Closes ]
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Siren Wailing ]
[ Siren Continues ]
[ Radio Dispatcher,
Indistinct ]
[ Man ]
THESE JUST CAME IN, SIR. ONE
OF CORBETT'S STUDENTS TOOK THEM.
YOU'RE SURE THIS IS HIM ?
YES, SIR.
NSA CONFIRMED IT.
IT'S PAYNE.
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE, SIR.
PAYNE'S A RELIGIOUS FANATIC.
- WHAT WOULD HE WANT
WITH CORBETT ?
- RANSOM.
CORBETT COMES FROM
SOME SERIOUS EAST COAST MONEY.
IT'S NOT ABOUT MONEY.
WHY TODAY ? WHY NOW ?
PAYNE KNOWS
THAT WE WANT CORBETT.
WE HAVE A LEAK, GENTLEMEN.
STILL LEAVES THE QUESTION
OF WHY, SIR.
SIR.
WHAT ?
YOU GAVE HIM A PRETTY GOOD
BEATING IN THERE THIS MORNING.
THINK ABOUT IT.
HE PULLED EVERY STRING HE COULD
TO GET THOR KILLED IN COMMITTEE.
IT'S POSSIBLE HE'D GO
TO EVEN GREATER LENGTHS NOW.
HE'S GOT A POINT, SIR.
SECOR'S A VINDICTIVE
LITTLE BASTARD, BUT WHAT'S
THE CONNECTION TO PAYNE ?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S A POLITICAL ANIMAL.
PROBABLY HAS CONNECTIONS
NONE OF US KNOW ABOUT.
OR WANT TO.
PUT HIM ON FULL SURVEILLANCE.
THE BEST CASE SCENARIO,
WE FIND CORBETT AND WE GET THOR
GOOD TO GO.
NOW WHAT'S THE EXTREME LIMIT
OF OUR LAUNCH WINDOW ?
THREE DAYS,
IF EVERYTHING GOES PERFECTLY.
AFTER THAT--
ALL RIGHT, SHUTTLE CENTAURUS
GOES UP TOMORROW WITH
LINEBACKER ABOARD.
HAVE  OLYMPUS
OUTFITTED AND ON STANDBY
TO BE LOADED WITH THOR.
THAT'S ALL WE CAN DO
UNTIL WE FIND CORBETT.
- YES, SIR.
- IF YOU DON'T MIND
MY ASKING, SIR,
WITH NO WAY OF CONTACTING PAYNE,
HOW DO YOU PROPOSE TO DO THAT ?
THAT'S FAR ENOUGH,
UNLESS YOU WANT SOME
DEAD PEOPLE IN HERE.
I'M SPECIAL AGENT TYRELL
WITH THE FBI.
I'M UNARMED.
I'M NOT WEARING A WIRE.
I JUST WANNA TALK.
IT'S A FUCKIN' FED.
GO AHEAD ! TALK !
I THINK IT WOULD BE BETTER FOR
ALL OF US IF I JUST CAME INSIDE.
[ Man Whispering ]
TELL HER TO GO FUCK HERSELF.
COME ON IN, THEN.
- WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU DOIN' ?
- GETTING US A HIGHER-QUALITY
HOSTAGE.
- WE HAVE A HOSTAGE.
- THEY AIN'T GONNA COME SHOOTING
WITH ONE OF THEIR OWN HERE.
YOU'RE FUCKIN' CRAZY.
FUCKIN' CRAZY.
[ Grunts ]
UP AGAINST THE WALL, HONEY.
NO FUNNY STUFF NOW,
OR LEO'LL PUT A NICE
BIG HOLE IN YOU.
YEAH, YOU TOO
FROM THIS ANGLE.
LEO, THIS COP MOVES, BLOW
THAT FUCKIN' WHORE'S HEAD OFF.
GOT IT.
[ Whimpers ]
WHAT THIS ?
THAT'S YOUR TICKET OUT OF HERE.
THE WAY IT WORKS IS
YOU WRITE DOWN YOUR DEMANDS,
WE TALK ABOUT WHICH ONES
WILL WORK, YOU SIGN, I SIGN,
I TAKE IT TO MY BOSS,
HE RUBBER-STAMPS IT,
WE GO HOME HAPPY.
SHE'S SO FULL OF SHIT,
IT'S RUNNING OUT OF HER EARS.
YEAH, WELL BELIEVE
WHAT YOU WANT.
AFTER WACO AND RUBY RIDGE,
MY BOSSES ARE REALLY TOUCHY.
ALL THEY'RE INTERESTED IN
IS AVOIDING BLOODSHED.
SO RIGHT AWAY, DEMAND
WHAT YOU WANT, WITHIN REASON,
AND WE'LL WORK IT OUT.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL GIVE YOU MY DEMANDS.
GODDAMN IT, ED,
SHE'S STALLING US.
SHUT UP.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
I'LL MAKE THIS A LOT EASIER,
'CAUSE THIS JOB REALLY SUCKS
AND I HATE MY BOSS.
AND PLUS, IT'S MY BIRTHDAY,
AND I REALLY JUST WANT TO GET
THE HELL OUT OF HERE, OKAY ?
SO I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
I'LL SIGN IT FIRST.
THEN YOU CAN MAKE YOUR LIST,
AND WE'LL CALL IT A DAY.
- UH-UH !
- IT'S MY PEN.
[ Whimpers ]
OKAY ?
GIVE ME THE PEN.
- [ Screams ]
- FUCKIN' BITCH !
[ Woman Screams ]
[ Groaning ]
AH !
THAT'S MY PEN.
[ Siren Wailing ]
SPECIAL AGENT TYRELL ?
I'M TYRELL, YES.
COULD I HAVE A WORD
WITH YOU ?
IT'S ME.
I'M HERE...
BEARING GIFTS.
ARE YOU IN THE TUB,
NAKED, I HOPE ?
YEAH, MY MESSAGE LIGHT'S
FLASHING.
GENERAL, I'M REALLY HAPPY
THAT WE'RE HAVING THIS NICE
LITTLE CHAT,
BUT I WAS DUE IN SAN FRANCISCO
THREE HOURS AGO.
SO IF WE COULD GET TO THE POINT,
I'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
CERTAINLY.
YOU WERE ASSIGNED TO
A TASK FORCE THAT ATTEMPTED...
TO NAIL THOMAS PAYNE
A COUPLE OF YEARS BACK.
WE WERE INVESTIGATING
HIS SO-CALLED CHURCH, YEAH.
YES, THE NEW TABORITES.
RIGHT.
AND THIS MORNING...
HE KIDNAPPED THIS MAN--
DR. DAVID CORBETT.
HE'S ONE OF OUR TOP SPACE
DEFENSE WEAPONS RESEARCHERS.
AND HE KILLED TWO OF OUR AGENTS
WHILE PICKING HIM UP.
WAS THERE A RANSOM DEMAND ?
NONE. NO STATEMENT.
NO CALL TO THE PRESS. NOTHING.
FROM WHAT YOU KNOW OF PAYNE,
IS THERE ANY POSSIBILITY
DR. CORBETT IS STILL ALIVE ?
PAYNE IS AN EX-ARMY RANGER,
TRAINED TO KILL.
HE WOULD HAVE DONE HIM AT
THE SAME TIME AS THE OTHER TWO.
THERE'S A REASON
HE LET HIM LIVE.
WELL, WHATEVER THE REASON,
WE NEED HIM BACK... FAST.
WE'RE HOPING YOU CAN HELP US
FIND HIM.
WHY DO YOU NEED MY HELP ?
YOU MUST HAVE SPECIAL OPS PEOPLE
WHO DO THIS KIND OF THING.
WE NEED AN OUTSIDER.
WHY ?
IT APPEARS
THAT MR. PAYNE HAS A PIPELINE
INTO OUR INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY.
NOT SURPRISING.
THE NEW TABORITES WAS STARTED
AS A SECRET SOCIETY
WITHIN THE MILITARY.
AND WE THINK WE MAY
HAVE ISOLATED THE SOURCE,
BUT WE CAN'T TAKE ANY CHANCES.
CAN YOU HELP US ?
[ Sighs ]
IT'LL TAKE ME A WEEK OR SO
TO GET A TEAM TOGETHER.
NO TEAM.
YOU'D BE ON YOUR OWN.
YOU WANT ME TO DO THIS ALONE ?
I MEAN, IF THIS GUY
IS SO IMPORTANT, YOU SHOULD BE
ASKING FOR AN ARMY OF FEDS.
YOU WANT THE JOB ?
I'LL NEED LATITUDE.
A LOT OF IT. NO QUESTIONS.
YOU'RE AUTHORIZED
TO USE ANY MEANS NECESSARY
TO GET DR. CORBETT BACK ALIVE.
THERE'S ONE MORE THING.
YOU GOT THREE DAYS.
ACTUALLY, 68 HOURS.
[ Laughs ]
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
AFTER THAT, IT REALLY
DOESN'T MATTER ANYMORE.
ANY MEANS NECESSARY ?
[ Alarm Buzzing ]
[ Gate Opens ]
HEY, REESE.
LONG TIME NO SEE.
YEAH, ONE YEAR, 357 DAYS.
BUT WHO'S COUNTIN' ?
WHERE'S YOUR BOSS ?
COULDN'T MAKE IT.
THEY FIRE HIS ASS ?
NO, THEY PROMOTED HIM.
YEAH, THAT FIGURES.
WHAT'S IN THE BOX ?
AIN'T MY BIRTHDAY OR NOTHIN'.
THAT'S GOOD.
HATE TO THINK
WE HAD THAT IN COMMON.
LOOK FAMILIAR ?
THAT'S MY SHIT.
WHAT YOU DOING WITH IT ?
GIVING YOU A CHOICE...
BETWEEN PUTTING IT ON NOW
OR PUTTING IT ON IN TEN YEARS.
- I AIN'T INTERESTED.
- YOU HAVEN'T HEARD THE OFFER.
I DON'T CARE. I AIN'T FUCKIN'
WITH NO DEALS FROM NO COPS.
YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT BY NOW.
THIS IS DIFFERENT,
AND I'M NOT A COP.
FED, COP, IT'S ALL THE SAME.
SO IS THE DEAL. FUCK IT.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE WASTING AWAY
IN THIS SHIT-HOLE.
SO WHEN YOU GET OUT IN TEN YEARS
YOU CAN GET PAYNE YOURSELF.
I'M GIVING YOU THAT CHANCE NOW,
BUT IF YOU DON'T WANT IT,
THAT'S FINE.
SO, WHAT YOU SAYIN' ?
I'M SAYING WE GOT A NEW DEAL.
YOU DIDN'T LIKE THE LAST ONE
'CAUSE WE COULDN'T GET
THE CHARGES TO STICK TO PAYNE.
HE MANIPULATED
THE JUSTICE SYSTEM
AND BEAT THE RAP, RIGHT ?
SOMETHIN' LIKE THAT.
OKAY, WELL, HE CAN'T MANIPULATE
SHIT IF HE CAN'T MAKE IT
TO THE TRIAL.
SO HERE'S THE SITUATION.
PAYNE KIDNAPPED
A GOVERNMENT SCIENTIST.
THEY WANT HIM BACK.
I NEED YOU
TO HELP ME FIND PAYNE.
ONCE WE GET THERE,
MY PRIORITY IS THE SCIENTIST,
AND WHATEVER HAPPENS TO PAYNE...
IT'S NONE OF MY CONCERN.
SO YOU'RE TELLING ME
I CAN KILL PAYNE, AND YOU'RE
JUST GONNA LOOK THE OTHER WAY ?
I'M TELLING YOU THAT IF I HAPPEN
TO BE LOOKING THE OTHER WAY...
WHEN PAYNE GETS KILLED,
HOW AM I GONNA KNOW
IT WAS YOU ?
THAT CLEAR ENOUGH ?
WE UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER NOW ?
YEAH, I UNDERSTAND YOU.
SO THAT'S THE DEAL.
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
TAKE IT OR LEAVE IT.
I KNOW WHAT PAYNE DID
TO YOUR FAMILY.
AND I KNOW
HOW IT MUST HAVE FELT--
NO, YOU DON'T. I MEAN,
YOU HAVE NO FUCKING IDEA.
I'M SORRY.
THAT WAS PRESUMPTUOUS OF ME.
BUT IF I DID, I'D TAKE
EVERY CHANCE I COULD GET.
GIVE ME THE BOX.
[ Children Giggling ]
HEY !
[ Laughing ]
[ Corbett ]
HEY.
WHO ARE YOU GUYS ?
[ Giggling Continues ]
YOU'RE NOT GONNA ANSWER ME ?
WE CAN'T.
YOU'RE A DEMON.
DID--
DID YOU JUST CALL ME A DEMON ?
YES.
- WHY ?
- 'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT MY DAD
TOLD ME YOU ARE.
HE SAYS YOU WORK
FOR THE DEVIL.
YOU CAN'T STOP THE STAR.
IT'S WHAT GOD WANTS.
STOP THE STAR ? WHAT STAR ?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ?
CHILDREN.
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
NOT TO BOTHER THIS MAN.
[ Together ]
SORRY, DADDY.
IT'S OKAY.
JUST REMEMBER, WHEN WE CONSORT
WITH THE EMISSARIES OF EVIL--
[ Together ]
WE BECOME EVIL OURSELVES.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WHY DON'T YOU RUN ALONG WITH
THAT BEAUTIFUL MOMMA OF YOURS ?
GO ON, NOW.
SO YOU MET THE FAMILY, HUH,
DOC ? HOW ARE YOU DOIN' ?
FINE.
WHAT WAS HE TALKING ABOUT ?
WHAT'S THIS STAR ?
YOU GOT YOUR BIBLE WITH YOU,
BROTHER CLARENCE ?
ALWAYS.
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE IT
TO THE DOCTOR HERE ?
YOUR ANSWER'S IN THERE.
YOU GOT A LITTLE TIME
ON YOUR HANDS.
WHY DON'T YOU DO
SOME READING ?
KEEP AN EYE ON HIM,
CLARENCE.
[ Door Closes, Locks ]
OH, I NEED SOME COFFEE,
LIKE REAL SOON.
WE SHOULD GET SOMETHING TO EAT.
I KNOW THIS PLACE UP AROUND
THE CORNER. WE CAN GET
SOME CHICKEN AND WAFFLES.
TOGETHER,
AT THE SAME TIME ?
YEAH.
FORGET IT.
HOW YOU KNOW YOU WON'T LIKE IT ?
YOU AIN'T NEVER TRIED IT.
I JUST KNOW.
[ Scoffs ]
THERE'S GONNA BE
A LOT OF PEOPLE THERE.
WE COULD MAKE SOME CONTACTS,
GET SOME LEADS.
NO CHICKEN
AND WAFFLES, N.F.W.
NO FUCKIN' WAY ?
THAT'S RIGHT.
SO YOU A COP.
WHAT DO YOU EAT,
DONUTS ALL DAY ?
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT, DONUTS ?
YEAH, AND YOU'RE A FELON.
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU KNOW ?
THAT'S WHY YOU AIN'T MARRIED.
FOR ALL YOU KNOW,
I COULD BE.
I LOOKED AT YOUR HAND.
YOU AIN'T GOT NO WEDDING RING.
ARE YOU A LESBIAN ?
- NO, I'M NOT.
- IF YOU ARE,
IT'S NOTHING TO BE ASHAMED OF.
THESE ARE THE '90s.
YOU CAN TALK ABOUT IT.
- I'M NOT A LESBIAN, ALL RIGHT ?
- ALL RIGHT.
BESIDES, I'M NOT THE ONE
WHO SPENT THE LAST TWO YEARS
IN PRISON.
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN ?
THINK ABOUT IT.
LOOK, I GOT NEWS FOR YOU.
I'M NOT CUTE ENOUGH
TO HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
BENDING OVER IN A SHOWER.
AND NUMBER TWOFUCKIN' SOME GUY
IN HIS FUCKIN' HAIRY ASS...
IS NOT MY IDEA
OF A GOOD TIME, ALL RIGHT ?
WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO
TO SHUT YOU UP ?
LET ME FIND OUT
WHAT THE FUCK IS GOING ON.
YEAH, LET ME SPEAK TO OLA.
OLA, YEAH.
HEY, LOOK. WHAT'S ALL
THIS SHIT YOU SAYIN' ABOUT ME,
I OWE YOU SOME DAMN MONEY ?
LOOK, I DON'T GIVE
A FUCK WHAT THEM SAID.
I DIDN'T STEAL SHIT FROM YOU.
HEY, LOOK.
YOU KNOW YOU KEEP YOUR MONEY
IN YOUR DAMN TITTY.
HOW I'M GONNA TAKE YOUR MONEY
OUT YOUR TITS ?
ALL OLD LADIES KEEP THEIR MONEY
IN THEIR TITTIES.
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
- DAMON.
- GIVE ME YOUR HANDS.
ABOUT TIME.
YOU'LL LIKE THIS.
I PROMISE.
- HEY, WHAT YOU DOIN' ?
- THIS IS GONNA BE
A TAKE-OUT ORDER.
LOOK. THE REASON I BROUGHT YOU
HERE IS I THOUGHT WE COULD FIND
SOMEBODY TO TALK TO.
- I SEE SOMEBODY RIGHT NOW
THAT CAN HELP US.
- WHO ?
KID RIGHT THERE
ON THE CELL PHONE.
HIS NAME IS DAMON. I KNOW HIM.
IF HE WANTS TO SEE ME,
TELL HIM COME TO MY HOUSE.
HEY, WHAT YOU DOIN' ?
HE AIN'T GONNA TALK TO YOU.
HEY, LOOK.
I HAVE TO GET BACK AT YOU, DOG.
[ Woman ]
OH, NOW YOU DON'T LIKE IT,
BUT YOU ATE HALF OF THEM.
OKAY, FINE.
JUST GIVE ME THE RECEIPT.
LOOK, GIVE ME THE RECEIPT.
[ Man ]
THIS AIN'T WHAT I ORDERED.
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
[ Chattering ]
HEY, COME HERE FOR A SECOND.
HI. HAVE YOU SEEN A GUY WITH
A CELL PHONE COME THROUGH HERE ?
LOOK. I SEE A LOT OF PEOPLE--
OH, LORD.
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunting Continues ]
DAMN, DAMON. YOU GOT TO WATCH
WHERE YOU'RE GOIN'.
SEE THIS THING ?
I FOUND IT RIGHT HERE
LAYIN' ON THE GROUND.
YOU'RE LUCKY I PICKED IT UP.
YOU MIGHT'VE TRIPPED OVER IT.
[ Groaning ]
MY NOSE ! MY NOSE !
[ Chattering ]
TALK TO ME, DAMON.
[ Sighs ]
HEY, LOOK, MAN. I TOLD YOU
I BEEN CLEAN FOR A LONG TIME.
I GOT A MOTHERFUCKIN' JOB
FLIPPIN' BURGERS AND SHIT,
MAKIN' MINIMUM WAGE, MAN.
EVERYBODY HAVIN' IT THEIR
FUCKIN' WAY EXCEPT ME, MAN.
SHIT, I AIN'T SEEN PAYNE
IN OVER A YEAR OR SO.
AND I DON'T KNOW NO ONE
WHO HAS, EITHER.
- WHERE'S LUTHER ?
- I AIN'T SEEN HIM, EITHER.
LOOK, MAN. I'M TELLING YOU.
I DONE GOT MY LIFE
TURNED AROUND NOW, MAN.
[ Sighs ]
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING, ALL RIGHT ?
I KNOW ONE DAMN THING.
I THINK YOU DONE BROKE
MY FUCKIN' NOSE, REESE.
THINK SO ? I'M SORRY, MAN.
LET ME SEE. COME HERE.
BRING IT OVER HERE.
- YOU WANNA SEE ? SEE ?
SEE THAT RIGHT THERE ?
- NOW WHAT'S UP ?
YOU DID.
LET ME TELL YOU.
I AIN'T BROKE IT, BUT I'M GONNA.
I SWEAR I'M GONNA BREAK IT
IF YOU DON'T TELL ME
WHERE LUTHER IS.
NOW !
ALL RIGHT ! JUST LET GO OF
MY FUCKING NOSE ! SHIT !
GODDAMN.
BEEN IN THE PEN ONLY TWO YEARS,
AND YOU ALREADY ACTIN' LIKE
A FUCKIN' MADMAN.
HANGING WITH WHITE WOMEN
AND SHIT.
LOOK, JUST DO ME ONE FAVOR.
WHAT KIND OF FAVOR ?
JUST MAKE A PHONE CALL
FOR ME.
[ Laughs ]
NOW, SEE, THAT'S SOME SHIT
I CAN DO.
I CAN DO THAT.
SEE THIS HERE ?
I MAKE PHONE CALLS
ALL DAY, BABY.
- IT'S DIGITAL ?
- YEAH, THAT'S THE NEWER
DIGITAL "NOKIO" SHIT.
MAN, IT'S GOT THE CALLER ID,
MESSAGE CENTER, ALL THEM SHITS.
YEAH ? OKAY, THIS IS WHAT
I WANT YOU TO DO.
I WANT YOU TO HOOK UP
A MEETIN' WITH LUTHER.
TELL HIM I WANT TO MEET HIM
WHEREVER HE WANTS TO--
DOESN'T MATTER.
AND THEN I WANT YOU TO CALL ME
ON THIS PHONE.
WHAT THE FUCK, MAN ?
THAT'S MY PHONE, MAN !
THAT'S RIGHT.
SO I KNOW YOU KNOW THE NUMBER.
SHOULDN'T BE A PROBLEM.
HERE. I GOT THAT.
DON'T FRONT ME,
'CAUSE YOU HANGIN' OUT
WITH PIPPI LONGSTOCKINGS NOW.
OH, YEAH.
SON OF A BITCH.
HEY, YO, BIG BOY, GET ME
A NEW BAG OF ICE, MAN.
SHIT.
[ Door Opening ]
THANK YOU.
YOU OUGHT TO SAY GRACE.
- WHY ?
- THANK GOD FOR THE FOOD.
WELL, GOD DIDN'T GIVE ME
THE FOOD. YOU DID.
BESIDES, I'M...
NOT A BELIEVER.
[ Sucks Teeth ]
YOU AN ATHEIST ?
[ Laughs ]
YEAH, I'M A--
I'M AN ATHEIST.
I REALLY FEEL SORRY FOR YOU,
DOC.
WHY DO YOU FEEL SORRY FOR ME ?
JUST SAD, MAN.
YOU THINK THIS IS ALL THERE IS.
WAIT A SECOND. BEFORE YOU GO,
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING ?
- GO AHEAD.
- LOOK, THIS, THIS STAR STUFF--
I'M NOT EXACTLY EVELYN WOOD,
AND THERE'S QUITE A BIT
OF READING MATERIAL HERE.
YOU GOTTA KNOW
WHERE TO LOOK.
OBVIOUSLY.
[ Flipping Pages ]
IT'S IN THE BACK.
REVELATIONS,
CHAPTER EIGHT, VERSE TEN.
THAT'S WHAT YOU NEED.
[ Muttering ]
"AND THE THIRD ANGEL SOUNDED...
"AND THERE FELL
A GREAT STAR FROM HEAVEN,
BURNING LIKE A TORCH.
"AND IT FELL
UPON A THIRD OF THE RIVERS...
AND UPON THE FOUNTAINS
OF WATERS."
MY GOD.
THAT'S
AN INTERESTING REMARK...
COMING FROM AN ADMITTED ATHEIST
LIKE YOURSELF, DOC.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS ?
CLARENCE,
ANYTHING ELSE FROM ARCHANGEL ?
NOT SINCE THE NEWS
ABOUT REESE.
HEY, ANSWER ME !
IT'S REAL SIMPLE.
THERE'S A ASTEROID THE SIZE
OF KANSAS CITY HEADING FOR US.
WE ONLY HAVE A FEW DAYS LEFT
ON THIS EARTH.
AND I CAN'T ALLOW YOU
TO INTERFERE WITH GOD'S WILL,
MY BROTHER.
- CLARENCE, GET UP HERE, PLEASE.
- YOU GOT IT, BROTHER THOMAS.
[ Door Closes ]
I DON'T WANNA HEAR ABOUT IT.
RELAX, TYRELL.
I WAS RIGHT, YOU WERE WRONG.
IT WON'T BE THE LAST TIME
IT HAPPENS. GET USED TO IT.
WHAT ?
SO, THEY JUST HAPPENED
TO HAVE A HANDCUFF KEY ?
LOOK, I ALWAYS USED TO CARRY
HANDCUFF KEYS, LOCK PICKS.
JUST LIKE THAT CREDIT CARD--
YOU NEVER LEAVE HOME WITHOUT IT
IN THE HOOD.
[ Doorbell Buzzes ]
JUST A MINUTE !
[ Buzzing Continues ]
COMING !
OH, MY GOD.
- MATTHEW ?
- HEY, RHONDA.
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
THIS IS MY SISTER RHONDA.
HI. JANINE TYRELL.
YOU'RE A COP.
YEAH.
I THOUGHT YOU DIDN'T
COOPERATE WITH COPS.
YEAH.
THIS IS DIFFERENT.
I JUST NEED TO USE YOUR PHONE
AND MAKE A FEW CALLS.
SURE. COME ON.
MAKE YOURSELF AT HOME.
[ Reese On Phone ]
LUTHER SAID WHAT ?
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
I WAS FOUR.
HE WAS NINE.
SO YOU WERE CLOSE ?
MM, INSEPARABLE.
WE'VE HAD
OUR DIFFERENCES OVER THE YEARS,
BUT HE'S ALWAYS PROTECTED ME.
YOU WERE LUCKY TO HAVE THAT.
MM-HMM.
- MUST HAVE BEEN GOOD.
- SORRY ?
WHATEVER YOU DID
TO GET HIM TO WORK WITH YOU.
HE WAS OFFERED A DEAL.
HE COULD HAVE GOTTEN OFF--
TWO YEARS, TIME SERVED.
I KNOW.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TELL ME,
ARE YOU ?
I CAN'T.
SORRY.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, GOTTA GET GOING, OR
I'M GONNA BE LATE TO WORK.
THERE'S COFFEE IN THE KITCHEN.
YOU COULD HELP YOURSELF.
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT, DAMON.
YOU DID THE RIGHT THING
FOR ONCE IN YOUR LIFE.
THAT'S GREAT. OKAY.
ALL RIGHT. SO I'M GONNA HOOK UP
WITH YOU GUYS IN A HALF HOUR.
ALL RIGHT ? DONE DEAL.
IT'S ALL SET UP.
SO WHO'S LUTHER ?
- LUTHER'S A WEAPONS DEALER,
A SURVIVOR.
- IN WHAT SENSE ?
IN THE SENSE THAT PAYNE
GAVE HIM THE SAME CHOICE
AS HE GAVE EVERYBODY ELSE--
STOP WHAT YOU'RE DOING
ON YOUR OWN OR--
- OR HE'D STOP HIM.
- YEAH.
AND NOW THAT PAYNE HAS TAKEN
WHAT I GUESS WE CAN CALL
A LOWER PROFILE,
LUTHER AND OTHERS LIKE HIM ARE
COMIN' UP OUT OF THE WOODWORKS.
CAN'T WAIT TO MEET HIM.
LET'S GO.
LIKE THAT ? MIGHT AS WELL PUT
ON YOUR BIG WINDBREAKER WITH
THE BIG YELLOW FBI ON THE BACK.
AIN'T NOBODY GONNA TALK TO YOU
LIKE THAT.
IN CASE YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED,
I PACKED KINDA LIGHT,
AS IN, THIS IS ALL I GOT.
IS THAT RIGHT ?
WHAT DO YOU WANT NOW ?
I'M ALREADY RUNNING LATE.
I NEED TO CHECK YOUR CLOSET.
DON'T LOOK SO SHOCKED, HONEY.
I'M THE BLACK SHEEP
OF THE FAMILY.
NO PUN INTENDED.
THEY SAY PRISON WILL DO
STRANGE THINGS TO A MAN.
I'VE TRIED
TO TELL HIM THAT.
[ Laughs ]
WHATEVER. COME CHECK
SOME OF THIS STUFF OUT.
DO YOU MIND IF SHE LOOKS
THROUGH YOUR THINGS ?
NO, AS LONG AS IT'S FOR HER
AND NOT FOR YOU.
DON'T YOU GOTTA BE AT WORK
OR SOMETHIN' ?
SEE YOU ALL TER.
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND,
THE CAUSE IS GREATER
THAN ANY ONE INDIVIDUAL.
EXCUSE ME.
I WAS JUST SAYING,
REESE HAD A FAMILY TOO.
I KNOW, AND SO DID I.
I LOST MY BROTHER THAT DAY,
DIDN'T I ?
BUT NO ONE SAID
THIS WAS GONNA BE EASY.
LOOK HOW WE LIVIN'.
WE HAD TO GO UNDERGROUND
TO DEAL WITH THE UNDERWORLD.
THIS IS GOD'S WORK.
GOD'S WORK IS NOT EASY.
NOW MY FAITH IS STRONG.
I JUST HOPE YOUR FAITH
IS STAYING STRONG, MY BROTHER.
MY FAITH IS STRONG TOO,
BROTHER THOMAS.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT, BIG MAN.
GOD BLESS.
HEY.
HOW YOU DOIN' ?
[ Kids Giggling ]
GIVE ME MY HUG.
COME HERE. COME HERE, MAN.
YOU READY FOR DINNER ?
YES.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU LET HER TAKE MY CAR.
HEY, RHONDA'S A COP NOW.
LET HER TAKE THE COP CAR.
HER CAR IS MORE SPORTY.
IT'LL BE BETTER
IF YOU LET ME DRIVE.
KIND OF HARD WITH THESE,
THOUGH.
DON'T MAKE ME REGRET THIS.
YOU KNOW, YOU MIGHT WANNA
HOOK ME UP WITH A PIECE
WHILE YOU'RE AT IT.
THEY GONNA THINK SOMETHING
IF I AIN'T STRAPPED.
DON'T PRESS YOUR LUCK.
YOU'LL BE SORRY.
NEVER KNOW WHEN YOU'RE
GONNA NEED SOME BACKUP.
HERE YOU ARE, SIR.
THANKS, DOUG.
ANY WORD ON TYRELL ?
NOTHING YET, SIR.
WE HAVE THE INTEL ON REESE,
SIR.
WHAT DO YOU GOT ?
WELL, APPARENTLY REESE'S WIFE
BELONGED TO THIS NEW TABORITE
SECT.
SHE AND SEVERAL OF THE CHURCH
MEMBERS WERE TAKEN HOSTAGE...
BY THIS DRUG GANG
THAT PAYNE HAD TARGETED.
THE GANG LEADER WANTED
TO MAKE A DEAL WITH PAYNE,
GET HIM OFF THEIR BACK,
BUT PAYNE WASN'T INTERESTED.
INSTEAD, HE WENT OVER
TO THE PLACE WHERE THE HOSTAGES
WERE BEING HELD,
BLEW IT AWAY,
TOOK OUT EVERYBODY--
DRUG DEALERS,
HIS OWN CHURCH MEMBERS.
EVERYBODY.
HELL OF A GUY.
WELL, REESE WANTED REVENGE,
SO HE AMBUSHED PAYNE'S CAR--
SHOT IT OUT WITH PAYNE,
HIS BROTHER, BODYGUARD.
REESE WAS ABLE TO TAKE OUT
TWO OUT OF THE THREE BEFORE
PAYNE WOUNDED HIM.
THAT IS WHY HE'S DOING
12 YEARS IN LOMPOC.
AND THAT IS THE THREAD
THAT CIVILIZATION CURRENTLY
HANGS ON, SIR.
THANKS, TOM.
THAT'S VERY COMFORTING.
I RATHER THOUGHT SO.
♪ DON'T HATE THE PLAYA
HATE THE GAME, NIGGA ♪
♪ SHARPEN YOUR AIM
EVERY BUM ON THE STREET'S ♪
♪ IN SEARCH OF FORTUNE
AND FAME ♪
♪ SOME COME UP, SOME GET DONE UP
ACCEPT THE TWIST ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE OUT
FOR MAKIN' CHEDDAR
YOU GOT TO GO HIGH RISK ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I GET ILLY
COCK BACK THE NINE-MILLI ♪
♪ I CHOOSE NOT TO BUST
SMACK YOUR PUNK ASS SILLY ♪
♪ JUST BOUGHT A CRIB
IT COST 2.5 MILLI ♪
♪ SWIMMIN' POOL
IN MY LIVIN' ROOM
I GUESS I'M A WILLY ♪
♪ I DON'T GET HIGH SO I DON'T
SPLIFF THE PHILLIES ♪
♪ NIGGAS SAY THEY GONNA KILL ME
AND I SAY, "OH, REALLY" ♪
♪ HIT MY KAWASAKI
I PULL OFF ON A WHEELIE ♪
♪ THIS IS STRAIGHT-LACED PIMPIN'
I KNOW YOU HOS FEEL IT ♪
♪ I COME THROUGH
MAKE YOUR WHOLE CLUB PETRO
YOU MIGHT AS WELL LET GO ♪
♪ I BLAST
MAKE THE WHOLE CLUB ECHO ♪
♪ YOU DON'T REALLY WANNA TEST
A L.A. VET, THOUGH ♪
♪ MOST OF MY CREW'S
ON DEATH ROW ♪
♪ FOR REAL
QUICK WITH THE TRIGGER
NICE WITH THE STEEL ♪
♪ STEP INTO THE KILL ZONE
CATS GET PEELED ♪
'SUP, LUTHER ?
'SUP WITH YOU ?
WASN'T EXPECTING TO SEE
YOUR ASS FOR ANOTHER TEN YEARS.
THAT'S THE WORD I HEARD
FROM THE INSIDE.
WORD FROM THE INSIDE
MUST BE WRONG.
GUESS SO.
- WHO'S THE BITCH ?
- THAT'S MY BITCH.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT HER.
ME AND YOU
GOT SOME BUSINESS TO TEND TO.
- RIGHT.
- SEEMS WE BOTH GOT
A MUTUAL ENEMY.
THIS IS TRUE, BUT I AIN'T
SEEN HIM IN A WHILE, THOUGH.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYIN' ?
MOTHERFUCKER CALLED ME LUCIFER
OR SOME SHIT.
SAID I WAS DOIN'
THE DEVIL'S WORK.
FUCK HIM.
THAT WAS SOME FOUL SHIT HE DID
TO YOUR FAMILY, MY BROTHER.
BUT I CAN'T HELP YOU, THOUGH.
YEAH, YOU CAN'T HELP ME.
YOU WANNA GET HIM YOURSELF.
QUITE TO THE CONTRARY, SEE.
BROTHER PAYNE IS NO LONGER
A HINDRANCE TO MY BUSINESS,
THEREFORE, HIS DAY-TO-DAY
WHEREABOUTS DON'T CONCERN ME.
THAT AIN'T WHAT I HEARD
ON THE INSIDE.
THEY SAY YOU WATCHIN'
EVERY MOVE HE MAKES
SO YOU CAN HIT HIM YOURSELF.
NOW, REESE, IF, UH--
IF I DIDN'T KNOW BETTER, I'D SAY
YOU WAS CALLING ME A LIAR.
WELL, SOMEBODY'S LYING.
CHECK THIS OUT.
I AIN'T GOTTA
TAKE THIS SHIT FROM YOU
OR THIS MOTHERFUCKIN' COP.
YO, MAN,
YOU CHECK THIS OUT !
YOU DON'T TELL ME WHERE HE IS,
I'M GONNA KILL YOUR ASS.
DROP IT !
MAN, WHAT THE FUCK WRONG
WITH YOU ?
SHOOT THIS MOTHERFUCKER, MAN !
SHOOT HIM !
- SHOOT HIM !
- I SAID, DROP IT !
FUCK THAT BITCH !
SHOOT HIM !
SHOOT HIM, MOTHERFUCKER !
[ Grunting ]
DAMN, YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO DO THIS, MAN.
FUCK YOU.
ALL RIGHT, LUTHER.
YOU CHECKIN' OUT.
THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCE
TO DO SOMETHIN' RIGHT, MAN.
WHERE'S PAYNE ?
- I SAID, FUCK YOU.
- LUTHER, WHERE'S PAYNE ?
YOU DIDN'T HEAR ME,
MOTHERFUCKER ?
I SAID, F--
LET'S GO, REESE.
MOTHERFUCKER
PULLED A GUN ON ME.
GIVE ME THE GUN.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
I SAID, GIVE ME THE GUN.
I'M NOT KIDDING AROUND, REESE.
I'M NOT GONNA TELL YOU AGAIN.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL
SQUEEZE THE TRIGGER,
'CAUSE I'M NOT GOING
INTO ANOTHER SITUATION
LIKE THIS WITHOUT A GUN.
WHAT, I'M SUPPOSED TO BE SCARED
OF YOU NOW, AFTER THAT SHIT ?
CENTAURUS  IS UP, SIR.
WHAT'S THE RENDEZVOUS TIME
TOMORROW AT, DR. SECOR ?
0748 HOURS, EDT.
[ Secor ]
WE'RE REPROGRAMMING
THE REMOTE ARMING SYSTEMS NOW.
WELL, I HOPE YOUR PLAN WORKS.
SO DO I.
COME ON. YOU CAN DO IT.
IT'S JUST LIKE
HOLDING YOUR BREATH.
JUST TAP ME ON THE LEG
WHEN YOU WANNA GET SOME AIR.
THAT'S ALL.
FOOL, YOU DONE LOST YOUR MIND.
I AIN'T DOIN' THAT.
NOT IN THE WATER, ANYWAY.
COME ON, BABY.
DON'T YOU SEE I'M HURT ?
I GOT A INJURY HERE.
YOU AIN'T GOT NO SYMPATHY
FOR ME, HUH ?
NO, I READ IN THE PAPER
THE OTHER DAY THAT SOME CHICK
IN AUSTRALIA OR SOMEPLACE...
DROWNED DOIN' THAT,
AND MISS LAKWANDA
AIN'T GOIN' OUT LIKE THAT.
MISS LAKWANDA IS A LIAR.
YOU AIN'T READ NOTHIN'
LIKE THAT.
I AIN'T LYIN'.
HE HELD HER BY THE HEAD,
WAS HOLDING HER DOWN ON IT,
AND SHE DROWNED.
LOOK, THAT'S A BUNCH OF BULL,
OKAY ?
I'LL SHOW YOU.
IT'S NOT THAT COMPLICATED.
GO FOR IT.
WHAT ? WHAT DID YOU MOVE FOR ?
I DIDN'T BITE YOU.
HEY, DAMON.
OH, SHIT ! REESE !
[ Lakwanda Screaming ]
WHAT THE HELL IS WRONG WITH YOU,
NEGRO ?
THIS IS A BRAND NEW HOT TUB !
NOW THIS FUCKER'S GONNA LEAK
ALL OVER THE PLACE !
YOU, GET OUT OF HERE !
HEY, LOOK, LAKWANDA, BABY.
I'M GONNA GIVE YOU A CALL ABOUT
THAT GET-JIGGY-WITH-IT THING.
WHAT THE HELL IS WRONG WITH YOU,
PIPPI LONGSTOCKINGS ?
YOCAN'T JUST COME UP IN HERE,
SHOOTING UP SHIT. YOU A COP !
SELF-DEFENSE.
YOU REACHED FOR YOUR WEAPON.
REESE, TAKE CARE OF HIM.
I'LL BE OUT FRONT.
OH, W-W-WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
ALL RIGHT. THIS IS HOW
WE GONNA DO IT THIS TIME, DAMON.
YOU GONNA GIVE ME SOMETHING
I CAN WORK WITH THIS TIME...
OR I'M GONNA BLAST
YOUR LYING ASS ALL OVER
THIS FUCKIN' BACKYARD !
COME ON, REESE, MAN.
DON'T YOU THINK IF I COULD,
I'D HELP YOUR LIGHT-SKINNED
ASS OUT, MAN ?
YOU OBVIOUSLY AIN'T FEELIN' ME.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT. LOOK.
ALL RIGHT. POINT THE GUN
AWAY FROM THE BEEF, OKAY ?
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING,
ALL RIGHT ? MY COUSIN
WAS FRIENDS WITH A GIRL.
SHE WAS A REPORTER
FOR THE LOCAL NEWS. SHE WAS
AT ONE OF PAYNE'S MEETINGS.
AND PAYNE'S MEN CAUGHT HER
WITH A HIDDEN CAMERA.
ALL RIGHT ?
THEY LET HER GO. AT LEAST,
THAT'S WHAT SHE THOUGHT, ANYWAY.
AND THEY FOUND HER
ON THE SIDE OF THE FREEWAY,
ALL RIGHT ?
IT SEEMS SOMEBODY RAN
HER CAR OFF THE ROAD.
SHE WAS IN A COMA FOR TWO WEEKS.
THEY THOUGHT SHE WASN'T
GONNA MAKE IT.
BUT SHE DID, APPARENTLY.
PAYNE DON'T EVEN KNOW IT,
THOUGH.
I NEED A NAME AND A ADDRESS.
LOOK, MAN.
I DON'T KNOW NO NAMES.
OH, YOU THINK
I'M FUCKIN' WITH YOU, RIGHT ?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
I SEE YOU GOT THE PISTOL
POINTED AT THE LEFT BALL.
HER NAME IS TERESA MILLER.
SHE'S LIVIN' IN A TRAILER
SOMEWHERE IN THE MIDDLE OF
BUM FUCK SOMEWHERE, OKAY ?
THERE'S NO ADDRESS
OR NOTHIN' LIKE THAT,
BUT I'LL HOOK YOU UP, ANYWAY.
GET YOUR ASS OUT OF E POOL.
ALL RIGHT, NIGGER.
YO, YOU AIN'T GOT
TO POINT THAT SHIT.
SHUTTLE BAY DOORS OPEN.
INITIATING FINAL DEPLOYMENT
SEQUENCE... NOW.
LINEBACKER DEVICE RELEASED.
MAIN ENGINE'S IGNITION
CONFIRMED.
DEVICE IS AWAY.
WHEN DID YOU FIND THAT OUT ?
[ Children Giggling ]
HE AIN'T GONNA LIKE
TO HEAR THAT.
[ Giggling Continues ]
YOU GUYS WANNA SEE
WHAT YOU GOT ?
[ Together ] UH-HUH.
- YOU WANNA SEE ?
WHAT DO YOU THINK, MOM ?
- I THINK SO.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, LOOK AT THAT.
DOES IT LOOK NICE ?
YES.
OKAY.
YEAH. LOOK AT YOU,
LITTLE PRINCESS.
IS THIS THE DRESS I'M GONNA
WEAR WHEN I MEET GOD ?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE GONNA LOOK SO PRETTY,
HE'S GONNA PUT YOU RIGHT UP
TO THE FRONT OF THE LINE.
WELL, BROTHER CLARENCE,
SIT DOWN AND HAVE SOME DINNER
WITH THE FAMILY.
- WE NEED TO TALK.
- CAN IT WAIT ?
I'M GONNA GO SEE
THIS BIG MAN.
OKAY.
[ Whispers, Indistinct ]
WHAT'S UP, MY BROTHER ?
JUST TALKED TO ARCHANGEL.
THEY KILLED LUTHER.
LUCIFER. YOU SEE THAT ?
NOW YOU SEE THAT ?
YOU REAP WHAT YOU SOW.
WHAT ELSE ?
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SOMEONE
ACTUALLY LIVES OUT HERE.
SOMEBODY BETTER, OR DAMON WON'T
BE LIVING TOO LONG HIMSELF.
[ ese ]
A MILE TO THE GATE, MY ASS.
THIS IS MORE LIKE THREE.
[ Tyrell ]
I HAD NO IDEA
YOU WERE SUCH A WUSS.
HELLO ?
TERESA MILLER ?
LEAVE NOW !
[ Tyrell ]
HEY, TAKE IT EASY.
I DON'T WANT TO TAKE IT EASY.
I WANT YOU TO LEAVE.
NOW, GET OUT !
WE'RE HERE TO HELP YOU.
I DON'T NEED YOUR HELP.
TELL HER WHOOU ARE.
HEY, LADY,
THIS IS MATTHEW REESE OUT HERE.
YOU'RE LYING.
MATTHEW REESE IS IN PRISON.
- I'M NOT LYING.
- THEN, PROVE IT.
HOW AM I GONNA PROVE IT ?
I DON'T HAVE ANY I.D.
OR ANYTHING.
COME IN HERE.
[ Teresa ]
I KNOW WHAT YOU LOOK LIKE.
OKAY, RELAX. ALL RIGHT ?
ENOUGH SHOOTIN'.
[ Door Opens ]
[ Reese ]
ALL RIGHT. I'M COMIN' IN.
JUST BE CAREFUL WITH THAT GUN.
DON'T GET NERVOUS.
SEE ?
OKAY, SO IT IS YOU.
BUT WHO'S OUT THERE WITH Y ?
- OH, OUT THERE.
- DROP IT !
NO !
LOOK. IT'S OKAY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S OKAY.
THIS WAS HIS LAST SERMON
BEFORE HE WENT UNDERGROUND.
[ TV: Applause ]
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU,
BROTHERS AND SISTERS.
THANK YOU.
- I WANT TO ASK A QUESTION.
- [ Tyrell ]  WHAT WE NEED...
IS ANY KIND OF INFORMATION
WHERE HE MIGHT BE HIDING.
JUST WATCH IT.
GUN DEALERS TO SELL THEIR WARES
IN A RICH NEIGHBORHOOD ?
THEY DON'T, DO THEY ?
WELL, HOW COME THEY TURN
A BLIND EYE TO IT DOWN HERE ?
DO WE HAVE GUN-MANUFACTURING
PLANTS IN THIS SO-CALLED HOOD
OF OURS ?
WE HAVE INCOMING !
[ Computers Beeping ]
[ Chattering ]
OBJECT IS 60 METERS LONG
AND SIX METERS WIDE.
TRAVELING AT...
32,000 MILES PER HOUR.
IMPACT IN APPROXIMATELY...
90 SECONDS.
WHERE ?
122.5 WEST LONGITUDE,
[ Computer Beeping ]
37.6 NORTH LATITUDE.
THAT'S SAN FRANCISCO, SIR.
HI. IT'S ME. PICK UP.
YOU THERE ?
OKAY, I GUESS YOU'RE NOT THERE.
LOOK, UM,
I GOT FINISHED EARLY,
AND I CHANGED MY FLIGHT.
AND I GUESS I'LL BE SEEING YOU
IN A COUPLE OF HOURS.
WE HAVE ENTRY
INTO THE ATMOSPHERE.
I, UH, I MISSED YOU
LAST NIGHT.
[ Man ]
TWENTY SECONDS.
OKAY, UH,
I WILL TALK TO YOU SOON.
IMPACT IN TEN SECONDS.
SIX... FIVE...
FOUR... THREE...
[ Roaring ]
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S GOD'S WILL THAT WE ACT,
THAT WE DO SOMETHING !
[ Turns TV Off ]
THIS PLACE IN THE VIDEO--
WHERE IS IT ?
I COULDN'T TELL YOU.
COULDN'T OR WON'T ?
I DON'T THINK YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DEALING WITH HERE,
AGENT TYRELL.
THIS MAN IS A HERO
TO HIS PEOPLE.
ANY OF THEM
WOULD TAKE A BULLET FOR HIM.
I CAN'T CONCERN MYSELF
WITH THAT.
[ Sighs ]
IT WAS A FACTORY
OR A WAREHOUSE OF SOME KIND.
SOMETHING TOOL & DYE.
WHAT'S THE NAME ?
I DON'T REMEMBER.
IT MAY HAVE STARTED
WITH AN "E," MAYBE.
[ Clattering ]
HOLD ON.
A LITTLE EARTHQUAKE.
YEAH. LITTLE.
I DON'T LIKE THEM.
THEY ARE BAD OMENS.
I'M FROM TEXAS.
WE DON'T HAVE TO DEAL
WITH THIS KIND OF CRAP.
JUST HURRICANES
AND TORNADOS.
I'LL TAKE ANY ONE OF THOSE,
ANY OLD TIME. AT LEAST
YOU CAN SEE 'EM COMIN'.
- GET DOWN !
- [ Grunts ]
COME ON !
[ Grunts ]
FUCKIN' DAMON.
I'M GONNA KILL HIM
WHEN I SEE HIM.
LET'S GET THE HELL
OUT OF HERE.
ALL RIGHT, GODDAMN.
LET'S GET THIS SHIT STRAIGHT
SO I CAN GET MY HO BACK UP HERE.
IT SAYS,
"USE IN WELL-VENTILATED AREA."
WELL, SHIT, MY BLACK ASS
IS OUTSIDE. I GUESS THAT'S
WELL-VENTILATED ENOUGH. SHIT.
WHAT'S HAPPENING,
BROTHER DAMON ?
OH, SHIT.
YOU ALMOST SCARED ME, BABY.
NO NEED TO BE SCARED, BROTHER.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR NOSE
THERE ?
OH, THIS ? OH, MAN, SHIT.
I WAS WORKIN' DOWN AT THE JOB.
I WAS FLIPPIN' THEM BURGERS,
AND I CRACKED MYSELF ON THE NOSE
WITH THE SPATULA, MAN.
SHIT, I ALMOST LOST MY JOB.
I'M TRYIN' TO GET THAT
WORKMEN'S COMP AND SHIT.
DAMON...
YOU'RE LYIN' TO ME.
YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU LIE TO SOMEBODY...
YOU SURRENDER YOUR REALITY
TO THE PERSON YOU'RE LYING TO.
DID YOU KNOW THAT ?
MY REALITY, MAN ? I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKIN' ABOUT.
WHAT DO-- WHAT DO YOU MEAN ?
HAVEN'T I ALWAYS
TREATED YOU RIGHT, BROTHER ?
YEAH. I MEAN, SHIT,
YOU'RE BROTHER PAYNE, BABY.
YOU ALWAYS LOOKIN' OUT FOR ME.
WHEN YOUR MOTHER WAS SICK,
DIDN'T I BRING HER MEDICINE ?
DIDN'T I TREAT YOU LIKE FAMILY ?
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, YOU LOOKED OUT FOR
MY MOTHER WHEN SHE HAD THAT--
WHY WOULD YOU ATTEMPT
TO DELIVER ME INTO THE HANDS
OF THOSE WHO WOULD DO ME HARM ?
COME ON, BROTHER PAYNE.
YOU KNOW I WOULDN'T DO
NO SHIT LIKE--
YOU KNOW YOUR BIBLE, DAMON ?
UM, I HAVEN'T BEEN TO CHURCH
IN A WHILE, 'CAUSE I AIN'T
HAD NO OFFERIN' MONEY.
BUT, I MEAN, A LITTLE BIT.
I KNOW SOME.
MATTHEW 10:36:
"A MAN'S FOE SHALL BE
THEY OF HIS OWN HOUSEHOLD."
SHIT.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND, MAN.
WHY DON'T YOU THINK ABOUT IT ?
[ Groaning ]
GOD, PLEASE !
OH, GOD, PLEASE HELP ME !
LORD HELPS THEM THAT HELPS
THEMSELVES, BROTHER DAMON.
WE NEED TO GET OUR HANDS
ON A PHONE BOOK.
[ Newscaster ]
I'M TRYING TO GET IN CLOSER,
GET AN IDEA OF THE DEVASTATION.
THERE ARE FIRES BURNING AS
FAR AS YOU CAN SEE. IT'S LIKE
THE WHOLE GROUND IS ON FIRE.
[ Newscaster #2 ]
IS THE CITY VISIBLE AT ALL ?
CAN YOU SEE ANYTHING ?
[ Newscaster #1 ]
OH, GOD, SAN FRANCISCO,
OAKLAND--
THEY'RE JUST GONE.
THEY'RE GONE.
WAIT, WE'RE BEING WAVED OFF
BY A MILITARY AIRCRAFT.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO GET BACK--
[ Newscaster #2 ]
MIKE, ONE MORE THING.
[ Newscaster #1 ]
I'M GONNA HAVE TO GET BACK
TO YOU BECAUSE WE NEED TO--
[ Newscasters Continue,
Indistinct ]
OH, GOD.
[ Newscaster #2 ]
IT APPEARS WE HAVE LOST HIM,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
- [ Newscast Fades ]
- SHIT.
[ Busy Signal On Phone ]
[ Tyrell Sobbing ]
OH, GOD.
[ Knocking On Door ]
CLARENCE, IS THERE ANY WAY
I COULD GET SOME PAPER
AND A PENCIL ?
SOMETHING TO WRITE WITH
LIKE THAT ?
THAT'S AGAINST
BROTHER THOMAS' RULES.
I'M GOING NUTS IN HERE.
I-I CAN'T SLEEP.
MY MIND JUST KEEPS GOING,
AND I GOT SOME THOUGHTS...
AND I CAN'T FIGURE THEM
IN MY HEAD, AND I NEED
TO PUT 'EM DOWN.
I CAN'T TURN IT OFF, CLARENCE.
I'M GOIN' NUTS IN HERE.
I'M GONNA SEE WHAT
I CAN DO, BUT I CAN'T
PROMISE YOU ANYTHING.
THANK YOU.
GENERAL MEECH,
THE LATEST TELEMETRY SHOWS
THE LINEBACKER'S ON TARGET.
SET TO RENDEZVOUS WITH
THE ASTEROID IN 30 MINUTES.
THANKS, TOM.
[ Phone Beeps ]
MEECH.
I WANT THE TRUTH
ABOUT CORBETT, GENERAL.
TYRELL, WHERE ARE YOU ?
DID YOU GET HIM ?
YOU SAID THREE DAYS.
CORBETT COULD'VE STOPPED IT,
COULDN'T HE ?
THERE'S NOTHING
HE COULD'VE DONE.
DON'T FUCKING LIE TO ME !
ADVANCED SPACE DEFENSE WEAPONS
RESEARCH. COME ON, GENERAL.
TYRELL, CALM DOWN.
DON'T TELL ME TO CALM DOWN !
SOMEONE I CARED ABOUT A LOT
WAS KILLED UP THERE.
TYRELL, LISTEN TO ME.
THERE ISN'T ANYTHING CORBETT
COULD'VE DONE. NOTHING.
THE FRAGMENT WAS TOO SMALL.
WE ONLY PICKED IT UP A MINUTE
AND HALF BEFORE IT HIT.
FRAGMENT OF WHAT ?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT ?
AN ASTEROID
IS ON A COLLISION COURSE
WITH THE EARTH.
WHAT HIT SAN FRANCISCO
IS A PEBBLE BY COMPARISON.
UNLESS WE STOP IT,
CIVILIZATION
LIFE AS WE KNOW IT--
WILL CEASE TO EXIST.
ANYTHING THAT MANAGES
TO SURVIVE THE INITIAL BLAST
WILL DIE IN THE IMPACT WINTER.
- HOW LONG HAVE YOU
KNOWN ABOUT THIS ?
- UNDER 48 HOURS.
AND THAT'S
THE GOD'S TRUTH, TYRELL.
WHY AREN'T PEOPLE
BEING WARNED ?
COME ON, TYRELL.
WE'RE TALKING MASS PANIC.
BUT YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT CORBETT.
HE'S DESIGNED A WEAPON...
THAT HAS THE CAPABILITY
TO DESTROY THE ASTEROID.
THEN, WHY DOESN'T THE PRESIDENT
HAVE EVERY GODDAMN RESOURCE
AVAILABLE ON THIS,
AND WHY IS IT THAT ME AND SOME
GODDAMN CONVICT ARE THE ONLY
ONES LOOKING FOR THIS GUY ?
'CAUSE HE DOESN'T KNOW.
HE HAS NO IDEA THAT I'M--
THAT YOU ARE OUT THERE
TRYING TO FIND CORBETT.
DON'T YOU THINK IT'D BE
A GOOD IDEA TO TELL HIM ?
TYRELL, A WEAPON
CALLED LINEBACKER IS ON ITS WAY
TO THE ASTEROID RIGHT NOW.
IT WAS DESIGNED
BY THE PRESIDENT'S
COLLEGE ROOMMATE...
WHICH MEANS IT GOT BOUGHT
AND CORBETT'S DIDN'T.
IT'S ALSO COMPLETELY WORTHLESS,
GIVEN THE TARGET.
THAT'S CRAZY.
THAT'S POLITICS.
SO, HOW CLOSE ARE YOU
TO FINDING CORBETT ?
MOMMA, MOMMA, HUSH.
I JUST CALLED 'CAUSE
I WANTED TO HEAR YOUR VOICE...
AND TELL YOU THAT I LOVE YOU.
YEAH. NO, I KNOW.
I KNOW YOU DO. I KNOW.
I JUST, UH-- I JUST
WANTED TO CALL AND SAY THAT.
OKAY ? SO, I'LL, UH--
I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
YEAH, I LOVE YOU TOO. BYE.
[ Phone Beeps ]
I KNOW IT MAY NOT HELP,
BUT I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
GOING THROUGH.
IT'S LIKE SOMEBODY
REACHES INSIDE AND JUST
TEARS YOUR INSIDES OUT.
ANYWAY, I FOUND 15 PLACES
THAT START WITH THE LETTER "E."
SO WE GOT A LOT OF WORK TO DO.
WE SHOULD GET WITH IT.
WHAT'S THE FUCKING POINT ?
YOU GOTTA LISTEN TO ME.
YOU GOT A CHANCE
TO SAVE THE PEOPLE YOU LOVE.
I DIDN'T HAVE THAT CHANCE.
I'M GONNA TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF IT, IF YOU DON'T MIND.
I'M NOT ABOUT TO JUST
LET YOU SIT AROUND HERE
AND QUIT, OKAY ?
SO GET YOUR LEG IN.
WE'RE GOIN'.
I DIDN'T GO THROUGH
ALL THIS BULLSHIT JUST TO GET
THREE DAYS OF FREEDOM...
AND THEN GET KILLED
WITH EVERY OTHER DUMB
MOTHERFUCKER ON EARTH.
HEY, REESE, I CAN'T LET YOU
WALK INTO ANY MORE OF THESE
SITUATIONS WITHOUT A GUN.
[ Chuckles ]
YOU CALL THIS A GUN ?
IT'S MY BACK-UP.
ALL RIGHT. BACK-UP. COOL.
I AIN'T TURNIN' DOWN NO GUNS.
WE HAVE VISUAL CONTACT
WITH THE ASTEROID.
IMAGE COMING UP NOW.
[ Keller ]
THIRTY SECONDS TO IMPACT.
ARM THE DEVICE.
- [ Gauges Beeping ]
- DEVICE IS ARMED.
STANDING BY TO DEPLOY
MULTIPLE WARHEADS.
IMPACT IN 15 SECONDS.
STANDING BY, SIR.
[ Meech ]
DEPLOY MULTIPLE WARHEADS.
[ Keller ]
DEPLOYING.
DEPLOYMENT COMPLETE.
FIVE SECONDS.
FOUR, THREE, TWO--
IT WORKED.
[ All Cheering ]
WAY TO GO, MAN !
[ Cheering Continues ]
HOW LONG
FOR THE DOPPLER DELAY ?
GIVE ME A MOMENT, SIR.
[ Tapping Keyboard ]
DOPPLER DELAY DATA READINGS
COMING IN NOW.
[ Monitor Beeping ]
IT DIDN'T WORK.
IT'S STILL COMING AT US.
TRAJECTORY DIFFERENTIAL:
.00682 DEGREES.
I THINK I GOT THE IDEA.
[ Sighs ]
WHAT DO WE DO NOW, SIR ?
WHOA, WHOA.
THIS IS IT.
ANY IDEAS ON HOW TO GET IN ?
THERE'S ALWAYS A WAY IN.
DOC, GOT SOME FOOD FOR YOU.
I'M NOT REAL HUNGRY
RIGHT NOW. THANKS.
I'LL BRING IT IN ANYWAY.
YOU MIGHT NEED IT LATER ON.
[ Grunting ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
TRYING TO GET YOURSELF KILLED ?
[ Growls ]
I CAN'T JUST SIT HERE
AND WAIT TO DIE.
IS THAT WHAT
YOU'RE AFRAID OF ? DYING ?
YES.
BECAUSE YOU DON'T HAVE NO FAITH.
YEAH, WELL, IT'S
A LITTLE LATE FOR THAT NOW.
NO, MY BROTHER,
IT'S NEVER TOO LATE.
I FOUND THE LORD
THREE YEARS AGO.
PAYNE ? HE, UH--
HE BROUGHT YOU TO THE LORD ?
YES, HE DID.
GOD BLESS HIM.
LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
DOESN'T IT BOTHER YOU ?
A GOD THAT WOULD DESTROY
WHAT HE HAS CREATED ?
THAT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
DOC, HE'S ALREADY
DONE IT ONCE, BY FLOOD.
THIS TIME BY FIRE.
IT SAYS SO RIGHT THERE
IN THE BIBLE.
RIGHT, RIGHT.
BUT IT SEEMS TO ME...
THAT IF GOD CREATED ALL OF US,
THEN HE CREATED ME TOO, RIGHT ?
- YES, HE DID.
- THEN, IF GOD GAVE ME...
THIS KNOWLEDGE
TO SAVE ALL THESE PEOPLE,
THEN ISN'T THAT
GOD'S WILL TOO ?
DO YOU BELIEVE EVERYTHING
YOU READ IN THE BIBLE ?
- YES, I DO. EVERY WORD.
- THEN, WHAT ABOUT THIS ?
"TAKE HEED THAT YOU
ARE NOT LED ASTRAY,
"FOR MANY FALSE PROPHETS
SHALL COME IN MY NAME...
"SAYING THAT I AM HE
AND THE TIME IS AT HAND.
DO NOT BELIEVE THEM."
[ Payne ]
YOU'RE GIVING BIBLE STUDY
LESSONS NOW, HUH, DOC ?
SEEMS LIKE ONLY YESTERDAY
YOU DIDN'T CARE MUCH
FOR THAT GOOD BOOK.
YOU OBVIOUSLY DIDN'T THINK MUCH
OF MY WIFE'S COOKING, EITHER.
NEVER MARRY
A SKINNY WOMAN, HUH ?
CLARENCE, YOU WANNA
GIVE US A MOMENT ALONE ?
DON'T LEAVE THESE
LAYING AROUND, BROTHER.
SOMEONE COULD GET HURT.
SO YOU THINK
I'M A FALSE PROPHET.
I THINK
YOU'RE FUCKING CRAZY.
AND I ALSO THINK
THAT ALL THESE PEOPLE THAT
YOU PRETEND TO CARE ABOUT...
ARE GOING TO DIE.
I LOVE THEM.
I LOVE THEM DEARLY,
MORE THAN MY OWN LIFE.
THAT'S WHY I'M DELIVERING
THEM INTO THE LOVING HANDS
OF THE LORD...
AND NOT THE TALONS
OF YOUR SO-CALLED SCIENCE.
THAT IS SUCH BULLSHIT.
IF YOU TRULY CARED ABOUT THEM,
THEN YOU WOULD LET ME SAVE THEM,
ALONG WITH ALL THE OTHER
PEOPLE ON THIS PLANET.
I DON'T DOUBT THAT YOU'D
BE ANXIOUS TO GET OUT THERE...
AND TAMPER WITH MOTHER NATURE
OR GOD'S WILL.
SCIENTISTS HAVE ALWAYS BEEN
VERY READY TO DO THAT,
BUT, YOU SEE,
THEN HUMANITY SUFFERS...
AND WE HAVE TO FIGHT
THE SAME BATTLES WE CONTINUE
TO FIGHT AND CONTINUE TO LOSE.
IT IS TIME
TO BRING THIS TO AN END.
IT'S NOT YOUR DECISION
TO MAKE.
SHUT UP ! HUT UP !
DON'T SCREAM
OR YOU'RE DEAD.
WHERE'S CORBETT ?
WE AIN'T PLAYIN', BITCH.
DROP IT !
I SAID DROP IT !
LET HER GO. GET OVER THERE
WITH YOUR FRIEND.
YOU GO ON BACK THERE
AND GET YOUR HUSBAND
WHILE I HOLD 'EM HERE.
GO ON ! GO ON !
I FIGURE WE GOT
A MINUTE AND A HALF
BEFORE SHE GETS BACK WITH HIM.
WE GOTTA MOVE REAL FAST
IF YOU WANT DR. CORBETT.
COME ON.
COME ON !
SO WHAT ?
WHAT'S YOUR ANSWER ?
JUST TO DESTROY THE WORLD ?
YOU KNOW, MAN, IF YOU'RE
THAT DISGUSTED WITH IT,
THEN WHY DON'T YOU
JUST TAKE YOURSELF OUT AND LET
THE REST OF US GET ON WITH IT ?
DOC, SURELY YOU KNOW THAT
TO COMMIT SUICIDE, IN ALMOST
EVERY RELIGION, IS A SIN.
SUICIDE IS A SIN ?
YOU ARE COMMITTING SUICIDE BY
NOT LETTING ME STOP THIS THING !
I DIDN'T CREATE THIS COMET.
THIS IS A NATURAL PHENOMENON.
SEE, THIS IS GOD'S MERCY.
[ Scoffs ]
NOW, GOD
IS A MERCIFUL GOD.
HE'S A LOVING GOD.
HE'S A FORGIVING GOD.
BUT HE HAS SAID ENOUGH !
IF I WERE YOU,
I'D LOOK INTO MY HEART,
I'D LOOK INTO MYSELF AS A MAN.
MAKE PEACE WITH YOUR GOD.
MAKE PEACE WITH YOURSELF.
TIME IS RUNNING SHORT.
THOMAS !
THERE'S A WAY OUT
UP THEM STAIRS.
THOMAS, REESE IS HERE
AND THE WOMAN.
CLARENCE IS HOLDING THEM.
BROTHER REESE
IS VERY PERSISTENT. LET'S GO.
- WHERE DID YOU GET THAT ?
- I BORROWED IT FROM DAMON.
- WHY DID I GIVE YOU MY GUN ?
- THAT WAS YOUR BACK-UP, RIGHT ?
- YEAH.
- WELL, THAT'S WHAT
I'M USIN' IT FOR.
IT'S ALL CLEAR.
LET'S GO.
BROTHER CLARENCE !
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
HE WAS HERE.
HE WAS.
YOU GOT A KEY ?
YEP !
HURRY UP ! HURRY UP !
HI. I'M WITH THE FBI.
I'M HERE TO TAKE YOU OUT.
THANK GOD.
WE GOTTA GO !
WELCOME, BROTHER REESE.
NEXT TIME I FIRE, YOU GO
BACK THE WAY HE BROUGHT US.
YOU BEER BE WITH ME.
I'LL BE THERE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, REESE ?
DON'T YOU HEAR ME ?
YEAH, I HEAR YOU. GO.
GET HIM OUT OF HERE !
I'M SERIOUS !
[ Gunfire Continues ]
PEOPLE ARE DEPENDING
ON YOU. GO !
- WE'LL E YOU OUTSIDE.
- [ Machine Gun Firing ]
THAS !
LET'S GO.
YOU BELIEVE I'VE
WRONGED YOU, BROTHER ? HUH ?
MAYBE I THINK
YOU'VE WRONGED ME TOO.
- [ Gun Clicking ]
- AHHH !
TIME TO LET GOD DECIDE.
TELL ME WHAT HE SAYS !
GO !
[ Groaning ]
OKAY, COME ON.
[ Grunts ]
LET'S GO OUT THIS WAY.
JESUS CHRIST.
- [ Touch Tones Beeping ]
- [ Phone Buzzes ]
MEECH. TYRELL !
YEAH, I HAVE CORBETT.
YES, SEND A CHOPPER RIGHT AWAY.
SHE'S GOT HIM.
WHERE ARE YOU ?
WE NEED YOUR COORDINATES.
ESSENTIAL TOOL & DYE.
FIFTH AND SANTA FE.
OKAY, YOU STAY PUT.
WE'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
PUT CORBETT ON THE LINE.
I NEED TO TALK TO HIM.
YES, SIR ?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING ?
I'M NOT LEAVING
WITHOUT REESE.
WAIT !
STAY HERE.
YES, SIR ?
YES, SIR, THE CONTAINMENT FIELD
IS CALIBRATED AT EIGHT SEPARATE
POINTS WITHIN THE VESSEL.
CORBETT, I'M GONNA HAVE TO STOP
YOU, BECAUSE I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
THE HELL YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
SAVE IT FOR THE CAPE, 'CAUSE
THAT'S WHERE YOU'RE HEADED
AS SOON AS WE PICK YOU UP.
I CAN GIVE THEM
THE EXACT PARAMETERS.
IT WILL BE READY
BY THE TIME I GET THERE.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE THE TICKET.
YOU'LL HAVE ACCESS TO SECURE
COMMUNICATIONS ON THE BIRD.
GOOD LUCK, CORBETT.
LOOKS LIKE WE MADE IT, SIR.
NOT YET, BUT WE GOT
A FIGHTIN' CHANCE.
BROTHER REESE.
FUCK YOU, PAYNE. I'M TIRED
OF THAT "BROTHER" BULLSHIT.
PUT THAT SHIT DOWN.
DROP IT !
GO AHEAD AND SHOOT ME,
BROTHER.
SURELY I DESERVE
THE LORD'S WRATH.
HE'S MADE HIS DECISION.
GO ON.
YOURS WILL COME
IN A DAY OR SO.
WE GOT CORBETT OUT OF HERE.
HE KNOWS HOW TO FIX THAT THING.
YOU CAN'T CHANGE
THE LORD'S WILL, MY FRIEND.
[ Grunting ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Screaming ]
I WANT YOU TO KNOW
SOMETHIN', BROTHER.
YOUR FAMILY
DIDN'T DIE IN VAIN.
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO TAKE
A STAND AGAINST EVIL.
- SOMETIMES THE COST IS HIGH.
- [ Groaning Continues ]
BROTHER REESE.
GUESS THE BACK-UP
CAME IN HANDY AFTER ALL, HUH ?
YEAH. LOOKS LIKE
YOU COULD'VE USED IT.
YEAH. I'M OKAY.
LOOK, THERE'S A CHOPPER
ON THE WAY, SO WHY DON'T
YOU COME ON DOWN ?
I'M SICK
OF THIS FUCKIN' PLACE.
[ Roaring ]
[ Keller ]
THOR DEVICE ON FINAL APPROACH.
ARM THE DEVICE.
DON'T TOUCH IT.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING, DOUG ?
- I CAN'T ALLOW THIS, SIR.
WHAT IS WRITTEN
CANNOT BE CHANGED.
- THIRTY SECONDS TO IMPACT.
- SECURITY IN HERE, NOW !
MAN MUST BE DESTROYED
FOR HIS SINS.
BROTHER THOMAS WAS TO GUIDE US
THROUGH THE TIME OF TRIBULATION.
THAT TASK NOW FALLS TO ME.
CAPTAIN McNALLY,
I ORDER YOU--
THE DAY OF JUDGMENT
IS UPON US, SIR.
- TWENTY SECONDS.
- SAFETY THE WEAPON, CAPTAIN.
- I CAN'T DO THAT, SIR.
- SAFETY THE WEAPON
AND STAND DOWN NOW !
- NO, SIR.
- FIFTEEN SECONDS.
THIS IS YOUR
LAST CHANCE, SON.
SAFETY THE WEAPON.
STAND DOWN NOW.
- I WILL NOT, SIR !
- ALL RIGHT, FIRE AT WILL !
[ Men Shouting, Indistinct ]
DEVICE IS ARMED.
IMPACT IN TEN SECONDS.
NINE, EIGHT...
SEVEN, SIX...
FIVE, FOUR...
THREE...
TWO, ONE--
[ Static ]
DOPPLER DELAY,
WHAT DO WE GOT ?
[ Computer Beeps ]
IT'S GONE, SIR.
ALL FRAGMENTS
BELOW IMPACT THRESHOLD.
[ Applause, Cheering ]
- GOIN' BACK TO TEXAS, HUH ?
- HEY.
YEAH, YEAH, THEY'VE GOT
A REALLY NICE GIG FOR ME
IN DALLAS.
PLUS I THINK IT'LL BE NICE
TO BE CLOSER TO MY MOM.
- FAMILY'S IMPORTANT.
- YEAH, IT IS.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, BELATED.
HOW SWEET.
[ Laughs ]
I DON'T THINK I'M GONNA
BE NEEDIN' THAT ANYMORE.
PLUS I HEARD THERE'S A LOT
OF OUTLAWS DOWN THERE IN TEXAS.
RIGHT.
A LITTLE MORE SCRATCHED UP
THAN WHEN YOU GAVE IT TO ME,
BUT YOU KNOW--
NO, I WAS LOOKING
TO SEE IF THE SERIAL NUMBER
HAD BEEN FILED OFF.
SEE, THERE YOU GO
WITH THAT ATTITUDE.
[ Chuckles ]
THANK YOU.
SO TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELF, HUH ?
YOU TOO. ANIF YOU EVER
COME BACK, LOOK ME UP.
WE'LL HAVE COFFEE.
OKAY, BUT NONE OF THAT
CHICKEN AND WAFFLES, HUH ?
SEE, YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE MISSING.
I GUESS NOT.
I'LL SEE YOU.
♪ ICE T, BABY ♪
♪ THIS GOES OUT
TO ALL YOU HATERS OUT THERE ♪
♪ ACTIN' LIKE A BROTHER
DONE DID SOMETHIN' WRONG
'CAUSE HE GOT HIS GAME TIGHT ♪
♪ DON'T HATE THE PLAYA
HATE THE GAME ♪
HATE THE GAME, NIGGAS
SHARPEN YOUR AIM ♪
♪ EVERY BUM
ON THE STREET'S IN SEARCH
OF FORTUNE AND FAME ♪
♪ SOME COME UP, SOME GET DONE UP
ACCEPT THE TWIST ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE OUT
TO MAKE A CHEDDAR
YOU GOT TO GO HIGH RISK ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I GET ILLY
COCK BACK THE NINE-MILLI ♪
♪ I CHOOSE NOT TO BUST
SMACK YOUR PUNK ASS SILLY ♪
♪ JUST BOUGHT A CRIB
IT COST 2.5 MILLI ♪
♪ SWIMMIN' POOL
IN MY LIVIN' ROOM
I GUESS I'M A WILLY ♪
♪ I DON'T GET HIGH, SO I DON'T
SPLIFF THE PHILLIES ♪
♪ NIGGAS SAY THEY GONNA KILL ME
AND I SAY, "OH, REALLY" ♪
♪ HIT MY KAWASAKI
I PULL OFF ON A WHEELIE ♪
♪ THIS IS STRAIGHT-LACED PIMPIN'
I KNOW YOU HOS FEEL IT ♪
♪ I COME THROUGH
MAKE YOUR WHOLE CLUB PETRO ♪
♪ YOU MIGHT
AS WELL LET GO A BLAST
MAKE YOUR WHOLE CLUB ECHO ♪
♪ YOU DON'T REALLY WANNA TEST
A L.A. VET THOUGH ♪
♪ MOST OF MY CREW'S
ON DEATH ROW ♪
♪ FOR REAL
QUICK WITH THE TRIGGER ♪
♪ NICE WITH THE STEEL ♪
♪ STEP INTO THE KILL ZONE
CATS GET PEELED ♪
♪ YOU WHACK, YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR A RECORD DEAL ♪
♪ BOW DOWN, ON SECOND THOUGHT
PUNK BITCH, KNEEL ♪
♪ DON'T HATE THE PLAYA
HATE THE GAME, NIGGAS
SHARPEN YOUR AIM ♪
♪ EVERY BUM
ON THE STREET'S IN SEARCH
OF FORTUNE AND FAME ♪
♪ SOME COME UP, SOME GET DONE UP
ACCEPT THE TWIST ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE OUT
FOR MAKIN' CHEDDAR
YOU GOT TO GO HIGH RISK ♪
♪ DON'T HATE THE PLAYA
HATE THE GAME, NIGGAS
SHARPEN YOUR AIM ♪
♪ EVERY BUM
ON THE STREET'S IN SEARCH
OF FORTUNE AND FAME ♪
♪ SOME COME UP, SOME GET DONE UP
ACCEPT THE TWIST ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE OUT
FOR MAKIN' CHEDDAR
YOU GOT TO GO HIGH RISK ♪
♪ DON'T HATE ME 'CAUSE MY GAME'S
MUCH TIGHTER THAN YOURS ♪
♪ MY GIRL'S FINER THAN YOURS
MY SHOE SHINE'S BRIGHTER
THAN YOURS ♪
♪ YOU LOOK ME DEAD IN MY FACE
THEN YOU ACT LIKE
YOU DON'T SEE ME ♪
♪ YOU WANNA BE ME, YOU HATE
MY MOTHERFUCKIN' GUTS ♪
♪ LISTEN, NUTS
WHAT'S THE DEAL ♪
♪ IT'S A LEVEL PLAYIN' FIELD
MY GAME'S AGAINST YOURS ♪
♪ HUSTLIN' WARS
ROLL THE DICE ♪
♪ RISK YOUR MOTHERFUCKIN' LIFE
BANKROLLS AND LOW HOS ♪
♪ ANYTHING GOES
RIDE ROLLS IN A WEEK ♪
♪ CLAP A NIGGA WHO SPEAKS
I'M SUCCEEDIN' ♪
♪ A TRYIN' TO KEEP
FROM BLEEDIN' IN THE LANE ♪
♪ CRYSTAL METH, ECSTASY
AND CRACK COCAINE ♪
♪ YOU'RE THE NIGGA TRYIN'
TO FIGURE OUT THE BEST ROUTE ♪
♪ I GOT COPS IN MY REARVIEW TOO
BUT I'LL SHOOT ♪
♪ EVERY BITCH I MEET
IS FUCKIN' UP TO SOMETHIN' ♪
♪ TAKE A NIGGA TO THE CRIB, LAY
HIM DOWN AND START DUMPIN' ♪
♪ GAT PUMPIN', THEY'LL
KILL YOUR ASS FOR A G ♪
♪ HATE THE GAME, MOTHERFUCKER
DON'T HATE ME ♪
♪ DON'T HATE THE PLAYA
HATE THE GAME, NIGGA
SHARPEN YOUR AIM ♪
♪ EVERYUM
ON THE STREET'S IN SEARCH
OF FORTUNE AND FAME ♪
♪ SOME COME UP, SOME GET DONE UP
ACCEPT THE TWIST ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE OUT
FOR MAKIN' CHEDDAR
YOU GOT TO GO HIGH RISK ♪
♪ YO, MY NAME IS STAMPED
AND I'VE BEEN WRECKED
LIKE THE ACROPOLIS ♪
♪ SUCKERS MIGHT AS WELL
STEP BACK, THERE AIN'T
NO STOPPIN' THIS ♪
♪ WHACK MAGAZINES HAVE TRIED
AND TRIED TO TOPPLE THIS ♪
♪ I STILL GOT ROLEXES AND GATORS
ON MY SHOPPIN' LIST ♪
♪ MAKE A FIST
TAKE YOUR BEST SHOT ♪
♪ BET YOU'RE DROPPIN', KID
GET MORE LICKS THAN YOU ♪
♪ AIN'T NEVER CAUGHT A BID
MADE THE WHOLE WORLD
GO CRAZY ♪
♪ THEY SAY THE COP'S A PIG
BALDHEADED HO, STEP BACK ♪
♪ BITCH, GO AND COP A WIG ♪
♪ WHEN I DO A SHOW
BEST BELIEVE IT'S ROCK ♪
♪ EVERY NIGHT I PACK MY STRAPS
BEST BELIEVE THEY COCKED ♪
♪ SOME BITCH TALKS CRAZY
THEN THAT BITCH GETS SOCKED ♪
♪ IF A MAN STEPS UP
THEN HE TOO GETS DROPPED ♪
♪ FUCK THE COPS
I'M STILL FOLDIN' FAT KNOCKS ♪
♪ CATCH ME ON THE WEEKEND
FLOATIN' MY YACHT ♪
♪ SAY ICE KICKS SOME GAME
AND I'LL TEACH YOU A LOT ♪
♪ KNOCK YOU, BITCH
NO MATTER HOW HARD YOU BLOCK ♪
♪ DON'T HATE THE PLAYA
HATE THE GAME, NIGGA
SHARPEN YOUR AIM ♪
♪ EVERY BUM
ON THE STREET'S IN SEARCH
OF FORTUNE AND FAME ♪
♪ SOME COME UP, SOME GET DONE UP
AND ACCEPT THE TWIST ♪
♪ IF YOU'RE OUT
FOR MAKIN' CHEDDAR
YOU GOT TO GO HIGH RISK ♪