*
(all shouting)
Who the hell are you
to tell me
that we're not
qualified at The Hive?!
I may have too many aches
rolling off my tongue,
but I can tell you this...
I know that these boys
are only in danger of...
(all shouting)
And I know that
they'll be extinct
if we leave it
up to you!
Now, you
check the stats!
(all shouting)
I'm trying my best
to wrestle them away
from the jailhouse guard
and the graveyard dog,
because those are
the only two options
y'all are giving them.
(all shouting)
I'm up at 5:30
in the morning,
cooking for 'em
and here I am on
a Friday night
fighting for 'em!
(all shouting)
Why don't y'all go
and take some money
from some of them
white programs
and leave us
the hell alone!
We trying to make
a difference.
What the hell kind of
difference are y'all making?!
Leave my school alone!
Enough, enough!
(man) Yeah, nigger, do
something. (Man) That's
how you do it.
(woman)
That's it!
That's what
I'm talking about, man.
Y'all straight?
Yeah.
We're straight.
Go on, partner.
6-8.
Y'all know the 6-8,
right?
(man)
6-8 for life,
for life.
Making real niggas out here
in these streets, right?
Yeah.
(woman)
That's right.
That's what we do.
Go to the ground
for you.
(children shouting
in distance)
*
(woman)
I said, if you ain't got
a school or a job to go to,
you need to get your asses up
out of here.
Every last
one of you, trifling.
Don't make me have to
get up.
Move out of the way!
No, you move
out the way.
(boy)
Come on, Gem,
wake your ass up.
Shit, X.
Do what you wanna do,
but I'm still gonna be asleep.
Just turn your
ass over.
(girl)
Ooh!
What y'all doing?
Y'all nasty...
Stop it, X, why you
always starting stuff with me?
Move.
I got to beat y'all asses
day in and day out, huh?
Y'all know I had to wipe 100
old wrinkled asses last night?
The least y'all could do
is let me sleep.
(X)
I live by a few simple rules.
First one: Live in confusion
and never with
a confused mind.
Yeah, uh-huh.
Told you, partner.
That's your
probation officer.
You don't want to go to
school and be somebody?
Okay!
I'm gonna have him
take you down to jail
and put you with your
daddy
so y'all can be
stupid asses together!
You and baby mama ain't
gonna lay up on me
like I'm
the hotel keeper.
(baby crying)
Now this baby's up.
Mama, that ain't
his probation officer.
It's some other
white man.
*
Now, the way
this thing works is,
I'm the head of all the
schools in the county
and there's not
a one who will let you enroll,
but you four are lucky.
Your probation officers
believe in second chances,
so now consider me
and The Hive
your last chance, fellas.
You can either go to
117 County Farm Road
and learn from the books,
or you can go down to 119
and learn from the crooks.
Trust me.
I'd bet on 117
if I were you.
So are you boys helping us
out or you in trouble?
Now, over there is
the technology room.
We got boys designing their
own video games,
taking computers apart.
State of the art.
They've earned all
the big-screen TVs in there
and the PlayStations,
everything you see.
We partnered
with a DC company.
And then some of the boys take
what they've learned here
and they go back
to Birdie High
and they are
placed in advanced...
(man)
This is neutral ground,
young man.
You don't rep Crip, Blood,
C-Block,
Cherry Lane, 6-8s
or any other gang.
It's all Hive
up in here.
Ah, Mr. Hawk.
These four were just telling
me how sorry they were
that they missed
the first week of classes,
but they are happy
to be here now.
Aren't you, gentlemen?
All Hive boys call me
Mr. Hollis.
Any of you
boys have jobs?
Okay, well, in a class that
we like to call Wise Guy,
we're gonna be learning how
to fill out job applications.
Your name, sir?
Que.
Que what?
Always introduce yourself
with your entire name.
Que "Kick Your Ass"
Patterson.
Good to meet you,
Mr. Patterson.
Let me tell you something.
You're big, but it
would take you, your mama,
your daddy and his daddy
to kick my ass.
I'm Rack Robinson.
Middle initial "R."
Wow, man.
How tall is you?
6-6 and some change.
What kind of
business you in
to pay for all this
razzle-dazzle?
Oh, you know,
it's all legit.
I'm a businessman of
the highest order.
Some people call me C-note
'cause I know about 100 ways
to make them dollar signs.
Well, I'll be
calling you Mr. Robinson.
Wasn't there a Rack Robinson
used to play football?
Yeah, he's supposed
to be my father,
but I ain't
never met him.
His loss.
I'm glad you're here,
Mr. Robinson.
I can come back to you.
Man, why you keep
looking at me like that?
Shaking hands is gay.
And you would know
all about that now, huh?
(Rack laughing)
Consider this, gentlemen.
A real man is one
who is never afraid
to look another man
straight in the eye
and shake his hand,
unless he's hiding
something
or he's
scared of something.
Everybody sign in.
Assembly in five minutes.
Hey, big man.
I ain't scared of
nothing.
Especially you.
Oh, really?
Well, the day is still young,
Mr. Whoever You Are.
Gentlemen, please.
This way.
*
(woman)
I'm sure you've heard of
Whitmore Investment.
My family
is richer than dirt
but I want more for my life
than identifying
the next investment.
I'd rather invest in kids,
do you know what I mean?
Oh...
Did I tell you that
I got a flat tire in Jersey
and then when I finally
got here,
I couldn't find
the teacher's house?
Here it is.
This is the address
that I had.
Oh, that course is wrong.
You have to get off
at 17, not seven.
Oh, but that's okay,
don't you feel bad about it,
I got a little
ADHD myself.
I'll excuse
your lateness this time,
but just don't make it
a habit.
Excuse me, but I am
an experienced teacher.
Folks are late in these
boys' life all the time.
We here at The Hive,
we show up on time.
Sorry.
Did you say that there's
a teacher's supervisor
or a principal
that I could speak to?
I didn't say.
You know, Teachers for America
usually send me
some good people,
so if you come, you gonna
have to come correct.
And if you stay...
you better be sure
and pray.
So... the teacher supervisor
is where?
(chuckling)
Honey, you looking at her.
I am executive director
of The Hive.
Family Resource Center.
Now, there's a washroom
right down that hallway.
I know you may want to
freshen up
because assembly
starts in a few minutes.
You being such an
experienced teacher,
you're gonna want to wash off
that New York face
and put on a fresh Hive face.
Now go on, sweetheart,
it's right down there.
(man)
Morning.
Oh!
Some new boys for
The Hive.
Y'all come
on in, fellas.
(man)
I'm late for a meeting,
so I'm gonna leave these
four here with you,
but I'll probably
come back here for a plate.
On second thought...
And don't forget about the
school board meeting tonight.
All right, let me
look at you fellas.
Good-looking young men.
Every last
one of you.
You hungry?
Yes, ma'am, I am,
I'm...
(laughing)
Would be,
the littlest one.
Yeah, but I eats big.
My sister said it
goes straight to my feet.
My feet big.
Oh, I'm in love with you
already.
What's your name?
Courvoisier Carter.
Oh...
I swear on it, it's my
birth significant name.
Well, Mr. Courvoisier,
"everything go to my feet,"
you like technology?
Maybe,
but what is that?
Well, you're
gonna find out.
Okay, now, everybody
give me a hug.
We gotta go to assembly
and then tell me your name.
Okay.
I don't
like to be touched.
Well, honey, you're just gonna
have to humor me, young man,
'cause I plan to
love the hell out of you.
They call me Ms. Inez.
And, um...
Oh, yes,
and this is your new
English teacher, Ms. Whitmore.
She's here
all the way from.
Upper East Side Manhattan,
New York.
Did I quote you right,
Ms. Whitmore?
Yeah.
Hi, I'm Parker.
No, no, no.
Please call me
Ms. Whitmore.
And I have a lot of fun
things planned for us this year.
Why don't you plan on
sucking my...
(Mrs. Inez)
Oh, no, no!
Don't bring that
kind of hell up in here.
You can get on your
knees too, bitch.
Oh, you done bucked up
to the wrong person!
(clattering)
Now who's the bitch?
Now, you apologize to me
and Ms. Whitmore.
Today, I will listen.
(all)
I will speak.
I will see.
(all)
I will think.
I will feel.
(all)
And I will reason.
I am not a no-name
statistic.
(all)
I am not
a no-name statistic.
I am a man who is
too smart to waste today.
(all)
I am a man who is
too smart to waste today.
(banging)
Second rule:
Never let disrespect
go without being addressed.
Revenge is like the air.
Always necessary.
(clattering)
(spray paint hissing)
*
Look, I already
know the answer.
Please just let me call
the sheriff.
(sighing)
Yeah, well, he's typical.
Numerous suspensions
since kindergarten.
Stabbed a boy with
a pencil in third grade.
Fourth grade, he brought
a BB gun to school,
expelled for kicking
a teacher in the seventh,
was shot in the eighth.
Broke into a neighbor's
trailer last year.
His father's in jail,
awaiting trial
on armed robbery
and manslaughter.
Shall I continue?
Oh, baby, use the coffee pot
in my office.
New kid?
Mm-hmm.
What's the atypical
on him?
Uh...
His reading level's
not bad, fifth grade.
Well, he can't spell
worth a damn.
It says here he should
be in his junior year.
He'll be 17
in a couple months
and he's got zero
high school credit.
Oh...
But it does say he has
an aptitude for math.
I knew that boy had
something on the ball.
Look, don't read me
no more.
Baby...
now you go on
out of here.
Have yourself a nice day
at The Hive, all right.
Oh, bless her heart.
She going somewhere
and pray behind this.
You know what?
I gotta give it to
Ms. Christa.
She may look terrified,
but at least she's committed.
Now, Ms. Parker
punk rocker?
We may have to
take the hook out of her
and throw her back in
the creek.
Does she ever
even comb her hair?
Ms. Parker,
she got all style.
She just like
these kids.
Just needs somebody
to believe in her.
Well, come on,
drive me over there.
I'm gonna have to lasso in
this crazy mother for ya.
X, there ain't
nothing to eat
and Mama didn't
come home again last night.
Ain't no food stamps
coming for another week.
How many times I gotta tell
y'all to seal this shit up?
Don't you have any money?
Do I look like
I got any damn money?
You know what,
you always crying.
(all shouting)
No, X, don't, don't!
What you gonna do
now, punk, huh?
Stop it, X!
Cryin' little bitch!
(baby crying)
Remember me?
Your worst nightmare.
The black cunt you
can't even spell right.
(girl)
Thank you again,
Mrs. Inez.
I'm sure Mama's at
the grocery store right now.
She usually makes sure
we don't get this low.
Oh, that's
all right, baby.
At The Hive Research Center,
we have a food pantry.
You tell your mama that
nobody in this county
has to go hungry
as long as Mrs. Inez has
something to do with it.
Oh, look at this
little rascal.
He is smart just
like his daddy, ain't he?
Xtra's not smart.
I'm the one doing good
in school.
Oh, I can
see you're smart.
What you wanna be
when you grow up?
I don't know.
Just somebody going
somewhere out of here.
Shit, rest in prison
or rest in peace!
We all in the express lane
going towards one of 'em!
You a knucklehead,
you know that?
If it were up to me, you'd
be up under somebody's jail.
But Mrs. Inez,
she sees something in you,
and once you root
in her heart,
she ain't
giving up on you.
Even after
what I've done?
what you've done.
But you will make
restitution.
Man, you using
too many big-ass words.
Whatever you've done wrong,
you gotta make it right.
Whatever it takes.
You got a son.
You want him fighting
everybody he loves like you?
Man, Deuce
ain't gonna be like me,
'cause I'm the one
raising him.
Yeah, you are.
And kids repeat
what they know
and they do what they see.
So one day he gonna beat
his son and his chest,
the same way
somebody did you.
Is that what you want?
Look, we got a punching bag
down at The Hive gym.
It does
wonders for anger.
I ain't no dummy.
Remember that.
First time somebody treats
me like a dummy, I'm out.
(Mrs. Inez)
I always keep this around
in case we get a creative
sort, like you.
You see the outside
of The Hive?
All the paint's the same
because we've
never been tagged.
Every OG knows...
Oh... oh, yeah.
I got a PhD in your
little gang slang.
(sighing)
The Hive
is neutral territory.
Anybody knows to mess with it
is to ask for STS.
Street takes care of street,
and I know you know what kind
of justice I'm talking about.
See, you may be a Blood
or a Crip or a 6-8 for life,
but bangin' is always
a choice, boy.
You already
been shot twice.
I know you've heard about
three strikes.
Look, I ain't
afraid to die.
No.
Your type
is afraid to live.
I'll heat you up something
to eat for when you're done.
Oh, just for the record.
"Cunt" is spelled with
a "C," not a "K."
And "pussy"
has two "S"s in it.
So, yesterday, I took
Polaroid pictures
which I scanned to create
your individual stationery.
Now, you should see your picture
in the top right-hand corner.
So today, we will continue
to work on your bios, okay?
So who completed
the "Who Am I?" survey?
Come on.
"Who are you?"
How hard
can that be?
Age, name, hobbies.
We ain't never seen
a white woman like you.
Except on TV.
Is you related to
Lady Gaga or...
Do all white women
where you're from
switch up their
style like you do?
Uh... no.
And that's what
this assignment
is about today, gentlemen.
You know, what makes
you unique?
Different from others?
I never wanted to be
like everyone else.
So you in a white woman gang
or something?
(all laughing)
(Que)
Nigga, they don't got
no white woman gangs.
Too busy getting
9-1-1 on speed dial.
And how you know,
fat ass?
You ain't never been
nowhere to see no white women!
Okay.
No women, period!
Okay, shh!
Just sit down.
Oh, I guess you
getting up.
(Ms. Whitmore)
Stop it!
Guys, stop it!
(Mrs. Inez)
Good afternoon!
Stop.
You miss me?
(Ms. Whitmore)
How am I supposed to
teach someone who's...
The harder the child,
the greater the need
to find
a soft place in him.
And that ridiculous platitude
is supposed to do what?
Certainly
not reassure me.
Look, there is no way that
I can teach some...
All right.
You're right.
You can't teach
what you don't respect
or what you're
afraid of.
So don't teach him.
First, start off
by caring for him.
Until these boys know
you care for them,
they won't
care to learn.
(crickets chirping)
Look at you.
You up waiting on
your mama, hmm?
This used to be our
favorite time of the day
when you was
a little boy.
Remember?
Yeah.
So tell me
all about your dreams.
You still dreaming?
Not really.
What you mean?!
Dang, Mama, why you
always gotta hit me?
You're still not going to
that school?
Yeah, most times.
Well, make it
all the time.
Shit.
I'm thinking about
going back to nursing school
my damn self.
(sighing)
You know, X...
sometimes...
sometimes I don't even
wanna greet the morning.
You know that
ain't me.
Yeah, otherwise you get
backed in the corner
before you know it.
Back me in
the corner?
You know me.
I just come out
fighting.
Yeah.
Mama, don't you ever get
tired of fighting?
*
(humming)
(clattering)
Who that out there?
(Courvoisier)
Mrs. Inez, that thing had to
be about ten feet long.
You should have seen me
get up from under there,
that's what
you should have seen.
Now, why would your mother
make you sleep
under the porch?
She didn't.
You know, my mama,
she lives in
some city named Connecticut.
It's in New York,
I think.
But, you know,
she coming to get me
so I can live with her and my
new twin brothers.
See, my stepdaddy
played for the Seahawks,
some name like that.
You know, I got pictures of
him in a magazine he sent me.
Come on, I do,
Mrs. Inez.
You know, we got the same
last name and everything.
When the last time
you saw your mother?
You know, my sister said
she saw me when I was a baby.
Hmm...
What about your
father?
Man, he in the wind.
Half the time,
he think he a helicopter.
You know, he mostly leave
me and my sister
to get along
the best we can,
but it's like every day
she yelling about
sending me away somewhere.
My mama better hurry up
and come get me, I know that.
Did your mama tell you she
was gonna come and get you?
Not exactly, Mrs. Inez,
but you know a mother always
come back for her baby
sooner or later.
Yeah.
Mrs. Inez?
Yeah, baby?
Look, I don't care
what nobody say.
I don't never want
you to put me out of here.
You know, I can tell you
kind of care about me
like my mama would.
You know, real
tender-hearted like.
That's why I'm watching you
so I could learn to cook.
Maybe if I learn to cook,
it wouldn't matter that
I didn't read so good.
How well
do you read now?
Like in the first grade.
You know, kids always
laughing at me
for being
little and stupid.
Why I'm always fighting.
I mean, I can't help it
when I read,
my letters do jumping jack.
Boy, when the last time
you had your eyes examined?
Never.
'Cause you think in my eyes
they'll be able to tell me
why my brain's so bad?
Oh, stop talking
about yourself like that.
You are not dumb
and there's nothing wrong
with your brain.
Now go ahead and wash up
and we'll fix you something
real special to eat
and don't you tell nobody
'cause these folks around here
get very jealous
when they found out
I made someone my favorite.
*
(Ms. Whitmore)
How are they ever
gonna catch up?
They have...
no critical thinking,
no impulse control.
Everything is a joke
or a cause for a fight.
Their vocabulary is rudimentary
at best.
They have
no interest or respect
for anything
other than...
smoking weed...
waving their gang flags
or banging bitches.
You know, I'm drinking
right now,
so I'm probably not being
very PC at the moment,
but frankly...
they scare me.
You know...
I'm starting to believe
that black boys...
really are
innately more violent.
How are you
gonna learn anything
if you can't even control
yourself?
You learn that in
kindergarten, for Christ sakes.
My hero is my son, Deuce.
You're Daddy's hero,
little man.
(man laughing)
See, it was that
last rib.
That last rib,
I've got to tell you.
Hey.
How's my little man,
huh?
I thought
you went to work tonight.
They didn't need me.
Jake, this here
my oldest boy.
How you doing?
Don't he look
just like me?
'Cept he ain't as
friendly.
(laughing)
That's his baby boy,
Deuce.
Can you believe
I'm a grandma?
Working with all of this?
Girl, this beer running
straight through me.
Daddy gotta
relieve his self.
All right, big Daddy.
Bathroom's straight
back there.
Right back there?
Right back there, Daddy.
I'm gonna be with you
in a minute.
All right.
Go, make
yourself at home.
You coming?
Oh no.
(laughing)
We gonna go round for round,
round for round.
Don't you
keep me waiting!
(door closing)
Here, go to the store
and buy some milk,
cereal, eggs,
lunchmeat and bread.
That ought to hold us
for a minute.
I got fired tonight.
Patient
said I was stealing.
He crazy.
But that damn supervisor
believed him over me.
(Jake)
Billie!
Be there in a minute!
Hold on!
Mama, you know I been going
to that Hive school all week.
You have?
You like it?
Yeah, it's straight.
Long.
I don't get out of
there 'til 6:00!
Billie!
But they got computers there
and they're gonna teach me
how to take one apart.
You even earn points
for showing up.
See, look.
It's called an incentive.
They gonna take us
to some Bobcat games
if we earn enough points.
Take us on some
other trips, too.
They got you
reading this?
Billie!
Yeah, some slavery book
for social studies.
Billie, bring that
ass on in here, baby.
Be there in a minute,
Daddy.
Hold on now,
get ready for me now.
I know you ain't
judging me.
How else am I gonna
feed your asses, huh?
That's my slavery.
Billie!
Baby, please!
Baby, I'm coming, baby.
Come on, baby.
Hold on, big Daddy!
Ha-ha-ha!
Got my live-and-die-by rules,
but ain't never came up with
one that works for Mama.
Women, period.
That's why I don't
like to feel nothing.
Way too much work to
love somebody
and hate 'em
at the same time.
*
(giggling)
Extra points will be given for
the best invitation design.
Now you can go
online and get some ideas.
But I want the focus to be on
The Hive invitation dinner
for your families.
The dinner's gonna be here
at The Hive,
so to give you a chance
to show what you've learned
and also get you prepared
for the big school board banquet
in November
in which you will be
the student hosts and servers.
Mr. Hollis?
Yes.
I just wanna say, if you need
an emcee of ceremonies,
I'm your man.
Are you ready to
write a speech?
Already written.
Oscar, Grammy.
MTV, BET.
I'm ready to
orate on any day.
Anytime on your dime.
(all laughing)
Ladies and gentlemen,
holla back at Mr. Rack!
I'll keep you in mind,
Mr. Robinson.
(yawning)
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry but
it's after 4:00,
and my body says that school's
supposed to be over.
If you plan to
achieve grade level for all
your subjects,
Mr. Keys,
you will need to
fully participate in
the afterschool program.
I'm already at my
grade level, bitch.
(all)
Ooh...
Please refrain from using
profanity in my class,
because
I can assure you...
I am not your bitch.
(all)
Ooh...
And now since you've
disturbed everyone,
why don't you come up here and
read your grade level for us.
Wow.
Shh!
(clearing throat)
"Even as a..."
"you..."
Youth.
"Youth..."
"Tupac...
die..."
"Tupac discerned."
"discerned..."
"the price paid
for..."
"revo..."
Revolutionary.
"Revolutionary."
"And then
the people say
"I'm trying to make
a dollar out of
(school bell ringing)
15 cents."
Oh, look at my boys,
all working hard!
Well, if y'all hungry, I got
some collard greens heated
and some hot corn bread
and some fresh baked cookies,
so come on with me.
You can take
your break now.
*
Why you do that for?
You knew I wasn't
reading the right words.
Yes.
But I respected your
resourcefulness.
Why you lying?
Look, every boy at
The Hive looks up to you.
And one day,
I'm hoping that you will
channel
your considerable
gifts for their good
as well as your own.
You have chutzpah.
I'll give you that.
That ain't foreign for
calling me a "nigger"
on the sly, is it?
No.
Look it up.
C-H-U-T-Z-P-A-H.
It's a Yiddish word.
Describes you perfectly.
(Que)
Mrs. Inez,
I'm trying a diet,
so how many calories
you think be in
corn bread and greens?
Boy, I don't know.
But try eating
with your mouth closed
and take smaller portions.
Every time I see you going
through the line,
you heaping up
food on your plate
like you can eat three times
Mr. Hollis.
I heard that.
I'm cutting hair out back
for the next hour or so.
Some of you guys' naps
look like they need tending.
So if you're caught up
with your schoolwork,
meet me out back.
Oh, Lord.
That was yummy.
I've never had
stewed greens before.
Que?
Hi, could I see you
outside for a minute?
(boy 1) Mm-mm.
(boy 2) Uh-oh.
Oh, hush, y'all,
now go on, finish eating.
Stay out of other
folks' business.
Ahh!
What'd I tell you?
"I am...
"am a...
"multi...
"ti...
ti..."
The word is
"multitalented."
You plagiarized it.
I know you
didn't write it, Que,
and I do not tolerate
cheaters.
Do you understand?
I only did it because I don't
have that many points earned,
but I really
want to go on the trip.
Ms. Whitmore, I've never
been anywhere
except two miles
each way from here.
I don't want to go to
another foster home.
Please.
I'm asking you.
Don't tell on me.
Please.
(Xtra)
Chutz...
Chutz... chutz...
Chutzpah.
"Shameless...
audacity..."
Audacity?
Audacity.
"The willingness to take
bold risk."
Yeah, that's me.
Bold like a motherfucker.
(man)
I'll never disparage books,
but, y'know, I've had some of
my most meaningful connection
with the boys
on the basketball court.
I'm a teacher,
Aden, not a jock,
and basketball worship is
part of their problem.
Their only aspiration is
to be in the NBA or the NFL
and probably none of them
will make it.
*
You know, you the only one to
ever see what Daddy created.
Check it out.
You like it?
Now I'm gonna take it
and get it printed out
so your granddaddy
can see it.
(Deuce cooing)
Yeah.
(cell door rattling)
You ain't got no love
for your daddy?
You ain't seen
your daddy in two months
and you ain't got no love
for your daddy?
Come here, boy.
Boy... huh?
Your mama must get mad
every time she see you.
She carry you, I sure enough
spit you out, though, huh?
True that.
She says I'm you
inside out.
Yeah, yeah?
Yeah?
Yeah.
How come you
going soft?
I'm not.
Just been kind of
going to this new school.
I was gonna show
you this.
See, at the school
that I'm going to,
they're
teaching me technology,
and how to live in the world
like a man.
Mm-hmm.
Ain't no school
can do you that.
That's my job.
How's your leg?
It's okay.
Doctor said
I lucked out.
Just missed my artery.
Yeah?
Luck ain't got
nothing to do with it.
You got my blood running
all through you.
Bullet can't do
nothing but ricochet on you.
(laughing)
Keep on laughing through
this thing I'm gonna tell ya.
I'm gonna tell you a little
something-something,
all right?
I heard you
been messing up, huh?
You're not handling your
business out on the street.
You been breaking the rules
and shit, huh?
Maybe it's
this so-called school
that you've been going to,
huh?
Keep on smiling
through this thing.
Smile through it.
Yes.
That's it.
Now, what'd I tell you about
these peckerwoods out here,
white people?
Huh, playing puppet games
on your head, turn you soft.
The folks that are running
The Hive are black.
Oh, yeah.
Well, you know, niggas,
they good with delusion.
Huh?
Look at this.
See?
She drew that
for you.
You see that?
Look at that,
look at that.
Creek, pond,
they got a dead tree on it.
(laughing)
That's nice.
Uh-huh.
So when you take
the shovel out there, son,
stick it in, for yourself,
not for nobody else.
I need some
money up in here.
Anything else?
What, I thought you were
gonna show me something?
Nah.
It's nothing.
All right.
Careful, Mr. Hollis.
Messing with my
glad rags!
I worked hard
to look this good.
Boy, what kind of weed
are you smoking
where it makes you can
never shut your damn mouth?
That sheriff only needed half
an excuse to charge you
with possession.
The only reason he didn't
because you part of The Hive
and Mrs. Inez went to
bat for you.
What?
Possession, me?
I don't smoke
no marijuana.
But I do engage in
a little bit of commerce.
You like my compound word?
Get out of here.
*
Oh, man, Xtra.
This is good.
You know, you got a real
knack for design.
I took it
to show my father,
but...
he had other things
on his mind.
I guess
I should tell you now
I ain't coming back to
The Hive no more.
Why?
You've been
doing so well.
You cool people,
Mr. Hollis,
but where I come from,
stink still lives on shit.
Xtra, you know why
I like your name?
Because you got
a whole lot of extra.
Extra smarts, extra talent.
And extra capacity
to lead others.
It only takes one bright
light to lead out of darkness,
and that's what you can be
for the other boys.
And with you
and only you,
I definitely see college.
I took one of
the laptops.
Oh, I know.
I got eyes all over
The Hive.
You broke the honor code,
but I'm proud of you.
Not for the stealing part,
but because you told
the truth like a man.
I'll make you a deal.
You come in Monday early
with that computer,
and we'll consider
you had a special permission
for a weekend loan-out.
You gonna
use my design?
I doubt if one comes in
any better.
But you will also
write me a letter of apology
with a signed promise that you
won't steal from The Hive
ever again.
So don't let me down.
'Cause, boy, if you don't
show up with that computer,
I will hunt you down
and deliver you to
the jailhouse myself.
(crying)
Xtra, you okay?
Why don't you just stop
playing puppet with my head?!
I ain't never gonna
be nothing!
(frogs croaking)
*
(car approaching)
(police radio chatter)
(zipper unzipping)
*
(Rack)
Hey!
What you up to?
Life's been good.
And business
even better!
Got a little extra.
Hey, let's go
find us a party.
Nah, man.
I got something else
I gotta do.
What, man,
I gotta do my laundry.
So you're at
the gas station?
Come on, man.
You gotta think about what
Mr. Hollis call it.
You know,
the repercussions.
Shit, nigga, when you ever
start talking about
some repercussions?
Nigga, just now.
Here.
Here, take this.
Man, take it,
'cause I don't want you to
have to shoot me tonight.
Stop, I'm good, man.
You will, nigga,
'cause I ain't gonna
let you mess yourself up.
Shit, if I had half the brains
that you got,
I wouldn't be out here
selling this shit every night.
I'd be an astronaut,
or like that California doctor
Miss Christa
be telling us about.
You know, the one that
drill holes in your brain.
Yeah, Dr. Benjamin Carson.
He's a neurosurgeon, man.
See, that's what
I'm saying.
You don't forget shit.
I'm gonna keep it 100.
I ain't never
seen a nigga
that got a computer mind
like you do.
So you gonna have to
step over me tonight,
'cause I'm gonna be laid out
in that gas station doorway
if you insist on
doing your laundry.
Don't aim for
my face, though,
'cause I'm gonna need all
kinds of women
crying over my
casket, like, "Rack!"
Rack!"
(Gem)
Your new friend sure
got plenty of money.
We could have us
a car like that.
Maybe I need to go to
a Hive school for girls.
Why you looking at me
like that?
I used to be
good in school.
I'll try again if
you wanted me to.
If I wanted you to?
Damn, Gem.
You got a mind, why don't
you think for yourself?
Ever since you been
going to that school,
it's like I ain't
good enough.
You don't want me
no more, do you?
I'm letting you
live here, ain't I?
You?
Since when you
paying the rent?
(Rack)
Hey, I'm gonna take a little of
this pizza with me,
but I left most of
it in there for y'all.
I can order more for y'all
if y'all want before I go.
All right.
No.
*
Hey, I gotta
go chase that paper.
Hey, this was
a good time, man.
*
If we still alive,
see you at The Hive.
Rack!
Baby, come dance
with me.
Go ahead, man.
(Rack)
You know,
I really gotta go.
Come on, give me a quick
little two-step, come on.
Come on, you got...
(laughing)
That's why I hate the weekend.
No good ever comes to me
on the weekend.
I'm trying to remember
what Mr. Hollis said
about believing in me
and me going to
college
and what my dad said
about me playing the game,
and Mama, who I know
loves me,
but...
She got a whole
lotta "but" s.
And Rack with his crazy ass
talking about repercussions
and Gem...
needing everything
I can't give her.
During the week
at The Hive, life has order.
It makes sense.
(cupboard creaking)
On the weekends,
nothing ever does.
*
(zipper unzipping)
(bell ringing)
Sounds like somebody's
pies are ready.
In Jesus' name!
Amen.
Boy.
Oh, my goodness.
Mm-hmm.
Your release hand
is bad.
Use your other
hand as your guide hand.
Okay.
Whoop.
That's why you're
the teacher.
Ms. Whitmore,
can I ask you a question?
How come you changed
how you looked to
look like
everybody else?
I mean, I liked the way
you were different
and unique in yourself.
I didn't copy that.
And I worked on it
all weekend.
(Que)
My grandfather
always telling me
to trust my gut...
but he don't know my gut
sometimes lies.
Like a double-headed snake.
Even though I ain't never seen
one of them.
I want to be good
and not lie or cheat
or do any of
the bad things I do,
'cause I like The Hive.
And the teachers
who teach me to think
and talk like people on TV
and Mrs. Inez
and Mr. Hollis,
they like a mama
and a daddy
to us who ain't got that.
See...
I ain't never been able to
hold on to no family.
They always
leaving me behind.
But, Ms. Whitmore,
please don't let it
happen to me again.
I need you to teach me
how to express myself better
so people don't always
leave me behind.
I know you somebody
I can learn from
'cause you're unique
and different in
yourself.
P.S.
This took me 11 hours
and 37 minutes to write...
and then check all
the spelling.
The end.
Que.
Man, what you
looking at?
Can you... help me
with my homework?
Kids at school,
they laugh at
how I read
and... I want
to quit school.
Listen, first off, you don't
ever quit something
because of somebody else.
You hear me?
It takes chutzpah
to keep going at something
when it's easier
to quit.
Yeah, look it up.
Here.
Here's a dictionary.
Now, go get
your books.
You read, I'll listen.
Now hurry up, come on,
'cause we gotta get to school.
(Mr. Hollis)
All right.
Good morning.
I got some more awards points
to give out.
I'd like to tell you
we've reached the halfway
semester point
and we've almost earned our
overnight stay to Charlotte
to see the Bobcats.
All right, all right.
Okay, okay.
For perfect attendance...
Courvoisier Carter,
50 points.
(boy)
That's right,
little bro.
Congratulations,
Mr. Carter.
(all clapping)
All right,
just two more.
For always being meticulously
pressed and dressed.
(all)
Rack Robinson!
Congratulations,
Mr. Robinson.
Thank you, Mr. Hollis.
Yeah.
And our last award goes to
someone who has
demonstrated
not only competence
in math and technology,
but has also exceeded his own
personal goals.
Xtra Keys, 100 points.
(applauding)
Good job, Mr. Keys.
*
You the man, Xtra Keys!
(Mr. Hollis)
All right, settle down.
I was watching
a weekend special,
talking about the state of
African-American boys.
Talk about depressing.
That's why I don't
watch the news.
(all laughing)
I don't need nobody
broadcasting
how messed up
my life is.
Like I don't know.
Come on, man.
What was alarming was them
saying that white boys
your same age are twice as
likely to graduate than you.
So you know what
that means.
What it means is,
Mr. Hollis,
it means we don't count.
(all laughing)
Gentlemen!
Teachers, will you
excuse us, please?
We're about to have a special
Wise Guy.
All right.
Half of you over here
and half right here, come on.
Move.
Okay now,
where I put these chairs,
we're gonna call it, to use
Courvoisier's words,
"The No-count Corner."
So this half of the room,
the laughing 50% of you
that won't graduate school,
get to stepping to
"The No-count Corner."
Come on, dropouts, step in
the corner where you belong.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, move,
y'all moving too slow.
Move!
Get in there, get in there.
Not so funny now,
is it?
Don't you
dare move an inch.
Don't sit.
Don't lean.
Don't move a chair.
You made the choice,
so stand there and represent.
Come on, no-counts!
And get used to
that label,
'cause somebody's
gonna be calling you that
and telling you what to do for
the rest of your lives!
Hey, Mr. Hollis,
there ain't enough room!
And what do you want me to
do about that?!
You made that choice,
so stand there
and deal with it!
Okay, those of you who
are left standing,
5% are gonna go to college.
There's only
ten of us left.
That's a half a person
unless you base it on
the percentage
of everybody in here.
You come over here.
Since you so smart,
you stand right there
as our one and only
college-bound.
Okay, now those
of you still standing,
half of y'all going to prison,
so you five, get to
stepping to the no-count corner
and assume the position.
That's right, raise your hands
in the air
'cause you about to
spend the rest of your life
being friends.
Get to the corner,
come on, all y'all.
I said, crowd in the corner,
gentlemen!
'Cause that's what
it's gonna be like in prison.
Overcrowded.
And that's what your families
are gonna feel,
'cause they couldn't count on
you to do something different,
to be something other than
a statistic.
Now don't you
dare move an inch!
And if you feel like fighting,
you're gonna have to
fight me first
and I mean that.
Okay.
So there's four of you left and
our one college man over there.
Since you two will likely
kill the other two
or die by some violence,
let's just do this as random
as your choices.
All four of you join
your comrades in the corner.
Come on, go.
You want me
to play "D"?
Okay.
So how does it feel to be
the only one
destined to make it?
I don't know
how I feel.
'Cause I don't
feel for nobody.
I just know it ain't fair
for me to be over here
and for all of them to be
over there in the corner.
I mean, part of
me wants to make it,
the other part wants to
be over there
with who I know
and what I know.
Really?
How many of you want to
take Xtra's place?
You just a lot.
Put your
damn hands down!
'Cause even if given
the opportunity,
you gonna crawl right
back to what you know!
To what feels familiar,
and that's being
a bottom-feeder!
Laughing at yourselves,
perpetrating you
in charge of something
and you ain't in charge
of one damn thing.
Not even yourself!
Anybody still laughing?
(all)
No sir.
I can't hear you!
(all)
No sir!
All right, now take your
behinds back to your seats.
You definitely don't give a damn
about your past, gentlemen.
It only cares about the choices
you are making right now,
all of which
add up to your future.
Now let's see if we can't get
this day started correctly.
It didn't get wrong overnight
and you certainly ain't
gonna get it right overnight.
So let's start the day
over with a purpose.
I believe in myself and my
ability to do my best.
(all)
I believe in myself
and my ability to do my best.
Louder!
(all)
I believe in myself and my
ability to do my best!
Louder!
(all)
I believe in myself and my
ability to do my best!
(clearing throat)
I wasn't trying to
scare you,
I just wanted to
know if you had any books
for really little kids?
But it's okay, I can just
go ask Ms. Christa.
No!
Come in.
I'm in school almost
nine hours a day.
And it's paying off.
Your reading has
vastly improved.
You're almost at
an eighth-grade level.
First I was just trying to
read to my son,
but now
I got this brother...
He's struggling, too.
He's kind of
nervous-like.
Cries all the time.
I don't really
want him to know that
I can't read that good.
Okay, wait here.
I got something
in the car.
*
Only way to
get better at reading
is to read all the time,
all kinds of books,
not just the ones
assigned here at The Hive.
When do I have to
give them back?
You don't.
Not for a while,
anyway.
I bought them
with my own money.
You're the first boy...
Young man...
who might
really read them.
Why you doing all
this for me?
I thought
you hated me.
I never hated you.
Don't take this
the wrong way.
I kind of like the way that
you got your hair right now,
all crazy-like.
You look fresh.
Uh... so,
speaking of fresh,
I have a proposition
for you.
What would you think about
starting a school newspaper?
It would help you boys
with reading and writing
as well as show the community
how we do it at The Hive.
Okay.
Yeah.
Call it "The Buzz."
Excuse me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
only one "horse" d'oeurve
a piece, fellas.
You ain't
gotta be so greedy.
Excuse me, you all have
as many as you want.
Courvoisier...
the food is here
for them.
It's not just
to sit and look pretty.
And the word is
"hors d'oeuvres."
There's no "horse" in it.
Mrs. Inez, my sister
ain't coming.
I don't
think she coming.
You think she coming?
*
Aw, shit.
Excuse...
Shoot.
I forgot something in
the kitchen, I'm...
Boy, you better go
and greet your father.
Do you know how
many boys here
wish that their
father had shown up?
Now, he may look
a little torn up,
but he is still
your father.
Take him to that closet
and get him some clothes,
a clean shirt,
but first, you're gonna
go over there
and tell him how
happy you are he came.
I said go.
Use your feet to
pray the way.
Yo, Pops.
Pops.
*
When you get glasses?
Mrs. Inez took me to
the eye doctor.
Sorry I ain't get
all dressed up for you.
I hope I didn't
embarrass you, man.
I'll wait for you
outside.
No, no.
No, I'm glad you came.
You too, Tina.
Come on.
I got something
I want to show you.
(Rack)
Looks like you and me the only
ones that ain't got nobody.
Yeah, my mama's supposed
to be coming.
Hey, how you doing?
All right, thank you.
Welcome, welcome.
Gem, too.
Her ass better
be bringing my son.
They probably waiting
on a ride, though.
Don't think
I'm hanging around.
Why?
You supposed to be
giving the opening speech.
For who?
You don't see nobody
wearing my nametag.
My mama, she want to come,
but, you know, she thick.
(laughing)
And she worried about
everybody laughing at her.
I'm sorry.
All she do is sit around
all day watching stories
pretending she in one.
How you doing?
(woman)
Hi, good.
How are you guys?
All right.
Come on, Rack, man,
that's your mama, man.
I know, and for real.
I love every ounce of her
400 pounds,
but...
sometimes I just wish she'd
get up and do something
instead of expecting
me to do everything.
At some point, you gotta get
over what some man did to you
and get on with it.
Man, sometimes I gotta even
help her wash her own butt.
You know that ain't right.
How you doing?
Welcome, welcome.
Thank you.
Have a good time.
There they are.
You lucky, X.
You have a mom that takes
such good care of herself.
Hey.
How you doing,
what's up?
Hey, son.
I told you
I was coming.
What?
(cheers and applause)
Remember, here at The Hive,
we just don't
measure test scores.
The true measure of a man,
we believe,
is in the total
of his character.
Where's my mama at?
She left.
What you mean
she left?
Where'd she go?
Who knows?
She got in the car
with your boy Rack.
Mr. Xtra Keys.
X, get up there,
everyone's waiting.
Good evening.
Mrs. Inez is always saying
that there's always
a savior in every group.
You just have to know
which one is meant for you
or meant for somebody else.
Or not meant
at all.
See, we got real
saviors here at The Hive.
Mrs. Inez.
Mr. Hollis.
And our teachers.
And we have
each other.
But most important...
we have you guys,
our families.
Thank you.
(door opening)
What you doing
sitting here in the dark?
Waiting for somebody
to come home.
It's just me and Deuce.
Shay ain't here yet.
X, where'd
you get a gun?
Can I hold it?
Hey!
Don't you ever ask nobody
to see no gun!
Do you hear me?!
Do you understand me?!
Don't you start
that crying.
I ain't crying, X,
I ain't.
*
Oh, shit.
Look who it is.
Where the fuck you
been hiding, nigga?
I been here, there,
you know.
You been here?
No, the truth is,
you been everywhere
but where you need.
Just say the word, X.
I can keep you busy.
Yeah, I know you can.
You know,
I promised your daddy
I'd look out
for you.
I kind of owe him.
See, X...
one hand
washes the other,
but don't nobody tell
the left
what the right is doing,
but then again,
some of us...
don't always know
which is our left
and which is always
right.
You understand me?
Yeah, I got you.
Look, man, I'm just looking
for Gem, man.
Oh, Gem.
Man, you better
take care of your woman.
'Cause these bitches
will stray on you.
You feel me?
Man, go home.
These streets ain't
for you tonight, playa.
Hey, yo, X!
One more thing.
You better
check your sister.
She out here trying to
get loose
a little too soon.
You feel me?
Bad night?
You want some cereal?
X, Mama come home yet?
Boy, why are you
talking so loud?
That's your bowl of cereal
right there.
You made me cereal.
Shay, come on,
so we can eat!
Goddamn, X!
Why you gotta
be so loud?
Go wash that
shit off your face.
And change your
clothes, too.
Tony, take Deuce
in the back for me.
Listen, I'm trying not
to hit you,
but you're moving
a little too fast.
And just because your mama
hangs out all night
doesn't mean
you supposed to.
It wasn't all night.
I was home by 2:00.
Yeah, that's five hours
too late.
What?
You playing daddy now?
You trying to play
ho now?
Who you calling a ho?
Look, I need you to
stay on track, Shay!
I don't need you out there
trying to hang,
bang, or none
of that shit!
You leave that for them girls
who wanna play skank.
Yeah, 'cause he talking
about skanks like me.
You so full of shit, X.
I liked you
a lot better before
you started going to that
punk-ass school,
perpetrating
like you something.
Like you some Obama
and shit?
Doing damn
speeches and shit?
Well, you ain't
no Obama.
You ain't shit.
You know, you lucky
I'm going that school.
They teach me how to
control my temper.
Otherwise I'd be choking the
shit out your ass right now.
Yeah.
I'm really
proud of 'em.
Mmm...
Now next is the banquet
and then I have to deal
with those
school board members.
Oh, don't worry about them,
they'll be all right.
But you know who
I am worried about, though?
Rack and Xtra.
You know, something just
ain't right with them.
Good morning.
Oh, I am so jazzed
about last night.
Honestly, wasn't it, like,
every shade of wonderful?
Oh.
Hey, I'm not sure
if I mentioned it before,
but some of the boys are
wanting to help me start
a Hive newsletter.
They would write the articles,
take the pictures.
Xtra's agreed to
design the layout
and Que's going to be
my assistant editor.
Aden and Christa
would help the boys
fashion articles from their
respective disciplines.
You know, maybe
a monthly math problem
to solve or a social studies
winning essay.
What do you think?
You think
it'll work?
Great, 'cause we've
already started.
I am so jazzed.
Okay, have
a blessed day.
Okay.
Bye.
Hollis, have I ever
told you
how much
I love The Hive?
I mean, every day,
a new adventure.
Ain't that the truth.
(car approaching)
Ooh...
(giggling)
(Xtra)
Where you been
for two days?
You been
waiting up for your mama?
Again?
Thank you.
Lord.
Sorry I had to cut out early
on your little shindig, X.
It was nice, though.
What I saw of it.
Seem like they teaching
y'all a lot over there.
So what kind of things
Rack been teaching you?
Who?
Rack.
My friend Rack.
Mama, please
don't do this.
He's my age and I gotta see
him every day at The Hive.
He ain't nothing
but a two-bit hustler.
Why don't you just
let him be?
You don't
run my life.
I'm the mama.
And if I want to
see him,
or anybody else,
ain't nothing
you can do about it!
You understand that?!
Ain't shit
you can do about it,
you understand what
I'm saying?!
Dammit!
(Shay)
It looks a little better,
but it's gonna take more than
just two days to heal.
It'll be all right.
Maybe if she hadn't
lost her job.
I thought Mama liked
working at the nursing home.
Mama always like something
in the beginning.
Pretty sure she
used to even like us.
When?
I must have
missed that.
I can't believe Mama left
out of here last night
after she did
this and got arrested.
I want a mama, X.
Somebody I can
count on
instead of somebody trying
to act like she my age.
I hate her.
No, you don't.
It's embarrassing.
How many times you gonna go
to jail for something stupid
following behind some man
or in this case,
some boy?
As soon as anybody find out,
we gonna get evicted again,
they gonna split us up,
put us in some foster home.
You and me,
we'll be all right.
Tony, you know he
can't survive.
He won't have to.
I promise.
Your promises
aren't worth shit.
She wouldn't be sitting
in jail
if it hadn't
have been for you,
that damn school and your
little friend.
Can't your
father do something?
Call in a favor to get
the money to get Mama out
or maybe I could talk to Shoot,
somebody told me...
You stay your fast ass
away from him!
You hear me?!
Or you'll end up
right where your mama is.
That's if I don't kill
your ass first.
In the meantime,
what am I supposed to do?
Look, you got a sister,
don't you?
You got a brother.
Billie had two kids with
some other fool, right?
So you get your family
in business.
You get that boy,
you get that...
You get
that little girl
and you get...
What do you call it, huh?
A website.
Get you a little sexy
website going on
with these
kids, get paid.
That's my brother
and my sister.
I can't even believe that
you would even say that.
I can't believe that
I have a son that I raised
who don't know how to
get paid.
You see,
that's the thing.
You didn't raise me.
I can remember
every beating.
The ones you gave mama
and the ones
you gave me.
Throwing us
into walls and shit?
I guess I didn't throw you
hard enough, did I?
I really
wanted to love you.
You know I still have
very long reach.
So?!
You brought me in
this fucked-up world,
it might as well be you
to take me out!
They turned it
off today.
Electricity's next.
You go by
the jail yesterday?
Gem, this ain't
easy for me to say,
but...
I need you to stay
here with me.
For what, X?
To wrap my legs around you
whenever you need to
relieve yourself?
That ain't love.
Love would be me
trying to wrap
my heart around you,
but that ain't never
gonna happen.
You don't
even give a shit.
Those are our pots,
you stupid ass bitch!
You know,
living with you, X,
has been worse than
living at home.
At least at home,
I knew nobody loved me
and I didn't care.
But here...
you made me care, X.
I ain't never forgiving
you for that shit.
Gem.
I'm trying to change.
I'm not.
I don't want
to stay at home,
watch you do homework,
playing patty-cake.
You don't like
the streets no more?
Well, I still do.
It's in my blood,
6-8 'til I die.
You think 'cause
your mama's in jail
so now you expect me
to play mama
to everybody
up in this piece?
You better call
dial-a-mama,
'cause that
ain't me, X.
You got somebody else?
What does it matter?
Bottom line, I stay here,
we kill each other.
What about my son?
Our son.
You're not taking him
away from me, Gem.
I'll beat
the shit out of you.
Shit, do it, then, X.
Beat the shit out of me
and get it over with,
'cause I'm still leaving,
now or when
you asleep,
but I'd rather do it now
before I have to
play out this scene again
in front of Tony and Shay.
Please.
Don't take him
away from me, Gem.
You can't go to school
and take care of him, too, X.
I'll quit school.
Don't do that.
I see how
it's changed you.
And I hate it.
Maybe Deuce needs
at least one parent
to be an example for
him one day.
Come back and get him
when I get straight.
*
I think we should print
a couple of hundred more,
though.
My roadie
brothers can hand them out.
It'll do wonders for
our PR.
You really think
it's that good?
Are you fishing for a
compliment? (Courvoisier)
Mr. Hollis!
Mr. Hollis, Mrs. Inez
needs you right now!
Now what's wrong?
Everybody come
right now!
*
(all)
Happy birthday!
(Mrs. Inez)
Surprise!
(laughing)
*
Make a wish.
Come on,
make a wish!
(yelling)
I got you!
(panting)
Oh, my goodness,
you okay?
Oh, the last
time I tackled you,
you wasn't too happy
about it, was you?
No.
Ooh... ooh...
So... here's how
it's gonna go.
I want you, Shay,
Tony and little Deuce
to come on and stay
with me and my husband
for a few days
'til we can figure out how
to get your mama out of jail.
I don't know, Mrs. Inez.
I mean, I need to be back
at that trailer.
Oh now.
You can go by that trailer
every day if you want,
do check on it.
I'll come up with a plan
to get your mama out of
jail sooner than later.
This is how it's gonna go.
You gonna go home,
pack up some
of your brother's
and sister's things
just for a few days
and then I'm gonna
come over
and pick you up
this evening, all right?
It's a deal?
Thank you.
Oh.
X, the door's open,
somebody broke in.
*
Y'all stay here.
Let me go in
with you.
I said stay here.
(gun cocking)
(grunting)
Tony.
That gun is loaded.
I want you...
to slowly...
put it down.
Boy, didn't I tell you never
to touch one of these?
Never!
Man, you could've...
You know what, I'm taking these
out of here tonight.
I should have done
that in the first place.
What were you thinking?!
(car approaching)
*
That sounds like Rack.
(car doors closing)
X, are they the ones
that broke in?
Your brother in there?
Yeah, he in there.
His daddy want us to come
have a little talk with him.
You know.
Look at this
little dude, huh?
Give 'em to me.
Come on, come on
to papa, baby.
Yeah, give him to me.
Yeah, look at you,
boy, how you doing?
Yeah.
Little boy, huh?
You're big, hey.
Lookee here.
There's your daddy.
Give me my son.
We all 6-8 family
out here.
You know that, X.
The 6-8 don't tolerate
no disrespect, do we?
Yeah, I know.
True that.
So when we got a message
from 1-1-9
saying that you had been
a little disrespectful...
we thought we'd come
have a little talk with you.
I said give me my son!
*
Come on, Shoot.
You already know I'm gonna
be 6-8 'til I die.
I delivered your message.
Now here's mine.
I ain't
scared of dying.
What I am scared of
is dying on him,
'cause he don't
deserve that.
There's rules
to this shit, X.
You ought to
know that.
Yeah, I hear you.
Now I'm just trying to make
a few new ones for myself.
So if you
gonna shoot me...
you gonna have to do
it through my back,
'cause I'm out.
(Xtra)
As I said...
I always live by a few
simple rules,
but I've learned
a real man realizes
his rules have to work
not just for him...
but for all the people
who count on him.
All you gotta do
is stay alive...
just one more day.
*