Remember, in times of trouble,
let your conscience be your guide.
Here goes.
I never knew you were one
to jump to conclusions.
You can't get rid of me that easily.
I'll be back. You'll see!
Okay, kids. This is it.
- Well, that wasn't too bad.
- Oh, speak for yourself.
I personally was never cut out
to be a contortionist.
- A contortionist, what's that?
- It's a political party.
But don't worry, the Republicans
are still way ahead.
Well, actually, it means
a person's ability
to twist their body into
strange and unusual positions.
Well, that certainly sounds
like Roxanne to me.
- Really?
- Oh, dream on.
Hey, let's get this stuff out.
I feel like I'm on display here
in the middle of the street.
Let's do it.
Now, you girls understand the deal, right?
I drop you off,
you clean up the house
real good for the new owners,
I pick you up Monday morning,
and you each get 100 bucks.
My mouth's watering
just thinking about it.
A lousy 100 bucks.
You'd think there'd be an easier way
to earn some spending cash.
There is, but you'd have to
beat around the bush to get it.
And how!
- What did she mean by that?
- Just keep pulling out the stuff, Megan.
Hey, just sign this, saying you
understand the game.
And I can get
the hell outta here.
I hope someone has
the keys to this palace.
Don't worry.
As your team leader,
I've got everything we need
to get through the weekend.
Did you bring any men?
Oh, I see you're hiding them
under your shirt.
- Sign up, Roxanne.
- Oh.
Too bad, it's a couple of midgets.
Yeah, well, listen... In case
you didn't hear it down at the office,
there's no hanky panky
going on here.
You leave your boyfriends
down at the football field
or wherever the hell
you found them.
- Power even turned on?
- Well, the electricity is.
The phone's out until
the new owners move in.
Well, what if there's
an emergency or something?
Oh, I think we're suppose to go
running down the street screaming, right?
No. There's a neigbor,
Mr. Hinchlow.
He's got a phone.
I spoke to him earlier in the day.
He's gonna drop by later
and introduce himself.
- Great, we can call out for pizza.
- Yeah, but remember, no monkey business.
- I got a reputation to think of.
- He's got his reputation to live down.
- Sleaze ball.
- Aw, I think he's kind of cute.
Well, in a weird, sort of
twisted way, of course.
Very twisted.
Let's get going, guys.
Guys. Hold on.
Oh, look. Hell House.
Looks like our
sorority house to me.
It displays a certain charm.
Not altogether unpleasant.
Maybe you can assume the mortgage
after the new owners disappear.
- Put this down.
- All right.
What was that stuff you were saying
about the new owners disappearing?
Well, this house has a long history
of mayhem and madness.
Pretty strange and unusual
and weird things have happened here.
- Such as?
- Well...
It was the Mortimer family,
the last ones to live here
They simply vanished one night
after about a month of moving in.
- What happened to them?
- Nobody really knows.
But it's assumed they took off
in the middle of the night,
so freaked out,
they left everything behind.
- Everything?
- Even their CD player.
No shit?
Let's get this junk in the kitchen
and see if the fridge is in working order.
Meg, go get the bags
from the street.
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Saw the van.
Figured it was you.
Thoght I'd stop by,
let you know I was here.
- Are you Mr...
- Hinchlow.
Yes, I have the house
down the block here.
I'm Megan.
I'm just here for the weekend.
Ah, short stay, huh?
Good thing.
Um, would you like
to meet the other girls?
Oh, I'd be delighted.
You know, I remember this house
when it was only about that tall.
Oh, heh. No kidding?
I don't know about you guys,
but this place doesn't look so messy.
You know, it should be a cinch
if we all pitch in and get to it.
- Fridge is in working order.
- Great. Here, put this stuff in there.
- Ham.
- Yeah.
- Cheese, cool.
- Mm.
Beers.
- And butter?
- Don't ask.
- Look who I found outside.
- Mr. Hinchlow?
Yeah.
You the guy with the phone?
- That's right.
- Well, I'm Terry. Hi.
I represent
the Wheatley Cleaning Company.
And this is Roxanne
and Jan, and...
- I guess you already know Megan.
- I had the pleasure, yeah.
There something we can do
for you, Mr. Hinchlow?
No. No, no, I just, uh...
Came in to have a look at your faces.
In case I have to
identify you later on.
- Identify us?
- Your bodies, I mean, for the cops.
- Um, if there's a need, you know?
- I'm afraid we don't know.
Well, there's been several murders
in this neighborhood.
I... I wouldn't want anything
to happen to you girls, of course.
Of course.
Well, we really appreciate
your concern, Mr. Hinchlow.
And now, if you're done memorizing us,
we've got a lot of work to do.
Of course. Uh, yes. Uh, well, if you
need anything I'm just down the block.
It's the brown house
that's slightly green with mold.
Just holler if you need anything.
Thanks.
We'll remember that.
- So now what?
- Well, I say we start in the basement.
- Why the basement?
- 'Cause it's dark and creepy.
And probably the last place
you wanna be after sundown.
You got it.
- Come on.
- Let's do it.
Why do these things
always have to start
with young, beautiful coeds
going into the basement?
This must be where
all the missing bodies are buried.
Don't worry.
We're not doing any digging.
- It's not in our job description.
- Come on.
Come on, scaredy-cat.
Get in there.
I just wanna be
the last one to get it.
Oh, come on.
Well, what are you chickens waiting for?
Let's get the light turned on.
You do it. We're not budging.
It's dark in here.
Geez, it's just a basement.
Maybe to you, but I say
it's the guts of Hell House.
Is this the part where we
find the secret Ouija board
and all become
possessed by demons?
No, I think this is the part
where we get just plain bored,
and get possessed by
the spirit of Mr. Clean.
Look, guys...
No bodies, no monsters.
Just an old storage space
that smells like a locker room.
- It's even too ugly to mop.
- So, what do we do with it?
Well, I say we just straighten up.
Now why don't you guys
stack up some of the boxes,
and we'll move things around.
It'll start looking better,
and we can call it a day.
Terry's right.
Let's do it.
- Hey, check this out.
- What?
What's the big deal?
There's a lot of trunks down here.
Yeah, but dig this tag.
I've seen a lot of odd languages,
but never one like this before.
I wonder what it says.
Probably some kind of travel tag
from an exotic location.
Yeah, in hell.
Come on, cut the ghost stories
and help me get it open.
Oh, stink-o!
Smells like something died.
Look here.
- Great. Where's the rest of him?
- There's more.
- Well, that--
- Fuck!
That just about completes our tour
of Dr. Satan's neighborhood.
Tune in next week,
when we hear Roxanne say:
Let's get the hell out of here.
- Yeah, we can finish tomorrow.
- I need some air.
Well, I'm gonna take
some of these things with me.
- Why?
- They may be important.
Well, you remember
what that Hinchlow said.
- About bodies?
- Yeah. There may be clues.
What you're really trying to say,
is they may be antiques.
Valuable ones, that nobody but us
knows about or will miss.
Well, maybe.
But listen...
If they are valuables,
we'll split whatever we have, okay?
- Deal?
- Deal.
- Come on, let's get.
- Let's do it.
This place doesn't induce
much of an appetite in me.
Well, it isn't exactly Mama San's
brand of bologna
but it'll do if you're
as hungry as I am.
Great. A thunder storm.
How come every time
we stay at an old, spooky house
it has lightning and thunder?
Well, I think it's standard issue.
- Let's go join the others.
- Okay.
How can you read that stuff
on a night like this?
In a house like this?
"And then Reginald,
with an insane look,
grabbed the long, twisted
blade of the Demon Sword,
and plunged it deep into the exposed
breast of young, nubile Catherine."
Are you okay?
Just some sandwich
stuck in my throat.
Have you guys seen Rox?
Wanna see how I got my hooks
in to Biff Bullock, the football captain?
Again?
I do!
Okay! Here's how it starts.
Ready?
- Wow, that was interesting.
- Gets them every time.
Here. Come on.
I'll show you how.
- No, I couldn't. I--
- Come on.
Come on, it's easy.
Come on.
- Stop!
- Come on!
Come on.
Hey, girl. Hold on.
Stop it.
- Check her out.
- Oh, not too bad.
My, my. Where have you
been hinding that?
We've got some
stiff competition here, girls.
Remind me to show you
how to use it sometime.
Who could that be?
It's probably Hinchlow
looking for a good time.
- We shouldn't answer it.
- Please, it's just a doorbell.
Can I help you?
Is there anything
we can do for you?
Delivery.
We don't live here.
And the new owners
won't be around until Monday.
Maybe you should
come back then.
Delivery.
Uh, sure.
Do I need to sign anything?
Um, let's close the door.
- I wonder what it is.
- A box of candy?
Look, it says: "Open immediately."
Let's see what's inside.
No. It doesn't belong to us.
Well...
Maybe it's perishable.
And if we don't,
we might get in more trouble.
- There's a point.
- Well...
Okay, but if it's not,
we wrap it right back.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's open it.
Ooh, yuck.
What a hideous thing.
What is it?
A book or something?
It's the Transylvania
yellow pages, ooh.
- Should we look inside?
- We've gone this far.
- Ew! I don't really like touching this.
- It looks like somebody's face.
- Probably human skin.
- Probably worth a fortune.
Hey, do any of you guys
read foreign languages?
Jan, you do, don't you?
I know how to say
"how much?" in Spanish.
I can answer that in five languages.
But that's all.
I'll bet little miss egghead upstairs
knows how to read this.
Roxanne, why don't you
go up and find out?
Okay.
That is gross.
It is.
Now that's gross.
It's only a picture, but it looks like
some ancient sorcerer's wet dream.
Yuck.
- Ready to rejoin the troops?
- I guess so.
- A little embarrassed?
- No, I...
- A little.
- Well, don't be.
I mean, you've got a great body.
You just need to get some use out of it.
What a night.
Yeah, but right now,
Terry wants you downstairs.
Some creepy old man delivered
a book with a face on it.
And she thought maybe
you could read some of it
and tell us what it's all about.
- Really?
- Yeah, so...
I could try.
Get a load of that drawing.
- Ew, it looks like they're--
- Doing it!
Gross!
Look where that thing's
tongue is going.
Makes me squirm in my seat
just thinking about it.
Well, don't show it to Roxanne,
or she might wanna try it.
- Where's that strange book?
- It's right here.
- That guy's tongue is--
- Yeah, yeah, we saw it. So can you read it?
Well, it looks like ancient Latin.
Great, the one class
I skipped regularly.
Ooh, a handsome fellow.
Yeah, we know, but
can you make out anything?
Well, it's kinda rough,
but I'll give it a try.
"Demons of the mind,
hear this summons."
"Give of our energy
to that of the unliving."
"For that which lives not,
may never die."
Does it get any better?
"We, your devotet slaves,
give of our bodies,
that thou may live
but a life unto death."
"We beg of you,
answer our pleas."
- Okay, so are there any jokes in there?
- It gets pretty rocky after that.
What do you mean, rocky?
Are you the Latin wiz
of this katonic ewe or what?
Well, ancient demon incantations
aren't covered until next semester.
Rats!
Oh, wait a minute, here's a footnote.
I think I can read this.
"In the name of God,
if you value your immortal Soul,
never ever, ever, ever
read the above incantation aloud."
"And I mean, don't. Never."
Well, that was fun.
- Any dirty pictures in here?
- Tons. But I'm turnin' in, not turnin' on.
Yeah, me too. And if you guys
had any sense, you would, too.
- I'm ready.
- Not me.
- I'm expecting some company.
- Company?
Yeah. Biff Bullock said that he
might drop by around midnight.
You remember what Burt Wentworth
said about no monkey business?
Sure, but Biff's not a monkey, and
he'll only be here for, like, an hour or so.
Who's gonna know?
If it's Biff, it'll only be five minutes,
and the whole school's gonna know.
- And Rox?
- Yeah?
- He does look like a monkey.
- Oh, you're just jealous.
Listen, don't screw up this gig, okay?
Or we might get in some big trouble.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Night.
- See ya.
- Later, kid.
- Night.
Wow... how does he
get his tongue in there?
This place sure spooks me.
Well, if you hear a scream
in the middle of the night,
it'll probably be Roxanne
losing her virginity for the fifth time.
I wish I had her
sense of adventure.
Just be glad you don't have
her sense of propriety.
But it must be so exciting to trice
for so many strong, muscular men.
"Trice?" Listen, Meg, the next time
you wanna know what it's like,
just do that little dance
Roxanne showed you.
I'm sure that'll at least
cover the foreplay.
- Was I good?
- Oh, honey, you were great.
Why, you just reeked of sex.
Okay, everyone, let's get some sleep
before the carnal olympics start downstairs.
Okay.
Got you now, Biff.
Oh, God.
Cool.
Okay.
My, my, my.
- Nice ass.
- Biff, is that you?
Come on out.
I recognize your voice.
Yoo-hoo!
Time for din din.
Hello, baby.
Nice tits!
Listen.
Yup, that's number five.
- You mean...?
- Well, they're not playing Twister.
Maybe they are.
Oh, boy.
- It stopped.
- What did I tell you. That Biff?
I didn't even hear the whistle
for the two minute warning.
Good boy. Well, they always said
he was the fastest guy on the team.
Now maybe we can
get some shut-eye.
That did not sound like the extatic
coupling of young lovers to me.
Maybe she's in trouble.
Why don't you check in on them?
I'm sure they'd appreciate it.
Well, maybe just a peek.
- To be sure?
- Help yourself.
- And Meg?
- Yeah?
Be sure to tell us where his tongue is.
I'm dying to know.
She's such a drag.
Roxanne? Biff?
Hello?
Rox, you scared me to death!
Hello, Meg.
- Can I help you?
- What are you doing?
We heard screams, and now you're here,
naked and covered in blood.
Are you okay?
I cut myself opening a bottle of wine.
It ruined my nightgown.
- I was just changing.
- What about the screams?
So I got a little carried away.
Why don't you go back to bed?
I'm all right, and
Biff will be here soon.
We wouldn't want to
spoil the moment now, would we?
No, of course not.
I was just worried about you.
- Megan, you're so sweet.
- Uh... well, goodnight.
Later.
What's gotten into you?
Yeah, did you penalize him
five yards for illegal use of hands,
or was it backfield in motion?
Biff's not here yet.
Well...!
I know what it is. Roxanne was
practicing for the big moment.
She was standing there like
some kind of robot or something.
- Naked and covered with blood.
- Are you kidding?
She said she cut herself
and ruined her nightie, but...
I didn't see any cuts.
- Well, is she all right?
- She said she was, but...
- But what?
- Well, I don't know.
She was just really strange, weird.
It was really creepy.
Forget it, babe.
This whole place is creepy.
Just try to get some sleep
if you can.
Alive.
Alive again!
Hiya, baby.
- You miss me?
- Like the plague.
Neat place.
- You got your own room?
- The other girls are upstairs, so...
I thought we'd camp out
down here for a while.
Sounds swell, huh.
Hey, what's--what's with the sticky stuff?
Uh... some kind of new lotion?
Close.
Let's get comfortable.
Sound great.
Wine too, huh? You sure know
how to make a guy feel welcome.
I've been waiting
for you to come.
Oh, yeah.
Me too, baby.
Here's where it gets fun.
Oh, yeah.
- Huh?
- What?
I think Biff just screamed.
So lots of guys do.
Especially those who are with Roxanne.
It wasn't that kind of scream.
Are you on that kick again?
I think somebody
should just check into it.
- Well, I nominate you.
- And I second it.
Why me?
Face it, Meg, all you wanna do is
see Roxanne in action
and pick up a few pointers.
- I do not!
- Either way, it's a dark, stormy night.
We're four young, attractive girls
in a big, spooky house, all alone.
If we don't go downstairs
one at a time,
how will we ever get bumped off
without the others knowing about it?
That's a terrible thing to say!
Well, maybe.
But I think you've got
the "you're it" syndrome.
You're gonna be
the first to get it,
so you have to go downstairs and
check out the situation before we do.
It's not our time to go yet.
I think Jan's right; I think you've
got "you're it" written all over you.
You guys are just
trying to scare me!
You're right, so why don't you
just go back to sleep
before Terry and I decide
to murder you ourselves?
- Going anyway?
- I'm just going to the bathroom.
Honest!
I'll be right back.
I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
- That kid is weird.
- Yeah, she is.
A canvas is a canvas
or a painting.
A rock is a rock or a statue.
A sound is a sound
or it's music.
Come on. Be a nose.
Be a nose.
Frankie, shut up!
Oh, what's the matter, Frankie?
How'd you get yourself stuck in the wall?
Wait a minute.
I'll get you out.
Hello.
Yes, it's Burt. Who's this?
Hinchlow? What the hell do you want?
You know what time it is?
No, I'm watching TV.
What the hell are you doing right now?
Yeah, well, I didn't
give you this number
so you could call me up
in the middle of the night and bug me!
They did what?
Screaming at the top
of their lungs?
Were they screaming in pleasure,
or something like that?
You know, one of those girls
is a contortionist.
Yeah, it's a political party.
Oh, in terror?
Real blood-curdling stuff?
What? And a guy
parked his car out in front?
What the hell are you doing,
watching them with a telescope?
Oh yeah?
What kinda lense you got?
Now, listen...
Okay, okay.
Yeah, I'll be over there.
This better be serious.
A nice, fresh piece
of halibut for ya.
I'll give you to her
in the morning.
How come this guy
never won an academy award?
- Burt, honey?
- Yeah?
- Where ya goin'?
- Out.
I gotta go check on those broads
I left at the old house.
- Something funny's going on there.
- But Burt, it's Friday.
So what? I gotta go.
Burt, Friday night.
Why does every week have to
have a Friday night in it?
You're gonna hurt yourself
like that some day.
- That's Meg.
- Maybe she really was it.
Now we gotta go down there.
Things may be getting a little rough.
We should get something heavy in case
we have to conk that Biff on the noggin.
Yeah.
Don't spare the weight.
- How's this?
- It's a killer.
Let's go. But quietly.
- Okay.
Meg!
Are you all right?
Biff's dead.
Oh, shit.
Why is he covered
with this tapestry?
Someone's trying to hide the body.
That's like sweeping him
under the rug.
- It's a soul shroud.
- A what?
A soul shroud.
When souls are offered up to Satan,
they go by means
of a soul shroud, to Hell.
Sort of like gift wrapping.
Gift wrapping?
Happy fucking birthday.
- How'd you know that?
- It says so, right there on the corner.
Who's that?
Come on, girls, open up.
It's me, Burt.
- What do you want?
- What do I want?
I want what any man wants.
I wanna be called up in the middle
of the night and gotten out of bed.
I wanna go for a ride in my car
in the middle of a thunder storm.
Find out if there's any trouible down here.
What the hell do you think I want?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, Hinchlow called me.
Said someone was screaming down here
loud enough to wake the dead,
he thought there
might be some trouble.
He also said he thought he saw
a guy coming here a little while ago.
You know anything about that?
- No.
- Nope.
Well, let me in. I wanna see
if everything's okay.
We can't.
We're not dressed.
Well, toss somethin' on.
I haven't got all night.
- We've got to hide this body.
- You mean touch that guy?
Look, he's already dead,
we can't help that.
But if Burt finds out he was here,
we're gonna get fired.
But is it worth a mere 100 bucks
to become implicated in a murder?
- Yep.
- Yes.
Let's do it.
Come on.
Were do we put him?
He weighs a ton.
Uh, the kitchen.
It'll be easier to clean up later.
- How do you think this happened?
- Who knows?
Looks like Roxanne gave him
an eternal hickey.
Okay.
Oh, man!
Where is Roxanne?
I never saw her.
I think she ran away
after killing Biff.
Hey, chickies, come on.
I'm catching my death out here.
You'll have to
come around back.
- This door's locked.
- Oh, it's you.
What the hell's going on here?
Everybody's acting so screwy.
Well, if you'll come with me,
I can explain everything.
- This better be good.
- Oh, it will be.
Okay, everybody.
Cool and calm.
- Yeah, right, cool and calm. Cool...
- Okay.
- Calm...
- Okay, ready?
- Okay.
- Let's do it.
Where is he?
Maybe he split.
He looked kinda loaded.
I guess he got tired of waiting.
Lucky for us, but we still
have to deal with the Biff situation.
Don't worry.
I'll think of something.
Now here is where
it all started.
- I'm still with ya.
- Now, stay close.
It's dark in here.
Ah, some dump.
We just started cleaning
this afternoon.
It ain't terrible, but
it's got a ways to go yet.
Here is where we found
the sacred shroud and dagger.
This is where
all the trouble began.
Trouble? What trouble?
You lookin' for trouble?
I'm trouble.
Oh, boy.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy!
Oh, boy!
Oh! Oh, boy!
Oh, boy! Oh, boy!
Oh my God!
Look at this.
- What is it?
- Roxanne's nightie.
Or what's left of it.
- Do you think...
- Biff attacked her?
She had to grease him
in self-defense?
Sure looks like it.
Oh, check this out.
- What?
- Remember the drawing of the beast?
- It's gone.
- Maybe somebody ripped it out.
I don't think so.
Everything else is the same.
- But the drawing is vanished.
- Hey, look, guys.
I think we have
more important things to do
than to worry about
some old witch's coloring book.
Look, it says something
about the beast on this page.
And there's the darwing of the dagger
that we found in the cellar earlier.
Well, can you read it?
I'll try.
It says that, in reading
the incantation out loud...
- The one you read out loud earlier?
- Right.
That, in reading the spell,
the spirit of the beast
will be released into
the world of the living,
to corrupt, kill,
and collect souls.
It even mentions the soul shroud.
What about this?
It says that
it'll kill the beast, if...
I can't understand the rest.
Well, I'm not ready to believe
that the drawing in that book
is alive and running
around the house somewhere.
Look, everybody, somebody cooled Biff,
and it wasn't one of us.
If it'll make you feel any better,
we'll find Rox.
- I'm sure she can explain everything.
- Okay, gals. Let's go. Come on.
Why are we starting in the basement?
I hate the basement.
I think it's better if we start at the bottom
and work our way up.
I wouldn't want this to be
the last place we ended up in.
Hey, look. The light's on.
Maybe somebody's down there.
- Oh, great.
- Come on.
- Nobody's here. Let's go.
- Not so fast.
It's obvious someone's been here.
- And recently.
- Well, it's obvious they're not here now.
Boy, are my feet killing me.
What the hell's with you two?
What are we gonna do?
We don't have a car,
we don't have a phone.
- We don't got shit.
- Okay, everybody calm down.
Now, we know Roxanne is dead.
That means there's somebody else around.
- Maybe even in this house.
- The beast in the book!
Will you stop with the frickin' beast?
This is reality!
Now, let's get to the kitchen
and get a big knife.
Then what?
Then we get our asses
over to Mr. Hinchlow's,
use his telephone
and call the cops.
There goes our paychecks.
Hey, Burt's dead, so
who is gonna pay us anyway?
You're right.
Well, at least we don't have
to clean up the place. Come on.
Biff's gone!
That means the killer
is probably still here!
Well, I guess those owners
didn't exactly leave everything behind.
So now what?
Well, there's a dagger
out on the coffee table.
Right, let's get it!
- Oh, geez, don't do that!
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I just saw your boss pull up in front,
and I thought I'd check on you myself.
- Everything all right?
- No, everything's not okay.
- Someone's killed three of our friends.
- I was afraid of that.
- There's something very odd about this place.
- We're figuring that out.
Can we use your phone?
Oh, certainly.
I live down the block.
F-follow me.
Very strange weather we're having.
They say it might rain.
You sure you wanna go out
in that weather dressed like this?
Buddy, we'd go out
naked if we had to.
- Well, let's get the dagger for protection.
- Yeah, let's do it.
Y-y-you don't need that.
You're perfectly safe with me.
Just a little insurance,
Mr. Hinchlow.
You ever seen this before?
Well...
It's a wild guess...
...but I'd say that this...
...is an ancient Cantarian warlock's
demon spell book
from late
17th century England,
brought here by Gideon Fisk
in the early 1930s.
And the source of
all the problems in this house.
Sounds like you know it
pretty well, Mr. Hinchlow.
You might say I've
gotten something out of it.
Roxanne!
- You're alive.
- Where's Hinchlow? He was just there.
Mr. Hinchlow's gone.
That still doesn't explain
how you happen to be alive.
We thought you were dead.
Yeah, was it some kind of
joke or something?
I'm sorry. I couldn't resist
playing a trick on you.
I mean, this place
is so spooky.
You mean Biff and Burt
are in on this, too?
- Ooh, I could just kill you guys.
- Please, not yet.
What's with the book?
Meg thought some drawing came to life
and was trying to kill all of us.
That's pretty far out.
Can I see?
Remember that horrible drawing?
The one of that ugly, disgusting,
repuslive, inhuman slime beast?
- Yes. I remember.
- Well, the drawing is gone.
Meg, I think your eyes
must be playing tricks on you.
- I don't think so.
- Such an imagination.
- So where's Biff and that Burt jerk?
- In the cellar.
Probably laughing
their heads off right now.
- Come on, girls. Let's go kick some butt.
- Let's do it.
All right, macho man, the game's over!
Get up on your feet!
You slimeballs are really
in for it now, come on!
That was really cruel, you guys!
Not funny at all!
Playing possum, huh?
Let's see if I can kick
a field goal this time!
Roxanne...
- I don't think this guy's kidding us.
- He's not.
Oh, shit!
Meg was right.
The book is one picture short.
And it's me.
You let me out.
I suppose I should
thank you for that.
But I haven't
got the time right now.
- Where's Roxanne?
- Why, dead, of course.
After my release, I needed
only a taste of human blood
to be come real again,
but I can only truly be free
if I send the master
some fresh souls for his collection.
- Us?
- Yes, he'll like you.
Nice tits.
Of course, getting there
is the unpleasant part.
I think the book said
that the beast could be destroyed
by plunging that old dagger
into its heart.
Great, I left it upstairs.
I think Terry and Jan
should go first.
You and I can play for
a little while if you want to, Meg.
- K-know any good games?
- I think we should make a break for it.
- Ooh, when?
- Now!
Oh, Meg, let's get going!
Come on!
Meg, get the knife!
It's gone!
The knife is gone!
- She's upstairs!
- What are we gonna do?
Why don't you
check out the book?
There must be some other way
to kill her.
- Well?
- I'm too scared! My brain won't work.
Shit!
- Maybe this'll do the trick.
- The book only mentions a dagger.
Well, fuck the dagger!
This is all we've got! Come on!
Come on!
Where are we going?
- Straight to Hell, if you don't watch it.
- We've got to get her.
If we wait for her,
we're gonna be sitting ducks.
Well, we can make a run for it.
We don't have to fight it.
Look, kid, if we don't get it right now,
it might be loose forever, and then what?
I mean, we've got some kind of
supernatural monster running around!
It's not gonna just leave us alone
because we ran away from it!
- But--
- No buts!
Now, we've gotta do this
while we have a chance!
Okay, this thing has killed our friends!
Now we've gotta do something!
We can go to Hinchlow's and call the cops.
Let them handle it.
How do we really know
that Hinchlow is Hinchlow?
Now come on!
Let's kick some monster butt!
- Don't do that!
- Sorry.
I don't see her.
Get away from me,
you monster!
Run, Meg! Run!
It's just you and me now, Meg.
I'm coming for you, Meg.
We have some unfinished business
to take care of.
I hope you're not too tired.
Tangy, but not too tart.
This is a very old
piece of material.
All I have to do, is place this
over your body when you're dead,
and your soul will fly
to Hell... like that.
But you have to be
careful how you use it.
- It can be very indiscriminate.
- Why are you doing this?
You're free!
What more do you want?
Can't you guess?
No?
I want all the others
set free, too.
All the pictures in the book.
They want to live again, too.
Just like me.
I want you to read
that incantation out loud.
Again and again,
until they've all been released.
And then I want to eat your soul.
So, it's you.
Yes.
- Get lost on your way to Hell?
- I've come to destroy you.
And you think that
will save your soul
from the eternal damnation
you brought upon yourself?
It's a good place to start.
You'll never be free.
As long as there's a dark side,
we'll always be here.
Waiting. Ready.
You can't kill us.
We're too strong for you.
- For anyone.
- I can try.
After all, you're
nothing but a doodle.
- How dare you!
- I may have failed in the past.
But this time I'm going to
erase you once and for all.
And how do you plan to
accomplish that, Gideon Fisk?
With this.
Man, that really hurts.
Better get back in that book.
The book!
It's trying to get back into the book.
If that happens,
it can never be destroyed.
The fireplace!
We can burn it.
If I can just make it
another step or two.
Oh, boy, this really
cracks me up.
Hey, where ya going, baby?
Don't be so hasty.
Not the fire! No!
Anything but the fire!
- Throw it in the fire!
- Oh, I was hoping he wouldn't say that.
Now!
Oh, man, why'd you
have to do that?
You little bitch!
I'll get you in the sequel for this!
What a world!
I'm melting!
I suppose you're wondering
what this is all about.
I know I must seem
a little late to you,
but I had to wait
for the right time to act.
What happened?
I'm the one who brought the book
to America years ago.
I thought it held knowledge.
How wrong I was.
I released a terror that has cursed me
for an eternity, until now.
I don't understand.
Who are you?
I am the cause of all the misery.
For years after my death,
I waited in limbo,
hoping to find someone
who could transform the book
into a living thing,
so I could destroy it.
Now you've done that for me,
and it's over.
So now what happens?
The curse which hangs over me
because of my evil mischief has lifted,
and the demon
is vanquished to Hell.
Your world is safe now.
Yes...
...but all my friends are dead,
because of your mischief.
Oh, I don't think so.
I think you'll find them
very much alive.
You see, the beast
never truly existed.
And now, neither do I.
Goodbye, little one.
Good luck.
Hey, Meg.
What are you doing up so early?
Oh, God, it's you!
It's really you!
Well, of course it's me.
Hey, where are the others?
In the cellar, I think.
Did you guys have a party last night
after I crashed out, or what?
Yeah, sort of.
But I think it's over now.
Morning, kids!
Thought I'd stop by
to see how your night was.
It was rough, Mr. Hinchlow.
I think I sprained my knee or something.
- They were partying all night.
- Oh, is that so?
Well, I think I have an Ace bandage
down at my place if you'd like to use it.
But first, how about
some hot coffee?
- I brung it on my thermos!
- I think I could use it.
- My God, what a hangover.
- You're telling me.
What happened?
I don't know, but you guys
have some explaining to do.
I don't even remember
who I did it with.
At least you're alive.
I brought along my portable TV set
in case you'd like to use it.
That's nice, but why?
Hell, it's Saturday morning.
Don't tell me you kids
don't enjoy a good cartoon?