There are two types of soldiers
in this world: the quick and the dead!
R-Division, we are the quick.
You got that'?
Yes, sir!
There ain't no breaks in this war.
You think the Re-Ans take breaks?
- Kill, kill and re-kill!
- Yes, sir!
That's your job. That is the R-Division.
Oprah!
What is a cell?
And what happens when it's attacked?
It's a simple organism,
which reproduces itself by dividing.
Our bodies are made up
of mil/ions of cells.
They're the building blocks
of our blood and tissues.
Now, powerful radiation strikes...
and cells are injured or destroyed.
Some cells less able to function
at top efficiency.
Should the body fall behind
in its recovery...
severe illness or death could result.
The key then is the amount-
Mommy?
Daddy?
We measure radiation the same way-
Hello?
0n/y instead 0f a speedometer,
we have a rate meter.
And instead of miles per hour...
we measure the rate in roentgens per hour.
We need another device
cal/ed a dosimeter...
to record how much radiation a person has
accumulated over a period of time.
In the same way we record
accumulated distance in-
where the island is once again open-
- herbivore.
- Bum' f hand/e any urban 0000927190.
This is what the scene
looked like just moments ago.
Peace of mind, assurance, safety.
These things are a way
of life at Gated Gardens...
an award-winning, fortified community.
This family-oriented
neighborhood is surrounded by...
an 18-foot, reinforced concrete wall...
and our 360-degree watchtowers...
are manned by world-class sharpshooters-
Due t0 the graphic' nature
of this program...
viewer discretion is advised.
Five years ago, our world changed.
A dead man kills six at a food court.
[ Man j And this unknown vxrus seems
f be re-anxknafxhg the dead.
Yes, these are
disturbing reports coming in.
The government has just detonated a nuclear
weapon over San Francisco.
The city of Manhattan has been quarantined.
I can't believe it! They were all dead!
China has released
a biological weapon on Beijing.
And this bill will give us
specialized troops...
to eliminate this scourge.
The death toll from the Re-An virus...
now tops 70 mil/ion nation wide.
There were 4 1/2 billion dead.
They keep us free. They keep us safe.
They are the men and women of R-Division.
Previous/y on Re-Kill.
This is Erica Hamilton...
coming to you from Chevallier Square.
We are in the outskirts of-
Hold!
We are on the outskirts
of New Orleans, Louisiana...
tonight investigating
the report of Re-An activity.
Some sort of attack seems
to have taken place here.
Eyes on the rooftops.
Hold!
Sergeant McKinney is investigating.
Clear.
Now we're moving deeper
into Chevallier Square.
Hold.
Jennings, clear. Go.
For the viewers at home...
please keep our men and Women
in R-Division 6...
in your thoughts tonight.
As a reporter for Re-Ki/L.
This is typical of Re-An activity.
Over there.
♪♪
- Move.
- Sorry. Sorry.
On the roof!
Oh, God!
- You okay?
- We’re clear.
- You all right'?
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
Line up!
Regroup.
Stick together!
Form up, squad.
One of the
soldiers have been bitten.
Oh, no!
- Oh, God!
- Easy out?
Oh, God.
Keep moving. Keep moving.
As harsh as it seems...
this man was given an easy out
to avoid becoming a Re-An.
Hold.
Something is in the car.
Hold your fire!
- Hit!
- L-lolcl your fire!
- Second floor!
- 10:00!
They got everyone.
Come on.
It's going to be all right.
- No! Oh, my God!
- Tactical retreat!
- She’s been bit!
- Put your gun down!
Up there!
Shoot them!
They’re coming from all sides.
They’re fucking everywhere!
Move now!
Run!
Look out!
Move now!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Get in!
Get me out of here!
Hang on!
Oh, get me out of here.
Get me out of here. Look out!
II
[Crying 1
on, God! on, God!
Here vve go!
You all right?
Hey!
- You got bit.
- No!
Yeah, you did.
Tonxjghfs broadcast of Re-Kill...
is sponsored by the Coalition
to Re-populate America.
N
She was in the yard gardening.
We never saw them coming.
Thankfully I had taken Vivodine.
I saw what was happening,
so I called 9-1-2.
It took nine minutes for help to arrive.
If it vvasrft for Vivodine,
it would have been too late.
But she’s alive thanks to Vivodine.
Vivodine is a revolutionary new drug...
that increases your chances
of surviving a Re-An attack...
by stopping the virus cold in its tracks.
Vivodine, the last line of defense.
A chance for life.
Vivodine, available where all
ﬁne products are sold.
The Outbreak News Channel.
We now return to Re-N“.
The debacle of last week's
attack on Chevallier Square...
left a startling number of casualties...
including eight R-Division
personnel and 152 civilians.
Re-KilFs own fie/o’
correspondent Erica Hamilton...
was also tragically killed
in taping last week's episode.
When R-Division reinforcements arrived...
over 480 Re-Ans were re-kil/ed.
The subsequent press release
from the Re-Animate Bureau...
assures the public that the magnitude
of Chevallier Square...
is an isolated and rare occurrence.
Stay with us tonight as field
correspondent Jimmy Mitchell...
is embedded with R-Division 8...
as they continue to
eliminate the dwindling re-animate menace.
My first day arriving
at R-Division headquarters...
was awkward and tense.
The team preps for its next assignment.
İt's always dangerous.
Let’s meet some of this vveek’s team.
Hey, guys.
Do you Want to do an interview?
Tom, ifs your first day, are you scared?
Well, sure. I mean, you know, I clon't-
I clon't want to say “soared.”
Uh-
You know, a little jittery,
you know, nervous maybe.
But, uh, you know, definitely not soared.
My-My insides are kind of knotted together.
Uh, but, you know, I'm excited.
You know'? I'm ready.
The only survivor
of Chevallier Square, Alex Winston.
I write a blog about Gods Sanctuary.
Winston believes that
everyone is gonna die...
and a few selected by God will be put on an
ark to start the world over.
Those people will survive.
So you think mankind
is just gonna be wiped out?
Except those chosen by the Lord.
Officially, ifs called NS 115.
İt's a decommissioned nuclear facility...
built during the cold vvar
in Mount Rogers, Virginia.
Wnds gonna be in this government ark?
Officials, top scientists.
But mainly...
it’|| be those chosen by the Lord.
Do you think you'll be
one of them, Winston'?
It's up to him.
Critics of your Web site say you’re crazy.
What do you have to say to them?
The call to arms against the re-animates...
has shattered many
social boundaries including...
age, F806, EVEN 86X.
Lefs meet the only Woman in R-Division 8...
Rose Matthews.
During the outbreak, I was a nurse...
and my husband was a paramedic.
He was one of the first to get infected.
Back before we really knew
what it was.
As we prepare to go out into the field...
some of the team members
become introspective...
While others cope
with their problems differently.
- Camera man.
- Ah, God!
That's not funny, guys.
Omar Hernandez. l-low did you end up here'?
I got caught ripping off
a store near the edge of The Zone.
I had two strikes against me already.
People had to eat. People vvere starving.
They’re still starving.
The judge gave me a choice.
Fifteen hard in Chino or two doing this.
Excuse me. Sergeant.
Did you vvant to answer a couple of
questions about yourself before-
So the sergeant has a lot on his mind.
That's fine. I get it.
We'll get an interview from him later.
After arming up, we left
for our first mission...
and I got a chance to speak
more with the team.
- Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
- Tom, you look nervous.
- Sorry. Sorry.
- No, ifs okay. We can bleep it out.
Yeah, well-bleep this shit,
you...
- Whoa, okay.
- Guys, come on.
- You're ruining my show.
- l-low come the show's
about him anyway, huh'?
What the-
makes you so special?
I'm gonna get to everybody.
Sergeant, do you Want
to say something, please?
- Just Sarge.
- Right. Sarge.
The team has just arrived at a small farm.
Whafs the plan, Tom?
Re-Ans inside. Search and destroy.
- You two stand back. Got it?
- Yes, sir.
Lefs move.
Come on, Bobby. l_et's go.
Looks like they’re gonna try...
and make contact with vvhoeveﬁs inside.
- Get down!
- Oh, my God!
Two tours in Afghanistan...
one tour in Iran, one tour in Pakistan...
before it Went up in smoke.
That place was-.
The guys got soldiering questions,
they come to me.
- Cover me!
- Got him!
Move! Move!
Sarge is approaching the front door.
Jesus!
Stay down!
- Get the-out of my way! Move!
- Oh, okay!
- Move!
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Where is it?
- Where’s What?
Matthews, Hernandez, check it out.
Yeah. I'll go with them to the barn.
I'm staying with the Sarge.
- Keep close.
- Yeah.
- We got Re-Ans.
- What?
Why would they keep Re-Ans in a cage?
- Call it.
- On three.
One, two-
Wait!
Sarge?
Sarge, What are you doing?
Oh, Jesus.
Just food for whatever
they got inside.
All right, you camera boys
want to know why we're here'?
We’re— We’re protecting her.
We’re protecting her.
We’re gonna see ifthere’s gonna be a cure.
You dorft know there’s not.
Tell me where.
You dorft know What ifs like
to see-to watch your-
You think you're the only one
who's lost somebody?
He’s hiding something.
Where is it?
I do R-Division two years.
I get a green card for
me and for my family.
Thafs why I do this.
- Where is she?
- The attic.
In the attic.
We have a confirmation
there’s a Re-An in the house.
Remember five years ago?
L-low it spread so quickly?
People got bit...
but hoped against all hope
that they vvouldrft turn.
They hid their infected relatives...
their husbands, wives,
girlfriends, cousins, whatever.
They were all dead, all infected...
but we ooulcln't accept it.
Couldrft let it go.
It was our humanity
that nearly wiped us out.
Shit. Shit.
All right, rookie. You ready?
- It looks like we're moving in.
- I'm sorry, Sis!
- I'm sorry!
- Shut up!
Okay.
We are headed upstairs.
Oh, God! lt smells awful.
Oh.
I think I hear it.
_
D|d you get it? Did you get it?
Get her, Winston! Find her!
Goddamn it!
Tom got bit.
Oh, no. Ah.
Eve Please, no!
- Sarge.
- Dispatch.
- Sergeant.
- R-Division 8, over.
- [ Dispatch j Dispatch. Go ahead
- Sarge!
- One re-animate located
and destroyed. Over and out.
Sarge, he’s turning! Sarge!
I was a lost soul.
Did a lot of bad things
before the outbreak.
Then I found God.
And I was reborn as one of his warriors...
to remove these things
from the garden of his creation.
Do you really believe that, Winston?
Mom?
Mom died during the outbreak.
And-
No, she vvasrft infected or anything.
She— She starved during the long Winter.
So... she Went out human.
- Ls that important?
- Yeah.
I mean, we-
You know, we're born human.
We die that Way.
You know, not like one of them.
It's always hard losing one of your own.
I dorft know.
Dad-He said-
Basically told me not to be dumb.
But, uh, I think he’d be proud of me.
You know, this is my way of honoring him.
N
U
Ooh.
You’ve lost a lot of people like Tom.
- Ls that hard?
- Yeah.
İt's part of what we clo.
The most unpleasant part.
But it comes with the job.
Every man and Woman that
signed up for R-Division knows the risks.
And they’re Willing to pay
the ultimate price.
Are you prepared to pay that price?
Is anyone?
All right, let's make the boy's mark.
L-low many of your own
guys have you hacl to-
You know?
We dorft talk about that.
You sure were shit out of luck, Tim.
His name was Tom.
Whatever.
Hovv do you think the outbreak got started?
İt's Gods will.
But ifs not Judgment Day.
Maybe ifs just a cleansing
to weed out the bad...
to bring us back to simpler times and ways.
Hovv do you know God
doesrft mean it to be the end?
Because he has a bigger plan for us.
I mean, you’re still here, right?
Just.
When I was a soldier,
|’d— die for my country.
But I'm telling ya, if there was ever a
truly-situation...
you can bet the military's involved.
I mean, you got any idea hovv much money
they spend on biovveapon research?
I figure they screwed up one day...
and invented something
they couldrft un-invent.
Right, Grizzly?
He believes me though. Right, Grizzly?
About the army.
Yeah.
Command and Control.
This is the brain of the entire
R-Division operation.
R-Div 8, this is Command Central.
- Come baa/c
- R-Div 8. Go ahead.
I need you to intercept a semi truck...
less than a quarter of a mile
away from your current location.
The vehicle is moving at a high rate of
speed and possibly carrying Re-Ans.
- Proceed with caution. He's gonna run.
- Over.
All right, crew, look alive.
İt's gonna get ugly.
This is R-Division! Pull over now!
Move it! Move, move, move!
Out of the cab! Now!
- Get out!
- Okay, okay, take it easy!
Get out of the truck. On the ground!
What the hell is
your problem, man? Come on!
- What do you have in the back?
- I got DVD players in the back, man.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Show me. Come on. Back, cover!
Why would they be running if
they weren't hiding something?
- Move!
- I need a lawyer!
- I need-
- Case dismissed. Cuff him.
- Take it easy!
- I got this thing on TV.
- Open up.
- All right.
This doesrft feel right.
I dorft like it.
Get up there. Go.
Th-There's just DVD players in here.
There’s nothing else in there.
Look-
There’s nothing else in there!
Hernandez!
- There’s just-
They’re just DVD players in there!
- Move!
- There’s nothing else in there!
- Parker, Winston, check it out.
They're tough to put clown, yeah.
|t’s got to be a head shot,
but sometimes even that dorft get it done.
You gotta destroy the brain stem.
And I seen them take five or six bullets in
the head before they go dovvn.
And I svvear to God, it’s like
shooting them just pisses them off...
and they come at you even harder.
Clear it, Grizzly! Yeah! Get them!
I mean...
they died once already.
It airft easy making them do it over.
Adams, close the gate!
Close it!
RPG!
Welcome back.
Right now the guys are going around...
To re-kill all of the Re-Ans.
|t’s never been seen before on TV.
- You ready for this?
- Yes, sir.
L-low will we know
when we finally achieve victory?
Officially...
the outbreak is over.
But look around us.
Look what we do every day.
It only takes one.
One uncontained bite
can trigger another massive outbreak.
İt's only a matter of time.
You know why'?
Because we're stuck with being human.
These... things are getting smarter.
Hey, camera boy, come here.
Check this shit out.
Boost your ratings.
They're learning.
We oarTt win this war.
This whole things gonna end
us dead and gone...
and these... things...
Wandering around starving to death.
So then why fight?
Because we're human.
Re-N“ will return in a moment.
Tonight on Heroes of the Outbreak...
Bob Waynevvright,
the Oklahoma school principal...
who saved his student body
from sure death...
after suddenly being attacked
by multiple Re-Ans.
What a story.
It-It all happened so fast.
From-From What l, uh, can remember...
um, l-l was telling the children
to get behind me...
and, uh, luckily, a-a bat had dropped...
from-from two of the children
who had been playing a little ball.
And l, uh, grabbed that and, uh...
I kind of Went ballistic.
And at some point, I remembered...
“My God, the kids.
L-l dorft Want them to see this.”
Well, l-l just-I just told them to-to run.
L-l got in front ofthem and I guess, uh...
there is something to, uh,
having a schoolteacher voice sometimes.
They-They all listened and-
and-and did What I told them.
Wow. A truly heroic feat.
Hear details tonight along
with other tales of bravery...
only on the Outbreak Network.
Your trusted source for outbreak news.
A/l systems ready.
- He’s the man!
- It was a good day.
Good day, good day, good day.
After the initial outbreak,
they sent us out in hazmat suits.
They used to slow us clown.
The suits didrft protect you,
so they changed the rules.
Now we can survive.
But we still gotta go
through decontamination.
Good day on the street.
Yeah, I look over at you today
and I savv you...
- Hey!
- Thump, thump, thump!
It was-
crazy, man.
You were a-
animal.
- Did you see it explode?
- Awesome, man!
- Come on.
- Love it.
Most people dorft understand What vve do.
Why would they?
İt's tough. it's serious.
You put yourself in harm's way.
It's stressful.
Sometimes you gotta
let off a little steam...
in What may seem a weird Way.
- Yeah!
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Eve
Whoo!
What do you do to blow off steam?
I pray. That's just me.
Hey, there, camera.
You guys out in the field too?
- Uh, yeah, but we wererflt in-
- All right. Both of you, come on. Go.
Yeah, R-Div’s a boys’ club.
R-D! Oprah! VVhoo!
Sure, um, well...
you saw there's no separate facilities.
Um, I heard I was
one of 121 females nationwide...
but that was a While back, so by now some-
Come here. He’s got
a scratch on his left arm.
İt's nothing. I got it this morning.
A door scratched me. Sarge, tell him.
Sarge!
Guys, come on. This ain't right.
Come on. You know the rule.
Twenty-four hours observation.
Lefs go.
This is bullshit!
What?
Never had an infected in the building ever.
I'm sure Officer Nguyerfs fine,
but safety first.
We gotta do the checks.
Truth is, we clon't know
how infectious it is.
We know a bite can do it, but, um...
What about scratches?
On, uh...
there's one thing about this war
that's different from the other oonfliots.
There’s no scars on the veterans.
Once you get out...
you’re dead.
- Are they sending us back out?
- I don’t know.
Ain’t you gonna say nothing about this?
Oh, yeah, great. That's what I thought.
As a result of the truck drivers
you caught today...
are we gonna go back out'?
Sarge? Sarge.
What else you want me to say, man?
They told me they were
DVD players in the back.
You think I ‘m stupid, huh?
That's all I Know.
You know what / think is really stupid?
Spending the rest of your life in prison.
Your partner just told us...
your destination was inside this zone.
I need-I need-
I want immunity. Then I'll talk.
Screw your immunity!
Tell me why you were going there.
You're looking at mandatory life in prison.
- I don't know anything!
- Come on.
You're carrying a truckload of re-animates.
That's it. I'm throwing you back.
- Everything you've given me is useless!
- Okay, all right.
Ah, it's-it's something
called the Judas Project.
The Judas Project? Tell me more about that.
Sergeant, these Re-Ans are
different, smarter, very dangerous!
After discovering the truck
driveﬁs final location...
Captain McAdams and the Sarge argue...
over whether they should deploy
R-Division 8 deep into The Zone.
That's it! Deploy now, Sergeant!
Hey, get away from me, camera boy!
My name's not camera boy. it's Jimmy.
Jimmy was the name of his son.
He died during the outbreak.
What happened?
You’re gonna keep pointing that
thing at me till I tell you, aren’t you?
Uh, no way. I'm not going there.
That's the Sarge's business.
If you neecl to know, you'll know.
Everyone on R-Div thinks the Sarge was a
cop or a soldier before the outbreak.
They’re wrong. He was a
supermarket manager.
Just doing What vve were told
to do when it started.
Staying holed up in his house
with his Wife Ronnie and his kid.
He was only three years old.
They ran out of food, so he Went to the
store to get more and, um...
when he got back,
his Wife was so badly eaten...
she was gone.
She was the lucky one.
Jimmy vvasrft.
He had to re-kill his ovvn little boy.
Hi. We all remember the outbreak.
The people we lost.
Of course we'll never forget.
But now we have to cope with the aftermath.
At Gibsons Post Trauma Clinic,
vve understand.
We know just talking isn't enough.
Thafs why vve prescribe
the Widest range of drugs.
No one prescribes harder, faster or more...
even over the phone.
Gibsorfs Post Trauma Clinic.
Pain medication for emotional pain...
the kind that really hurts.
Head shot.
Re-K ill.
Good aim.
Well done.
|’ve tried other guns,
but I just never felt safe.
The Desert Eagle .50 caliber.
The human skull is made of
16 joining plates of bone...
some over an inch thick.
- » Point, shoot.
- - Game over.
For the children.
Please have ID check ready.
Stay inside your vehicle
unless instructed otherwise.
R-D 8, proceed to zone
coordinates 1-5-niner-7—
All right, listen up.
We got an address from the driver we picked
up from that truck.
Something about some Judas Project.
|t’s deep in The Zone.
You gotta be kidding me.
This is fantastic.
A camera crevv’s never been
in The Zone before.
I'm Jimmy Mitchell.
And tonight vve have
an exclusive on Re-K/YL.
That will be unlike anything
you’ve ever seen before on television.
My camera crew and I are going to travel...
with the brave men and Women
of R-Division 8...
to an unknown point deep inside The Zone.
As you may know,
The Zone is the sealed-off area...
that encompasses most
of Manhattan Island...
in the once proud city
formerly known as New York.
In the dark and violent months following
the patient zero Re-An outbreak...
New York was heroically
sealed off by engineers...
in an unrivaled construction project.
But no one, besides the military...
has been allowed in this area
in nearly five years.
During that time, rumors have spread Wildly
across the Internet...
and several best-selling authors
have written books...
speculating on What exactly
is going on behind these giant walls.
The conspiracy theories
range from the mundane...
to the outlandish.
Now as you may know,
Re-Kfl/ is filmed live on a two-hour delay.
This is especially necessary tonight...
because communication will be completely
blacked out once vve’re inside these walls.
So every two hours our Re-Ki/l drones...
are going to rendezvous with us
and ferry our camera footage...
back to our mobile broadcast studio...
and then directly into your home.
So sit back and be the first
to discover...
What truly lies inside The Zone.
Captain McAdams, can you tell us
a little more about The Zone?
The, uh, Zone is, uh, part ofthe city...
that vve never managed
to clear after the outbreak.
So, for five years...
we just built a wall around it...
and, uh, let vvhafs inside rot away.
Hopefully.
So tell me, Winston...
vvhafs your thoughts on The Zone?
|t’s a no-marfs-land.
İt's a place we, uh...
had to contain after the initial outbreak.
We had to wall it up, seal it shut.
Now it's the Re-An ghetto.
A few Weeks ago,
another R-D unit Went in there.
No one came back.
Hey, Parker,
have you been in The Zone before?
Do I look that-
dumb to you?
- Huh? Get the fuck out of here.
- No. Ovv! God.
Do I know why we're here'?
Dude-
I'm just as blind as you are.
- Except I got an M-16.
- You got a-camera.
Nobody wants to be here, Jimmy.
Nobody.
- What the shit are we doing here, Sarge?
- There's been rumors...
of something called a Judas Project-
a re-animation experimentation-
going on in The Zone.
Guy from the truck confirmed the rumors.
What are they doing with them?
That's what we're here to fincl out.
You think this Judas Project thing is real?
I read plenty of blogs about it.
People say they’re
trying to create some super Re-An.
Why would anybody wanna do that?
Desperate times, desperate measures.
And if ifs that big a deal,
why all six on our ovvn?
I do know the Lord is ever
constant and vigilant.
Should have picked Chino.
I started out in a different unit-
R-Div 6.
We were ordered
into The Zone six months ago.
But I had the flu that day.
I'm alive because
of the-flu.
Keep it tight. Stay alert.
- Turn that light out now.
- Oh, yeah. My bad.
Anyone have anything?
Fan out. Two to the right.
The rest of us straight ahead.
What is this place?
" [ Vomitin Am g1
Hey, are you all right?
Jesus.
God.
L-low long have these people been here'?
- Guess ifs real.
- The Judas Project?
We’re too late.
Hey, you see this?
Whafd I tell you, boy? Had to be the army.
God, they must have hated him.
They dorft hate. They eat.
- You sure about that, Sarge?
- Lets move.
We don’t know nothing
about What they think...
or what it's like... to be one of them.
Lefs not break formation.
Sarge? Sarge.
- What is it'?
- Um, I just-I saw something.
- Where'?
- Keep it together.
- Ah, yeah.
Oh, Jesus.
It's Survival Week again here at ONC.
And all this week we'll be sharing
unique stories of survival...
from our viewers.
We wanna know where you were
when the outbreak ﬁrst began.
Where was I the day of the outbreak?
To tell you that, I have to tell you about
Amos. Uh, that's my stepclacl.
Proud owner of Amos Trees, LLC.
He’s a piece of vvork.
He was just always riding me, you know?
“Ellis, what the hell's wrong with you?”
“Ellis, why are you so lazy?”
“Ellis, vvhafs your problem?”
“Ellis, you on— drugs?
Your body is a temple...
and you’re ruining your-temple,
god-.”
One of those religious types.
So anyway, day of the outbreak...
I'm-I'm out here doing my thing,
minding my own business.
And here comes Amos stumbling up to me.
I just thought he was drunk again.
The old man had
a little thing for the sauce.
“Your body’s a temple.”
Anyway, so |’m out here.
He stumbles up and he tries to grab me.
And l gotta tell you vve-vve dorft really
have that kind of, uh, relationship.
I'm like, “Whoa,” you know.
“What the hell's your problem?”
Then he tries to bite me.
I was like,
“Oh, hell no,” you know?
So I took a shovel to him hard, real hard.
And, uh, it didrft seem to faze him.
It just kind of pissed him off.
Anyways, that goes on for a little while...
and luckily, I had old Johnny with me.
And I Went at him with it.
I cannot tell you What Went through my mind
when I Went at him with this.
But, uh, I can tell you
What happened immediately afterwards.
I just thought... I'm going to prison.
But for once, uh, you knovv,
luck was on my side.
Everywhere was going batshit crazy.
So it kinda worked out
for me, uh, you know?
I got the family business,
uh, changed the name.
That's, uh-That's how
I survived the outbreak.
Coming down!
We out shit.
Send your story of survival
to the Outbreak News Channel.
Attention." I Survived.
565 Monument Square...
New York 2, New York...
9 7052.
Still got power.
So whatever happened clown here-
Dicln't happen long ago.
Or nobody knows about it.
- Halt.
- The truck was bringing more Re-Ans.
Somebody thinks this
project is still alive.
What is happening?
They’re messing with the power.
I got a bad feeling about this.
Man up, PUSSY-
They tracking us?
Shit.
Are you talking about the Re-Ans?
All right, let's keep moving.
Got something here, Sarge.
Lefs move.
Parker.
Parker. ls that the Re-Ans?
For the viewers at home,
it may be too dark to see-
Listen!
Wait. I hear something.
- Sarge.
- Ah, shit!
Did you guys fucking see that?
See What?
What the fuck? We’re after it or What?
- Calm clown.
- Vvhat-What if it's true'?
Yeah, right. They
got the brains of turtles.
- I think we should stay here.
- Parker!
Come on. Search and destroy!
That's what we clo! Fuck this!
Parker!
- Move!
- Cover him! Cover him!
L_et's go.
GO, 9O, 9O, 9O, 9O, 9O, 9O, 9O!
Hernandez, you okay?
- Yeah.
- You better be.
Stay alert.
Here they come!
- Come on!
- Get them back up!
Lefs move! Go, go, go!
Got you, bitch!
Don't leave me. I've dropped the oamera.
Get-Get up!
Get your ass up!
Too late! Get out!
Reloading!
Sarge, we gotta get out of here!
Hernandez, get him!
Help! Come on!
Guys, I think Parker got bit.
- I saw it.
- Parker.
- İt's just a scratch.
- Scratch or bite'?
İt's just a scratch. I'm fine.
- Thats no scratch.
- He’s bit! Look at him. He’s infected.
İt's a fucking scratch, Sarge.
All right'? I'm fine.
- Look at him. He’s turning.
- Hey, I said |’m fucking fine!
Look, I'm taking these Vivocline pills,
man. I take 'em every fucking clay.
The frioking pills clon't work, man.
Ahhh!
Fuck it!
Fuck!
Fucking stupid! Fuck!
Stupid mother-
Parker, stand clown. Stow your weapon.
Back the fuck off! I'm not infected.
Sarge.
Do it or
|’m gonna have to do it.
Fuck you, Hernandez! Fuck you!
|’m not a fucking coward!
Shit!
It's starting again.
They’re coming back. Lefs move.
Sorry, Parker.
Hey, Grizzly.
I know you’ve had to kill
a lot of your ovvn men on the field.
Do you think if it was Parker,
you could pull the trigger?
- Are you afraid to die?
- No.
If you had to go,
hovv would you Want it to happen?
In a... damn
blaze of glory.
What if you got bit?
L-low would you react?
Re-N“ will return in a moment.
VVhoo!
Yeah!
Where was I on the day of the outbreak?
Is that What you really wanna know?
Can you please just answer the question?
On the day of the outbreak, I was on
a date with a friend, my boyfriend.
And dinner must have gone vvell
because he got us a room at a hotel-
a really nice hotel.
So vve Walk into the room,
and John, my boyfriend...
starts acting really aggressive.
And this somehow led to
a fight about money.
Couples fight all the time
about money, right?
So anyway,
he just looked around like he was lost.
It was really Weird.
I was having a hard time
taking him serious...
because he’s not wearing pants.
So I start laughing. Thafs when he decided
to put his hands on me...
which is a huge no-no.
I know exactly Where to kick.
- I mentioned he wasn't wearing pants'?
- Yes.
Hmm. Anyways, sol kick him,
and there’s zero response.
- So then I show him this.
- She’s got a gun.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Do you Want me to finish my story or not?
Cherry interview, take two.
- Anyway, so then I tell Jim-
- John.
Yes. Then I tell John to back the “F” off
me. You know What I mean?
So he lunges at me,
so I shot him in the ass.
I mean, that should have been enough
to stop him, but he just goes psycho.
So I take off running clown the hallway.
|’m screaming my head off,
and this little old Woman comes out...
and John attacks her instead of me.
No. So I Went up to him.
I put the gun to the back
of his head and boom!
And that fixed it.
But then the old lady started
kind of looking weird and-
No. Good-bye. I gotta go.
So I reached clown. I grab his keys.
He has a really nice car, by the Way.
And I got the hell out ofthere.
That's what happened to me
on the clay of the outbreak.
Fifty dollars, right? Yeah?
Welcome back to Re-Ki/l
If you're just joining us...
vve are deep inside The Zone right now...
where WeK/e just lost two of our own-
Trent Parker and Corporal Adams.
It seems to be quiet.
Quiet is good.
Ankle biters.
All right, spread out.
Um, “Ankle biters” is a slang term...
used by the R-Div team,
referring to Re-An children.
Oh, this is not good.
This is fucked up.
You got something?
Over here.
Oh, God.
You guys, maybe vve should get out of here.
[ Sarge 1 Regroup!
Shit!
Easy, ‘cause ifs out.
This is What God has planned for me.
- Can you believe it'?
- There's more of them.
- Sarge?
- Get out of here.
Okay, let's move.
I/aya con Dias.
Remember, they’re gonna
need you in the ark.
They’re gonna need you!
The ark is Gods home for those he has
chosen to survive, to start over.
Do I think Winstorfs right about his ark?
HQ_
Do you believe in God?
I used to.
Just like the Sarge says,
Outbreak Two will happen.
It's just not gonna kill all of us.
- Let’s get the hell out of here.
- Yeah.
Jimmy, take this.
- What?
- Take it!
- L-I've never firecl a gun before.
- Keep up.
Shit.
Hey, drop the damn cameras!
Dorft do it, Bobby. Lefs just keep going.
Slow them clown a bit.
Take cover!
Squad, fall back! Fall back.
Here they come!
|’|| cover!
Move back!
Watch out! Watch out!
We’re under fire!
Move! Move!
Cover!
Move back! Move back!
- 6:00! 6:00!
- Stop.
Get down!
Grenade!
Get back!
Jesus Christ!
We gotta find cover. Find cover.
They’re everywhere!
Just get back. Get back! Move!
- Run!
- Stairs! Go!
Lefs move!
Come on! Lefs go!
Hernandez, go! Come on!
L_et's go!
Right behind you.
Go, go, go!
Come on! Go!
They’re still coming.
Die!
This way!
- Reload! Cover me.
- Got your six!
RPG!
Move, move, move,
move, move! Lefs go!
Watch it! Got it!
Come on! Go, go, go, go, go!
Sarge, the dooﬁs locked!
Move it, Matthews!
My God, vve’re trapped.
Sarge, what-what are you doing?
Why are you taking your gear off?
- In case they get us.
- So we're not bulletproof.
- What about Jimmy'?
- I'll take oare of the camera guys.
It's Hernandez.
Sorry, man.
Wait! NO!
- Where we going?
- Gotta keep moving.
No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
That was Judas Project. Dumb assholes.
Thought they had answers.
Thought they vvere gonna save the World.
- What are you talking about?
- What were they doing in there?
You know What? I dorft even know.
I was just another grunt to them, you know?
Save-the-vvorld types.
Scientists. Fuckheads, all ofthem.
Come on! Come!
Lefs fucking move! Move! Now!
In fucking here! Lefs go!
Go, go, go! Come on!
Go on. Go, go.
Go!
Go, go, go, go. Come on, come on.
That-That's all that's
left of the Judas Project.
Maybe someday somebody will find it,
Work it out.
All they told me one time was, uh, to be-
To try to find a Way
to make ‘em turn on each other.
Here.
To fight each other instead of us.
Eat each other like they eat us?
One clay we got a new batch.
And one of them-He was different.
Subject is still unresponsive.
I'm cutting the skin tissue.
They all changed.
Uh, the Way they acted,
the Way they watched us.
They changed.
They started acting like,
uh-in a group. Like they had ideas.
I clon't know how to say it.
I'm not an eggheacl or a scientist.
Just doing my job.
What was your job?
- I worked in the holding pens.
- Holding pens?
Oh, yeah.
We had hundreds.
Locked them all up together.
- That was our big mistake.
- What happened?
Levels are spiking.
When did this happen?
I uh-I kinda lost track of time,
but, uh, two weeks ago now.
J.
Three.
Mm. Maybe four Weeks.
L-low come nobody knows about this'?
'Cause they're smart enough to sit tight.
The longer they stay here,
the bigger their army gets.
You know, the more Re-Ans
get delivered in the trucks.
- Army?
- Oh, yeah.
Army of the dead.
We’re no longer top ofthe food chain.
We’re food.
Why are you still filming this?
We’re gonna die here.
No one’s ever gonna see this.
No, that's-that's not true...
because every time we go outside...
the network sends drones
so we can upload the files.
- If we can just get out there-
- l-low far behind are they'?
- Uh, about two hours.
- Then we still got a chance.
We gotta let people know. Come on!
- Hovv far do these tunnels go?
- Uh, forever.
I think they link up
with the subway somewhere.
Every-fucking-vvhere.
Not a good fucking place.
- What do you mean?
- They come out of here.
Fucking anywhere. They are like wolves.
They hunt in a pack. Hunting.
Then let's make this quick.
This is a bad place, man.
They'll come out of fucking anywhere, man.
- Tunnel dwellers.
- Tunnel dwellers?
They’re hunting us here, and this is their
fucking hunting ground right here.
See this? See this?
Those fuckers will come out of there, man,
like water.
They just ooze out of that fucker, man.
- Hovv did you survive?
- I guess I was born lucky.
Oh, God. Oh!
Oh, God.
Whafd I fucking tell you?
- A lucky-|’m a lucky fucker.
- Yeah.
There’s one.
Okay, vve’ve made it through the tunnels.
Now we're on our way
to try ancl film some footage...
of the so-called Re-Animate army.
This is wrong. This is fucking wrong.
In there.
They’re-They’re in there.
You see 'em, huh'? Can you see 'em'?
Can you see 'em'?
What are they doing?
That's the one. Fucking move.
- What?
- Move.
- What is it'?
- That's Elvis.
Elvis'?
That's what we call him.
You know, like the King'?
Soon as he showed up,
they all changed. They all fucking changed.
Like they found themselves a leader.
An alpha male.
- Where did it come from?
- I dorft fucking know.
We need to get closer,
find out vvhafs going on.
No, no, no, we oarTt. We oarTt.
- Hey. We need to find a Way.
- Fucking crazy.
We’re following Sarge in...
to try and get a better shot
ofthe Re-An army...
to show the world vvhafs happening in here.
This is crazy. We’re too close.
You said vve gotta show people.
- Yeah, but-
- Listen.
We shoot it all with one camera,
fight our way back to our APO.
You guys can broadcast from there, right?
Yeah, yeah. We can upload it.
Your APCJs too far. We'll never get there.
Then vve’|| go back to your hole and Wait
for the network teams.
There’s a catwalk up here.
You'll be able to see
everything from there.
All right, let's go.
- I'm gonna go get the shot.
- Bobby's getting the shot.
Shit.
There's thousands of 'em.
Bobby! No! Shit! Bobby!
On, no!
Bobby!
We gotta move. Go, go! Come on! Lefs move!
Shit!
Come on! Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Come on, come on!
Move it!
Come on! God!
Go, go, g0, 90, 9O, 9O, 9O!
Come on!
Head for the building right there!
They’re catching up!
Jimmy, Jimmy! Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Sarge! Easy out! Come on!
Sarge, easy out!
Oh, my God.
L_et's go!
In there.
Jesus.
There’s thousands of them.
This is it.
Outbreak Two.
I didrft think it’d come this fast.
Come on, Sarge. We can make it out of here.
Sarge.
I dorft know if anyone will ever see this.
But if you do...
I'm sorry.
- Sarge-
- Lefs go.
Come on.
Lefs go.
Oh, God.
It's like a lab.
That door downstairs is never gonna hold.
Why the hell haverft they eaten all this?
I dorft know.
- Oh! Hey. You okay?
- Yeah.
Oh, God!
Sarge!
Kill it!
Find us another Way out!
Oh, God! Push!
They’re getting in!
Go!
Sarge! Jimmy!
Look out!
Get off her! No!
Sarge!
Sarge, vve need help in here!
Hey!
Get off her!
Get off!
What was Jimmy like?
He was a great kid.
What keeps you going?
I mean, why you do this?
I do this so no other parent...
has to do What I did.
Do you ever think about dying?
When my day comes...
I finally get to go home.
Eve
Some religious scholars
believe that purgatory is a place...
for souls that are equally balanced
between good and evil...
and that your actions, they determine...
whether or not you will go
to heaven... or hell.
The jury’s out for you all.
'Cause you are corrupt...
by doing What you do with that lens.
But then you know that. God bless you.
We interrupt this program to bring you
breaking news from the Manhattan Barricade.
Sean Griffin is on the scene.
Mary, two weeks ago
we started getting reports...
of re-animate attacks in the subway.
And two days ago, they started coming up.
Yesterday, the entire downtown area
was placed under quarantine...
and the downtown barricade
here was erected.
But now it appears
a large group of re-animates...
is headed toward the barricade.
Early estimates of the numbers-
50,000 or more.
There’s no way of knowing
ifthe downtown barricade can hold.
It seems clear
that Outbreak Two is happening.
Mary, back to you.
Underground, this is Delta 5-16
requesting permission to land two Hawks.
- Oven
- 5-7-6, permission granted.
Welcome to the ark.
- Whafs happening?
- We got another radio call.
More survivors. They’re trapped.