[Music playing]
INTERVIEWER: So what
are we up to here?
We are about to go audition for
Troma Films "Toxic Avenger 4."
INTERVIEWER: And what's
your ideal situation here?
Well, to get the part of Toxie.
MAN: And why, exactly,
do you want to be Toxie?
Well, it's gonna
be a lot of fun.
[Laughs]
I know, [inaudible] to cry.
Yeah, crying.
This is the house of stupidity.
MAN: Oh, that
looks really great.
MAN: This is truly fucking art.
MAN: Fuckers.
MAN: By and large, the people
who work here are idiots.
And you can't complain about
it, because all you're doing
Is complaining to
the same idiots.
Fuck Troma.
MAN: Jesus Christ,
it's like Stupidville.
Seriously.
I don't want to waste my 160
IQ on this particular problem.
MAN: Fire in the hole.
MAN: God dammit.
Who's got a leaf rake?
Boom gets in my
frame one more time,
I'm gonna fuck
this place up, boy.
MAN: [inaudible] just
look at the fucking stuff
And be scared.
MAN: They don't care.
No, they just
don't fucking care.
MAN: This is ridiculous.
You're supposed to
stay in your line.
We may have a camera problem.
But I don't know about
it, and he's gonna
Shoot him right in the chest.
MAN: At the end of the film.
Anybody bring Toxie
to makeup, or are we--
INTERVIEWER: How's the
experience been so far, man?
It fucking sucks, man.
I suck!
Trent is totally losing
his mind on this set.
I'm the director.
I'm the boss.
Ah!
[Thud]
Ever since then, it's
all gone down hill.
[Gunfire]
[Explosion]
Well, now you're in
safe haven-- calm, quiet,
Relaxing Tromaville.
All your cares
just dissolve away.
INTERVIEWER: So do you have any
day number one, pre-first shot
Comments or thoughts?
[Motor whirring]
First shot comments, mm.
No, I'm looking forward
to "Citizen Toxie," right?
INTERVIEWER: Geoff, what
are you doing right now?
Well, here we have 800,000
pages of script revisions.
INTERVIEWER: All from yesterday?
Well, from the past
couple days, really, so.
Pretty soon the entire
script will be pink.
Script revisions.
Oh, nice.
Good, good.
MAN: Coffee?
No, thank you.
INTERVIEWER: How's it going
on the day number one?
It's going all right.
I would ask that you don't
come downstairs for today.
It's going OK.
I guess I'm supposed
to be the AD. [laugh]
INTERVIEWER: What's
happening downstairs?
We're getting Toxie
ready and Heidi ready.
It's costume and
makeup is down here.
But they're a little bit
proprietary about their area,
And maybe just for now.
You know, sometime we
want to get the Toxie
Makeup applied and stuff.
But not today, OK?
INTERVIEWER: OK.
All right.
Yeah, because you know
Gabe's rule of thumb
Is everything that you should
not do, you should get on tape.
But I--
-Yeah, yeah.
But it's--
INTERVIEWER: Yeah.
Dude, it's gonna
come down on me.
Then I'll have to
come down on you.
And I don't want to be
[inaudible] gonna have to.
OK?
WOMAN: Hi.
-Oh, hi.
-How's it going?
-Good.
How are you?
Good.
You look fresh as a daisy.
-Yeah.
-Good luck.
Thanks.
Only a few revisions
today, by the way.
This is all for your scene.
-I heard.
-We've got it all [inaudible].
-OK.
This is all you.
I didn't actually
get these yet.
-No, I'm kidding.
-Oh.
-Yeah, [inaudible].
Oh.
INTERVIEWER: So what's
happening today?
We're gonna shoot a scene, two
or three-- sex scene, woohoo!
Sure.
INTERVIEWER: So what's your
biggest fear about today?
Fear?
I have no fears.
INTERVIEWER: What's the
word of the day so far?
Uh, I think it seems very
tranquil and very pleasant--
A lot of people
standing around waiting,
Waiting, waiting for Toxie to
emerge, the new '90s Toxie.
Huh?
INTERVIEWER: How's it
going on day number one?
Oh, good.
INTERVIEWER: Are you excited?
Yeah, I'm really excited.
INTERVIEWER: All right, what's
your biggest hope for today?
Uh, I'm not that
ambitious, either.
MAN: I don't want a title.
No, no, you got-- you've got
to put them in the script.
WOMAN: Could be three hours.
These are revisions.
Oh, OK.
So you want notes in
the margin to go--
Page 18 replaces that page 18.
These are replacements.
Don't you have these?
I don't personally
have them, but these--
Oh, you should get them.
These are script revisions.
This 18 replaces that 18.
OK, so how do I know
which ones replace--
Just take-- just take the page.
Right?
You'll see the scene
numbers, right?
I don't think I follow you.
Do you want--
Could be the-- what
you do is, let's say--
What's the first page here?
Page one.
All right, so do I
have a page one there?
Yes.
OK, so you take
out that page one.
[Chatter]
You take out page one.
Then you put page one in, see?
Oh, so anything with
notes in the margins.
No, no.
Any pink sheet,
that's a revision.
That replaces the white sheets.
Pink is more
important than white.
So you take out-- you see?
This is page one.
Right, so now page one, i
principal, we will not use,
Except I have notes on it.
So then this is page two.
So page two-- it's
a new page two.
You see?
It's actually-- it
looks the same to me.
It's not the same.
It may look the same, but
there'll be differences.
It's like "Sesame Street."
You know, it's like
one of those quizzes
Where you have to
see what's different.
So there's something in here
that either I or somebody made.
So you will find
a change in here.
That's what these are all about.
OK.
But because there's
how many right now?
Look, look, right here.
Here's the change.
See?
-OK.
-That's different.
You see?
You see "Tex smashes
the teacher in the face
With the back of the book."
That was added.
That's not in the first thing.
So you take this away.
In principal, we're
gonna throw that way.
And you replace--
there's a new page two.
OK.
So you don't want the
whole script to be pink.
No.
No, these are revisions.
You just want certain--
These are revisions.
Every time you do revisions,
you do a different color.
Now, page four,
you take another--
Take that old page four.
OK, this is pa-- oh, OK.
-See?
-These don't have-- OK, I see.
At least-- no, you don't see.
No, I do see.
This is omitting certain pages.
No, it's not omitting anything.
The whole idea is that
when this says page four,
This is now page four.
It's going to be pink.
We don't like white page four.
MAN: Right here.
So you take out that.
A racial thing.
[Laugh]
Pink is better than white.
So that's all it is is
a matter of-- pulling
The sheets out in
this program cuts them
So that the lines are the same.
Oh, OK.
That's perfect.
And everything
should be all right.
So the idea is that this-- this
color-- slowly, every time you
Do revisions, you do a different
color, so that way people know.
And you ought to
be getting them.
If you're an AD,
you should get them.
-All right.
-OK.
So now you know what to do.
Now you take seven, and you
put seven where seven is.
Go to a table, though.
Do you want me to
deliver this to you?
Yes, hand it to me as
soon as you're done.
Yeah.
Sit at a table, though, because
it's-- maybe sit at a nice,
Comfortable table, one of
the beautiful German tables.
Double check that the script
is tasked with the [inaudible].
TRENT: Yes, yes.
I will make sure that-- I
think it's pretty damn simple.
You take out page four and
replace another page four.
Yeah, I would think so.
Yeah, I will
double check that--
And the reason why they're pink
is so that we know that those
Are the revised pages.
-Exactly.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: We should
start shooting soon, though.
Yes, sir.
We will be ready for a costume
rehearsal in about 20 minutes.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK.
What's that?
INTERVIEWER: I'm a
little bit unclear on how
These script revisions work.
Oh. [laugh] You're
trying to annoy me.
You're trying to get me going.
And I'm gonna be calm and cool.
Needles and pins,
pins and needles
Makes us-- whatever Jackie
Gleason said, that's me.
I don't see any changes.
That was the best part.
"Looks the same to me."
It was great.
I made a prediction
as of yesterday,
Which is OK, that we would
be-- that first shot would
Be up by 10:30.
Now, what do you
think about that?
It's 8:30 now.
And I'll tell you, we're
still in mad makeup,
And no one knows what
the fuck's going on.
It's 10:30?
Yeah, yeah.
It's 10:30, and
tomorrow's a big day.
What's happening out there?
Um, basically special
effects is five minutes away.
And then they have 10
minutes of work to do.
They're putting the final
touches on Toxie's arms.
Well, tell them,
so they get out
Of there when the actors come.
Let's get ready.
You got to tell your crew, too.
TRENT HAAGA: Yes.
That was if you got-- well,
how many minutes would you say?
TRENT HAAGA: I would say--
-Just tell them.
Tell them.
You got to say-- you
got to yell it out.
Eight minutes.
Six minutes.
All said, we got
about 10 more minutes
Till we'll have our actors on
set for a camera rehearsal.
OK?
MAN: Thank you.
Awesome.
I would like to be
shooting right now.
I can't believe that we're not.
I will always wait for makeup.
Yeah, did you get that?
INTERVIEWER: Yup.
You have revisions?
You have the pink sheets?
MAN: I gave them to [inaudible].
Well, why don't you
have them in your script?
MAN: No, that way
this rests for you.
You're the script boy, man.
Go get them.
Jesus Christ.
It's like Stupidville.
Seriously.
Geoff, did nobody
tell you how to do it?
You're supposed to
be following the text.
Right, I got--
So how are you gonna
follow it if you
Don't have the revisions?
This scene hasn't--
Doesn't matter.
You don't know that.
I'm made changes this morning.
Right.
Yeah, I need those.
-Go.
You've got to get-- yeah, well
you should be getting them.
You should get them.
Yep.
Shit, that's what
it's all about.
That's what the pink
papers are there for.
Go.
Trent, this is fucked up.
The script guy doesn't
have the revisions.
How is he gonna be script guy?
He doesn't have
them in his book.
He's got to be reading them
so that we don't fuck up this.
Someone's got to keep track
that we're doing the dialogue.
TRENT HAAGA: Could
you repeat that?
You should have them.
Everyone should have
the fucking scripts.
This was nuts.
I hope the actors have it.
WOMAN: All right, got my own.
We're gonna get out
there on toxic speed.
[Footsteps]
[Chatter]
MAN: Awesome.
MAN: Oh, man.
[Clapping]
MAN: Here comes
the Toxic Avenger!
[Cheering and applause]
MAN: Uh-huh.
Hi, Toxic.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK, let's go.
Let's go.
Call it.
Let's go!
Start rehearsing!
Jesus Christ.
It's fucking 11 o'clock.
MAN: Lights.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Go [inaudible].
MAN: Lights up, George.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Let's go!
Let's go!
Do a master on the beautiful
lovemaking, fornicating.
And then we'll go into
the-- we'll cover it.
Then we'll cover it.
And then we'll
deal with the food.
INTERVIEWER: What's the
word of the morning?
There isn't one yet.
It's been too hairy
to have a word.
It's, uh-- I've been given
incorrect information,
So I've been late.
And ever since then,
it's all gone downhill.
OK, here we go.
Standing by.
This has to be the
most erotic scene
That has ever been filmed in the
history of man and womankind.
[Moan]
[Moaning]
Oh!
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Cut!
We got the-- the
breast isn't coming
Off, which is why you should
always rehearse with costumes.
You should rehearse with them.
And I've been
saying it for weeks.
Rehearse with costumes.
'Cause now we're
Having a major problem.
We'll cut this thing down.
TRENT HAAGA: No,
I'm starting down.
I'm starting at off.
All right.
You know what I mean?
That's the--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Well,
just tell her that.
TRENT HAAGA: Oh, yeah.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: So she knows.
TRENT HAAGA: She knows.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK.
Yeah, yeah.
That's what you gotta do.
You've got to rehearse
with everything.
This is gonna be the bane
of this production is
That nothing's been looked at.
I've been saying
it for eight weeks.
I should've looked
at every effect.
at every costume.
Every scene should've
been rehearsed in costume.
You know, now we're
paying the penalty.
Keep your hand away from--
just pull the dress down.
Take your--
-[panting]
There you go.
OK, we'll continue it
from there, please.
But can you bring it-- can
you get out of that thing,
In terms of the-- just
pull the thing down.
All the way down?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yeah, get
your arm out of there.
Yeah, but I can't pull
it back up afterwards.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yeah,
well, you will.
We'll cut, and you'll
have [inaudible].
To pull it back up.
-Yeah.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Just
for this scene, so we--
Sure.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: All right.
So let's pick it up from here.
OK.
TRENT HAAGA: Uh,
bring your dress down.
Yeah, right to your underwear.
Thanks.
INTERVIEWER: So
Lloyd, how'd that go?
Uh, we're getting there.
It's starting to happen.
The magic, the true magic,
is slowly starting to happen.
Yeah.
CREW: 15, Charlie, Take one.
[Beep]
CREW: Mark it.
-Mark.
[Clap]
CREW: One second, please.
Holding, and ready, Lloyd.
Action.
[Gasp] [moaning]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Right arm down.
Left arm back, Toxie.
[Moaning]
CREW: No, it's not--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Cut.
When I tell you there's
noise, there's noise.
What you have to do is
you don't go to him.
You go to me.
I say there's too
much noise outside.
If your people are
making the noise,
You've got to lock up the set.
You've got to shut them up.
That's your job.
You don't go to Evan
and say, is it OK?
Because that's what
schlock is all about.
Schlock is accepting
noise on your soundtrack.
Now, we're gonna have plenty
of noise on the soundtrack.
And we're gonna accept
plenty of dogs barking.
But the PA's
yapping and slamming
Doors we don't have to accept.
I'm intending to perhaps
do it like "Toxic 1."
MAN: That's what I thought--
-But don't--
That's what I had in my mind.
But don't-- assume
we're using his.
Absolutely.
I'm assuming we are.
But, like, that's also
in the back of my mind.
[Inaudible] Toxie, too.
Trent, is Jesse standing by
with that, um, Bromo grain stuff
And the Rosco smoke machine?
Is somebody still getting
the Bromo-Seltzer?
Why don't we have
that Bromo-Seltzer?
I don't get it.
What, they don't
have Bromo-Seltzer?
That was two days ago.
We're doing a "Toxic
Avenger" movie.
Trent!
TRENT HAAGA: Yes, sir!
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Are
they still getting it?
TRENT HAAGA: Yeah.
CAT SARREAL: Yes,
they're coming back.
Yes, they are coming back.
With Bromo-Seltzer.
CAT SARREAL: Yes.
TRENT HAAGA: It better
not be Alka-Seltzer.
Where's the fucking
Jared, right?
Hey, Trent.
Having the PAs in the car
doesn't do you any good.
Where-- do they know
where they're going?
I told them just to
get green food coloring
And then Bromo-Seltzer.
I didn't tell them
what store to go to.
OK, well, that's
what you have to do.
See, that's why
I'm the director.
Where is Jared?
Let's get Jared here.
Let's have Jared come
to the set, I guess.
I don't know to get out of it.
This is a "Toxic Avenger" movie,
and we don't have any Bromo
And vegetable coloring.
Now, you guys should be telling
me what else we don't have,
When I make like a list
of-- each day, I should--
This is not good.
You should, like, give
me a-- like, tomorrow,
If we're not gonna have
guys heads getting squashed.
Ah, good.
All right.
Have it standing by with the
green vegetable dye, please.
[Chatter]
Now, we're gonna do
a shot at the end,
With the close-up
of Toxie, where
He's doing his Bromo and green.
TRENT HAAGA: All right.
Thank you.
Also, we're gonna need the
Bromo-Seltzer on this shot,
Folks, on this angle.
Just have all the Bromo
standing by, folks.
TRENT HAAGA: I got the Bromo.
OK, he's putting the
Bromo in everybody.
Let's--
But maybe take a shit load
so it forces itself out.
Take a lot more.
OK.
Take a huge amount, and
then it'll kind of force you.
You'll find that
it'll will almost--
It'll build up so you almost--
This is about
quantity, not quality.
MAN: That's self-evident.
MAN: Is it green?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK,
everybody be quiet, please.
This is a very, very
difficult acting thing.
CREW: Toxie.
CREW: Yeah, ready.
CREW: Come a little bit closer.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: You better
turn the camera on!
CREW: Yeah, I've got it.
It's rolling.
It's OK.
Go for it.
Head up a little bit more.
Excellent, nice.
[Camera shutter clicking]
Yeah.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Look up more.
Head up more.
CREW: Excellent.
CREW: Oh, that's nice.
Cut.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK, good.
Beautiful.
Thank you.
Please clean up Toxie.
[Applause]
Bravo.
Thank you, Toxie.
TRENT HAAGA: You
are the screen's
Definition of beautiful, Lloyd.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Well,
you are beautiful.
So are we going straight to
the kitchen shots after this?
I guess so.
Uh, no.
Actually, [belch]
Is there more?
Oh, oh, we're
doing the fantasy.
Yeah.
And then the--
(SINGING) It's all part
of my Fabio fantasy.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: So the idea is
to get-- you have Sarah's eyes
After they've just
had the huge orgasm.
And she says, "Toxie, the most
beautiful person in the world."
And then you cut, and there's a
close-up of-- instead of Toxie,
It's Joe Anthony.
What's the next scene?
TRENT HAAGA: Uh,
it's fucking Joseph
Anthony, Toxie fantasy guy.
[Slurping] Bad idea.
Really bad idea.
Yeah.
Stupid idea.
I mean, besides green vomit.
Uh-huh.
[Sigh]
[Inaudible].
[Slurping]
What the hell was that?
[Slurp]
Uh.
INTERVIEWER: So, big man.
What's up?
INTERVIEWER: Tell us
about your first morning
In a feature film.
As the lead?
INTERVIEWER: Yeah.
Um.
It's been busy, very busy.
I have absolutely no idea
how it could be possibly
Be too something or near to.
INTERVIEWER: So it's
been very traumatic?
Oh, yeah. [slurp]
Yup.
Yes, indeed.
BRAM LEWIS: It was today?
Uh, today was good.
Day one.
Pshew.
In the bag.
[Sigh]
-[sigh]
It was a little weird.
I'm still getting used to Lloyd.
But, uh--
--[laughs] And his
type of direction.
Yeah.
And his changing things,
like, all the time.
He's constantly changing.
And I had several guys
come up to me today
Afterwards and say, wow, man.
I knew you were big.
And I knew, you
know, you could do
The stick stuff
and all that stuff
And the stunt work and all that.
But I didn't know you could act.
INTERVIEWER: [laughs]
A bunch of people
were like, are you
An actor, like professionally?
And one guy came up and he
said, I've been a fan of Troma--
He's, like, you know,
20 or something.
He's like, I've been a fan of
Troma since I was, like, five.
And he said, I've
seen all the movies.
And you're the best Toxie ever.
Wow.
So that was cool to hear.
[Applause and cheering]
Yahoo.
I can't believe you're here.
Is there anything that's,
like, not-- just, I
Mean, your instinct
will guide you, period.
Is there anything that's,
like-- if there's anything
That you want to talk over
at any point, just, you know,
Don't hesitate.
Yeah.
Everything changes all the time.
So, um--
We're doing the
retarded school scene.
We got to keep it
on the low-down,
Because we're actually at a
school for special students.
So we don't want
to offend anyone.
MAN: (SARCASTICALLY)
I'm working here!
Don't make up the
special children.
They should look
sweaty and disgusting.
INTERVIEWER: So how
does it feel to actually
Be a part of a Troma movie?
Oh, it's incredible.
It's a dream come true.
I just hope I get killed.
ACTOR: Pretty smooth.
It's a little hot
and muggy in here.
But, well, that's
filmmaking, I guess.
No big deal.
If you don't like
it, then you probably
Shouldn't be here, so--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: We're
shooting now, correct?
Yeah.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK, come on.
Come on.
Let's go.
Hey!
There's a little
schmutz in the gate.
Can we do it again?
OK, all right.
Everybody back into position.
Did you clean it yet?
Have you cleaned it yet?
Yeah, I have.
And is it hot in here?
Let me ask you.
INTERVIEWER: I
think it's pretty--
DEBBIE ROCHON: There's no air.
I think the air-- we
finished using all of the air
Maybe three hours ago.
See this strip right here,
these blue lines right there?
INTERVIEWER: Yeah.
Right, when you get the
diaper, they're yellow.
And then they're supposed to
turn blue as an indication
When you've urinated
in your diaper.
But I've also found out that
it turns blue if your testicles
Sweat excessively.
I guess we're working
up to the point
Where something really
bad is gonna happen.
MAN: Hold on.
Hold on.
Can you hold on, please?
I may have a little
technical problem.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK, hold on.
MAN: Hold on please.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Don't
leave yet, folks, 'cause
We may have a camera problem.
OK, we are going to
break for one half hour
For lunch-- granted,
if the camera is OK.
If not, we'll retake
this last thing.
Ready, action!
ACTOR: Teach?
Teach?
What's the fucking
point in trying to teach
These soap heads, lady?
[Laughs]
[Chatter]
Get him!
Cut!
Good.
OK, excellent.
Super, super.
Very good.
Bravo.
Terrific.
2 o'clock, and
we still-- maybe.
I don't now.
I thought we were not being
too ambitious for today.
MAN: Hey, what are we on?
Like, page two?
We have like eight.
Yeah, we're going very slowly.
It's been slow.
Everything is OK.
It's just we're a little
behind on the shots.
My actors are great.
They're sitting here.
They're being quiet.
They're getting it in one take.
It's just the set-ups
are so effing slow.
I can't stand it.
We'll never get eight
pages today at this rate.
There was this situation
where one of the diaper mafia
Spilt some milk all over my
face in a very sexual manner.
It was very disturbing.
Got milk, fucking retard?
LISA TEREZAKIS: It was very,
very, very similar to someone
Ejaculating all over me.
But it was a milk
bottle with milk.
Mommy!
Borderline, borderline pushing
the envelope, if you ask me.
But it was all in
the name of art.
[Chatter]
Hey, Zork, what's
going on, man?
INTERVIEWER: How is
day number two going?
It's exciting stuff, but I'm
really, uh-- what happened, Zo?
I got a call from
Gabe a couple days ago.
Oh, Gabe told you
to say it, huh?
That's what Lloyd told him.
Oh, Gabe lied to you, man.
But then I talked to
Pat, and Pat agreed.
Well, yeah.
They both-- Gabe and
Pat wants you to say.
Lloyd don't care.
He said it would
be better without.
People make decisions
without Lloyd around here.
That's what happens.
I'm good if you want
to put it back. [laughs]
I like it.
I like the look, man.
You look younger.
I just didn't want
to do the hair thing.
You know, only because
of growing out.
Something like these
things, which wash out,
But this, the dye
wouldn't wash out.
TRENT HAAGA: No, no.
And that's fundamentally
what it is, man.
Those guys-- this isn't
"Masters of Light."
It's about retarded
kids and guys
In diapers with machine guns.
It needn't have perfect
kick lights and whatever.
And we're back.
We're back from lunch.
Fuck this man.
I've had it.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Cut.
It went soft.
MAN: Something went--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yeah the
camera turned off, too.
INTERVIEWER: What's
happening right now?
They're having camera trouble,
so we're standing here.
This happens every
hundred thousand miles.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yeah, right.
OK.
It had to happen today, though.
MAN: What's up?
I don't know.
I've never heard or
seen this happen before.
I don't know.
It's one of the belts.
It's not working right.
It sounds like we
are quite fucked.
MAN: Don't do [inaudible].
INTERVIEWER: Right, yeah.
All right.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: I told everybody.
Keep all your acting
going, because it's
Very improvisational.
And we're sort of moving around,
since you never know when
The camera's gonna be on you.
So please keep up
the performance.
Hopefully, we will
have a camera.
No, I got a bit of a problem.
WOMAN: Do you know if we
can use the other one?
Yeah, we can use
this other one.
It's noisy, though.
But that's the option right now.
We're fucked.
It could be the end of the film.
INTERVIEWER: Why?
Can't do it without a camera.
Can't shoot it
all without sound,
Unless we do a silent movie.
What do we do?
I made arrangements
for somebody to pick up
Another body in New York City.
Can you send somebody from
your office to go down there?
-Oh, my god.
-So it's-- yeah.
We're fucked.
I mean, I'm gonna work
on the camera myself.
Yeah.
But I want to make this
arrangement before something
Closes for Labor Day.
Yeah.
Unless Brendan fixes
the camera, we'll be MOS.
And then there's another camera
body coming from New York.
Wow.
Let's just keep
going with the scene.
We'll get as much of the scene
as we can without dialogue.
CREW: Rolling?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Roll.
Action lighting.
[Camera whirring]
Cut.
Fuck it.
It's absolutely fucked up.
Totally fucked.
All right.
Come back.
It's just this-- it's very wide.
My head hurts.
It really, really hurts.
INTERVIEWER: Why does it hurt?
What happened to you?
I was assaulted by a breast.
Belladonna will push
her out of the way
And flap her with her heavies.
Does Belladonna know that?
TRENT HAAGA: Yes, I--
Why don't you go and
just tell Belladonna?
Go in the back and tell
her what to do, please.
So he wants you to do
redo your entire film.
We're gonna [inaudible]
poor, little retarded--
Is that all I am
is a pair of tits?
No.
We'll get your face
in there somehow.
[Laughs]
Yeah, yeah.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: And run through.
Action.
That's it, good.
OK, perfect.
All right.
Do a still take.
[Chatter]
This is art, man.
This is truly fucking art.
It is definitely a Troma day.
TJ knows this is art, man.
I didn't think it would hurt.
But then I thought, well,
that was the last time.
And then it happened again,
but it was even more painful.
So when you see-- if it's
on the film-- my face,
That's not acting.
That was real.
I was in pain.
Nobody's been trained in breast
combat before, I don't think.
So they didn't know
how to fake it.
And the girl just went sick.
I mean, I had a
headache the whole day.
She was just sick.
She was, like, going sick.
I don't know.
Letting out some steam, I guess,
some frustration or something.
[Panting]
What's the word of the morning?
Um, ugh.
[Grumble]
INTERVIEWER: So what's
been happening on set?
I'm not happy.
INTERVIEWER: Why?
I don't mind working hard.
I don't mind the long hours.
I don't mind, you know,
sitting in the hot room
With people who don't know
what the hell they're doing.
They keep doing the same
thing over and over again.
How about, like, invest
a little more money
And get a second camera?
Hello?
INTERVIEWER: Right.
I mean, I wasn't
born yesterday.
And this just looks
like-- well, you guys have
Been around for a long time.
What's going on, man?
INTERVIEWER: I'm not--
Take some of that money
you made from the past films
Or whatever.
And I'm sure they're
raking in the dough.
Take some of it and reinvest
it in a better production,
And maybe you'll get
a better product.
Maybe somebody will start
taking you seriously.
Because, you know,
half the people I asked
Have never heard of Troma.
I don't want another
part that involves me
Beating people up with my tits.
I mean, I can do that in
the stuff that I've done,
Which pays.
INTERVIEWER: Yeah.
I mean, this is almost like
the pornos that I've done,
Which is mostly girl-girl
and fetish and S&M
Stuff, which pays
really, really good
And is really, really easy.
I've already had this
kind of exposure.
I wanted some legitimate, like,
acting exposure, you know.
And now the whole world
knows me as this ditzy bimbo
Who can't act.
And I can act.
They didn't ask me
to have a monologue.
They just asked me to come in,
and be myself, and do my thing,
And do what I do, whatever.
And I did a little striptease.
And I jumped on one of the
guys who was on the couch,
And I beat him up with my tits.
INTERVIEWER: Right.
And that was just
something that came to mind.
I figured let me shock
them a little bit.
There's not much
else I could say.
Lloyd just treats me like
a dumb bimbo, and I'm not.
And my feelings are hurt.
And I don't think I'm
coming back, so there.
INTERVIEWER: So what
happened with the--
What's up with the
status of the camera now?
Yeah, yeah.
We got the new camera
brought in and set up here.
And it's right here, big
and beautiful, ready to go.
Hey, there.
INTERVIEWER: What's the
word of the day so far?
Word of the day is relaxed.
I had the day off yesterday,
and I enjoyed that.
And they don't need
me for a while yet,
So we took a really long
time to get the makeup on.
Just took our time,
no rush, no fuss.
Nobody continually coming
in to see what was going on
And how soon it would be
done and all that stuff.
So it was cool.
INTERVIEWER: A little bit
different than day number one,
Eh?
Very different, yeah.
Can we just like put
the squibs at some point?
And then have-- just like sort
of put them back in the scene,
And just leave them on
there for a little while?
No.
You've got to just
put them on and do it?
OK.
I mean, you have one shirt
of each for each person?
No, we have more.
You have one extra.
Right now we have
one extra shirt.
One extra shirt.
Total.
Like, we have all
of these people--
You have one total
shirt, or one extra shirt?
I'm sorry.
These are all the shirts, right?
Uh-huh.
MAN: That equals five shirts.
I have one more
that's not being used
By a character in the scene.
CRAIG: You mean one
for each person?
No.
Just one more shirt.
Yeah.
Then we can't do it.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Can I have
someone slightly intelligent?
They can go to
some store to buy--
I mean, here's the deal, man.
We don't need them to
be the exact same shade.
We don't care, as
long as they're green
And they got loops and
you can iron some shit on.
I don't know.
Is Nives dressing
people right now?
No, she's not, man.
I need her to fucking--
She's dyeing shirts right now.
She's dyeing.
Oh, man.
They're going to have
to dry those shirts.
We need them today, you know?
45 minutes.
And we need them
sooner than that.
We literally have
to go to any store.
You have to ask yourself
what's more important,
Like guarding our equipment
or sending out green shirts?
I'm sorry.
We're working the best I
can, we just don't have
The fucking people to do it.
We can have extras do it.
That might be a good idea.
Are we going to
be able to shoot?
You have six shirts.
Because you remember--
We still be able to
wardrobe the classroom
After the squibbing?
Once the shirts back, I just
have to put on some type.
And then--
Now, who went to get
the shirts? 'Cause
It seems like they went,
like, four or five hours ago.
No, they came back.
They couldn't find them.
And then they came back
and asked them what to do.
And I told them to
get white shirts
And I would just dye
them, because it's
Just a dunk in green.
That's all it is.
And then just stick them in
a dryer, and they're done.
Who did you send?
How long ago?
Two PAs.
They probably left
20 minutes ago.
They should be back any minute.
-Oh, it's hopeless.
OK.
NIEVES: OK?
It's hopeless.
INTERVIEWER: So what's just--
what are you doing right now?
The shirts that we
bought originally
Had blue collars on them.
But we can't find
those shirts again.
So now we have to
paint the blue rings
Around the collars and stuff.
INTERVIEWER: Is that fun?
No.
But the squibs are
condoms filled with blood
With a protective padding
to protect the skin,
And a explosive on
top of the padding.
Then the shirt is
scored and glued back
Together what toilet paper.
It's an electric wire
goes out the back.
You hook it up to a
battery-powered thing,
Press a button, and bam.
[Chatter]
Who needs squibs?
You, you, you.
You need a squib?
Yeah.
The squibs are 10 minutes off.
There still are no green shirts.
And so-- but the
squibs-- so I think
By the time you finish
wacking in the balls,
Then we'll be ready for squibs.
You know, we're just
on the third day,
Too, so I'm reserving judgment.
But it's definitely-- it's
a little-- little fucked up.
If you're on props, have
the props already there.
If we're shooting something,
have everything there.
If it's costumes, they're there.
Props, they're there.
Whatever it is, try to think
ahead and have it there.
TRENT HAAGA: OK, everybody's--
We shouldn't have to remember
there's a stick in the scene.
You guys should be
ahead of the game.
Please be ahead of the game.
Same with the actors.
The AD department should
have the bloody actors here.
OK.
Let's run the--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: We're
filming, right?
We shouldn't-- how
are we gonna remember?
And script boy, script
boy, please remember this.
Tell us you're
missing assistants.
You're missing the stick.
And whatever it is
you're missing, tell us.
OK, Geoff?
So--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: We've been doing
-OK.
This is the third day.
And it's the same--
we are not learning.
We are not learning.
We're not getting better.
We should get better.
TRENT HAAGA: We're trying
to speed up, though.
We got everything.
We have all our props.
We should be thinking ahead.
We are not thinking ahead.
TRENT HAAGA: OK.
Now, for example, is
there not gonna be blood?
Is the blood boy
here with the blood?
There's no blood yet, Lloyd.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Well, there
may be blood, though.
Think ahead.
Have it standing
by so we don't have
To stop and ask for the blood.
TRENT HAAGA: Everyone
in the room--
Think ahead.
That's all I'm suggesting.
You are absolutely
right, Lloyd.
Can we do the take?
Can we rehearse?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yes.
-Thank you.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Rehearse
it in slow motion.
OK.
Trent-- Trent and
I will survive.
The rest will go down in flames.
About that classroom scene--
So it's up to you.
Whatever you want to do.
Just get out of here and go do
some shots and clear your head.
All right.
--[inaudible] you're
starting to crack up, man.
You're out of control.
TRENT HAAGA: I got to just
get out of this diaper.
Change your fucking diaper.
TRENT HAAGA: Let me
get out of this diaper.
I mean, by and large, people
who work here are idiots.
And you can't complain about
it, because all you're doing
Is complaining to the
same idiots, you know?
INTERVIEWER: Lloyd.
Yo.
INTERVIEWER: What's the
word of the day so far?
It's a total waste,
that's what that it is.
We said if we have a
squib man and a gun
Man who get thousands of
dollars, and the day is over.
So we've wasted a lot
of times, and they're
Being paid for all that time.
And we haven't done one
squib or one bullet.
So it's totally fucked up.
It's very fucked up.
Now we're in
[inaudible] total, you
Know-- I hate to use the word
stupidity, but it's stupidity.
Incompetence, maybe
that's better.
Stupidity, sloth.
INTERVIEWER: And what's your
other problem this morning?
Yo.
OK, squibs are ready.
So we'll do it right
after this shot.
Maybe we should rehearse it.
There's nothing to rehearse.
The stunt man'll
come in and do it.
MAN: Let's rehearse
the cues, please.
The rehearsal only.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: And action.
You're so--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: [inaudible].
Blood.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Good.
OK, cool.
There will be fire number
one, then fire number two.
OK, meanwhile, you keep
those things going.
Standing by.
First action, then duck.
Then fire one.
Ready?
OK, I'm rolling camera.
WOMAN: And we're rolling.
BRENDAN FLYNT: And speed.
Roll camera B, please.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Roll B.
BRENDAN FLYNT: B!
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Action.
Action!
Duck!
Duck.
Fire one.
[Gunshots]
BRENDAN FLYNT: Oh,
so B is-- back up.
Back up.
LLOYD KAUFMAN:
Fire two-- oh, cut.
MAN: Cut!
Cut!
[Shouting]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Fire two!
MAN: Cut.
[Gunshot]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Cut.
Good, OK.
[Clapping]
It looked good, bravo.
[Applause]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: But he wasn't
supposed to fall down.
He was supposed to
wait for [inaudible].
BRENDAN FLYNT: If
he falls down--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: So
you got nothing?
BRENDAN FLYNT: The cut.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: So you
didn't get anything?
TRENT HAAGA: You got
it, right, Lloyd?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: I got it.
MAN: Yeah, you got it.
TRENT HAAGA: All right, well.
MAN: We were waiting the
fire number two, right?
-Yeah, that's right.
-Yeah.
LLOYD KAUFMAN:
'Cause he went down.
He shouldn't have gone.
He didn't listen.
MAN: But then you
yelled cut, Lloyd.
You guys did not listen.
[inaudible] fire number two.
MAN: Lloyd.
--thing to fire.
MAN: Well, 'cause
he didn't feel--
I don't know what he did.
It's pretty funky.
Silly German guy fell
too soon, you know?
That's why they don't make many
movies in Germany, I guess.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Listen
for your number.
[Chatter]
Camera A.
-Whoa, whoa.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Oh, I'm sorry.
Blood.
MAN: Hold on.
MAN: Brendan, too.
MAN: OK.
We're ready.
BRENDAN FLYNT: OK, I'm rolling
camera A, and I've got speed.
MAN: Run camera B.
BRENDAN FLYNT: Rolling
B. Go ahead, guys.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Action!
[Gunshots]
1, 2, 3, 4!
[Inaudible]
[Gunshots]
Cut.
[Chatter]
INTERVIEWER: What's
been happening here?
We're getting shot.
But they're just plastic
bullets and shattering.
It's just plastic.
Only at 130 miles an hour.
It's not gonna hurt us.
It's like embedded in my skin.
Do you want to see?
I have two pieces of clothing
on, and it hit my arm.
Really gross.
Look, look-- this crap.
Look at this.
Look at that.
It hurts.
It hurts bad.
INTERVIEWER: So what's
on the slate for today?
Waiting till they need me.
INTERVIEWER: And then what?
That I don't know.
I go by the call sheet.
First thing I'm
officially listed for
Is a scene I'm not in.
So we'll see what's
up with that.
And if we skip that scene, the
next scene that I'm officially
Listed for is at 7:00 PM, so.
I got here at 6:30 AM, and
it's quarter after 12:00.
Do you know how much it costs
to get a fucking handgun?
It's 200 bucks.
And you got to pay some guy
to come and fucking show
You how to use it.
INTERVIEWER: Mr. Wilkeban?
No, not Wilkeban.
This guy's name
is Rick Washburn.
INTERVIEWER: Oh, yeah, yeah.
I think he changed
it from Dick.
But he-- he and I don't
get along too well.
We have the best gun
guy and the best guns.
But unfortunately, we
could only afford one day.
We had our first major,
major effects scene today,
And it was a shooting.
And it was fucked up by the guy
who brought the guns, the guy
Who brought the firing guns.
And it was one of these guys
that Lloyd has always said,
He's so professional.
And he's so good.
And blah, blah, blah, you know.
But Rick Washburn did
a very-- he's the best.
He did "Troma's War" and came
up with some great ideas.
Fucking winds up
totally wasting our time
And our film and our
fucking-- half our day
With just dicking
around, you know,
And taking up our valuable,
like, cars and shit
Like that, to pick him up.
So you see, Washburn's day
started at-- to be picked up
At-- I think he was supposed
to be picked up at 8:00
Or something.
So we started
paying him at 8:00.
I guess.
Or 6:00.
I don't know.
Whenever they gave him the call.
I mean, he didn't
show up on time.
They sent the wrong car.
They sent a car that
didn't-- he and his assistant
And the things wouldn't fit.
That fucking guy.
When John picked him up,
his car was too small
For two guys and a gun.
Big enough for
one guy and a gun,
But not for two guys and a gun.
Why do they need two guys?
I don't know.
Because he had to
bring his fucking kid.
He brought his fucking kid to
the thing, to a Troma movie.
Then they sent another car.
Aha.
So now he's pretty
much-- his day is over.
And is he en route?
-I don't know.
-Or is he back in New York?
My guess is that
he will get here,
And then it will
be time to go home.
His day is over. [inaudible]
been ready since 6:00.
So when he gets here,
his day will be over.
So you have to send him back.
-All right.
Lloyd?
MAN: This is their position.
What you may want to do is--
you said you want to do four,
And then shoot [inaudible].
That's right.
MAN: OK, so--
TRENT HAAGA: Come here.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: So we'll have
two a little bit off to the side
And four in the center.
INTERVIEWER: What's the deal?
Dude.
I don't know how to
deal with him sometimes.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Let's try this.
A big mess.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Brendan,
how much time do you think?
Both physically and mentally,
it's been a big mess.
INTERVIEWER: Is this the first
time you've been involved
In such a traumatic experience?
Um, as far as Troma, yes.
This is the first time I've
been involved with Troma,
As far as working on sets now.
I'm probably like
the worst person
To be talking to right now.
My brain is completely dead.
INTERVIEWER: How does Troma
compare with normal production?
No comment.
INTERVIEWER: Hey, Rick Washburn.
Hey, Lloyd, how you doing?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: How you doing?
Welcome.
This is Rick
Washburn, everybody.
[Cheering]
You have to listen.
You have to follow instructions.
What we're going to do with
these weapons can be dangerous.
We're going to keep it
from being dangerous.
And that means you pay attention
and you listen to what I say.
Blanks can hurt you
at very close range.
Safety's number one
in these scenes.
When you hear "cut," whoever has
a gun, put the gun in the air.
Stay where you are.
I will come to you, and we'll
prepare for the next scene.
Does anybody have
any questions at all?
OK.
Something to add, Rick.
If you have one
of the guns which
Are not Rick's, treat them
exactly the same as Rick's.
When cut happens, they
also go in the air,
So every gun in the
room is in the air,
Just so there's no
confusion with anybody else.
The gun we'll be firing
will be an M60 machine gun.
It's belt fed.
Word of today?
Let's see.
I have on-- the sound
guy has ear plugs
That have been cut in half,
for a big, huge M60 machine
Gun that he has to listen
to through a high-power
Microphone.
I think the word for
today is "cheap."
[Chatter]
OK, everybody ready?
Fire in the hole.
[Gunshots]
MAN: OK.
That's what you're gonna get.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Do everything--
What's that?
They're gonna shoot an M60 at a
kid and hopefully not kill him.
As a matter of fact, as
soon as you pass his plane
And he's down, stop firing.
MAN: I'm not going
up against the wall.
RICK WASHBURN: Oh, whoa, whoa.
Do you see?
We can't do this, guys.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Hold it.
I thought you were going down.
MAN: I'm going against the wall.
That's what they told me.
RICK WASHBURN: Well,
OK, who told you that?
MAN: Uh, the effects guy and
me, we choreographed that--
All right, here's
what we have to do.
We have to choreograph together.
You guys can't come in
choreographed by yourselves.
We just told him that
he was gonna go down
And we were sweeping across.
If you come behind and
tell him to stand up
And I don't know
about it, he's gonna
Shoot him right in the chest.
We cannot do that in
this kind of thing.
We have to work together.
INTERVIEWER: Is
Troma well-insured?
Oh, yeah.
But this poor
bastard has no idea.
They just said-- the gun guy
just said if he does this,
He's gonna get his
brains blown out.
I saw the kid go--
BRENDAN FLYNT: Lloyd,
roll your camera, please.
RICK WASHBURN: Hold
the gun steady.
That's the important thing.
WOMAN: Standing by, and--
MAN: Rolling.
WOMAN: We're rolling.
BRENDAN FLYNT: One second.
[Camera whirring]
MAN: Speed, ready.
Rick.
MAN: And action!
Cut!
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Cut the cameras.
Cut.
MAN: Cut camera.
Yes, sir.
RICK WASHBURN: OK.
Let's get out from under it.
I've got to check it.
MAN: Speed, ready.
Rick.
RICK WASHBURN: And action!
[Gunfire]
MAN: Cut.
TRENT HAAGA: Yeah, it
looked like a couple.
MAN: You all right?
[Chatter]
[Banging]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: All
right, standing by.
Get out.
BRENDAN FLYNT: OK, rolling
camera B. Roll camera, Lloyd.
MAN: Rolling.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Rolling.
MAN: Speed, ready.
Rick.
MAN: And action!
[Gunfire]
RICK WASHBURN: Cut.
Yeah, but you got a
lot more [inaudible].
INTERVIEWER: Did you have
a near death experience
When you actually-- did
your life flash in front
Of your eyes or anything?
It didn't flash in front of
me, but I almost shit my pants.
I mean, the gun was
pretty fu-- well,
Like I can say "fucking," right?
It was pretty fucking loud.
I mean, even with the ear plugs.
And then they sort of scared me,
saying, like, that the gun was
Gonna blow, like,
air really hard,
So I had to drop really quickly.
And so I got my ass on the
floor as quick as possible
When that gun started shooting.
And the squib exploded
on me and blew
The blood out from both sides.
And I just dropped as
soon as that happened.
So I didn't have a near-death
experience, but I sure as hell
Was frightened.
MAN: Camera B's rolling.
Ready.
RICK WASHBURN: And action!
[Gunfire]
Jammed?
That time I had it.
Sorry.
RICK WASHBURN: Cut.
I saw [inaudible].
See how you pulled
back on the belt?
I did?
Yeah.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: You need time
[inaudible] you get back.
I think it's the
way he's feeding
The belt. Let me try something.
The problem is that
we paid this guy
A lot of money to do something,
and he didn't fucking do it.
The M60 we rented fired three
to five rounds at a time max.
I think the best one
we got was maybe 10.
MAN: Gun up, please.
And I'm ready.
Go ahead.
[Gunfire]
OK?
RICK WASHBURN:
That's all we got.
And then the worst part,
the most galling part of all,
Was when he says to me, like, I
won't charge you for the time I
Spent fixing the gun.
He showed up with a
malfunctioning weapon.
You know what I mean?
And I don't know what to--
I didn't know what to say.
I was so pissed off.
I basically said, well, OK, then
I won't charge you for the film
That you wasted.
Never had one of
those break before.
TRENT HAAGA: Man,
things were going
Really well until that
gun started to fuck up.
OK.
We had a little
trouble with the M60,
But we cleared it up at the end.
They got all the
shots they needed,
And that's the important thing.
And they got them
within the time limit
Within the budget we needed.
So I guess that's
the bottom line.
And action!
[Gunfire]
[Screaming]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Good.
[Chatter]
RICK WASHBURN: You
shot the belt up.
I figured out the problem.
No.
RICK WASHBURN: It will
break at some time.
Of course, if it breaks
at the wrong time,
Then you're stuck with that
kind of cost to the film.
Fucking Rick Washburn, man.
This is where someone like
myself, a weapons coordinator,
Really earns their money.
Fucking assload of money,
you know what I mean?
Because we can fix
something on the set
And keep it running
when normally,
We'd just be down for the day.
You're paying an arm and a
leg to do this bullshit job--
What I did do was we had
an actuator handle break.
--that a fucking
monkey can do--
So I took one off
the fake gun, which
Happened to be the real
part, and swapped it
With the one on the other gun.
--that they teach
idiots to do in the army.
Then it seemed like we
were having a little bit
Of pressure problems,
probably because we're
Close to the sea level.
Clean a fucking gun.
So I overpressured the gun
just a little bit by putting
In a different restrictor.
You know what I mean?
Load a fucking gun.
Shoot a fucking gun.
You know, that's all it is.
And now we've got
things running.
You must cancel the check to
Rish Washburn for the deposit.
I have a feeling that he will
try to deposit it and rape us,
Steal our money.
So you must cancel that
$2,000 check to Rick Washburn,
Because we had very
many problems today.
We went over time.
And it was because of
his faulty equipment.
So I cannot-- you know, I
cannot allow that to happen.
So that's $2,000.
I have no idea how
much he plans to take.
So you've got to cancel
that check to Rick Washburn
First thing in the morning.
Half the crew went out
drinking last night,
Didn't come home until 3
o'clock in the morning.
[Loud music playing]
[Karaoke singing]
We had a 6 o'clock call.
INTERVIEWER: Were you among
those out late last night?
No, not tremendously late.
INTERVIEWER: Till when?
Not that late. [laughs]
INTERVIEWER: 'Til when?
I'm tired, Zork.
I'm tired.
I'm just gonna sleep.
Some people stayed
out all night.
INTERVIEWER: How late?
What'd you say?
I'm sick, Zork.
MAN: He's hungover.
Sick.
INTERVIEWER: How late?
INTERVIEWER:
(LAUGHING) How late?
Sick.
Like 11:15.
And then also I
heard that there
Was basically a fistfight
in the cafeteria
This morning in this location.
I guess Kevin had a
little bit of a hot temper.
And some things
Gary said upset him.
And he just got a little angry.
Then he was getting
violent and scary.
And I thought he
was just joking.
And then he grabbed the
shit out of my hands.
He said, don't fucking drink.
I see you, pussy.
Blah, blah, blah.
And started getting in my face.
INTERVIEWER: What
was the fight about?
Um, the PA didn't want
to get up to come here.
You know, after
night of drinking,
Somebody wakes you up
at 5:00 in the morning.
He's like, come on, dude.
Get up.
- Get up.
So Kevin said that he was
being a wise-ass to him, and--
Well, that's why he had to go.
I mean, he didn't
do anything to him.
But I guess just,
you know, we're
Only four days into shooting.
And if you're prone to
doing things like that,
It's only going to get way,
way, way, way, way worse.
So I guess they just didn't want
that kind of stuff happening.
Like, 11:15.
INTERVIEWER: Like, uh, 1:15?
11:15.
INTERVIEWER: Like 2:15?
11:15
INTERVIEWER: Like 3:15?
Security to the set, please.
Please remove Zork
from the premises.
INTERVIEWER: What did you
hear about the little scandal
Last night?
The little scandal?
What, that guy pissing?
So what did piss on
the floor last night?
Do you know that?
I got woken up at 2
o'clock in the morning
Last night because somebody
was pissing in the hallway.
Yes.
I can't believe they peed.
And I woke up.
I'm like, up the fuck
are you talking about?
[Laughs] You walk out.
And I'm like [sniffing] [laugh]
I don't know what
to think, you know?
Who are these people?
And why are they here, you know?
With alcohol comes trouble.
[Inaudible].
Like, and they won't care
who was out last night
And didn't get up
at 6 o'clock call.
The only problem--
Which I understand is about
half the people on this movie,
So--
A major problem that
we're having is just--
I have a major problem with
you not listening to me.
I'm sorry.
Because I'm basically
very upset right now.
Whatever happened this morning,
I consider a direct result
Of people going out last
night, drinking too much,
And not being able to get up
this morning in a proper mood
To do their job.
Don't drink and make movies.
OK.
It was 11:30, Zork?
INTERVIEWER: How late?
11:30.
I don't want to be
filmed now, Zork.
INTERVIEWER: So we've
been having a fun morning?
Actually the stuff
we're doing for the shoot
Is fun and all that stuff.
The actual stuff we're
shooting has been a lot of fun.
It's been a great deal of fun.
It's just really
hard to stay cool.
The only trouble spot is when
I'm unable to try to get cool,
You know, when I'm in
there waiting for stuff.
And it's mostly
the disorganization
As well, the lack of
responsibility being taken.
So that's what
today's been like.
INTERVIEWER: There have been
some challenges and dilemmas
With Joe Fleishaker, and--
Well, Joe Fleishaker,
apparently there was some issue
About food, believe it or not.
And I think we resolved that.
I got him the turkey.
We got him the turkey sandwich.
He doesn't eat pastrami or any
kind of ham or even provo--
Or what do you call
it-- prosciutto.
So we got him a turkey,
no mayo, of course.
He'll take a roll-- or you
know, take a French bread.
But he will not take mayonnaise.
I don't think he wants coleslaw.
But we worked through that.
But then today we had a problem
in that Joe Fleishaker didn't
Want to get into costume.
That was a big problem.
Regular job.
Now I can't do that,
because they want me here
On Tuesday and on Thursday.
We'll cut the scene out
finish this scene is,
And whatever that scene
is, we don't need it.
Right?
That's easy enough.
-I'm just very tired.
-All right, so you're tired.
-I'll get into my costume now.
-Come on.
You were eating by a escalator.
How can you be more
tired than that?
JOE: But that was
done in a long day.
Come on, this is different.
Four days in a row--
You said you wanted-- you
said you were planning.
You had your vacation to do
the "Toxic Avenger" movie.
-That's correct.
-This is your fucking vacation.
But whatever plans
that I've made--
Just please put the
costume on, all right?
I'll do that.
Finish this scene,
and then we'll
Worry about what comes later.
Yeah, Scarlett O'Hara said that
tomorrow is whatever it is.
But he did it. he
rose to the occasion.
He got into costume.
But then he had to leave.
He had to leave the set, because
he has to rest up for tomorrow,
So--
I'm feeling OK, but we
have some possible troubles
Coming over the next
few days with him
Cutting scenes or something.
I hope we can--
You know, Lloyd
had a lot of nerve
Telling me that I scheduled
my vacation [inaudible].
Sure I did.
But every single element, every
single day of that schedule
Has been turned on its head.
Every day I told my
boss I would be in,
And he's now asking
me not to be in.
And I can't stay.
I can't come back tomorrow
to do those other scenes.
I'm not really ready for them.
They want me to do
the alleyway scene.
We are not going to do
the Joe Fleishaker bladder
For his giant fart explosion.
Instead we will use the
bladder, the Joe Fleishaker
Expanding during his sex scene.
And if they can't use
it in the sex scene,
Then we'll figure out
something else to do with it.
INTERVIEWER: So what do you use
to prepare for your character
Here?
Well, my whole life
has been my preparation.
My whole life has been
one big, giant joke.
And when you add to the fact
years and years of overeating
And under exercise, here I am.
That made Lardass.
Today we are trying
to make up a scene,
Because we lose this location
forever in about three hours.
INTERVIEWER: Trent, what's
the word of the day?
[Sigh] Panic.
We're shooting around the gore.
And then those will
be done in-- we
Cleverly created these posters
so that you could create
The classroom-- sections
of the classroom
Anywhere, knowing that
we might run out of time.
We can reproduce
that door as fake.
So that door can be reproduced.
This is the door where Trent's
body will be disemboweled.
We just have to get
the sinew here here.
So we've got to get the
skeleton, sinew, of this scene,
And then the bowels.
Right?
Yeah?
We need you running through
the students on the set.
[Inaudible] right now.
Right, right.
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
I don't want to fuck things up.
But we should try to shoot this.
TRENT HAAGA: Here's what
we need to do, Lloyd.
Come here.
Is something going wrong here?
I'm just-- I'm hot.
I'm hot, and I'm
trying to get cool.
And they can't prepare anything.
Why do they keep bothering you?
Why do they-- Trent,
why do these guys
Have to keep talking to you?
No, Trent was
listening to me explain
That it doesn't make
sense for me to go in
And be hot and sweating.
And they can't patch me.
No matter what they do, they
can't patch me if I'm sweating.
Because the makeup they're
using has water in it.
-Yeah, I understand.
-Put it on.
And if I'm sweating
more than that--
-Don't worry about it.
- --it's not gonna stay.
Yeah, it's all right.
So OK?
You all right?
Are you happy?
David, are you a happy Toxie?
Are you OK?
You're happy, and-- it's
only day four, man, so--
All right, so basically--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK, all right.
Can we get Toxie in
the costume, please?
I think we can shoot it.
We're ready to go.
Toxie should be ready.
I'm sorry.
We're waiting on
the mop, Lloyd.
It's coming.
INTERVIEWER: I don't
care about the mop.
It should be ready.
It's not right.
We're sitting here.
Everybody's got their faces
in tacos, taco sauce, blood.
We should be ready to
shoot when we're ready.
If the guy wants to have
a movie, we can't do it.
We've got to go faster.
We can't make [inaudible].
MAN: He's here.
[Chatter]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK, are
we gonna shoot, folks?
TRENT HAAGA: Do you to
rehearse with Toxie once,
So he knows what's going on?
He watched it, but--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: I
don't have time.
I've got to get a scene.
I must-- or we can
not have a scene.
What do--
TRENT HAAGA: All right.
No, let's get smoking.
Let's have him go.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Can we
come back tomorrow?
TRENT HAAGA: Here we go.
Let's go.
MAN: No.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Can we
redo it late tonight?
TRENT HAAGA: You're right.
Let's go.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: No.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Let's go.
Smoke!
Lights!
Everyone get ready.
This isn't how you make a movie.
MAN: This isn't fun, no.
I'm telling you right now, man.
This-- this is how
you make a movie.
Get people to
argue with another.
And then you go,
(IMITATING LLOYD) what
Is this, a fucking debate squad?
Is this debating club?
Am I standing in the
middle of debating club?
I'm like, you fucking died.
That was pretty good, huh?
Dude, there's no way.
Oh, he's gonna kill me
when he sees this, man.
LLOYD KAUFMAN:
Yeah, we'll shoot.
We'll shoot it.
We need Toxie, though.
MAN: Do you need background?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yeah
you can sit there.
Doesn't hurt.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: What the--
who [inaudible] him?
I didn't--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Get him back.
Tell him to put
the makeup back on.
We'll just use his body, right?
Who wrapped him?
I didn't wrap him.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yeah, I know.
Well, nobody should
wrap until we wrap.
That's ridiculous.
Just get him in with
his body, right?
Oh, that's bad stuff, right?
I won't continue with that.
CAT: I didn't wrap him.
I'm sorry.
Well, who did wrap him?
CAT: I have no idea.
He's in effects getting
his makeup taken off.
MAN: Easy.
Easy, Lloyd.
MAN: Well, where
does the [inaudible]?
Yeah, you got to-- you
can't do that, right?
Hey, you guys
can't do this stuff
Until he's wrapped, right?
I'm the director.
I'm the boss.
Don't wrap until you get the
word directly from the top.
I'm sorry if you
were misinformed.
It obviously was a boo boo.
And again, I'm grateful.
It's the best makeup
we've ever had,
The best Toxie we've ever had.
But there might be some
major miscommunication.
And if it happens, it'll
be a four-hour wait.
So please-- this didn't
matter, this one.
But please just
check first, right?
Please, please, please.
Tox-- uh, David,
thank you very much.
It was a wonder day.
Are you satisfied?
Everything all right?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: But you're OK?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: We
can't do any better.
We cannot do any better.
I can't make the
movie any other way.
This is the best-- this may be
harder than most of the days.
I don't know.
But the only good-- the
only thing I can suggest
Is when we're outdoors, we
only have so much daylight.
That may help you
at the bottom end.
But at the top end, it means
earlier, you know, David.
So I wish we could
do better for you.
Your patience is gonna be tried.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: There is, but it
ain't-- the movies-- at least,
In our movies, the shooting
schedule, it means very little,
Because things happen.
Shit happens, you know.
So you got to let me know
if there's some problem.
You know what I mean?
Hopefully, things will be better
as we go on with this thing.
But there are gonna be
unexpected things, and--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: It won't happen.
I'd love it.
No one would like
it more than I,
But I don't think
we will get it.
I just am afraid
we will not get it.
This stuff, we had
a lot of actors.
So maybe, you know--
maybe tomorrow
Will be a little easier.
I don't know.
[Laughs] He cant' leave.
I told him to dye his hair.
I told you I needed to
make his hair black,
Because otherwise it
looked like-- people
Was saying it's Tromaville.
But now I don't
know where he is.
We're late again.
Every day, it's late.
It's fucking-- we're
shooting exteriors, right?
What time is it?
It's almost fucking 10 o'clock.
How's it going?
Well, we haven't
got a shot off yet.
This is exciting.
The script is exciting.
I loved it.
-Oh, I'm glad you liked it.
I thought it was so funny.
It's so funny.
So you liked the script?
You think it's as good
as "Shakespeare in Love"?
Oh, much better.
When you're not busy, could
me and him talk to you?
Sure.
Because he has something
pretty big going on.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
Pretty big?
Well, I ought to hear
about it right now.
He wants to make a movie?
Yeah?
He's making a book right now.
Uh-huh.
And he has his own
characters and everything.
And he wanted to know if he
could make a movie out of it.
Why not?
Just keep-- you have to have,
like, a script or something.
You got to get some money.
You have to raise money.
You need money to make a movie.
Well, I guess he could
bring it to us, you know.
He's made his own book.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Oh, maybe--
-We have a club.
We have everything.
-Really?
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Cool.
Good going.
It sounds really interesting.
Well, let's-- what's
the next step?
The next step is--
I guess talk about
it at some point.
Yeah.
-Yeah.
All right, all right.
Well, maybe after we
finish shooting this one,
Perhaps we can
have a discussion--
He looks a little worried.
[Laughs]
He is.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: It's a movie--
Ever since he was four, he's
been making up this thing.
Really, no kidding?
Wow.
What's the name of the story?
"Ochie and Friends."
LLOYD KAUFMAN: What is it?
LLOYD KAUFMAN:
"Ochie and Friends."
Great.
And who is Ochie,
or what is it Ochie?
They're, like, these
beings from, like,
Far, far into outer space.
And they're in their own
kind of solar system.
But they have to go to a
totally different planet.
And they're only, like, 12.
But they still get
all this stuff.
And they get rockets.
It sounds too good for Troma.
It sounds like big Hollywood.
We're a small company.
You guys haven't seen any
of our movies, probably?
No.
Our movies are kind of raunchy.
So it sounds pretty good.
Let's get together, and
maybe I can be helpful.
And I'll certainly try
to help you with it.
It's nice of you to
help your brother, too.
Yeah.
Good older brother.
Well, we'll try to-- Troma
team will help the Ochie team.
Anyway, have a great
day and thank you.
Thank you.
Good luck with it.
Thanks.
Bye.
See you later.
INTERVIEWER: So Joe,
how's today going?
JOE: Well, considering I just
got here and I'm already tired,
Thirsty, and
sweating like a pig,
It's just another
day at Tromaville.
[Set chatter]
INTERVIEWER: So what's
on the plate for today?
JOE: Well, today's my first
appearance as Chester,
The particle physicist.
So there's going
to be, you know,
What, my great love scene.
There's going to be my first
interactions with Toxie,
A lot of mistaken identities.
INTERVIEWER: So are you
looking forward to all of this?
JOE: I'm looking forward
to getting it over with.
[Chatter]
10 minutes.
I need Lloyd's approval, though.
[Chatter]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: You
should get the house
Of stupids here doing the sign.
You got eight people.
They can't get a sign up.
That's what you DVD.
This is the house of stupidity.
Can we do it now?
How is that thing?
If somebody, like, does
a little flick to it,
Will it-- blow on that sign
and see if it blows over.
[Blowing]
MAN: Did you guys dig deep?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: The
astrological signs are down,
But the signs are up.
Cold pizza after 10 hours
of straight shooting.
It was cold pizza.
INTERVIEWER: Well, if you'll
remember, the first five hours
Today, we didn't shoot at all.
It wasn't your fault.
Yeah, but food
is not determined,
Like, by how footage we shoot.
INTERVIEWER: [laughs]
It's usually determined by
how long the day goes by.
INTERVIEWER: How's the
experience been so far, Mike?
It fucking sucks, man. [laughs]
I'm sleeping bad,
losing 20 pounds a week.
MAN: Oh, that's not [inaudible].
Yeah, actually, I need
to lose the weight.
So it's all right.
INTERVIEWER: So you love Troma?
I love Troma.
I'm excited to do the next one.
[Laughter]
There you go.
Set yourself up for that one.
WOMAN: OK.
We're going to get liquor,
liquor, liquor. [laughs]
We're on our way to
the junkyard scene.
[Inaudible] got to be drunk,
but we have no liquor.
And you got ID?
Because underneath
your makeup and mask,
I can't tell-- not that I'd
be able to tell-- [laughs]
What the hell's the difference?
Hey, honey, how am I gonna
be able to tell if it's him
Anyway. [laughs]
MAN: Have someone else buy it.
Look at their ID.
Yeah, you look old enough.
[Laughter]
"The Toxic Avenger."
MAN: You should see his costume.
I've heard of that.
MAN: You've heard of that?
We're shooting part 4.
(SLURRING) Aw, shite.
This isn't the hospital.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: No, come on, man.
Concentrate, man.
You're not doing it, right.
It's like, (SLURRING)
oh, fucking, shite.
What the-- this isn't the--
you've got to get over here.
This isn't the-- the camera's
looking at us, right?
This isn't the fucking hospital.
Aw, shite.
This-- you know, this
isn't the fucking hospital.
Do it like-- I'm
a fucking failure!
I suck!
INTERVIEWER: Could you do that
again for the camera, Lloyd?
[Laughter]
Well, I'd say that.
(SLURRING) I fucking suck!
My movie was a fu-- no, no.
[Laughter]
HEIDI SJURSEN: I told
my mom this morning
That I was gonna be making
out with a chick today.
What did she say?
[Laughs] My mom's so cool.
Like, she didn't flip.
She was like, really?
Like OK, honey,
have a good time.
Yeah, have a good time.
Did everything
work out yesterday
With the Sapphic love scene?
No.
Why, what happened?
There was a revolution.
The actress did not wish
to take her clothes off.
And, you know, and she
did the first scene
With Toxie lovemaking.
She's been established.
So there wasn't really
too much we could do.
[Inaudible] [gasp]
Yeah, baby.
It's good for the baby.
HEIDI SJURSEN: Oh, baby.
[Moan]
Cut.
It's done that way
just to [inaudible].
LLOYD KAUFMAN: I'm just
trying to convince the actress
To take her clothes off,
something which was contracted
To, and something
which was agreed upon,
Something which was
rehearsed, and something
Which was pre-recorded on tape.
INTERVIEWER: And this
isn't gonna happen?
That's what's going on.
But now we're gonna shoot Toxie.
Who's doing Toxie's makeup?
Anybody doing Toxie's makeup?
Or are we not making this movie?
Yeah, we have somebody
who's doing it.
[Chatter]
MAN: Lloyd, it was a closed set.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yes, I agree.
But people can stand by.
They can stand by.
And when we're ready for
somebody, they can be there.
MAN: How are they
gonna be there, Lloyd?
They can be right in the back.
And then when we call for
them, they can be there, right?
I'm sorry.
I've been making
movies for a long time.
People can stay
off the set and be
Available when they're needed.
There's a little
bit of-- I'm not
Quite sure how to describe it.
But you can interview
some people on the set.
There was a little bit
of that actress stuff
Going on yesterday, I'm afraid.
But I think we managed
to nip it in the bud.
No, not at all.
And I didn't plan
on not doing it.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yeah,
yeah, it's gonna be fine.
[High-pitched noise]
If we don't shut
this off, we won't
Be able to hear the church bells
when they start going, see.
OK, camera is ready.
Quiet on set, please.
Standing by.
WOMAN: No more bell ringers.
[Bell ringing]
ALL: Aw.
Man.
Sorry.
[Laughter]
(SINGING) How low is the true--
MAN: You're making it
up as you go along.
--[humming] I know
it, believe me.
I know them all.
WOMAN: Where are you
picking these things up?
I love Coltrane.
Oliver Wendell Holmes
said, "the man cannot truly
Live unless he
shares in the actions
And passions of his times."
Right, [inaudible]?
Uh, yeah.
Pretty soon, it's [inaudible].
Every time I hire someone who
is a friend of Lloyd's, it's
Inevitably a fucking
nightmare, you know.
So I don't know.
It's 'cause Lloyd's old,
and all his friends are old.
And they're all
fucking assholes.
[Laughs]
INTERVIEWER: What's
happening here?
We're gonna set a man on fire.
INTERVIEWER: Why?
Because it's cool.
Because the school
has blown up.
And this flaming janitor
comes out the door.
TJ is the janitor
of the school.
And after the building
blows up, he's the person
One that comes out in flames.
So Kimberly's gonna light him.
BRENDAN FLYNT: Now,
this is a broomstick
That's lit in flames?
WOMAN: Just the tip.
It's like a long match.
BRENDAN FLYNT:
Yeah, a long match.
OK.
OK, so she ignites him,
staggers along here,
Runs around like a maniac.
Slides down the
banister here and we'll
Put him out right down there
where that big blood patch is.
INTERVIEWER: He's
playing a janitor.
Who you don't actually
see before or after this.
But you know, hey, we
can light a guy on fire,
So might as well, right?
Now is there flames
only on his back,
Or his front, or his side?
His full back.
BRENDAN FLYNT: Right, right, OK.
Nothing on the front.
So that's why he's
gonna be twisting.
Yeah, I'll be twisting and
getting the flame all the way.
And [shouting]
BRENDAN FLYNT: Right, right, OK.
INTERVIEWER: And that way
it's cheaper to set on fire
A non-established character.
I don't think it matters.
I think it was more like
that was on his resume.
And they went, oh,
there's an idea.
So now he starts right here.
MAN: Where are your cameras?
He'll do the whole stunt.
I get most of the flame.
You'll still get
your stuff here.
Is that OK?
So I'm gonna have both
cameras at the bottom.
MAN: So both the cameras--
BRENDAN FLYNT: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Put my cameras down here.
MAN: Yeah that' my
buddy TJ up there.
I'm a little nervous
just for him.
INTERVIEWER: You're
worried for him?
Hey, how long have
you been doing this?
About 22 years.
Setting myself on fire,
probably about 10.
INTERVIEWER: Yeah?
You nervous at all?
No.
INTERVIEWER: So Lloyd, do you
think that this body burn will
Be better than "Terror Firmer"?
You're up.
[Screaming]
--[sigh] Nothing
could be that good.
[Laughs]
Nothing could be
that unbelievable.
Not since the Vietnam
Buddhist priest
Was there such a flame up.
INTERVIEWER: So how
do you guys do this?
How do you light him on fire?
Carefully.
[Interposing voices]
Come over here.
I'll show you where to do that.
We have Nomex
underwear, two pairs,
In here soaking
in fireproof gel.
[Church bells ringing]
This should be the soundtrack!
Then we have a Nomex jumpsuit
over here, which doubles
For his janitor costume.
We get that all on
him, all gelled up,
His face and hair gelled up.
Then we put on lighter
fluid and rubber cement.
Light him on fire.
He runs around like a maniac.
And we extinguish him down here.
Maybe you should practice
it now, before he
Gets the stuff on him.
Look at this.
Look at this here.
[Whimpering]
Whoa!
[Grunting]
INTERVIEWER: Damn.
[Chatter]
OK.
Here's what's
happening right now.
We are locked with camera.
The stuntman is prepping.
OK, we need some nice,
respectful silence
While we do this work.
And then we're gonna
light him on fire.
[Whistle] Safety guy up here.
INTERVIEWER: What do you
think about this next stunt?
Every time I've done these,
they've been really horrible,
So--
INTERVIEWER: They have?
TRENT HAAGA: Yeah, I'm
not really optimistic.
But, you know, we'll see.
Want to make a dollar bet?
We'll make a dollar bet.
INTERVIEWER: OK, I'll
make you a dollar.
All right.
I'll make a dollar bet
saying that this sucks.
Special concerns concerning
the stairs that he
Has to run down on fire?
No, actually.
He's kind of looking
forward to it,
Because it's sort of
like two stunts in one.
It's a regular fire
burn and the stair fall,
So he wants it for his reel.
So he's kind of
looking forward to it.
Is everybody ready?
Kimberly, are you ready?
-Ready.
-TJ, ready?
Yes, sir.
Camera and crew ready?
MAN: Ready.
MAN: Quiet on the set, please.
We're gonna do this now.
Roll camera A.
[Beep]
MAN: Speed camera A.
MAN: Roll camera B.
[Whirring]
MAN: Speed Camera B.
Action, TJ.
[Screaming]
And cut.
[Applause]
[Chatter]
What was that for?
I bet that this would suck.
[Laughs]
What a fucking, fucking,
fucked up thing, man.
It was a fucked-up burn.
These guys are doing a
high fall for us later.
It's the same shit every time.
Never hire Lloyd's friends.
Never.
INTERVIEWER: What's your
biggest fear of today?
Not getting the shots
and not going on schedule
Are my biggest fear every day.
We had a-- we had to
have a Toxie stand in,
Because our Toxie was late.
He's usually
incredibly punctual.
He's been consistent
every single day.
I think he's one of the first
people on set almost every day.
And yet today, he overslept.
Fucking dammit.
I said 6 o'clock.
It's three hours and they
can't get the guy into costume.
INTERVIEWER: That did not
make Lloyd very happy.
No, it didn't make
anybody very happy.
[Inaudible] at the office.
Yeah.
I can't hold their
fucking hands, Lloyd.
You can kick them in the ass.
You can certainly ring
their bloody necks.
And you know, mules-- if
you kick a mule hard enough,
You get it to pull the plow.
That's all I know.
And you have mules.
And you're not kicking
them hard enough.
It's ridiculous.
It throws the rest of
us in a tailspin whenever
The first shot involves Toxie.
Toxie's late.
It takes two hours
to get his makeup on.
And even if he's supposed
to be there at 5:00,
And all of a sudden it's 6:30 or
something and there's no Toxie,
It's, like, major.
Because then we know the first
I can't get off until like 8:30.
INTERVIEWER: Lloyd, do you
have a word of the morning?
Uh, a lot of very,
very bad production.
No actors.
INTERVIEWER: What
are you doing, Sandy?
I'm making this
guy a Toxie double.
INTERVIEWER: Why?
Because supposedly
Dave-- unfortunately,
His costume takes
a while to prepare.
So they want to get
this shot done, so--
One just wasn't enough.
They're using--
INTERVIEWER: Are you
gonna be able to tell
That's a different guy?
We have a great editor.
[Laughs]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: We'll get
Toxie coming out of--
Who's Toxie?
He's not doing
stunts or anything.
No, no.
We just-- we got to have
some stuff with Toxie, man.
We can't wait around.
It's been like five hours
since his call time,
And he's still not
here yet, you know.
--[inaudible] close-up
when they were coming out
Oh, is he here now?
I see the van.
That's our van, right?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: I
don't see him, though.
Let him see.
We got our Toxie, right?
Instill the fear
of God into Toxie.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: I think
it's time to-- I'm
Not too happy with this.
I'm happy to use this guy.
It's 10 o'clock.
This is ridiculous.
We shot with the stand-in,
who was inconspicuously
Tito's height, when
Dave, our really Toxie,
Is at least a foot taller.
And he normally carries both of
us, which is the humor in it.
He carries Tito
and Sweetie Honey.
It's kind of funny, 'Cause
Dave's a strong guy,
And he can do that.
Ah, there you are, sir.
Yes, sir.
He's been here for
like 20 minutes.
Oh, god, do they suck ass?
And you're already dressed.
And what they're
gonna do is they're
Gonna bring you out
through this side,
And we're gonna
put on your shoes.
Great.
I'm gonna shoot
with this guy, who's
Half an inch taller than Mike
in the 10-year-old fucking mask?
That's brilliant.
Who's fucking idea was that?
Oh, that looks really great.
Motherfuckers.
INTERVIEWER: What's that?
They got the fucking
10-year-old mask on a 6'2" guy.
MAN: It doesn't look anything
like-- we have a stunt man.
Somebody could have asked.
Anybody could have asked.
I had no idea they
were shooting with it.
I'm sure--
I put together pieces of
this makeup for a stunt man.
They don't care.
No, they just
don't fucking care.
They could do the rest of
the movie with a 10-year-old
Mask and 6'2" guy.
Right?
Why not?
They just don't care.
It's great.
Fucking brilliant.
[Crowd shouting]
MAN: Hey, that's a cut.
That's a cut.
MAN: That's a cut.
Cut, cut, cut.
We need to just have
Toxie get up and leave.
[Chatter]
He's just the stand in so
they could try to get some
Shots off that don't really--
That guy is like 6'2", if that.
I know.
That's what I'm talking about.
MAN: It's just the shoes.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Morning, David.
What's that?
We need to have
Toxie move, remember?
TRENT HAAGA: Yes, I--
He can't stay on his knees,
otherwise there's no movie.
So how do we-- let's
just get the next move.
I'm very wide.
INTERVIEWER: So
why didn't they--
Why didn't they use Dave?
Because Dave was
late to get in makeup.
But by the time we did
the scene, he was ready.
They just said no.
I don't know, really.
Hi.
I got you, man.
I got you.
We had people standing by.
We had no idea what we
could do without Toxie.
And nobody could call.
But let's just--
can we get past this?
All we did was this
long shot with a fucking
Shitload of smoke.
Yeah, can we do
it again with me?
All right.
Let's see what I can do.
DAVE: Tell me what
you want me to do.
All right.
Trent give me
some blocking here.
TRENT HAAGA: Do you want to pick
this one up from that point?
Just have him get up--
Can we just fill
him up with smoke
And have him bring
the kids on again?
Why?
I don't want to do it again.
-All right.
-Absolutely not.
In fact, if it happens
again, there's gonna
Be a fucking 'nother Toxie.
TRENT HAAGA: All
right, no problem.
And In fact, I
want that other guy.
I want you to get-- hey.
Rhonda, Rhonda.
We're gonna sign that other
guy, and we're gonna pay him.
So we can't do
the first 12 feet?
No, Lloyd won't do it.
He's fucking pissed at me.
He's pissed at everybody.
He's totally psycho.
This is a super long
shot over the tops
Of the heads of crowds.
We got fog and--
I was gonna carry them both up.
Yeah.
Wasn't that good?
That was excellent.
You know what I mean?
I agree.
But--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK, let's do it?
Can we just--
Unbelievable.
All right?
And it looks like shit.
It's gonna look like shit.
I can't get through
that little flag there.
But this guy can.
He's a half inch taller
than Tito, for christ sake.
I know.
And now we're not together.
Well we just got to--
like I said, man.
We're gonna get
this in a master.
We're gonna get closer,
and we're gonna get this.
We just need this for the
master shot, all right?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: So--
Is there any way
to go back and just
Do the first 12 feet of this?
Because in the rehearsal,
you said I would
Carry both of them, right?
-We'll do a close-up.
We'll do close-ups.
We'll do this thing.
We'll have you carrying
them out tight.
You're like this big
in the stuff I'm doing.
So we'll get you--
we'll do it again.
It's just not gonna
match if I'm-- I mean,
I was carrying them both
in rehearsal [inaudible].
Now we're going to do it
to match the way it was
When you walked out the door.
And that was--
That's what I'm saying.
When you walked out the
door in there, you had him,
And you had her on your arm.
And we did that.
We had her on--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Well,
can we just do this
So I can break this set up?
You mean from the other shot?
So like--
TRENT HAAGA: Yeah.
-We're very late.
We're never gonna get a movie.
I'm just worried--
You're absolutely right.
Can we [inaudible]?
DAVE: So I get
from here to here.
Is that it?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Hey, Hasan.
Thank you.
That was great.
Hang in, though.
We can still use you as the
super stud that you are.
[Laugh]
And we may need
you as Toxie, too.
Now, why is he getting
out of the costume?
Because he might be-- I
guess we got the real Toxie.
Yeah, you're right.
WOMAN: I mean, I can
put him back in it.
Nah, it's all right.
Just stay handy.
And we'll keep
doing this, I think.
Like tomorrow we
ought to do it also.
INTERVIEWER: So what are
you looking over here?
It's a short-term, I
believe, contract-- 21 days.
And it looks in order.
But I'm gonna read
it just to be sure.
Make sure I don't have
to give up my first-born
Or something like that.
INTERVIEWER: And what
will that be for?
I'm gonna be Toxie's double
whenever they need it, I guess.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yo,
you're supposed to stop
People from going up here.
You see, if they fall down,
break their neck with babies.
So stop them from going through.
[Chatter]
We're gonna have
a little problem
Today, because people are
going to be going up that step.
We're shooting now.
If somebody goes up the steps
when the cameras are rolling,
That's very bad, because
it means we waste film.
Yeah.
Because you know
what'll happen,
They'll look at the
camera behind them,
And then that screws it up.
Because then people
know that they aren't
Supposed to be in the movie.
So have to make sure that the
pedestrians, very politely,
Are told to go around the back,
that we're making a movie,
That we're going
around the back.
I don't want women with tiny
babies coming through here,
Tripping over wires,
bumping into people.
Right?
Now, if you want to see the
most unpleasant side of me,
Have another person
come up the steps.
But I'm a nasty, horrible guy.
I'm not worried
about-- right, you guys
Are the sensitive young people.
You're worried about-- you
know, seriously, come on.
Wake up.
I'm not gonna screw
around, man, when it comes
To the people whose little
babies are coming through here,
I don't care.
MAN: Yeah, I'm making a sign.
You can dislike
me all you want.
But I'm sorry.
I've been here for an hour.
I've been asking for some
kind of polite system
Of the Poughkeepsie-vilians
to go around.
They're perfectly willing.
They don't want to
go through here.
You don't want people
falling on cables, right,
Especially little tiny babies.
MAN: I got it.
Yeah, well I didn't think
you got it, because it's
Like the eighth time.
So until it gets done, I'm
gonna keep being unpleasant,
Which I'm pretty good at.
And have somebody here.
Whatever it takes, right.
MAN: I think we're--
I don't want to hear about it.
Just do it.
It takes the brain
of, like-- right.
I don't want to waste my 160
IQ on this particular problem.
You probably have a genius.
Solve it, please.
Or I'll just go back
there. [inaudible].
I'm not gonna have
women and babies
Walking through the-- you
know, falling down on you guys.
I'll go back there.
I'll stay there.
You guys run it.
I'll handle it.
INTERVIEWER: Do you think
we should have some people
Just walk up the steps?
--[laughs] Just to
piss Lloyd off?
INTERVIEWER: Yes.
Oh, yeah.
You missed the big
explosion this morning.
He-- no, I'm just kidding.
I'm making this all up.
Like, I don't even want
to start any rumors.
INTERVIEWER: Oh,
no, no, no. [laughs]
Oh.
[Laughs] You missed it.
[Chatter]
Those are the brakes, right?
But here we go-- the signs.
This is no entry.
INTERVIEWER: This is such
a beautiful location here.
How come we're not
filming inside?
Oh, inside here?
INTERVIEWER: Right.
Why are we not filming
inside the mansion,
Like we were planned
and slated to?
Well, an incident happened,
where Aaron Imeson, who
Is one of our head
production assistants,
He created a bold rumor that
there was harmful lead paint
On the premises.
We were here
scouting a location.
We were videotaping.
And on the videotape,
he said, god, it
Smells like lead paint in here.
And then Trent went
over to the camera
And started going nom, nom, nom.
Oh, yeah.
Lead paint tastes good.
Nom, nom, nom.
And of course on a Troma set,
rumors just take about 10
Minutes for everyone to know.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: The issue
came up in pre-production.
[Backseat chatter]
And Trent put it to rest.
He went to the
environmental board.
And they assured him
he could shoot there.
I'm calling from
Troma Entertainment.
My name is Trent.
I just spoke to him on the
phone about five minutes ago
Regarding lead
paint safety issues.
We cleared it up
in pre-production
That lead paint is not harmful.
We went to the health
department and all these people.
Um, no, they had
said it's cracking.
And then there's
stuff on the floor.
Yeah, cracking paint
and paint on the floor,
Paint chips on the floor.
OK, well, if you could talk
to me mano a mano, just
From a human point of view.
I mean, what are the issues?
I mean, how harmful could it be?
You can shoot in a
place with lead paint.
You can shoot in a day.
For lead paint, it
would be perfectly fine.
And I went to Aaron, who's
working the art department.
Hey, Aaron, look.
Take two PAs.
I want you to clean Graystone.
So blah, blah, blah, blah.
Clean it up so we
can shoot there.
No, I'm not doing it.
That place has lead paint in it.
I say Patrick, Ellie,
and Trent they can save.
Clean it.
Yeah.
Let them clean it. [inaudible].
He said, fuck you, Jared
and went to the library.
Got all this information
about lead paint.
It got back to Dave Mattey.
And then it got to this
whole big thing, where lead
Paint-- we couldn't shoot here.
No, he was going to quit.
And you started
this whole campaign
That everybody was gonna quit.
Dave was gonna quit and
everybody was gonna quit.
Fuck Troma.
INTERVIEWER: How many
people are going?
Eight.
INTERVIEWER: Raise your hand.
Who's leaving?
-Eight people.
There's eight people total.
And then there's five
more leaving tomorrow.
INTERVIEWER: Say
their names right now.
Mark Hugo.
Fuck you.
Say your name.
Steve Ramsey.
Fuck off.
Aaron.
Double fuck you.
We're all gone.
But then the issue kept
coming up in production.
And then we had to
use another location.
It should have been
our option to shoot
In here if we wanted to.
And I think he really
overstepped his boundaries.
He caused, like, this
panic [inaudible] where
There was no cause for that.
And he sucks.
We'll give our name, but--
But I will not have three
testicles for lead paint.
But I was saddened when
actually some of our crew
Left on a major-- there
was a big day, where, like,
About 20 people left.
So what happened
today that was so--
That thing in there.
Oh, really?
You have to fire that other
guy when he gets back.
[Laugh]
Dan, you're coming back, right?
It had a major impact on,
I think, the rest of us.
It made us stronger in the end.
But on that day,
I think morale--
Which is a word that
I tend not to use--
Was at an all-time low.
Yeah, I guess it was Julia.
She was office coordinator.
She got fired.
That worked out.
That was great.
I've never seen so much crying.
WOMAN: Yeah, crying all around.
Every time I go out,
there's somebody else crying.
So humiliating.
INTERVIEWER: Still love Troma?
--[laughs] Not the
time to ask me that.
[Laughter]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: She
didn't get fired.
She quit.
INTERVIEWER: Ah.
No, Patrick says she got fired.
No, no.
I mean, unless he fired her.
No, she just had too much.
She quit.
She was driven off.
I think Julia just quit.
She quit.
HEIDI SJURSEN: Here, my
dad wants to talk to you.
INTERVIEWER: Oh, it's
one of the ex-employees,
One of the 30% that left.
What are you going
to do from here?
Where are you going?
The smart 30%.
INTERVIEWER: Were are you
going from here, Aaron?
I'm going down to Florida.
Then I'm going to Virginia.
Then I'm going to Cali.
Then I'm going to Australia.
INTERVIEWER: You're
going to Australia?
Australia for Christmas.
INTERVIEWER: Well, if you had
to sum up your experience here,
What would you say?
It was very much a
learning experience.
INTERVIEWER: A
learning experience?
Yeah, you learn a
lot of shit here.
INTERVIEWER: So is that
positive or negative?
You seem kind of frazzled.
I was very frazzled.
You weren't getting
[inaudible] here.
INTERVIEWER: Yeah, well.
It's all good.
Salute off.
Goodbye, young sir.
Goodbye.
But then, after we fired
Aaron, we hired him back again
As a still photographer.
And I heard all his
pictures are out of focus.
INTERVIEWER: So wait, where
are we filming now, though?
Oh, we decided to shoot
inside Toxie's shack
And make it Noxie's shock.
We're hanging up a a
couple different signs.
"We're in [inaudible]."
And we show him walking in here.
And when he enters
in here, we're going
To be in-- it's not gonna work.
INTERVIEWER: It's not gonna
look right, you don't think?
No.
I mean, Aaron fucked
up the shoot for us.
INTERVIEWER: So why did you
guys hire him back then?
Well, he basically--
in order to get back,
He had to ask a couple people.
He asked Lloyd, who wanted
him back in, for some reason.
Patrick said OK, under the
condition that he asked me.
He's like, is there gonna
be-- and I expect an apology.
And even when he came up to
me and he said he apologized,
I told him that I-- I
told him I didn't care.
I do not want him back
on this production.
And I will do everything
possible to make sure that he,
You know, gets fired again.
INTERVIEWER: [laughs]
[Laughs] He's a total asshole.
INTERVIEWER: So
how does it feel?
You pumped?
No.
INTERVIEWER: No?
INTERVIEWER: Aw.
You do the job.
You get it done, like they say.
INTERVIEWER: I think
you're doing a good job.
Well, thank you.
We try.
There are no old bold stuntmen.
You're an old stuntman
or bold stuntman.
I let the audience get excited.
I try to keep it chill.
Oh, so you're going far.
Well, yeah.
So it'll be out.
So I pass over you completely.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK, I hear you.
I'm gonna try and see if I
can land right about here.
OK.
All right.
Fine.
That way I may be able to
clear your frame altogether.
Ready.
Action.
Tito, you're right on
the inside, aren't you?
Can you get there please?
Yeah, like that.
And then Toxie--
INTERVIEWER: Can I
ask you a question?
Sure.
INTERVIEWER: Like, why do
you think it's a bad idea
For the actors to just jump?
Every time you put an
actor through anything
That could be risky, you
always [inaudible] actor.
That's why stuntmen are hired.
INTERVIEWER: Even for a little--
-[inaudible].
INTERVIEWER: Even for a little
fall like that, you think?
Well, they had already
done it six times.
Every time you do it increases
geometrically the chance
That your lead actor
will be injured
And the production
will be halted.
That's why stuntmen do the work.
Plus, what I did was extended.
They're doing a small jump.
What I did was extend it over
camera and take it longer.
You start doing that
with the actors,
You increase
geometrically the chances
Of an actor being injured.
Every single time they
do it, you risk it.
So--
INTERVIEWER: All right.
That's why stuntmen
came into existence.
Thank you.
MAN: Go to 24.
MAN: Eight.
Get towards eight.
Hold on, baby!
Yeah, I don't want to go.
That's great.
You got to jump.
Go!
That was great.
I think we should give him it.
You know pay him for whatever
the Noxie-- what do we
Have for Noxie?
300 bucks or something?
-Yeah, we had to pay--
I think he'd appreciate it.
--stunt doubles
and shit like that.
Well, that's not David's fault.
Yeah, it's somebody's
fault. It's not mine.
Well, it's my
fault. I shouldn't
Have hired that fucking
fat load of stuntmen.
[Laughter]
2,000 pounds of stunts.
No, we should have hired--
INTERVIEWER: Tell us a little
bit about the past couple days
In Tromaville.
Well, it's been as life
Tromaville can be, it's been
Sort of an up and down kind
of thing, some good, some
Not so good.
Mark Torgl, the original
Melvin was here.
What's up dude?
INTERVIEWER: Just
recording you for the DVD.
Can I ask you a few
questions while--
Sure.
INTERVIEWER: All right.
So how did you become cast
in the first "Toxic Avenger"
As Melvin?
I was going to NYU.
It was actually the year
before, for "The First Turn-On."
And I needed a summer job.
Or I just want to work
on a film for the summer.
And somewhere along the
line when we were shooting,
There was a counselor.
And the actor that
played her boyfriend, who
Was supposed to be a
really nerdy guy, quit,
Like at the very last minute.
So they were, like,
stuck without an actor
To do this role.
And they're like, who can
we get to do this role?
And I happened to be there.
And I said, I'll do it.
So I played Dwayne in
"The First Turn-On"
And had some really disgusting
scenes with mashed potatoes
In my hair and cold cuts.
And it was some
pretty funny stuff,
I think some of the
best stuff in the movie.
And the next year, when
they made "Toxic Avenger,"
I understood that they had
auditioned hundreds of kids
To try and find
someone to do Melvin.
And finally, Lloyd said,
why don't we just call Mark?
And so they called me and
asked me if I wanted to be
Melvin in the Toxic Avenger.
OK.
And the rest is history.
INTERVIEWER: Why weren't
you in the second one?
Let's see.
What happened.
Oh, yeah.
I wanted $50, and Lloyd
said that was too much.
INTERVIEWER:
[laughs] What was it
Like working on the first one?
Was it like it is, like,
when you look around now?
Was it the same conditions?
Exactly the same.
Everyone was sleeping
on the floors.
We used to be fed with Jarlsberg
cheese, three meals a day.
By the end of the movie, we
were all so sick of cheese.
They had, like, five or
six of these big loaves
Of cheese left.
And the crew all, like,
took these big loaves
And threw them down
a side of a mountain
So that we wouldn't
have to eat it anymore.
But then they were
like, well, sorry.
There's nothing to eat.
You guys don't eat.
MAKEUP ARTIST: Oh, no.
INTERVIEWER: Do you know
what you'll be doing?
Any details in the
scene or anything?
Yeah, I'm coming out of
the mayhem at the big battle
At the end.
I'm evolving out of dead Noxie
to become bad, evil Melvin.
All right, we got it.
So we talked to
David and rehearsed
A little with David down there.
I think you guys should work
down there with yourselves,
Just [inaudible].
Yeah, I think it's
better on your own.
If you want, Trent can
come and work with you.
But I think you guys on
your own would be better.
MARK: I'd like to
have your opinion.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yeah,
I'll come down when
You feel you're comfortable.
I just don't to-- I find it's
better if you are allowed
To do it without me there.
Pretty much the
whole scene-- improv.
So that was kind of cool.
We had a framework of
what we wanted to do.
And then we just
kind-- we winged it.
And you can be, like, what?
You know, what are you doing?
I'm you, you know.
And to the point it's
got to keep progressing,
Where I'm just, like,
doing disgusting things
And hurting you, even.
And then at one point, we talked
about hurting you bad enough
That you drop you mop.
And what it progresses into is
I stick the mop between my legs
And attempt to, like,
buttfuck you with the mop.
OK.
INTERVIEWER: That's got to
be the third time this film.
So how do you like being back
in costume and everything?
It feels like an
old, moldy pair
Of socks-- very comfortable.
INTERVIEWER: Do you like it?
I love it.
INTERVIEWER: [laughs]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Wait a minute.
Don't.
Hold on.
Come up the stairs,
and we'll do it again.
[Laughs]
He needs a mop!
WOMAN: [inaudible].
Melvin needs a mop.
Ready?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yeah.
OK, and action.
Hey, it's Mark Torgl,
everybody, 15 years later.
[Applause]
Oh, beautiful.
Hey, how's it going?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Mark Torgl.
Oh, ho.
My heavens.
Unbelievable.
[Inaudible].
History in the
making, everybody.
The whole idea is so David
doesn't have to be tired.
No, nobody's saying no.
But why does he
have to be Hasan?
Because that's
why I want Hasan.
I've got to have
the guy's arms, man.
This guy's got to fucking-- it's
little Melvin coming out, man.
TRENT HAAGA: It
could've been TJ.
TJ's standing right here.
He just got out, but
we can put him back in.
It has to be Hasan?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: It's
got to be somebody
With big arms, that's all.
So it's not-- not-- come on,
folks, use some brains, please.
In the future, stop
dismissing people.
Like, not so stupid.
They kicked out Hasan.
He was happy to do it.
I don' understand what
you're trying to tell me.
We tried to take
the [inaudible]
Off and put it on TJ anyway.
TJ--
But where is Hasan?
I'm just telling you.
We have time.
If he's here, you
can put it on him.
MAN: Toxie had a time conflict.
-Yeah, exactly.
He had a time conflict.
And--
No, no he didn't.
He could have been told to come.
And someone should've
said to me--
I called and left a
message for him, Lloyd, OK?
Yeah, well now it's too late.
Well, now find somebody
who's got big arms.
You need to find
somebody with big arms.
That's all, arms and the mask.
TJ was just wearing
it, like 30 minutes ago,
And he took it off.
Let's put TJ back in it.
If TJ is willing.
Well, maybe TJ doesn't
want to go back in.
[Laughs]
Lloyd, we got a volunteer.
Yeah, but it's
got to be big arms.
If we dress his arms up,
that'd look pretty big, right?
Yeah, use Miller.
You don't mind.
What's going on in
terms of David tonight?
David's got to be in
the reverse of this
While he talks to them, yeah?
LLOYD KAUFMAN:
Yeah, that's right.
I'm not striking
anybody out of anything
Ever until we are
totally wrapped, man.
God dammit, we should just ask
Lloyd what he wants to shoot.
You know what I mean?
He changes his mind, his idea.
Every time we try
to make a plan,
It gets totally
fucked, because he
Knows what he wants to shoot.
He just didn't tell us.
You mean with this scar thing?
No, no, I'm not talking to her.
Look who's here.
It's a perfect match.
[Laughter]
He looks like Mr. T.
INTERVIEWER: Why did they dress
you up as the Toxic Avenger?
Because I'm the best.
INTERVIEWER: Really?
Honestly.
Because we didn't
have anybody else.
I got to stick my head
through his whole.
INTERVIEWER: Right.
[Chatter]
So you're gonna be the arms
and the legs, basically.
Arms and legs.
Well--
INTERVIEWER: I
mean arms and head.
Arms and head.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Gurgle,
twitch, twitch, twitch.
Gurgle, gurgle, and Mark, mop.
MAN: Move your arms
a little bit more.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Mop,
mop is coming up.
Good.
Now you, Mark.
Quick.
Beautiful.
Good.
Ah, nice.
Don't put that in
front of your face.
That's good.
That thing's good.
You can put it in your mouth.
Just don't let it
cover your face.
Look up at Melvin.
You're so happy.
Melvin!
It's you.
It's me.
[Maniacal laughter]
It's us!
It's us, Melvin.
[Maniacal laughter]
Give me a hug.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Cut.
Cut.
Good.
OK.
[Laughter]
[Cheering and applause]
INTERVIEWER: How did you
like coming out of Noxie?
It was beautiful,
beautiful experience
INTERVIEWER: Was
it like a rebirth?
Absolutely.
[set chatter]
I was reborn, reborn as Melvin.
I think we're out.
We're done.
Mark, yay.
Mark Torgl.
[Applause]
Beautiful. [inaudible].
Mark Torgl.
History, Troma
history, movie history.
MAN: Give him a hug again.
[Inaudible].
MAN: Slime him gain.
He's getting his revenge.
Ew.
[Laughter]
This is Hank.
Do you guys know each other?
Corey Feldman.
How are you?
How you doing?
Love your work.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: This is Cat,
your assistant director.
Hi, nice to meet you.
And Trent Haaga
wrote the script.
And he stars in "Terror
Firmer," the perhaps
New movie from Troma, on which
Brendan Flynt was the DP.
And he's now DP on this movie.
Troma, yeah.
COREY FELDMAN: I love you.
I love it.
[Chatter]
This guy here, whatever his
name is, this actor person--
Is he on an hourly thing--
No.
--where we have
to get rid of him.
We got him all day?
No, he's getting a
flat rare for the day.
So it's not-- when does it end?
That's what I want to know.
Is it an eight-hour
day, a six-hour day?
It just says for the day--
12-hour?
--the day of in
his contract, so.
Just make sure that we're
not gonna be told at 4 o'clock
That we have to stop.
No, we're not.
MAN: How you doing?
How you doing?
MAN: Good.
-Dave?
How are you?
Nice to meet you.
A little warm in that makeup?
Oh, yeah.
It looks fun, I
got to tell you.
Can you hear in that?
DAVE MATTEY: It's hard.
I hear through it.
-Yeah.
Muffled, right?
DAVE MATTEY: Yeah.
And it's sealed, so I can't
even hear, like, out of spaces.
I have no depth
perception at all.
Cool.
Exciting.
Yeah.
It's [inaudible] like that.
COREY FELDMAN: Yeah.
Doing like an action
sequence in the dark.
All right.
I need to get out
of the heat, man.
It's too hot out here.
[Inaudible].
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Do that again.
Just do that line again, Hank.
Do it again.
Ready?
-Which part?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: "Go
back to Tromaville."
And "All right, you go
back to Tromaville." ready?
And action.
All right, you can
go back to Tromaville.
Just remember, though--
Trent is totally
losing his mind.
Trent is totally losing
his mind on this set.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Start from
"yeah, you can go home."
"All right, you can
go home." [inaudible].
Whatever [inaudible].
Yeah.
MAN: OK.
[Inaudible].
You shouldn't have
spoken to them.
All right, let's go.
Come on.
TRENT HAAGA: [laughs]
That's nice, man.
INTERVIEWER: I just
don't understand.
MAN: Let's make
sure the rope length
Matches what was shot before.
INTERVIEWER: So what
might happen to this?
TIM: Uh, it might get road rash.
Road rash.
INTERVIEWER: Will it shatter?
No, I don't think
it'll shatter.
[Scraping]
(MEXICAN ACCENT) Hey, ese.
Man, you look kind of funny.
You look pale today, huh?
It was the cerveza.
It's a hangover, I know.
[Chatter]
INTERVIEWER: So why's
everyone wearing sombreros?
It's the heat, man, the sun.
We've already been standing
out here for a long time.
We don't want to get burnt.
Hola.
Mark.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: And action.
DRIVER: [shouting]
I love black people
Don't hurt me, please.
Please!
I love black-- ah!
INTERVIEWER: What are you
guys gonna be doing here?
What's the stunt?
Well, we're pulling the actor
along for a closeup of being
Dragged behind the truck.
And we also have
the dummy to match.
And this is for the close-up
of the actual actor,
To be able to match into it,
so that they have the three
Choices-- actor,
stunt man, and dummy--
To cut back and forth with.
[Screaming]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Cut.
He heard don't-- all
he heard was let go.
Let's just don't analyze it.
Do it again.
Let's just do it again.
BRENDAN FLYNT: I didn't
want to let him go early
Because I wasn't ready.
MAN: I know, but he's
screaming, so he heard the--
BRENDAN FLYNT: Well, why
does he have to scream?
He doesn't have to
scream this time.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Fine,
he won't scream.
Just show your mouth open.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Let's go!
BRENDAN FLYNT: --so
he can hear me, OK?
Lloyd, we're ready
to go with this.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK,
we got one more take,
Then we're going down
to the makeup on Mitch.
Mitch Cohen, the original
Toxic Avenger, was here.
We got to chat a bit.
And pretty much the
budgets have gotten lower.
The boobie count
has gotten higher.
Evidently, they're paying
actors less than they did then.
Pretty hard to
imagine, but they are.
[Motor running]
It's all good, Lloyd
DAVE MATTEY: Basically,
drag him out of the car,
Bash his face into
the engine, and then
Throw him into a KKK rally.
There are definitely things that
have gotten worse, like my skin
And that kind of stuff.
There have been
things that we've done
That have been a lot of fun.
Me and Paul did the fight.
We did our fight upstairs.
And it took a while, but I
think it's gonna look awesome.
Now, question about
the art department.
This place, it looks
so clean in here.
Are we gonna put a
lot of blood around?
WOMAN: We have blood.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: I won't
have to keep it there.
But we should defintely--
it seems like this stuff
Could be bloodied up.
MAN: You lost your
light a little bit.
INTERVIEWER: Excess.
DAVE MATTEY: And
this guy, this guy
Is the Boba Fett of this movie.
I think we're gonna get
done with the movie,
And they're gonna go-- the stuff
they're gonna talk about are
Things like [inaudible]
head coming out
Of his ass and evil Kabukiman.
So instead of just like
coming for his stomach,
Just come a little
bit to the side.
-Right.
-Over there.
OK.
And it should play
for that camera.
Over to this side, just
to fudge the uppercut.
Boom.
And uppercut over here.
Pow.
MAN: Wow.
So just cheat it.
Cheat it over to the
side a little bit.
With the hair.
[Fighting sounds]
And camera!
CAT: Rolling.
-Rolling.
Action.
[Fighting sounds]
[Shouting]
MAN: So it's gonna
be an awesome fight.
And Paul is good.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Come on in
and meet Joe Fleishaker.
He's kind of
Troma's action star.
He's been in about five--
Hi.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: How many
Troma movies have you--
JOE FLEISHAKER: This
is number seven.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Seventh, wow.
We met each other
when we were doing
A movie called "Troma's War."
REPORTER: OK.
And it's Joe Fleishen?
Fleishaker.
F-L-E-I-S-H-A-K-E-R.
It's not big bucks.
It's--
REPORTER: I think you're
doing it for the love of it.
For the love of it.
Oh, it has to be.
If you don't have the love
of it, you can't do this.
'Cause the stuff that
I did in this movie
Were pretty, pretty wild stuff.
There was something about
the cum on your face, Joe.
JOE FLEISHAKER: Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Yeah, yeah.
JOE FLEISHAKER: It'll look good.
Has anybody seen the footage?
MAN: Yeah yeah.
It looks great.
They say not only
is Joe Fleishaker
An amazing actor, he's
one fine cock sucker.
JOE FLEISHAKER: Fellatio Joe.
[Laughter]
MAN: Was it mayonnaise?
JOE FLEISHAKER: Yeah.
MAN: We're loading Joe.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Joe is armed.
Action!
[Groaning]
It's a little weird to
just take it straight.
But I used to eat it
straight sometimes.
This is my brand, so-- I ain't
no fucking Miracle Whip guy.
Forget about it.
The real, real mayonnaise.
As I said to
everybody, the reason
Why I wasn't really that
good at spitting it out
Is because I usually swallow.
[Laughter]
That's what I heard.
JOE FLEISHAKER: Yeah.
That is what I heard
from Michael Herst.
[Laughter]
We just did today the big
romantic reunion scene.
WOMAN: Aw.
JOE FLEISHAKER: It was
quite, quite [audio out].
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Action.
WOMAN: Ooh.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: No,
no don't do that.
Work it, kind of.
WOMAN: Ooh.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: That's it.
That's it.
And then do your fingers.
WOMAN: Ooh, ooh, oh.
Ooh, ooh, mm, ee, oh.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK, good.
WOMAN: [moaning]
MAN: Slow.
Whoa.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Play
it straight, Joe.
Real.
You're really in ecstasy.
Lower your chin.
Lower your chin, Joe.
MAN: Down.
Lower your chin.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Lower your chin.
That's it.
OK.
Now start doing what you did in
the scene, Heidi, kissing him.
Oh.
[Moaning]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Go low.
-Mm, baby.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Go down
his stomach, please.
Kiss down his stomach.
Can you see it?
Keep going down a little
bit so we can see his face.
Mm.
Love it, ooh.
Yummy, oh.
Oh.
[Inaudible]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: See
her hands, Brendan?
Cut.
Perfect.
MAN: Beautiful.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Very good.
Thank you.
Do that conversation you had.
I was always
[inaudible] slutty girl.
When I was in high school, I did
30 miles a day on the bicycle.
I used to cut class and
go to play basketball.
But I used to eat
enormous amounts of food.
A typical day, I would have
three loaves of Italian bread,
Couple of boxes of donuts.
I used to drink Pepsi
by the quart an hour.
But I worked.
I did so much exercise
it didn't matter.
Once I got to
college and I started
Doing less time for exercise,
I started gaining wait.
Before you knew it,
I was too big to play
The sports I was doing.
The bicycle couldn't
handle me anymore.
And then it just-- I
never did stop the eating.
Uh-huh.
But I always ate a lot.
But I also worked a lot.
Now, I, you know-- now
I don't work that hard.
Now I sit at a desk and, you
know, play with my fingers.
My fingers are trim.
[Laughter]
It's really useful.
It's kind of sexy.
He's great.
[Door creaking]
[Door slams]
Yes, thank you for coming.
INTERVIEWER: [laughs]
[Fighting sounds]
[Grunting]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: And remember,
we're on Noxie now.
The main purpose of this fight
now is to get Noxie's craps
All over the place.
SCOTT RHODES: We need somebody
in the art department in here.
MAN: OK.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Art department!
This is deteriorating
on our heads.
[Grunting]
[Shouting]
INTERVIEWER: What's
the word of the day?
People, please.
Hey, I'm not good
at that, Zork.
I'm not good at
defining the word.
Blood is the word of the day.
MAN: Today was the gore day.
And it's all about blood.
It's the big triumphant
massacre before they
Face off with Noxie.
It's taking slightly longer
than any of us had anticipated.
INTERVIEWER:
"Slightly," meaning?
Hours.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Uh, sound?
MAN: Speed.
MAN: Mark.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Hit
it, and action!
MAN: Action background.
Oh, no!
I've got AIDS!
[Scream]
MAN: Can we do
that one more time?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yeah, cut.
CAT: Cut
LLOYD KAUFMAN: So
let's do chin up more.
You're looking down too much.
CAT: Rolling.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: And action.
[Camera whirring]
[Gurgling]
LLOYD KAUFMAN:
Get over near Rob.
Hand at the hip to Rob.
WOMAN: Rob.
INTERVIEWER: And what's
gonna happen to you, sir?
Well, sir, I am
gonna have a broom
Embedded through my spine.
And it is gonna come
through my stomach,
Therefore creating
blood, guts, and maybe
Just a little bit of blood.
INTERVIEWER: Mm, man.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Action.
[Shouting]
Oh, God!
Oh!
[shout]
TRENT HAAGA: Hold still.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Move forwards.
TRENT HAAGA: Move forward.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Where's
your fucking mark?
TRENT HAAGA: OK,
right there, Joe.
Just stay in the [inaudible].
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Roll tape.
TRENT HAAGA: Roll tape.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Stay
on your fucking mark!
Get over on your
mark, god dammit!
Oh, you fucked it.
TRENT HAAGA: Oh, shit.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Cut.
That was ridiculous.
You're supposed to stay
on your mark, right.
BRENDAN FLYNT: All right, Lloyd?
Take it from there, Lloyd.
-I'm never--
BRENDAN FLYNT:
Take it from there.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yes,
now do it right.
Get close together and just
look at the fucking stuff
And be scared.
All right, give me the camera.
Here we go.
Ready?
Do not look at the sign.
You're looking at the carnage.
Why'd you read the sign?
Sorry.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Ready?
Concentrate.
Now we're focused on the--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: I'm gonna
look at Tromaville Hospital.
And action!
[Inaudible]
BOTH: [panting]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: That's it, good.
That's almost it.
BRENDAN FLYNT: That's great.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK?
Good.
Stay close together.
That's it!
OK.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Now get out.
[Beep]
And action.
Blood.
[Screaming]
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Bring it up.
Bring it up!
BOTH: [scared panting]
BRENDAN FLYNT:
Carnage over here.
[Screaming]
BRENDAN FLYNT: No,
carnage over here.
Oh, my god!
What the hell is happening?
What the hell is that?
Oh, no!
BOTH: [whimpering]
Oh, my god!
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Cut.
OK, beautiful.
Bravo.
Excellent.
[Cheering and applause]
Yay, OK.
TRENT HAAGA: OK, next!
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Very
good. [inaudible].
Just because of the camera.
Good job!
Get that [inaudible]
light on, please.
Try to get it on his chin.
I think that-- you see,
like, the pool of blood there,
The reflection that it makes?
That would be such a great
shot if they just shot it
Down on, you know, the blood.
LLOYD KAUFMAN:
Let's do it, right?
BRENDAN FLYNT: Get the camera--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: [inaudible].
MAN: And the comb?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: I think we need
to comb out the crap pieces.
So this stuff in here.
MAN: Does anybody got a comb?
MAN: Or just push it.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Comb?
Would that do it?
Comb, yeah, you're right.
Comb or a leaf brush, maybe.
A leaf rake.
Do you have a leaf rake?
Get a leaf rake.
Who's got a leaf rake?
MAN: God dammit!
MAN: All right, somebody
was yelling for--
I have to say it's a
very, very dedicated group.
You know, I mean, I really
do believe that it's worth as
Much as an Oscar to have people
this dedicated to a project,
Who are just incredibly nice.
And things are moving along.
And there's quite a
fine film in progress.
And it's impossible to
ask for anything more.
[Eerie music playing]
And do we know that
we're crashing the car
Through the door in the--
MAN: We do.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: So
everybody knows that.
Brendan, you know we're
going to do the car crashing
Through the garage tomorrow?
The car is gonna shut off
here and stop about here.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: OK.
Brendan doesn't want
anyone where Patrick is.
No, you cannot be there,
nor can Caleb, or that guy,
Whatever his name is.
Jared, get out of the frame.
Why is that?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: We
feel it's dangerous.
Yes, sir.
BRENDAN FLYNT: OK,
everybody clear there.
I don't want anyone there.
I want this whole thing--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Come
over by my camera.
Sound man, Brendan
says no, but this
Is between you and Brendan.
LLOYD KAUFMAN: What's that?
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yeah, right.
OK.
TRENT HAAGA: Everybody ready?
And action, car.
[Crash]
[Shouting]
[Chatter]
MAN: Oh, my god,
the ladder, dude.
Wow.
[Inaudible]
MAN: He was supposed
to stop there.
MAN: His front was--
MAN: Right there.
MAN: His front was
supposed to stop there.
Is everyone OK?
CAT: Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, everyone's good.
MAN: Man, look at that.
MAN: Why do we pay these
stunt guys so much?
MAN: 'Cause they're so good.
Brendan Flynt, bravo.
[Scattered applause]
CAT: [inaudible].
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yeah, because
people would have been knocked
Over by the fucking stuff.
It was exactly where
you all were standing.
Did you not see that shit?
INTERVIEWER: Yeah, I saw
the car go all the way in.
I'm like, I think
he missed the mark.
Did you see me fall off
the 12-foot fucking ladder?
INTERVIEWER: No.
So you're saying the
car stopped only about--
Yeah, about like that.
INTERVIEWER: --a foot
further than what
You thought it was gonna do?
Yeah, because I put the
sand bags to stop the car.
Like, it would be about
that far form the cage,
'Cause Brendan wanted me to
come into the [inaudible]
As much as I could
INTERVIEWER: Mhm.
So because I didn't
feel the sand bags,
I hit only just maybe a
fraction of a second late.
But that's why, too, 'cause I
knew nobody would be back here.
And I knew everybody
would be back here.
So I just wanted
to, like, give them
As much clearance as possible.
So I gotta calm down a
little bit right now, man.
INTERVIEWER: Yeah,
I feel the same way.
Don't worry.
My heart's about to break
in my chest right now.
It's fucking-- it's crazy.
INTERVIEWER: Did you
get scared, Tito?
A little.
I thought I almost died.
Fucking [inaudible].
It looked great.
INTERVIEWER: Yeah, looks
good for, like, the DVD.
[Inaudible] humans.
INTERVIEWER: Yeah.
Oh.
Lloyd.
Yes, sir?
Can I get your view
on how that stunt went?
Um.
The three rules of production,
Troma's rules of production,
Were not posted.
They're not posted here because
we moved back to this location.
And I think that is the primary
reason why this stunt, while it
Looked very good on camera, came
very close to killing people.
I'm not happy.
I don't think it's worthwhile.
I don't think that shot
really was worth it.
And it wasn't really
that good, so--
MAN: There's Aaron afterwards.
MAN: And action, car.
[Crash]
Shit!
That's not good.
Whoa.
[Chatter]
I got all that.
You all right, Aaron?
Yeah, dude.
Holy shit.
CAT: Everyone OK?
MAN: Yeah!
Give him a hand there, dude.
[Chatter]
LLOYD KAUFMAN:
It's not worth it.
It's only a fucking movie, just
for later in life, that's all.
-Yeah.
-It's only a fucking movie.
If there's any risk at all.
I mean, you're the lead
paint guy, for Christ sake.
That's what I was thinking about
in the middle of the night.
Here's the lead paint guy.
The lead paint
thing was bullshit.
The thing you did
was total stupidity.
And you disobeyed an old man and
an older director/photographer
And all these professionals who
you should have listened to.
I honestly didn't-- I really
didn't-- you know, just--
Nobody thought that
was gonna be a factor.
Well, no, I thought it
would be, and so did Brendan.
We cleared everybody out there.
I made announcements.
We kept making announcements.
And we know there's
always that risk.
There's always a risk.
You know, that car, who knows?
It could have hit something.
It could have hit
computers that don't work.
I don't know.
And again, it's just
a fucking movie.
That's why you don't
do those things.
You don't.
It's just not worth it.
But it's my opinion that
had those signs been up--
The signs were up today,
like they should have been--
I think everybody would
have it on their mind
And would have been a
little more cooperative
About being anywhere near it.
So luckily, nothing happened.
Is Jared here?
JARED: Yes, sir.
You have to do a better job.
This place is a pig sty.
Look.
There's glass all over the
place, ready to fall down.
Look at this filth.
Look at this.
Why don't you have these guys
like Terrence and Joe Cortese?
Well, again, you didn't have to.
But it's nice of you to do it.
You don't have to do this.
We'll fire them,
one or the other.
This is gonna fall down.
It's been here all day.
It's been smashed.
This is plastic, but it's--
this has been here all day.
It's filth, and it's dangerous.
And that's their job, right?
So please have Terrence--
or get rid of them.
We should fire both
of them, I think.
I mean, no.
We didn't have coffee.
I am really happy
about the fact
That we're gonna do
this scene with Roy
Winning an Academy Award.
And Toxie wrapped tonight.
[Cheering and applause]
The best-- the best
Toxic Avenger ever!
The best!
Thank you.
No, seriously, I would not
have been able to do any of it
Without the fantastic crew that
was here for this entire movie.
And I really appreciate
everybody getting water
And running around
like freaks [inaudible]
Doing everything everybody did.
And seriously, I couldn't
have done it without the crew.
I mean--
LLOYD KAUFMAN: Yeah!
Totally a team effort.
[Applause]
So it's not even
gonna be Dave Mattey.
Here we go.
Ready?
Action!
[Crazed laughter]
You like me.
You really like me!
I
Would like to thank God, Jesus
Christ, the MPAA rating board
For creating this incredibly
historic occasion.
And now, if we could bow our
heads for a moment of silence
In honor of all the alcoholic,
crack-addicted, ugly,
Native American unmarried
mothers, and all
The other distasteful minorities
whom the Hollywood elite have
Banned, blacklisted, whose
property has been taken away,
Who have been
totally fucked over.
What-- why-- award?
I don't want this
fu-- fuck this award!
I don't-- you take it.
And in fact, you can
take that fucking award
And shove it up my sweet pooper.
TRENT HAAGA: Freeze.
And unfreeze.
Yeah, Hollywood, we don't
need your fucking awards.
We're the Troma team!
Fuck you!
[Cheering and applause]
Mr. Trent Haaga will make a
very important announcement.
[Applause]
Everyone, everyone,
thank you all very much.
That has completed principal
photography for "Toxic
Avenger 4-- Citizen Toxie."
Thank you Troma!
PATRICK CASSIDY:
They said the best
Thing about working on a
movie is the people you meet.
And the memories that
you take with you
Are all of those people, not
all the production stuff.
You do try to block
that out of your memory.
Because it's the worst part.
Making the movie is the
actual the worst part
Of making the movie.
The process of getting
actors, honestly,
Getting the special
effects ready,
Getting the stunt people to do
what they're supposed to do,
Which they never
do-- all that stuff
Is just fucked up and
hard to deal with.
So you want to forget
almost immediately.
And we finished the movie.
And it's gonna be great, so
that's what the beauty of Troma
Is-- dedicated individuals
doing hard work for a good cause
Just to make art,
to make Lloyd rich.
MAN: Because Lloyd is rich.
Oh, yeah.
He's a rich motherfucker.
[Music - "radetzky march"]
And I guarantee you, when they
edit this film, at some point
When they listen to
the sound, they're
Gonna have scenes
with the sounds
Of snoring in the background.
I guarantee it.
Because there was
snoring up and down
The hallways during the last
few shoots this morning.
[Music - "radetzky march"]
[Snoring]
MAN: Where's Brendan?
Oh, [inaudible].
Ah.
INTERVIEWER: So what stunt--
is he rehearsing anything?
--[laugh] It's the infamous
snoring stunt for the film.
It's something that the rest
of us don't get to do is sleep.
So watch me get
unchanged-- unchanged.
(SINGING) Watch
me get unchanged.
WOMAN: Do the deodorant.
Do it, do it.
Should we have the
deodorant dance?
WOMAN: That's right.
-There's not much left.
Zork, you want to see
my morning ritual?
INTERVIEWER: Let's see
Tito's morning ritual.
[Dog barking]
TITO: Allie, I can borrow money?
That's cool?
I was like, sure.
You're the greatest.
[Spraying]
(SINGING) Deodorant time,
deodorant time, deodorant time.
Wait for the rub.
Deodorant time.
Deodorant, ah, ah,
deodorant time.
Deodorant time, ooh,
ooh, deodorant time.
INTERVIEWER: No wonder
you got cast as a retard.
He is one.