How could you let that happen?
You were supposed to short it.
- I don't care what the indicators said.
- Hey, Bobby, can you bring the car around?
We're gonna be ready to go
in like 10 minutes. Thank you.
Well, I operate on information,
not market trends. You know that.
- This is Pierre.
- Come on.
- How may I help you?
- Hello, Pierre, this is Mrs. Dutchman.
We're running about an hour behind so
I'm gonna need to push our reservation.
- Is that all right?
- Not a problem.
Your table will be ready for you
whenever you arrive.
Gorgeous.
- It's okay.
- Absolutely gorgeous.
But... there's something missing.
Close your eyes.
Happy 19th, baby.
Mark.
- It's... it's stunning.
- Just like you.
Only the best for my girl.
- I love you.
- Love you.
Let's go.
Welcome to the Boom Boom Room.
One drink and we're out.
We can raise whatever you need.
You believe that you Italians invented sex
whereas everyone knows...
- We could have a little private party.
- ...that we Greeks did.
- Hey.
So that cryptic message on the phone,
what are we talking about?
- Bronson and Jennings.
- The pharmaceutical company.
It's selling at 25,
come Monday, it's half that.
Their new cancer drug is shit.
It's getting squashed next week.
So we short B & J?
And buy up what's left with the profit.
- I didn't see you at the conservancy lunch.
- I know, I'm sorry, I couldn't make it.
- You know, there's an opening on the board.
- I know, but my plate is so full...
...and I was thinking
that Deanna would be perfect.
- I'd be honored to help out.
- We should talk.
- Positiv.
- What the fuck is Positiv?
The most successful female Viagra
the world has ever seen.
B & J holds the patent.
Now you have my attention.
Ladies, you know
it's my anniversary, so I am...
- Happy anniversary.
- Yes, say goodnight.
Well, in that case, I'll wire the funds.
- Use the...
- Yeah, yeah, the family account.
I know about the family account.
Family account? What are you boys plotting?
Our new summer house in South Hampton.
- Suzanne.
- Ladies and gentlemen.
Miss Sasha Lazard.
Taxi for you, Mr. Dutchman?
My driver's here, thanks.
How do you know my name?
I've seen you on Mad Money and The Crunch.
"Put your drive at the top of the list
and you become an unstoppable force."
- Not bad.
- Your words really hit home with me.
Keep watching, kid.
Sir, any chance a hard working guy
who's ready to put the job first...
...could catch a break and come work for you?
Why the hell would I give you a job?
How else is a guy from the outside
supposed to get in?
Give my office a call tomorrow.
We'll see if we can use you.
Now that is what I'm talking about.
What was that business with Howard
about the family account?
It's just an opportunity
that shouldn't be missed.
I know, but what did it have to do
with the family account?
Just tax reasons, baby.
Let me worry about the business, okay?
- I've done well so far, right?
- Excellent.
Did I tell you who called me the other day?
Who?
- Aaron.
- Steele?
- Your old boss, huh?
- Yes.
For what?
That they're looking for an executive editor
and he was wanting me to come back.
For what, 120 K a year plus dental?
Why bother?
Well, it's not really
about the money and it's...
Baby, between India and China
and this new deal with Howard...
...I need... I need all your attention
on me right now. All of it.
It's too important.
I love you so much.
Stop wasting my time, Lewis.
I don't want to hear it.
Yeah, don't call me again
until it's done. All right?
We're only interested in alpha projects
with outsized returns.
Stop nodding when you
don't understand something.
- It's your worst tell.
- Tell?
Pick up a copy of Doyle Brunsen's
Super System.
Read it cover to cover by next week
or don't bother coming back.
- What's it about?
- Power poker.
- Got it.
- Don't say got it.
Faster than I would have given you
credit for, Lewis. Let's hear it.
You just earned your Hanukah bonus.
Congratulations.
- You play golf?
- Not well.
Learn. You only play the
Deep Dale Cub in Long Island.
Why the Deep Dale Cub?
You don't know something, act like
you do until you've figured it out.
And what if I can't figure it out, boss?
You can't figure it out,
join the fucking peace corps...
...'cause that means
you're not cut out for this game.
I should have my own show. Fuck Trump.
Fuck me.
That's a true story.
Oh, hold on.
My, my, my, I like this place. Indeed I do.
Excuse me, I have to go
speak to my concierge.
Yeah, give me that leg.
Are you sure you have enough?
My dear woman, I'm an aristocrat.
We always have enough.
You're facing real time, Howard.
And believe me, we would love
to see you do that time.
But there's something we'd love even more.
Inhale, the right leg up. Exhale, step
the right foot in between your hands.
Inhale, open up your chest. Exhale and
pop the left knee behind the right ankle...
...sit down seated, final twist.
Inhale, the right hand down, the left arm up.
Exhale, twist, look over your right shoulder.
Suzanne Dutchman?
Yes?
I'm gonna need you to come with me. Let's go.
What the hell is going on?
This is all Howard.
We are not guilty in any way.
Without his testimony, they ain't got shit.
Why are they holding you without bail?
You know they're saying
they're gonna charge me.
No, no, no, no. The lawyers
are going to straighten this out.
Listen to me. Nothing is gonna happen to you.
Okay?
- Is this your first time?
- Yeah.
- What made you come?
- Sorry?
Why did you volunteer?
I wanted to do something good
for the community.
When people see a blind man start to get
up, their instinct is to grab his arm.
- Big mistake with Bill.
- Got it.
Don't use hand signals.
Bill can still see some shapes and light...
...but he won't be able to discern
any waving or pointing.
No gesticulation.
I'll take two.
I'll take one.
Flush, jack high.
Sorry, Sonny, straight flush to the king.
Damn.
When you speak to a blind person,
don't omit words like see or look.
No one wants to be asked if they've
heard any good movies lately.
Got it.
Remember, he's a person. His disability
is only one feature of his personality.
- I know who he is.
- He doesn't like fans, either.
No, no, no, what are you doing
with that fucking thing?
If the luddites had persevered,
we'd all be a hell of a lot happier.
- I'll give this shit something to worry about!
- Becca, what's wrong?
I was trying to teach him
about the new GPS app...
...and he started screaming saying that
technology was gonna rob us of our humanity.
Good luck.
Gavin O'Connor, meet Bill Oakland,
our very own Indominus Rex.
You know I prefer the sound
of a lady's voice, Ella.
- Well, he's pretty like a lady.
- When are you going to run away with me?
When are you going to shave?
Everybody keeps talking about how beautiful
you are, Ella. But to me, it's your spice.
Gets me every time.
I'll see you in two hours,
you blind son of a bitch.
Hello, young man, come in, sit down.
Thank you.
- Speak.
- Excuse me?
I'm gonna need a little bit more than that.
- Sorry, I don't understand.
- Keep going.
- Keep going with what?
- For the love of God...
...would you connect three sentences together
so I'll have some sense of whether or not...
...the next two hours of my bleak
and blind life will be bearable...
- ...or torture to my ears. Could you do that?
- Yeah, I...
You're not doing community service, are you?
I volunteered.
Why? You got a hard-on for blind men?
- No, I couldn't get into your class.
- You're an undergrad.
- Sophomore.
- You couldn't get into my class...
...so you found out where I go to have
my students' stories read to me?
- Pretty much.
- I don't appreciate stalkers, O'Connor.
I'm not.
- Seen any good movies lately?
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Why are you here?
- I want to learn how to write.
- I don't teach people how to write.
- What about your students?
I teach them what not to write.
If they learn something from that,
that's their business.
Sorry I bothered you.
Jesus Christ! O'Connor...
...you're never going to get anywhere
in this world if you give up so easily.
- I mean...
- So you don't want me go?
Well, I don't particularly want you
to stay, you creepy fucking kid...
...but as you can see, there wasn't a line
of people begging to come in here and...
...read my students' mediocre stories
to me, now is there? So...
...proceed.
How To Love A Woman by Joseph Epstein.
Joey Epstein.
Jewish kid from the Bronx who thinks
he knows all the ins and outs...
- ...of how to love a woman.
- Well, does he?
- No.
- Does anyone?
One or two.
Do you?
Read.
Far, far away, behind the word mountains...
...far from the countries,
there lived the blind texts.
Separated, they lived in Bookmarks Groove.
Right at the coast of a large language ocean.
I guess sometimes people get in a rut
and can't see how to get out.
But what Momma must have forgot is,
there's always a way out.
Suzanne Dutchman, while your name
is on the account associated...
...with your husband's
alleged illegal activities...
...and while you did stand to profit
from your husband's actions...
...I do believe that you were not
fully aware of those activities.
Therefore I endorse your plea to 100 hours
of community service effective immediately.
Hey, Ella.
You platza?
- Excuse me?
- The Russian baths out in Brighton Beach.
- Platza.
- I'm still not following you.
They lay you down in a sauna and then
a big fat hairy Russian guy comes in...
...with an oil-dipped oak-leaf brush
and just beats the stress...
...right out of your back and shoulders.
Wow, people pay for this?
They say it keeps you young.
I'm going this Saturday if you're curious.
Back to work, Jimmy.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you so much.
I'll see you soon, have a good one.
Hello.
I'm Suzanne Dutchman.
I think I'm supposed to report here.
Dutchman.
Docket number 2564.
Welcome to the Beacon for the Blind.
Right this way.
Always keep in mind his disability
is only one aspect of his personality.
Yeah, you'll get used to it. Use his name
when addressing him in a group setting.
Oh, hey, Janice.
- Don't ever push, poke or shove him.
- Of course not. Why would I do that?
Well, when people see a blind person start
to get up their instinct is to help him.
But with Bill, if he ever needs
any help, he'll let you know.
He can still see shapes and light,
but don't use any hand signals or gestures.
He won't be able to make them out.
And then one last thing...
...for the visually impaired,
feeling is seeing.
- So don't be alarmed if he touches you.
- Touches?
Just give me one minute. Bill?
- Bill.
- Yes?
Good news for you today.
We finally have a female reader for you.
- What does she look like?
- What do you care?
Well, I wasn't always blind.
Suzanne?
Suzanne Dutchman, meet Bill Oakland.
How do you do, Mr. Oakland?
Tough name to carry around
these days, I'm sorry.
- Excuse me?
- Dutchman.
The guy who wanted to lay off 3,000 workers
to make a buck that he didn't really need.
You must have heard of this sociopath.
Yes, I have.
He's my husband.
Well, I'm sure he's nice
once you get to know him.
I'll be leaving you two alone then.
Just... just one minute.
You're not leaving me
alone with him, are you?
- Yes.
- But are you sure that he's stable?
Stable?
He's not the one here because of
a court order, Mrs. Dutchman, you are.
And please keep in mind that if I report
one violation of your agreement...
...you will be remanded to prison.
- I... look, I don't want trouble. I just...
- Then don't commit any violations.
Okay.
Won't you sit down?
What would you like me to read first?
Before we get to that,
I'm just curious, why are you here?
I was given 100 hours of community service.
No, I mean, how did a nice girl like you...
...end up married to an asshole
like Mark Dutchman?
I don't have to explain myself to you.
Well, I already know
everything I need to know.
- Do you?
- Oh, my dear.
Even a visually impaired man
can see what you're all about.
- And what am I all about?
- I know your type.
- And what type is that?
- The type who loves...
...her enormous penthouse and her
ridiculously oversized diamond ring...
...enough to cast a blind eye
to all the heartless acts...
...her husband had to commit
in order to get her these things.
I don't have to tolerate this.
You know, it's actually my civic duty
perhaps to punish you just a little.
Your civic duty to punish me
for a crime I didn't commit...
...and something that you know nothing about.
You know what, go fuck yourself, Mr. Oakland.
It's go fuck yourself, Bill.
- I'd like to request a transfer.
- You're not allowed to leave the room.
Well, I did and I am not spending the next,
I don't know, however many months...
...reading to that cretin in a prison cell
of a room. He's absolutely repugnant.
Did someone tell you
this is supposed to be fun?
You have an hour and 40 minutes left.
And remember, one violation.
So I suggest you get back there.
Now.
Oh, my God.
Can we just start reading?
You know, it's rude to leave
the room without telling me.
I was sitting here talking
to you and now I don't know...
...what you heard and what you missed.
You could be nicer to me.
Look, we got off on the wrong foot.
Could we start over again?
No.
Why not?
Because I don't want to.
Why don't we begin with...
Margie Thompson, Jeannie Lost Her Way.
So, what's the latest with Mark?
When's he getting out?
He just keeps telling me not to worry.
But I'm worried.
Well, he's going to get out, right?
It's Mark, I'm sure
he's gonna figure out a way.
Can you believe that he
hasn't even apologized to me?
I don't know whatever this crap is
that he and Howard got into.
Using the family account, what an idiot.
- Everyone makes mistakes.
- Yeah, well, this is a big one.
At least you're not the one in prison.
After all, how bad could reading
to a blind man really be?
You try it.
- If it were me.
- Yeah?
I'd make the most of it. Have a little fun.
Why not? Try something outrageous...
...that you can only get away with
if you're stuck in a room with a blind man.
I mean, is he good looking?
Believe me, there is nothing fun
about spending time with this man.
Hey, it's me calling, I just want to
let you know that I went to the store...
...and I'm gonna cook you
one hell of a sexy dinner.
So work up an appetite.
Hey, it's me calling.
Have I told you lately
how brilliant and bold...
...and how beautiful, and brave,
and all the other b-words...
...that mean perfect man, that you are?
In case you don't know
who's calling, this is your wife.
Anyway, I love you.
- Hey, how it's going, Ella?
- Oh, Gaelin, how are you?
No, it's Gavin.
- Oh, sorry.
- That's all right.
We tried to call you but the number
you gave us didn't work.
Yeah, I'm sorry, I had to switch my service.
Bill's been assigned a court ordered reader
so he won't be needing you anymore.
Can I go up and say goodbye?
Please.
Pretty please.
Five minutes.
Thank you.
So I hear you finally got a woman's voice.
- Is that you, Gavin?
- The one and only.
Come in for a minute, sit down.
I just wanted to come by and say that...
...it's been real fun hanging out with you.
You are a true masochist, Gavin.
Well, the truth is my father
ran out on me when I was two.
- Hold on, let me get out my violin.
- Would you just listen to me for a second?
I got into a lot of fights as a kid.
- Good for you.
- My mother was great to me.
She... she was really lonely.
Ended up with a really nice guy
and I should be thankful, but...
He wasn't a man, you know what I mean?
I might.
When I read "Throw it
on the Line for Venus..."
...for the first time in my life,
Bill, it was like...
...someone taught me
what it meant to be a man.
When did I tell you you could call me Bill?
- Seriously.
- What is it you want to say, Gavin?
You still live up to your book.
And I lied to you. I'm not enrolled at NYU.
I moved to New York two months ago
with 700 bucks in my pocket.
And you know what, Bill?
It was worth it.
Are you handy, Gavin?
What do you mean?
I have some projects I'm working on at home.
Maybe you could come by
and give me a hand this weekend.
Call me on Friday.
Cool.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to disturb you.
No, not at all.
You're just in time to meet my protege.
The only kid crazy enough
to volunteer to read for me.
Gavin O'Connor, meet Suzanne Dutchman.
- How do you do?
- Fascinated to meet you.
- Oh, why is that?
- I just can't imagine anyone...
...volunteering to spend time with this man.
Well, he's an acquired taste,
but he's worth it.
All right, Gavin, I'll talk to you on Friday.
- Thanks, Bill. It was nice meeting you.
- Nice meeting you.
I'm sorry I talked to you that way.
I had no call to treat you like that.
Thank you. I appreciate your apology.
How was your day off?
It was fine.
That's good.
You still don't like me, do you?
Am I supposed to like you?
You might try.
I'm sure that you were self-centered
and narcissistic before your accident.
And now you're self-centered,
narcissistic and blind.
I brought you a present.
Is it a green tea candle?
It might be.
- Why, can you smell it?
- Yes. It stinks.
- You don't like green tea?
- No.
But I'll tell you what I do like.
I like your perfume.
Muguet de Bois.
How do you know Muguet de Bois?
They don't make it anymore.
My stepmother used to wear it.
Well, she's got good taste.
Yes. In everything except men.
So do I just take one
from the top of the stack?
Yes, and please get rid
of that foul smelling candle.
- It really does stink in here.
- You'll get used to it.
So where are we?
The grand jury's being sworn and they're
gonna start to hear evidence soon.
- How long?
- It's impossible to say at this time...
- ...but you know, maybe 3 or 4 weeks.
- Not good enough.
Mark... I need you to take
an honest look at what you're facing.
There's a possibility of you
doing substantial time.
Your associate is testifying against you.
Arnold, let me ask you something.
Why the fuck am I paying you
$1200 an hour for?
- To represent your interests.
- Tell me again?
- So why are you telling me the obvious?
Do your job, stop dicking around
and get me the fuck out of here.
Okay.
Thank you, my beautiful wife is here.
- Hello, Arnold.
- Mrs. Dutchman.
- Hey, baby.
- Hi.
Any progress?
I have faith in the legal system.
Is he saying how long?
Soon. Soon.
- Are you doing okay in here?
- It's not a situation I can't handle.
Where's your ring?
I didn't think it was a good time
to be flaunting what we have.
I want that ring on your finger. You hear me?
- Mark...
- There's nothing to be ashamed of.
It's just a little uncomfortable.
- Tell me about the community service.
- It's fine.
What do you want to know?
This blind man you read to.
What's he do?
He was a novelist and now he teaches.
Teaches.
- What's his name?
- Bill Oakland.
He wrote that book,
"Throw it on the Line for Venus."
- It made a lot of money.
- He doesn't have a lot of money now.
What'd you think?
- Of the book?
- Yeah.
I never read it.
"She put down her book, leaned back and
clasped the paper knife tightly in both hands.
"There was nothing to be ashamed of.
She called up all her Moscow memories.
"She recalled the ball, and Vronsky
and his humble, enamored gaze...
"...and their relations with one another.
There was nothing to be ashamed of."
Hold on. Hold on.
Why are you reading it that way?
- What way?
- As if it has no meaning.
This is the most
important moment in the book.
This is the moment that Anna realizes
that she can no longer go on...
...bullshitting herself
that she's happy with her life.
- Okay.
- And once you cross that line...
...you either have to make the terrifying
change that will alter your life...
...in ways you can't imagine...
- ...or.
- Or?
You take the safe route.
To live out the rest of your days
drowning in that familiar security...
...while at night your dreams are filled
with feasts you never touched...
...and love you never tasted.
Why aren't you saying anything?
I thought I was supposed to be
reading your students' stories.
I'm teaching Karenina next semester.
I wanted to get reacquainted.
Okay, sorry, I'm...
- Where were we?
- "Nothing to be ashamed of."
Right. "There's nothing to be ashamed of.
"And yet...
"...at this very point
of her recollections...
"...the feeling of shame was intensified...
"...just as though when she
was thinking about Vronsky...
"...some inner voice said to her,
warm, very warm, hot.
"While she said to herself resolutely
changing her position on the seat...
"...what about it? What does it mean?
"Am I really afraid to look straight
at what passed between us?
"Well, what did pass between us,
is there really...
"...can there be anything more
between myself and that boy officer...
"...than there is between me
and every one of my acquaintances?"
Oh, honey pot, you like your Chanel No. 5.
"Something in my blood was screaming out...
"...at the top of his lungs,
can we still save the big easy?"
Can we open the window?
- I'm sorry, would you repeat that?
- Can we open... open the window?
If I may, please don't break
the rhythm of a sentence...
...to ask some question.
I mean, the kid was getting close
to writing a halfway decent line...
...and now the rhythm is lost to me.
It's just really uncomfortably hot in here.
- What is going on with you today?
- Nothing.
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine, it's just...
...it's just hot.
Look, it isn't easy to edit
when you can't look at the words.
I'm sure you understand.
We can't open the window...
...because the noise from outside
makes it hard for me to...
...follow the rhythm of each sentence...
...paragraph, page, so...
...can you help me?
Yes, yes.
"The snake...
"...of the river below...
"...as you fly into the city
is a good portent for the balance...
"...between sweet and sinister
one encounters in New Orleans.
"The winding river works
his way through her center...
"...providing the city with life
knowing all the time...
"...he can take it away on a whim.
"Down by the river, in the heart of
the quarter, there stands a statue.
"Old man river, a man with a past.
"Arms reach empty handed...
"...God to a city in love with..."
Wait.
- What just happened?
- I don't know, he kinda lost me here.
No, I mean with you.
- Nothing.
- Your scent just changed.
- What do you mean my scent?
- Your pheromones got stronger.
Hey, Bill, just getting the...
- ...trash.
- Hey, Joey.
How's that Shakespeare workshop coming?
Just great, Bill.
- In fact, it's fan-fucking-tastic.
- That's good to hear.
Okay, then... you two have a good time.
Where were we?
"God to a city in love with water."
Hi.
It was just really,
really hot in there today.
What?
I feel like I'm going crazy.
Like I'm... like I'm losing my shit.
I don't even know what's real anymore.
I don't even know if I know
who Mark is anymore.
I don't even know if I know who I am.
Well, I know who you are
and I think you're fucking fabulous.
That's real.
Do you think Mark's a good guy?
What? I mean, yeah, of course.
Do you really think that he's a good man?
Yes. Why would you ask me that?
He's having an affair.
My God.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Do you know who she is?
Not yet.
God, I feel so stupid.
- You're not stupid.
- No, I really, I feel so stupid.
Like such an idiot.
Fuck him. What are you gonna do?
I don't know,
it feels like it's all falling apart.
- Suze.
- Literally everything...
...everything is falling apart.
But something has to change...
...'cause this isn't working.
What you looking for?
I was just checking to make sure
this is the right place.
- The right place for what?
- I'm looking for a friend of mine.
- Papi, who?
- Bill Oakland.
Yeah, this is the right place.
I'm the super, he expecting you?
- Yeah.
- Hey, you want a beer?
Thanks, but it's a little early for me.
Don't ever let people tell you how to live.
Bill's on the second floor.
- Thanks, man.
- You got it, buddy.
Bill?
I'm back here.
Hey.
Welcome, Gavin, make yourself at home.
Gee, thanks.
So...
...what's this project you're talking about?
You know this wasn't really what I had
in mind when you said projects.
Scrub.
You don't have a vacuum cleaner?
No.
- Bill.
- I don't entertain much.
So what are you having me do all of this for?
You ever see the Karate Kid?
Yeah.
You're awfully quiet, Gavin.
I just had an idea for a short story.
See, there's a method to my madness.
Right.
I'll be out soon, baby.
Best assured you won't be doing
community service any longer.
It's not that bad, actually.
Not that bad?
What, you like reading to this guy?
No, it's not that.
It just feels good to be productive again.
What's that supposed to mean?
I need stability outside of you.
Why would you say that?
Why?
Because you made choices.
Choices that you didn't consult me on.
You know how many choices I make in a day?
Am I supposed to consult you on every one?
I don't care how many decisions
you have to make.
I care about this decision
which landed you here...
...and implicated me.
We're not guilty!
Howard is. You'll understand that
when I'm out of this hellhole...
...and you won't have to read
to any fucking cripple anymore.
I'm sorry, baby, I'm sorry.
Just this place is getting to me.
You can... listen to me.
I got your back, huh?
You can depend on me.
I promise you.
So how come you never finished
your second book?
- How come you never finished your first?
- I'm building life experience.
What's your story, Gavin? You got a girl?
There's a girl. I'm just waiting
for the moment to present itself.
- What's she like?
- Well, you know her.
You mean Ella?
- Yeah.
- Forget it.
- What?
- Don't stop cleaning, by the way.
You are definitely not ready
for a girl like that.
You might not know this, Bill,
but I am a very good-looking guy.
That's so funny, because you
don't come across like one.
Well, I was voted best
looking guy in high school.
Not enough for a quality woman,
a keeper like Ella.
And besides, your looks are
only one part of the equation.
So what's the rest?
Smarts, humor, money.
The ability to make her feel safe.
The... the unpredictability of a great lover.
So I got four out of five,
with potential for money.
- How you gonna make money?
- Writing.
What?
One day, you're gonna meet a girl.
And she's gonna be
lying in your arms in bed...
...and everything is just...
...going to make sense.
Jesus, Bill. You're getting me
all hot and bothered over here.
No, but seriously, when was the last time?
You know, the last time
you were with a woman?
Not since my wife.
- Jesus!
- Your sympathy is much appreciated.
I'd lose my fucking mind.
- How do you know I haven't already?
- Oh, that explains a lot.
Hey, Bill, I'm leaving.
Bill.
Gavin!
What?
I didn't expect you to work
for the privilege of my company.
I don't want to take your money, Bill.
I'm not offering you money,
you presumptive little shit.
I'm inviting you to sit in on my class.
- You mean that?
- Consider it a token of my appreciation.
Thank you, Bill.
You're all right, O'Connor.
- Not the worst you ever met, right?
- You're quoting my book.
Get the fuck out of here.
What's your problem, Michelle?
I don't know how many more
of these parties I can do.
Well, the party is in my honor.
It would be rude not to show up.
Rude? How about how rude it is
that you're never home anymore?
Our strong readers
could come in three hours early.
And then you can do the rounds
I would normally be doing...
...when I'm talking to the volunteers that
first come here. That would be helpful.
And then there was one other thing
that I wanted to ask you.
Oh, hey, Bill. You're here early.
I just thought I'd do a little cleaning
before she gets here.
Oh, my. You do windows too?
Anyway, where was I?
I must be in the wrong room.
I was looking for Bill Oakland.
You inspired me.
I inspired you?
Every time you walk in this room...
...you make me feel something
I thought I never would again.
And what's that?
Possibilities.
- Do you need to get that?
- Yes, I'm sorry.
Is everything okay?
Yes. Great.
May I ask you to do something for me?
Sure.
It's a lot to ask, but you'd
really be doing me a big favor.
I used to love the smell of this.
Reminds me of when I was a kid.
My father injured himself
in a grilling accident...
...and I had to shave him for two weeks.
That sounds so naughty, but I love it.
Don't be obscene.
We're all just trying to get home, I suppose.
I'm about to put an extremely
sharp razor against your neck.
I would choose my next words carefully.
They could be your last.
I'm in your hands.
Nice.
How many times did you say
you shaved your father?
I was a kid.
Look, I need to get your chin.
There you go, stretch it out.
Sexy.
How do I look?
Very handsome.
Suzanne Dutchman.
What's up, homes?
What's the matter? You got ass-burgers?
- What?
- Ass-burgers.
You anti-social or something, hey?
You mean Asperger's?
No, I don't. I just don't particularly
want to talk right now, okay?
Listen to this particular motherfucker.
From now on, you don't eat.
You bring your food, you put it on a tray
and you bring it to me.
Big Ricky G. Entiendes? You understand?
Didn't your mother teach you
not to touch another man's brownie?
What the fuck did you say about my mother?
Break it up, break it up!
Now exiting subway.
Your destination is 200 feet straight ahead.
Beacon for the Blind.
Approaching 50 feet.
You've now arrived at your destination.
Turn right.
Hello.
- Oh, you're here early.
- I am.
How are you today?
Well... I'm doing okay.
- How are you doing?
- I'm pretty good.
What would you like to
start with today? Maybe...
Margie Thompson? "Get her out of the way."
I want to go to the park.
I want you to take me to the park.
I'm not allowed to leave the room.
I know, so...
...we'd better not get caught.
- I want to hold onto you.
- But I don't know if I know how to do this.
It's okay, I'll show you.
- How you doing, boss?
- What'd you find?
She reads to him two hours, three times
a week and then she goes home.
That it?
Yeah, I don't think you got
anything to worry about there.
Have you seen what my wife looks like?
Yes, boss, but he's blind.
That doesn't make him a eunuch.
I'm on it, Mr. Dutchman. Take care.
I feel like we're the bad kids
ditching school to go smoke.
- What's wrong with that?
- You were one of the bad kids.
I was as a matter of fact,
but that's a long time ago.
Isn't this pond just beautiful?
And that rock face over there,
its just exquisite. Don't you think?
Yes, I do. It's stunning.
Do you still remember what it looks like?
Oh, yes, yes, I do.
I have to reimagine it over
and over again so I don't forget.
No, it's the other things
that are hard about going blind.
- Like what things?
- You have to...
...relearn everything like a child.
How to wash yourself.
How to boil water. How to function.
It took me a year just to get up the nerve
to step outside my apartment.
Well, and now look at you,
escorting me to the park.
What are the chances?
- Is this the ball field?
- Yes.
- You know what I like about this ball field?
- What's that?
Is that I can walk around here
without my hands in front of my face.
You don't walk around
with your hands in front of your face.
That doesn't mean I live without that fear.
You know, I played football on this field
every weekend until I was 40.
- Are there kids on the field right now?
- No, we're...
Okay, then hit me long!
Bill!
Oh, shit.
Bill, are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I think so.
Don't ever do that again.
- Wait.
- What?
I think I can see.
Shit, we're gonna be late.
Get... get up, come on.
Get up, get up.
- She's there.
- Let's take the stairs.
10 o'clock, 10 o'clock.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
"When she read how Lady Mary
rode to the hounds...
"...teased the bride and astonished...
- "...everybody by her boldness..."
- It's 4:04."
Ella, if I could have another moment
with Mrs. Dutchman.
- I want to hear the end of this chapter.
- Yeah, well, that's up to her.
Oh, it's a page and a half. It's fine.
Okay, suit yourself.
- What is it?
- It's a leaf.
Hi.
Okay, okay, now you all know I respect
y'all's opinions, but I'm sorry.
Can we please just talk about...
...the obvious latent homosexuality
rampant throughout this chapter?
I mean, the blood, the flesh...
...and the 11 Greeks
piling out of Camille's house...
...and Dean stays in bed for three days.
Hello? Is there any question that Sal
wants to stick it up Dean's ass?
Hey, come on. A little respect, please.
Oh, I'm sorry, did you have another
interpretation, homophobe?
I see on the road as being a little deeper...
...than Sal just wanting
to stick it up Dean's ass, yes.
Darling, you can go as deep as you like.
I think Kerouac's saying Dean is Christ.
- Closeted!
- All right, enough of this shit.
A writer is always entitled
to his intention just as the reader...
...is always entitled to his
interpretation of the work.
A lot of people think that Kerouac
was, as Kyle put it, closeted.
But when it comes to on the road
I tend to agree with O'Connor...
...in terms of Kerouac's intention.
Page 185, Dean says "they came into
the room and found me lying on the bed...
"...my arms stretched out forever."
This is after three days, page 186.
"They unwrapped the bandages and showed me.
"The flesh, about half an inch,
was missing under the nail..."
...which could be an interpretation
of a stake going through the hand.
The 11 greeks?
How about the 11 apostles,
Sal being the 12th...
...which makes Dean...
All right now, get the hell out of here
and go get some experience.
Bill, thanks for letting me sit in.
You're better than the rest of them.
- You mean that?
- I told you not to ask me stupid questions.
See you later, Bill.
"I think about that night every day,
but still he haunts me.
"He hovers over my bed at night
and whispers in my dreams.
"I still have integrity.
What are you left with?"
The end.
I'd say that's a step up for Joey Epstein.
I'd hate to see his early works.
What are you reading now?
Franzen. Although I...
...did just come across
this really interesting writer...
...Bill Oakland.
So...
- ...what did you think?
- I was pleasantly surprised.
It certainly wasn't the worst I've ever read.
You... know what this means, don't you?
- No, what does this mean?
- You must have dinner with me tonight.
What?
Come with me to Brooklyn,
and I'll take you to Paris.
Paris?
Everybody knows that Brooklyn
is the new Paris.
- Really?
- Bien sur.
Well, it's been a long time
since I've been to Paris.
- So?
- So.
What do you say?
Brooklyn it is then.
Hello.
Allow me.
Chivalry is not dead among the blind.
Milla...
...may I have a vodka
on the rocks, and for you?
- Just a glass of red wine. Thank you.
- Red wine.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for inviting me.
You're probably wondering
why I asked you to come to dinner.
No, I was actually asking
myself why I said yes.
Well, I am guilty of a crime...
...that I would never forgive
someone else for committing.
I judged a book by its cover
and I misjudged you.
And in spite of your ridiculously
oversized diamond ring...
...I was wrong about you.
You're not at all...
...what I thought you were.
Well, I actually misjudged you as well.
I said that you were self-centered,
narcissistic and blind...
...and I realized that you're
self-centered, narcissistic, blind...
...and a little charming.
Thank you.
Thank you, Wes.
So maybe we can start over.
To starting over.
Do you like to travel?
I love Paris. Do you love Paris?
I do love Paris, in fact,
it's my favorite place in the whole world.
I begged my father to take me
on my 13th birthday.
And I got there and it felt
like this was home.
And I was determined to live there.
That was my plan.
I was gonna go there, write poetry...
...sit in cafes and smoke cigarettes.
- Did you end up living there?
- No.
Why not?
Just... just life and...
...you know, it just seemed
like it was a romantic notion...
...of a teenage girl and...
...and, you know, it didn't fit Mark's...
...agenda of building an empire.
'Cause for him, business is pleasure.
And that's pretty much it.
The cage with the golden bars.
I know it well.
I never planned to stay in New York.
I always thought I would end up
in Paris like the lost generation...
...or better yet in some seaside
town in the south of France.
And once I learned that you don't
need a lot of money to travel...
...I was hooked.
I went all over Europe
with very little in my pocket.
Who cared if the bed was lumpy
or the bathroom was down the hall.
The cheese was splendid and the wine
was out of this world, so...
...what more do you need?
That truly sounds heavenly.
Except for the lumpy bed.
And here we are.
How do you know this is where it's at?
That's amazing. Really impressive.
- Hey, Bill, how ya doing?
- Well, hey, Frank.
Frank, this is Suzanne. Suzanne, this is
Frank. Frank's the super of our building.
How do you do?
- You're beautiful.
- Thank you.
I tell people like it is
and you are a beautiful woman.
In fact, the two of you look pretty
freaking beautiful together.
Bill, what'd you do? The Botox.
No, Frank, it's just a shave,
but I appreciate the thought.
- Hey, no problem.
- Nice to meet you.
- Quite a colorful character.
- Yes.
Thank you for a really lovely evening.
Where are you going?
I'm... I'm gonna go home.
Wait a minute, you came all this way,
and you're not at least curious...
...to see what a blind man's
apartment looks like?
Well, I didn't realize that it was different.
Come on.
Thank you.
Can I get you something to drink?
Would you like a glass of wine?
- Sure, that sounds lovely.
- White or red?
- Red is perfect.
- Good, because all I have is red.
Is this your office?
Yes.
You look good on the track.
Well, it's how I put myself through school.
Is this postcard from the south of France?
Yes, it's from the Cote d'Azur,
my favorite place in the world.
The town is called Eze.
Your wife is very pretty.
Thank you.
No kids?
No, I...
...I realized that I...
...couldn't be a good father
and good writer, so no kids.
- How about yourself?
- We tried for a long time, but...
...it didn't work.
Here you are.
Straight, 12 o'clock.
Thank you.
So tell me, dinner at the French
restaurant, the stroll...
...the wine...
...I don't know, is this part
of the normal Bill Oakland routine?
Actually, I haven't had a woman
up to this apartment in...
...five years.
Well, I guess then I should be honored.
- May I ask you a question?
- Sure.
I can see shapes.
I can make out your skin tone, but...
...what do you look like?
I have brown hair, hazel eyes.
No, what do you look like?
Why don't you see for yourself?
I can see that you're beautiful.
And I can see that you're fragile.
I wanna see the way that you see.
How you see me.
I can see that you're fragile too.
Suzanne?
Hello?
Okay.
Yeah, okay.
I have a reservation at Versailles at 7:00.
You think I'll make that?
- Yes.
- All rise.
Due to the untimely death of our key
witness, the government has no choice...
...but to drop all charges
against Mark Dutchman.
Mr. Dutchman, excuse me!
Mr. Dutchman, what do you think happened
to your former associate Howard Cunningham?
Howard Cunningham told lies
about me and I'll never know why.
But let's get one thing straight. I am...
...I am still grieving over the freak
accident that took my friend's life.
That's all I have to say.
Sir, did you have any comments?
Didn't I tell you that
it was going to work out?
You did.
Home sweet home.
What's wrong?
What really happened to Howard?
He got hit by a bus.
Karma's a bitch.
I had nothing to do with Howard's death.
How is your blind man?
I guess he'll be sad now he
doesn't get to sit in his little room...
...jerking off about my wife.
Thought you'd be happy about that.
Of course I am.
I'm gonna take a bath.
Yeah.
So they dropped all the charges.
So this is it? This is your last session?
I don't know how I could justify coming.
Well, you could volunteer.
You do charity work all the time.
You're not a charity case.
You're not coming back, are you?
Please come back.
- Please come back.
- No.
Oh, yeah.
You're welcome, Mr. Dutchman.
- What are you doing here?
- Just in the neighborhood.
Did Mark have you follow me?
I don't know what you're talking about,
Mrs. Dutchman.
What, you feeling guilty or something?
- What's it gonna take?
- Not to tell him?
I don't know if I can put a price on that.
Try.
Not tonight.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I'm tired.
Hey.
- What'd you find?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
- I mean, she reads to him.
- That's it?
- That's it, boss.
Are you lying to me, Landry?
No.
You're fired.
Fired?
You got a hearing problem?
You sure that's a good idea?
I'm sorry?
Well, considering everything I know about
you and given your current standing...
...with the US attorney,
are you sure that's a good idea?
Now, that's the kind of spirit
I like to see in my team.
Maybe you're not such a pussy after all.
There may be hope for you yet.
Thank you, Mr....
Fuck, fuck.
No, boss.
If I even dream, you ratted me out...
...I'll take your fucking head off
with this golf club. You hear me?
- Are we clear?
- Yes, sir.
Now I'm gonna ask you one more time.
Is my wife having an affair
with the blind man?
- Is she?
- Yes!
Yeah, yes!
Fuck.
"He soaked in the intoxication
of her scent...
"...before diving headfirst
into her holiness.
"Sending her into a paroxysm of pleasure...
"...she did not know existed...
"...before his gentle touch."
You fuck as good as you write?
Who do I have the pleasure of addressing?
Mark Dutchman.
Suzanne's my wife.
Dutchman's not your real last name, is it?
- What makes you say that?
- Your voice has a ring of Queens to it.
Polished, but you can never take all the
Far Rockaway out of there, now can you?
- And where are you from?
- Brooklyn.
You got balls for a blind man.
I'll give you that.
What is it you do for my wife?
- I don't wanna fight with you, Mark.
- No, I wanna know.
I need to know. What is it you do?
You really need me to spell that out for you?
I'm gonna say once, only once.
Do not see Suzanne again.
That's fine.
Just don't ask me to keep my hands off her.
You think you can say that shit to my face...
...and I'm gonna give you a pass
because you're blind?
No.
No, Mark, no.
I... I want you to...
...treat me just like any other guy
that's banging your wife.
What the fuck is going on in here?
Get your hands off me.
What's wrong with you?
Get out of here.
Remember what I said.
You alright, Bill? Hey.
You remember this?
I had never been as happy in my life
as I was in that moment.
You love him?
- Mark.
- Tell me.
I don't know.
I forgive you.
Just end this thing with him.
Oh, I don't know if I forgive you.
I've made mistakes.
Everyone makes mistakes. Even you.
But we can change.
I've changed.
You know what I thought of
when I was in prison?
You know what got me through?
You.
The thought of coming home and holding you.
That's the only thing that held me together.
Is that why you had me followed?
What do I have to do to keep the one
uncorrupted thing left in my life?
Just tell me what you need, Suzanne. Tell me.
And I swear to God I'll give it to you.
You're my everything, baby.
You know that, everything.
I know...
...I know you think you love him...
...but let me tell you something.
Bill...
...Bill's a short story.
I'm your novel.
Novels are work sometimes...
...but the short story,
it doesn't go on to the next day.
It doesn't endure.
It's fun for a while, but then fun runs out.
Then you realize,
there's no new chapter to turn to.
I don't know what this is anymore.
I don't know you.
Don't leave me.
Don't, I can't live without you.
I can't.
Please don't leave me.
Please don't leave me. Not when
my whole fucking world is falling apart.
Baby, please.
Please, baby.
I need you so much.
And I need you. I need you.
I need you.
- Suzanne, is that you?
- Yes, yes, it is.
Please come in.
You are not going to believe
the kind of day I've had.
I actually was inspired to write.
That's great.
What happened to your face?
Nothing, I... I bumped into something
when I was doing something.
May I offer you...
...a glass of champagne?
I'm sorry, Bill, I... I can't do this.
You can't drink champagne
in the middle of the day?
No, I... this can't go any further.
I'm married. It's...
...it's not right, it's...
It's only wrong...
...if you stay with him.
Do you still love him?
- He's my husband.
- That's not an answer...
...Suzanne.
Yes, I still love him.
I don't believe you.
I am sorry, Bill. I have to... I have to go.
Suzanne...
...good to see you.
Nice to have you around.
- Frank!
- Yeah?
- Which way did she go?
- To the left.
Suzanne!
Jesus. Buddy? Buddy? Buddy, are you okay?
- You okay? Hey, come on.
- Come on, come on. Come on, come on.
Hey, you're looking to get yourself killed?
- You got him, you got him?
- Yeah, I got him. Breathe, okay.
- Frank? Is that you, Frank?
- Yes, it's me. It's me, Bill, I'm right here.
I'm right here. You got hit by a cabbie.
- My stick?
- I got your stick right here.
- Don't move, don't move. I'm right here, yeah.
- Buddy, you okay?
Hey.
It's me calling.
I just wanted to tell you to be nice tonight.
You've been a grouch
for the last three nights and...
...I'm feeling kinda fragile, so...
...please just be nice tonight, okay?
I love you.
Michelle, this cannot come
as a surprise to you...
...but I want a...
What's going on here?
I lost something.
I took it.
What?
Here.
Nothing Left To Win Or Lose.
When I was cleaning your apartment.
I would have told you, but I knew
you wouldn't let me read it.
- That's because it's not finished.
- But it's not far.
Goddammit!
- How dare you?
- Are you gonna finish it?
Yeah, I'm gonna finish it.
- I'm gonna finish it.
- What are you, what are you...
No, stop!
- Let it burn, Gavin!
- No!
Let it burn!
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
- Why don't you mind your own business?
Why don't you get off your ass and do
what you were put on this earth to do?
It's time to move on.
Enough with the self pity shit!
You're blocked. Change up the scenery.
I'm blind, Gavin.
The scenery doesn't change... ever.
- Everyone makes their excuses.
- Come on.
But it's only the losers
who quit because it's not fair.
- Please.
- Nobody said it had to be fair.
- All right, so?
- Well, you wrote that.
If you wanna give up, that's your business.
But if you need help in getting your
life together, then you give me a call.
Do we all cave eventually?
Convince ourselves
not to take the final leap?
Just when our dreams are within reach.
The opposite of love
is not hate, but indifference.
"He saw that the spring had sprung...
"...the food was gone. But no mouse.
"You see, the mouse would come
in the middle of the night.
"She called for my grandfather. "Papa," he
came quickly! "What's the matter?" He asked.
"There's a mouse in our house," she yelled.
"But the mouse was gone.
"Don't worry," said papa. The next morning...
However the Nemesis of love is fear.
Fear creeps into you.
Builds up walls.
Traps you inside yourself.
Fear strangles you, slowly...
...subtly...
...until one day there's
nothing left to win or lose.
Nothing left but the thirst...
...for the one drink you don't have.
Nothing left, but the memory...
...of the one pair of lips
that could have saved your soul.
If only fear hadn't kept you
from taking the leap.
Okay, that's great. Thank you so much.
- All right, bye.
- How are you?
Oh, Mrs. Dutchman.
I didn't know you were reading today.
No, no, I'm not.
And please call me Suzanne.
Okay, Suzanne.
Do you know where he is, Ella?
Bill? No, not a clue, he just vanished.
But by the way, it was really nice
to see you reading to those kids.
They really loved you.
Hey.
- Suze, hi.
- What are you doing here?
I...
...I was just in the neighborhood
and I thought I'd drop by to...
...see if you want to have lunch.
That Chanel No. 5?
Every now and then it's fun.
Honey pot.
He likes five minute eggs, not three.
Hey, I was just gonna call you.
Wanna grab some lunch?
Don't... don't do that.
- What's wrong?
- I'm done.
I am...
...really done.
- Are we really gonna go through this again?
- No, we're not.
Deanna will love that.
All I ever wanted...
...was for you to be happy.
- Hello, Bill.
- Bonjour, Jean.
Hello, Bill. How are you today?
a va Marie, et vous? How is your little dog?
Still peeing on the sofa,
but what can you do?
Well, either kill him
or learn to live with it.
- Like men?
- Well, not all men.
All of them.
- The usual?
- The usual, Marie. S'il vous plait.
You think today is the day?
Today is as good as any day.
That's what you say every day.
Bill...
...why do you never offer a glass to me?
Because it's for me.