- The Trust (2016)
- IMDB #3733774
- Created by DonToribio (Subscene.Com moniker)
- Posted FIRST to Subscene April 23, 2016
It's off.
- Did anybody see me come in?
- I don't think so.
- I did.
- Fuck off, Bert.
Okay, now, young man, look here.
All of this,
okay, you can get a hit off of any of
these and change the whole investigation.
With this is an very
interesting ashtray.
Sorry, Lieutenant, Captain Harris
is out front, he's looking for you.
- Already?
- Yes.
All right, hold on,
let me just...
Don't let anyone touch my bag.
- Wish me luck.
- Good luck, Sir.
These guys have been
in business for a while.
- Can you hand me a bag, please?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Ooh! Check this thing out!
This mobile unit is
specifically designed to help with
chain of custody for the
evidence we collect on-site.
- It's all computerized,
- Uh-huh.
we check for DNA, fingerprints
without ever needing to change hands.
- It's uh...
- It's very detailed, I know, but...
Expensive!
Look, Jim, I don't know
what I can do about this,
you're gonna have to
talk to the Commander.
But I did, and he told me
I need to speak with you.
Right.
Ya know, you really should just
talk to the Commander about it.
Yes, Sir,
absolutely, Sir.
Oh!
I'm fucked! Help!
Ah!
- Are you all right, Bert?
- Fuck no, I'm not all right!
I haven't had a cigarette.
So what was it you needed
to talk to me about then, Captain?
You guys down at Property
had tagged this little puppy
and it's goin'
up for auction this week.
Okay.
- I want it as a gift to my son-in-law.
- That's... very thoughtful of you.
Well, ya know, he's a good kid.
Would you mind headin' down to
the O.P.G. and checkin' it out?
I want our guys in the
garage to know I got my eye on it.
- Well, I can look into it for you, of course.
- Great.
That's great, 'cause I think we have
everything under control here.
No, I have my...
no, you can keep that.
I'm sorry, you want me to
go to the garage right now?
Yeah.
What the shit is this?
- Is that a lawn mower?
- It's for Harris.
For a Captain,
that guy's a real shit heel.
And $5,000, the bill to bid to buy,
I'm gonna get 5 where, who'll give me 2,500.
twenty-five, thank you, Ma'am, now I'll
take a bidder, think big, so now it's better...
I'm 7, who's gonna give 7,
now 7, now 8, give me 9...
- He wants this thing for his son?
- Son-in-LAW.
Well, okay, that's quite the gesture.
Yeah, we'll keep it off the floor.
Nice car.
What happened here?
That car was dead when we got it,
someone gutted the engine completely,
But, look what we found
when we popped the hood.
- This is full of cocaine.
- Yes, I know.
This needs to be
submitted as evidence.
Yes, right, absolutely, sorry,
It will, it will be
submiited, check this out.
Fits like a glove, right, quite the
clever way to move coke, if you ask me.
I mean, who check the engine block.?
- Well, I guess... I did.
- Who owned the car?
A local guy,
a drug dealer, obviously.
I got the paperwork for the arrest on the
desk back there, if you want to check it out.
Yes, Sir, he's out back.
Hey!
The Captain wants to know if you can take a few
new pictures of the John Deere before you leave.
Just, like with your phone...
or whatever.
What do you think?
Well, I think that there's a lot
more to makin' a cop than just paper.
Yes... but I just...
thought it was unusual.
It is.
Ya know, a good cop is gonna
look at it and know exactly what to do.
- Hello?
- Yes, I do, I just have to...
- Was it something I said?
- No, I just have to make a phone call.
What the fuck, Dude!
What?
- You don't see anything unusual?
- Where have you brought me?
Look at the guy's sheet.
- Why, why would I...
- Look, what do you notice?
- He had a lotta priors.
- And?
- "And", what "and"?
- All right, the girl's coming.
Hi, I'll have a refill and...
- Water.
- Okay.
She never told me...
She had a pot in her hand...
Okay, well, that's all right, she's probably...
where are you going?
This place is freaking me out.
Would you just hold on a second, please,
there... there... there's something to this...
Could you just sit down...
humor me for a second.
- Let's just talk about it tomorrow.
- Check out the guy's bail receipt.
Excuse me!
'Scuse me!
- Bro, this can't be right.
- It is.
- How do you know?
- I checked.
- Was it a bond?
- Cashier's check.
- For $200,000?
- Yeah.
- Who paid that?
- I don't know.
What do you think?
- What do I think?
-Yes.
I think that guy has a
friend with deep pockets.
That's deep, very deep.
I think that guy's
getting a hand job.
He's still eating,
so it's hard to tell.
- Are you gonna have those, can I get one?
- What?
Who could get that much
cash together that quickly?
Wha... what's that for?
- Have you ever tried it?
- I can't say that I have.
All right, well, you take this one...
and I'll take the other.
What are we, in the sixth grade?
I'm not gonna eat this!
He has cash in hand, I'm just sayin', if someone
risked a fortune to get this kid outta of jail,
then, right now, you and I are the
only two people who even seem to notice.
So, whaddya wanna do, ya want
me to rob a drug dealer for ya?
Rob a drug dealer?
Well, right now, I just wanna find
out where the cash is coming from.
I don't think
it's a good idea.
I'm not talking
about anything crazy.
Look... look, this guy is a... well,
you read his sheet, he's a nobody.
But he can't be a nobody,
who spends $200,000 on a nobody?
If you want my opinion...
Something like this it is worth doing
if you can keep it quiet and simple, okay?
And what you're talking about here would be
neither of those things, I can promise you that.
Wow, that sounded so cool.
The way you just said that,
right now, that sounded cool.
- What, it tastes good to you?
- Naw, it doesn't.
Sometimes I think I
should really pull it together...
a little bit.
- I think they're checkin' us out.
- No, they're not.
- I think they are.
- You're wrong.
I just wanna put a tail on him.
If it's a den then so be it, life
goes on, none the richer.
I'll cover your time off.
All right, I'll do it,
I'll find this guy.
But only because when it come
to you and me, I truly, and...
I mean this sincerely, I truly have
nothing better to do, and I despise my job.
That's the spirit!
You are a bad ass!
What the fuck!
What does he do in there?
He works in the first floor restaurant.
I know, but...what is it?
You know, he gave us drinks, stocks the bar.
Could you stop that?
Someone has him scared.
- Whaddya mean?
- He shows up to work five nights a week...
- Yeah.
- on time...
- to stock a bar?
Uh-huh.
He's a drug dealer, Dave.
Jesus!
Jim! Jim! You can't just go
marching up to this guy right now!
- You're dressed like a cop.
- I am a cop.
- You know what I mean!
- Look, you gotta give this another week at least.
For what? The kid got rolled and now
his people have him cleaning dishes.
Jesus! Will you stop looking around!
- Are you sure you didn't miss something?
- Yes, I'm sure.
Well, you're out there smoking
that refer, so you might not...
I'm sorry? Am I on an official assignment here?
Short of getting hired as bellhop,
there's nothing that more I can do.
And I'm not wasting anymore
vacation days on this, either.
Don't take this the wrong
way, because we're friends, and
and you're also my boss...
fuck you, Jim!
- This is some bullshit right here.
- David.
David! Stay positive, Dude!
I'm leavin' this with you guys,
Treasury'll be by to pick it up.
It's all fake.
- When are they coming?
- How should I know.
- Come on, man, I got a lot of shit to do.
- Oh, God, sorry about that.
Can't you just wait for 'em?
I'll tell you what,
I'll flip you for it.
What are you doing?
Would you like to go first,
or should I?
- You?
- Stop it.
Okay, I'll go first.
Jesus!Fuck!
What the...
- That's a rush... your turn.
- No.
- No?
- Oh fuck!
- Sergeant Waters.
What?
What's this about?
Lieutenant Stahl requested you for his desk
while he's away on a special assignment, Sir.
What are you talking about?
What special assignment?
Jesus Christ!
Jimmy, it's your friend!
Where the hell are you
going at this hour?
- Official Police business, Dad.
- Who's the cop?
I am, Dad, we both are...
goodnight.
- Good luck.
- Dad's unusually up-beat tonight.
I know, yeah,
it's good to see, yeah, right?
- What the fuck is this?
- It's my tips.
Don't laugh,
it's more than we make.
So, they're closed on Sunday.
They do the drop-offs in the back,
but where does it go once it's inside?
- Did you check it out?
- It's funny you should mention that.
What, you didn't get hired
as a bag boy or something?
- You take these?
- There's one in there, that's...
Ah! Let's just see if you can spot it.
- They're terrible.
- Yeah.
It looks like a bum from
the street took these.
Well, the Lord knows I wasn't
gonna go marching around back there.
You made a homeless
person that these photos?
Why... I paid them a little.
- All right.
- Right.
So, I think this is more than just a
money drop or however you call it.
Why would you say that?
Because whatever they're
bringing here, stays here.
Nothing goes out... ever.
- What is this?
- Huh?
Look at the freezer, that lock.
Makes you wonder, doesn't it?
- Look at you.
- What?
- And I'm skippin' right into your little...
- My what?
What's the name of that
girl that solves the crimes.
Nancy Drew...
this is some Nancy Drew shit.
Did you see that one?
Spotted it!
It's that grocery store.
I haven't heard anything from
your Department about this.
- What kind of nonsense is this?
- No, no, I...
- You just reached for my phone.
- Yes I did.
- In a suspicious manner.
- No, I wasn't, I swear...
I would suggest that you're here
under the auspice of illegal activity.
- What crime is it anyway? You think...
- I'll call the Sheriff.
- I'll give you $100.
- Okay.
All right.
Well, you are very lucky that this
investigation is so well funded, I'll tell you that.
Yeah, wipe it.
- Wipe it.
- Delete, delete.
- Right there?
- Yeah, stop there, go a few frames back.
- Okay.
- Okay, stop, replay that.
Okay, okay, stop, can you
give me some other camera angles?
Sure.
Now, pause it.
Isn't that that sandwich shop on Decatur,
the one that makes the cheese steaks?
Oh, yeah, I've been
there, that place is legit.
Man, that place is delicious.
How ya doin', Bill?
That's the way to go.
The way the cheese
spills over the bread.
- Hey, gotta get a cheeseburger.
- Jim!
All right, give me a hard
copy of that, then wipe it,
- and just keep goin' with the time codes there.
- You got it.
- I looked at the store.
- Yeah?
They recently installed
a new storage unit.
According to that work
order, that freezer has
got 36 inches of steel
reinforced concrete protecting it.
Now, it could be the world's
most secure meat locker,
but when you consider
the drug dealers,
the hotel front and phony laundry
service making one way trips to this place...
And nothing ever goes out.
I think you know exactly
what I'm getting at.
Holy shit!
- Sir.
- Oh, thank you.
- Wipe it?
- Wipe it.
Have you ever broken
into a vault before?
- No... are you serious right now?
- I don't know.
- Have you?
- No.
- What about this one?
- Yeah, go for it, Lewis.
Ya know, here's a question:
Somebody builds a safe in the
back of a grocery store, right?
Yeah.
- And we found it.
- Precisely.
And we assume it's filled with money, or
drugs or whatever... it's filled with stuff?
Yeah.
Well... how do we...
ya know, get it... out?
Hello, can I help you?
Yes, hello.
Just a moment.
Yes, good.
I need a drill.
Wait... wait...
How are you going to pay for it?
Well, my people will contact you
and arrange it, ya, yes.
The Yank's hiding something.
He must be a bank
robber or something.
Yeah, so cool.
- I gotta go, you finish up.
- But I'm not authorized.
Who gives a shit?
So this is the floor plan for the
apartment that's directly above the vault?
- Yeah, taped it out this morning.
- You did a fine job.
What's this?
That's from the guys in Germany.
This is the quote for the drill?
You know I don't have this money.
- I'm sure you'll think of something.
- Where am I gonna get this kind of cash?
You're smart, crafty.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Where's your money coming from?
I am refinancing.
- Refinancing what?
- It's a home equity loan, I already applied for it.
You're mortgaging your
house to pay for a heist?
- Do you have any idea how insane that is?
- We don't have a lot of time.
Okay, well, like I was saying,
the ceiling is where I think we go in.
The vault door isn't that old, messing
with it runs the risk of a fail-safe...
unless we want to
hire professionals safe crackers...
- Which we don't.
What you're saying is we drill
down through the floor of the apartment?
That's right.
- And where will we do that?
- The dining room.
Let's check it out.
The only other hitch is
there might be a tenant.
What's that?
Uh... that's nothing... A bee flew in
my face when I was doing that part.
- We'll have to deal with him.
- Who, the tenant?
- Well, do we pay him off?
- Pay him off? What? No!
We'll just tie him
up or whatever.
Tie him up or whatever, that sounds
complicated, which one of us is doing that?
Well, I'm sure it won't be easy.
Well, you just said it, like,
whatever, we'll just tie him up.
Well, let's table this for
now, we gotta get back... so...
Are you good for the money,
'cause I wanna put the order in?
Jim, it's 10 grand.
Well, are you good for it
or not, because I'm all in?
Don't leave me hanging.
This took me 3 hours, by the way.
And it's Da Vinci-esque.
All right, yeah, I'll...
I'll figure it out.
You're a positive thinker...
and I respect you.
And I fuckin' dig you.
Have you ever done
one of these before?
No.
I'm not doin' this out of
the goodness of my heart.
You're asking
for a lot of money.
This is a short term loan.
I know.
Let's go.
These guys know the score.
One... two might try to run,
if that happens, stop 'em.
All right, everybody up.
EVERYBODY UP!
Get up! Up! Get against the wall...
right now! Move! Get against that wall!
Get against that wall!
Right now!
- What's happening?
- You are under arrest.
If you'll just give me a minute.
...right to remain silent.
This is one, I said two,
I said I need two.
That's...
that's all I have.
- I said two!
- That's all I have, that's all I have.
I'll tell you what I'll do.
I'll flip ya for it.
No, no, don't, no, no,
please, don't, no, no.
- Whaddya wanna do then?
- No, don't, don't, don't.
- No, no, no.
- Whaddya wanna do.
No, no, no.
No.
Go with her, go!
Bobo, that's great.
Bobo, Bobo,
Bobo's interesting.
Especially for someone
who sells guns.
It's fun, ya know, it's...
I'm Jim, by the way.
Hey, where... where are we...
where are we now, is it far?
Man, shut the fuck up!
Fuck!
You can sit your ass right
there until I know we good.
And you ain't about that, I'll
stick the party to your ear right now.
You got me?
I'm 'standin' that,
it's far?
Get out.
The money!
That's a big one.
It's all there,
you can count it.
I mean, these are...
brand new, right?
I mean...
you didn't...
like...
scrape the serial numbers off
them or anything like that, did you?
Fuckin' whoever you have,
they are hopin' somebody like me...
hope for some corny
motherfucker like you.
Look at that mug.
Get used to it,
he's our new roommate.
- And he's alone in there, correct?
- I've barely seen him leave the place.
- Where did you stash the van?
- The van?
No, I just got the plates,
I thought you were gonna get the van.
You were supposed to
take care of both.
No, I remember you sayin' that you...
No, no, I didn't, the van was yours,
what the fuck are we gonna do now?
I guess I goofed up,
sorry, dude.
Jesus!
How are we supposed to pull this off?
Huh? Really?
Look at this thing!
He can't even keep the
the simplest thing...
We're about to risk our lives here!
Do you realize that?
Do you have any clue how
dangerous it is what we're trying to do?
How many things can go wrong? Or are
you just unable to see that at any point?
I picked it up and I stashed it
by the Airport this morning.
I'm sorry, David, it was just...
just a little... pre-heist... joke.
It was...
was just a joke!
Please don't be him, please don't be him,
please don't be him, please don't be him.
We okay?
You look so cool right now.
Now, I'm gonna go in and
make sure we're clear.
And when I KNOW we're clear, I'm gonna
invite YOU via walkie-talkie, all right?
Okay.
Fuck!
Get up!
Get the fuck up!
Move!
Get on the bed!
Stay quiet!
Christ!
Did you hear anything?
I looked away, he came after
me, dragged the girl with him.
I only shot the guy.
Throw her on the bed.
Shove her outta here.
- We need a paintbrush next.
- Where are we gonna put her?
Okay, get her back up.
Oh, God, she's choking!
Put her over here.
That looks pretty good...
maybe.
On three, two, one... up!
Okay, you know the drill.
The first bit's spent.
How far are we?
What up?
They changed the recipe.
Ya know, it has my approval.
We're about half way through.
I need a cigarette.
Fuck.
I'll take care of this.
- What are you gonna to do?
- Something.
Hey there.
Good evening.
You really gave us a start, man.
Yeah, well, I thought I saw some people
unloading some equipment down there...
Well, that's likely, we got a stakeout
going on and you nearly walked into it.
A stakeout?
- Detective O'Connor.
- Oh! Uh... Cliff.
Hey.
How long have you
been watching?
- Your guy here?
- Tonight?
18 hours, I think.
Hey, would you mind turning your lights off?
Ya know, I always wanted to be a
cop, it seems like a pretty good deal.
- There are perks.
- Yeah, I bet there are.
Ya know, I'm gonna need you
to turn those lights off, Cliff.
Oh, yeah, sure thing...
the lights.
I'm gonna need your radio, the other calls,
let her know what's going on here.
This is undercover stuff, man,
you really can't, sorry.
Oh, yeah, right...
Hey, not a problem, Officer!
- Good luck.
- Have a good night, Cliff.
No!
We gotta move,
we're running behind.
Good! Got a bite!
Keep going!
We must've tripped it.
...anything in there.
The belt.
It's broken.
Do we have any more?
What... what's next, Jim?
We'll think of somethin'.
- Are we fucked?
- No.
- Uh-uh.
- Okay.
We only had a quarter
of an inch left.
All right, grab it.
You wanna practice or something?
I'll hold it if you'd rather.
You haven't had a lot of
coffee today, have you?
J.K., go for it.
Two more!
Give it t'me good!
It bounces too much...
we're fucked.
I have an idea.
It's kind of... whacky.
Jim?
- Oh, fuck.
- Did you hear about...
- We're through.
- Okay.
Ready.
Okay, I've got the tumbler.
And you're right, I see
two fail-safes, which means
if we miss a number, that's it,
nothing's gonna get that door open.
All right, let's proceed.
Move slowly to the
right and clear it.
Moving to zero.
Ready.
Okay, continue.
Catch!
- Ready.
- Just give me a second.
Okay, continue.
Catch!
Ready.
Slow down, I can't see the notch.
Stop, stop, stop!
Catch... I think.
You think?
It's behind the other two
rings, and I can barely see it,
but I heard something
latch, did you hear it?
No, I didn't.
It's caught...
open it.
Are you sure?
Hello?
Yeah, open it.
Is it open?
Opened.
Is it good?
What?
What's happening?
Can ya hear me?
What is it, just steaks down there?
Talk to me,
what are you looking at?
You should come down here.
Okay.
This is okay.
What the hell is this place?
Did you open this?
We should go back up and clean.
Okay.
Hello?
I have a little boy at home.
He's three.
I need to call his father.
Please!
Please, that's all I'm asking.
Write the number...
write it on my hand.
- Hello?
- Yeah, it's me.
Hey...
do you know what time it is?
- I checked and it's early.
- Well, whaddya want?
- Can you help me out?
- What is it?
- Hi.
- Hey.
Jesus, fuck.
Do you live here?
Who lives here?
- I don't know what you mean.
- Whose guns are those?
What guns?
The guns in the closet.
I don't know anything about guns.
Whose... you don't know
anything about guns.
- Are they his?
- I don't know!
I don't know him!
- Whose guns are those?
- I don't know.
Whose' guns are those?
Huh?
- Whose guns are those?
- What do you want with me?
- I don't know him.
I don't know him, I just...
He's a goat.
I have... I have problems, and pain.
You had bad luck.
- What did she say?
- Nothing, she thinks they're his.
- Who the fuck is "he"?
- She doesn't know.
These aren't loaded,
you saw that, right?
We can't do this.
- Whaddya mean?
- Down there isn't just a little...
I don't know what this is.
I don't know where
we are right now.
We're in the heart of
"the American Dream."
I've never seen anything
like this before in my life!
- Well, it is a bit of a twist.
- We need to get out of here, man.
- Okay.
- Everything is staying
right where we found it,
this is crazy right now.
It is a little crazy, but that doesn't mean
you have to walk away empty handed, David.
Empty handed? We'll be lucky
to walk out of here at all.
You brought enough
bags to take everything.
Jesus!
- You knew about this.
- What?
You did, you knew this was here.
No... nobody just finds
something like this outta nowhere!
We did.
- You had your eye on this!
- No, David, I didn't.
- I'm just as shocked as you are.
- Well, you don't look it.
Well, I come prepared, that's what you
do when you're someone like me
who refuses to underestimate
the power of positive thinking.
You wanna know how positive I am?
I mean, this was going to be a surprise,
but I can tell you're a little stressed.
I'm so positive I've got two tickets in
my pocket right now for the Bahamas...
one with your name on it,
because when we're finished
here, we're gonna celebrate,
drinking rum and smoking cigars.
- That's how positive I am.
- Are you trying to stick this on me?
- Is that what's going on?
- Stick what on you?
I'm serious!
Well, if you're serious, then you
should know you're not making any sense.
How long have you been waiting
for someone like me to do this with?
A guy you could point the finger at?
David, I thought you were...
You know I'd have to be a
genius to plan something like that!
- So tell me another story, Jim.
- Okay... we're friends...
we've had a lot of money,
and I'm super happy about that.
There's your story.
- We're not touching...
- Oh, my God!
What does it take to get someone
to split millions of dollars with you?
Get in grip!
- Jim, the hunt is down.
- David.
Please open it.
I asked you nicely.
I'm sorry.
Look, if you're scared,
I get it, it's okay.
But I'm not.
And... and I've... I've come this
far, so, please open the door.
You'll get us killed for this.
I'm only gonna ask
you one more time.
Please open it.
I can't.
Open it!
- Open it!
- Jim!
Open it! Open it!
I think you should
wait with her,
while I finish loading
up from the gate,
and then we'll get
rid of her up north.
She saw my face,
what else could we do?
All right.
Hey, Dave,
I'm really sorry...
Some more here.
Okay, you're on soft
ground now, come here.
All right, let me put
you inside... step down.
That's good,
stay down.
Now, this is what's gonna happen:
If you do exactly as I say, you'll live.
If you do anything different,
you won't, understand?
Jesus! Yes?
Yes.
It's been a long
fucking night.
Once we stop,
I'll let you out.
That way you can move on from
this like it never happened, all right?
What do you want from me?
God damn it,
who are they?
Who did you call?
Tell me or I'll shoot you
through the fucking seat... tell me!
No, no, no, no, I'm a cop!
No, no, no.