...authorities say they've been
looking for the little girl
for the past two months.
Hopefully, they can find her soon.
Meanwhile, you're listening
to KWDD, the Dust Devil,
here in the Valley of Lordsburg.
I'm good ol' Jack Tumbleweed.
Here's one that I've been keyed in
on KWDD, the Dust Devil.
Hey, what about me?
So how do you know it's even a girl?
I know so.
Damn, someone's in a hurry!
Her brother was in my unit.
- PFC Reynolds.
-Oh, really?
And how does Private First Class Reynolds
feel about you and his sister?
I doubt he really cares.
- And why is that?
-'Cause he's dead.
They'd write each other letters.
He sent a picture of the both of us,
so she asked him about me.
The only person I had to write
while I was over there was like my pops.
She and I have
kept in touch over the years.
What's her name?
Sarah.
You got a picture?
Whoa! She's a babe!
She is very pretty.
Ooh, I want to see.
Uh, you need to pay attention
to the road, mister.
Oh, come on.
Well, maybe you should invite her.
To what?
You didn't tell him?
Babe, I didn't tell anyone.
Really?
What's the big deal?
We are getting married.
What the fuck?
Congratulations.
Dude, are you serious?
yeah, man. Next Spring.
Oh, look, babe, a rest stop.
I need to pee.
I second that notion.
Ugh, that's disgusting.
Thanks, man.
For what?
For this. You know,
you guys coming with me
and driving me and all. Thanks.
Don't mention it
It's just like old times.
Dude, I can't believe
you're getting married.
Yeah, me too.
I was like...
kind of thought you'd be the last.
Well, it looks like old Jude here
is gonna be the last.
Yeah, yeah. Well, boys, I gotta go
talk to a man about a horse.
Hey, the ladies' is on the right side.
Be outside, babe.
Hey! -
Hey, baby cakes.
Wanna go for a ride?
You want me to show
you boys how to ride that thing?
Any time, doll.
Hey, you guys ready to go?
Hey, Alice, where's Jill?
Same place she's been.
In the shitter, dude.
Alice, can you go check on her?
Yeah.
Hey, I've been waiting for the girls
to be gone. Check this out.
Hey, are you done yet?
Seriously, we're gonna leave you.
This is the only thing
my old man gave me before he died.
Jill?
Nolan! She's not in there!
What do you mean she's not in there?
She's just not in there.
Jill!
Did you see her come out?
No.
Neithed did I.
She couldn't have gone too far.
Jill!
Really?
Where is she?
Are you sure she didn't leave before you?
No, she was in there when I walked out.
Okay, calm down.
Let's just think about it.
No!
Where could she have gone?
Come on, guys.
We're talking about Jill here.
What the fuck
is that supposed to mean?
I'm just saying, man.
Dillon, shut up.
Maybe she got scared.
You know, there were those bikers.
- The fucking bikers.
-What?
-What about 'em?
Come on,
we gotta catch up with them.
Come on!
- Maybe we should just--
-Shut the fuck up, Jude!
You don't wanna help,
you can get out now.
But how do you know
that she's with them?
Nolan, dude.
Man, shut the fuck up.
what of jude's right?
Did you see the way
those guys looked at Alice?
Yeah, but that doesn't mean
that they took Jill.
you got any other ideas?
I thought the war
would have made you a man,
but you're being a little fuck...
Hold your fucking mouth right there!
This is stupid.
Shut up,Alice.
There was no one else there,
and that one fucking guy!
Nolan. Dude!
What? You pussin' out, too?
If you want, I can drop all your
asses off and take care of this myself.
I didn't say I was pussin' out.
I'm just sayin', how do you know
that they even got her?
Because there was nobody else there.
Because...
Fucking because...
She's all I've got, man.
There they are.
Did you see anything?
You drove passed them
like a hundred miles an hour.
How the hell are we supposed to know?
Shit! She's gotta be in the van.
Alice, stay here.
Dillon, come on, open the trunk.
what?
look, man
in about three seconds those bikers are
gonna be upon us. Now, open the trunk.
So, now...
Fuck it, Nolan. Just do it.
Babe, just stay in the car.
You boys wanna tell me
what the fuck you're doing?
I'm looking for my girlfriend
Look, man...
No, you look!
Where is she, motherfucker?
Nobody puts a gun in my face.
Yeah, well, I just did, asshole!
Think you're a man because you got a gun?
Tell him to get out.
I'm not gonna ask you again.
Don't move!
Tell that asshole
to get the fuck out of the van!
Now, look,
you boys have no idea what
you've gotten yourselves into here.
Now, I'm gonna give you a chance
to get your tight little assess
in your pretty little car
and drive the fuck away,
and we forget about this.
I'm the one making
the rules here, not you!
My girlfriend was at the rest stop
and now she's gone,
and you fucks were the only ones there.
Sit the fuck down!
Answer my fucking question!
Well, I tried...
tried to be decent,
but now, you done fucked up.
Now...
What we got here is a Mexican standoff.
You know what that is, boy?
That's where I shoot you,
and he shoots him.
And i blow off tour fucking head.
Hey, fat-ass,
unless you wanna
see the insides of this man,
I suggest you drop it.
Now, any of you others carrying,
or just Mama Bear and Tinker Bell here?
Oh, okay.
Real hard-asses, huh?
Line up over there!
Did I fucking stutter?
Now, my friend here asked you
a simple fucking question
that deserves a simple fucking answer.
Did you see the girl?
Fuck you.
I will not hesitate to kill
every last one of you!
Give me your fucking keys!
All right.
Now, this is how it's gonna go.
You boys are gonna walk to those hills
until you don't see us anymore.
Easy enough?
This is not the end of the road.
It's just a detour.
It's not the end of this.
Yeah, it is.
Now turn around, beat your feet.
You're dead.
Where the fuck did that come from?
Yeah, I don't even know what to say.
What happened?
They didn't have her.
What do you mean they didn't have her?
How do you know?
Well, I checked the van
and she wasn't there.
I'm going back to the rest stop.
just drive.
No, I'm going back.
Nolan, she isn't back there.
I still think we should
go back to the rest stop.
Nolan, just drive!
But what if she's back there?
Yeah. I mean, we can't just leave her.
She isn't back there.
How can you be so sure?
Well, I'm not, but going back there
just doesn't make sense.
She could've just gotten scared.
Look, man, the best thing we can do now
is find the law around here.
I think we can handle this.
Didn't you see their colors?
- Whose colors?
-The bikers.
- Colors? What do you mean colors?
-You cut their fuel lines.
That isn't gonna stop them.
It's just gonna slow 'em down.
They're not gonna forget
what just happened.
Hey, what do you mean colors?
It means they belong to something.
And they were on a schedule.
- What do you mean schedule?
-Oh, shit!
It doesn't matter.
We just need to find the law around here.
Where the fuck could she be?
Okay, Alice, where was she whenever
you left the bathroom?
She was in the stall.
Okay. Was there anyone else
in there with you?
Not that I know of.
I didn't see anyone.
Dillon, was there any other cars there?
No.
You were in the bathroom when Jill was.
Did you hear anything?
Just some strange noises.
What do you mean noises?
Um.
It was like a dog whimpering
or something.
The real weird thing, though,
was all these fliers of missing people.
- There were stacks of them.
-Oh, God.
Wait, I did!
I saw a purple Cadillac pull up,
right before we left
Like the one from the highway?
I think so.
What are you talking about?
The car that passed us on the highway.
I was at the stop?
I think.
Come on. We'll find her.
Jill, come on, baby.
Where are you?
Oh, you son of a bitch!
Those fuckers cut our fuel lines.
They cut this tire, too.
Man, you got lucky.
Mickey doesn't usually
let prospects off so easily.
Nah, Mickey is just smart.
He'll be whooping my ass
after I get his bike up and running.
Rev, you find those keys yet?
Sure thing.
Hold on to 'em. It's gonna be
a long time before you're riding again.
Though, hey. hey.
If you can get these bikes
and the wagon up and running again...
Fifteen.
Can you do it?
I can get the wagon,
two of them bikes up and running.
I don't know about that third.
Get mine and Derek's going.
We'll pick up Victor's on the way back.
- What about my bike?
-Did I ask?
No. Help him.
Fix the tire.
All  right.
Damn it.
I haven't seen a soul for miles,
and we really need gas.
We were sitting on a quarter of a tank.
How did you expect...
Hey, I didn't expect to be traveling
the back woods of this fucking state!
Oh, yeah. It was a shortcut.
No. It was Jill's idea.
What did you say, pussy?
no, stop!Fucking stop!
- Fuck you, Nolan!
-Dillon, shut up.
-What?
-I said stop the car.
Well, we're almost out of gas.
It may be our only chance.
Goddamn fuckin'...
Come on.
Come on now.
Ain't that hard.
See, you pulling it off.
What are you yelling about
your clothes for, huh? There we go.
We should've buried those kids.
Whe shold've buried'em
But instead, my bike is gonna
be sitting out here in the desert...
rusting in some bush.
You Know...
If it were up to me,
we'd be moving dirt right now.
What would you have done about the car?
Hmm? Don't be shy.
What would you do about the car?
I would've parked it in the desert.
How about that.
What next? Come on. Go on.
Well, we...
We would've just rode off.
Check the wagon for the dope'?
You didn't, did you?
Stupid piece of shit!
I like this road!
Nobody gives us any problems!
Now, is pride more important
than making our delivery?
No
Now, if you'd kept
your fuckin' mouth shut, you'd know,
you and Rev are gonna go
make the delivery.
Derek and I are gonna go
take care of the pride.
Does that work for you?
Yeah.
Good. I aims to please.
Rev, you got the bikes ready?
Yes, sir.
Good! Derek, let's go.
Hello?
Hey! Anybody?
Let's go look around.
It doesn't look like anyone's
been here in quite some time.
Yeah.
What the hell is that?
What are you doing?
- What the fuck, man?
-What the hell are you doing?
- Trying to get to the phone.
-Not like that.
What is your problem?
The last time I listened to you,
I had to put a gun in a man's face,
and I'm not gonna do that again.
Fuck, I should've gone back
to the rest stop!
Are you crazy?
She isn't back there, you idiot!
Stop it!
Jude, come on!
The last thing we need right now
is these people to find us in their place.
We don't need another mess.
Fuck you!
Fuck all of you!
We should've gone back!
Jill's out there, alone, and I'm
the only one who seems to give a shit!
Dillon, just let him cool off.
Let me see your eye.
It's fine.
Maybe we should've gone back.
For what?
Hello?
Ugh! What the hell is that?
What was that?
What?
I don't know,
but I'm pretty sure I saw something.
- Where?
-Just over there.
It must have been a dog or something.
We probably just spooked it.
What I saw was larger than a dog, Jude.
Maybe it was a grizzly
Yeah, because grizzlies
roam the buildings in the desert
Hey, you never know.
help me , please!
Somebody help!
We need to get the fuck out of here.
I was hoping you would say that.
There's something about
this place just ain't right.
I didn't say anything earlier,
but when we pulled in,
I could've sworn there was
someone right over there.
Why didn't you say anything then?
I thought I was seeing things.
It doesn't matter. We just need
to find Nolan and get out of here.
Where is Nolan?
Is somebody there?
Fuck this.
We're halfway there,
and we get our asses kicked again.
Again?
because..yeah, again.again.
I haven't gotten my ass kicked.
- At least not today.
-Shut up, Rev. Shut your...
Just wait till I come up.
You know it and I know it, okay?
- Yeah.
-lt's gonna happen. It's gonna...
Hold it. slow down.
What's that sign say?
It looks like gas up there.
Let's make that-- Make a right.
Make a right, right here. Okay.
Oh, shit!
Oh, shit. The bikers.
Dillon!
- Did you find Nolan?
-No, we've got another problem.
- Shit, where are we going?
-Hide!
Now they're not going anywhere.
Sure we should've stopped here, though?
We're not.
Don't worry.
The shipment will make it.
It'll make it. It'll make it.
Besides... we take care
of this business here,
and you'll be getting
your colors soon, son. All right?
I just don't want Mickey on my ass.
Don't you worry about Mickey, all right?
What you gotta worry about
is me, putting my foot...
Rev, what the fuck am I looking at?
Hey! Hey, boy.
Come on.
The hell's he wearing on his head?
I don't know. It's kid shit.
Didn't your mama teach you to share?
Mean little son of a bitch, ain't you?
Hey, where are your folks, kid?
Oh, does that mean you ain't got none?
Come on. Come on!
- What the fuck was that?
-It doesn't matter.
- What about Nolan?
-If he saw that, he's already gone.
Stay down.
Who are you?
Why are my hands tied?
Did you hear me?
Why are my fucking hands tied?
Answer me!
You're just gonna leave me here?
Come on!
Jill? Jill!
You leave her alone, you fucker!
Don't touch her, motherfucker!
Look, man, just...
Just listen, please.
Fuck!
Jill, come on, baby.
Please, wake up.
Wake up, Jill. Wake up!
Jill? What did you do to her?
What are you doing?
Oh, wait.
What? No. Don't...
No! No!
No! You're dead!
Do you hear me?
You're fucking dead!
I'm gonna cut your fucking heads off!
You son of a bitch!
I'll kill you, you piece of shit!
- You two heard that, right?
-Sounded like Nolan.
That was Nolan.
What are you doing?
I can't go.
Listen, I want you two
to head east on the highway.
stop anyone that comes. Anyone.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna go get Nolan,
then I'm gonna find you two.
Here, take this.
And no matter what you hear,
you keep going, okay?
Go!
Fuck!
Wait!
Come on.
Remember, don't stop.
But what if they got him?
Just come on.
Let's keep going.
Come on, baby.
Why is this happening?
Where is everyone'?
I don't know, baby.
Hey, look at me.
It's going to be okay.
- Okay?
-Promise?
Have I ever lied to you?
We'll get out of here, and...
we'll be listening to wedding bells,
before you can say when.
When?
Now, come on.
We have to keep moving.
Nolan!
Nolan.
Shit
Do you hear that?
what are you talking about? locusts?
No.
Just listen. It's different.
It sounds like a car.
Well...
Whatever it is,
it's getting louder. Come on.
Let's get off the road.
Is it a car?
I don't know. I can't see it.
Oh, shit! It's the bikers!
The bikers?
alice.
what?
This may be our only chance.
Talking
We've been walking for hours,
-and we haven't seen anyone.
-So we'll find someone.
But what if this is our only chance?
You guys stuck guns in their faces.
Yeah, but I can explain the situation.
Tell 'em what happened to their friends.
They're probably looking for 'em.
Dillon, no
babe, i got to..
But...
It's going to be okay.
stay down.
You guys have to help.
Help?
Just let me explain.
I told you we'd get you.
Wait. Just let me explain.
There's a guy back there killing people.
A guy. huh?
Yeah, a big motherfucker.
He killed your friends.
Game again
Your friends are dead.
What about my wagon?
-What?
-My wagon!
Ah, it's back at this place.
Place? Come on, what place?
There's this place.
We stopped. There's a tourist...
There's this town or something.
- Where?
-lt's back there!
We stopped, and all this weird shit
started happening.
So your friends have my wagon?
No!
Your guys stopped,
and this big guy, he killed 'em.
Where are your friends?
They're back at this place!
And how did you get here?
I walked
Listen, we need to get
the sheriff or something.
So you're trying to tell me
that Victor and Rev are dead,
and your friends are holed up at this
tourist place-y thing-y with my wagon.
Is that right?
Yeah, but it's not what...
- What? Not what?
-Not just them!
Oh, yeah. A big guy killed
Victor and Rev. Got it.
Yes!
You're telling me the truth?
Come here.
Oh, yeah.
There is one thing, though.
What's that?
Nobody sticks a gun in my face.
Dillon!
Whoa, shit!
it's gonna be okay, baby.
- Just go.
-l'm not leaving you.
No. No. You promised.
it's... it's okay.
- I love you, Alice.
-I love you.
- Now go.
-No.
You remember the wedding bells?
You were going to be my husband,
so you can't leave me.
Just go. Now Go.
Don't leave me.
Please.
Yes!
Come on.
Come on. Oh! Damn it! Come on.
Stay there, stay there, stay there.
I've been looking for those.
Come on, you son of a bitch!
Come on!
Hey! -
Wrong room.
Alice..
Don't worry.
I'm gonna get you out.
Bleeding
Where's Dillon?
Nolan?
We're getting the fuck out.
Stay here.
come on..
Alice, it's getting dark.
We need to make it to the highway.
Alice!
Alice, I need you
to stay with me, okay?
Hey . Hey -.
We made it this far, okay?
Here, come on.
We're gonna make it, okay?
Try to keep that tight.
I'm so thirsty.
It's the blood loss.
You can rest,
just don't fall asleep.
What do you think they are?
I have no idea.
Why would they kill Nolan?
In the war...
I saw things.
Things I never thought I'd see.
Things a man can do
to another man.
it's all right
CSM Robart
PFC Reynolds, myself, and two others
were on a small recon mission.
We came across this village
after Charlie had been there.
The things...
things they did to those people.
That feeling...
That barn had the same feeling.
what are you talking about?
Death.
After a while, you just get used to it.
Walked by dozens of bodies
Some with faces and some without.
And that's how it was
most of the time I was down there.
I can't believe Dillon's gone.
I know.
We had planned on
getting married last year.
He was so excited
when he heard you were coming home.
He wanted to wait.
When you left, we weren't sure
you were coming back.
I'm sorry, Alice, I didn't know that.
I know.
I promise you this, though.
When we get out of here, we're gonna
blow the lid off of this place.
His death won't be in vain, okay?
These crazy fucks will pay.
Come on. I got you.
Look.
There's a town.
All right, come on.
Be careful.
Look. They're back.
Help!
help us!
Anyone?
Help!
Hey!
Hey, mister!
- We really need your help.
-Alice, get back!
Alice
Alice, you head north,
you gotta come across the highway.
What are you saying?
I'm staying behind.
-I'm staying with you.
Listen, I can handle it.
You go. Find somebody. Anybody.
- We can go together.
-No, there's no time.
- Just go!
-I can't!
You have to! Go!
Go now!
And no matter what you hear,
you keep going, all right?
Go!
Oh, shit!
What do you think we should do, man?
I don't know, man.
There's a town over there.