[BREATHING THROUGH MASK]
[SOMEONE COUGHS]
[CLATTERING]
[BREATHING ACCELERATES]
[WALKERS GRUNTING]
[STABBING SOUNDS]
[EXHALES]
Why are you following me?
I've watched you.
You can kill them.
I can't.
Please!
Don't leave me!
What happened?
I twisted it,
on the road, it's just
a sprain. I'm not bitten.
Please.
I'll die alone.
- Synced and transcribed by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
There's nowhere to go.
What if I knew a place?
If you knew a safe
place, you'd be at it.
South.
Mexico's better.
The border's swarming with sick.
Folks trying to get south and
north when this all went down.
We avoid that.
There's a tunnel.
My boyfriend was Border Patrol,
he seized the tunnel
after all this started.
He went ahead to see if it was safe.
And he didn't come back?
What does that tell you?
You need a place to go.
I can't get there alone.
We both benefit.
Fine.
I'll help you.
But I don't need you.
- Are you from here?
- No.
- Where are you from?
- L.A.
We left when the military moved in.
The bombs followed us.
I'm sorry.
Pick up the pace.
You're not the only that lost someone.
My sister didn't make it.
***
***,
brainstem or eye.
Anywhere that penetrates the brain.
You hit the skull.
Blade skips off.
Which way?
Follow me.
Try.
- I can't!
- You're stronger than you think.
Colton?
You're alive.
I never thought I'd see you.
I can't believe you're here!
Oh, I thought we lost you in the ***.
Who's that?
That's Sierra.
She's the one that got me here.
I'm thankful.
Did you tell anybody
else about the tunnel?
No, just Sierra.
No one else is alive.
Your sister?
We waited as long as we could.
- You said you'd come back...
- I'm sorry.
That shot will bring more.
She's right. It's not
safe here, come on.
Head down, I'm right behind you.
- Sierra too.
- Uh?
Sierra.
Yeah, of course.
Of course. I just need to
shut the entrance after us.
- OK.
- OK. There you go.
I can't let you down.
I just want to get
somewhere safe, that's all.
But then you will tell
others about the tunnel.
I can't have that.
- Gabi!
- What happened?
Don't move, ***.
- Don't listen to her!
- What happened?
- He tried to kill me.
- What?
- Why?
- Gabi!
He left you behind. You don't need him.
Let's go.
Gabi!
Gabby?
Gabby? Are you OK?
Follow my voice!
Can you hear me?
***. Gabby!
We have to move now.
Follow my voice!
I told you, they're waiting for me.
- If I tell you, you wait for me.
- I'm sorry.
No, no, don't co...
Get back here!
Oh God.
Let her go.
It's not an option.
I need to get to her before they do.
Who else is down there?
Quiet.
Stay close.
Come on!
It came from down here.
What were you thinking
bringing a stranger here?
... look out for herself.
I wouldn't be alive
if it wasn't for her.
Yeah, well, I'm protecting you now.
Colton, that you?
Get in here, now!
Don't come out.
- Yeah, it's me.
- Who tripped the wire?
I don't know.
I got in after the explosion.
- Someone did the packing.
- If they did, we're gonna find 'em.
I'm gonna keep looking out here.
You go back to your post.
- If you see anybody, take care of them.
- Copy that.
Why did you lie to him?
Nobody else can know about this tunnel.
Let's get out of here, come on.
What  are you talking about?
This is more than just a passage.
It's a bunker.
We stay down here, and we live.
You lied.
You were never coming back for me.
Gabi, come on.
You left me to die.
Where the hell did they go?
Put the knife down.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I don't believe you!
You think that they're just gonna
let you outta here alive, huh?
You need me!
I can handle myself.
Gabby!
Sierra!
You're not worth it, baby.
Don't leave me ***!
You did what you had to.