Bloodsport!
Woman: come on, keller, get up!
[Crowd chanting "kill"]
[chanting dies down]
woman: rip his head off!
Man: take him out!
No.
I will not kill.
This man fought with
skill and dignity,
and you would have
me destroy that integrity.
And why?
To satisfy your lust for death.
There was a time when
kumite meant honor.
But i see now that
kumite here is dead.
It has become nothing
more than a blood sport.
I want him.
But he won't kill,
so what good is he to you?
When he is mine...
i'll make him kill.
You know, i don't get you, keller.
You compete in these
underground cockfights,
and then you're surprised
when things turn ugly.
Hey, i compete to stay sharp.
Fine, i can respect that.
Just don't expect the
paying audience
to share your high ideals
on skill and courage.
You know, blaire, you're the
best partner i ever had.
But you're a pain in the ass.
Same to you, tough guy.
Jesus!
These fights get me all tense.
Hey, don't people say
excuse me anymore?
Why don't you just break down
and get a new pen, rita?
Oh, no way. This is my lucky pen.
It was a christmas
present from my kids.
Let's go for a drink.
Ok, i'll buy for you.
No, i'll buy.
No, i'll buy you a drink.
I'll buy you.
[Dance music playing]
where's the fucking money?
[Woman screams]
no!
Man: what the hell are you doing?
Everybody down!
I'll blow your fucking brains out!
Why are all policewomen so obstinate?
Because we can be.
I'm a police officer.
Release the girl!
Ow!
Aah! Aah!
Oh, my god.
Drop the gun! Release the girl!
Woman on police radio: all
units, a 2-11 in progress
be advised, shots fired at
1100 south robertson.
Suspect is a white male...
let's go, blaire.
[Siren blares]
get back, blaire.
Watch your ass, keller.
What's up, asshole?
I thought you were dead, asshole.
You thought wrong.
You were on death row.
You were supposed to
have been executed.
Jesus christ, keller,
take the shot. You've got him.
Go ahead, take the fucking shot.
Ok, schrek, this can be win-win.
Lower your gun,
and we all walkout of here alive.
[Click]
[gasps]
ahhh!
Blaire!
I'm unarmed, officer.
Backup's outside. It's over.
Assume the position, asshole.
Whatever you say... babe.
Sh-sh-sh-sh-sh-should've
taken the shot.
Blaire: schrek's en route.
Commander anderson also called.
He's stopping by, wants
to be in on this one.
I put schrek's ass away6
years ago for murder.
He was supposed to be executed.
I read the file.
Look... in retrospect,
it wouldn't have mattered
if you'd taken the shot.
He'd have killed the girl anyway.
Bullshit.
I let that girl die.
I need 5 minutes.
Alone.
Keller...
commander anderson wants a 2-man
guard on him until he arrives.
Gentlemen, why don't
you go take a piss
and give us some breathing
room here?
You, too.
Ah, come on, keller.
Your record is clean.
I want to keep it that way.
Out.
Out!
I sure hope you know
what you're doing.
Should've taken the shot, man.
Foreplay.
I'm diggin' it.
Where's keller?
Oh, great. He's
alone with that psycho?
I need him alive and able to talk.
He's in lockup, sir,
safe as a baby.
How the hell did
you get out of fuego?
What the hell are you doing?
Put down the goddamn gun, john.
Get him out of here.
Ehh, let's go!
John...
you know i'm a man of
strong beliefs.
And one of my strongest beliefs
is that when a
commander gives an order,
it's to be followed to
the goddamn letter!
It's my fault, commander.
Agent keller... save it!
You'll have my official
resignation in the morning.
John... hold on.
You want another crack at schrek?
'Cause it's clear to me, john,
you have a hard-on for that psycho.
I have a problem with
cold-blooded killers,
especially cop killers.
Could just be me.
Ok.
He's yours.
But... this is
not unconditional love, john.
There's a catch.
What?
My attitude?
No vigilante bullshit, john.
You're still a cop.
We work together on this.
Clear?
Clear.
Blaire?
Yeah.
Schrek was being transferred
to a state facility somewhere
outside of yuma
when the van blew a tire.
He killed 3 guards and a driver.
Where was the transport
heading when schrek escaped?
We don't know exactly,
and no record sindicate a transfer.
Schrek was officially executed
one month ago.
Now he turns up alive and
lethal in my jurisdiction,
and that pisses me off.
Well, now we know why.
We can't confirm any bodies.
The warden at fuego says that schrek
was being transferred to
a state facility
for psychiatrice valuation.
4 other prisons are experiencing
the same disappearances.
No bodies, no records?
Zip.
That's right.
Corpus disappear us.
So here's the deal, john:
i want you to go deep
cover into fuego.
Find out what the
fuck's going on down there.
What's my cover?
Can we talk?
Look, you go in there,
you aren't coming out.
Is that what you want?
Now, listen.
I want to know what's
going on in that prison.
Fuck you, captain ahab.
You're going after moby dick
for hurting you.
Just remember one thing...
what was that?
Revenge.
And at the end of the day,
revenge emerged victorious.
Hey, asshole.
Gun down! Freeze!
Blaire: drop the gun, keller.
What the hell have you done?
Order! Order in the court!
This court finds you
guilty, john keller,
for the aggravated and
unprovoked murders
of 2 law enforcement officers.
I'm recommending a life-term
sentence without parole.
You'll be remanded
to the
maximum-security penitentiary,
fuego penal.
John keller... a decorated
s.w.a.t. officer for this city,
now a convicted murderer...
is to serve out the rest
of his life in prison.
An isolated tragedy
or an early warning to
high-stress law enforcement agencies
that other such incidents are...
th-there he is!
Mr. Keller!
Do you feel like you
got a fair trial?
Keller, do you feel the
sentence was fair?
Right here, sir.
Preston here.
Man on telephone:
he's heading your way.
Uh, yes, i... i just read the paper.
What do we know about him?
My sources tell
me keller's case is legit.
Don't screw this up.
My bet?
He's dead by morning.
Keller is one of the
world's greatest fighters.
He is rare.
I want him.
Well, i... [dial tone]
welcome to my universe.
[Click]
[click]
welcome, gentlemen, to fuego penal,
a place where you will live out
your miserable, worthless
existences indefinitely.
I'm files. Think of me as god.
Screw with me, and by
sweet, sunny jesus,
i will use your prostates
as goddamn trampolines.
Preston: hello, girls.
I'm the warden.
I have one rule in my prison.
There are no rules.
Move it, keller.
Inmate: john matthew keller,
hero of the people.
Holy shit.
Sound like you know the
man, winston.
Only what i read on the net.
Hey, billings,
wasn't keller the guy who nailed you
for armed robbery a few years back?
Yeah.
* And now i know
* there's a living god *
praise jesus.
Keller has been delivered to me.
Howdy.
Name's winston,
as in churchill.
Man with a marvelousth rift
of language.
I like that.
Yes, i do, indeed.
Shows character,
shows innate wisdom.
Shows, um... shut up.
Shows shut up. I can do that.
Hey, listen, i'm a guy that
you need to know and like.
Why?
I get things for people:
drugs, cigarettes,
good book,
even women.
I got contacts.
Well, just thought you'd
like to know.
Hey, officer keller,
meet the famous dr. Rosenbloom.
Killed his father and
mother with a corkscrew.
But don't hold that against him.
Deep down, he's a real sweetheart.
John keller.
You look much larger on television.
The first one... is free.
It's for all the pain.
Don't look now, keller,
there's a couple of good old boys
coming your way with orders to kill.
How do you know?
Got contacts, like i said.
I just did you a favor...
you owe me one.
Well...
our new playboy is
definitely a player.
Heh.
Did he... disappoint?
Absolutely not, sir.
I saw him fight once.
He was masterful.
However...
we don't want to move too quickly,
after the schrek incident.
We'll keep it simple, mr. Caesar.
Conventional indoctrination,
as per policy.
One last thing, warden.
About schrek...
how did things go so wrong?
U-uh... bad luck, sir.
The transport that was
moving schrek blew a tire.
Schrek acted quickly,
killed the guards,
escaped within minutes.
It garneredunnecessary attention.
S-s-s-such an incident
will not happen again, sir.
Good.
Keep me apprised on
keller's progress.
Files...
bring in our new guest.
[Shackles clanking]
mr. Keller.
Very impressive performance
in the kitchen this morning.
I was told they were
ordered to kill me.
Who told you that?
Heh heh.
In any case, it's probably true.
You're an ex-cop, mr. Keller.
Not a lot of people around here
have warm, fuzzy feelings for you.
However, i could
make your stay
a little more tolerable.
Interested?
If it allows me to pursue a life
of religious and
spiritual fulfilment,
of course.
I appreciate a good fighter,
mr. Keller.
Sarcasm from some
shit-fuck cop killer,
however, is something i
simply will not tolerate.
I'm prepared to make you an offer.
Listening?
I asked you a question.
Are we listening?
Yeah, i'm listening.
Good.
Pray, gentlemen, a word with you.
Apparently, some of you have
requested religious counseling.
Well, we aim to please,
so the holy sisters of mercy
have come in answer of your prayers.
Now, mind your
manners and play nice...
or i'll reach my fist so
far up your asses
i'll pull out your lungs.
Clear?
Dr. Rosenbloom:
they're all penguins!
They're all penguins! It's a
conspiracy! A conspiracy!
[Quacks]
sister, i must talk with you.
I have sinned.
I am hereto listen to
your troubles, my son.
I can only imagine the
sick fantasies
rolling around in
your head right now.
Now that you mention it,
the outfit is kind of kinky.
Eat me.
I'm glad to see you're alive.
You got anything yet?
Nothing yet.
However, the warden runs a
small-time black-market cockfight.
He wants me to fight.
What are you gonna do?
You guys got anything yet?
Negative.
There is something, though...
what?
U.s. marshals office has a
man in here, deep cover.
Been here about a month
working on the same case.
He's their top mole,
real performer.
I'll keep an eye out for him.
When do you come back?
One week.
Same place.
Hey... what?
What kind of meat do priests eat?
Nun.
Stay safe, keller.
Hate to lose my best partner yet.
Happy trails.
Gentlemen!
One rule, and
only one rule:
there are no rules!
Billings.
Agent keller.
Long time.
What are you doing here?
I'm your corner man.
I volunteered for the job.
Any particular reason?
Because nobody's gonna
kill you but me.
When we gets quared off one day,
i'm taking you out.
Praise jesus.
That's ivan.
And looky who his corner man is.
Round one.
[Clang]
crowd: yeah, come on!
Man: looks like your boy's losing!
Yeah? Don't bet on it.
Crowd: come on. Go, go!
Get him, keller.
Nail him!
Get him.
Man: get off of the
rope, you idiot!
Stand up and fight!
[Bell rings]
i don't care how the fuck you do it.
Tear this motherfucker's
head off, you understand?
Break his fucking neck.
[Bell rings]
man: let's go, let's go.
Get some now, ivan. Come on!
Take him down! Take him down!
You fucking finish it,
you son of a bitch!
You finish it now!
You kill him!
Keller, you kill him!
It's over.
Goddamn you, son of a bitch!
You will!
You think you're king, are you?
I'll come down there and
get you myself!
I'll rip your skin off!
I'll kill you!
It's only a game. It's ok.
[Neck cracks]
[clock ticks]
preston: h-hello.
He... m-mr. Caesar?
Uh, hello? Hello, sir?
H-hello?
Hello? Mr. Caesar?
Goddamn phone.
Hello?!
What?
Did you see the video
of the keller fight?
Of course.
The son of a bitch refused
to go for the kill.
Have you been
monitoring his behavior?
He's been watched morning,
noon, and night.
Nothing suspicious.
Still... before
you implement.
Mr. Keller's execution...
perhaps there is a way
to erase all our doubt.
I'd like to be certain, but i...
[dial tone]
[sighs]
anderson: yeah, i'm sorry
to hear that, marshal.
Thanks for the tip.
Good-bye.
[Sighs]
bad news.
They made the marshal's inside guy.
Is he still alive?
Unknown.
Their mole said he was a dead man.
They nailed them all.
They'll nail keller next.
I think we should pull him.
We can't, blaire.
Keller is now our only
link to the inside.
Commander...
[sighs]
keller volunteered for
this operation.
He knew the risks.
I understand your
relationship with keller.
You're a good team.
But you're still cops.
Don't forget that.
You meet with keller in a
couple of days, right?
Yep.
Well, if at that time, he
gives us any indication
his position's compromised,
we pull him.
Agreed?
Agreed.
[Groans]
ohh.
Contusions.
A concussion.
And, uh, subcutaneous hepatoma.
Hey, hey. Speak
english, rosenbloom.
How's he doing?
Well, basically, he's
pretty fucked up.
Ha ha ha ha.
Ohhh.
Ohhhh.
Unh.
Rosenbloom: you'll be all right.
Hey, doctor, why don't you keep
the good guard company for a while?
Paging dr. Rosenbloom.
Keller, are you clear
enough to understand me?
Yeah.
All right, listen carefully.
In another day or two,
you are going to have a visitor,
a woman, a spy.
A spy from whom?
The warden.
He suspects you of being a
deep-cover agent.
Where does the woman fit in?
Well, she's gonna keep you company
in a cell that's wired for sound.
It's an opportunity for you
to convince the warden
of your genuineness.
You're the mole.
U.s. marshal.
I've been nailed.
My days are numbered.
I understand that you are
the last line of defense.
Have you been tapped?
How could you manage this?
Well, the good dr. Rosenbloom and i
have quite a little company going.
At any rate, the warden
doesn't know who the mole is.
Not yet, anyway.
You got to get out of here.
Ha ha ha ha.
Well, if i'm still alive
in a few days,
we'll talk.
Hey.
2 days, remember.
And, keller, be convincing.
Whatever it takes, stud.
Hey, rosenbloom!
[Cell door slams]
blaire?
Where am i?
In a room.
I'm regina.
I'm your...
reward from the warden
for winning your first fight.
Well, that's very
thoughtful of the warden.
And all this time, i thought he was
a sick, twisted,
sadistic bastard...
who likes watching men sweat.
Prick.
And i was afraid you
would be too sick.
Never too sick for that.
Ow!
Ahhh.
Ohhh.
[Moans]
ohhh!
Ohhh.
[Regina moans]
what happened, keller?
I lost my mind.
Suddenly the gun was in my hand,
and i was firing it.
Bang, bang, and they were all dead.
That's so sad.
You don't look like a killer.
I have killed,
and i will kill again.
Would you kill me?
If you give me a reason,
i will kill you.
Promise?
Promise.
[Rings]
preston here.
Caesar: don't preston me.
Inform me.
He's clean.
I know you have an agent there.
Find him.
Kill him.
Make it look accidental.
We begin in 7 days.
Understood.
Sir, if i may make a suggest...
[dial tone]
[sighs]
[dogs barking]
winston: listen up. I
know all about your cover.
Your commander anderson communicated
to my section chief,
who then leaked
the intel down to me.
How?
Through our head guard mr. Files.
Files? But...
he knows nothing about it.
Rosenbloom and i have
got him hooked up
on a pcp-cocaine combo.
You see, files knows that rosenbloom
needs outside constituents.
So i make out my grocery
order list to my contact,
and then files hooks up
with him on the outside,
and the shit comes down
to us via single flower.
The flower's encrypted?
Acetylene?
Bingo.
Water, a little lemon juice, voila!
Invisible ink.
My plastic homing pigeon
to the outside world.
What do you know about the
missing inmates?
[Sighs]
not much.
Men are executed on a regular basis,
ostensibly by orders of the state.
But when, uh, family or friends come
to collect the remains,
zip, nada, nothing.
This corpse-snatching, it
doesn't make any sense.
I've pressed all my sources,
but i can't figure it out.
There's no rhyme or reason
to steal dead cons.
That's about it for now.
Meet you at the mess in 20.
Aah!
Guard: go get him! Grab his arms!
Easy! Easy!
Thanks.
Like i said,
you're mine.
Only on my terms,
no one else's.
[Door opens]
hey.
What are you working on, blaire?
Oh, trying to construct a pattern
that needs a little old-fashioned
extrapolation.
5 prison facilities,
including fuego,
all within 300 miles of each other.
Connect the dots,
you have some
what of a circle.
Schrek's transport was disabled
on interstate 62 going
west out of fuego.
So somewhere within here
is our answer, huh?
Ha.
Yeah, wonderful.
Only, that leaves about
1,000 square miles
of mountain and
desert as possibilities,
and, uh, we don't even know for sure
if schrek is connected to
the missing bodies
of executed inmates.
Hmm.
Well, let's hope keller comes up
with some more useful information.
Yeah.
Have your report on my
desk in the morning.
You got it.
Go left, right.
That's it. Go, turn, turn.
Hands up. Here you go, come on.
That's it. Go, go.
That's it. Go. Left roundhouse.
Come on. Come on.
Stay back. Go back, go back.
Ok.
That's it. Stand up.
You ain't showing him right, man.
See, it's the element of surprise
that throws the enemies off.
Isn't it right, keller?
Man: this is it, man.
Watch this, boys.
I see your point.
1, 2... 3!
You picked a fine
day to die, keller.
Man: quit dancing, boys. Let's go.
Breathe, keller, breathe!
Crowd: go, go, go!
Get him!
Crowd: go, go, go! Get him!
The secret is...
one more blow, and you
snap his windpipe.
Yeah.
I... i see.
Suffocate him! Yeah!
Rosenbloom: get my glasses.
Look. See him suffocate.
Rosenbloom.
See him suffocate.
Hey, hey, hey!
Calm.
Calm, calm.easy.
You missed a
great opportunity, keller.
I just return eda favor.
I don't like debts.
Next time.
Next time, you die.
[Laughs]
files: all right, break it up.
Break this up.
What the hell is going on?
Order just came down
from the governor, billings.
Tonight you hold
hands with jesus.
Guards: come on, let's go!
Come on, get up!
Come on, pick it up. Pick it up.
Keller!
Keller.
What?
Keller, they're coming for you.
They're coming for you.
Who?
The warden and his men.
I know what they're gonna do to you.
Just like the others.
Files: schrek first!
Save keller for last.
Do me a favor, doc.
Ha ha ha.
Time to check out, keller.
What's up, warden?
Well, that's a
good question, keller.
Here's the answer.
Tonight, you die.
Keller.
What the hell is going on?
Your execution's been
moved up, cop killer.
No reprieve, do not pass go,
do not collect $200.
I want to see a
governmental approval.
Take my word for it?
Stay back! I can break his neck.
Stay back!
This will help you relax.
Eh?
Priest: "though i walk through the
valley of the shadow of death",
i will fear no evil."
By special penal order 456.1,
john keller, i hereby authorize
your formal execution.
I have the right to an...
you have no rights, mr. Keller.
Parting is such sweet sorrow.
Priest: "be with me all
the days of my life."
[Medical equipment beeps]
[camera clicks]
no, you can't do this.
[Click]
keller: no, you can't do this!
No!
You can't do this!
[Sighs]
what is it?
John's dead.
No.
It's a mistake.
It's over, christy.
It's over.
He's not dead.
I know keller.
He is the most
unstoppables on of a bitch
on the planet.
Nobody's unstoppable, christy.
Not even john fucking keller.
I'm staying on this.
You're too close to this.
Go home. That's an order.
It's company policy.
Oh, don't give me that company
policy bullshit, anderson.
You sent him in.
You're on indefinite leave
until further notice, agent blaire.
Screw you.
I'd like to speak with
john keller's cellmate.
[Sighs]
you're keller's sister friend.
This poor troubled soul over there
would like to speak with me.
Move closer to the glass.
Move closer.
I can't see you.
Move... closer.
Move closer.
Where is he?
Please, move closer.
Move closer.
Look into my eyes.
Can you see my soul? Ha ha ha.
Creep!
Ahh. I have something for you...
from john keller.
Guard: all right, time's up.
Let's go.
I know where he is.
Where is he?
The gates of heaven.
People talk when they're
flying high.
[Whistles]
rosenbloom: bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Mmph.
Preston: welcome, gentlemen.
[Medical equipment beeps]
keller: where am i?
Winston: it ain't club
med, i can tell you that.
What's up, warden?
Ever the inquisitive one,
aren't you, keller?
Well, don't worry.
Everything will be made
clear soon enough.
In the meanwhile...
get some rest.
Preston: oh, and by the way...
no quarreling.
If any of you even thinks of
stepping out of line,
the punishment is simple...
death by slow torture.
Get some rest, ladies.
Hi, keller.
Hey.
Happy you could join the party.
Well, at least we're getting
closer to solving our mystery
of missing corpses, huh?
Let's hope we find out
before we end up corpses ourselves.
[Blaire sniffs]
[sighs]
[sobs]
[dogs whimpering]
welcome, john keller.
Why am i here?
Why, mr. Keller?
To do what you do best:
fight.
You are the only one of your kind,
so we had to have you.
So what's your excuse?
I guess we have something in common.
Mr. Keller.
A great honor.
I'm justin caesar.
This is my humble, little home.
Amenities completed.
Mr. Keller, now...
down to business.
Mr. Keller...
you are here to participate
in an ancient ritual,
the ritual of kumite.
Kumite?
Ahhh.
You know of it.
Keller: the origin of
kumite are japanese,
second dynasty.
It's a thousand years old.
It's the most sacred event
for the ancient samurai warriors.
Hmmm.
Very good.
Only, this kumite
is to the death.
What do you want from me?
I need your spirit
and your dedication to survival.
You brought us here to
murder one another.
Mr. Keller, you misunderstand caesar.
You see, he's actually performing
a service to you and
these other men.
Is that how you see it?
You will fight.
If you win,
you'll be granted your freedom...
and one million
dollars with plane fare
out of the country.
If you lose...
well... if you lose,
you'll not need plane fare
where you'll be going.
Bring in the next man.
I love you.
[Sobs]
[sobbing]
[chuckles]
ha ha!
[Quick music beat plays]
* hey * what's up?
* Hey * what *
you * know?
* Hey * hey *
what's * up?
* Say * up * your
bella * but, see
* bello bella
* bello bella *
ah * bello, hey
* bello bella
* bello, hey
* bello wella
* bello wella *
bello, hey * hey
* bello wella
* bello bella
we have to get out of here.
I'm open to suggestions.
* Bello, hey * hey
* bello wella
* bello wella *
ah * ah * ah
[cheering]
ladies and gentlemen...
friends,
welcome to kumite.
As you are aware,
this will be our final performance.
But i guarantee you,
it will be an
experience of a lifetime.
Inside these pens,
we have the finest selection of
warriors we have ever assembled:
masters of savate...
mui thai, judo, jujitsu, boxing,
wrestling, and, uh...
let's not forget
about the eclectic.
They are here...
for you.
So without any further ado,
your host... justin caesar.
Hail, caesar! Hail, caesar!
Ladies and gentlemen,
as the romans of yesteryear
once heralded before such events,
let me now say...
let the games... begin!
[Cheering]
[cheering and screaming]
ladies and gentlemen, we
start this evening's feast
with a tasty appetizer.
Schrek... tooley...
you're up.
[Cheering]
you try anything stupid, schrek,
and i'll put a bullet right
in your heart.
[Applause]
i bribed files.
It's gonna be you and me, keller.
Don't get your hopes up, billings.
We might not even get paired up.
Hooh!
[Crowd cheers]
[crowd claps]
ohh!
Ohh! [Crack]
[cheering]
ohh...
man: yeah! Take his throat!
Hummhh!
[Stifling laughter]
[audience applauds]
i only count10 guards.
And i count 10 ak-47s.
What's your point?
Oh... ladies
and gentlemen!
A difficult act to follow!
Billings!
Wess!
Showtime!
[Cheering]
woman: whooo!
Ohhhh!
[Audience shouting and applauding]
unhh! Ohh!
Aahhh!
[Crack]
uhh!
Yeah. Heh heh.
[Crowd cheers]
[cheering]
plan "a" escapes meat the moment.
Uh... well, you have a plan "b"?
I'm working on it.
[Cheering]
ladies and gentlemen...
my friends...
we are especially proud to
introduce to you
a man of some distinction...
and if you have followed the
news of late...
some notoriety.
Agent john keller was...
once the pride of law enforcement...
until he butchered2 fellow officers
in the heat of homicidal passion.
Help me give it up for...
john...
the cop killer...
keller!
Keller! Elko!
[Women screaming]
man: yeah!
[Shouting and applause]
yaaahhh!
[Both shouting]
[cheerfully]
uhh! Ohh!
Yes!
[Cheering and shouting]
ohhh!
[Light applause]
[men shouting]
come on! Come on!
Come on.
[Crowd chanting "kill"]
[cheering]
ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha! Ha ha ha!
[Laughing and cheering]
caesar: the cop killer!
Hee hee hee hee hee!
[Cheering]
[men shouting]
hey.
[Wind howling]
[light applause]
congratulations, winston.
[Gunshot]
ohh!
[Women screaming]
you survived your first round.
Billings! Schrek! Move out!
No! I paid for keller.
You fight who i tell you to fight!
[Applause]
come on!
Yahhhh!
Yahh!
Man: fight! Fight!
Man: break it! Break it!
Break it!
Kill him now!
Kill him!
Second man: no! Wait!
Man: kill him!
I'm coming for you, baby.
Heh heh heh heh heh!
Praise jesus!
Aaahh!
[Crowd chanting "schrek"]
hoohh!
[Cheering]
[man laughs]
man: yes!
Yeeeesssss!
Kill him!
[Crack]
uhh!
Ooh!
[Crack]
[cheering]
aaahh!
[Cheering]
man: kill him!
Keller...
well done... mr. Schrek.
This one...
is for you.
You won't be...
disappointed.
Mr. Keller...
a u.s. marshal for you.
A token of my
respect for your skill.
Enjoy.
Ohhhh... yeah!
[Cheering]
ladies and gentlemen...
mesdames et messieurs...
a very tiny morsel to
help cleanse the palate!
Winston!
[Cheering]
winston!
Keller.
I don't want to fight him.
What, are we girlfriends?
Like i give a shit what you want.
You will both get your
asses out here,
or you will both get shot.
Please?
One... [cheering]
2...
all right.
You know what you have to do.
Just make it quick.
[Sighs]
come on.
[Silence]
What the hell you doin'?
[Cheering]
i will not fight.
Ohh! Ohh!
Man: boo!
Boo!
Yaahh!
[Cheering]
uhh!
Ahh! Ohh!
That's right!
You fight me, god damn it!
You fight me!
Man: yeah!
Come on, john!
Me!
Come on!
Uhh!
Come on! Uhh!
[Cheering]
man: kill him!
Second man: kill him!
[Crowd chanting "kill"]
i will not... kill him.
[Boos and moans]
finish it!
I will not... kill him!
Why does he not kill him?
I have a revelation, my dear...
a painful one.
It has become clear to me
that mr. Keller is an...
undercover agent.
How could he, then,
kill an associate?
A pity.
Now...
whether he continues to win or not...
i will have to kill mr. Keller.
I will not... kill him.
Kill him.
Next time i say "kill him..."
you kill him.
Ladies and gentlemen...
boys and girls...
our gracious host and hostess
would like to present to
you this evening's
main course...
keller!
[Cheering]
schrek!
[Excited cheering]
it's time to dance.
What do you want...
waltz or tango?
Hoooo yah!
Now... you... die!
Aaahh!
I seem to have misplaced my pen.
[Reverberating distantly]
keller! Keller!
Keller! Keller!
What's up, asshole?
Aaahh!
Aaahhh!
Huhhh!
Haahhh!
[Crowd screams]
[applause]
keller.
The moment i've been waiting for.
Aah!
You son of a bitch!
Everybody, get down!
Blaire: keller, behind you!
[Moans]
mmhhh...
no...
you're gonna be all right.
[Gasping]
maybe i'll...
see you in another life.
I should've known better...
than to bring you...
up here!
Once a cop...
always a cop.
Drop the gun!
Take the shot, john!
Take it.
Even if you kill me...
right between the...
the eyes...
take the shot!
[Blaire sobs softly]
aaahhh!
[Machine gunfiring]
all right, nobody move!
You all right?
Yeah. Yeah, it's a...
friggin' picnic.
You ought to try it sometime.
Ohhh! Ohh...
you're too scrappy to die.
Uh, no, no. I ain't gonna die.
I gotta come back and kick your ass
for punchin' me in the gut.
[Chuckles]
hey, john... yeah.
Thanks, man.
You're welcome.
By the way, this is blaire.
Howdy.
[All chuckling]
bloodsport!
Bloodsport!