I'm on my period.
So?
I love fucking you
on your period.
I do, too. But that's nasty.
Keep scrubbing that shit, boy.
I want it clean when I cop it.
Man, you can't afford
this shit, D.
Man, I'm a cop that shit from Frankie
by the end of next summer.
- You gonna see, bruh.
- If you say so.
I'm gonna be in this next summer
with your bitch!
Hey, I got something for you.
I wanted to give it to you
on your birthday,
but I figured
I'd give it to you early
just so you could try it on
to see if you like it.
Damn, girl.
You shouldn't have.
You like it?
Like it?
I love it.
Okay, D. Stop.
Come on.
All right, I tried.
Where you going?
Shit, I'm finna go smoke
at Rell's house real quick,
take care of some shit.
You're not going to hit
another lick, are you?
What make you think
some shit like that?
Because you know my mama
don't want that around me no more.
Baby, that's why I'm finna go
look for a job.
I'm not hitting no more licks.
Promise?
I promise.
I'll call you later on tonight.
What you doing out here,
little runt?
- Spying on you guys.
- You better not be doing that.
I'm going to tell your mama
on you, all right?
Where the fuck
you was at earlier, D?
All that slow programming
and shit,
niggas know
we got a schedule to keep.
Well, shit, man. I just went
to go check out Frankie's car.
- What, that Chevy?
- Yeah.
Yeah, that shit fly as fuck.
Nigga, stop lying,
you was with the bitch.
Nigga, so?
Yeah, I went to go see her
for a minute afterwards, nigga.
You mad you ain't got a bitch
to go see?
You've been fucking that bitch
for a minute too long now.
- Not even, bruh.
- Yes.
I couldn't even fuck anyway.
She was on her period, bruh.
Yo what!
See you know I love fucking bitches
on their period, man.
Blood, that's what I told the bitch.
You can't get them pregnant
and they're even hornier.
- Hell, yeah.
- I love that shit, man.
You niggas nastier
than a motherfucker.
Hey, man,
fuck all that shit though.
You niggas ready for this shit?
Hey, Barry Bonds!
Nigga, you ready?
- Come on, man.
- You ready for this shit?
Yeah, man. You know I'm ready, bro.
Come on.
Then why the fuck you still got
that stupid ass baseball outfit?
I just got out of practice, nigga.
You look stupid as fuck.
You ain't gonna be saying that shit
when you see me in the league.
- Yeah, whatever.
- Yeah, fuck you.
What?
Man, fuck all that shit, man!
Nigga, just get your foot heavy
for that pedal, nigga.
You sure you want to do this shit?
- Yeah, man. I'm good.
- You hear these niggas?
Sup with you niggas
with that whispering?
You niggas go together
or something?
D.
- Fuck, man.
- What, nigga?
I ain't got
my motherfucking gun, bruh.
Where the fuck your gun at?
Man, I must have left that shit
at Aliky's house or something.
You left it at the bitch house?
I told you, man.
That bitch got you fucked up.
Fuck, man.
Man. Fuck all that, nigga.
Nigga, take this.
- Huh, nigga!
- Is you fucking serious?
Nigga you want a gun or not?
I might as well use my hand
with this dumb ass shit.
Nigga,
a hand don't look like a gun!
Fuck, man. Come on.
- Niggas ready?
- Hell yeah.
Come on, nigga.
All right, come on.
Open the motherfucking register!
- Open this motherfucker!
- Easy, easy man!
- Hurry the fuck up, man!
I'll give you anything.
Just don't hurt me!
- Just don't hurt me!
- Ain't nobody up in here, y'all!
- Open this...
- Get down, get down!
Hey, they got a room back here!
Hey, check to see
if he got a safe in the back.
- You got a safe? You got a safe?
- No, I ain't got nothing please!
- I ain't got nothing back there!
- He's lying, man!
Come on. Let's go, nigga.
We taking too long, bro.
Come on!
Watch him for me. I'm gonna go
see if he got a safe!
- Come on, bro.
- Watch him for me!
No, no, don't shoot, man.
Don't...
Okay, just...
Just take anything you want.
Hey, there ain't shit back here!
Come on. Come on, man!
He ain't got shit!
Come on, man. Let's go!
- Come on, D!
- Aye, hold up!
Come on!
Oh, shit.
Where the fuck is D?
- Where the fuck is he at?
- He coming, nigga. Be cool!
You all hear that shit?
What the fuck was that?
Damn it, boy!
Don't make me do this!
What the fuck, man?
What the fuck is you doing?
- Just slide out your gun now!
- I ain't got no gun!
I swear to God, man.
I ain't got shit!
- Where's he at?
- I mean, he was just behind us.
I swear to God he was!
That nigga ain't got
no motherfucking gun!
That nigga still in there, man.
I'm about to get that nigga!
- What the fuck's wrong with you?
- I'm about to go get that nigga!
Fuck that shit! Fuck that shit!
I ain't going to jail!
Empty your pockets now,
you little bastard!
Take it out slow now!
This gun cocked and loaded!
- Lil' D.
- Maalik.
You look less swoll
than when you went in.
You look fat.
What? This all muscle, kid.
I'm like the ghetto iron man
out in this motherfucker.
You wish you was eating like me.
- You still eat pork, nigga?
- Yeah, nigga.
Good, 'cause Bertha got something
cooking for your ass.
Let's roll, nigga.
You feel guilty?
- Well, for what?
- You know what, nigga.
What happened with D.
Shit I did for a minute, nigga.
I ain't gonna lie.
But then I slept on it.
And, nigga,
that shit ain't on us.
Nigga, what?
Nigga you feel guilty
or something?
Hell no, nigga.
Nigga knew what the fuck
we was doing.
Shit would have been way different
if I could have got up in that bitch.
Shit's fucked up.
Nigga, what's fucked up
is how you left me on the blade
30 minutes before them niggas
ran up on me.
You see what happened
to my eye, bruh?
That little ass shit, nigga?
Stop tripping.
I'm not your motherfucking
assistant pimp.
Should've had one of your bitches
come and get you.
- Man down, pimp in distress.
- Joking ass nigga.
Just start pimping
Money Mike ass nigga.
Fuck you, nigga.
Man, stop tripping, nigga.
God damn!
Told you, nigga.
I'm gonna handle that shit.
Slide on every single
one of those suckas!
We'll see.
Keep rubbing on that
little ass shit like it hurts.
What the fuck we doing here
anyway?
Nigga, you remember that bitch
from the other day?
Who? The bitch
with the crazy ass daddy?
Yeah, nigga. You know the one.
Nigga, I got this bitch ready.
I just need you to be my brother
and post up out here
until I get back my nigga.
- Post up out here?
- Yeah.
Fuck that, nigga.
I'm coming with you.
Come on, bruh.
You know you're going to scare
the panty's back on that bitch.
You got me fucked up, nigga.
All right, then, nigga. Pay me.
Yeah, nigga, that's right,
pay me.
I ain't no motherfucking
lookout nigga.
Nigga, that's what you want,
huh?
I ain't waiting on you, nigga.
Nigga, D is out.
- He out, nigga.
- Yeah, nigga, I know.
And I'm about to put my boy on.
That's why I'm taking care
of this shit first.
Nigga, you asking me
to pay you and shit.
That ain't got nothing to do
with D getting out.
You're snorting
too much of that cocaine.
It's like a blizzard
up your nose.
No, Nigga. Chill on that, nigga.
She said her daddy drive
a red Cadillac truck, nigga.
So post up outside and holler
if you see him coming.
Yeah, I'm supposed to be the one
up there fucking.
Man, I got you.
Keep your eyes
on that window sill right there.
You might see a titty
or something.
Man, go somewhere
with that shit, nigga.
Just fuck the bitch good.
I wanna hear it.
Man, she on a blue dolphin.
You're gonna hear, nigga.
Trust me.
Loud and clear.
I told you I'd do it.
I feel really, really good.
Is this how
I'm supposed to feel?
This good?
No, I could make you feel
better than that.
Close your eyes.
Egypt is America.
Egypt is Babylon.
Egypt is bondage. Read.
"By the way there
by stake they're to be."
Wait a minute.
He said he's going to bring us
back into bondage with ships.
You Negros, Latinos
and American Indians
got here on slave ships. Read.
"Thy shall see it no more
again."
You didn't see it no more again.
None of you been back to Israel
as a nation. Read.
"And there you shall be sold
on to your enemies."
Who was sold to their enemies?
You Negros, Latinos
and American Indians. Read.
"For bond men."
For bond men
meaning slave men. Read.
- "And bond woman."
- And slave...
Hey.
What?
Your fucking nose is bleeding.
You're bleeding on me.
So? You ain't ever seen
no blood before?
Get the fuck off me, nasty ass.
What the fuck?
Stop it...
"And I will not cause my anger
to fall upon you."
We were taken out of Israel...
You see that nigga's face, babe?
Baby, stop it.
You're being mean.
- And in anger.
- In anger.
And in wrath.
Moses didn't
tell us to get out of that land.
He ruled us out of that land
with anger. Read.
"And in great indignation..."
Please help us!
Bitch ass nigga!
You was talking all that shit!
- What are you doing?
- Shut the fuck up, bitch!
Stop honking that fucking horn
before I shoot you!
Get the fuck out the car!
Who got the fucked up face now,
bitch?
Where the rest at, nigga?
I know you got some more.
Come on, nigga.
Don't touch me like that.
Shut your bitch ass up, nigga!
Yeah, yeah,
I know you had something else.
Faking ass nigga.
Now I would take this car,
but I ain't a dumb nigga.
I ain't dumb. You feel me?
So to show you all
what I think about it...
Here's what I think
about your bitch ass car.
Bitch ass nigga!
So how does it feel
to be back, bro?
Different.
I can finally breathe.
Yeah, nigga.
You almost bled out
and died on us.
Then you held it down
for two years.
I'm proud of you.
Ain't nothing changed.
It's still your hood, you know?
You'll get used to it.
Nigga, I said a red Cadillac.
Her daddy almost killed me.
What the fuck were you thinking?
Nigga, you was doing
what you had to do.
I was doing what I had to do.
- Give me my $30 back.
- You got me fucked up.
How much gate money
they give you when you got out?
Three hundred dollars.
- Niggas only gave you $300?
- Hell, yeah, they did.
Almost two years
working in there, bruh,
and you only made 300?
That's some bullshit, bruh.
That's a prison system,
little nigga.
- You better know about it.
- Hell, yeah.
My nigga Ressy
is in the Marines.
He said they make
all that niggas shit in prison.
That nigga's working
like a slave.
That's what they do, blood.
Ain't none of you all seen Ty
around here?
I told you.
He got cut from the minors
a few months back.
- He don't fuck with us no more.
- Fuck that, nigga.
You all know
where he's staying at?
Look, I don't wanna hear
this nigga's name in this house.
- You understand?
- I say whoever name I wanna say.
Just wondering if y'all seen him,
that's all.
I'm just really glad
that my baby's home.
Me too. Me too.
I remember
when my man came home
after three years
from Pelican Bay.
The good girls,
they always stick by their man.
Always.
So anyways,
when you all moving to Sac, B?
In about three weeks, baby.
You know I've had
my financial difficulties lately
and my position
at the clinic is ending
and I can't keep this house
anymore.
- Sorry to hear that, B.
- Me too.
So what you doing
with the house?
- What do you mean?
- Are you gonna sell it?
This house?
You thought I own this house?
No, I've been renting this house
for the last 15 years!
I don't own this house!
Y'all thought I owned this?
That ain't funny, B.
Okay.
Okay, I'm sorry, baby.
But what I'm saying is this.
You got about one week
to decide what the hell
you're gonna do with yourselves.
And that decision
is yours to make.
Not mine.
You all thought
I owned this house?
He's here.
Shit.
I threw in 20 extra pills
for you.
- Good looking, bruh.
- It's good.
Aye, that nigga D
got out tonight, huh?
Yeah, I just seen him.
Yeah, you know, if you ever need
to make some dough,
you know I fuck with him
on behalf of the streets.
- It's good.
- Fosho that's love.
Yeah, man.
He still fucking with Ty though?
No, man. Ain't nobody fucking
with that nigga, man.
Yeah, when you see D,
let that nigga know, man,
Ty ain't the nigga to be around.
Fuck with that nigga,
he going to have to duck
with that nigga straight up.
Still got racks
on that nigga's head, man.
Man, fuck that nigga, man.
You heard about that shit
in The Bottoms the other day?
Yeah, some nigga from the Rich
got hit up on some stoop.
But niggas don't know
who shot him though.
Yeah, wrong place, wrong time.
That's fucked up.
Yeah.
That's life though.
But, yeah, man, I got bitches
on the deck hit my phone, nigga.
I'm out this thang.
You already know what it is.
Aight, G.
Something tells me you don't
plan to step foot on this
or any field like it again.
Your whole life
you wanted to preach, right?
I always figured
I'd end up being a preacher.
Then you got
what you always wanted.
It's not what I wanted, Ty.
I mean,
I know I'm work in progress.
I realise that more and more
every day.
I'll never be satisfied
and neither will the Lord.
And that's the reality, son.
My whole life
I wanted to play baseball.
It didn't work out.
That's my reality.
When did you say
you got back here, Ty?
About the middle of August.
Well, shortly before you quit
out there in Nevada...
... my wife had a miscarriage.
This wasn't the first time
either.
See, we've been trying
to have children for years now.
Her belly was bigger than ever.
Ty, I mean,
there's nobody to blame.
Not my dad, not me.
And not God
because he was next on the list.
These things, these tragedies,
these let-downs,
they're a part of life.
And they can and they will
only make you stronger.
Yeah.
I guess you're right.
Ten toes down, son.
I'll see you Sunday.
Remember this?
And my nigga, D. Wassup, man?
- Whose car is that?
- Okay, that's my shit, man.
You know I had to cop
once my money was right.
Like that?
Damn, man.
Frankie finally
came up off that shit, huh?
Hell, yeah, man.
He was going through
some money problems, man.
A little family bullshit,
you know.
So he took a couple L's
and I got that whip up off him, man.
She beautiful though, huh?
I'm already treating her
like shit though, man.
I ain't gonna lie, bruh.
That motherfucker is wet though.
Hell, yeah, nigga.
You know, boy.
That's wassup, bruh.
I'm happy for you.
It's good, man.
We all gonna be on 26's
before we 26, man.
You gonna get yours next, D.
- I promise that.
- Fosho that.
You need to see
what this pimping is all about.
- This nigga Elvis is guaped up.
- I told him, man.
Both of you need to see wassup
with this pimping.
Yeah. Whatever.
If I can't
knock me a bitch today,
nigga, I'm robbing Bings.
You ain't robbing
no damn Bings, bruh.
What, nigga?
All I need is one lick.
Nigga, before a nigga
hit a lick on anything,
we smoking first.
Oh, I know you been wanting
to smoke, huh, D?
Shit, yeah. I'm on parole, bruh.
First parole meeting is today.
She gonna be all over a nigga.
Come on now, nigga.
You know I got you.
- Tell him about that shit.
- What do you mean, bro?
Nigga,
I brought you my shit, man.
The "Whizzanator".
- What the fuck is that?
- You gonna like this, boy.
Man, I used this shit back
when I got out of Rita, man.
This shit been passed down
through generations, boy.
Just get in the car, nigga.
- This shit white, bruh.
- So, nigga?
Ain't nobody really looking
at your dick.
You niggas like that shit, huh?
I ain't gonna lie.
Whoever they modelled that after
had a funny looking ass dick!
All right,
so I just strap this thing on?
Shake it
and press the button, right?
It's that easy, D.
Aye, aye,
stop at this store right here.
We got to get a swisher.
Nigga,
I thought you already had one!
Hell no. It's good.
We got to stop at Big John's
anyway.
Big John?
Yeah, that nigga been wanting
to yo holla at you, too.
Him and Cory.
Hey, bruh,
where can I dump these guts at?
Put that shit on the table, bruh.
It's all good.
You seen some crazy shit
in the pen, huh?
Got you acting funny already.
Nigga, he just got out,
Big John!
Shut up, nigga!
D, it's good, bruh.
When you're trying
to get some real money,
come holla at us.
What's up with you though,
nigga?
How the game been treating you?
Shit, you see
how I'm living, my nigga.
Just trying to get my niggas
here on the same hype.
That pimping money cool,
don't get me wrong.
But when you put one of these
in a nigga's face,
it ain't nothing
he won't give up.
What are you all about to go hit
anyway?
This little Asian spot
in the Rich.
A happy ending joint,
you feel me?
We still need a driver, too.
I don't trust this nigga,
Cory, behind the wheel.
Uncle John,
why do you always rob Asians?
What? Simone!
Get the fuck out of here!
What you doing in here anyway?
I ain't gonna lie,
them Asians
been busting back lately.
Not on me! Not on us!
Simone, go get some ice cream
or something.
You ain't supposed
to be in here.
Kids all innocent and shit, man.
Let me hit that, bruh.
What you think
about this pimp shit, D?
Sound good. Shit.
Niggas locked up
say it's hella drama though.
Nigga drama?
Nigga, that's if you don't know
how to pimp.
You can't tote a mac
if you ain't a mack, nigga.
- On mamas, nigga!
- Believe that.
The only drama I had with this
pimp shit happened last week.
What happened last week?
He's a pimp,
that's what happened.
No, nigga.
My older partner Uncle Chuck
turned me onto this pimp shit.
So I leave my bitch
in the room with him for a night
to see if she can handle
some real pimping, you dig?
You know,
see if she's game tight
or a loose bitch fucking
for food and shelter and shit, man.
The nigga fucked her,
but he ain't break her.
He said she ain't let him hit
that third hole neither.
So what happened last week then?
Nigga, I took that booty
virginity from her.
Hit them cheeks.
What was the drama then, bruh?
Nigga, you ever fucked your girl
in the ass for the first time?
- Man.
- Nigga, that's drama!
Let's see.
Staying out of trouble.
That's good.
Now where did I put those?
I know, there you go.
Got you right here.
- Hun, are you okay?
- I'm fine.
You tried to rob a liquor store
with a hand held mirror, huh?
Yeah.
You're lucky no one was hurt.
Actually, I got shot...
... twice.
I'm not talking about
self-inflicted wounds here.
It would have been a tragedy
if someone innocent was hurt.
You feel me?
You know you are too damn young
to go to prison for two years.
You know that, right?
Yes.
But that's what's cool now days,
getting shot, going to prison.
Here's a list
of potential employers
who hire convicted felons.
And in your case, parolees.
So, what's your number one priority
now that you're a free young man?
Not going back.
I'm not going back to prison.
That's good.
So have you consumed any drugs
or alcohol since your release?
No.
Good, follow me.
Come on, nigga!
Nigga, what you doing, bruh?
Fuck these bitches, nigga!
Come on, bruh!
Fuck you too, bitch!
Punk ass ho's!
Don't trip off no bitch, nigga!
Man, these weak ass
motherfucking ho's!
I told you
I'm gonna get you a bitch, bruh.
- This shit takes time, nigga!
- Fuck that, nigga.
I ain't got
no motherfucking time!
Nigga, that's on you, bruh.
Don't take that shit out on me!
You see what the fuck I did
to that nigga last night?
- Take me home, nigga!
- You tripping, nigga.
We got time, boy.
Chill the fuck out!
I'll catch the bus, nigga.
You got me fucked up, bruh.
What the fuck is you acting
like this for, bruh?
Because I'm a real nigga!
That's why!
I'm gone, nigga.
Whatever, bruh.
Clown ass nigga man.
What's happening?
- I got the money.
- Money?
Throw it on the ground.
I'm going to pick it up.
Aye, meet me around the corner.
That nigga gave me $300.
Look at this bum ass bitch.
Look at your bum ass bitch.
Don't even look at me, bitch.
I ain't even the one.
For real, bitch!
- Big bro, what's happening?
- What's up, baby? What you need?
Shit, let me get something
for a hundred.
He want 20 pills.
What you do last night?
Shit, you know,
just handled business.
Hell, yeah,
I'm going to see you later.
All right, bruh.
What's up, my nigga Reez?
You good?
I am, you know.
Hell, yeah, boy.
Still doing that rapping shit?
You already know.
I'm going to go bust this move.
I'ma see you in a minute.
Grandmomma?
Grandmomma!
- Grandmomma!
- Jerell?
- Baby, is that you?
- What happened, Grandma?
Why you ain't call me?
I couldn't reach the phone.
I fell out my chair.
I must have gone to sleep.
Thank Lord Jesus Christ
I got you, baby.
I'm going to call Para transit
in the morning, Grandmomma.
Tell them
to get some more Metformin.
You only got two doses left.
Where'd you get
all that money from?
Don't worry about where
this come from, Grandmomma.
Let me know if you need anything and
I'll go get it for you, all right?
I got to go, Grandmomma.
You need something
from the store?
You be good, baby.
You be good, all right?
Tell B to hit me up, okay?
- All right.
Hey, you ever thought
about leaving?
You know,
when Bertha goes to Sac.
What? Out the hood?
Yeah, I guess.
Shit, I don't know where I'd go.
Hey, you better go look
for a job today.
I'ma see you in a minute.
Nigga, I know that ain't Lil' D.
Man, what's up with niggas?
What's going on, Cam?
You know ain't shit changed
and the number's still the same.
But fuck all that though, man.
Bounce in my nigga!
Come on, nigga.
We got shit to do.
This nigga had his first parole
meeting yesterday.
Parole meeting?
You think me or him
give a fuck about all that, man?
This shit concerns us, man.
It will only be a minute though.
What? Niggas touched down
and don't fuck with me no more, man?
You all making this harder
than bumping a bitch, man!
I said come on, man!
All right, bruh.
What the fuck you all eating
anyway, man?
Eating jail house sandwiches?
Nigga's free, man.
Little fucking D! My nigga!
I know you've heard
about all the mobbing me
and your brother was doing
while you was locked up, nigga.
- You're in a real good position.
- Come on, nigga.
- I told you he just got out.
- It's all good, Maalik.
We're just talking.
So what's going on, bro?
Where we going?
Oh, you'll find out soon enough.
I just wanted to holla
at you niggas
about this nigga Ty real quick.
What about him?
That nigga's fucking done.
It's on site with this nigga, man.
What's the number one rule?
Never get high
on your own supply, right?
The only reason why this bitch
ass nigga didn't break that rule
is because he was higher
than a kite on my dollar though.
Man, that don't even sound
like Ty.
What? Niggas change, boy.
Fuck that!
And you've been gone
two years, man.
A lot of shit done changed
in two years.
That nigga started getting
that fast money
and didn't know how to act.
One minute, boom,
I ain't gonna lie.
Nigga moving faster
than anyone on the team.
Then bam!
This nigga started taking
most of the pills
he supposed to be selling!
Damn near knock status.
Now can you believe that?
Is that adding up, nigga?
See, you hear me talking
but you ain't listening, nigga.
How much money he owe you all?
Nigga, enough to put
a new set of 32-inch rims
on this motherfucker
and throw a QP of purple
in the glove compartment, man.
Well, shit. I ain't seen him.
Nigga, we seen him.
I just want you to be there
when the shit pops off.
You know that shit unforgivable,
right?
You do the crime,
you do the time.
Ain't no way in hell
I would've left you on stuck
in the middle of a lick, nigga.
That's that sucka shit!
Straight up!
I just got out, bruh.
I got a lot of other shit
on my mind.
Yeah, some pussy, right?
You know whose Ty's
number one customer was
when he was moving for us,
right?
- Come on, bruh.
- Maalik ain't tell you, nigga?
Nigga Alakeeyee, Alikai.
However the fuck you say it.
Nigga, your bitch!
Yeah, he was doping her up
real good.
Got your bitch
strung the fuck out!
Come on, bruh.
What you trying to do?
What you saying, nigga?
Nigga, I'm saying
she eight-pills-a-day easy.
All that money
going to that nigga Ty's hands.
Not your books.
Did that nigga write you, bro?
That nigga write you a letter?
Put something on your books,
nigga?
Did Aliky write you?
They ain't do shit, nigga.
Got played out, man.
Maalik here will tell you, man.
Is it true, Maalik?
Maalik!
I mean...
I don't know.
The whole time, huh?
See, that's why I came
to holla at you, bruh.
I don't know why these niggas
leading you on.
But don't trip though.
You know I don't play
them little kids ass games.
See, earlier in the day,
one of my amigo partners
said he saw this nigga Ty
go into these apartments
last night.
Nigga, this is where
his sister stays at.
Now you see that hammer
under the seat?
Yeah, I see it.
Well, as a favour from me to you,
because we all want answers,
we're gonna get
a lot of shit handled.
Right now.
Bitch, I just had to ride
a motherfucking bike
from 96th and Bancroft
all the way to North Richmond
last night
because my granny needed
her motherfucking medication
and you're trying to tell me
you can't go outside tonight
because you got a broken heel.
Is you crazy?
Get the fuck out of here!
Get off of me!
Ty's not here!
Be the fuck quiet, bitch!
Hey, this nigga ain't here!
- This nigga ain't here, huh?
- No, this nigga ain't here.
Let's bounce
before niggas hear us and shit.
- Hell no!
- Send this nigga a message, D!
Let's fuck
this piece of shit up, man!
Come on, nigga. You heard me!
He fucked Aliky life up!
Ain't no telling
what else he did.
Nigga, he fucked us all over
and he put you in jail
for two years, nigga.
Look at me! Get active, nigga.
Nigga, get active, nigga!
Get that shit!
Fuck that nigga, yeah!
Aye, you good.
You good, nigga?
Hey, your old girl,
she stay in the Looney's.
You know, right across the way.
You know, where AJ stay at.
I seen her today.
But let me get that hammer,
ain't no use for it now.
Yeah, I'm about to make sure
this bitch
ain't on no funny shit
calling nobody.
Fuck!
What the fuck, nigga?
Is this what you planned
the whole time?
Man, fuck all that, man.
Bitch wouldn't stop screaming!
If she's fucking dead.
I'm out, nigga!
D bring the bat!
No fingerprints!
Fuck.
Let's go, you stupid ass niggas!
Let's go!
Come on, nigga. Let's go.
I said let's go!
- I got something for you.
- Damn, girl. You shouldn't have.
You sure
you want to do this shit?
- Yeah, man, I'm good.
- You hear these niggas?
- Come on, man. Let's go!
- Hey, hold up!
He fucked Aliky life up.
Ain't no telling
what else he did.
Okay, D. Stop.
Look at me!
Get active, nigga!
Your old girl,
she stay in the Looney's.
You know, right across the way.
You know, where AJ stay at.
Hey, come here.
I'm gonna go upstairs to see
your big sister, all right?
- She's babysitting me.
- She is?
Hey.
You need to leave.
Why?
Cuz AJ's getting back soon,
that's why.
Man, fuck AJ!
I ain't seen you in two years.
I know.
But he has.
Wait. I got something for you.
Stay right there.
You left this at my mama house
the last time I saw you.
Your mama had another kid?
No. She's mine.
Don't worry, she ain't yours.
- She look just like me.
- Well, I said she ain't yours!
AJ want me to give her up.
Look, if you need some help,
just come and see me.
I'm back for good now.
It's a little too late
for that, D.
I know people that can help you.
- What, like Ty?
- Naw.
Why the fuck you mentioning him?
He came over here the other day,
asking about you.
The only reason
that nigga getting better
is cuz people trying
to kill him.
But you probably
already know that, huh?
He the one
who got you like this?
I know he used to play ball
with AJ and shit, too.
Is that who you all
been coping from?
He got you on this shit?
Ty?
Ain't nobody cop
from that knock ass nigga.
He was only selling for a month
before he got hooked.
What you mean?
The last time I saw Ty
before he came over here
asking about you,
he was begging me for money.
AJ take care of me. That's it.
I thought you wanted better
for yourself?
I wanted a lot of things.
Look, you really need to go.
AJ getting back soon
and he ain't right, right now.
Can I see you again?
No.
No you can't, D.
Why you got to be
like this then?
Please.
Leave.
For me.
Go.
So what we looking for
anyway, bro?
We looking for the freshest whip
in the parking lot.
Bro, if they got a nice whip,
more than likely,
they got a nice house.
Hell, yeah, that makes sense.
- That look like the one.
- Yeah, we see you.
This is it right here, bruh.
Yeah, Big John's coming
to dinner tonight, baby.
- Man, I appreciate this, man.
- You know it's good.
You gonna be getting
that money now.
Buy you a new sweatshirt, nigga.
Yeah, for real.
You going to get back, stand up.
Feel me?
I know it be hard out here, man,
but you can't let these niggas
push up on you like that, man.
Got to yolk up on a nigga
sometimes.
You already know, man.
I appreciate you, bruh.
It's good. It's good.
- What's up, AJ, nigga?
- Sup, man?
What you got in that bag?
Just a lunch.
Man, it's way past
lunch time, man.
What's up with that money
you owe me?
I'll have your money soon.
Nigga, I promise.
My bitch been nagging me, man.
My fucking kid, man.
I got a fucking baby now, man.
Man, fuck your baby, bruh.
On everything, bruh!
Bitch ass nigga.
Get that shit!
Shut up.
Don't make a fucking sound!
Grab it.
Yeah, get all that shit.
Shut the fuck up.
Be quiet.
Hun, you mind
grabbing me a towel?
Baby? Babe, you there?
You be good, baby.
You be good, all right?
Why the fuck you ain't tell me
Aliky had a kid, bro?
Is she a motherfucking
dope fiend, my nigga?
Why the fuck
you ain't tell me, man?
You know that's the last thing
you need to worry about
coming out of that slammer, bruh.
You know
that ain't your kid, boy.
How the fuck you know that?
If you want it to be your baby,
that could be your fucking baby.
Don't want it to be your kid,
it ain't your kid, nigga!
Man, it ain't even about
the motherfucking kid!
That shit fucked up, bruh.
Man, but fuck all that shit,
man.
We right up here.
I told you I'm gonna make up
for everything, bruh.
You gonna love this.
I promise, my nigga.
Get the fuck up
out this car, man.
All right, baby.
Just meet me at the spot
around 19:30.
- You got this. All right, girl?
- Yeah, all right.
You know I wanted to go
by my house later
to get some of my things.
You know,
like my flat screen and shit.
What? You remember
what your daddy did to you?
I'll get you another TV,
whenever, baby.
You don't need
to go back there yet.
Besides, you know
I really don't want you to.
- Can we get one tonight?
- Yeah, we could get one tonight.
If you get this money coming in.
I already spent all that
on your clothes and shit, right?
- Yeah.
- All right, so we good for it.
Just call me
if you need anything, baby.
I will. Thank you.
I ain't buying that ho
no flat screen, nigga.
Nigga, fuck that bitch!
Just bring me my money.
That's what I say
to these bitches.
Let's find my man.
Here he go, right here.
Hey, hey, hey, pimpin'.
- What's good, pimpin'?
- What's up, Uncle Chuck?
Elvis and that...
Oh, this Lil' D.
You can call him D though.
No, I'm gonna call this nigga
Lil' Pimp.
How that sound?
That's fine with me.
- Nice to meet you, bruh.
- Yeah, you too, pimp.
Hey, man, my client
just finishing up, man.
Why don't you niggas meet me
back of the old rail road.
Yeah, that's cool, that's cool.
- All right, T.
- Come on, D.
Come on, man.
Hurry this shit up.
You too, bitch, get the molasses
out of your ass.
- All right, Unc, man.
- Any time, Leroy. Any time, man.
Come on, shit, time is money.
Now break yourself, bitch.
All right, go get my money.
So Elvis here tells me
you want to get in the game?
- Yeah, he does pimpin'.
- Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, nigga, I know how it is.
I just did six years in Avenal.
And it took a pimp a minute
to get back on his feet, too.
But, nigga, you lucky.
You see, you young.
But these hoes out here
is young and dumb.
You hear that, boy?
Now that's pimping.
Your nigga, Rell?
That nigga is a gorilla,
and he ugly!
See, you can be
an ugly gorilla pimp,
but you better be rich first,
you dig?
Nigga, you only got one whip?
No, D, man, you know you can use
my whip, man.
You know, get a date or two,
pull a few tricks.
Good, good.
So, nigga, what you need to do,
you need to get down there
to 85th and International.
She's set up down there
with my bottom bitch.
Scoop her up, take her around.
You know, show her what
this pimping is all about. You dig?
Elvis ran this shit
down to you, right?
- Yeah, I been at a game though.
- Good.
So nigga the next time I see you
you should be pimpin'.
Now you gonna go
by the name of Lil' Pimp.
I know that shit
sound fake as fuck.
But guess what, nigga?
You gonna be the only nigga
out here officially called that.
I'm gonna post out here
with Uncle Chuck.
What are you waiting for, man?
Handle that.
Wassup with this nigga, man?
I told you, man.
My nigga just got out.
So what this girl look like
you hooking him up with though?
- Man, the bitch is five-star.
- Is she?
- So how old is you?
- Old enough, you know.
I said how old are you?
Old enough ain't an age.
I'm 14 about to turn 15.
Everybody think I'm older
anyway.
Look,
this view real nice and all,
but what we doing up here?
What you want to do?
I'd fuck,
but people come up here,
you know?
Yeah, right.
So, are we gonna make this money
or what?
Yeah, let's go do that.
Now, ma'am,
if you don't come pick her up,
she will be placed
in a group home.
Oh, okay, sorry to disturb you.
So what's going to happen
with her?
Well, I just got off the phone
with her grandmother
and she wanted nothing
to do with it, nothing.
So she will be placed
in a group home,
and they'll take it from there.
D, you did the right thing.
You know that, don't you?
I guess.
Well, it's gonna be marked
on your progress report
for next quarter.
So that's huge.
It's gonna help you get through
this parole a lot faster.
Come on now, it's getting late.
Why don't you go see if you can
get a few more of these.
I got to sort this out.
Bye, D.
Come on now, fix your face.
We're gonna find somewhere
for you.
We're sorry, but your call
will now be disconnected.
2-1-5-4...
Man, this nigga, D, fucked me.
After everything I did for him,
he played me like a sucker.
Got my whip towed
and everything.
You believe that, baby?
Man, is this motherfucking trick
coming over here or what?
Yeah, he said
it would be like 50 minutes.
50 minutes?
Bitch, is you stupid?
- Look at you!
- What?
You don't look fucking ready
to me, bitch!
Put your motherfucking face on!
You know what? Fuck you!
Hurry the fuck up, too!
What's good, my nigga?
You all right?
Yeah, everything cool.
You driving that, bro?
Where Candy at?
Shit at the house,
watching music videos,
fucking with her cousins
and shit.
Lazy ass bitches, man.
But I don't know what happened
the other night, man.
I swear, man. That bitch would not
shut the fuck up, man.
What, you believe me, don't you?
You did what you had to do.
You feel me?
You're fucking right I did.
I'll put two holes
in any motherfucker
that say something different.
I'm gonna kill this nigga, Ty.
Something telling me
this nigga in town, man.
I wish his ass was there.
I would've laid his bitch ass
right next to his sister.
If a nigga got to go,
a nigga got to go, period!
Thank you!
Well, it's good.
I'm a holla at niggas though.
Nigga, do you know
how late it is?
Sorry.
For everything.
I never should've hit that lick
with you all that day.
Everything happened so fast
and I got spooked.
I fucked up.
I think about that shit
every day.
Nigga, I did my time.
And the ones that stuck with me,
they stuck with me.
Yeah?
Are they with you right now?
You know, I never was really mad
you drove off on me that day?
At the time, yeah.
I wasn't going to make it up
out of that store.
Not before that old man
had a chance to kill me.
If I would have had this...
... I don't think
I'd be standing here.
For some reason, bruh...
... I thought shit would be different
when I came home.
I feel like
I ain't ever even left.
There's something real fucked up
about that, bruh.
Look, bruh.
You got to get you
the fuck up out of here.
But you can't go anywhere
without any damn money, man.
What the fuck you mean?
I got no one.
No family, no nothing.
I know, but you got me.
I got a plan.
- D, you woke?
- Yeah, I'm just getting changed.
Well, I got some moving boxes
out here.
All right, B.
You know what to do with them,
right?
Yeah, put shit in them.
I'm taking most of your stuff
with me.
You know I paid
for most of that shit anyway.
I'll be gone until tomorrow.
Okay, sounds good.
All right, baby.
Where this bitch ass nigga at?
So you're sure
you wanna go about it this way?
What the fuck you think?
Nigga, you all checked
his pockets, right?
- Right?
- Yeah.
And what he have? Shit!
So what I look like
if I let a nigga rob me
walk the streets
with a heartbeat?
Nigga, this is how the game go.
I'm tired of your ass
questioning every fucking move, man.
Put yourself in my shoes
and man the fuck up!
I can't pull the trigger out
on this one.
Suck ass nigga.
I thought
we was in on this together.
If it's me pulling the trigger,
then it's just me
doing the dirty work,
with two spectators.
Man, I'll do it.
What?
Okay, Maalik really did
put you on, huh?
You ever kill somebody before,
nigga?
I mean, I shot a nigga once.
Hit him,
when he was running though.
He just didn't fall.
All right, so you got a gun?
No...
but I could use yours though.
Grab them gloves.
See that towel?
That's where my banga at.
Be careful, it's loaded.
All right, let's do it.
My nigga, D,
slid through in the clutch!
You said you had big cheese
on a nigga's head.
This bitch ass nigga
owe four racks,
so that's what it pay.
Blood money.
I got ten right here.
But that ain't for you.
I'll pay D
when I see him in the traffic.
Maybe if you would have been
the triggerman,
I'd break your ass off.
Young boy's cut now.
That's respectable.
I'll get the horn then.
Yeah, do something.
- You ready, nigga?
- Yeah, I'm ready.
Just watch out for the ricochet.
Ricochet, huh?
Y'all never said
you was gonna kill him.
Thought it was just a lick.
It was.
More like a murder.
Shit became too personal.
You heard about that boy
who got killed in The Bottoms
the other week?
It was on the news for a minute.
Yeah.
Cuz everybody knows
Cam was gunning for you
when he killed him.
Nigga, don't act like news
don't get around out here.
But that was Cam's
biggest mistake though.
Missing you.
One bullet.
Because you know
who that boy was, right?
Mitchy.
I used to cop from him before
I started selling for Cam.
Yeah, he was from The Rich,
barely came out this way.
You know who got family
in The Rich, right?
It's Lil' Santi.
Shit, I'm at the house
playing a game, man.
Wassup with that shit, man?
What?
I been told my cousin Gina
to tell you, man.
When I saw you at Maxwell's.
But fuck all that shit, man.
Wassup? What you doing later?
Come fuck with a nigga.
Who got the fucked up face now,
bitch?
Now what?
Now we wait.
Why did you do this for me, D?
After everybody else
went bad on me.
Why you?
Cam set you up for failure, bruh.
Shit, everybody knew that.
Me not helping you,
after everything
you been through?
That would have been
too easy for me.
You deserved
a second chance, bruh.
You got that money
for Maalik, right?
Yeah, I've got it.
That should help you out
wherever you end up.
Help with your sister's services
and shit,
and whatever else.
Get low, bruh.
You're sure
this the house, right?
Yeah.
I stayed there for a minute
when I got back.
Wait right here.
Turn the car on though.
All right.
I want you
to make good decisions.
I know you will.
Who is it?
Hello. Is anyone there?
Here's something special.
She was extra special.
You remember me?
Well, I guess
I'll take this thing down.
You sure you wanna keep
renting this house out?
Yeah, I do, B.
All right then,
that's your decision.
We're running late, so I need
to get up to Sacramento.
- We got to sign this lease.
- All right, Mama.
Now you be good to Candy,
you hear?
And tell Little D to call me
and let me know
how his interview went.
All right, you know I will.
- All right. I love you, baby.
- All right.
So what brings you by here?
I seen the sign you had
in the window.
I decided to come in
and apply for the job.
Really now?
Now why in the hell
would I want to hire you?
I grew up around here.
I was raised around stores
like these my whole life.
You know how to work
the cash register?
No, but I can learn.
So you're telling me
you're a fast learner or something?
Yeah.
Well, why didn't you
just say that before?
Look, I can learn
how to operate the register.
I can take instructions,
you know?
Whatever it takes
to make the store run,
I can do that
and make that happen.
Boy, making a lot of money
is just not that important
to me anymore.
But what really is important,
is getting somebody here
I can trust.
And I got to tell you,
I'm going to be frank with you.
I don't like you very much
and I sure as hell
don't trust you.
But you know what?
I might just be willing
to give you a shot, young blood.
Because somebody did it for me,
a long time ago
when I was about your age.
And that somebody was my father.
You now beginning to understand
what we're talking about, boy?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Now do you have an ID on you?
Oh, yeah.
Okay, this looks in order.
I'm gonna have to go next door
and make a copy.
Meanwhile, why don't you start
filling out some of these forms.
So maybe I can pay you someday.
Where are my keys?
Oh, and I believe
this belongs to you.
I'll be right back.