...:::Lord Sadler:::...
lordsadler2012@gmail.com
!Vuela la conga, muchachos!
!Conga! !Conga!
- God!
- So bloated.
- She's bingeing.
- Bingeing? She's fat.
Honey?
Whew! I thought
I lost ya, honey.
- God, I think it's a thyroid problem.
- I think she's just fat.
Oh, yeah.
What's wrong?
What's wrong, honey?
- It's too soon.
- Oh. Oh! Josh, come here!
Hold on, honey. Easy. Easy.
- Brian, what's happening?
- Help!
- I'm only in the first trimester.
Would someone please help?
We have an emergency here. I think--
-Yeah, call the doctor.
-Um, please, could you call Dr Benfante?
- Help.
- Calm down. Now, now.
- Huh?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Help me!
- Help me.
- Over here. One at a time.
Dr Brandon--
- Come on, now!
- Put it over here.
- No, I don't have anything!
- Put it in the tray.
- Honey, it's your tin.
Huh? Oh!
Okay.
- It's okay.
- No smoking in the hospital.
- No, no. No smoking in here.
Put that out.
I'm gonna quit tomorrow.
I swear.
No, no, sideways.
Come through-- Tha-That's it.
- When are you due, ma'am?
- N-Not for another seven months.
- Susan, wh-where's Dr Benfante?
- Brian, come here.
- Just hold my hand.
- There we go.
- The l.V. set?
- Have you had Lamaze?
- Uh, well, I haven't even
signed up for the course yet.
I'm only two months along.
- That's the epidural talking.
- She hasn't had an epidural.
What are you babbling about?
It's-- It's too soon.
- It's too soon, Brian.
- Here he comes.
Okay, guys. Calm down.
- Take it easy.
Calm down, everybody. Calm down.
- And now a deep breath.
It's too early for contractions.
- Hold tight. Hold my hand, honey.
Hold my hand.
- All right.
- Let's just relax.
- That's right.
- Okay. Okay.
- Christ.
- Wait, wait.
- You said, "Come back next week." Huh?
- Yeah.
- You said it was just fluid retention.
"Go home. Have fun."
- Yeah, I'm not having fun.
- Yeah, you gotta breathe.
Sonogram's fine, Doctor,
for a full-term pregnancy.
- Doc, what's going on?
- Okay, it's really important
that you relax and breathe.
- She's fully dilated.
- It's gonna be all right.
- Now you're gonna push.
- Push, okay? Yes.
- No. It's too soon.
- Push hard. Push. Hold it. Hold it.
- Push. Push. Push.
- Good girl.
- Give it all you got.
- No, it's too soon!
- One more time.
- One more deep breath.
- Deep breath in.
- One more. Deep breath.
- And out.
- Push.
Push.
Look at that.
You've got a baby.
It's a beautiful,
beautiful boy.
Hey there, bud.
Hi.
- Don't rust up on me now.
- I'm sorry.
We'll call him Jack.
What you gonna be
when you grow up
What you gonna do
when your time is up
What you gonna say
when things go wrong
What you gonna do
when it's all over
There's a road
Long and windin'
The lights are blindin'
But it gets there
Don't give up
Don't look back
There's a silver linin'
It's out there somewhere
Everybody wants an answer
Everybody needs a friend
We all need a shining star
On which we can depend
So tonight we're gonna wish
Upon a star
We never wished upon before
What you gonna be
when you grow up
- To find what you're lookin' for
- What you gonna do when your time is up
There'll be times
In your life
Yeah, when you'll
be dancing and shit
But you ain't gettin' it
Don't get disillusioned
No, don't expect too much
'Cause if what you have
is all you can get
Just keep on tryin'
It just ain't happened yet
Everybody wants to be a winner
Everybody has a dream
We all need a shining star
When things ain't what they seem
So tonight we're gonna
wish upon a star
We never wished upon before
I'm sorry this
has taken so long.
Like you, we're puzzled
by your son's premature birth.
This is Dr Lin. He's an
infant disorder specialist from Cornell.
I want to assure you both that
there is nothing debilitating
about your son's condition.
He's totally healthy
and normal in appearance...
alert and quite happy.
However, his cells are
developing at what we feel...
is four times the normal rate.
Even though your son was only
ten weeks old when he was born...
physically he was nine months
and ready to leave your womb.
Nature has given us all
an internal clock.
It meters out lifespan,
controls our growth.
Your son's internal clock...
seems to be ticking
faster than usual.
- But he's healthy?
- Absolutely.
I'm sorry.
I still don't understand.
I've never heard
anything like this before.
Well, quite frankly,
neither have we.
There are other aging syndromes
that we know of.
Progeria, for example, which is
very devastating to the child, but--
Jack's cells are replicating
at an unheard of rate.
Is he gonna age like this
the rest of his life?
Well, sir, this is
only speculation...
but, uh, we feel that
at age one...
your son may be physically
around age four.
And if this continues
throughout his life...
by the time he reaches
age ten, well, he could--
Appear to be
an ordinary, full-grown...
40-year-old man.
Are you serious?
That's where he lives, right
down the street my whole life...
and I didn't even know about it.
I don't believe any of it.
He's lying.
Yeah. He's not a monster.
There's no such thing.
I'm telling you.
He's our age, but he looks 40.
All hairy and everything.
He's like a freak or something.
Just like in that one movie.
- Which movie?
- Duh! The one--
- Sorry.
- The one with the freak in it.
What did I just say?
Oh. Oh, yeah, l-l saw that one.
You didn't see it. His mom wouldn't
let him see it 'cause he has nightmares.
- I mean you no harm.
- Why haven't we ever seen him then?
I heard he's got
all kinds of toys too.
His parents buy him everything.
If he's our age,
why ain't he in school?
Because he's dangerous.
He's huge enough to hurt other kids.
That's why they keep him locked up.
Friend.
- What do you see?
- Nothing.
A teacher comes
to his house every day.
Jack, you're not paying attention.
- Jack, you're not paying attention.
- Don't be afraid.
I saw him in the store
with his mom.
I thought it was her husband at first,
but he's like a giant boy.
- He shaves and stuff.
- There's no such thing as giants.
Well, how'd he get like that?
Maybe his mom took drugs.
Maybe it was that fertility junk,
and she was gonna have quintuplets...
but just turned into
one big baby.
- Doof.
- Oh, he sleeps up there.
He's a monstrosity.
That's why they hide him.
No wonder they keep him
outta school.
Maybe they got him chained up.
Maybe they only let him loose
once a day to eat.
Is that like a big pile
of bones in his backyard?
- Where? Uh, what?
l-l don't see anything.
- Look!
Look!
Look out!
Come on, Louis!
- We gotta-- We gotta get outta here!
- Oh, gross!
Come on, Louis!
He's watching you! Come on!
Come on!
Ow. Ow.
- What happened? What'd you do?
Where does it hurt?
- Ow!
- My knee.
- Let me see.
Well, it's not bleeding. Okay.
- It's not?
- I can fix it for you.
- Okay.
- I'll bite it.
- No, no. No, don't bite it.
- Oh, yeah.
- I really do. I have to bite it.
- Don't.
- Yeah?
- It'll get infected.
- Oh, okay.
But this leg has got to come off.
I'll get your father's saw.
No, no. No, no, don't get that.
I saw-- I saw your butt.
- Yeah, you did.
- Sorry.
Let's see.
- What do you hear?
- Nothing. It's okay.
- How about the toes?
- The toes are okay. I can feel that.
- Here?
- I can feel that.
- How about that?
- That's o-- That's--
- Yeah? That's much better?
Oh, go--
- Now--
- That feels good now.
- I told you about those laces, champ.
- Yeah.
- Hmm?
- Okay.
- You did. Sorry.
- So, where were we?
- History.
History. Okay.
So, by the time he was 18...
the young Alexander
had already conquered
most of the Greek city states...
and some feel that
he had learned everything...
from his tutor, Aristotle.
Jack.
- Jack.
- Hmm?
- What did I just say?
- Aristotle.
- Where's Aristotle?
- Book.
- Where's Jack?
- Outside.
I think what you have
set up here is wonderful.
I'm not trying to take
anything away from that.
I know you're not.
But to say that Jack should start
going to public school is crazy.
Yeah, but because
a person is different...
you can't make
an outcast of him.
But we'll talk to the principal.
The principal will prepare
the students.
Mr Woodruff,
he's got a 5:00 shadow.
I don't think he can fit in.
I wish he could.
But nobody said
it would be easy.
Jack's developed defence mechanisms just
like any child with a shortcoming does.
I appreciate what
you're trying to do...
but Brian and l,
we've seen how people react.
We've been through this before.
I just don't want Jack...
to have to face that.
Look at his eyes.
His child's eyes.
Look at his eyes
when he sees other children.
His life moves faster than ours,
and he wants to lead a full life...
and I don't think you
ought to let it pass him by.
It's not fair.
- Marco.
- Polo.
I've found you now.
- Got ya!
- Gotta touch me!
Would you two
knock it off up there!
"You better knock it off up there!"
- Marco.
- Polo.
Gotcha! You're it!
Oh, honey. Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
You know, if something's wrong,
Jackie, you can tell me.
Mr Woodruff mentioned
something today.
What, honey? Huh?
You can tell me.
Mom, am I a giant?
No, of course not!
- Where did you hear that?
- Is that why I don't go to school?
Honey, I've told you.
It's lots of things.
What things?
We'll talk about this, okay?
When?
-Well, not right now. It's time for bed.
-Time for bed.
- Brush your teeth. Put down the lid.
Good night, Mom.
Woodruff doesn't know
what he's talking about.
If he doesn't know what
he's talking about, then why
are we paying him all this money...
to tutor Jack?
I blame him, filling Jack's head
with all these ideas of going to school.
Imagine that.
A teacher wanting a kid
to go to school, hmm?
Where do they get such ideas?
That's how we do it?
Just throw him into school?
- Mm-hmm.
- You know how children are.
They make fun of
the fat kid and...
the kid who wears glasses.
What do you think they're gonna do
to a six-foot, hairy kid?
Mom, Dad.
Jackie? You okay, honey?
- Something wrong?
- Oh, I'm okay.
Just can't sleep.
I had a scary dream.
Can I sleep in here?
Uh, yeah. Of course, buddy.
Stimpy too?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Oh. Hey. Easy.
Okay.
Hey, come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
- Jackie. Go to sleep.
- Okay.
- Good night, Mom.
- Good night, sweetie.
Good night, Dad.
You sure he's ready for school?
Jackie'll be fine.
It's the rest of the world
I'm worried about.
Taking a look at traffic
approaching the Bay Bridge, not too bad.
The metering lights have been
switched on at the toll plaza.
The wait begins right about
the Oakland army base right now.
Marin County is under fog,
but the driving's at the speed limit...
down and across the Golden Gate Bridge
as you make your way into the city.
That's traffic.
Back to you, Rick.
Hey, it's Rick the Lip with you
on the "Z" Morning Zoo.
Another beautiful one out there
in the city by the bay.
And guess what.
We're still here.
How about that little wake-up call
that happened this morning at 5:00?
- Only 3.2 on the Richter scale,
but I tell you what...
- 3.2!
it was a big fat 10
on the scared-the-hell-outta-me scale.
- Didn't scare me!
- This man hasn't shaken
so much since I was single.
Hey, hey, you got someplace
to be at 7:00?
- Yeah, Rick, I gotta be at school!
- You're kidding. You're late.
- 7:05.
- I'm late?
- Get yourself outta bed.
- I'm late, I'm late, I'm late!
- You got a whole day out there
waitin' for ya.
- Go! Yeah!
- I'm livin' it. Let's go!
- I'm livin' it, too, Rick!
- Let's do it, people.
- I'm gettin' to it, Rick!
Misunderstood
Got an--
I hate that song.
- There you go. Easy.
- Dad, let me do this on my own, okay?
- Well, just--
- Watch.
- Okay, okay, okay.
But ta-- Take it easy.
Take it easy.
- And--
- Okay.
- Okay, okay.
- Dad, l-- Dad, Dad.
- Okay. Okay, just--
Okay, hold it. Hold it.
- Let me help you. Oh!
- Ow! Dad!
- Here. Oops. Put this little Kleenex--
- Okay, put that there.
- Ah. Okay.
- Okay. Thank you.
Let me just get
that last little part there.
- Yeah, just finish up...
- Okay.
- and come on down.
- Hurry up.
- You psyched?
- Psyched.
- Okay.
Oh, wow.
Look at all those kids.
- Just remember, you can come
home anytime you want to.
- Uh-huh.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I'm okay. Thanks, Dad.
Hold it, Jack!
Come here. Let me get this.
Okay. Here we go.
- Come on.
- I pledge allegiance to the flag...
of the United States of America.
- And to the republic--
- Welcome, welcome, welcome.
- One nation, under God--
- Thank you, Mr and Mrs Powell and Jack.
Jack, how nice to see you.
I'm Mr McGee.
I've heard so much about you, Jack.
- Hello, Mr Magoo.
- McGee.
- Oh. McGee.
- Yes.
- Magoo.
Jack, how would you like
to see your classroom? Yes?
- Yes.
- A little louder.
- A little louder, Jack.
Yes!
Follow me.
- Is he deaf?
- It's okay.
- Tell me, Jack.
What do you think of it so far?
- Humongous heck-a-cool.
It is "heck-a-cool"
and a wonderful school.
A fun school, an upbeat school.
And I hope you'll have
the time of your life here.
You'll have some wonderful
teachers and wonderful pupils.
- And you're going to be one of them.
- Wow!
Here's your classroom right here.
Miss Marquez.
One second. Honey,
you want to be buttoned up, don't ya?
- Too tight.
- That too tight? All right.
- Okay.
- Don't give me a snuggie.
Mom, don't. That's gross.
You're embarrassing me.
Listen, honey,
if anybody's mean with you...
you just tell your teacher and someone
will call me and, and I'll kill 'em.
- Karen.
- Now are you ready, Jack?
Yes. Um--
Are there any other questions?
Miss Marquez, excuse me, but your new
student, Jack Powell, has just arrived.
Jack, this is Miss Marquez...
your fifth grade teacher.
Come in, please.
Don't be shy.
Come in, Jack. Come in.
Whoa! No way.
- Jeez, he looks like my dad.
- Except hairier.
Come on. It's okay.
Welcome to our class.
I'm glad you're here.
This place is for fun.
Everybody, this is Jack Powell.
Class-- "Hi, Jack."
- Hi, Jack.
- Hi.
Hi.
All right. Uh, I know some of
you must be curious about Jack.
So, why don't we just take
some time right now...
and ask him some of the questions
that you've got on your minds.
- Is that all right with you, Jack?
- Sure.
- Okay.
- I don't mind.
Go on. Ask him something.
- I'm not askin' him.
- Louis?
Anybody?
Come on.
Since when is this group shy?
All right. Fine. I've got plenty of
questions. Jack, when's your birthday?
Mm, September 12th.
1902.
That's enough. Hmm, let me see.
Uh, oh! What kind of foods
do you just hate?
- Broccoli.
- Broccoli, yuck!
- Makes you fart.
Anybody else here hate broccoli?
Hands. Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Well, it looks like you've got
more in common than you think.
Jack, your seat's right there
in the back. Why don't you go
sit down and we'll get started.
- Okay?
- Okay.
All right. Everybody,
take out your giant book--
I mean, your geography book.
Turn to page 78.
Okay. So, what we
found out the other day...
was that the name "California"
was initially used for--
- Everybody, calm down. Come on.
- I think he's stuck.
Was used for what we know today
as Baja California.
It was first used by Cortez
in the 1530s...
and was found in the journal
of Juan Rodriguez Cabrillo in 1542.
Victor, eyes up front!
Everybody! Come on now. Calm down.
Timber!
Jack, are you okay?
- Are you all right, sweetie?
- Oh, man!
Are you sure you
don't need my help?
- You okay, Jack?
- I'm okay.
Jack.
Is he in our class?
Hot, hot, hot. Almost.
Shoot. Ooh-ooh. Ah.
Dog always gets 'em.
Oh, man, he's lookin' at us.
He probably recognizes us
from the street.
He's probably planning on
kicking our butts or something.
- Hey, punk, why don't you watch
where my ball is going?
- You're funny, Victor!
Maybe if you knew
how to play the game.
- What was that?
- You heard me.
You know what the problem is, Victor?
You have "Zackly" disease.
- What's that?
- Yeah, what's that?
It means your mouth smells
"zackly" Iike your butt.
- Oh-ho!
- Shut up! That's pathetic.
- Shut up.
That's so funny
I forgot to laugh.
- Losers say, "What?"
- What?
- Losers!
- Loser!
You think you're so tough?
Take it out on the court,
'cause I can whup your butt.
- Yeah!
- We can do it, man. Let's go.
- Come on, John-John.
- Let's kick their butt! Yeah!
Why does he always have to drag me
along? You know he's gonna cream us.
Ow! Don't!
- Are you a freak?
- No.
Oh. Well, Jane says
that you're a freak.
- Who's Jane?
- I'm Jane, and I think you are a freak.
Look at your hairy arms
and your eyebrows and--
Yeah, he has receding hairline.
Well, I'm not a freak.
Don't, or I'll tell!
- How old are you?
- I'm ten.
- I'm eight.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- So?
- You don't look ten.
Look. You got the hairy arms.
You got hairy knuckles.
You look a lot older than us.
It looks like you shave there.
Yeah, I do. So?
A ten-year-old doesn't shave,
so then you can't be ten.
Yeah, you can't be ten if you
shave and you have hairy arms
and you're tall, really tall...
- For real.
- and you're bigger.
- Yeah.
- So I'm big for my age.
- Look. You have no hair.
- You ha--
- I have hair. I got hair. See? Look.
Yeah, but look. Right here you have
no hair. It looks like you're bald.
I'm not bald, and I'm not a freak.
You're a freak, four eyes.
He's ten, a whole two years
older than us. See?
Oh, sure. Like that
explains it. Please.
"Please."
Don't poke me, or I'm telling.
Over here! Yeah!
- Oh, yeah?
- Losers. Yeah, losers!
Shut up, you brat!
Hey, how about a little help?
- Throw it over.
- Yeah, throw it over.
Wait! I'm not touchin'
that thing.
It's been contaminated
now that he's touched it.
- Yeah, I ain't touchin' it.
- Oh, my God!
- Me neither!
- I ain't-- Uh! I ain't playin'
basketball for a week.
- Me too!
- Five weeks!
- Cooties!
Cooties! Cooties!
Jack? Honey?
I made sloppy joes for dinner.
I'm not hungry, Mom.
- Really juicy ones.
- Yeah?
- You're gonna love it.
- No, I won't.
- Guess what I made for dessert.
- What?
Ya have to guess.
- Can you smell it?
- Not through a box.
Chocolate pudding!
- Your favourite.
- Not any more, Mom.
It's still hot.
Mmm! I can smell it.
It's steaming.
No, thanks.
- This is serious.
- What happened?
What do you think happened?
Children whispering. Children pointing.
- Oh.
- He's not used to that, Brian.
Karen.
Jack?
Hey, your mom made sloppy joes.
Mom hates sloppy joes.
Uh, that's true.
In fact, all adults
hate sloppy joes...
but sometimes we make 'em
to cheer up a kid who's had a bad day.
- You want to tell me about it?
- No.
Okay.
You know what I was
just thinkin' about?
- First time you ever rode
a bike. You remember that?
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah. I mean, you,
you were so determined to ride.
- You kept wipin' out and--
- Yeah.
You nearly took out
a couple of the neighbours.
It took a couple of days
until you finally got it.
But look at you now. I mean, you--
you're, you're riding like a pro.
- Kinda like school, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Well, anyway, I just wanted
to see how you were doin'.
You need anything,
give me a holler.
Hey, Dad, could we
put up a basketball hoop?
Yeah.
All right. Get the ball.
- Hi.
- I'll be back in a second.
Hey in there.
How ya doin', Jack?
Hi, Miss Marquez.
Oh, are those Gummi Bears?
Could I have a red one?
The red ones are my favourite.
Yeah? Oh. Thanks.
So, how do you like it so far?
- Miss Marquez and Jack
- Marquez and Jack
Sittin' in a tree
K-l-S-S-l-N-G
- Girls!
- First comes love, then comes marriage
Jack, if anybody bothers you,
you just come and tell me, okay?
Okay.
Thanks for lunch.
All right.
- Phoebe and Jane.
- I told you.
- It's all your fault.
- Over here right now. Today!
- Come on. We're gonna
go see your teacher.
- She started it.
- Please.
- That was very rude, you know.
Let's kick their butts.
Hey, Louis, you "Iouiser."
To ten.
I'm not in the mood to get
my butt kicked today.
Well, we got the new kid.
What, are you crazy?
Wait. You can't pick him.
He can't play with us.
- Yeah.
- Hey, I can pick whoever I want.
- What? Are you afraid to lose?
- No.
Pick whoever you want.
We never lose.
Yeah, pick whoever you want.
Hey, you! Big guy.
You shoot hoops?
- Me?
- No, the 40-year-old kid behind you.
Yeah, you.
You play ball?
Yeah. With my dad.
- Are you fried?
- Hey, at least nobody's gonna slam him.
- All right, let's do it.
- Losers take out.
- So you take out.
- Yeah!
Yeah, you take out.
- Come on, just one chip.
- No!
- This is gonna be a good game, man.
- Let go, man. Gimme some room.
Wanna grab a burger
after school sometime?
Now, listen. All you gotta do
is just stand by the hoop, okay?
And I'll feed you the ball
like this.
- Let's do this.
- Kick their butts.
- Yeah, kick their butts.
Now, stand under the hoop.
Get your hands up.
Who let Godzilla out?
- And block him.
- I'll try.
- Let's do it.
Oh, boy.
Come on!
Get 'em, Jack!
Yes!
You said stand here.
- Just move your feet.
- Okay, move my feet.
- Pez?
- Sure, thanks.
Stand here and move my feet.
Move my feet.
Come on!
- Jack, get him!
- Yeah!
- Hello, McFly.
- Hello.
- You gotta block him.
- Invincible!
- Yes!
Fake out.
Come on, Jack!
Block him!
- Yea!
- Yes!
- No!
Good work.
- Get him!
- You get him!
- That's right, Mario!
- Give us the ball.
- Losers take out.
Defence! Defence! Defence!
Defence! Defence!
- Defence! Defence! Defence!
- Come on, John-John!
- Catch it! Catch it!
- Put it in the hole, Jack!
- Yeah!
- Like that's real fair.
We're kickin'
some major butt!
- That was good.
- Give me the ball.
Hey! What'd you stick at him?
Loser takes out!
Losers take out!
Give it to Mario!
- Mario!
- Shut up! Shut up!
- Loser!
- Next time.
Shoot it back.
Get it!
- Victor!
- Bouncer.
Unstoppable!
Come on, man. Give it up.
Come on, Victor.
- Give it up!
- Get off me!
Get off of him! Man!
Everybody take out your notebooks.
We have a new assignment.
And it's something I want you to
put some serious thought into.
- I would like you all
to write an essay--
- Oh!
- Mm.
On what you would want to be
when you grow up.
Be sure to include reasons
for your choices...
and watch the spelling,
punctuation and grammar, please.
You'll have till the end
of the semester to finish it.
Write the date on the top
of the page. Don't forget.
- You too, George. The date.
- I want to be a gynaecologist.
If that's so, then I want
good reasons why.
You are the reason why,
Miss Marquez.
I want you to think about this.
It's going to be
a big part of your grade.
Maybe you ought to think about
using one of the choices
from the board. All right?
We're gonna have to change
your name from Jack to Shaq.
Nice shooting. Way to go.
Please, people. Don't leave this
till the last minute.
This the kind of assignment
I want you to spend some time on.
You have the whole semester to do it.
Just take your time.
Don't sit down and write it all
in the last weekend.
- Hey, guys.
- I got the new blueprints
for the new tree house.
- We made it.
- Hey, guys. It's finally Friday.
Who are we waitin' for?
What's her name?
- Mrs Durante.
- Yeah.
Problem is, we don't have
any "Playboys."
- Are you done with it?
- I hear George has a new girlfriend.
- Right over there.
- Hey, guys, I gotta go.
- Glasses.
- Tree house in an hour, all right?
- She's late.
- Yeah.
- We can't stay here all day.
- I think we'd better go back inside.
- We'll go back inside.
Hey. Great game today.
Thanks. Thanks for pickin' me.
Now you gotta do me
another favour.
- What kind of favour?
- Follow me.
Listen, my mother's coming here
to meet the principal today.
- She wants to talk to him.
- So?
- Well, you're gonna be the principal.
- Wh-What?
You gotta do it.
My mom talks to Principal McGee,
he'll tell her I've been bad.
- Well, have you been bad?
- Well, I haven't done homework
since, like, the third grade.
- W-- Your dog must be pretty full.
- Yeah, right.
Here she is.
You gotta do it. Here.
- Louie, I can't be a principal.
- Turn around.
- I can't do this.
- Turn around!
Principal McGee's really old!
- I can't do this.
- Louie!
- It's a fib.
Oh, hi, honey.
Oh, sweetie, The Beef and Brew
only gave me 10 minutes off.
So I gotta hustle.
Hi, sweetie.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- So, where's the principal?
- Um--
This is Principal Powell.
He's new here.
- Oh.
- He just came a couple of weeks ago.
- I told him you were coming.
- Oh, well, hello, Mr Powell.
My name is Delores,
but my friends call me D.D.
So tell me, what happened
to Principal McGee?
I just talked to him on the phone.
I don't know what happened
to Mr McGee. Mr Powell?
- He got diarrhoea.
- Diarrhoea?
Yeah, he got diarrhoea.
Uh, and he-- he spewed.
Threw up. Yeah, he had--
And, uh, he had the squirts.
- He had diarrhoea.
- Oh, boy, that's more
than I needed to know.
- He-He had to go to the hospital.
Appendicitis.
- Yeah.
- He had a bellyache.
- Oh, my God, appendicitis.
Oh, that's too bad.
Well, honey, listen. I swiped you
a chocolate mousse from the restaurant.
So go sit down and eat it
while I talk to the principal.
- No, let me stay, Mom.
- Oh, sweetie, please don't
bust my chops over everything.
Go sit down. Oh, God, you see?
That's what I'm talking about.
He-- He doesn't listen. I mean, I don't
know whether it's all kids or just him.
- Am I right?
- What'd you say?
I said kids don't listen.
Am I right?
- Don't listen. No.
- Yeah. Well, that's what I thought.
Of course, you could say
the same thing about men too.
- Probably your wife does all the time.
- Oh, no.
- Aren't you married?
- Married?
- No, I'm not married.
- I'm divorced, myself.
And that's another thing, you know.
Ever since my husband left us...
he's got such
a chip on his shoulder.
Potato or corn?
Anyway, uh, you know.
He's-- He's starting
to get interested in girls.
I found some dirty magazines
under his bed.
Wh-What am I supposed to do about that?
What? l-l don't know what to do.
Uh, it's a tough age.
I know. I mean,
l-l-l-- I remember.
I mean, I re--
I'm remembering now.
- It's a tough age.
- Uch!
- Rough, tough age.
- Feh.
So, tell me, meanwhile,
how is he doin'?
'Cause last September
he was failing out miserably.
Oh, um, Louie's showing
a lot of improvement.
- He's on a roll, really.
- Really?
- Rolling.
- A roll?
- Really.
- Rolling along.
- Really, really rolling along.
- Wow.
And, uh, I would say,
uh, he's, uh...
the smartest kid
in the whole school.
Yeah. If not, maybe
the smartest kid I've ever met.
Oh, my God! I can't believe
I'm finally getting a good report.
It makes me so happy.
I mean, I can't believe
you're telling me this.
'Cause you know, this means
that maybe he's happy...
and I made the right decision
about moving us out here.
Listen, you know...
if you want to have
lunch or something...
we can talk about Louie and, you know,
just kind of shoot the breeze.
- What do you think?
- Don't.
- Oh.
- Got a problem?
- It's bad for you.
Since when is bein' bad...
bad?
Oh, no.
Oh, here she goes.
So, um, what do you think?
Do you wanna do lunch?
I get a discount
at the Beef and Brew.
Well, my mom brings my lunch usually.
I mean, she makes it.
Honey, you've got to cut
those apron strings.
- Hi, sweetie.
- Hi.
Hi, angel. Well, Mr Powell's been
telling me what a good boy you've been.
-I told you.
-And I didn't believe you, but now I do.
And I'm gonna give Mr Powell
my number at work...
so that you can call me
and let me know how he's doing.
Can stay on top of things.
That's my number at work.
You can get me there anytime.
Well, my mom said
I shouldn't touch matches.
Oh, you live with your mother?
- Well, yeah, at night.
- Well, to each his own.
- Yeah.
Anyway, you can call me, uh,
to talk about Louis...
or, you know, any old thing.
So, uh-- Oh, and that's Memories.
That's a club that
I hang out at sometimes.
You know, if I'm not at work,
that's usually where I am.
But it's a nice place
for people our age to hang out...
have a little drink,
take the edge off, you know.
Oh, I gotta go.
Ooh, I'm gonna get fired.
- Love you, "face."
- Okay, love you too.
- Nice meeting you, Mr Powell.
Ooh, you got a strong grip.
You're a manly man.
All right, you got your key to
the house? Okay, I'll meet you at home.
- I love you.
- All right. Love you too.
Bye.
...:::Lord Sadler:::...
lordsadler2012@gmail.com
Wow! Whoa, that was great.
- How'd I do?
- You did great.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Boy.
- Whew!
- Hey, man. I owe you one.
Sorry about my mom, Jack. She's lookin'
for love in all the wrong places.
Yeah, I know.
Maybe I'll see you
over the weekend.
Cool.
- Pal.
- Thanks.
Mom! I'm home!
I'm here. I'm here!
Where are you?
Yeah. Okay.
- Phone call for you, Brian.
- Yeah, just--
- Okay?
- Okay. Yeah?
- Can I talk to him? Can I talk to him?
- Jackie wants to talk to you.
Dad! Hey, Dad. Dad.
I got your hair, Mom. Sorry.
Hey, Dad. Yeah. Hey, Dad.
I got to play basketball today.
They picked me. Yeah, and not
just 'cause I'm humongous.
Because I'm real good. Yeah,
I scored a thousand points.
No. You're right.
It was only a hundred.
I'm kidding. It was 14.
Yeah, but each time I got the--
I scored! Just like this.
Wait! Listen, Dad.
Yeah, and I met this
really cool kid named Louie.
Not Louis. Louie. Yeah.
His mom gave me some matches.
Yeah. Those are the matches.
Can I play with them?
Okay, slow down, buddy.
Slow down.
Hey, Dad.
Louie has dirty magazines
under his bed.
What are dirty magazines?
I got to be principal.
Yeah, I pretended to be.
And I got a lot of homework to do.
I got a great homework assignment.
And you know what? Miss Marquez
ate one of my red Gummi Bears.
She said, "Way to go." Yeah,
but not because of the red Gummi Bears.
Because of the way
I played basketball.
Yeah, it was great.
She said Shaq better watch his back.
She's what Grandpa says
is a real piece of work.
Really great.
What are you doing?
No, I'm just-- Just, uh,
shootin' an ad layout.
Carrots, for the Carrot Board.
Just giant carrots, yeah.
Wow, that's pretty boring.
Listen, Dad.
I gotta go.
No, I really gotta go.
Number one.
Okay. See you.
Yeah, listen, Dad?
Don't hug me any more
in front of the guys, okay?
Yeah, you know.
It's like-- You know.
It's weird. Yeah, okay.
See ya. Yeah, I'll take
the matches in the bathroom
so if I do number two, I'm ready.
Okay, put your mom on. Yeah.
Brian. Yeah, I can
hear you all right.
No, it's this cord. Oh, wait!
You okay?
- Honey!
- Is he okay?
Yes, he's all right.
He's so excited.
Hey, Jack's mother!
- Hey, Jack!
- Psych!