[Phone ringing]
RICHIE (ON PHONE): Hello?
JOEY (ON PHONE): Hoo!
Hey, Richie!
Yoohoo!
I'm getting married!
RICHIE (ON PHONE): Is this Joey?
JOEY (ON PHONE): Liz and
I are tying the knot.
Everyone's coming back
into town for a huge bash.
RICHIE (ON PHONE): It's
4:00 in the morning
And you're calling
about a goddamn wedding?
Yeah.
I'm telling you, buddy,
it's gonna be great.
Yeah.
Liz is gonna
decorate the garage.
We're gonna have everything...
Kegs, booze, hot dogs.
RICHIE (ON PHONE):
Big get together, huh?
Yeah, party's Saturday night.
I expect everyone to have
a hangover for the wedding,
You got it?
RICHIE (ON PHONE):
I can't believe
You're gonna marry that broad.
Yeah, she finally broke me.
But hell, after six
years of going out,
You kind of run out of excuses.
RICHIE (ON PHONE): Joey, I gotta
get up for work in two hours.
Listen, I gotta go, OK?
RICHIE (ON PHONE): Good night.
Yeah, it's gonna be great to
see you and the whole gang.
All right?
RICHIE (ON PHONE): Bye.
OK, bye.
[Inaudible] Lola.
I gotta tell you.
You and your girls have done
a hell of a job tonight, man.
Really.
You've really
outdone yourselves.
I wanted your last night
to be very special with us.
Yes, you've been a
loyal customer, Joe.
You have been so
loyal that we are
Going to put you in our hall
of fame scrapbook, Joey.
Pictures?
Cool!
I've come to bury
Caesar, not to praise him.
Friends, Romans, countrymen,
lend me your ears.
The evil that men
do lives after them.
The good is often
interred with their bones.
So let it be with Caesar...
[Barking]
What did he do?
Knock you up or something?
Shut up, Carol.
Will you look at
the size of it?
How'd Joey pay for that?
Oh, he put it on
Mom's credit card.
Top line cubic zirconium.
What's that freak doing here?
She comes in here every day.
Hi.
Can I help you?
Um, yes.
I... I'd like to see the, um...
The ring?
The, um... yes.
Sure.
Are you actually
going to buy it today?
Or do you just wanna look it?
I just wanna look at it.
Thank you.
Eww.
Next time, try washing
your hands, you
Little piece of trash.
Hey.
I'm sorry, honey.
I didn't mean you.
Yeah, whatever.
Hey.
Can I have 50 bucks?
Hi.
Mr. Thatcher's math class.
You were in the first row.
Cassandra.
Cassandra Heimlich?
Holmbeck.
You used to be so smart.
You used to be different.
Want a chocolate?
Oh god.
Mother of baby Jesus!
Do you hear that?
I'm sorry, Daddy.
Do you?
That's what I found the
radio tuned to this morning.
Now get in the car!
And take off those
ridiculous stockings.
God be with you.
You're going home
to pray, young lady.
No, Daddy.
I'll teach you the
meaning of discipline.
But I was only talking.
LUTHER: Talking
leads to touching.
And touching leads to doing.
Hi, Joanie.
And here are your films.
You're welcome.
[Singing]
No!
You know, this
is gonna be great.
You know, just getting out
of the city for a while,
Spending a nice,
relaxing weekend
In the sleepy little
hamlet where I grew up.
Still can't believe they
gave you the weekend off.
Only been working here
for a couple of days.
Let's just not
talk about that, OK?
I can't believe
I'm hearing this.
You're not.
I
I can't believe you
lost another job.
Do you know how much you
owe me in back rent alone?
Oh come on, for Christ's sakes.
No, it was a stupid video store!
No!
I have too much
education for that.
Besides, they had a
lousy foreign section.
Oh god.
What?
All right.
How much is it?
[Horn beeping]
Listen, Liz.
We're gonna split now.
Yeah.
Ah, and speaking of split,
don't forget about the league
Tonight.
Mark's picking us up at 8:00.
Bowling tonight?
I thought you were gonna be
with me when the guests arrive.
I'll give you a call later.
Listen, tiger, I got work to do.
Come on.
How about a little,
uh, afternoon delight?
No, Sloppy.
Someone's gotta start
paying for that honeymoon.
Oh, come on.
Haven't had my recommended daily
allowance of, uh, Vitamin F.
Here, but promise me
no more bets, Joey.
And don't forget to
clean up the kitchen
Before the guests arrive.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh my goodness, baby.
Look what you've done to her!
Ow!
Damn it.
Mom, what is it?
Hey.
Can you tell me where I
can get a beaver license?
I said, can you tell me where
I can get a beaver license?
I hear there's good
to beaver hunting
Up near where the river meets
Trogsden, Trogsden High School.
Are you gonna just sit
there all day or what?
Yeah, sorry.
My trunk release is broken.
You know how it is.
Whoops.
Sorry about that.
Come on, buddy.
Get the lead out.
Come on.
Let's go!
Just try to have
a good time, OK?
Sure.
Please?
Oh, come on.
Look.
Have a little more consideration
for my stuff, all right?
Is that too much to ask?
Damn it.
Stop complaining
just for one minute.
I don't care.
Look.
Just for one weekend.
Oh my god.
Look at this.
Great.
What?
Please, just for me... hah-hah!
Sloppy Joe!
Man.
How you doing?
Great.
Couldn't be better.
Looking good.
Oh, this must be
your better half.
We're... we're just friends.
Oh, come on, honey.
She's just kidding.
We've had sex many times.
I'm glad.
So, tell me, Goon.
What you better
up to, old buddy?
Huh?
Nothing, huh?
That's great.
Real proud of you.
Where is everybody, man?
I thought everybody would
be rocking here by now.
Well, Stumpy should
be here any minute.
Grease got here this morning.
I sent him to pick up
Goon at the bus stop.
Wait, wait, wait.
Ted is here?
I thought Ted was
killed in South America.
No, he was just
missing for a while.
Great.
So come on, man.
How's New York?
You still writing poems?
No way.
Poetry's dead.
Yeah?
I'm working on a pretty
major novel, actually.
Cool title... Days of
Blood, Nights of Sin.
I love it, man.
Got a lot of violence,
lot of sex in there?
No.
No, actually.
Well, you know what?
I better get on KP before
little Dink gets home.
If I know her, she'll
have a goddamn cow
If she sees all of this.
[Horn beeping]
Speak of the devil.
Get the bastard, Liz.
Get him!
Liz, baby, take it
easy on those tires.
Uh, Cliff's here.
Remember him?
How you doing, Liz?
Good to see you.
You cocksucker.
You motherfucking cocksucker!
Liz, stop her!
A whorehouse?
A whorehouse and
you have my Liz?
I'll kick you in the balls.
Kick him in the johnson, honey.
Kick him in the johnson.
Asshole!
MOTHER: Did you kick
him in the johnson, Liz?
I told you to kick
him in the johnson.
LIZ: Mother, shut
up and move over!
MOTHER: I told you to
kick him in the johnson!
[Car drives off]
What is it?
Que pasa, amigos?
Shit.
[Vomiting]
Well, looks like
the shitkickers
Have finally arrived.
Goddamn.
What's shaking, bacon?
You feel all right, man?
Dude, you want some painkillers?
Oh my god.
Is that Stumpy?
I don't believe it.
She got thin.
Hi, everybody!
I just can't believe
this, Emmett.
I mean, this document's
such a betrayal of trust.
Is she reading Shakespeare?
Uh, excuse me.
Does anybody know
where the bathroom is?
Uh, sure.
It's, uh, back down the
hall, past the kitchen
And to your right.
Be careful though.
The first flush doesn't
always clear the bowl.
Oh my god!
Gross!
No, no, no, no, no.
That was not part of
our arrangement, man!
Well, you gotta be shitting me.
Come on!
You listen to me, hombre.
I almost had my ass blown
off down there, man.
We had a deal, goddamn it!
MAN (ON PHONE):
[speaking spanish]
No, no, no.
Never mind where I am.
OK, man?
I'll get you the shit.
You just keep up your
end of the bargain, OK?
Pal?
MAN (ON PHONE):
[speaking spanish]
What?
MAN (ON PHONE):
[speaking spanish]
Oh, come on.
Fuck that!
Hello?
Fuck.
[Knocking on door]
Hey, you planning on
finishing any time this year?
Just a minute!
I mean, the twists and
turns have been stressful.
But I'm a step away
from becoming an editor.
Oh, and I feel so good.
I feel so damn healthy and
psychically aware, you know?
Well, that sounds very nice.
[Flushing]
Everything come out all right?
Gee, I guess it does
take more than one flush.
Whoa, whoa!
The lady's got some fire.
Ouch!
Woo.
Comic coming through.
We got a comedian in the house!
Smartass.
Well, what are you
doing with yourself?
Um, I inspect things.
Such as?
Um, doors, um,
windows, vinyl siding.
Um...
Well, well, well.
Aren't we the domesticated type.
I live in the city, Ted.
It pays to keep
the kitchen clean.
Oh yeah?
Well, why don't I
give you a hand there?
I'll rinse.
Why don't you dry?
Figure I can handle that.
Grow up, will you?
So why do they call you Grease?
I dunno.
Just a crazy nickname, I guess.
So you're good
friends with Joey?
Yeah, so?
So how could he do
something like two days
Before his own wedding?
Well, Paula, when you've
been together with someone
As long as Joey and Liz have,
you're out there working
Like a dog every day,
reading of all the things
You've read about the
night before in "Hustler"
And "Penthouse Forum,"
it's kinda hard
Not to thirst for
the type of freedom
That irresponsible
behavior can bring.
It's no reason to go out and
penetrate a pair of whores.
You know you're
absolutely right.
I mean, you can't blame it all
on cable TV and pornography,
Now can we?
I mean, what modern society just
doesn't want to admit, Paula,
Is that deep down inside,
we're all still animals.
And the male is, by
nature, a polygamist beast.
Ask any anthropologist
and he'll tell you.
You are really warped.
So tell me.
Is, uh, Scoop still hung
like a baby or what?
Well, we're back.
Hey, hey.
Scoop, we were just
talking about you.
So you've already made
yourself at home, Felix.
Just trying to help
Sloppy Joe out, you know?
The guy's got a lot on his
mind, if you haven't noticed.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, you know, we had a real
heart-to-heart talk out there.
I think I got him coming around.
Is that right?
Yeah.
[Barking]
Listen up!
I've got something to say.
Fact... many were called here
for this weekend of festivities
And few were wise enough
to make the journey!
Hey, I wouldn't miss it
for the world, Sloppy.
He's drunk.
In fact, I do not intend to
let some stupid little fight
Break our chances of enjoying
our few precious drops
Of freedom!
[Barking]
I want my socks.
I want my favorite
bowling socks.
[Interposing voices]
They're ruined!
Liz, come on.
We all think it's
really brave of you
To try and forget
about Joey tonight,
But maybe you should stay home.
Yeah, skip the
lanes tonight, Liz.
You don't need
the stress, honey.
That's right, Joanie.
Stay home, darling.
Stay home.
That's right.
I am going bowling and
nobody's gonna stop me!
No, darling.
Stay home and play
Scrabble with Mommy, huh?
Woo!
I'm gonna hit the town, baby.
Party, party,
party, party, party!
Hey, look.
It's lovable old Mr. Holmdick.
It's Mr. Holmbeck.
He was our assistant
principal in grade school.
And before that, he
used to be a priest.
Hey, Holmdick.
It's a little early for you
to be out of your cloister,
Ain't it?
Leave him alone.
He's an old man.
Fella used to get off
on beating kids' butts.
Should be arrested!
Hey, Commandant, where's
your freaky-ass daughter?
Pulling tricks at
the local graveyard?
I remember you, Theodore.
I never forget a face, you know.
Oh yeah?
Really?
Well, how about this?
Remember this face,
you sick fuck?
Huh?
Remember this?
And to think how I tried to
help you, Theodore, all of you,
In fact.
I tried to give you discipline!
[Inaudible]
You're nothing but
a bunch of deviants!
So Luther gets kicked
out of the church
And has to marry
this woman, right?
And then there's his daughter.
Oh, that's freak
Cassandra, man.
No, OK.
So anyway, the woman
dies, all right.
Oh no, man.
I heard her killed her, man.
He drowned her in a
bathful of holy water.
Oh, Ted, that's ridiculous.
At any rate, he
becomes a principal.
Oh, and the paddling
rate only went up
About 800 fucking percent.
Hey, man.
Let's go there.
Yes!
ANNOUNCER: Freddie's
Bowl-a-rama would
Also like to welcome
the Rico Spring
School of Special Education.
That's right.
Bowling is for everyone, folks.
Hey, you know what?
You losers have a good time.
Margaret and I are
gonna talk business, OK?
Cliff, Cliff!
Hey, where you going?
Come on.
You ready to bowl?
I... I don't bowl.
You go ahead.
Oh, come on.
It's easy.
I'll teach you.
Come on.
Let's go.
ANNOUNCER: We'd like to wish
the special kids a very special
Time tonight here on our lanes.
Fun is the name of
the game, everybody.
Relax and enjoy.
Oh rats!
Oh, we worked all
season to get here!
ANNOUNCER: Remember to confine
all drinking to the bar area
Only.
Margaret, Margaret,
you look great.
Thanks.
Well, I'm probably a lot thinner
than what you remember, huh?
[Inaudible] So,
Margaret, Goon tells me
You're in the publishing biz.
Can you imagine the
nerve of that woman?
Yeah!
Coming out here to bowl
after the way she treated you?
Come on, Liz!
[Interposing voices]
The characters and
chapters, they... they
Randomly change throughout.
I came up with this
after a particularly
Heroic dose of mescaline.
It's... it's a bit difficult
to take it all in right now.
Maybe you should take
off your sunglasses.
Oh, no.
I can't.
It's really bright in here.
What are you talking about?
All right!
All right.
Looking good, baby.
Looking good.
Next time I've
got a team record.
Team record!
ANNOUNCER: There is no
nudity allowed in the lanes.
Please respect the rights of
families to relax and enjoy.
Oh goodie!
He knows how much
bowling means to me.
He's Satan, honey.
I have something that
I wanna share with you.
But you have to promise
to keep it a secret.
Uh-huh.
Uh, why don't I guide you
through the first roll.
That's OK.
I got it.
No, no, no.
Really.
Trust me.
I... I'm a very good bowler.
Just a little.
All right.
What you want to do is aim for
that center [inaudible] OK.
Pull back.
Snap.
OK.
Um.
That was great.
I'm gonna go see
what Cliff is doing.
All right.
That's good.
Good.
You do that.
ANNOUNCER: Gentlemen
in lane 4, please
Refrain from spitting tobacco.
Tobacco products
are not allowed.
How long have you been
having these dreams?
Almost a year now.
And... and you're always on
this empty road, and... and you
Encounter this bright light.
And then everything goes black.
And then you wake up hours
later, nude, along the highway.
That's just the beginning.
Under regressive hypnosis, I was
able to visualize experiments
That they performed
on me and given
Details of the big secret.
The big secret?
They told me to leave medical
school and go into publishing.
So I did.
Oh.
And that's the big secret.
Well, they haven't revealed
all the details yet.
But I feel like I'm
a channeler of sorts.
They wanna write
a book through me.
Cliff!
I've been looking for you.
Really?
Hi.
Whoa!
Yeah, buddy.
[Inaudible]
Hear, dear.
Why don't you take Mark's turn.
No thanks, Carol.
I don't need your charity.
Mark, wait!
What now?
Oh, that's it!
Hey, asshole!
[Interposing voices]
Thanks a lot, Liz.
She attacked me, Joey.
I swear.
I had nothing to do with it.
No, get out of my way.
I just know Joe's gonna kill me.
Excuse me, sir, but we're
in the middle of game.
Could you come back at
a more convenient time?
Like never?
Goddamn it, Liz.
How can you do that?
Huh?
How can you kiss him like that?
In front of everybody?
Out of my way!
Liz, you didn't even give
me a chance to explain.
You marched up to the house
like some sort of crackpot.
And before I could
get a word out,
Your mother was beating
the shit out of me!
Get the hell out
of the way, Joey!
Goddamn it!
You can't do this to me!
People respect me in this town.
[Laughter]
ANNOUNCER: We request
that bowlers please return
To their respective lanes.
Management is on the way.
Liz, spot the violence!
You have to
communicate with him.
Tell him how you feel!
Stay out of this, you bitch!
My mother was right about you.
You're a cheating,
lying bastard!
Why don't you admit it?
I wanna hear you admit it!
Admit what?
You're not even sorry, are you?
You never are!
You're always right
and I'm always wrong!
I'm sick of it, Joey.
I'm sick of it!
What the hell are
you talking about?
I can't live with
someone who doesn't pay
Attention to me when I talk!
I listen to you rambling
about car engines, and racing,
And that stupid airplane.
Oh, for Christ's sakes!
Shut up, Joey!
Because it's not a lot to want
someone who can save his money
Instead of borrowing mine!
Yeah!
Someone who can listen
to my family problems
And not complain every
time I gain a few pounds!
Someone who isn't
too tired at the end
Of the day to sweep me
off my goddamned feet!
Fine!
You want blood, huh?
Is that what you want?
Well, here you go, baby.
Come on!
Lay one right and
knock me on my ass!
[Cheering]
Come on, baby.
[Interposing voices]
Oh yeah.
That'll kill the tapeworm.
Come on, Goon.
I'm whooping your ass here.
Come on.
Drink up.
Could you not do that, please?
I'm trying to enjoy the music.
Yeah, whatever.
Hey, bartender, another
round on me, huh?
Thanks, Grease.
Hey, know what?
I was gonna jump in
and help you back
There at the boiling alley,
but I lost my manuscript.
And...
Well, well, well, if it isn't
Daddy's little pride and joy.
Hi, Cassandra.
How you doing?
My, you certainly have changed.
So I don't see the
old man around.
What's the good
reverend up to now?
Smacking a few butt cheeks, hmm?
Saving a few souls?
Hey, Grease, do you
want another beer?
So you seem kind of
nervous, Cassandra.
Do I make you nervous?
Are you afraid I
might spank you, hmm?
Come on, Cassandra.
Daddy's gonna have to
teach you some manners.
spank your butt good!
[Laughter]
What'd she ever do to you?
That's totally
uncalled for, Ted.
God, that is one
fucked up family.
Cassandra?
Cassan...
[Vomiting]
[Inaudible]
Listen, I'm gonna say it again
and I'm gonna say it slow.
OK?
You need new pussy.
No, I don't wanna go back
to fucking Lolas, Grease.
That's how this
whole thing started.
I'm not talking
about that crap.
Though that's a damn good idea.
What I'm talking about
is virtual titty.
Oh no.
You're sick.
See, it it's hard
driving interactive porno.
OK?
I'm gonna sell it
to all the perverts
Out there who are tired of
spanking their franklins
And just watching
the shit happen.
You know know what I mean?
And like I should
talk, you know?
You know, it's
such a pipe dream.
Now, if you just look at
this, this one part, I think...
Cliff, shut up.
Ted is talking.
So what's the big
deal about this thing?
Well, let me tell
you what I'm gonna do.
Seem I'm gonna videotape
couples indulging
In various full fledged
pornographic acts, right?
OK?
Oh, Ted.
Is this your big dream in life?
It's no dream, my dear.
OK?
The great thing is, the
best part about this,
Is you get to choose, right?
OK?
You don't wanna bang this broad?
Boom.
You go back to the
main menu and you
Select another one... French
Maid, a Nurse, a Nun...
You know, whatever you want.
You mean, you actually get to
hump the girls in the video?
Aw, what bullshit!
Could this work for
women too, Grease?
Actually, yeah.
I'm patenting a
latex masturbatory
Device for both sexes, right?
With thousands of
ultra-tiny electrodes, OK?
Thousands of them per
square inch, right?
These little vibrators
can instantaneously
Receive and transmit
the implication
Of what they call tactile
presence, if you get my drift?
Sounds good.
OK, now why don't you just
look at this part right here?
Cliff, will you stop it?
I can't read 300 pages of...
Of... of typos those in a bar.
Oh yeah?
Well, you do it
for those aliens.
I bet you do it for
those fucking aliens
And read their books!
You gave me your word.
I think I have to get
out of here before...
Oh yeah.
Smooth move, Scoop.
Very smooth.
You just don't get it, do you?
You are so self-absorbed.
So you have no idea what a
stupid pseudo-intellectual you
Come off as.
Yeah, you have been laying
it on kind of thick, Scoop.
Oh, shut up, Grease.
Who asked you?
Did you know Cliff
can't hold a job for more
Than two weeks, Grease?
That I have been paying the
rent for the last seven months?
Every morning I wake up to
slave away in Manhattan,
And old Cliff is blissfully
sleeping off last night's
Heavy duty writing session.
[Inaudible] just
happen, you know?
OK?
You can't just spit it out
of a computer terminal!
No, just out of trendy cafes
and half empty vodka bottles.
Right, Cliff?
Agh!
GREASE: Whoa, score a few
points for Paula there.
Butt out, Grease!
Gimme the keys.
I'm going with Mark.
Oh.
The key.
OK. Well, here.
Give me the keys, Cliff.
No.
Gimme the keys!
Give me my fucking keys!
Was he like this in high school?
All the time, honey.
Just suck a dick then!
You asshole!
Gimme the keys!
You [inaudible] bitch!
Gimme the key!
You can just peddle
your ass home OK?
You want me to be
creative, Cliff?
Huh?
You give me those goddamn
keys, or I'll give
You something to write about.
I'll find a creative way to
make you a soprano, you pussy.
Give me the keys.
If you want a ride, be
outside in five minutes.
Don't do me any favors, OK?
Yeah, I'm kinda bushed.
Think I'm gonna head
on home, Sloppy.
You coming?
Think, uh, Cliff and I could,
uh, close this joint up?
Sure.
OK, man.
Be careful.
Oh, honey.
You're getting puke on yourself.
Here, come on.
Man, I got a lotta calls
to make tomorrow morning.
Call all the relatives.
Tell 'em the wedding's off.
Listen, can we just
stop talking about
The stupid wedding already?
Big deal!
Right?
I mean, so what?
So Uncle So and So and
Auntie This and That
Can't take pictures and
get drunk at the wedding?
Oh, the world's
gonna stop revolving!
Perhaps you're right.
So, um, what's up with
you and Paula, huh?
Oh please.
You two ever think about, uh...
[Whistling]
Oh yeah.
Right.
Oh, that emotional vampire.
I can't... that is the
one reason I can't get
Any of my work published.
She's just a... shit!
You know, It's not easy pouring
your soul into something
When she's in the
background complaining
About the freaking phone bill!
You know what, Scoop?
Kind of admire you a little bit.
Why?
Oh, because I'm a writer.
No, because you, uh, got
out of this dump, you know?
You made something of yourself.
Shit.
Vodka.
Yes, ma'am.
Rocks.
Twist.
Yes, yes, ma'am.
Who the hell's that?
Lola.
Oh my god.
Is that Ted?
He looks so young.
Oh, and that's you.
You had such pretty eyes.
Oh, and there's Cliff
before he moved away.
You know, I'm sorry
about tonight, Paula.
I feel like it was all my fault.
Oh no.
No, it was nobody's
fault but his own.
He's a total baby.
Before he moved in with me, I
used to listen to his drunken
Soliloquies for hours.
I actually thought he was deep.
Yeah, it's odd.
I used to think that Cliff
was so aware in high school,
So open-minded, always
listening to Ornette Coleman,
You know, quoting William Blake.
[Laughter]
Did he try to hit
on you tonight?
Well, um, I think he really
just wants to get published.
Ladies.
Coming for you, man.
She's got your number.
So, Joey, I've heard some very
sad news about your wedding,
Ja?
Well, your pictures didn't
help matters very much.
That is the least of
my concerns now, Joey.
Hi, Lola.
What is it?
I call it. Uh, Cosmic Grease.
It's a mystical
lubricant I concocted
Three years ago
while playing tennis
With some businessmen in Japan.
Oh lord.
I have to go to bed.
OK.
Whatever.
Mmm.
It's really good.
Mhm.
What's in it?
Lola, I'm very tired.
Believe me, I've
had a very long day.
We're going straight home.
We're closing up, people.
[Whiplash]
Lola's very tired too, Joey.
Tired of bounced checks
and bad credit cards, yeah?
Well, about that, I mean, I
was gonna go to the bank, see
You in the morning and... I go...
You owe me money, Joey.
Lots of money.
And I want it by tomorrow, ja?
Entschuldigung, Joey.
Aren't you having any?
Well, I got my own poison.
Drink up.
It's good.
So tell me, Grease,
about all these nicknames.
I mean, like, Goon, Sloppy
Joe, I feel like I'm dealing
With the mob or something.
But, like Cliff, how
did he get his nickname?
Well, Cliff probably thinks he
got his nickname 'cause he used
To work for the school paper.
But I actually call him Scoop
because he used to scoop
Girls' asses in school.
What?
Scooping girls' asses?
What's that?
You never heard of scooping?
No.
- Get out.
- No.
What is it?
I'll show you.
Come here.
What?
Turn around.
What is it?
This is scooping.
Hey!
Let me go.
Make me.
And Goon?
How'd that come about?
Well, he just looks like goon.
What about Margaret?
Well, she used to be
fat, really, really fat.
You know, short and
squatty, like a tree stump.
And Grease?
Because of my Machiavellian
schemes, I guess.
Am I one of your
Machiavellian schemes?
Maybe.
Is that wrong?
Oh god.
Oh my god.
It's all right.
It's just a scratch.
But it's bleeding.
It's bleeding all over.
You... it's... Ted,
go take care of it.
And I'll get...
All right.
Now get comfortable.
Don't go away.
I'll be right back.
OK.
Grease is all fixed up now.
Mmm.
Shit.
I knew I put too much in.
Damn it.
Hey, man.
Hey, remember me?
[Inaudible] I
delivered something
To you about six months ago.
Yeah.
Yeah, I did [inaudible]
a product for Alejandro.
Remember him?
Yeah.
Yeah, well, listen.
I got some new stuff for you.
I'm totally my own
shop and everything,
And I got some good product.
What are you talking about?
No.
He's not after me, man.
No, the shit is not hot, man.
This stuff is my own
primo stuff, man.
Very good product.
I... No.
Roberto, he couldn't...
He couldn't fucking
Find his dick if it was
glued to his hand, man.
Come on.
He's not gonna find me.
Oh yeah?
All right.
Thanks.
What the hell's she doing?
Sleeping, I guess.
Is just me, or has she
gotten really weird?
Jesus.
Are you nuts?
Sorry, man.
Sorry?
What the hell are you
doing with a gun anyway?
Maybe I'm just happy
to see you, Cliff.
Oh yeah.
That's funny.
Funny!
It's real funny!
Look, there's nothing wrong
with being a little cautious,
You know?
Guys, has anyone
seen my glasses?
It's rather important.
Weren't they on your face?
Hey, has anyone seen Goon?
I thought he came
home with you guys.
I dunno.
[Snoring]
Uh, where... where am I?
I brought you home.
You were really drunk.
Oh, I... I see.
Uh... my clothes?
They're in the sink downstairs.
You puked all over them.
Oh.
Well, thank you.
So why are you...
Well, you puked
on my clothes too.
Oh.
I... I'm sorry.
Um, I was hoping maybe
we could have lunch later.
I mean, when you're
feeling better, of course.
LUTHER: Cassandra.
Oh god.
LUTHER: Cassandra, it's
time for morning devotion.
My father's back already.
Sorry.
Put this on.
LUTHER: Cassandra?
Cassandra?
Quickly.
Out this way.
Dear god in heaven.
Come here, boy.
Come here!
You sinful pervert.
Daddy, Daddy, it's
not what you think.
Did you enjoy your
accommodations for the night?
Daddy, I can explain.
I knew it.
Emmett Farley, son
of old Joe Farley.
Yes, Daddy.
Tell me, Emmett.
Did I ever paddle you?
Uh, no.
Oh.
That's too bad.
It might have done
you some good.
Uh... uh... uh.
Ow, ow, ow!
Ow!
Daddy, no!
Ow, ow, ow.
OK, ow.
Daddy, no.
Please, it's a misunderstanding.
He... he didn't do anything!
Daddy, wait.
Let us pray.
Daddy, no.
Hello, my old friend.
Surely, you remember
The Enforcer.
CASSANDRA: No, Daddy, no!
This is wrong!
Ow!
Goddamn!
You little slut.
No, Daddy.
If he can't do penance,
then perhaps you will!
Repeat after me.
Lord have mercy.
No!
[Paddling]
This is your brain.
This is your brain on drugs.
This is your brain on
drugs with a side of bacon.
Yeah.
There we go.
A little sauce for
the Grease, huh?
Yeah.
There we go.
Shit.
Uh, uh.
Here.
Ted?
Ted!
[Radio chatter]
Oh.
Hello, officers.
Can I help you?
Yes, ma'am.
May we speak with Joey, please?
Uh, sure.
Just a second.
Let me go get him.
All right.
It's OK.
How's it going, guys?
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
We received a
complaint from Liz.
She claims you attacked
her at Freddie's
Bowl-a-rama last night.
Are you kidding me?
She was one throwing
bowling balls.
Ah, shit!
Motherfucker.
Shit.
Oh man.
Not fair.
Not fair, man.
A restraining order?
I never laid a
goddamn hand on her.
Well, what can I
tell you, Sloppy?
She's really pissed.
Thanks for trying.
Well, you guys want
some eggs or something?
No.
I mean, wait here.
I'll bring 'em right out to you.
And a couple of joes.
Cliff!
Oh my god!
You moron!
What are you nuts?
What are you doing?
Look what you did, Cliff.
You ruined breakfast.
OK.
Think, Grease.
Think.
OK.
All right.
Shit's going down.
What do you do?
[Gunshot]
Jesus
What was that?
Sounded like gunfire.
What are you?
Nuts?
Maybe it was a
couple of hunters.
It's not hunting season.
Sounded like it
came from out back.
Come here.
Come here!
Get down.
Get the fuck down!
POLICEWOMAN (ON RADIO):
127 Rosco to 92 Parker.
92, go head.
POLICEWOMAN (ON
RADIO): Complaints
Of a car stuck in an open septic
tank down in Hilltop Farms.
Over.
You guys there?
Roger.
Be right over.
Looks like this'll
have to wait till later.
We'll be back.
Well, at any rate, I
wouldn't be doing any bowling
For a while, Sloppy.
Yeah, especially
not on ladies' night.
Thanks for the advice, guys.
Hey, isn't that Ted
Condosta down there?
Thanks a lot, man.
Thanks a lot.
Hey.
Hey, Ted!
[Siren wails]
A fucking restraining order?
I can't believe it.
Fucking bitch.
I'm gonna kill her, man.
[Mumbling]
Hey, man.
They coming back here or what?
Can you believe that bitch put
a restraining order on me, huh?
The fucking nerve!
Wow.
What a bitch.
Uh, technically, she
can't actually have one...
Shut the hell up goon!
Goddamn it.
I feel like I'm just gonna...
I know what you feel like, man.
I know exactly what'll make you
and me feel a whole lot better.
What?
Whirly.
Whirly, whirly, whirly, whirly,
whirly, whirly, whirly, whirly!
I haven't flushed yet, guys!
Aw, shit!
Whirly, whirly, whirly!
Listen.
I don't care if she
already picked it up.
No.
There's no way I'm paying for
that fucking wedding cake.
Do you hear me, huh?
No way!
Please, Cliff.
You have no idea how
much light hurts me.
Well, all I can say
is if somebody wants
Their stupid
sunglasses back, they'd
Better sit down and just take a
few moments to look at my work.
OK?
God, I have such a hangover.
Yeah, probably used
too much bourbon.
I'm sorry.
I hope you don't
think I was trying
To take advantage of you.
There's nothing
to be sorry about.
You were wonderful last night.
Oh yeah?
Well, I guess I have picked up
a few things over the years.
That's the first time
I've ever cheated on Cliff.
Wait a minute.
You wanted it just as bad as me.
And it's not cheating unless
you actually do it, OK?
No, no. You don't get it.
Have you ever gotten
completely shit-faced
And then made out with
someone you're not
Even remotely attracted too?
Yeah.
It's so fucking liberating.
Wait a minute.
What's that supposed to mean?
You know, you should
get some sleep.
You look like shit.
Hey, wait a minute!
Morning, everybody.
How we all doing?
One hell of a night.
ANSWERING MACHINE: Joey,
this is Aunt Merkie.
What's this I hear
about a whorehouse?
You used to be such a nice boy.
Don't...
ANSWERING MACHINE:
Joey, Uncle Sal.
We're getting drunk over here
on account of your troubles.
And we just wanna know, can
we return our gifts yet?
Wait to go, killer.
Hello?
May I help you?
Yeah, hi.
Can I speak to Liz, please?
She doesn't wanna to talk
to you, you fucking creep!
Oh, just put her
on the phone, bitch!
Asshole!
Mother, give me the phone!
What?
Listen, I want a truce, OK?
I wanna talk about getting
things back on track.
Are you out of your mind?
Oh come on, Dink.
You know you still want me.
Oh, Dinkie, in a
week or two, you're
Gonna be climbing the wall.
I am hanging up now, pig.
Oh, wait, Liz.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
OK?
Oh man.
Look, Joey, forget it.
I am not marrying you.
Blow it up your ass,
you fucking creep!
Thanks a lot, God!
Come off it, Joey.
There is no God.
Sorry, Cliff.
I can't take this anymore.
This book is absurd!
And your attitude is
just as bad, Joey.
I'm going right
now to talk to Liz.
No, you're not.
All right.
The next person who doesn't
get along in here gets shot.
Put that away, you cokehead.
What is going on in here?
Stumpy, you can't go see Liz.
You two don't get along.
Yeah, she hates
your fucking guts.
And besides, I
think someone would
Rather keep her
nose clean and spend
The afternoon with a good book.
Paula, I usually abhor
violence, but could you?
Cliff, you son of a...
No, stop it!
Stop it!
So if you don't mind my
asking, what's the bad blood
Between you and Liz?
Oh, actually, none
of us got along
With Liz when we were kids.
It wasn't until years
after high school
That Joey started
going out with her.
Oh man.
It's beautiful and all tax-free.
Some good tit, huh?
Hey, aren't you
afraid those guys
Might come looking for you?
In this town?
They got bigger fish to fry.
I wish I sold drugs.
It's more complicated
than that, Scoop.
I don't just sell drugs, OK?
But you still hate her.
Well, Liz and her friends
used to taunt me all the time
About my weight in high school.
You know, prank phone calls
in the middle of the night,
Spraypainted pigs on my locker.
That's horrible.
Yeah.
It must have caused more
than one suicide attempt.
Oh, but hey.
That's all in the past.
What do you say, gentlemen?
Ready to blast off?
Yeah.
Hi, can I help you?
Hi, Liz.
Well, well.
It's been a long time, Stumpy.
Come here to gloat?
No, I came here to help.
I think that we
can work this out.
Oh.
How sweet.
We're quite the saint
today, aren't we?
Who are you?
Paula.
Love your earrings.
Love your cake.
Take a a walk, you freak!
Yes, it was a nice cake.
It used to symbolize
something, something sacred!
Let's get married.
Oh, yes.
I love you so much.
Let's get married.
OK.
But first let me go
over here and fuck
This broad one last time.
Hey, baby.
I'm getting married.
How about a little
Vitamin F, huh?
Ooh.
Ooh, yeah!
Ooh!
Hmm.
Mmm.
It's good.
You want some?
Liz, we need to talk.
[Shouting]
Damn, can't believe
you still got that kite.
What?
Are you kidding me?
I'd never get rid of it.
Does it still fly?
Heck yeah.
Geez.
I remember when the old man
used to take us up in it, man.
Those were some good times, eh?
He used to sweep down
on our Little League team
And practice strafing runs.
I know.
You guys deserved it.
You sucked.
So have you talked to him?
Nah.
Well, a couple years
ago when Mom died,
He had some big construction
deal or something
Going on in Antigua.
So wait a minute. He doesn't
know about the wedding?
I mean, [inaudible]
Nah, man.
Funerals and weddings,
old man can't stand 'em.
Well, who can?
Guys, come here!
Look at this!
You know what this is?
Yeah, I know what it is.
It's for Mr. Costos's garden.
Put 'em back, Scoop.
Morning glory seeds.
So?
Natural hallucinogens!
God given psychedelics!
No shit.
Yeah.
Really?
Oh.
Oh God.
This is very good.
This always makes
me feel better.
Have some fries.
You eat like a bird.
Oh, I stopped eating for
pleasure a time ago, Liz.
What's that supposed to mean?
Here we are, ladies.
Paula, what are
you doing with that?
What?
Girls, I don't have a
license for that shit.
Take it outside!
Shirley, can I
have some glasses?
I'm in a crappy mood
and I wanna drink.
This things taste disgusting.
I forgot how long
it's take to work.
I wanna see some trolls
or something, you know?
You know that's a
waste of time, guys.
The government would never
allow that on the market.
Goon, you don't take any
seeds, you're not gonna
Be part of our secret club.
What secret club?
The secret club Goon
won't be allowed in!
All right.
Listen to me.
Goon, if you don't partake
in these [inaudible],
I'm gonna blow your
fucking head off.
Will you put that thing away?
Shut up, or I'll shoot you too.
- First, you have to...
- Margaret.
- Liz.
Liz, first you have to...
Margaret, I know you're trying
to be the peacemaker here,
But I am sick to
death of the guys.
Fuck it, girl.
That's what you all should say.
And ask for that stinking,
whore-loving bastard you
Were gonna marry, you should...
I don't wanna talk
about it anymore.
OK?
You have to talk about it, Liz.
You and Joey both have to
stop hiding from each other.
Once you open your receptors,
you'll be surprised
How clear the message becomes.
You fucking liberals
are all the same.
Do you know what I'd do
if I found that stinking
Bastard handcuffed to my bed?
I don't wanna think
about this anymore!
Can we just get drunk?
You girl ever hear
of World War II?
Yeah.
You ever hear of the Japanese?
What?
Oh.
Hey, Scoop.
Want a scoop?
Man.
Goon was right.
Those seeds are nasty.
Oh God.
[Fart]
Aw, man!
Sure do give you gas
though, don't they?
Man, you're classy.
Let me tell you.
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and
gentlemen, all the way from Los
Angeles, CA, Sloppy Joe Ramsey!
The Bataan Death March
was just the beginning.
What happened after
was sheer genius.
It's what that rat
bastard Joey deserves.
This is counterproductive.
I think...
Let her finish.
And they marched
the men into a room
And make 'em whip
out their weenies.
Then they take a
glass tube, about 1/16
Of an inch in diameter,
and slowly, ever so slowly,
They insert the tube into
the hole and up the urethra.
Then, adding injury
to insult, they
Take a blunt instrument and...
Oh my god, that's horrific!
It wouldn't work on Cliff.
The tube's too big!
Aw, honey.
I was trying to cheer you up!
OK.
Do Jack Nicholson
as Captain Kirk.
All right.
Hi, this is Captain James T
Kirk of the Starship Enterprise.
Hmm.
You think you're so cool!
Here's what we're gonna do.
I'll be myself over there.
We will sit down, we will
have a little Romulan ale
And we'll just call
it a day's work.
There's more fish in the
sea, and they are for me!
Do Marlon Bra... Marlon
Brando as Mr. Brady when
Peter's voice is gonna crack.
All right.
OK.
Peter, I understand you're
coming of age and your voice is
Starting to change,
and... you're gonna have
To stop sneaking into
Cindy's room at night,
Because, you know...
Ah, your mother's a bitch!
I pick that witch
and I got an itch!
And you can scratch it!
Liz, Liz, you have
to get over it.
You can't just sign
your life over to them.
You just take it and
run away with it.
Paula, you're drunk.
Liz, just look at us.
You made sure that I was the
most unpopular girl in school
And I used to pray
for your death.
But people change.
Situations mutate and
lend deeper meaning
To our lives and relationships.
Cut the bullshit, counselor.
No.
I mean, Margaret's right.
The situation has mutated.
Nobody knows this, but,
um... well, I'm pregnant.
Sweet Jesus.
You've gotta abort that thing.
Oh my god!
We're going to the
house right now.
Joey has a right to know
what he's throwing away.
Where's Leon?
Leon?
OK, we want a first-rate
bistro with the brute sleekness
Of middle American autorepair.
Oh my god.
Jesus, [inaudible] And
Pedro, my boss at...
For your mother!
So they can have a lifetime
supply of bacon food
At the bar?
All right.
I'm gonna need
more things though.
Leon, Leon!
Get away from me.
Stop it.
Stop it!
[Inaudible] Cut it
out, you freaks!
You're freaks!
Yeah!
Joey!
You gotta calm these guys down.
They're tearing up the place!
Total world domination!
Woohoo!
Yeah!
Oh yeah.
I'll save you, Romulus.
Damn son of a... somebody's
disturbed my Saturday.
Gotta come out and see
what the hell is going on.
Bash his freaking
head in for him.
Company, it's Joey's boss.
What the hell's wrong with you?
You look like a goddamn freak.
Where's that goddamn Joey
Ramsey, that son of a bitch?
What's going on here?
What the hell!
Where is he?
Jesus Christ.
You find that son of a bitch.
What the fuck?
Get the hell outta here!
[Inaudible]
What the fuck?
Cliff!
Sloppy Joe!
Joey, where the hell are you?
[Phone ringing]
Hello.
MAN (ON PHONE): Si, I am looking
for a Senor Ted Condosta.
Ted?
Is Condosta Ted's last name?
Yeah.
MAN (ON PHONE): This
man has a briefcase?
Yeah.
MAN (ON PHONE): And
he's staying there
At the dos ciento cuarenta
y uno Haddock Road.
Yeah, he's staying here.
MAN (ON PHONE): Ah.
Muy bien, muchacha.
Muy bien.
Man, I can't believe he
flipped out like that.
I'm sure once he calms down and
realizes what he did... I mean,
He just can't fire
you like that, man.
Yes, he can.
See?
I told you Joe was
gonna get in trouble.
Nice going, Goon!
Way to ruin a perfect afternoon!
Hey, man.
Why don't you lay off?
Can't you see the
guy's not feeling well?
Oh, fuck you!
Listen to me, you little shit.
Get away from me, you prick!
Huh?
You know, everybody's
sick and tired
Of your superior
bullshit, Cliff!
You think because you went
to some fancy university,
'Cause you live in
New York fucking City
That you're better
than the rest of us?
You stupid, decadent slob!
Oh, fuck you, man!
You know what?
Your novel sucks!
And I almost fucked your
girlfriend last night too.
What do you think of that?
Bullshit!
Paula would never cheat on me!
What do you know
about my book anyway?
You can't even read, asshole!
No, you're the asshole!
No, you're the
asshole, asshole!
Come on, Sloppy.
I'm gonna fucking kill him!
My writing [inaudible]
is so above you!
It's so above anyone in
this stupid-ass town!
Oh, I'll give you something
to write about, heavyweight.
Come here!
I just need to get outta here!
Put me down!
Fucking come on!
Sloppy Joe, you put
me down right now.
I wanna take him to
the fucking cleaners.
Where you going?
JOEY: I'm going to
the store to find Liz.
Liz?
Joey.
Liz, open the goddamn door!
Let's go.
Come on.
[glass shatters]
Oh shit.
[Alarm wails]
[Inaudible]
[Glass shatters]
Come on.
Let's get outta here.
Come on, get in the fucking car.
[Inaudible]
No, we gotta get outta town.
[Interposing voices]
VOICE: Emmett, come to me.
Oh, Emmett, come.
Emmett, come.
Emmett, Emmett.
Shh, it's me.
Emmett, what are
you doing here?
I came to get my clothes.
And I heard you call.
Wait here.
[Humming]
My prince charming.
I knew you'd come.
I even packed.
Mmm.
Let's go.
They're coming to
get you, Barbara.
My family plot is
right over there.
That's where my
grandfather is buried.
I often come here, Emmett.
Some people think
it's kind of creepy,
But I find it therapeutic.
My father says I should
be afraid of death,
That I'm going to rot
in Hell most likely.
Emmett, let's
leave town tonight.
We can go out West.
It's warm out there.
Oh my, Emmett.
You're just full of surprises.
It's a full moon, Cassandra.
[Moaning]
Emmett?
Mhm?
We're near my
favorite tombstone.
Oh.
Uh.
[Moaning]
Oh, wow.
Hey.
Hey, man.
I can't stay in here.
I'm claustrophobic.
I'll die, man.
GREASE: I can't believe
we went back to Lola's.
JOEY: I told you it
was a bad idea, Ted.
GREASE: Hey, how was
I supposed to know
Lola was friends with the cops?
CLIFF: Friends?
They were customers, brainboy.
They weren't wearing any pants.
GREASE: That's not the point.
CLIFF: No.
Joey owes a lot of money.
Goddamn it.
GREASE: Why didn't you tell me?
I got tons of cash, man.
JOEY: Yeah.
Right.
That's all I need to do...
Start laundering your drug
Money through the fucking town.
GREASE: Excuse me,
Mr. Ungrateful, Mr...
CLIFF: Shut up.
Shut up!
We'll get in trouble!
Boy, am I glad to see you guys.
You gotta get me
outta here, man.
I'm dying in here.
Paula!
Paula, it was
entirely their idea.
I mean, ah, they're
on drugs or something.
I was just along for the ride.
GREASE: Fucking bullshit, man!
That's bullshit!
No, it's a horrible mistake!
Shut up!
Paula, I did nothing wrong.
You have to believe me.
Tell it to the judge, Cliff.
GREASE: Bullshit, man.
What bullshit.
CLIFF: Paula, call
my mom and dad.
You gotta get me outta here.
Liz?
Liz, is that you?
You gotta forgive me, Liz.
I was crazed last night.
I mean, I got fired,
and you wanted to put
That restraining order on me.
And I went looking
for you, baby,
But you weren't at the store.
All that was there was
that goddamn poster
Of me and that wedding cake.
And I guess it was then that
I got a little immature.
Joey, you break my heart.
I'm sorry, Liz.
I'll do anything to repay
you for the store, OK?
I'm not talking
about the store!
I'm talking about Lola's!
Why'd you go back there, huh?
Oh, nothing happened!
Ask the cops.
I mean, it was all Ted's idea.
That stupid fuck wanted
to establish an alibi.
GREASE: Will you give
me a break already.
CLIFF: It's true, Liz.
It's all his fate.
GREASE: That's it.
You're dead, Dugan.
[Shouting]
What the hell is
going on in here?
Everybody shut up!
Joey, I believe that Liz
has something to say to you.
I just hope you're
man enough to take it.
Go ahead, Liz.
Joey, I'm, um,
dropping the charges.
JOEY: Oh, thank Christ.
GREASE: Bless her, Lord.
CLIFF: Hallelujah.
Shut up, [inaudible]
You're not free yet.
Let me outta here.
She said she was
dropping the charges.
Liz?
Joey, I'm pregnant.
D'oh!
GREASE: Well, one step ahead
of the shotgun, eh, Sloppy?
CLIFF: She doesn't
have to keep it.
Yes, I'm keeping it.
Because it's mine and I want it!
Yeah, I want one too, you know.
Yeah, I think it'd
be pretty cool, man.
Having a little guy around.
Teach it to fly.
Maybe play a little guitar.
Hey.
Baby, you gotta give
me another chance.
Hmph.
I'll give you
another chance, Joey.
All right.
You're not gonna
regret it, honey.
There's gonna be
a lot of changes.
Anything you say, sweetie pie.
And one hell of a
probation period.
That's fine.
Now come here.
Give me a kiss.
Hey, take it to
a hotel room, OK?
I wanna get the fuck outta here.
Oh, and one more
thing, honey pie?
Yeah, my little dinkie doodle?
That's for wrecking my store.
GREASE: Will somebody please
get me outta here now?
[Snoring]
You snore loud enough
to wake the dead, Emmett.
Thought you got away nice
and clean, didn't you?
I saw you kidnap
her, you bastard.
And now you are going to pray.
I am gonna stick this
right up your ass
And blow the shit up into
your mouth where it belongs.
Daddy, put that thing away.
Father, put the gun down.
What's with the suitcase,
my darling child?
Hmm?
Emmett and I are
running away together.
What?
Get the candle wax out
of your ears, Preacher.
Emmett and I are
going to Los Angeles.
And there's nothing
you can do about it.
Of all the hellholes
in the world.
That's impossible.
Never.
I won't allow it, by Christ.
No fucking way!
You wanna shoot him?
Go ahead.
You don't have the guts.
Go on!
Pull the goddamn trigger.
Pop him one right
between the eyes!
You can hang around waiting
for the Second Coming, Father,
But I've already
found my savior.
Sweet Jesus, help me!
It's empty.
How do you expect to be a
psychopath without bullets?
But you can't leave.
I need you!
I'll die without you.
No, no!
Don't go, please!
[Shouting]
[Sobbing]
Well, one things
for sure, amigo.
You'll never catch me
up in this tin can.
Yeah.
Hope it doesn't crash.
Oh, thanks a lot, guys.
I'll send you a postcard.
Where you getting hitched?
We're gonna play it by ear.
Goon, you old dog!
You and Cassandra,
you take it easy, man.
All right?
And do whatever it
is, um, that you do.
OK.
We got him now.
Huh, Boss?
I'm gonna miss you, fucker.
I'm gonna miss you
even more, buddy!
Let's get your ass
up in the clouds.
I ain't going
anywhere for a while.
Excellent.
Make sure you make your
court date though, all right.
Cousin Billy don't
like to be stood up.
And water the plants.
Step on it, Joey.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, you goddamn monster!
No, no, no. [Inaudible] No, no!
No, no, no!
Baby, come back to mommy.
How long do you give 'em?
I dunno.
How long's it take
to get to Vegas?
[Chuckling]
MOTHER: I want my baby!
Hey, kids.
How you doing?
Scoop, no hurt feelings?
Oh, by the way, you
left this inside.
Keep it.
I'm gonna write a new one.
What?
I thought this was your
fucking masterpiece, man.
Nah.
You know, I... I
feel like the muse
Is pushing me somewhere else.
I think I need to pander to the
masses just a little bit more.
Yeah.
Well, good luck.
Thanks.
You take care.
And Scoop, get a
job, you deadbeat.
Drive safely.
CLIFF: Could you not grind
the clutch a little more
When you're backing up?
PAULA: Cliff, just shut
up and let me drive.
CLIFF: Well, then maybe you'd
like to pay for a new clutch
Then?
PAULA: I said, shut up.
Buenos dias, Senor Condosta.
Como estas?
Hello, Ted.
Estas buscando esto?
The briefcase.
Estoy muy decepcionado contigo.
No puedo confiar en ti.
He's real pissed.
[Gunshots]
Aw shit.
Nobody gets the Grease Man.
Nobody gets the grease.
Shit.
Come on!
[Gunshots]
Goddamn it.
CLIFF: Come on.
This station sucks.
Let me put my CD in.
What are you doing?
PAULA: Get out!
CLIFF: What do you mean get out?
What do you mean?
What?
Whoa!
PAULA: Get the fuck out!
Now you can pedal your
ass home, pansy boy!
Paula!
Paula, come back.
That's my car!
Damn it!
My parents bought me that car.
Damn, I knew it.