Listen up, this is your play.
4 A.M. at K-Mart.
They have the best deals
and people camp out.
Then, across town
to electronics.
Then, to the mall.
The mall's gonna be a mad house,
so we should use the back
entrance and park at the bank.
Now, we're dalts.
Don't let anybody
push you around.
We'll be black Friday ninjas.
Full-contact shopping,
the true meaning of Christmas.
Yeah, well I need
those black Fridays.
I've got a daughter
in law school,
and it's not cheap.
Well, I have a
father and a brother
with expensive taste.
Hey, third piece?
You already ate half the Turkey.
No, see, it's moms and sisters
that have expensive taste.
Well, your mother
wants something
that can't be found in a
store this Christmas.
Oh yes?
She wants to win
the neighborhood house
decorating contest.
He winner gets featuredt n
west Michigan living magazinei
and it would really help
your mother's business.
But mom does interior design.
Listen, if Judy Gage
beats me again,
you know she's never gonna
let me hear the end of it.
It starts tomorrow
and this lady's
already out plotting
and scheming in her yard.
She takes great
pride in beating me
because I'm a design person.
Which is why Jason and
I are starting at dawn
while you two shop.
Nuh-uh, nope, not gonna happen.
Uh-huh, so we don't
have to go shopping.
( Hat ridiculous themew ID the
neighborhood associationd
vote for this year?
Christmas bells,
and I have had no time to plan,
so I am just thinking off
the top of my head silver,
all silver, silver bells.
Oh no, no, nope, nope, nope,
nope, nope, nope, nope.
What?
Darling, we're dalts. We
never go for the silver;
we always go for the
gold, for the win.
Speaking of which...
Off to work, we know.
Even on Thanksgiving.
The sports must go on.
♪♪♪
If you watched the central
Michigan game yesterday,
then you know the play
michiganders are just
celebrating tonight.
I hope you were able to
feast your eyes on...
Feast your eyes?
Eighty-yard touchdown
by Derek Jensen
that sealed it for the chippewas
in the final quarter.
That is Jensen's fifth
game-winning touchdown
in five straight games.
Now folks, I want to
tell you something.
He is the one we are giving
thanks for at our house.
Hat is your Thanksgiving
dayt sports round-up.
Tomorrow, our ridiculous
ref of the week award.
Here it comes.
I'm Bruce dalt, action
8 sports, for the win.
For the win.
Thank you, Bruce.
Very exciting. Well,
tomorrow is...
I can't believe you're
still letting him
do this ridiculous ref segment.
It's lowbrow.
It's the only segment we've
been able to get viral.
Viewers love it.
You know what they
would really love?
An exclusive with Derek Jensen.
Yeah, well that kid's
a media hermit.
He doesn't let the
press get near him.
He's a lock for the
heisman this year.
We should have a
home-field advantage;
he grew up in Garfield park.
If someone could get
that interview,
would they have a shot
at the on air desk?
Sure.
♪♪♪
Hey, Arlo, Judy,
you know you can't start
decorating 'til tomorrow.
It's 12:15, Bruce.
( Nd we're goinga or the win. F
♪♪♪
Jason, psst!
Jason, come on, get up.
Judy's got the jump on us.
Jason, wake up!
Come on buddy, don't you
care about Christmas, huh?
We have a whole month.
It's not a race.
Look, we can't let the gages
get the psychological edge.
We both know...
Do not quote yogi berra.
Ninety percent of the
game is half mental.
Now get up.
Come on!
♪♪♪
Where'd you even go?
I thought mom was still
deciding on her design.
Well, we know
she'll want lights,
so we'll start right here.
This whole competition
is stupid.
It doesn't mean...
It's important to your mom.
Why do I get the feeling
you're not in it to win here?
Because winning is overrated.
Winning will give you
greater opportunities.
This is the year that'll
determine your future, buddy.
If you win state, if
you get a scholarship,
that scholarship will
determine your school.
That school will
determine your career
and your entire future.
We're still talking about the
neighborhood contest, right?
Mm-hmm.
Alright, let's see here.
And we can't win like this,
so I will get a few
more hours of sleep
while we wait for
the stores to open.
See you in awhile, crocodile.
♪♪♪
( Do not understandi
hy they needw
all these handicapped
parking spaces.
Because we have handicapped
people in America, dad.
( Hoa, there's onew
ight over here. R
out of the way, man.
Ome on buddy, c ake your time! T
- there's another guy there.
- I don't care.
E's smaller than us, h
on't worry about it. D
ey, hey, hey, hey! H.
Et that little thingg ut
of here, I got it! O.
What's the matter with you, huh?
I was there first!
I'm bigger than you!
Come on, this is a big space.
For the win, right?
You're the sports reporter.
Yeah, Bruce dalt,
action 8 sports.
No, I'm telling you,
you saw that we
were first, right?
People get so crazy
at christmastime.
They do.
They forget what's
important, don't they?
Yeah.
( Hank you very much,
t erry Christmas. M
merry Christmas to you, too.
Well, you can't do much good
with pocket change, can you?
( Erry Christmas. M
tell me something,
this money doesn't go to buying
those crazy uniforms, does it?
( O, the uniforms say we'ren
vailable to people in need. A
the money goes to them.
Save to serve.
To each his own.
I don't care how it
gets in the kettle.
It's all the lord's money now.
Somebody'll be blessed by it.
♪ Joy to the world,
the lord has come ♪♪
Do you want the cheese plate
shipped to aunt Mabel?
Yes, and that tea cozy goes
to great grandma Rose.
She always sends us something
and I always forget about her.
That's terrible.
You know the doilies
she makes us?
[ On the first day of Christmas,
♪ reat grandma gave to me ♪g
a hand-crocheted doily ♪
- Beautiful.
- She's 99, she's precious.
I know.
I was thinking that maybe
we could do more things
as a family this year,
like go to church.
Oh.
Church.
Like, church-church?
Yeah!
You know, it's Christmas.
Christmas is the birth
of Jesus, right, right?
It sounds like a
good time to go.
Sure, I agree.
If you want to do that, sure.
I have to drive back
to school tomorrow,
end of term, so...
( Unday's alwayss big game day. A
I mean, there's a lot to cover.
I won't be able to go with you.
Lright, well maybea could
go on Christmas Eve. I
Bruce, we can, you know...
( O, it's cool, mom. N
if it's not real enough
to go every Sunday,
then why go on Christmas either?
I can go on my own.
Something I said?
Honey, how did it go
with you two today?
It went great!
We put up the new lights.
Well, I mean, did you, you know,
have a chance to connect?
Like, what did you talk about?
What are you, speaking womanese?
( Ome on. C
well, what are you asking me?
No, I'm serious.
Bruce, he's gonna be out of
the house before we know it
and he needs to know
we support him.
I don't want to lose him.
Sweetheart, he is
asking to go to church.
It's not like he's out
drinking or something.
Unless he's asking because he
feels guilty about something.
It's probably just a girl.
Look, he has a big
game tomorrow night.
( Lready planning on it. A
come as a dad, okay?
Don't come as Bruce dalt,
action 8 sports, for the win.
Don't I always?
♪♪♪
You just made it. They're
about to come out.
Hold on, hold on one second.
Be right back.
Excuse me, good to see
you, good to see you.
Hey everybody, how are you?
Bruce dalt, action 8 sports.
Hi, how ya doing?
Good to see you.
State's been off to an
excellent start this season.
This could be your
year, you guys.
Yeah, we think so.
You know, Jason dalt, number 4,
keep an eye on him.
He could be your
ticket for next year.
Okay, right, number 4, got it.
Okay, good.
Good to see you again.
They're gonna come
out man-to-man.
We gotta be ready for it.
We're gonna run
flex one, flex two.
It's gonna happen between
these two spots right here.
Jason, stay with me on
the play calls, okay?
Bruce, is everything
okay out there?
Oh, it's good, it's
good, it's real good.
I just wanna say, guys,
go get 'em, huh?
Now, there's a scout
from state out there
and he has got his
eyes on you boys,
so play your best, huh?
Especially you, Jason dalt, huh?
Alright.
Thanks, thanks Bruce.
Hey, can we get a minute here?
Oh yeah, sure, sure, yeah, go!
Alright guys, forget
everything he just said.
Forget about the scout.
We're gonna play our gam.
Now, you with me?
Yeah!
- Jason?
- Yeah, I'm with you.
Okay, this team is aggressive.
That's how they try
to get in your head.
We're gonna be cool.
We're gonna play great defense.
Defense, defense, defense,
defense, defense!
Spartans on three!
One, two, three, spartans!
♪♪♪
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Come on, Jason!
Oh, moving screen!
Ref, come on!
Go, Jason, go, go, go!
Oh, oh, reaching, hey, ref!
Make a call here, will you?
What?
No, wait, Bruce, stay out of it!
Look, you gonna call
something or what?
You're a referee,
call something!
Smart defense, no fouls.
Take the cotton out of your ears
and call something, will you?
Bring it in, right now.
He's on his way to a
ridiculous ref award.
Go Jason! Come on, buddy!
Jason, get your head
in the game, come on.
Foot was on the
line, two points.
( Wo? t
that was a three, what
are you talking about?
I don't believe this.
And he was fouled!
Are you an idiot or something?
You're from channel 8
action sports, right?
The guy who hands out the
ridiculous ref award?
Yes, yes, because I know a
bad call when I see one.
One, two, three, spartans!
- I really don't believe it.
- You need to stand back.
You need to start calling
some fouls, man.
What?!
We got a technical foul,
white, interference,
red, two shots.
Are you kidding me?
Dad, get off the court!
You, out!
( Hen I said wew eeded
to support him, n
here was a middle groundt n
there I was shooting for. I
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, okay!
Just that... Well,
you were there!
Not only was he clear
of the three line,
he was fouled.
I couldn't just sit there
and watch them lose
the game to bad call.
Oh, so they lost in a
more humiliating way.
He's mad, I don't blame him.
His teammates are mad, Bruce.
Jason is furious.
I'll talk to him.
No, you won't.
Ou will not go in
therey ight nowr
because you'll make it worse.
How could this
possibly be worse?
♪♪♪
You, out!
All three competing
networks carried it.
I pay you to report the news,
not make it for other stations.
Okay, okay.
What do you want me to do?
An on-air apology?
I'm gonna have to take
you off the desk.
What, why?
I need you to talk
to Tony in legal.
The ref's pressing charges.
That's ridiculous, right?
I mean, you just saw the video.
Everybody's seen the video.
If you take me off the desk
it's like you're
saying he's right.
It makes me look
like a criminal.
Just until you get
it worked out.
You've been here a long time,
but we just can't afford
to lose viewers right now.
Oh, I'm sorry, I'll come back.
No, no, Lesley,
what do you need?
Wardrobe was just
wondering which dress
you want me in for
the 6 o'clock.
Tough loss, Bruce.
Let's go with that one.
♪♪♪
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
Aren't you supposed
to be at school?
I drove home for the night.
Mom thought I should help.
I am working with the
station attorney.
You just jump in your
car, and turn around,
and drive right on back.
Dad, this is a no-win situation.
( O such thing. N
did you see the video, huh?
He guy ist otally overreacting. T
he has got a problem with
my ridiculous ref award
so he's attacking me.
- He has a case.
- A stupid case.
But still a case.
What did Tony say?
He said I should plead out
as quickly as possible
if I want to get
back on the air.
He's right.
No, he's not right.
You're a dalt.
I didn't raise you to back down.
I'm not backing down.
I'm coming to the
meeting with the judge.
- Fine.
- Yeah.
♪♪♪
Gentlemen, tell me we have
something reasonable
figured out here.
Mr. Dalt is prepared to
pay medical expenses.
Your honor, the victim
isn't interested in money.
We feel any kind of jail
time would be unwarranted,
especially at Christmas.
As a first-time offender...
Not even an offender.
Your honor, have you
seen the video?
I have.
Prosecutor, what
are you thinking?
Community service
and restitution.
So you want to put a bloody
nose through my court system
so that he can watch this fellow
pick up trash along the highway?
Your honor, the
victim was publicly
called out and humiliated.
And injured.
He had to have his family
Christmas picture taken
with this bandage on his nose.
They want your ego,
not your wallet.
This is good.
Did I ever give you
the ridiculous ref of
the week award, huh?
Is that what all this is about?
We'll take it. We'll
take community service.
- What?!
- Yes.
What happened to dalts
don't back down?
She's right.
And restitution.
Done.
Okay, then community service
and restitution it is.
They don't put people on the
road crews in December.
Something as public as my
incident would be preferred.
Well, it's Christmas.
The army can always use a
little help this time of year.
The army?
You can't do that.
Report tomorrow to major lowell.
I'll tell him to expect you.
And next time, stay
off the court, okay?
The army?
Uh...
Major lowell?
Bruce dalt,
action 8 sports, for the win.
Ome on in. C
I'm being saved to
serve, aren't I?
Sit down.
You play an instrument?
I took saxophone
in middle school.
It was hardly a
community service.
I think I know exactly
where you can help us out.
Oh no, no, no, not bells.
Oh, no, no bells if
that's okay with you.
Why not?
You know, I can sort
things at a thrift shop,
you know, old things?
I'm good at sorting.
My wife taught me
how to wash dishes.
I'll bet you have
a soup kitchen.
Why not bell ringing?
Well...
You know, people recognize
me when I'm out and about,
you know, from the news,
and it sure might become
a huge distraction.
People like to see someone
they know at the kettle.
Honestly, I don't want
to see people I know.
I think that's sad.
A lot of people
enjoy bell ringing.
We got local service clubs who
hold a friendly competition
to see who can ring more.
More power to 'em.
Sorry, Bruce.
Judge's orders.
I'll see you tomorrow,
10 A.M., at the K-Mart.
Ou remember the spot. Y
dress warm,
it really gets
cold after awhile.
Yes, sir.
Good day.
- Merry...
- Well, here I am.
Bruce?
You said it would be cold.
I didn't say we were
robbing a bank.
Well, I've gotta protect my
skin from windburn, you know?
I'm on the air, you know?
Not until your community
service is up.
And I think the ski
mask definitely gives
the "don't approach me" vibe.
Alright, alright.
- Excellent.
- There.
Here's your apron,
and of course, your bell.
And don't ring it too much.
Just enough for
people to notice.
A friendly smile.
Good.
And please be sure
to thank the people
and say "merry Christmas."
Now, let's see it.
A little more.
I know how to ring
a bell, alright?
And someone will be here
to collect the kettle
when your shift is done.
Okay, okay, I got it.
Okay.
Thank you.
I know it doesn't
seem like much,
but it means a lot.
Hey!
I'm just grabbing a picture
for my ridiculous reporter
of the week award.
Oh, hilarious.
Ha, ha, ha, merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
Lesley, welcome.
Thank you, Harold.
E have exciting news forw ll
you chippewa fans tonight. A
entral Michigan'sc
wn Derek jenseno
has been awarded the
coveted heisman trophy.
Ensen is the... j.
( Oney, don't makeh
ourself miserable. Y
do I look miserable?
( Es.y
she's prettier than me.
( Et's hope so. L
and younger.
You know what would
make you feel better?
If you brought out
your inner griswold,
and you got up on the roof,
and you put up the
angels I bought today.
What happened to the
reindeer we had?
Well, they got worn out
in last year's blizzards.
But you know what? These
are really beautiful.
They're motion activated.
They play music when
people walk by and...
How much did you spend
on some musical angels?
Please, Bruce.
You know there's gonna
be a storm this weekend
and then they'll never go up.
Okay, your old,
non-pretty husband
who has been out in
the cold all day
will climb up on the roof
in the middle of the night
and put up your overpriced
musical angels.
Thank you, you're the best.
♪♪♪
Huh, no bells.
Can't win without
incorporating the theme.
We don't have enough
twinkle lights.
( Hese are pretty, t
hese are classy. T.
We're going to win with...
If we don't use these lights...
Twinkle lights will make the...
( Don't understand... i.
Okay, okay.
♪♪♪
Thank you, merry Christmas.
You want to ring for awhile?
I'm very happy right here.
Nice and warm, egg nog latte.
Enjoy.
I will.
Your release is here!
Merry Christmas!
Yes, it's a cold one, isn't it?
The rug helps.
Yeah.
It just feels so good
to give, doesn't it?
Yeah.
It really warms the
cockles of your heart.
I'm so excited!
I just love to greet
those shoppers,
and ring the bell, and
say "merry Christmas."
I got all the other ladies
from Bible study fellowship
to do it too.
We're gonna give the rotary
a run for the kettle
awards this year.
Oh, you're from one of
those service groups
that brings a bunch of people.
- Oh yeah!
- Oh.
We have so much fun.
And every spring,
they throw a really wonderful
banquet for the volunteers.
They give a silver bell award
to the group with the
most volunteers,
most hours on the kettle,
most money raised.
It can go to an individual, too.
Total raised, or per hour?
Well, of course that's
not why we do it.
Of course not.
You know, I've got 1 or 2
minutes left on my time.
Excuse me.
Ir, sir, can I talk to yous
bout making a donation? A
erry Christmas! M
♪♪♪
Hey you! You in the SUV.
Give to those who
need for Christmas.
Help us do the
most good, please!
♪ Joy to the world,
the kettle is here ♪
♪ And I'm going for the win! ♪♪
Can we go now?
Hey big guy, you
got a dollar, huh?
You got a dollar for me?
Come on, man.
Excuse me, excuse me, the
kettle is right here.
Please, make a donation.
Merry Christmas to you!
Alright, go away.
♪ Joy to the world,
the kettle is here ♪
♪ And I'm going for the win! ♪♪
No, no, no, you got
something for the kettle.
You know you do. Come
on, you know you do.
Come on, give it to me.
Give us a little help here.
A little help to do some good.
Okay, we'll catch
you another day.
Cheapskate.
$78.50!
Come on miss, every
little bit helps.
This is for those in need.
Really, this is for those...
Bruce!
What?
What are you doing?
I nearly cleared 300
bucks this shift!
Bruce, I think we need to talk.
- But I could have gotten more.
- Come on.
I thought getting the money
in the kettle was the point.
The point is to get people to
understand the joy of giving,
and we usually don't do that
through fear and intimidation.
I can stop singing.
Why do we celebrate Christmas?
It's the birth of Jesus.
But why was he born?
To grow up and to save mankind.
And why would he do that?
To defeat evil.
And how did he defeat evil?
Mighty power from on high.
With love, Bruce.
He came, he lived, he died
because he loves you,
nd he lovesa ll these people. A
that's why we love
all these people.
What is this?
Applications for Christmas help.
I want you to sort
'em alphabetically
so we can organize the pick-up.
No, no, no, you can't
take me off the kettle.
I'm just gaining on
the rotary club.
How many are there?
About 1,800.
♪♪♪
You can quit for the night.
I know it's a big Jo,
but you and I both need
to get home to our wives.
I'm sorry, I just
got distracted.
What, reading them?
I know they're confidential.
I know you do.
Bit overwhelming, isn't it?
Even just this one here,
ingle dad workings
minimum wage jobs, 2
6 kids, the power's been
turned off on his place
twice in the last 2 months.
Are all the kids on the
angel's tree list?
( Eah. y
and look at this kid here.
It's kind of funny.
Andre, he wishes he
could play for the NBA,
but he knows that
could take awhile,
so all he wants is a
pair of basketball shoes
for a good start.
Yeah, I like this kid.
I know,
but you need to get
home to your family.
Yeah.
I can finish this up tomorrow,
but if you want to do any
more behind the scenes work,
y wife Roberta'sm rganizing
a big sorting dayo
here we organizew nd
unpack food donationsa
for the Christmas baskets.
Nd you coulda ring your family. B
would that still count
towards my service hours?
Of course,
but it also counts
towards loving others.
Get out of here.
♪♪♪
- Hey.
- Hi!
How much do you think all of
this will add to our power bill?
Is it too much, too bright?
Oh, no, no, I was just
thinking how much it costs
to have so much Christmas.
Did you just get fired?
No, no.
Good, that is good
because things have slowed
down for me a little.
Well, you know,
people aren't really
starting remodels
this time of year.
Yeah, I mean, I hope so.
I've just... I've had a couple
of comments from clients,
you know, about the video,
your referee thing.
Seriously?
Yeah, but you know, I
think you're right.
I think it's this time of year
and it'll pick back
up in January.
Here, here, you
want it up there?
( Eah. y
here it is. Let me do it.
( Hank you. T
- perfect.
- There.
( Hanks. t.
It's so good to have
you on the team.
Thank you, Harold. I'm excited.
You're a natural.
All set for the broadcast?
We're good.
We had to rewrite the copy
you wrote for Lesley.
It wasn't quite her style.
Oh, well, I'm better
out on the field
than I am behind the
prompter, I guess.
Speaking of which,
about my assignment
for tomorrow.
I don't remember us covering
bowling that much in the past.
We covered it,
it doesn't always
make the broadcast.
In fact, Chad, can you
go as his camera op.
- Sure, yeah.
- Okay, great.
Just tighten up on that shot a
little bit and we'll be good.
Copy that.
Lucky us, right?
You don't deserve it, Bruce.
They have you on bowling
while Lesley gets the
Derek Jensen interview?
We got an interview
with Derek Jensen?
He doesn't give interviews.
She's trying.
She hasn't had any luck... Yet.
Thanks, Chad.
♪♪♪
What's all this?
These are fake
presents for the yard
which don't use any electricity.
What are you working on?
Did you know that Derek
Jensen grew up in this area?
The football star?
The key to getting my job back.
Just have to figure a
way to get to him.
He doesn't do interviews.
Well, if he's from here, honey,
there might still be
family in the area.
There might.
If you want to know what's
going on with the son,
ask the mother.
Hey, that's a good idea.
Unless, of course,
he's your son,
in which case I have no idea.
Why, what's happening
with Jason?
I don't know.
I feel like he's avoiding home.
E's out late, h
don't know where. I
what happened to
going to church?
I think he's going.
He just barely talks to
me unless he wants food.
Yeah, well, he's a teenage boy.
See, here he is.
Well, you try.
Jason, Jason!
Where were you?
Out.
Out where?
Practice.
Honey, what happened
to your letter?
I caught it on something.
So, how was school?
Fine.
Can I have some dinner?
It's in the fridge.
Jason, hold on a second.
Hold on a second.
I want to ask you cancel
any plans you might
have on Saturday.
There's something I'd like the
whole family to do together.
Not decorating.
No, no, no, no, no.
Major lowell asked if
we could all come down
to the Christmas food drive
at the salvation army,
you know, unpack and
distribute food boxes,
that sort of thing.
Bruce, I love that idea.
That'll be some great time
together as a family.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure, I'll do it.
Okay, I guess he'll talk
to us again on Saturday.
♪♪♪
( Lright everybody, a
claim a table in groups
of twos or threes.
Melvin!
You made it.
This is the family?
Yes, this is my wife, Piper.
- Nice to meet you.
My son, Jason.
We've met. Hi, Jason.
Oh yes, at the kettle
on black Friday.
Wow, good memory.
( Want to thank you alli
or joining us todayf
to serve with joyful hearts.
That's my wife, gotta go.
Grab that table.
( Ow, just a few instructionsn
efore we get started, b
but the main thing is we are
going to have some fun.
Okay, if you notice, there's a
stack of baskets on your table
ith a list of itemsw
hat go in them. T
ou can assign one persony t
your table to act as a runnera
o go and bring backt
he food suppliest
hile the othersw egin to fill. B
are we ready?
Yeah, whoo-hoo!
( Lright, great, a
et's get started. L
whoo-hoo!
Okay, team dalt,
let's do this, huh?
Who wants to be the runner, hmm?
Looks like it's me.
♪♪♪
That's the guy from
the basketball game.
What else?
Behind me is the guy who
banged up the ref's nose
at my brother's basketball game.
Now, he's trying to be
the super food packer.
Okay, canned yams.
Okay, what more do we need here?
We need flour.
Flour, come on, come on dalts.
We are falling behind. Go, go!
Oh, thank you so
much, sweetheart.
Very good, alright.
Last one.
♪♪♪
Please, here.
Thank you. No, thank you.
Bruce, what are you doing?
Dad, you are fighting a
little girl for flour.
( Hat is going on over here? W.
This is Bruce.
Oh!
What does "oh" mean?
Let's just get this
mess cleaned up.
Jason, there's a broom closet
out in the hallway
by the bathroom.
Piper, you can go clean up.
I'll have Bruce stand
guard 'til you get back
so no one slips in this.
( E're probably gonna have
tow tart all over again. S
Derek is leaving.
Everybody, everybody,
hold things up a minute.
We have a friend here who
eserves some congratulations. D
now, he has to leave right away,
so I want to get him up
here before he goes.
Derek, come on up,
and don't be shy.
You gotta be kidding me.
Some of you know
that Derek Jensen
was just named heisman
trophy winner.
But what you may not know
is Derek grew up right here,
just a few blocks
from the corps,
and he played his first football
on our field outside
in the back.
So somehow, e feel
like we raised him. W
so, we just want to say how
proud we are of you, Derek.
You're using your talents,
you're a shining
light for the lord,
nd somehow, you find the timea
o come back here every yeart
to pack baskets.
So, we thank you.
Alright, let's get back to work.
♪♪♪
The house looks nice.
Thank you.
How was work?
Oh, it was fine, you know.
I'm sorry about the flour and...
You're an Internet sensation...
Again.
Eighteen thousand hits?
How long has this been up?
Long enough for Jason to
get 30 e-mails about it.
It gets even worse.
Remember Derek Jensen?
Yes, Jason told me he was there.
I didn't even get to see him
until I was covered in flour.
Well, now you know
something about him.
Yeah.
♪♪♪
Mrs. Jensen?
Can I help you?
I'm Bruce dalt.
I'd like to have a
word with Derek.
You know Derek?
( O, but I saw himn aturdays
and I've been trying to
get in touch with him.
You're a reporter.
No, no.
Well, yes and no.
You can't even
make up your mind.
I am a reporter, yes,
ction 8 news, a ruce
dalt, for the win? B
wait, I know you.
You're the one that punched
the ref in the nose.
No, that's not true.
Why would I ever let
Derek talk to you?
Get on out of here.
Now, wait a second here.
Derek doesn't like reporters.
Neither do I.
You ever heard of calling first?
Well, of course.
I'd try, but I just didn't
think you'd let me...
Well, you're right about that.
I just want to talk
to him, that's all.
We have something in common.
Here's something you
can have in common.
Derek isn't here,
so you make yourself
not here either.
You want to see Derek?
Check out the instant replay.
Yes ma'am.
♪♪♪
( Ey, hey, hey, Melvin,
h 'm here, I'm here. I
I am sorry, I am so, so sorry.
I had to do something for work,
and I had to finish, and i...
Why are you here?
The last ringer
called the office
and I came down
when I realized you
were her replacement.
What's going on with you, Bruce?
You didn't tell me you
knew Derek Jensen.
You're a sports guy.
I thought you knew his story.
Well, I need to get an
interview with him.
Derek doesn't do interviews
and his mother is not
fond of reporters.
Well, I do know that.
Look, I'm sorry about
the whole flour thing
and I'm sorry about
being so late.
I just...
You don't have to report
this to the judge, do you?
I'm not worried about
the assignment,
I'm worried about you.
I'm fine.
Really!
♪♪♪
Where is everybody?
Assignment meeting is over?
Yeah, it's just a slow
week with the holidays.
Here were you? W
I had to put an extra
hour in on the bells.
That's probably for the best.
Why is that for the best?
Well, we went over the ratings
for the last few weeks
nd they're up. A
that's good, right?
( Hat fact is, t.
Lesley's brought some fresh
air to the broadcast.
She's getting great feedback
from the young male
demographic and women.
And what does that mean for me?
My service hours
are almost done.
That whole video thing
should be over soon.
Bruce, I'm making the decision
not to put you back on
the live broadcast.
You're firing me?
No, you'd still be in the field.
A demotion.
Well, if you want to
look at it like that.
Well, how else could it look?
That's the business, Bruce.
I'm sorry.
♪♪♪
I heard from Kasey this morning.
She's coming home.
Great.
You got in late last night.
Mm-hmm, it was a bad night.
Oh, more bowling coverage?
Jim's taking me off the
sport's desk permanently.
Why would he do that?
Lesley's ratings are higher.
People like her better.
He's gonna put me on
field assignments.
( Ou have been therey
lmost 20 years. A.
I know, I know, but honey,
they have to do what's
best for the broadcast.
No, no, no, no!
This was fine when I
came home last night.
Who would do this?
They left a pretty big clue.
"Quitter"?
( Hat's this all about? W hat
does it mean, "quitter"? W
I'm sorry mom, I didn't think
they'd do anything like this.
These were your friends, Jason.
Not friends.
Obviously.
Eammates? t
not anymore.
You quit the basketball team.
That's what this is about.
And you didn't tell us?
I was only playing because
you wanted me to.
You love basketball!
I loved it before it was the
key to my entire future.
You have no idea what
it's like being your son.
What happened out front?
( Ason quitsj he
basketball teamt
and his friends wanted
to say, "thank you."
You quit? Why?
Because it's not fun anymore.
God forbid you have
to do something hard.
Oh, you wouldn't understand.
Oh really?
The team was mad about the loss,
or was it other kids at school?
The coach?
No, no, no, the question is
where have you been going
fter schoola f not to practice? I
it's none of your business.
Oh, as your parents it most
certainly is our business.
I'm not doing anything wrong.
( Ason? j
that went well.
Congratulations.
I can't imagine for what.
You were here 3
hours today, right?
Well, that's the end of
your community service.
I have to say,
I'm mighty proud of you
for sticking it out.
I wasn't sure at first.
Everything okay?
Well, let's see, I got
demoted from my work,
some teenagers trashed
my wife's dreams,
my daughter's getting
ready to sue the world,
and my son is... I don't know.
He quit his basketball team.
He's off somewhere,
he won't say,
every day doing who knows what.
( Wouldn't worry about Jason, i
ut you say he quit basketball? B
yeah, I don't get it.
Basketball's always
been everything to him.
Bruce, you have some time?
I want to show you something.
Get in.
So, you never been to
the kroc center, huh?
No, no, I never have.
Well, you're in for a surprise.
Well, we have church
here on Sundays.
This is a church?
On Sundays.
The rest of the week it's
community activities,
fine arts, and
educational classes.
Yeah, well, Jason's been
bugging me about church.
I don't get it.
Maybe you don't know
what you'd be missing.
Well, if I go, I'll
be missing sleep,
I'll be missing a lot of work.
Well, if you don't go,
you'll be missing
the opportunity
to be in the presence of god.
With all due respect, Melvin,
I'm really not interested.
Well, okay.
Let's take a little tour.
We got something here I know
you'll be interested in: Sports.
Alright.
Jason did his service
work for school here,
and when we needed help.
You know he didn't tell me?
Of course I didn't know it meant
that he quit his own team.
Hey, you're Bruce dalt,
Bruce dalt from the news.
For the win, right?
Yes, I am.
Was just taking a tour withi ajor
lowell of the kroc center. M
coach Jason says if
I work hard enough,
you'll interview
me on TV one day.
Really, you're that good, huh?
I've got some moves.
Here Andre, show him your stuff.
Ooh, pretty good!
What's your name?
Andre knight.
Andre knight, I think
I've heard of you.
Aybe that's just a name thatm
ounds like a star, you know? S
you better get out
there and practice
if you want to be a star.
Yes, sir.
You listen to your coach.
He knows what he's doing.
Alright guys, let's see some
hustle, hustle, hustle.
♪♪♪
He's a good kid.
He's better than me.
Just because your
service hours are over,
doesn't mean that you
have to stop giving.
What have you got for me?
Well, we always got something.
But I don't mean just here.
I mean at home and at work.
So you're not the star anymore.
So what?
Matthew 23:11,
Jesus says if you want to be
truly great in his kingdom,
then you got to be
the servant of all.
"Humble yourself to the lord,
and he will lift you up."
Then you are a pretty
great man, Melvin.
And you should give it a try.
♪♪♪
I should have told you, I know.
You know, I am
really proud of you
for choosing to work
with those kids,
but why wouldn't you tell me?
Why would you hide it?
I don't know.
I mean, I guess I was worried
ou were gonnay ry
and convince met
not to quit the team.
Or worse, you'd
try and take over
and teach me how to
coach them for the win.
Well, it already looks to
me like they are winning.
It's fun, dad.
Why did you have to quit
the school team to do it?
You made a commitment
to coach Larry,
to the rest of the guys.
( Ith the kids, it feels likew
'm doing something worthwhile. I
but with the team and the guys,
it's just not fun
anymore, for me or them.
Because of what I did.
Anyway, I wasn't gonna
get a scholarship,
and volunteer work looks just as
good on a college application.
It's okay to change
your priorities,
but Jason, you are
not a quitter.
No, I'm not, but I
can't go back now.
If they didn't want
you on that team,
why are they so doggone
mad about you quitting?
You should come watch the
kids practice again tomorrow.
I think it really inspired them.
Well, actually, I am ringing
bells again tomorrow.
I thought you finished
your community service?
I did.
♪♪♪
My attorney thought
you were done.
Done with my hours.
Not done helping out.
They still have a lot
of people to feed.
By the way,
did you get the check for
your medical bills yet?
Yeah, thanks.
Are they gonna let you
back on the air now?
Actually, no.
That's too bad.
You know, besides that
ridiculous ref thing,
I actually thought you
were pretty good.
My kids think you're
really funny.
Hey, you've been
going by this kettle
every day I've been here.
Right.
Merry Christmas.
I'm here at the starting line
at the annual lake
Michigan reindeer run.
Now, normally you would
see excited faces
and runners warming up,
but as you can see, there is...
Whoa, nothing warm
about this morning.
Reindeer run officials ave
canceled this year's raceh
due to the weather.
'M Bruce dalt, action 8
sports, i or the win. F
it's an official demotion
when you're sent out to
interview the storm, isn't it?
I gotta admit, Bruce.
You handled this a lot better
than I thought you would.
The storm doesn't usually
give interviews.
I had to work an angle
to get that one for you.
( Kay, so is thiso
bout my decisiona
to keep Lesley on the broadcast?
Actually, I was wondering
if I could have Chad
and a camera for a
couple of hours.
Sure. What are you up to?
Defense, defense, defense.
Fast feet.
All right, go. Find
your open man.
There you go, there
you go, guys.
Be alive. Be alive.
Come on, I want your arms out.
Excuse me, coach, I'm here for
an interview with the team.
All right, guys, take a break.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Hey, Andre, got a
minute for the press?
Ready?
I'm standing here
with Andre knight,
superstar of the grand rapids...
Jaguars.
Sounds fast.
Andre knight of the
grand rapids jaguars.
Now, Andre, you're going up
against the pistons tonight.
How do you think the jaguars
are going to measure up?
Well, Bruce, we've got
hunter on the post
and he can rebound
all the baskets
the pistons are gonna miss.
And we've got shooting
sensation, number 44,
Taylor mccovey, and
the rest of the team.
We've been training
hard in the pre-season,
and we're ready to take it to
the championship this year.
Well, it's truly a
formidable team,
strong on offense and defense.
Well, we're looking
forward to the match-up.
Good luck tonight, fellas.
Thanks, Bruce.
Oh, oh, wait. Don't cut yet.
Do the thing.
What?
♪♪♪
This is Bruce dalt, action
8 sports, for the win.
All right, guys, get lost.
Go, go, go.
Come on, guys. Get out of here.
Now, what about your own team?
♪♪♪
Jason, we're glad to
have you back today.
And we have a special guest.
Hey coach Larry, boys.
Mr. Dalt is here
with my permission,
so let's show him our
respect, please.
I want to apologize to you
for my bad temper in the
game the other night.
I was caught up in
the wrong things.
You guys were playing
a heck of a game,
despite the efforts of my new
best friend, the referee.
I'm sorry I messed it up.
You lost us the game.
It's true.
Let me ask you something.
If one of you guys got
a technical foul,
what would happen?
We'd have to run ten suicides.
And if you boys lost a game,
how would you start
the next practice?
We'd run ten suicide lines.
Yeah, 10 plus 10, that's 20.
Who wants to count
'em out for me?
I will.
Then let's get to it.
♪♪♪
Come on, put some
muscle into it, pop.
Okay, tiger. I'm coming.
Where's that "for
the win" attitude?
Listen to you.
Come on, slowpokes.
♪♪♪
( Ow you doing? H
hello, how are you?
Here you go, sir.
Merry Christmas. God
bless you, sir.
Thank you.
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
- See you at the gym.
- Looking forward to it.
( Oach, coach, wait. C
thank you, coach.
My pleasure, little man.
♪♪♪
( Wish they couldi
ll go like that, a
but then there's too many.
Thanks for making an exception.
While we're in
this neighborhood,
there's another family I
want us to drop in on.
♪♪♪
Melvin, I don't think
this is a good idea.
Why? Where are we?
♪♪♪
Major lowell, merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
What are you doing here?
My friends and I were out
delivering Christmas boxes
and I wanted them to meet Derek.
As in, the heisman trophy guy?
Derek doesn't want to
talk to any reporters.
He's not a reporter today.
He and his son
were volunteering.
Volunteering because they knew
you would bring them by here?
Well, actually, he's been on
bells for the whole month,
and he was there for
basket-packing day
and for basket delivery.
( Didn't know melvini as
gonna bring us here, w
I promise you.
Mom, what's going on, mom?
Major lowell.
What's going on, sir?
How you doing, man?
Why are you out in the cold?
Mom, would you invite
him in, please?
Come on, man. Come on,
it's cold out there.
You have to excuse my mother.
♪♪♪
Derek, this man is a reporter.
But he's out on my business
today, not his own.
( Understand. i
you don't do interviews.
'M not askingi or anything. F
wait a minute, you're the
"for the win" guy, right?
Yeah, Bruce dalt.
Oh, man.
I saw the YouTube videos, man.
Both of 'em.
And you, you're the
shooter, right?
You play ball?
Yeah.
You were totally
behind that line.
That was 3 points for sure, man.
I mean, I don't even
play basketball,
but anybody could see that.
Thanks, man.
Listen, mom, you should have
seen this ridiculous call.
You would have flipped out, too.
( Hen it's your kid, you kind
ofw ose perspective, right? L.
Look, she's a nut.
Listen, this one game,
this referee kept calling
interference on me.
This woman, my mother,
stood outside of the
referee's locker room door
after the game.
I just felt that he needed
someone to lovingly remind him
that his optometrist
appointment was overdue.
Well, I doubt if it was
all that loving, mom.
Well, we all get a little crazy
when it comes to our
kids, don't we?
We do.
And when your kid is
as special as yours,
well, you want to protect him.
Derek, I'm curious.
Why don't you do interviews?
Lights and cameras,
they make me nervous.
I lock up.
There are lights and
cameras at games.
Yeah, but it's different.
Look, after everything my
family's been through,
I'd just like to
keep it private.
But maybe your story will
help encourage some kid
who's going through what you
went through years ago.
( Elvin, Melvin, it's okay. M
I mean, that's not the reason
we came here, right Jason?
We've seen what happens
when people get out there
and talk about
what they believe.
They get crucified.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
So major lowell, what do
you think I should do?
Do you think I should
do these interviews?
I'm not ashamed of
what I believe.
Of course you're not ashamed.
I just think that
you have a platform
that offers people hope.
Maybe you should use it.
You don't have to be a preacher.
I don't know.
I don't want to come off
like a holy roller.
Bruce, what do you think?
Well, I can see that your
faith is very real to you.
If others see it, too,
I really think
they'll understand.
♪♪♪
Hey.
I have no idea how you
scored this, Bruce.
I gotta tell you,
I tried every angle
I could think of,
and nobody would let
me through to the guy.
This angle is unexpected.
And why isn't Jim letting
you do the interview?
That doesn't really
matter right now.
Listen to me.
He's nervous about the cameras,
and he's gonna shut
down completely
if you ask him too
directly about himself.
If you really want
to get him to talk,
ask him about Christmas.
This is a serious sports
interview, an exclusive.
The entire nation is
gonna be watching.
Trust me on this.
Christmas.
Esley, we're ready for you. L
♪♪♪
Thanks for being here, Derek.
We're honored.
We're gonna let you and
Lesley have a conversation.
Just forget we're
here, all right?
You're gonna be great.
We'll shoot your wraps
when he's done.
If you would have pushed,
I'd probably have let
you do this interview.
I know.
I'm enjoying Lesley's
paranoia just a little bit.
Chad?
Okay, Lesley. Three, two, one.
Derek, you've had an
amazing run this year.
Everyone is still talking
about that 80-yard touchdown
at Thanksgiving weekend.
Thank you, ma'am.
Did you ever expect to be
such a star at this level?
I'm not a star.
Well, many people would
argue with that.
Look, I just catch a
ball and run, you know?
Play the game.
For the heisman trophy.
You are the first player
from central Michigan
who's ever done that.
Don't you consider that
quite an accomplishment?
Sure.
Maybe Derek doesn't
like doing interviews
because he's a lousy interview.
Be patient.
Christmas.
Anybody can see what's
happening on the field.
Maybe we should talk about
what's happening
behind the scenes?
Ou're home with youry
amily for Christmas. F
what are some traditions
you have with your family?
Well...
Well, Christmas is a great
time of year for my family.
I mean, we always help out
with the salvation
army gift center,
and we do it every year.
I mean, we never miss it.
You know, we also
help distribute
some of the food boxes, as well.
And why is that so
important to you?
That's how I got my start.
In football?
In life.
You know, I'll never forget it.
I was about 6 years old.
My mom, she got hurt on the
job, so she couldn't work.
Me and my brothers,
we didn't think we'd have
much of a Christmas at all,
but one day, these two guys
in funny-looking uniforms,
they came to our porch
and they had these big
boxes of food and Turkey
and those potatoes in a box,
which I thought tasted
like cardboard,
but I still liked 'em, you know?
It was a feast.
Then these guys gave
us some presents.
They were wrapped up
in these big bows.
I'll never forget
what they told us.
They said that, "it's
because Jesus loves us."
That's why we're giving
you this stuff."
Every year after that, when
we started to do better,
we made sure we helped
other kids get those boxes
with those big bows.
What was it?
What was in your box?
It was a football.
You know, that day,
I learned everything I
ever needed to know,
that god loves me
and I can catch a ball.
♪ He rules the world
with truth and grace ♪
♪ And makes the nations prove ♪
♪ The glories of his
righteousness ♪
♪ And wonders of his love
♪ and wonders of his love
♪ and wonders, wonders
of his love ♪♪
Thank you for reflecting
with us tonight.
May his hope and
peace be with you.
Merry Christmas.
♪♪♪
Oh, that Melvin.
Melvin.
Bruce, glad you finally made it.
You were right.
I didn't know what I was
missing, but I do now.
( Hat was a great interview. T
thank you.
You know, we've gotten
a lot of inquiries
from people this week
about volunteering.
Well, Derek is a
good role model,
even for someone like me.
This is our daughter, Kasey.
- Hi.
- Melvin lowell.
- Merry Christmas.
( 'M Mrs. Roberta lowell. I
- hi, merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas.
Oh, excuse me.
Ah, it's my boss.
- Oh, take it.
- Excuse me.
Hello?
Hey, Bruce.
Sorry to call you
on Christmas Eve.
I just wanted to make sure
you're still in town.
Can you come in on the 26th?
What's going on?
There's not much to cover
the day after Christmas.
No, I need you on the air.
I guess Lesley had applied
to the affiliate in Atlanta,
and when they saw her
interview with Derek,
they asked her to
come right away.
So are you around?
Can you come in for us?
What, for a week?
No, no, for good.
I really appreciate the
way you hung in there
with all those bum assignments.
I wouldn't ask
anyone else but you.
Of course.
I'll be there.
Thanks, Bruce.
Merry Christmas.
♪♪♪
Okay.
Aw, more doilies from
great grandma Rose.
( Ow we have a set. N.
( Erfect, perfect. P
h, it's your turn. O.
( Hat do you mean, w y turn? M
- dad's.
- What?
- This one's for you, dad.
- Oh, I'm excited.
This one's for you.
( Onder what this could be? W
it's not labeled.
It's yours.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- Okay.
Okay...
Very, very funny.
Who's gonna 'fess up
for this one, huh?
- Nope, Santa claus.
- Exactly.
Oh, wanna get it?
Who's up at this time of day?
It's cold outside.
It's Christmas.
It's the gages.
Look who's here.
- Merry Christmas.
( Ow, thank you. W ookies? C
fruitcake.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, we wanted to
let you guys know
that we weren't the ones that
ruined your decorations.
Oh, we know. Don't
worry about it.
And we sure do love what
you did with it instead.
♪♪♪
- You didn't do this?
- No.
♪♪♪
I have a guess.
Well, you didn't do
this all by yourself?
There were some guilty
basketball players
that were easy to recruit.
It's really, really beautiful.
Thank yo.
- Merry Christmas.
♪♪♪
It's great. Thank, you, Jason.
Check it out.
♪♪♪