People are throwing colored powder
and buckets of water at each other...
and I keep getting hit in the face
with this stuff.
So at this point, I must look like
some kind of crazy clown.
And all the while, we're trying to carry on
this incredibly serious discussion...
about antique furniture.
And he's telling me about this piece that
he's found that he thinks I might like.
And then, out of nowhere, he says...
I'm pregnant.
Seriously?
It is beautiful.
It's crazy.
Baby, I don't want to go back.
What if we stayed here?
Started a family here.
Are you serious?
Why not?
I'm going to have to come three times
a year to source antiques anyway.
What's to keep us from
setting up our base here?
What do you think?
I don't know.
This yours?
Hey.
What are you saying?
I'm asking her if you and I
should stay here forever.
How can you sleep?
So peacefully!
Sweetheart, stop. Stop.
It's okay, it's okay, I'm here.
It's okay.
Stop it, stop it.
I'm here, I'm here. It's okay.
I got you. It's okay, I got you.
Winston, come on.
Winston.
Good boy! Good boy.
Come on, boy.
Come on, Winston.
Lucy.
Come on.
Morning, sweetheart.
- Morning.
- How did you sleep?
Good.
Morning, Piki.
Morning, sir.
Michael.
Yeah, what's up?
I am...
Hey, you don't have to say anything, okay?
I'm lost, Michael.
I don't know if I can live with it.
We're going to be fine.
We'll get through this.
Maria?
Hello?
Mrs. Harwood
retired early for the night, sir.
She had a migraine.
I put Lucy to bed.
Right.
Okay.
'Night, sir.
Night-night, Piki.
Those are F and G fingers.
F and G fingers.
Wrists up like there's an orange.
And a one, two,
a one, two, three, four!
What?
Yeah!
Well done.
A bunch of scribbles.
You guys are fantastic!
Was that really you playing?
It was too good. You sure it wasn't Mommy?
No.
You're telling me it was
really you playing?
That's basically it.
- Can't believe it! My children are geniuses.
- Yeah.
- I'm so proud of you both.
- They worked on it all day just for you.
Happy Father's Day.
We're going to get through this.
Maria?
Maria!
Maria! Open your eyes, sweetheart.
Can you hear me? Maria?
I need you to listen to my voice, please.
Sweetheart, I need you to focus, okay?
I need you to fight this. Please!
Maria, I can't live without you.
Mommy!
Please help me.
Mommy! Mommy!
Mommy, I can't get free!
My leg's stuck!
Luce?
Lucy. No, no, no.
Lucy, please wake up, baby.
- Mommy, get me out!
- Lucy, please wake up!
No, no, no!
Mommy, I can't get free! It hurts!
Please get me out!
Okay, okay.
Please wake up.
I'm scared!
I know you're scared!
I'm scared, too! Pull!
Okay? Oliver, come on.
I don't care if it hurts, you have to pull.
You have to pull!
I know it hurts. You have to pull.
Keep your nose up.
Keep your nose all the way up.
Keep your nose on the ceiling.
We're all going to be okay.
Okay. Okay.
Baby.
I don't know what to do.
Please don't leave me!
I'm sorry, baby.
Mommy!
We need help! Please.
Please, somebody!
We need help!
My boy's in the car!
My boy's in the car! Please!
No! No! My boy!
Ollie!
No, my boy's in the car!
We need to get my boy!
Ollie!
Michael.
Yeah.
She's going to be fine.
But she took a lot of pills.
You are in Bombay Hospital.
Where's Michael?
He's talking to the doctor.
You are lucky to be alive, Mrs. Harwood.
I just can't bear life without him.
I had a daughter once.
Anushka.
She fell into a pond while
trying to pick some plants.
I was looking away for only one minute.
What if I could bring your son
back to you just one more time?
What if I could give you the chance
to say your final goodbye?
What are you talking about?
I was born in a village in South India.
Surrounding our village
was a big forest.
And deep within this forest...
there was an abandoned temple.
It is said that the line between
the world of the dead and the living...
is very thin at this place.
You should go there.
Take the ashes of your son...
spread them on the steps
of this temple...
lock yourself inside...
and when night comes...
he will come to you.
And you will be able to talk to him
through the door of the temple...
say your final goodbye.
I will leave you two alone.
I was so scared I lost you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
Come on.
Come on, boy.
If we do this...
you have to promise me one thing.
When Oliver comes to you at the temple,
you will be able to speak to him.
But no matter what you do...
no matter what he says
or how much ever he pleads...
you must not open the door.
Promise me.
I promise.
It has been too long.
Let me go.
Khan.
They are the Aghori.
They live by the cremation sites.
They cover themselves in the ashes...
and they feed off the flesh of the dead.
For they believe it helps them communicate
with the other side.
My village is the last stop,
then follow my instructions.
God, Michael.
I will give him your note.
No, he's going to be frantic,
and Lucy needs to know where I am.
I will take care of everything.
Dear Michael, please don't be worried.
I'm just taking a couple of days
to sort my head out.
I desperately want to find a way
to move on...
so that we can be a family again.
I love you and Lucy so, so much.
Be home soon. Maria.
I love you so much.
Who's there?
Oliver?
Who are you?
Mommy?
Mommy, is that you?
Oliver, it's Mommy. Can you hear me?
Yes.
Yes, I can hear you.
Where am I, Mommy?
Baby, press yourself close.
Come up right against the door
and press yourself close...
so we can be close together, okay?
Are you there?
Yes, Mommy.
Oliver, I miss you.
I miss you so much, baby.
You know I love you, right?
More than life itself.
I miss you, too.
I miss Daddy and Lucy.
Oliver, Momma has something to tell you.
I came here because
I wanted to say that I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for leaving you.
It wasn't your fault.
I love you, Mommy.
Baby, I think about you day and night.
I wish I could hold you in my arms.
The door won't open.
I can't get in.
I know, baby.
I'm not allowed to let you in.
It's dark out here. I want to come in.
I'm sorry. I can't do it.
Please, Mommy, open the door.
I want to hug you.
It's okay, baby.
It's okay to cry. Mommy's crying, too.
I have to go now, Mommy.
What?
I have to go back now, Mommy.
No!
No, you just got here.
No, please. Baby, no, don't go.
Don't go. I just want
a few more minutes, okay?
Just a few more minutes, baby.
Please. Please, Oliver!
Where are you?
Ollie?
Oliver!
I love you, baby.
Maria?
Maria.
There's nobody out here.
Quiet! Buddy, what's wrong with you?
Relax.
Are you all right?
Hey, sweetheart. What are you doing up?
Is Mommy home?
No, not yet. She will be soon.
Let's get you back to bed. Come on.
How much tea would you like?
The whole glass.
That's not how
you're supposed to drink tea.
You're supposed to drink tea like this.
Khan?
Where did you come from?
Mommy!
Hello.
I missed you so much.
I missed you, too.
Stop it! That tickles!
Lucy, let's get Winston a snack.
- Come.
- Come on, Winston.
Come.
I was worried sick. Where were you?
I was trying to get better.
You couldn't have...
We would have come with you.
I know, I know.
Hey, I'm back.
I'm really back. I'm back for you.
I'm back for Lucy.
What's going on?
It's okay, it's okay. It's just Winston.
I got him.
Come on, you.
Go to bed. Go to bed.
Momma's here now.
Miss Lucy?
Where are you?
Ooh, ooh, my name is
L-I L-I chicka-ni chicka-ni
L-I L-I chicka...
Hello, Mommy.
What you doing in here, Luce?
Just playing with my dolls.
And who were you talking to?
Just my dolls.
Okay.
Well, you know that Momma doesn't like
people playing up here, right?
So how about we go back downstairs?
Okay, Mommy.
Scoot, scoot, scoot.
Mommy, are you coming?
Yeah, I'll be right there, babe.
Miss Lucy, that sounds...
Hey, Luce, where did you get Khan?
Hey.
Hey, look at me, Luce.
I have something to show you,
but it's a secret.
Lucy, I need you to tell me
where you got the tiger, okay?
Did Piki give him to you?
Look, Mommy.
Lucy, please stop.
Lucy.
Lucy, I need to talk to you about...
Oliver's come back, Mommy.
Nighty-night, sleep you tight.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
You won't tell Daddy, will you?
About Oliver.
Why do you say that, love?
I think Oliver's hiding.
Who's he hiding from?
He doesn't want to tell me.
Just don't tell Daddy.
Well, what if we wait until
Oliver's ready to tell him?
Promise?
Yeah, I promise.
Get some sleep.
I love you.
Good night.
Sleep tight.
And don't let the bedbugs bite.
Okay.
Okay, let's see where we left off.
"Directly in front of him...
"holding on by a low branch...
"stood a naked brown baby
who could just barely walk...
"as soft and as dimpled a little atom
as ever came to a wolf's cave at night."
Hey, sweetheart.
I was just coming to find you.
Did I miss saying good night to Luce?
It's okay.
I kissed her good night for you.
Okay.
Sorry I was late.
It's okay.
Are you all right? You're trembling.
I don't know.
What's going on?
No, I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm good.
I'm really, really good.
Good.
Hello.
Hello?
Oliver, where are you?
What's going on? What happened?
What happened, baby?
Are you all right?
It's a dream. Just a dream.
- Sorry.
- Are you okay?
Yeah.
Mommy!
What is it, baby?
Chil and Bill are dead.
What?
Oh, no, I'm so sorry.
The gardener found all the fish
dead in the pond.
And all the plants are dying.
Can we bury Chil and Bill in the sea?
In the sea?
Piki said people in India
get buried in the sea.
Of course. Yes, we can.
How about you go get something
to bury them in?
You should have worn white.
I wore a white scarf. That's not enough?
No.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to be rude
to Chil and Bill.
It's a good spot right here.
Bye-bye, Chil. Bye-bye, Bill.
Mommy, who's that man?
It's all right, baby. He's far away.
Not that man, Mommy!
That man!
Why did that man put ash on your face?
I don't know, love.
Did I get it all?
Yeah, you got it.
Yeah?
Luce stay behind me.
Oliver?
Oliver, do you want to play?
Are you coming out to play, Stanley?
I can't.
Someone painted the wall pink...
I got the blame.
Detective Calamity at your service, sir.
Do we have any clues?
He did it! He did it!
What is it, Winston?
Sounds like you need a detective.
Look at you. Right where you belong.
Okay, baby girl.
Let's get those nits out.
I don't have nits.
Nits like clean hair. Daddy told me.
Okay, well, then you certainly
don't have them, Grumpy-stiltskin.
Turn around.
Come on, come on, come on.
Lucy, what happened to your shoulder?
I don't think I like Oliver anymore.
He's mean.
Oliver, I saw those bite marks on Lucy.
You can't hurt your sister, all right?
I said "no".
Oliver, you let me out.
Okay.
I'll read to you.
As long as you promise
not to hurt Lucy again.
Will you promise me?
"Shere Khan moved through the forest.
"He heard the thunder of their hooves,
and lumbered down the ravine...
"looking from side to side
for any way of escape."
Hello?
Hey, darling.
How was your day?
Did you have fun with Luce?
Yeah, I just put her to bed.
Okay.
I'm really sorry, but I've got to be here
for a couple more hours.
Shall I ask Piki to keep something warm
for you or are you going to eat there?
No, it's okay.
I'm just going to grab something here.
But I just wanted to tell you
that I miss you.
I miss you, too.
All right. I love you.
Give Luce a kiss for me.
Will do. Love you, too.
Bye.
Oliver?
I see you there.
I'll call the police!
Go on!
Go. Go!
Get out! Get out of my house!
You have no idea what you have done.
Did you think that you could bring back
somebody from the world of the dead...
and they would be the same?
Did you think there would be
no consequences?
I don't understand.
Hindus believe in the purification
and reincarnation of the soul.
That can never happen to Oliver now...
because he has returned to this life.
Instead, his soul will putrefy.
You have seen her, haven't you?
Myrtu.
She is getting closer to this world
every day.
When you opened the door, you upset
the balance between life and death...
and you awoke her.
She is the gatekeeper of the underworld.
She is here to take Oliver back
to the world of the dead.
And she will destroy anything
that comes in her way.
Oliver is no longer your son,
Mrs. Harwood.
Do you understand what I am telling you?
He is evil.
Burn every possession of his.
Destroy every photograph.
Get rid of anything which is
an anchor for him to this life...
and pray that he will return
to the world of the dead.
You are out of your mind.
I should never have told you
about the temple!
I thought I was trying to help you.
Lucy?
Baby.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Lucy?
Mommy.
You woke me up.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Come on. I've got to get dry.
I just think it would be
a really good idea.
I can't remember the last time
Lucy saw her cousins.
I know.
It would be amazing.
I would love that.
I'm just not sure it's the best timing
for business, but...
You are always saying that
you never have any time to relax.
You know, she's got a month
before she starts school...
and we haven't been to the States
for so long.
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
Yeah? You seem kind of flushed.
I'm just coming down with something.
Luce!
Luce?
Lucy?
- Luce?
- Lucy?
Lucy!
I'll go look for her out front.
Luce?
Lucy?
Mommy!
Lucy!
Luce!
Mommy!
Lucy!
Maria!
Hey.
Michael! Where were you?
She was just out front.
I tried to tell you, but you'd run off.
I couldn't find you.
I know you're there.
Oliver, stop it!
Amma.
Anushka?
Look, Mommy. It's Oliver's book.
Thank you.
What is this?
I'm not sure.
Maria? Maria!
Michael!
What?
Lucy, come here.
Stay there.
- I got you. It's okay.
- What is it, Mommy?
It's okay.
"And when the drawbridge closed
with a bang...
"all the people were safe inside.
"And deep in the dark forest
the dragon curled up in a heap...
"and went to sleep."
I think you can curl up in a heap
and go to sleep now.
You don't think that Oliver
did that to Piki, do you?
No.
No, I think what happened to Piki
was just a terrible, terrible accident.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am.
Now, how about you hop into bed?
Been a long day, little one.
Can Winston sleep with me tonight?
I suppose that's a yes, isn't it?
Do not hog all the bed.
Have sweet dreams. I love you.
Is Piki in heaven now?
I think so, yes.
Why isn't Oliver in heaven?
It's time for bed, sweet girl.
I'll see you in the morning.
Lucy?
Baby, are you all right?
Luce?
Lucy.
Lucy?
Luce!
Lucy!
Luce?
Are you in here?
Baby, are you hiding from...
No, no, no.
No, no!
Lucy?
Luce.
Oh, my God, sweet girl. You scared me.
So much.
What are you doing out here, baby?
I wanted to feel the wind on my skin.
It tickles.
Okay.
Okay, come on, let's go to bed.
Hey, guys. What's going on?
Daddy!
Hey, you.
What are you doing out here
so late, pumpkin?
I think
she might have been sleepwalking.
I missed you, Daddy.
I missed you, too, sweetheart.
How about we get you back to bed?
Come on.
I love you, Daddy.
I love you, too...
What...
What?
- Michael.
- No, no, no.
Michael.
No. No!
It's got to burn. It's got to burn.
What? Why?
Because Oliver came back.
What?
Oliver came back,
and I think he killed Piki.
Because she tried to burn
all of his things to send him back...
because he's not our boy anymore.
Stop.
Darling, stop.
I know it sounds absolutely crazy,
but it's true.
Right, Luce? Right?
I don't know
what you're talking about, Mommy.
No, no, baby, it's okay. It's okay.
We can tell Daddy now.
Tell him about your brother.
Tell him about the piano.
I don't know what you're saying.
Oliver's dead.
Luce, I don't know why you're doing this
right now, okay?
But you need to
tell your father the truth.
You need to tell him.
I don't know what you mean, Mommy.
Lucy, you have to tell him!
Enough! Enough!
You're scaring her.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, but...
It's all right.
Let's get you to bed, sweetheart.
All right.
You feel better, poppet?
Now that you're here, Daddy.
You sleep well, okay? I love you.
I love you, too.
Lucy, please tell Daddy about Oliver.
Maria, sweetheart,
you're not thinking straight.
- Can we talk about this downstairs?
- I'm not making it up.
I understand you don't think
you're making it up, but I...
What?
Oliver, what have you done?
Maria?
He's possessed her.
Maria, would you listen to yourself?
No, no, no!
Oliver?
Maria.
We can be together again.
You leave your sister alone!
Daddy, I'm scared!
Stop!
Come here, sweetheart.
It's going to be all right.
Michael.
You need help.
I'm going to get you the help you need,
and everything is going to be okay.
Okay. Are you all right, sweetheart?
Mommy was hurting me.
No, no.
Mommy's just not herself right now.
But she loves you very much.
And so do I.
Where are we going?
We're going on a little adventure.
What do you want?
Okay.
Just stay here. I'm going to make
a quick call, okay, sweetheart?
Everything's going to be fine.
Okay.
Come on.
Hello. Hi.
Yes, okay, my address is Dobra Villa,
satrah, Carter Road, in Bandra.
Yes, there's a group of men
outside my house...
and I think they're trying to break in
and get my daughter...
I'm not sure,
but I need help immediately.
Bad dog.
Yes. Yes.
As fast as you can.
Quiet.
I don't know, but they're naked almost.
Okay, please hurry. Yes.
Lucy, what...
Oh, my God. Baby.
What did you do?
Winston was being naughty.
So I had to teach him a lesson.
You're not going to be naughty
as well...
are you, Daddy?
No!
It's just Mommy and me now.
I'm sorry, Daddy.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
You're making a mess
all over the kitchen floor.
Mommy will be mad.
Lucy, what are you doing?
I'm not Lucy. I'm Oliver.
No.
But I am!
Michael?
Michael.
Oliver!
Help me, Mommy!
Leave her alone!
Lucy!
- Mommy.
- Lucy!
Baby!
Luce!
Lucy!
No!
Oliver, you leave Lucy
and you come to me.
You come to me. Do you hear me?
I don't want to go back.
I know. I know. But I'll go with you.
All right?
You'll be safe. You're safe.
I've got you. I've got you.
Take me instead.
No!
No! No!
Maria!
No!
Let me go!
Mommy!
Maria?
Michael?
Maria, can you hear me?
Michael, where are you?
I'm right here, sweetheart.
I can't believe I can hear your voice.
Sweetheart?
Maria?
Can you hear me?
Darling, please, I need to see you.
- Michael?
- Please, where are you?
- No.
- Sweetheart, can you hear me?
No.
- Please, I need to see you.
- Michael.
I need to see your face.
No!