(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
SUSAN: Excuse me, Paul.
PAUL: Mmm-hmm.
I canceled
all the patients,
like you asked me to.
But, uh,
you're so backed up
that I had to
reschedule some of them
in the evening next week.
(SIGHS)
It doesn't matter.
Paul, are you
all right?
You've been listening
to that for hours.
It's my favorite
Bach concerto.
Look, why don't
we go out and get
something to eat?
Maybe go to a movie?
You haven't eaten
anything all day.
Paul?
Here. This is for you.
What is it?
It's your
letter of recommendation
to work at the Institute.
They're looking
for a good nurse.
Dr. Quilly's Institute.
It's a fantastic
opportunity for
you, Susan.
Dr. Magnus Quilly
is a legend.
His work
with schizophrenics
is revolutionary.
Well, I know, but...
But you're just as good,
and I wanna work with you.
The Institute is too far away.
We wouldn't be able to see
each other. How would we...
No! No! Stop, Susan!
Susan, I'm sorry.
It's just that I...
I can't do this anymore.
You can't do what?
Nothing makes any sense.
(SIGHS)
Maybe you should
see a psychiatrist.
I want you to leave.
I was just kidding.
Paul. Did I
do something...
It's got nothing
to do with you!
Damn it, Susan,
please, just leave!
Paul, I love you.
Don't you know that?
I love you!
Are you gonna leave,
or do I have to
throw you out?
Oh, Paul, just talk to me.
Please, just tell me...
You've got to leave!
Paul, don't!
Let go of my... Paul!
(DOOR SLAMS)
Paul! Paul, open the door!
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Paul, please, please,
open the door!
Paul!
(GUN FIRES)
No! Paul!
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Paul, please!
(SOBBING)
No! Paul!
Paul!
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
Fairfield County, ma'am.
(KNOCK AT WINDOW)
Hmm?
Hi.
I'm Susan Manning.
I hope you're
here to meet me.
Yes.
Good.
Hop in.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
You know I thought
it was gonna rain.
Ah, the weather
changes pretty fast
in these parts.
It's hot.
Yup.
So, you're the new nurse.
If Dr. Quilly approves
my credentials.
Oh, he will.
Why is that?
It's not easy to get
new nurses way up here.
Oh.
Miss Manning?
Yes.
Come with me.
So, how many patients
do you have here?
No patients here.
What?
Guests.
Yes. Well, are you
one of the...
I'm Jones,
head of security.
Don't let my title bother you.
I'm here for safety,
both guests and staff.
We do have rules.
You will let me know
of any violators.
I am responsible.
Of course.
It's good to have
a cooperative nurse
this time.
Ms. Donnymead will
show you around.
Who?
Ms. Donnymead.
Administrative assistant
to Dr. Quilly.
At least, she likes
to be called that.
People like titles
around here.
You mean, like, um,
head of security?
(EXCLAIMS)
You're lovely,
Miss Manning!
But then the
superintendent, Dr. Quilly,
said you would be.
He claims to
have an intuition
about phone voices.
Ms. Donnymead's
affection for Dr. Quilly
gets out of hands sometimes.
Thank you, Mr. Jones.
We'll meet you
in the games room.
Come with me.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
This is our games room.
Guests, this is
Nurse Manning,
and she's come by
to say hello.
Hello. Thank you.
I look forward to
the opportunity of
getting to know
all of you better.
Make yourself comfortable
and I'll be back as soon
as Dr. Quilly is ready.
(IMITATES ENGINE REVVING)
Oh! Good morning.
No time to
chitchat, Nurse.
The world Olympics
are soon gonna be upon us.
Hello.
Hi.
This is an exact replica
of the Fokker 33A.
I made these.
This little Fokker
is the same plane
that Baron Von Richtofen flew
and was shot down in
June 17th, 1918.
Would you like to see it fly?
Sure.
And, look,
I even made a little
pilot to go inside.
That's very nice.
Very nice.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
...and through a
field of roses to a
many towered Camelot.
You're a poet.
No. It's a voice exercise.
Oh.
But I am a poet.
I just love
those hydrangeas.
You know that you
can make them pink
or blue or white
just depending on
what plant food
you give them.
It's just
such fun to...
Hello, ladies.
The man with
the baseball cap,
is he a patient?
I mean, a guest.
Oh, no. No, that's
Dr. Desmond Moore.
He's more or less
second in command
to Dr. Quilly.
He's an angel.
He's an Adonis.
But he's very professional.
When I think
about him I get wet.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Dr. Quilly, this
is Susan Manning.
Of course.
Welcome, welcome!
I'm so happy
you found us.
Thank you, Doctor.
Won't you sit down?
How about a
nice cup of tea?
Oh, please.
Ms. Donnymead,
would you be kind?
Again, Miss Manning,
my condolences
on your loss.
Oh, I appreciate
that, Doctor.
I think it's
almost an obscenity
for a psychiatrist
to commit suicide.
Why any more
than anyone else?
Because of our
responsibilities.
Can you imagine the
effect of a suicide on
a doctor's patients?
Yes.
(GRUNTS)
Not now, Henry.
I'm busy.
He's a brilliant
make-up man.
Quite comfortable
to play anybody
but himself.
Have you kept
in touch with your
family and your friends?
That can be a
comfort, you know?
No. I really wanted
to get my life
organized first.
I have my
credentials here.
Oh, there's no
real need for that.
Here at the Institute
we believe people are
who they say they are.
Now, Nurse, if you
are to be with us
I must ask that
you put aside any
preconditioned attitudes
you may have
as to the treatment
of the insane.
Oh, Dr. Quilly, a man
with your reputation doesn't
have to explain originality.
Well, our theories
are deceptively simple.
Our guests...
Well, they have fantasies
that are not accepted
in the so-called
outside, real, sane world.
But here, under extreme
controlled situations,
we allow them to
act out their fantasies
as if they were
totally sane.
Yes. I met some of
your guests earlier.
And we have found
that if they get to
exercise these fantasies,
after a time they
no longer need them.
Now, I realize
that takes a while,
but there are no
sudden therapies
for the mad,
so here
at the Institute
no one is mad.
Uh, would you
be willing to
dress as a nurse?
That's your prerogative.
I really want
this opportunity.
Then I take it,
Miss Manning,
that you are prepared
to commit to the Institute
and all its values?
Not only to the Institute,
but to all its people.
Ah!
Now I really believe
you understand us.
However, I will
need a commitment.
Your commitment.
You have it.
Done and done.
There is, I'm afraid,
some boring paper work.
Your withholding thing,
your RN registration number
and more ad nauseam.
Such a gigantic bureaucracy
for such a small formality.
It's just as bad at home.
Ms. Donnymead will fill in
all the details
from that letter you sent us.
Why don't you just sign here?
Ms. Donnymead's
swamped with paper work.
I can't tell you
how excited I am.
Uh, do you have
a phone that I could use?
Collect, of course.
I want to call my family
and tell them I'm all right,
very all right,
productive again.
I'm sorry,
I'm afraid we
cannot have that.
I promise it's collect.
Miss Manning,
you are not ready yet
to upset your
family and friends,
not at all ready.
Don't forget you have
just committed yourself.
I beg your pardon?
Did you say committed?
No, I'm here as a nurse.
Of course you are.
You are whatever
you say you are.
Don't you remember?
I told you about
our theories
and you said you
would commit to us.
I meant committed
in an entirely
different context.
I'm a nurse.
A real nurse.
If you want
to be a nurse,
be a nurse.
Dr. Quilly,
a person like you
couldn't...
Wouldn't make
an error like this.
True.
(DOOR OPENS)
I'm not staying here.
Oh, please,
let us help you.
(ELECTRICITY BUZZING)
Pity.
QUILLY: Miss Manning,
you're not ready yet
to upset your
family and friends.
Don't forget you have
just committed yourself.
Would you be willing
to dress as a nurse?
Let us help you.
Hello. I'm Dr. Moore.
Why was I locked up?
Locked up?
I think you've
been dreaming.
No, I wasn't dreaming.
I was locked up in a room.
Dr. Quilly has some
interesting theories.
He thinks that when
people break the rules,
they sometimes
punish themselves
in their dreams.
Are you threatening me?
No, of course not,
Nurse Manning.
I'm no threat to you
and I'm sure you'll
find that out.
Whatever happened
to you last night,
even in the mind...
It wasn't a dream!
...was very real to you,
and very exhausting.
Time for you to rest.
We'll speak later.
Son of a bitch!
Oh! Good morning,
Nurse Parker.
Parker?
Oh, good grief.
Miss Parker was the last...
I'll tell Dr. Quilly
you are here.
Dr. Quilly is on the patio
and he's anxious to see you.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Ah, Nurse Manning,
do sit down and join us.
Now, isn't this
a simply lovely day?
I don't have time
for polite conversation.
Oh, there's always time
At least sit down.
Do you know our
Dr. Moore here?
We met briefly
this morning and, yes,
we'll visit frequently.
No, we won't.
Let me make this
perfectly clear.
If you have any
question as to my
legitimate business here,
my credentials
are in my purse.
Do you have my purse?
Of course.
Jones found it
out by the gate.
You must have
dropped it when...
Well, never mind.
It's found, dear.
Here you are.
My credentials are gone.
You took them.
Oh, Nurse Manning,
why would I do
such a cruel
and ludicrous thing?
Now, look at me.
Am I a cruel man?
Dr. Quilly.
Would you
please reconsider this
whole, terrible mistake?
Once committed,
I cannot release you
until I believe
that you are a normal,
healthy human being.
Why did you
commit yourself?
I didn't!
He handed me a form and
he said that Ms. Donny...
Whatever the hell her name is,
would fill in the details.
Are you in the habit
of signing blank forms?
Of course I'm not
in the habit of
signing blank forms.
It just seemed so routine.
We spoke on the phone.
I was desperate
for the job and...
Desperate?
Will you please help me?
I'd like very much
to help you.
They put me in
a basement room.
Basement room?
Can you take us there?
No, I can't take you there.
I don't know how I got there
and I don't know
who put me there.
Basement room?
But there is
no basement room
or anything like
a basement room
in this institute.
Is there, Dr. Moore?
No.
It's somewhere.
Yes. It is somewhere.
In the mind.
In whose mind,
Dr. Quilly?
Yours or mine?
(MAN MOANS)
You're the new nurse.
My name is David.
David means beloved.
Actually, it means
beloved king.
I'm no king.
I'm no one.
No.
Everyone is someone.
Why are you
locked up?
They never told me.
They just feed me.
And someone
comes to wash me.
I used to
wash myself.
laugh and wash,
but now they
never bring me sweets
after feeding me.
After dinner could you
bring me a sweet
or anything? Please.
Of course.
Thank you.
You won't let them
kill you, will you?
They'll try, you know?
They like to
kill nurses here.
Why...
If I could,
I would help you
fly away home.
But I can't.
You won't forget my sweet.
Means a lot to me.
No.
PAUL: It's a
fantastic opportunity
for you, Susan.
Dr. Magnus Quilly
is a legend.
Nothing makes any sense.
I can't do this anymore.
I want you to leave.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
I'm sorry.
We wanted to tell you
about dinner tonight.
Oh, my!
Your lovely things.
And your suit!
Oh, my dear,
why did you do it?
I didn't do it.
I didn't do it!
The destruction of clothes
is a desire to be naked.
And what is naked?
Naked is to be
a fetus again.
Always back to the womb,
to go so far back
as not even to be born.
That's ridiculous.
Surely, you are not
saying you didn't
do it yourself?
That's exactly
what I'm saying.
Who... Why would
anyone do that here?
To force me to
wear this uniform.
Now, my dear,
Miss Manning,
try and think back.
I did ask you if you
objected to wearing a uniform
and you said you didn't.
That was before this.
I repeat, it's the
desire to be naked...
Etcetera, etcetera,
Dr. Preisser. I'm sure
you've made your point.
I insist!
The clothes represent
a deep hatred of self!
This is insanity!
That, I'm afraid, Nurse,
is the business at hand.
Dr. Moore, do you think
that this act of violence
and the suicide of
Nurse Manning's friend
had any connection?
Dr. Paul Swanson is dead.
He is not relevant!
And he will not be
given an autopsy.
You, gentlemen,
dishonor your profession.
More than that,
you exploit the ill.
May I have my
sweet now, please?
(SIGHS)
Oh, David.
I forgot, I'm sorry.
I was, uh... I was
upset and selfish.
Oh, all right,
perhaps tomorrow.
Thank you for
understanding.
You will have
your sweet tomorrow.
You stinking, rotten whore!
You promised!
At least the others...
(SCREAMING)
I killed you yesterday,
and the day before,
and you're still alive!
A sweet tomorrow
will be just fine!
I'll have something
to look forward to!
You are very kind!
(GASPING)
Please, don't beat me!
I did nothing!
She's my friend! Please!
(GRUNTS)
That will be all, Gow!
You will not
punish my people!
(COUGHS)
I'll be back.
Shut the fuck up!
Stop it!
You hear me? Stop!
Gow, you shit!
Now, we've
discussed this,
haven't we, David?
You mustn't hurt people.
(WHIMPERS)
Do you understand?
You could have killed her.
(SOBBING)
You're all right.
You're gonna be fine.
I'm not gonna
be fine here.
What on earth
possessed you to get
that close to David?
Pity.
Whatever possessed
you to commit me?
Therapy. And you
committed yourself.
You still don't believe
I'm sane, do you?
I believe that
I can help.
Dr. Moore,
I am not insane.
I came here to work.
I'll make time for
you tomorrow afternoon
at 3:00.
We can talk then.
Rest. Now, you'll
be all right.
It'll be fine.
Believe me.
(GASPS)
Hi!
Do you want
some company?
Do you remember me?
Yes.
You feel like
you don't belong here.
I don't.
That's the way
everybody thought
when they first came.
But then you...
You'll accept.
You'll see.
Would you like to cry?
Then cry.
I believe that crying in
the presence of someone
is more comforting
than to cry alone.
I cried for days
when I first came here.
And I cried alone.
You're not alone.
That's really nice of you.
What's your name?
Ronnie.
We're gonna be
great friends,
aren't we?
Mmm-hmm.
I've got my planes. Oh!
And I've got these.
(CHUCKLES)
Where did
you get those?
Nurse Parker
gave them to me.
Nurse Parker?
That's who Ms. Donnymead
keeps calling me.
Do you know where she is?
She's gone.
She's never coming back.
But we're gonna
be great friends,
aren't we?
Ronnie, tell me
more about the keys.
They open everything.
This one here,
key to my heart.
(LAUGHING)
ISANDRA: I've just
finished a poem.
My reading's
this evening,
you must come.
The acclaim will
be unprecedented.
Were you always a poet?
Always.
Great poets are born.
I didn't know that
until I arrived here.
Did Dr. Quilly
explain that to you?
Dr. Quilly is dead.
Dr. Quilly is dead?
Oh, yes. The man
we now call Dr. Quilly
explained it to me.
Now, if Dr. Quilly is dead,
who is the man that
calls himself Dr. Quilly?
Just a guest.
A guest?
One of us.
Oh, when Dr. Quilly died,
there was great unrest.
We all felt
so unprotected.
So a guest became Dr. Quilly.
Isandra, you sure you're
not making this up?
When did Dr. Quilly die?
Yesterday.
And when did you
arrive at the Institute?
Today or maybe tomorrow.
Time is of no
importance to a poet.
I see.
Um, I have to go.
You won't forget
my reading?
No.
Oh, Dr. Preisser.
Yes?
Oh, I'd like to
apologize if I seemed
rude to you
last night at dinner.
I appreciate that, Nurse.
You see, in the Institute
we all must be very, very
kind to each other.
Doctor?
Yes? Do you want
to talk to me?
Yes.
Then, please, sit down.
I just really wanted to know
if you knew Dr. Quilly before
you came to the Institute?
No. Why?
Well, frankly,
there's been some talk.
I don't take it seriously.
About Dr. Quilly,
the real Dr. Quilly.
He is...
Well, he's, uh...
Dead?
So you heard that?
Oh. everyone has.
You know,
Isandra's fantasies
are quite public here.
She's been saying
them for years.
How long has
she been here?
She came here
when she was a
very, very young girl.
Long before I did.
Oh.
Nurse Manning.
Won't you sit down?
Dr. Moore, you
know how I feel
about being here.
You've been
most articulate.
Well, it goes
beyond that.
I've heard the
most amazing things.
For instance, the real
Dr. Quilly is dead
and Nurse Parker,
she may have
been murdered.
And the other nurses,
they've just disappeared.
Dr. Moore,
it seems to me
that the Institute
is far sicker
than the patients.
Innuendo. All you're really
referring to is innuendo.
Are you saying
I've invented
all of this?
Let's find out.
Let's try to put things
in their proper perspective.
Are you willing
to help me try
to understand?
Yes, I am.
All right, fine.
Won't you sit down?
All right.
Now, let's try to
put things in order.
You're from Seattle?
Yes.
And you came
here as a nurse?
Of course.
And your Dr. Swanson,
you say he was
a psychotherapist.
Yes, he was.
And you believe
he killed himself?
I thought you said
you were gonna help me.
I thought you
were different.
I thought...
That I was your
knight in shining armor?
No.
I thought at least
you were a doctor
with some integrity.
SUSAN: Ronnie,
you've got to help me.
Of course
I'll help you.
Now, watch.
You must know
how I can reach my family
or anyone on the outside.
Shh! Isandra's gonna
read her poetry now.
Ronnie, I don't
want to cry alone.
Look, I'll tell you what.
Why don't you meet me
tonight in Quilly's office
at 3:00 a.m.?
Everybody's asleep then.
We can use Quilly's phone.
You know how to
get into Quilly's office?
Of course.
Remember these?
(GIGGLES)
Just be in Quilly's office
tonight at 3:00
and don't be late.
I get sort of
frightened when I'm
in there all alone.
Gentlemen.
I have a special treat
for you this evening.
The first public reading
of the Institute's own
poetess in residence,
the lovely Isandra Snow.
DONNYMEAD: Bravo! Bravo!
I shall make no speech.
Oh, goody.
How about no poetry?
Gow, you can shut up
or you can leave!
And miss all this?
My name is not Isandra.
It's Cassandra.
Or suiting yourself
something else.
Please, anything else.
She's beautiful.
(ALL LAUGHING)
This is a terrible
experience for her.
Don't they know what
they're doing to her?
Psychotics are totally
immersed in themselves
or whoever they
think they are.
May this flame,
this gentle flame,
rise slowly...
Cut the shit,
Sandy baby, come on,
take it off!
(ALL LAUGHING)
You all stop this now!
You're a guest!
If anything has to be stopped
around here, I'll do it!
You insist that
I'm the nurse?
The only nurse?
Well, so be it.
If your beloved doctors
won't stop this, I will.
Forget her, Sandy, baby.
Go on, you're great!
Mr. Gow, get out!
And are you
going to carry me out?
No, but I will.
You can all leave now.
Now you've proven how
strong and brave you are.
We'll all listen
to the nurse. Out!
Jones, please take these
people to their rooms.
Are you all right?
Oh, yes, but if
you'll excuse me,
I'll need my
pills and some rest.
I'm having this pain.
Donnymead.
Could you help
Dr. Quilly, please?
Isandra, it was fine,
it was just fine.
For God's sake.
Why humiliate a nobody?
SUSAN: Isandra,
you're not a nobody.
Don't dismiss
yourself so easily.
I was dismissed
a long time ago.
(SIGHS)
DESMOND: I'm impressed.
Very impressed.
Thank you.
(CLOCK CHIMES)
(CRASHES)
(GASPS)
It's only me!
(WHISPERS)
Did you hear a noise?
Yes, I tripped over
Darlene's damned bike.
What?
No, no one
else heard it.
Calm down.
Oh, I hope not.
Would you like to...
Shh!
(WHISPERS)
Would you like to see
my latest model?
It's the first Spitfire
that was ever made.
Ronnie, we are here
to help me. Remember?
We are?
Yes.
Oh, oh, we are.
Then, we could go
see the Spitfire?
Of course.
It's going to be
my masterpiece.
Ronnie, please try
to concentrate.
I get distracted.
I know.
Where were we?
Quilly's phone.
The phone, of course,
uh, he keeps the phone,
uh, in that drawer.
Bingo!
Oh, there's a
phone in there.
For heaven's sake,
Ronnie, that's what
we've been looking for.
It is?
Yes.
Oh, of course.
Go ahead and
make your call.
I will.
Tell your parents
you found a friend.
A savior.
WOMAN: Operator.
Hello? Hello?
Hello, operator? Yes.
I'd like you to
place a collect call
for me to...
Dear, you know
only Dr. Quilly can place
calls for his patients.
Well, I'm not a patient.
Well, what are the
code words for today?
What are the code
words for today?
Um, wait,
the code word...
You know you're a patient.
Now, why don't you
just go to sleep?
This is an emergency.
It always is.
You are a patient.
Now, just go
back to sleep.
Hello? Hello?
She hung up.
Let's go see the Spitfire.
No. Give me your keys.
No. Uh-uh.
Nurse Parker gave
these to me. Uh-uh.
Ronnie, this is
very important.
My papers are in
one of those drawers.
Now, if I can find them
and show them to Desmond,
he'll believe me.
Desmond?
Dr. Moore!
Oh! Then we'll go
see the Spitfire.
Later.
Give them to me.
Well, you're
my friend. Okay.
Oh, the file's over there.
How do you know?
Well, because when
I go to his session,
Dr. Quilly always gets
my file out of there.
Come on.
These are patient's files.
Wait, maybe
I'm in here.
The real me.
Well, you are
the real you.
I know that,
but I have to
prove it somehow.
These are all in code.
Of course, they'd be in code.
I don't know,
we might find some
pattern to this,
but this way it doesn't
make any sense.
"M-O-T-H-P-R-O-F."
Wait a minute,
this is beginning
to make sense.
This could be
Darlene Court's card.
"C-Y-C." Cyclist.
That means cyclist.
Father's in business,
mother perhaps a professor.
"P-A-R-S-C-H-I-Z."
Paranoid schizophrenic.
"L-I-K-T-Y-S."
I don't know
what that is.
"N-R-S."
Could be nurse.
Yeah.
"K-L."
Could be kill.
You don't think
this is my card,
do you?
No.
Ill. Could be ill.
It's kill!
Ronnie!
It's too late for
dear old Ronnie.
He's so scared of me
he starts to shit
every time he sees me.
So, you've been having
yourself a fine old time
going through
Dr. Quilly's desk.
Had yourself a nice
chat with the operator
at Crownpoint, huh?
(LAUGHING)
Oh, rifling a desk.
You are as bad
as I am, young lady.
We're both very bad.
No! You come near
and I'll scream!
Scream, Scream.
No! No! No! No! No!
No! No!
JONES: Gow! Nurse Manning!
Go to your rooms!
You fucking slime!
I'm gonna slit
your belly open
like a flapping fish.
(PANTING)
Damn!
Fucking pig!
Wait a minute!
I'll cut your
goddamn throat!
SUSAN: "There is a
chance for escape.
"A journey that
you can make.
"Come and see me
in the tower.
"Come at once,
before it's too late.
"I wish you well
in the dark.
"For the Institute is a place
where hyenas speak
and humans bark.
"Isandra."
No!
Dr. Moore.
Last night
before I found Isandra,
I went to David's room
and his door was unlocked,
and he wasn't there.
I saw David earlier
this morning. He was in
his room, peaceful, quiet.
He wasn't in his
room last night.
Can we discuss this later?
Jones, would you, uh,
ask one of the staff members
to bring out some candles
and the fancy table cloths?
We're gonna
have a little service.
She deserves a service.
JONES:
I'll take care of it.
Hi. You've gotta help me.
See, I came here as a nurse,
I had credentials, but they
took my credentials
and they say
I'm a patient,
but I'm not.
Please, you've
gotta help me.
Uh, yeah, we understand.
Listen, ma'am, why don't
you talk to Dr. Quilly?
He'll, uh... He'll give you
all the help you need.
Excuse me.
But...
I've been watching you
get out of hand, Nurse,
and I've been
patient long enough.
There will be punishment,
severe punishment!
I'll handle this, Jones.
But, Dr. Moore,
the nurse has been
breaking all our rules!
How the hell am I
supposed to keep
order around here?
You're doing a
splendid job, Jones.
Why don't you
help the others in?
Go ahead.
JONES: All right,
let's go. Back inside.
Okay, everyone
back inside. Let's go.
SUSAN:
Isandra told me
a way to escape.
Now, I know what
she really meant.
There's only one way
to leave the Institute.
Henry seems to
do him better
than the others.
You know, I have to admit,
my ego is slightly dented.
Henry has literally
never done me.
Maybe that's because you're
not the real Dr. Quilly.
Now, now,
you mustn't
mumble, Nurse.
We can't hear
what you say,
we can't help.
You didn't help Isandra,
and you heard her.
You made her speak
loud and clear and
everybody listened.
You knew they would laugh.
The theory worked.
Isandra did
become the poet
and the poet
was released
from the Institute.
Are you suggesting
my responsibility
for Isandra's death?
Is that what you're
saying, Dr. Moore?
I demand an answer.
Not here, Doctor.
We have patients here.
Jones, Ms. Donnymead,
Lucille, see our guests out.
This meal is over!
You too, Nurse,
may be excused.
(BELL RINGING)
How dare you
question me in public?
I asked you
not to make a scene.
Everything is a scene
here at the Institute.
It was designed that way.
Desmond, suicide was
Isandra's final fantasy.
Her final freedom.
Now, it's regretful,
but it does happen.
You didn't suppose that
the Institute was the only
mental hospital in the world
that didn't have its
percentage of failures?
Adler failed.
Jung failed.
Freud failed!
But they didn't
accept failure as
the ultimate therapy.
Dr. Quilly,
you know how long
I've admired you.
We studied your
books in school,
we practically worshipped
at your shrine.
I came here to learn
from a great man.
I'm still trying to
discover your theories.
Your real theories.
Those great books of yours.
Theoretical books
put into practice
are not necessarily
neat, Desmond.
A book belongs on a shelf,
you bring it to life,
it's no longer a book.
What is it, Doctor?
The Institute!
Doctor.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Are you all right?
Yeah.
SUSAN: Was it
bad with Quilly?
Yes.
Must be hard for you.
Well, for me to have
had the temerity even
to question that man...
Maybe he's
not that man.
Please, Susan, that's
Isandra's story again.
No, no, I'm not talking
about Isandra's story.
I'm just saying
that people
sometimes change
and the Quilly
that you respected so much
may be a different one now.
Some people have
paid a terrible price
for greatness.
Like your Dr. Swanson?
He could have
been a great man.
Susan, there are times
when I am absolutely
convinced you are sane.
Then,
as yesterday morning,
that fantasy about
David's disappearance...
David was not there!
All right, Susan,
anything you say.
Don't patronize me.
I was, wasn't I?
Yes.
Please don't scream!
I don't like screams!
Besides,
it wouldn't help!
David, I just saw
you in your room and
the door was locked.
No, it wasn't.
I was out,
but after I got
back to my room
no one ever came
to lock the door again.
No one knows
that your door
is unlocked?
Only the one
who let me out.
That is such
a hard mattress.
You really should complain.
David, who let you out?
Oh, it's always
the same person.
I only like it outside
for a little while.
I'm really quite
comfortable in my room.
Except when they wash me.
I used to wash myself.
You will again.
You promise?
I promise.
A person should
wash his own body.
I think I will.
I was told to find you
and kill you!
But I couldn't kill you.
Oh, what a lovely
person you are.
You remind me
of someone who was
very kind to me.
Nurse Parker.
She let me wash myself,
before they killed her.
They like to
kill nurses here.
And doctors, too.
And they bury them
in the cellar.
David, please tell me
who let you out
of your room.
May I have your brush?
I'm tired now.
Do you wanna
go to your room?
If you'll take me.
That was a lovely visit.
David, where is
this cellar?
Try the old...
Shh!
Try the old door
next to the kitchen.
Are you going there?
Maybe.
I'd invite you in,
but it's not very tidy.
That's all right.
(TOY SQUEAKS)
It's all in my mind.
Hello, Nurse.
(SIGHS) Luther.
You're not supposed
to know about this place,
neither am I.
How did you find it?
Gow showed it to me.
He knew it would hurt me.
Come. I have something
to show you.
This is Nurse
Parker's grave.
I worshipped her.
She was so kind.
She looked like you,
you know.
How do you know
that's her grave?
It's the newest.
She was the last
to be killed.
The last one?
Dr. Quilly was
the first to die.
He's here.
The others
are outside.
That's the
real Dr. Quilly?
Oh, yes.
The present Quilly
is a patient.
He took over
when Quilly died
to carry on his work.
That's what Isandra said.
Dr. Preisser said
it was just her fantasy.
Oh, Preisser's a patient, too.
We're all patients here,
except the dead.
Only the dead are
sane in the Institute,
Dr. Moore doesn't know
anything about this,
does he?
Does he?
LUTHER: Look!
"Registered Nurse."
They were nurses, too?
They bring nurses
here to the Institute
so that one of the
guests can kill them.
But you don't know
who's killing the nurses.
No, I don't know.
I know they get them here,
they bring them here
and they never leave.
You'll sleep here
one day, Nurse.
The candles told me so.
Oh, Lord God!
Lord God, vengeance.
Show thyself!
(GASPS)
Dr. Quilly wants
to see you now.
Suppose I say no?
Then you say no,
but you will see
Dr. Quilly now!
Good! Because I want
to see him now!
Soft evening,
eh, Nurse?
Almost as if
all elements conspired
to quiet the
beasts in man.
(SIGHS)
You are our most
difficult guest, Nurse.
Maybe that's because
I'm not a guest.
Intense shock therapy
is the last resort
of the Institute.
You have brought me
to that last resort.
You were here in my office,
you used the telephone.
Oh, don't lie, the operator
told me all about it.
You have tried to
destroy the Institute
ever since you arrived.
Then you used dear Ronnie
to let you in here,
you flaunted yourself
in front of David, undoing
a work of a whole year!
But the final infamy
was turning
Desmond Moore
from his work, my work!
Your work?
Turning a hospital,
a place of healing
into a parody of therapy?
Yes, I was here
and I used the phone.
I was also in the cellar.
You remember the cellar?
You're buried there,
so are the nurses.
(SCREAMING)
You were in the cellar?
Yes, and in the
basement room.
The one that
doesn't exist!
(STAMMERS)
That's a sacred place!
No, it's the burial site
for Dr. Quilly!
The real one!
How... How dare you?
How dare you?
And this whole damn place!
This is you, isn't it?
Paranoid schizophrenic,
kills nurses.
You tease and
kill nurses, don't you?
You're nothing
but a patient!
I am Magnus Quilly.
This is my hospital.
Mine!
(ALARM RINGS)
(CHOKES)
(COUGHS)
Magnus!
Don't do anything, Doctor.
I'll call an ambulance,
we'll have you in Stockton...
I'll be dead before the
ambulance can get here.
It'll be all right, Jones.
Dr. Moore here
will look after you.
(PANTING)
Desmond,
you'll have to
take command.
Good luck. Good luck.
(CHOKING)
You did this!
You brought this all on!
(GRUNTS)
Is he dead?
DESMOND: Susan? Susan?
Are you all right?
It's Dr. Moore.
Dr. Quilly is alive.
I just saw...
Oh, I'm sorry
if I startled you.
It was just to
honor Dr. Quilly.
Quite an effective
performance, Henry.
Perhaps a bit
too effective.
Thank you, Henry.
Sometimes we see
things not as they are,
but as we would
like them to be.
As I mentioned
to Dr. Paul Swanson
this morning.
You're saying you
spoke with Paul?
Yes, I called him
this morning.
It was sort of
a hunch really.
And you'll be
happy to know
he's very much alive.
Alive?
You weren't his nurse,
Susan, you were his patient.
You fell in love
with him, it seems,
and because
of falling in
love with Paul,
he felt that
another doctor should
take over your treatment.
The rejection was
too much for you to bear.
You imagined him dead
and ran away
here to the Institute.
Maybe I should go back.
No, of course not.
The new head of the Institute
needs a top notch nurse,
doesn't he?
I'll be moving
into my new office.
Maybe you'd like to help.
Thank you.
Needless to say
the order and serenity
that Dr. Quilly brought
to the Institute
will be one of the most
important priorities
during my tenure here.
Ah, yes, Jones,
set it right here, please.
Of course, it'll be
very important during
this transition period
that the rules
of the Institute
be strictly obeyed.
Jones here has
agreed to stay on
as head of security
and help us protect
our way of life.
(PEOPLE APPLAUDING)
Thank you.
Thank you all.
Nurse Manning.
Would you give me
a hand here, please?
Nothing like
a touch of home
in the office.
Maybe you can help
me arrange these.
(TOY SQUEAKS)
I saw a toy like this
in the basement.
It belonged
to a patient.
Paranoid, schizophrenic,
chemist, teases...
He teases.
He likes toys.
Kills nurses.
(GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
(ALARM RINGING)
What happened here?
There's been an accident.
Jones, I want you to
dispose of the body
in the usual manner.
Ronnie, I want you
to clean this room up.
Yes, Nurse Manning.
Donnymead.
Donnymead,
I want you to call a
staff meeting for later,
and I expect everyone
on the staff to attend.
But... Uh...
Do you understand?
Uh, yeah.
Miss Manning.
You must not forget
you are just a nurse.
I'm in charge now.
The rest we can discuss
later at the staff meeting.
That's all.
Jones, I want you
to call the driver.
The new doctor is
due to arrive tonight
and I'm gonna
meet him personally.
I don't think...
No, you don't think!
I'll do the thinking!
Now, go.
(CAR HORN HONKS)
Wait!
You can't leave.
I'm late!
You can't get out.
Why?
You need this
to open the gate.
Thank you, Jones.
DRIVER: Evening, ma'am.
You see? I told you
you'd get the job.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Can we please go?
The train station, ma'am?
Police station.