Is it on?
Ok.
How does it look?
Looks good. Ready?
Yeah, yeah. Come.
Take his...
All perfect praise be to Allah,
the lord of the worlds.
I testify that there is none
worthy of worship except Allah
and that Mohammed is his slave
and messenger.
We ask Allah to exalt
his mention,
as well as that of his family
and all his companions.
This is an ultimatum directed
to the American people
and the hypocritical
American administration
release all our brothers who you
keep prisoner in Guantanamo bay,
or these American soldiers
who served in Iraq
and Afghanistan
that killed our Muslim
brothers and sisters will die.
Don't believe that the
white house is allowed
to implement its
aggressive policies
against the weak in Guantanamo
bay without consequence.
Today is a wake-up call.
Don't believe that we won't
retaliate against the oppressor.
This message is directed to
the pretenders of freedom
at the white house
and the American people.
We expect the white house
to release a statement
within twenty four hours,
or we will kill one
of the soldiers.
Allah willing and nothing
is too great for Allah.
God is the greatest and
glory be to islam.
All praise is due to Allah.
AMERICAN HOSTAGE
Subrip: Pix
In the name of God all...
To implement its
aggressive policies
against the weak in Guantanamo
bay without consequence.
Today is a wake-up call.
Don't believe that we won't
retaliate against the oppressor.
This message is directed
to the pretenders of freedom
at the white house
and to the American people.
We expect the white house
to release a statement
within twenty four hours
or we will kill one
of the soldiers.
Allah willing and nothing
is too great for Allah.
God is the greatest
and glory be to islam.
All praise is
due to Allah.
Looks good.
-Yeah not bad.
-Not bad at all.
Ok.
All right you're up brother.
Now here is a map of...
Sunset mall.
You want to go here
to the garage.
There they have Wi-Fi.
User-name password
you have them?
Yeah.
Ok.
Keep your head down.
I understand.
May Allah be with you.
So how did it go?
You mean with the videos?
Yes.
Good, good.
Shahin is emailing
the news stations as we speak.
Do you want some tea?
Yes that would be wonderful.
So...
How long have you lived here?
In America.
Yes.
It's about...
Six years now.
Really.
Have you always
lived in Florida?
No,
actually I used to live in...
San Francisco before
I came to Tampa.
I hear it's beautiful there.
Yes it is.
So you're from Chicago?
Yes.
American citizenship.
Proper yankee girl
I'd love to go to Chicago.
Big Muslim population there.
Halal food.
Devon Avenue.
How did I know you were
going to say that?
I'm going to bring some tea to
Hamal.
I brought you some tea.
-Let's go outside.
-I want to talk to you.
Why do you always take off
your scarf when you get home?
Because I'm home.
I don't like it.
But I'm home.
You're here with two other men.
Yes, but I'm home.
Hey, I'm your brother.
I'm talking to you.
-Yes, I heard you.
-You're not my boss.
We have breaking news.
A video has just
been released
from an unnamed
terrorist organization.
Two decorated soldiers who
served in Iraq and Afghanistan
have been kidnapped.
The soldiers have now been identified
as Anthony Morales and Donald Young.
In the following
experts of the video
the terrorists
demand the release
of all prisoners at
Guantanamo bay detention center.
If their demands are not met they
will execute one of the soldiers.
We're going now live
to Tampa, Florida
where the video was
supposedly emailed
to several news agencies.
This is completely
unprecedented.
Terrorists have kidnapped
soldiers on us soil.
This sort of thing usually
happens overseas in war zones.
Now the alert
is nationwide.
So if you see anything
suspicious out there
please contact your
local law enforcement.
We're still waiting for a statement
from the state department.
When that comes
we'll share that with you.
I'll take over.
Finally.
Any problems.
Fine. No problems.
It is now confirmed
that a terrorist cell,
operating in Tampa, Florida,
has kidnapped
two United States
soldiers.
Anthony Morales and Donald
Young
we made the news.
Who served in Iraq and Afghanistan
are currently being held hostage
we received a video showing
the terrorists' demands
to release all prisoners of
the Guantanamo bay prison.
The terrorists are threatening
to execute one of the soldiers
-if demands are not met.
-I'm going for a run.
I'll be back in thirty minutes. The
FBI along with local law enforcement
are working around the clock
to locate this terror cell.
And they are seeking the
public's help in this matter.
We're going live now
to Tampa, Florida,
from where the video was
apparently emailed.
Smells good.
This is very good Fahdah.
I was just telling your sister
what a good cook she is Hamal.
It's good.
Very good.
So...
Have you ever been
to that restaurant.
On Devon Avenue.
Which one?
Uhm...
I can't think of...
You know they're
known for putting
the extra bell peppers and
mushrooms in the samosa.
Yes, I know which one
you're thinking of.
I love that.
So...
Have you ever been to Tariq's
Cafe,
where they sell
the fresh jaleibi?
Tariq's Cafe.
I love Tariq's Cafe. They're
world known for their jaleibi.
So.
What part...
Listen...
What?
You were saying something.
I was thinking,
what are we going to do
if the administration doesn't
come out with an
official statement
they're releasing the prisoners.
Then we send them a message.
So what part of
Chicago are you from?
You mean kill one of them.
You know we have our orders.
You understand.
We have to do what
we have to do.
It's...
It's probably not going to work.
Look. We are at war Hamal.
The west is waging war
against the Muslim people.
You're having fun?
What's the matter?
Cat cut your tongue?
Doesn't feel too good does it.
Come on say something?
I'm sure under different
circumstances who knows right?
We could have been friends
maybe? What do you think?
Yes.
Proceed with the next stage.
Ok.
How is the house?
House? Good. Yeah.
Good, you have
everything you need?
Yeah.
Report back in two days.
We can't believe this is
happening.
We just want him home with
us.
Saying the United States does not
negotiate with terrorists and that...
I wish they just could let
him go and...
trying to hurt his
father...
The us administration
released a statement today
regarding the kidnapping
of two decorated soldiers.
In this statement
the United States refuses to
negotiate with the terrorists,
and will not release the
prisoners.
This sparked an outcry
from the opposition.
Hey, Fahdah.
Could you go...
Get Hamal.
And keep an eye
on the prisoners
they want you inside.
I'll keep an eye on them.
Hamal.
What's going on?
Sit down.
So...
The administration
is not cooperating.
I knew it wasn't going to work.
Well...
It's time to show this country
who they're dealing with.
I spoke with Al-Saqri and he
wants us to go ahead with the...
Operation.
So it's decided. Tomorrow.
We do it tomorrow.
So are we going to kill one
of them?
Yes those are the orders.
It's not going to work. What makes
you think it's going to work?
It's going to work trust me.
I can't do it.
What?
I can't kill a man.
I won't be able to.
We haven't even decided,
who's going to do it.
Well I just can't.
This is our fight brother.
You knew that from the
beginning.
No, I know, but I mean
it seems so bizarre.
-I never thought that...
-Think about...
All the muslims
killed by those two soldiers.
I know but
before anything else
I'm telling you.
I can't kill a man
I don't know if you understand
what we're trying to do here.
But an order, is an order.
I'm going to take a shower.
Uhm...
Maybe I should put a call in
to Mr. Al-Saqri and...
He can remind you
what you're doing here.
No, I understand.
I'm going to take a shower.
Aren't you supposed to be
guarding the prisoners?
I'll watch them.
Is he going to be a problem?
I don't know.
So who's going to do it?
Ok, so...
This is how we're
going to do it.
We're going to draw names
from a bag.
Last name in the
bag has to do it.
No going back.
Ok.
Hamal.
I don't know.
Look.
If my name is the one that's
last in the bag then I'll do it.
But I'm not going to do it just
because you don't want to do it.
Ok.
Let's do this.
Ok, let's draw the first name.
Shahin.
Go ahead.
What does it say?
Asad.
Ok.
It's decided
I can't do it.
Exactly like I told you.
You understand?
Yes.
All perfect praise be to Allah,
the lord of the worlds.
I testify that there is none
worthy of worship except Allah.
And that Mohammed is his slave
and messenger.
We ask Allah to exalt his
mention
as well as that of his family
and all his companions.
This is a message directed
to the American people
and the hypocritical
American administration.
We will hold to account those
who have killed our brother and
sisters.
Just as you kill
our Muslim brothers and sisters,
so shall we kill yours.
Again release all our brothers
who you keep prisoner
in Guantanamo bay
who you hold for years of
humiliation and disgrace
or I swear to God that every
American soldier is a target.
Every Muslim must rise
to defend his religion
and his brother and sister.
All praise is due to Allah.
Grab his arms.
Morning.
How are...
How are you?
Fine.
Are you sure?
No, I'm fine.
How about I make you French
toast? Your favorite.
Instead of that.
I said I'm fine.
Stop trying to take care of me
all the time.
Hamal.
God is great.
You did well.
Look at this.
I don't have time.
Who's watching the American?
You guard him.
Hamal.
Where are you going?
All right.
Here is a map of
Redwood Mall.
Ok, you know what to do.
We have to get rid of the body tonight.
We have to get rid of it tonight.
Why don't we just keep the body
here?
Why don't we plop him on
the sofa. You know?
Put his feet up.
We could give him a fruit drink.
Better yet you could call
the police yourself.
And say hey we got a body...
You know.
The minute,
the human body dies
it begins to decompose
and smell.
We have to get rid of the body.
I say we throw it in the bay.
Perfect. I like that.
We'll do it tonight.
I think he wants
to say something.
Get Asad.
What seems to be the problem?
He wants to say something.
Take the tape off.
You camel fuckers.
I'll fucking kill
every single one of you.
Put the tape back on.
I'll cut you dicks off.
Put the fucking tape back on.
Every single one of you god
damn it.
I'm going to take a nap.
Hamal.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on.
Let's go
I'm very happy.
Hey.
Ok.
Get some rest.
Yes.
Yeah we got rid
of the body yesterday.
Good good.
Wait for the administration
to release a statement.
Listen one more thing.
Yeah. We're having
problems with Hamal.
It's always something
with that kid.
What problems with Hamal?
I don't know the guy, he doesn't
listen to me you know he's...
He just... doesn't listen to me.
And he's like under a lot
of stress. You know?
He's under stress.
Stress yeah.
Call tomorrow. Bring him.
I'll talk to him.
I'm not taking the tape off.
What. What do you want?
If I take the tape off,
are you going to yell?
What?
Some water please.
Thank you.
Thank you, you're the man.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
What is it?
Don't...
Don't put it on just yet.
Are you hungry?
Eat this.
Why are you doing this?
Are you going to kill me?
No.
-Don't lie to me.
-You killed the other guy.
Let me ask you this.
How many of my brothers and sisters
did you kill in Iraq and Afghanistan?
We wouldn't have gone to war if
you wouldn't have attacked first.
Did we really attack first?
So...
He wants to speak with you.
Why what did you tell him?
Nothing.
I may have mentioned,
that you're under some stress.
Why do you say that?
I'm not under stress.
It's obvious.
Don't speak for me.
You understand?
We're calling him tomorrow.
We have breaking news,
regarding the ongoing
story of the kidnapping
of Anthony Morales
and Donald Young.
An execution video of
Anthony Morales was emailed
to multiple news agencies
around the country.
Its authenticity is still
being confirmed.
But we now believe,
based on the video,
that sergeant
Anthony Morales
was killed by the unnamed
terrorist organization,
demanding the release of all
prisoners of Guantanamo bay.
We believe that
sergeant Donald Young,
their second victim,
is still alive.
We can only show you
an excerpt of the video
because of its
horrific nature.
Yeah, it's me.
Yeah, he's right here.
Ok
he wants to speak with you.
What is the problem?
There's no problem.
Asad tell me you have
a lot of pressure.
No pressure.
You still have the nightmares?
No. No nightmares.
Good.
Remember why we do this.
Remember what happened
to your parents.
They were my good friends too.
I took good care of you
and your sister yes?
I know.
Do you need anything?
No, nothing.
How is your sister?
She's good.
Good, good.
When this is over
we go back to Syria.
Put Asad back on.
He wants to talk to you.
Yeah it's me.
Yeah.
Listen to me very carefully.
Hamal has issues.
I can tell I can hear
it in his voice.
He's getting very Shaky Asad.
You have to support him.
You have to give him
more confidence.
We need to be strong on this.
Remember what happened
to the last adventure.
Remember what happened then?
Things have to be
more secure now.
There is much more at stake.
Much more.
Please.
Treat him kindly Asad.
If he gives you any problem,
you call me again.
I'll talk to him again.
We have to build this kid up.
You follow me?
Please.
We have to get
this operation going perfectly.
The last operation
there were some weak links.
We can have not
any more weak links.
We are finished with that.
We are professionals.
So make sure
you take care of Hamal.
Ok?
Ok.
Look Asad.
You do it a good work.
And I'm happy with you
for the most part.
But once things start to fall
apart
it goes into your lap.
We need everybody
a hundred percent on this.
This is too crucial.
Ok?
Ok.
The water feels good.
I like this house.
I could see myself living here.
But I miss Syria too much.
Al-saqri must be renting it.
Just to you know blend in
with the community.
Residential neighborhood.
You know and all that.
No one would suspect anything.
He's a good man.
He's a very good man.
I'm very indebted to him.
He took care of me and my
brother after our parents died.
What happened with that?
It was 2003.
My parents, me and my brother
went to Bagdad to visit my aunt.
I remember it well.
It was on a Thursday.
March twentieth.
There was an explosion.
Then more explosions.
Coming closer and closer.
Then a big boom.
I couldn't hear anything.
My ears hurt.
People screaming.
There was smoke everywhere.
I got up.
I went to my parent's room
and it was half destroyed.
And there was Hamal.
Standing there.
Looking at them.
Dead.
My mother...
Her legs...
My father...
Hey, it's ok.
It's ok.
I took care of him after that.
Hamal.
He was very vulnerable.
He still is.
If my parent knew the American
government would attack,
they wouldn't have gone to
Bagdad.
Then we went back to Syria.
And Mr. Al-Saqri
got us visas to America.
We stayed
with an uncle in Chicago.
Hamal would wake up
in the middle of the night...
Screaming.
Almost every night.
I would comfort him
until he sleeps.
I feel like I will always
take care of him.
He's not strong like you.
Can you please pour some water
over my head?
Come on man please
I'm fucking dying here.
Man I really appreciate that.
You know I was wrong
about one thing.
What's that?
About you attacking us first.
Really?
I know the us government
has been messing around
with different parts of the
world for quite some time.
But...
I was just doing my job.
That's what I'm doing.
My job.
Are you?
We're just trying
to free our brothers.
Here try this.
I love mint tea.
It's good
hey...
You know they're never going to
free the prisoners in Guantanamo.
They're not?
The us doesn't negotiate
with terrorists.
I don't know.
Depends on the public outcry.
You want to bet?
Besides it's not like the people
being held there are angels.
My older brother is
being held there
what's wrong?
Nothing.
You're not eating.
I am.
And now you're playing
with your food.
He's being a cry baby.
Shut up you hear me.
Poor little Hamal.
Asad stop.
I said shut up.
Hey.
Take it easy.
Please don't get
worked up Hamal.
I have one thing to say to you.
Whether you like it or not,
this is a war.
And what you did that
was part of that war.
Who's the real terrorist here?
And stop playing with your food.
He needs time.
He's starting to lose it.
Who is there?
Fuck.
What are you doing?
Hamal.
Hamal go to sleep.
Get some sleep.
You are crazy man.
Asad.
Yes.
We have to talk about Hamal.
No, we don't.
Asad please.
Later I promise.
I've been thinking...
There is nothing to talk about.
He's a psycho.
Later ok I promise.
I have to go check on the
prisoner.
How is it going in here?
Good.
Ok, you can go.
Hey.
One second.
Could you freshen the tea pot
for me, please?
What are you doing up?
Nothing.
Are you ok?
Fine.
Hey, can you guard the prisoner?
I'm kind of tired.
Are you ok?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Of course she's all right.
Why wouldn't she be?
I don't know. I was just
thinking maybe...
Nothing.
Did you see the news today?
Yes I saw the news.
You know the administration
released a statement,
saying they're not negotiating.
Yes I know.
It was on television.
I said I know.
It's just a standard statement.
Don't you think we should
rethink the operation and...
Shut up, Hamal.
I'm so tired of your antics man.
Don't tell me to shut up.
It wasn't going to work.
I told you it wasn't going to
work and you wouldn't listen.
Stop shouting like a donkey.
Besides it doesn't matter
we're going on.
Those are our orders.
Every day that goes by,
there is more of a chance of
them finding out about us.
They have no idea who we are.
Ok, they have nothing
to connect us with nothing.
I'm glad you're so certain, Asad.
Excuse me are...
Are you questioning me?
For your information if the agencies
have the slightest suspicion,
they'll come right
through this door.
Make us disappear
just like that.
No trial.
No jury.
No warrant, no nothing.
We're going to end up in
Guantanamo ourselves.
Maybe I'm breaking
the news to you,
it's not like we have the right
to a free trial in this country.
As if I didn't know that.
Yeah well
just making sure.
In the bay reeled in
the human remains
of what appears to be
sergeant Anthony Morales.
We're going now live
to Tampa, Florida.
Btv here reporting
live at ballast point,
where the police have
confirmed that the body found
is that of sergeant
Anthony Morales.
This is definitely
a tragic story
and the coast guard
is here on scene
and they're definitely
on high alert.
I'm here with
Roger Davis,
who's the man that discovered
the body while fishing.
Well I didn't know quite what
to... what to think at first.
I... I thought snagged my line
on a log out there or something.
After that I reached my phone
and I dialed up the police.
And kind of waited to
see... see their thoughts on it.
So you didn't reel the body
in?
No. No.
I didn't reel it in.
I... I didn't know quite what
to do.
I mean I didn't want to mess with
the crime scene or anything.
I mean I watch TV
and I know how those...
Those things work
a little bit.
So you know I just wanted
to leave it to the cops
see what they do.
Right. Right. You did exactly the
right thing in this situation.
Well there you have it I'm
Kelly...
What happened with your brother?
He went to Pakistan after 911.
We know he boarded the
plane back to the us,
but when the plane landed
he didn't come out of the gate.
That's crazy.
We finally found out
he's in Guantanamo Bay,
after three months of dealing with
those fuckers at homeland security.
Classified as enemy combatants.
No response, nothing.
What did he do? Go to a
training camp or something?
What are you talking about?
He didn't do anything.
He was visiting family.
He probably did something.
No, he didn't.
So you're from Pakistan?
My family is.
I was born here in the us.
Why did you join?
You mean the army?
Yeah.
I needed a job and
after 911 and high school
it was the only thing.
And you had to go to Iraq?
Yes.
-Where were you stationed?
-Bagdad?
Bagdad at first yes.
Then we went to fallujah
in the anbar province
and it was something
totally different.
What do you mean different?
Let's just say your people really
know how to hate each other.
What do you know
about my people?
I've seen my fair share
of what they're capable of.
Sunni killing shiite.
Shiite killing sunni.
And you want to know
the funny part?
What's the funny part?
You call it the
religion of peace.
And you're trying to
spread democracy right?
Or your version of it by
the push of a button?
Please.
Come here.
What?
I want to show you something.
What is it?
Back pocket.
Open it.
Inside there's a picture.
Who's this?
That's Jasmin.
I'm trying to bring
her over here.
Is she your wife?
Fiancee.
Where did you meet her?
I was stationed in the diyala province
on the east side of the tigris river.
As part of an operation we had
to block enemy movement
to Baghdad and to baqubah.
We had to clear the supply route
for humanitarian relief
and food supply.
She worked for the
humanitarian office in Bagdad.
What did her family say?
She only has a sister.
Her brother in law caused
a few problems at first but
I got him a job in the
Iraqi security forces.
She's beautiful.
She is.
I can't wait to be with her.
I'm going for a short walk.
Do you want to come?
I don't know.
I think we should keep
a low profile
leave the house
as little as possible.
-Ok.
-But...
I mean if you want
to go that's fine.
No. No, you're right.
Would you like to have
a fruit drink with me?
-Sure.
-Yeah?
Sit down.
Have a seat.
Relax I'll bring it to you.
Ok?
Like he had a frog
in his throat or something.
But you know,
he's a good guy though.
What are you doing?
Hamal! Calm down.
Don't tell me to calm down.
What were you doing?
Nothing.
I don't know.
I asked you what you were doing.
Put a scarf on.
Hamal.
We were just watching TV.
TV?
Yes! TV.
Hey, listen.
You really smell bad you know.
Why don't you go do wudu?
It's almost time for asr. Ok?
Hello?
Stay away from my sister.
Just go.
Ok, you done?
Come on, come on.
Pinch it. Let's go.
Come on.
Go put on the tape.
Ok, go get the bucket.
I was just wondering if you
wanted to hear a funny story?
Hold on. Hold on. Just let me
breath for a couple of minutes.
So how about that funny story?
What?
Ok, so...
Christmas a couple of years ago
my entire unit was at fort benning
before our next deployment.
One day I was the first
to wake up.
The other five guys
were still asleep.
So this guy mccormick wakes up.
And he tells me he's going
to fart in Rivera's face.
So he stand up and he lets out a
silent fart right in this face.
We started laughing,
because he was about to wake up.
So then Rivera wakes up not knowing he
had a fart thrown inches from his face.
He gets up and looks over at this
guy Winston who's still sleeping.
Then back at us and he smiles
and he whispers.
"Hey, guys. I'm going to
fart in Winston's face."
So he gets up.
Walks over to Winston
gets ready to throw
a fart in his face,
when Winston rolls over.
Keep in mind still asleep
and throws one of the loudest
farts we have ever heard.
I mean we were dying laughing.
It's a true story.
Hey.
What the fuck is
going on in here?
We're laughing over a joke.
So what we're doing here
is a joke to you?
This is all a joke to you.
Take it easy brother.
This guy is our enemy
do you understand that?
I need you to be a professional
and keep your mouth shut.
And his.
Go get some sleep.
I'll keep an eye on him.
What?
Just go.
Go.
Here is some breakfast.
Could you tell your... brother?
It's his turn to
watch the prisoner.
We have to talk about him.
Ok, later.
I'm worried.
Yeah so...
I don't... I don't know what
to do about your brother.
I mean...
He's got so many issues.
I know.
Just take it easy on him.
You look stressed out.
When this is all over,
I like to travel
with you to Syria.
Who's guarding the prisoner?
Didn't I tell you to stay away
from my sister?
Hamal, come on.
You be quiet.
And put a scarf on.
You know what? Get up.
Get up and go to your room.
Get your hands off her.
We weren't doing anything.
Don't fucking touch her.
Didn't I tell you
to stay away from her?
It's ok, Asad.
You need help Hamal.
I see you talk to her like that
again I'll rip your throat out.
I like to see you try.
Psycho.
What are you doing here?
Listen. I want you to stop
what you're doing.
Is this about me and Asad?
What do you think?
There is nothing going on.
Hamal is just taking it badly.
All I'm saying is wait.
He's on edge and
this is too much.
Look at me.
Ok.
Yeah it's me.
Finish it.
Get rid of the other American.
Do it tomorrow.
Ok.
The world is a screwed up place.
I'm planning on staying away
from it as much as possible.
How are you going to do that?
Build my own world.
What's your favorite
part of the world?
I don't know.
Come on man,
where would you live?
Where would you?
I was going to move to Nebraska.
I love Nebraska.
Visited my uncle
before my deployment to Iraq.
It's...
It's a little cold
but you know it's peaceful.
Start my own business...
House...
Bring Jasmin over...
Family...
You know what I mean?
Don't tell me
you don't know what I mean?
What the fuck is going on here?
Just chatting.
Shut up.
What the fuck are you doing?
You think this guy
is your friend or something?
No. No. I know.
-You know what?
Meeting in one hour.
Ok, so I spoke with Al-Saqri
and...
We have to go on
with the operation.
Did he say we have to kill
the other prisoner too?
Yes.
We have to finish the operation.
None of this is working.
We have our orders
and we do it tomorrow.
I don't think we should kill
him.
What?
He's engaged.
So?
To an Iraqi.
He's trying to bring her over
here.
I told you not to speak to that
prisoner.
Didn't I tell you not to speak
to that prisoner?
He's a good guy.
How do you know that?
Do you know how many muslims
he's killed?
No, you don't know that.
I just don't think
it's the right thing to do.
He's a soldier.
And you are a soldier.
Do you understand that?
Of course.
Ok.
So you do as you're told.
-Besides what do you want to do?
-You want to set him free?
No, really, I mean
do you want to set him free?
No.
Orders are orders.
You do as you're told.
All right.
I heard you.
Smells good.
That other guys,
is he in charge?
Asad?
He's my brother's best friend.
Reminds me of my drill sergeant
at fort benning.
You shouldn't take
it personally.
They're going to make you do it,
aren't they?
Kill me.
Is this my last meal?
Thank you.
It was good.
Do you have a woman, Shahin?
You don't shut up do you?
You're the only person
I can talk to around here.
Women are trouble.
Some women are.
Not all but...
Jasmin wasn't any trouble.
No trouble at all.
And her father was great.
I thought she didn't
have a family.
Only her sister.
Roadside bomb.
I was on my way to baqubah
when I heard.
I rushed to Bagdad but...
He had already passed
once I got to the hospital.
Is she a good woman?
She's a great woman.
I love her Shahin.
I'm thinking of her right now.
I want you to do something for
me Shahin.
What?
When they kill me.
Don't think like that.
They're going to kill me.
They have to.
I mean what else are they going
to do?
You're a soldier Shahin.
I need you to let her know,
that she's the only person I wanted
to spend the rest of my life with.
I want you to write to her.
The email address
is in my wallet.
Where is everyone?
I don't know.
Inside?
Fahdah.
Fahdah are you in there?
Overnight the president
received updates
from his assistant
for homeland security
on the ongoing investigation
into these kidnappings
in the Tampa Bay area.
The president put out a
statement
calling for unity
where were you?
He said words cannot begin to
express our sorrow
for the two families who are
grieving
were you in Fahdah's room?
What?
What were you doing in her room?
This is a reminder that we live
in a dangerous world
with threats from
those...
We were talking.
Why was the room locked?
Didn't I tell you
to stay away from her?
Hamal we were just talking.
You disgust me.
Hey! I'm talking to you.
-Did you hear me?
-Don't touch me.
Hamal please.
Fahdah stay out of this.
Didn't I tell you
to stay away from my sister?
I need you to back down now.
I'm not backing away.
What is your problem
your sister is a grown woman
in case you didn't realize that.
You're the lowest of the low
with no respect for anybody.
Don't fucking touch me.
You're lower than a dog.
And you are psycho.
You understand?
I don't know what happened to you in
Bagdad when your parents got killed,
but you got some serious issues.
How did...
Don't talk about my parents.
You don't know anything.
Hamal stop.
Don't.
I said don't... fucking touch
me.
Asad.
Asad, no.
He shouldn't have hit me.
No.
No, Asad.
Hang on, Habibi.
Hang on.
No. No. No, Asad.
No, Asad.
Stay with me.
No.
No, Asad.
Say something.
Call 911.
Asad?
No.
What happened?
He shouldn't have hit me.
So you stab him.
You take a knife
and you stab him.
If I do this are you
going to stab me too?
Are you going to stab everyone?
It was self-defense.
How is stabbing him
in the back self-defense?
Tell me.
Tell me how it's self-defense?
You killed your own kind.
Do you understand that?
This is bullshit.
This is total and
complete bullshit.
Unbelievable.
We need to take this
to the bathroom.
And we need to clean this up.
I'm going to get a sheet.
Go fix that mess.
I'm going to clean up.
I'm in the garage.
We have to give him
a proper burial.
Islam says that we have to
bury him as soon as...
I know what islam says.
I mean what do you suggest we
do? Bury him in the backyard?
There is a pool back there.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
We could...
Leave him at the mosque.
You really are an idiot.
I mean ok what do we do
when we leave him at the mosque?
With cameras everywhere the cops
will be at our doors within hours.
You know what just go clean up.
We have to do something.
We can't just leave him here.
We have to bury him
in the forest somewhere.
We'll wash him properly.
We'll wrap him in
clean white sheets.
We'll pray over him.
And we'll bury him.
We'll do it tomorrow.
I thought I saw something.
I thought I saw
some movement too.
I guess not.
Well.
Hello?
Hi I'm officer Kenneth
this is officer Cooper.
We received notice of a disturbance
coming from this house.
A disturbance?
Yes.
There is no disturbance here.
Can we come in?
What's your name, sir?
Hamal.
May I?
Sure.
Would you know where the
disturbance actually came from?
No, I would not. I...
I didn't hear anything.
And the others living here?
What about them?
Did they hear something?
No, not that I know of.
Have you heard anything or seen
anything suspicious around here
in the last couple of hours?
No, nothing. Sorry.
Anyone else home?
Only my sister she's
sleeping in... in her room.
Can you get her?
You want me to wake her up?
We won't be long.
Fahdah.
What do you want psycho?
Take it easy.
The cops are here.
They want to talk to you.
Please.
Are you ok ma'am?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yes, just a little tired.
Why did you call your
brother a psycho?
We had a little fight.
What about?
Excuse me?
What was the fight about?
Just...
Nothing really.
Trivial? Household?
Ok, well...
We received a call
of a disturbance
coming from this home.
A disturbance?
Yes?
Could it have been the fight
between you and your brother?
Fight?
Yes.
Yes. Yes. I... I mean...
I might have raised
my voice a bit,
but I don't think people outside
could have heard.
Well maybe they did.
Did you hear anything
before the fight?
No.
Nothing.
What about after?
No, nothing.
Well you call me
if you hear something.
Yes officer.
Definitely.
Can I take a look around?
Yeah sure.
So this is the office?
I thought you said
no one else was home?
This is my other roommate
he's...
Just went out for a walk.
Went out for a walk.
And what's your name sir?
Shahin.
I'm officer Kenneth.
This is officer Cooper.
We're here because of a
disturbance call we got.
I don't know anything
about a disturbance.
How long have you been gone?
Just about an hour.
And where did you go?
For a walk just down the street.
Ok.
Is there anyone
else living here?
No.
Just the three of us.
Ok.
And the bedrooms are this way?
Yeah.
Ok.
Well
that's it then.
What's that?
It's a verse from the quran.
What's it mean?
It says...
He's Allah the one and only.
Tell you what.
Here's my card.
You hear anything,
you give me a call
of course officer.
Ma'am?
You sure you ok?
Yes. Yes I'm fine.
Excellent you guys have
a good evening.
I think somebody was following
me when I was running.
Don't be ridiculous.
You're being paranoid.
I don't know.
You know what I think.
I think it's time
to end this operation.
What are we going
to tell Mr. Al-Saqri?
Look. I've made up my mind.
This operation is off.
It's final I'm done.
Think about it.
No.
Come on Shahin
what else are we supposed to do?
I said no.
Fahdah?
Leave me out of this.
This operation is over.
We have to talk to Mr. Al-Saqri.
And what do you suppose
we tell Mr. Al-Saqri?
About Asad and the fact
that you killed him.
Collateral damage.
How is that collateral damage?
This is a war.
You're losing your mind.
I'm going to my room.
I'm going to get some sleep.
Why don't you guard him?
-Get up on the ground.
-On the floor.
-Get on the ground mother fucker.
-Get on the ground.
-Shut the fuck up.
-On the ground.
Shut the fuck up on the ground.
On the ground.
Shut the fuck up.
-Get on the ground now.
-Get up and get on the ground.
Get up and get on the ground
now.
Shut up and get up on the
ground.
Shut up.
-Clear.
-Shut the fuck up.
-Get on the ground.
-Get on the floor.
Sergeant Young?
Sergeant Donald Young?
We're here to
take you home, sir.
Thank you.
Hi how are you?
I'm fine.
Ok.
Here's your statement.
Now I need you to read
over this carefully.
And then sign it at the bottom
when you're ready. Ok?
Well my colleague will
be in with you shortly.
He wants to talk to you
regarding your cooperation
in the capture of Mr. Al-Saqri.
I'll be right outside
if you need me. Ok?
This is Al-Saqri.
My men are in place.
Launch operation capitol.
What about the girl?
I'll take care of the girl.
She won't leave
the building alive.
Good. Good.
Get up.
Mr. askani. You're being transported
to Guantanamo bay Cuba,
where you will be held
as an enemy combatant
of the United States
until further notice.
Stand up.
You got to see this.
No. No. No right
now I'm serious.
Ok. Can you watch him?
First reports are coming in of an
attack on the United States capitol.
At least ten people have
been taken to the hospital
including several
congressmen.
No one has claimed
responsibility for the attack,
but this comes on the heels
of the terrorist kidnapping
of the two us soldiers who
served in Iraq and Afghanistan.
Sergeant Donald Young,
one of the soldiers,
was rescued last night
from a terror cell
operating in Tampa, Florida.