Congratulations, Joe.
I don't know how you pulled it
off my brother.
-Sebastian Case.
-Who?
Remember Alfonso Rafael?
Federico Sebastian.
The waiter.
Guy was a major gun runner.
You should have seen the
stockpile.
I knew he wasn't as goofy as
he looked. Anyway,
you're getting it easy
man. Five weeks paid vacation.
I'm stuck out here on patrol.
Look who's here.
-Hey, stranger.
-Hey.
Can I steal you away?
-Absolutely, bro.
-See you later.
See you tomorrow
you two lovebirds.
Don't get into any trouble,
but if you do,
name it after me.
I can't believe I have you to
myself for a whole month.
You know what I'm thinking?
A tropical island
-getaway.
-Maui.
Towel outs. Tahiti
-Micronesia.
-Yes. The South Pacific. Yes, I love it.
Please. Come on.
Thank you mister.
-You're welcome sweetheart.
-Wow, you're
-pretty.
-Thank you.
Do you think, if we
maybe had a couple
little samurais in a row.
Maybe soon.
Love you, Joe.
You know, Jennifer,
it's always been kind of
awkward for me to say this, but
I just want you to know
that after all these years
together, I...
Officer, my sister is missing.
You gotta help.
I went to go get her ice cream
and when I came back, she
-was gone.
-Alright kid, calm down.
Where is she? Where
did you see her last?
She's got brown hair.
It's tied in a pony tail.
She's wearing all pink.
Come on. You gotta hurry.
She's by the trees over there.
Jen!
Take care of yourself.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no!
No!
No, not tonight.
I don't feel so hot.
What's the matter my love?
Things are changing.
What is?
The times. I had to approve
a district plan today.
You wouldn't understand.
The district plan to
allow the inner universal trade
treaty with shinjuku?
Yeah, they gave me the money.
So, I, had to do it.
Katana might kill me for this.
Up until tonight, you're
pretty loyal to the Katana,
weren't you?
Yes, I was.
And I if I don't get caught,
I might have dodged
a clan war between
the Katana and the Shinjuku.
Which you inadvertently started?
Relax.
I have something just
what you need.
What is that?
Don't worry. It will be gentle.
It will send you somewhere
far beyond
the universe.
Relax.
I love you too.
My father is the
Katana's top general
enforcer, Tadishi Wakanaga.
He found me in the streets
as a baby and
raised me as his own.
I am his Katana blood.
I'll kill you!
To tell you the truth,
so what?
You're heading
toward the freezer.
I've grown soft in my old age.
I've spent the past twenty years
rebuilding this organization.
We are now well respected in
our own home country.
What is the matter, godfather?
We may have reformed,
but our enemies have not.
The Shinjuku
have infiltrated us.
We are about to lose everything
we worked so hard to build.
We knew this day would come.
-He has returned.
-Joe Marshall?
That's impossible.
You are mistaken I believe.
Do not talk to your
elders like that, Dogge.
Hey!
In this room, Dogge Chan
is a junior CEO.
She has the floor.
How did you know he has risen?
After all these years?
It was a vision.
In a foretold dream.
A vision?
In a dream?
And you,
did you have such a vision?
No.
But I felt it in my bones.
The storm is coming and the
evil one will rise again.
What is the meaning of all
this? Who is the evil one?
If you speak again,
I will slice you.
An ancient prophecy in his
family.
Joe Marshall is
an evil creature.
One of us will be chosen
to fight and defeat him.
If Marshall returns, our rivals
with side with him
-like they did before.
-For every Messiah,
there is an opposite.
I have fought Joe Marshall.
You must defeat him, and
bring peace to our country.
Do you take this
directive of honor?
It's my destiny.
The passion burns like a fire
that I have never felt before.
The honor is mine.
The planets, the stars, the universe.
I have watched your dinosaurs
operating under your
sickening fear of human
instinct instead of cosmic forces
which guide us.
The planets show me mine
because I am the chosen one.
Hello. Red Eye Night Club?
Bye.
Shit.
Are you ok?
-Yeah.
-Did I work you out that much?
You need to get back
in shape baby.
You work too much.
All that bang bang shit goes
straight to the gut.
It's amazing how much asian technology
has advanced in 25 years.
So much has changed,
but everything's still the same.
We still get everything from
holy wars to petty crime.
Nothing really changes.
People don't change.
Looks like you had a long
weekend, hey Frank?
-What?
-A dead senator.
So what do you think?
Wow. That is a rare
Katana medallion.
Wasn't it you and
that other guy, Marlo
-that stopped him?
-It's Marshall, Joe Marshall.
You know, this is the third
murder this month.
They were Japanese, Ginza clan.
Wow, so you think,
we have a Yakuza clan war on
our hands between
Ginzas and the Katanas?
We need to take a trip together.
Yeah.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I propose a toast.
To our honorable master,
Kitano!
It has been a win fall,
Leonard.
A big fat win all around.
For years, we've been
the underdogs, but no longer.
With the new inter-universal
treaty, we will have
full reign of the New American
northwest.
Railways lines will be ours,
finally.
And we have begun
a new operation.
You speak when I tell you to!
This doesn't look so good. You
should have never let her so much.
-You know how she gets.
-Me?
-Was supposed to be guarding her.
-I'm a woman.
-Let's show the mother fucker!
-Go!
-Shinjuku!
-Long live the Shinjuku!
What is the meaning of this?
The Moloch has risen.
I am the elected one
who has delivered.
I will eliminate all your atoms
and molecules.
The land of opportunity
is for everyone.
-It's wake up and play.
-The Katana has risen!
Surrender to Katana!
Very hard.
Punk bitch.
Ok, girls. Lunch time.
Avenge me!
I shall!
As god as my witness,
I will avenge you!
That's the master Katana's
VP, as I'm sure you
know, and Leonard
my partner, we are the
co-owners of this club.
You going to take my statement?
Was your buddy involved in
any Katana business? Hakuza?
Ginza? Guzu?
I'll take over from here,
alright?
-Please, Gail.
-Remember, you're not supposed
-to be on this case.
-Gail, please,
if anyone knows anything about
Oriental culture and their operations,
-you know it's me.
-I know.
I took them down before.
I know!
Why do you make it
so hard for yourself?
Frank, please.
Let's not go there.
What do you mean I'm not
officially on the case?
-Captain, you need me on this case!
-You on this case?
I need you on this
case like I need fleas
-circling my asshole.
-This has the Katana stank all over it.
I know they're back.
And with the body count rising,
it won't be long before
they Shinjuku and
the Ginza retaliate.
Yeah, and where's your proof?
What makes you think you have
enough evidence, dick head?
You read the witness statement. You know
the beating was tied to the Shinjuku.
We do not have a statement
from the owner.
I was there, man.
You were there does not
constitute a statement.
Now look. File the rest of your
paperwork and get the
hell out of here?
Go, go, go. Out!
-Ail's hair. No, go, go, goodbye.
-Yes, sir.
This is not a capital tone.
Jesus.
Dammit.
Hey, Frank! About
those medallions.
I got you a list of japanese artistsans
who specialize in these engravings.
Tokugawa Shogunate, late
nineteenth century
Do these look familiar?
I have a graphic memory.
I've seen these medallions.
In the living room of
a very close friend.
These medallions were
crafted by a local artist.
Named Yasuhiro Morikawa.
The distributor buys and sells
online. So, I couldn't get
an office address but I tracked
delivery services
and got you a location.
Yeah, Harmon
-owes you a raise Bobby.
-Yeah.
GPS systems is not working.
I don't know if I'm on the
right track or not.
Morikawa. Morikawaba.
Whatever this
guy's name is. Where is he?
What is this place. Jeez?
God. Look at all these
contraptions.
What the hell is this?
This doesn't look like a medallion
factory. Morikawa, are you here?
Anybody here?
Hello.
Morikawa.
Morikawa, are you here?
Morikawa, where are you?
What's with this music?
Where's it coming from?
Morikawa, where are
you? Are you here?
Anybody home?
Morikawa, where are you?
Anybody here?
I know you've
been looking for me
Washington. So, that's
what you've been doing.
Hiding out in Buddha land, while the
rest of the world has gone to shit.
Actually, it's more
Shinto than Buddhist.
Masters of Japan like
to hand pick the best
-aspects of their culture.
-Masters in Japan.
-My ass.
-That's a nice hello, Frank.
Good to see you, Joe.
There's been a string of
murders. It has
a smell of Katana.
The Shinjukus and Ginzas are
involved. Look familiar?
They should. I made them.
-Where is all this Morikawa?
-Yasuhiro Morikawa
is a pseudonym for
Joseph Marshall.
So he's not japanese either.
-You're such a fraud Joe.
-Hey.
So go to hell and
leave me alone.
Just give me the facts, Joe.
There were eight engravings.
Based upon the eight
virtues of the samurai.
Right, right, the Bushido code.
They were sold to a private
collector. Master Kitano.
Who was murdered two nights ago.
You are gonna come with me
downtown. This gang
-is about to turn nuclear.
-I foresworn violence, Frank.
I no longer live by the sword.
What about the code?
The code of
justice and courage and honesty?
Aren't they part of your code?
-So you were paying attention.
-You were a hero man.
When you disappeared,
people lost faith.
Now the world is a bit more
complicated. Come on man.
-What do you say?
-I have no stake in this
fight, Frank. Just let
me exist in peace.
You abandoned me man.
I got you covered, Joe.
What the hell
was that? I don't know.
I don't know, Joe.
You tell me. It's your medallions
showing up at all these murder scenes.
It's either they're
coming after me
because I'm getting
close. Too close.
Or they're gunning after
you to stop you from telling
-me something.
-What do I have to tell you?
I don't know man? All I know
is I just think
the deeper I dig,
I just get this feeling that
this is all connected to Jennifer's
death 25 years ago and
I just need your help.
-Please, come on.
-You need my help?
I came to you twenty-five years
ago. When I was following up
all my clues and all my
leads, trying to find out who
killed my wife,
and all I asked you to do is get
me the file on Captain Roma's desk
from internal affairs. You
turned your back on me.
Some of us don't have the
luxury of being a rogue cop.
We go by the book,
and I'm a by the book
brother. Last time you
and I were up against
this Katana gang, you
had no problem being judge
jury and executioner.
I'm getting too old for this.
I'm tired.
But I'm not washed up.
Just partner with me
man. One last time.
Help me out. I promise you we
will re-open the case and find
out who killed your wife and
then you can reign down
your deadly vengeance.
Ok, partner.
Let me grab my gear.
Empty plane. I like it this way.
Never been on a plane before.
No, shit. A worldly man like you?
I don't travel much.
My god.
Mr. Washington. Mr. Marshall.
How nice to see you around
after all those years.
-You gotta be kidding me.
-Mr. Sebastian.
I heard they cleared you of all
those charges a few years ago.
-Including that gun running beef.
-Yes.
I turn around my life. Now,
I'm an honest
member of the society.
Here I am.
-Anything to drink? I'll have a vodka.
-Vodka, sir.
-Thank you.
-How about you, Mr. Marshall?
-Kombucha, please.
-Kombucha.
That is a very expensive...
How about a
camomile ice tea, please.
Camomile ice tea.
Right away, sir.
What's that shit
you're drinking?
It relaxes me, after
what you've done.
-What I've done?
-The exact violence
I told you I want no part of.
Hey mister, do you want to buy
some cookies?
-No, thank you, sweetheart.
-How about some kale chips, mister?
-I'm fine.
-Shut up girls.
This is not a free
trade zone here.
Dude! I'm gonna kill your fucking
ass if you don't shut up right now.
Does your office
have to put us side by side
on this flight for four hours?
I would have been perfectly happy
looking at the back of your head.
Now, that's the Joe I'm used to.
Hey, what if I asked the captain
to grant you a temporary pass
see. You do good,
you're back on the force.
No.
Alright, ok.
Whatever you say.
Mr. Washington.
Here's a gift for you.
Congratulations.
My name is Alfonso
Frederico Sebastian.
The black gift.
Let me guess. You
want to know what
-book I'm reading.
-No.
Actually I was wondering
what that device is.
This?
This is so I don't have to carry twelve
heavy books every time I get on a plane.
-It's my entire library.
-Excuse me, um,
have we met somewhere before?
I don't think so.
What's your name?
Joe.
Joe. I'm Milena.
-And what do you do Joe?
-I'm a...
Follow my plan.
The time is now. Kill them.
Do it. Kill them all!
I'm confused.
Are we on the same side?
Let's go back to the office.
What the hell was that?
I have no fucking idea.
Did you recognize
anyone on the plane?
No.
Name.
-Milena Roberts. Occupation.
-Art broker.
-What kind of art?
-Oriental antiques.
-Where do you get your art from?
-Private collectors.
-Are you married?
-No.
-Boyfriend?
-Relation?
-No.
-How do you explain?
-Frank,
she's been through a lot. This
is turning into an interrogation.
She could use a little
peace and comfort.
Can you come back
tomorrow and talk to us?
Yes.
-Can I take you home?
-Yes. Thank you, Mr. Marshall.
-Hey, guys. You staying out of trouble?
-Yeah, man.
-Been sober for five months now.
-Good for you.
Hey, you gotta stick with dude.
He'll get you cleaned up in no time.
Is that right?
Those guys really
look up to you, Frank.
I do my part.
Hi, Frank. The usual.
Good. Hey baby girl,
-ou bring your old lady out here?
-Sure.
You're really
turning into a cliche.
-Sure is good though.
-The last time you saw
-the inside of a gym.
-Man, I'm just as fit as I was
when I first joined the force.
I don't care if there is an
import on sashimi
we have a party of fifty
tonight.
-My god, Joe!
-Peggy.
How are you?
Hannah, get out here.
Are you my daddy?
-So you're running this place now?
-Well, someone's got to, Joe.
-Lly good to see you again, Peggy.
-Well, I hate to rain
on this happy reunion, but
we need some inside dirt.
Of course. It's the only
reason Washington ever
-comes to see me.
-The only reason?
Let's just say that long stakeouts
are a thing of the past.
-So, what do you need?
-What can you tell me about
-the Red Eye Night Club?
-Only that the Shinjukus
now lost their leader and
key man, Master Kitano.
It's a real shame. I remember
when he helped us out
with the Katana gang. He even
convinced the Ginza heads
to turn state evidence, but the
Shinjukus weren't Kamikaze
like the Katanas.
They had more style.
They hid in plain site
like cameleons.
They've been really quiet recently
until the inner universal
treaty was granted to them.
How would that have effected
the Katana stature?
Under the treaty, the Katana's
chance of survival is like an ice
cube in a thousand degree oven.
Shit. Thousand degrees?
Looks like the Shinjuku
gang got re-armed.
With the
Shinjuku Kitano's death,
could be looking at
a full out clan war.
-Who's next in line?
-His son.
Goes by the name of Linton, but
he's a real enigma.
-E really sees or hears from him.
-We'd better get going.
You're staying for lunch.
How about a glass of Romo Wine?
Now this is a reunion.
Cheers.
The horror.
No!
It's not fair!
He cannot be gone!
No!
You have no right accusing me
like this. You're the one who's
-responsible.
-Me? Are you fucking kidding me?
Take some fucking responsibility
for once you, bastard.
Bastard?
How dare you say that?
-I'll come for you. I got my eyes on you.
-Sit your fucking ass down.
Right now and god dammit, don't
threaten me. I swear to god
you fucking owe me. You just wait
until the organization arrives.
You're scaring me.
Hey!
Hey! Knock it off!
Knock it off! Knock it off
you imbecilic clowns!
Madness, just madness.
I know I'm going to be
crucified for this, but
-welcome back, Joe.
-Thanks, captain.
You're gonna need this.
That's alright.
I got all I need.
It's good to finally see you
guys
together again. I've been
looking forward to this
-magnificent day.
-Don't look so surprised, Marshall.
-I mean, people recognize mediocrity.
-Marshall?
Marshall, my god.
Hey, how are you? Cashew?
-No, thanks.
-I love my nuts.
Anyway, here is
the file of the last
three murders, ok, and if
you're dealing with the Yakuza,
watch your back. You don't
have to remind me of that.
Do we have the needed intel
if the Ginzas are involved?
That's really funny.
That you should ask because
Roger Takahara of the Ginza
biotech. He arrived today
in LA for a summit.
Ginzu knives. I
own several myself.
They make good
stocking stuffers.
Ginza.
Looks like it's time for you
and I to set up some
surveillance. Now,
that's what I'm talking about.
Now boys, look,
I'm going to expect
some results. Alright, alright,
alright folks, don't let the
door hit you in the ass.
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
It's madness.
It's just madness.
Fujiyama son.
Our Tokyo attack
squad came back dead.
Joe Marshall has
rejoined the force.
Eliminating Shinjuku leader
Kitano was a success and we know
Takahara has arrived
in Los Angeles.
-The time to strike is now.
-Have patience, Dogge Chan.
We have been patient
for 25 years.
We have no choice
but to move forward.
The fire is burning now. Please,
let me take care of Ginza Takahara.
-The victory should be ours.
-I want him dead.
I want him more than dead.
I want his death to be
a lesson, an example
to all the clan.
Everywhere! That no Katana
will be pushed around
-or threatened with our honor.
-I will make you
proud and prove that
your lessons have been
profound and proficient.
I can handle it.
I've warned the Ginza
nothing will stop me!
Enough. We have
much ahead of us.
Now, I am tired.
I must get some rest.
Disappoint love.
I just lost one.
You dirty bird.
Hello.
Tina, the happy beaver.
It's the complex.
I know how to get
to the complex.
-Ave to give me that information.
-No.
Hannah, you do. I need
to have that information.
-No, you don't understand.
-You need to tell me.
I can't. I won't.
Jennifer!
-Smells great.
-One thing that I'm really
good at is whipping up a
fantastic meal
-for a beautiful girl.
-Well, thank you.
So, how's my cooking?
Good. It's good.
You're blushing, Joe.
I just can't get over how comfortable
and familiar I feel with you.
So, what do you
want to do today?
We can go shopping.
We can see a movie.
Maybe take in a winery.
It all sounds good.
By the order of Shinjuku,
by the law of Shimura
Hashimura alliance,
you Mister Ross saw the benefits
are here by the order to commit
harry carry for the crime of
murder our Shinjuku minister
Regime Azacazu.
AKA Tyler Kimbell.
Please. Have mercy.
You don't understand.
They're going against you.
The Katana is going
after all of us!
And they brought the warrior.
Him!
Hlm!
No!
You know Milena,
have you ever thought about
-going blonde?
-Blonde?
For a change.
Got eyes on the Katana.
Are you sure it's them?
No, not really.
You wanna take a look?
Namu myoho renge kyo.
Namu. Is there a problem?
Right now I'm glad we're
not gonna pull an all nighter.
-Namu myoho renge kyo.
-Come on.
Come on. Take a look.
They're here.
I'm going in.
Hey.
You're gonna need this.
Thanks partner.
I wanna talk to you!
Frank, can you hear me?
I'm on the roof.
Where are you?
Yo answer me. You're gonna
get killed. Get out of there.
Joe! Joe!
Frank.
-Can you hear me?
-I got you covered, Joe.
Copy. I'm going in.
Would you care for
some kale chips sir?
Fresh from the well-paid
employees at our factories in
-Portland Washington.
-Portland Washington?
I think you better study
your pacific northwest.
Joe, I have definite
confirmation that
Dogge Sakamoto was
spotted near the Red Eye.
Just before the Katana murder
and know she's eyeing
Roger Takahara of the Ginza clan's
enforcer, Lauren Kimura.
Hey there, what
can I do for you?
-Ey there, what can I do for you?
-One kabuto, please.
And some kale chips.
Sure you wouldn't like
something stronger?
You know, they say if
you drink that stuff
you'll live longer. I
just say it feels longer.
Because it tastes like shit.
It's like being married to
the wrong woman, right?
My first wife for example.
Married almost 8 years until it
feels like 8 minutes, underwater.
But I got a great wife
now. My second wife.
She's great.
Got a couple kids.
You know how kids are. Always got their
hand out right? Money, money, money.
Give me money. Alright.
I'm gonna go clean up
some glasses and give me a
shout if you need anything.
Pleasure chatting.
My, my.
Who might you be?
Joe. Joseph Tinen.
-I'm with the Katana office.
-Katano's dead.
Old news. I'm sure
you know who I am.
Dogge Sakamoto,
junior vice president
of Tokyo Robotics Incorporated.
You see that man over there?
He's not a good man.
He's corrupt.
I have a secret, Mr. Joe.
Something big
is about to happen here.
And you cannot escape.
Do me a favor.
Don't keep it warm.
Milena.
-What are you doing here?
-Happy birthday, Joe.
-Wow.
-Do you like it?
Takahara, this is the land of
opportunity and freedom and yet,
you insist on taking the freedom
and opportunity from the Katana.
You have lifted us
out of existence.
Joe!
Answer me! Answer me!
You're gonna get killed.
I'm the queen of death.
Look at me, you mother fuckers.
Go kiss your ancestors.
Kill them all! Kill them all!
I'm gonna get us out of here.
-Hirohito.
-What?
Joe and Milena, I got your back.
It sure ain't like
-the old days.
-Amen to that.
-Feels like a club up my ass.
-Let's get out of here, partner.
What is that?
No, I can't.
Is that the map?
It is the map. It's the
map to the complex.
The complex?
-You need to give me that map.
-No, no.
No. I must not.
The plan is moving forward.
All elements
are in place. Joe Marshall
is in love with me.
Poor fool.
-Conquest should be ours my love.
-I love you.
Come here.
Thank you.
You hold that a lot.
Your wife's?
I lost someone too you know.
He was my heart and soul.
Joe, I can't bring
her back. I know that.
But what I can do
is create a world where
that love can exist.
I just want to go away with you.
This isn't the city
I used to know.
People used to look up to us.
The corporations
have taken over.
It's like the people don't even
matter anymore.
The system doesn't work.
This. This is all forgery.
It's a corruption
of the human condition.
I saw this coming
even before my wife took a
bullet to the chest.
Can you believe in us?
Us?
I believe in you Joe.
I am not you!
I will never
be you!
I am Joe
Marshall!
No!
The day has come my
friend. We have risen
and secured all
that's necessary.
We can only succeed and prevail
from here forth.
Due to necessary nutrients.
It will be an honor
joining you on this journey.
My senior.
You taught me everything I know.
If you die,
I die with you.
You're always trying to escape.
You are like a Houdini. I was
fucking partner man and you
left me high and dry.
I stuck it out far beyond
anything you can understand.
Why don't you just try to do
your job and join us?
The force? This job?
They took everything from you.
It's you. You don't
exist.
That was you.
Excuse me?
When I was a kid,
I was on a camping trip and I swear I
saw you fighting some old Japanese dude
-in the woods, with a sword.
-No, that wasn't me.
There's a lot of maniac cops
running around LA.
Sorry to bother you.
Come on honey. Let's leave
these nice gentlemen alone.
By the way, your partner
is kind of hot.
Frank, what are you doing here?
You seen the girl lately?
No, I've been trying
to call her all day.
-Not sure I like your tone.
-You won't find her.
She skipped town man.
-What are you talking about?
-Milena Roberts.
It's not her real name.
She goes by several aliases.
It's Anya Tavolva,
Marlena McDonald.
She was fired by NYPD
ten years ago.
-She's playing you, man.
-Playing me? Playing me how?
I think she slipped you some
hallucinogens.
She's manipulating you.
I got some intel from Higgins.
A new building. A new location.
It's called a complex.
It's where all the
clans come together.
They're responsible for all
these attacks and murders.
They're trying to trap you.
Hold the weapon like it was
part of your body.
You know how to hold
the sword, don't you?
-Yes, I do.
-Mr. Katano.
I am undefeated.
Mr. Cozo.
-What's the news on Ginza?
-We don't expect any
retaliation any time soon.
However, the word on the street
is that Joe Marshall is back in
town and the Katana
believe that he
is the chosen one.
Hey, Washington. You and the
legend back together again.
Legend? From what I hear,
most people just thought
-I was dead.
-You fucking guys!
-Hey, Captain. Be nice. Nice?
-Nice, isn't in my vocabulary
-fighting the Kakuzu. You get it?
-Yes, sir.
Not another word. You're off
the case. Give me your badges.
You can't take my badge sir.
You can't! I worked all my life...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. To bring
down the Kakuzu in another 20 years.
Come on, Come on.
-Frank.
-No, don't say it.
And as for you, my
little provisional deputy.
You stay out of this mess because
it's my ass that's on the line.
Truth be told, the FBI is
taking over the damn case.
This is Director Cutter,
Federal Bureau Investigations.
Hello, my followers.
The case is under our
jurisdiction now.
Our organization will handle the Yakuza
problem expeditiously and fiercely.
We need your participation,
Mr. Marshall.
The forces in the world need to be
one of healthy spirit and energy.
You must join the regime.
Vitamins and herbs. Very good
for you. I take fifty a day.
Here. Drink it.
I said, drink it.
No, thanks.
Wuss.
Joe. Hey, Joe.
-T's going on man? Joe. Joe. Joe.
-Listen to me.
-I gotta go.
-Hey, Joe. Come on.
Hey that was a pretty cool move.
Are you going to teach me that like
you told me you would 20 years ago?
Where you going Joe?
The hell is wrong with that guy?
-How did I know you'd come by?
-Frank.
Yeah. Look whose peace you're
disturbing now.
Hey. I need your help.
I've sworn off violence man.
I came here to find inner peace.
Remember that one?
Don't bother me.
-I'm on suspension.
-Frank, I'm being serious.
Sorry, wrong number.
My ninjas have
failed me. It will
be I that kills you.
Damn.
Let's go get us some Katana.
-Ok, my man.
-Right on.
No!
I will handle that.
Give me the map.
But the complex? Certain guys.
I know what's gonna happen.
-Give me the map. No, our love.
-No, Niko, stay with me.
-I love you. Stay with me.
-Where is the map. I love you.
-Give me the map. I need the map.
-Stay with me.
-The map. Come on. You can do it.
-I love you.
I love you too.
Hey.
Please, don't go. Niko!
Marshall. Washington.
Listen, I think you two better
start watching your backs.
Captain Harmon. Well, he's
clean. I know this,
but there are some
higher ups that even
he has to answer to and I don't
think it's going to be very long.
-We'll be on the lookout.
-And Washington,
Jesus Christ, straighten
out your arms.
A 45 has a hell of a dig.
Hello, Joe.
Back again I see.
Good to see you, Lucky.
It's nice to see an old friend
after all these years.
How you been?
Well, I'm not so sure
about your lady friend.
You know, she claimed to be the PD.
I'm not sure about that because
she's been consorting
with the Katana executives. Now the
Feds have had an eye on this place.
They call it the complex.
But it's on embassy grounds and
they claim diplomatic immunity.
However, we do have a mole on the
inside and that's the key for you.
Now, if you get inside,
you contact him.
They call him Mola Ram.
You contact him and he'll help you.
The problem with the complex is
people walk in but a lot people
don't walk out. So, be careful.
See you soon.
Hey, Marshall.
Lucky isn't telling you telling
you the whole story.
If you go to the complex alone,
you might not make it back.
-I know.
-You sure you have to do this?
-I do.
-I have the map
that will lead you there.
This is the key
that will get you in.
-You feel you really need to go.
-Yeah.
You know, 25 years ago I lost
my arm, but I was given
a new life. I just
want to help out here.
I'd give you a hand,
but... Be well.
Namu myoho renge kyo.
-Okamura.
-Joe Marshall.
Samurai cop, it is I...
The evil in your brain.
It is I that keeps you awake.
I will share the secret of the
clan, but in return
I need your help
to kill every one
of my enemies. Do you hear me
samurai cop?
-I do.
-I need for you
to infiltrate the complex.
-Are you familiar with the complex?
-Yes.
When do you think you can
start on this journey?
As soon as possible,
Okamura son.
Tell me, Marshall. Do
you have what it takes
to rise to this challenge?
Samurai cop, don't fail me!
My warrior.
You should have gone to
japanese school.
It's over there.
Damn.
Damn Joe.
What did you do man?
Time is over for
you, Mr. Marshall.
You should have stopped
when you had the chance.
I'm gonna prosecute you
with your own system.
I am judge, jury and
executioner.
Vengeance is mine.
Ginzas are a one man jury.
-We are quality over your imperialism.
-And now Marshall,
the choice is yours.
Pull the string.
What is this?
I had miles to go.
There is no room for you.
Joe, go on your way.
God speed to you.
Remember Mola Ram!
Father! Father!
Father, I shall go
to the depths of hell
to avenge you. I shall
bring vengeance
and soul determination
to the kingdom. I shall
bring salvation.
You passed to the next level
samurai, but it ends here.
We finally got you and you
cannot escape.
Take him to the freezer!
You should have never come out
of your dead existence, Marshall.
You've done. You've uprooted us.
We are ghosts Marshall.
Not even a mirage.
Thought we broke up at the bar.
Dating game.
Over.
And now Joe,
I have you all to myself.
Do you want to play samurai?
Sweet.
It's over my darling, Dogge.
Now it's your chance
to make it right.
Do the right thing. We make
such a cute couple, don't we?
My italian lover.
I have watched you from afar.
My heart longs
for your touch.
In this lifetime on earth, Joe,
we are meant to be together.
-Not in this lifetime.
-Yes.
In this lifetime, Joe.
Shit. You made me bleed.
You're gonna pay for it.
Joe! You are mine.
We could have made such
an ultimate couple.
Just think of our
offspring together.
Only if you knew the pleasure
of being inside of me.
Joe.
Say goodbye!
What I've done
has been glorious.
Death is only a woman too.
Think of us.
It's not the final ending.
I'll be
I'll be back.
Why are you using
that medieval thing?
Because it brings
me good luck, Frank.
Shogun Takata gave this to me.
You're kidding me.
Let's go.
Hi Joe.
I was waiting entire my life for this.
You think you're
chosen one, Joe?
I never claimed to be.
You got that wrong, Joe,
and now
there is no more room
for words, Joe.
We have to do this.
This is something we must do!
There is no room for the words,
Joe.
No room at all!
I kill you Joe!
This is my destiny, Joe!
This is my birth rights!
Why you are
cheating my destiny,
Joe. Ever since
I burned. I earned, not burned.
Not born. Joe!
No one can stop me but I
can stop myself, but I will
not stop myself, Joe.
I own the palace. I own
25 of them and I built more.
I eat them for breakfast, Joe.
You got that?
I listen to humanity, Joe,
and I buried it in my sleep!
Ever since I was born, Joe.
When I reversed
little boys.
You gotta be a better.
I'm gonna kill you.
I will piss on your
eyes. I will throw
a curse on you.
Your mother will
not recognize you!
Chen Chow was my
best friend and he became
a woman because of alcohol.
Surprise stranger.
There is
something I have to tell you,
Samurai.
I'm listening.
My initiation to the Shinjuku.
I had to kill a girl.
A beautiful girl.
It was so easy.
She was so beautiful.
Most beautiful I ever saw.
I still see her in
my dreams, Joe.
Beautiful, long hair,
stained in red blood.
Red blood, Joe.
Red! She haunts me.
Wherever I go.
I see miracles. Elements.
You ever witness or see
the act of love and hate,
which both inspire me and
repel me, but I believe that love
is one continuous stream
which is never ends
It is through love to
experience ultimate love.
That what drives us
all, isn't it, Joe?
Don't kill him,
Joe.
How long have you been
in the Katana's pocket?
How did you know?
You didn't think I'd find
traces of the drug in my body
after I realized
what was going on?
Sorry, Joe.
Linton's my brother.
It's true.
You played with my emotions.
Joe, I'm sorry.
We had to. To take down Dogge
and the Katana,
we infiltrated them.
We ate like them.
We lived like them.
They didn't think you were
special and I believed in you.
You were special.
You're special.
You are specialist,
Milena.
You brought peace
to the Shinjukus,
Joe. We're good people.
Don't think of
this as a betrayal.
You sacrified your emotions
for an entire people.
And now, god speed
to you and your life.
Bye, Joe.
So, do I need to
send in more cavalry?
It's cool, Gail.
Just another day.
Fresh air. Isn't it beautiful?
-The best part of freedom.
-You got it.
Joe, pick up the pace man.
What's the matter, Marshall?
It's all over now.
It's time to move on.
It's only just getting started.
Hey!
Mr. Marshall. My god.
How fortunate am
I to see you again
and for you to be my first
customer? How are you doing?
-Mr. Sebastian.
-Yes.
Just exactly how many part time
transportation jobs do you have?
-A lot.
-Will you please take them home?
I won't be joining them.
What? So you mean,
the old undercover
cop has to go it alone?
I'm not going with you.
So what are you going to do?
You gonna ride off into the sunset?
I'll go where I'm needed.
I don't have a home anymore.
We did it, partner.
We took them all down.
Take care my brother.
Don't be a stranger.
I don't want to fight anymore.
I'm tired of being a bad girl.
Maybe we can join forces.
I know.
Keep it warm.
Bingo.
It's not over.