(INTENSE FUTURISTIC MUSIC)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
Outstanding job, as usual.
Your fee has been transferred.
Whatever you do, do not play the file.
(METAL CLANKS)
(ALARM BUZZES)
(METAL WHIRS)
Whatever you do, do not play the file.
(DISC PLAYER WHIRS)
(APPLAUSE)
Ladies and gentlemen and welcome to
our cinematic event of
Space Boobs In Space.
I am Zee Zee Poof and we are here to watch
the historical dramatization
of a very important event.
We are here tonight with the director,
with the led actress and
for cultural context,
the one and only Grand Muff Tit.
It's going to be an amazing evening,
stay tuned for Space Boobs In Space
and we'll be right back.
(APPLAUSE)
(WHIRRING)
Citizens of Iralane, my daughter has
sent back mission reports
from her expedition
to the planet Earth, home of that glorious
natural resource, the titty.
As we await her return,
I council patience.
This voyage promises a future in which no
Iralanian will be without
the milk of the human breast.
No longer will we rely on the antiquated
filtration systems that
harvest the unsuitable
nectar of the breasts of our home world.
Be strong and stand together.
We will yet bathe in the
fountain of their teats.
(INTENSE SPACE MUSIC)
♪ Space boobs
♪ Don't hear me walking
♪ Don't you leave me hungry
♪ Oh don't you leave me famished
♪ Oh don't you leave me empty handed
♪ Space boobs
(CLEARS THROAT)
Yes, Vizier, what news?
Well, Your Majesty, um,
your daughter has not yet
returned from her mission and
her charges died and
her cargo was spoiled
due to space bacteria.
Indeed.
Why, why must the
precious milk of the titty
be so vulnerable to space bacteria?
Vizier, we are not alone.
Yes, yes Your Majesty.
Of course, Your Majesty.
Send a shuttle for the Princess.
It's already been sent.
And what are our alternate plans?
I've had
something going for awhile now.
I sent a beacon out
with our coordinates,
also a little music,
humans are very susceptible to lures.
Hopefully, some of them
will find our beacon and
make their way here and we can
use them as specimens to create
our valuable milk of the titty.
Excellent,
report when you have further information.
You are dismissed.
(WIND WHISTLES)
[CAPTAIN WEAVER
VOICEOVER] Captain's log,
January 7th, 2092.
We are nearing the origin of the strange
message that has driven the space program
on our planet for the last 75 years.
It has been a long journey
and First Mate Fonda
is eager to be on solid ground
and I can't say I blame her
but now that we are so close,
I am preoccupied with
concern for the safety
of my crew and my ship.
We may be making the first contact
with an alien life form.
My next report will be
from the surface of the
alien planet.
This is Captain Weaver, signing out.
(INTENSE FUTURISTIC MUSIC)
Your Majesty, I have news to report.
Speak.
We have confirmed visual sighting
of a human spacecraft.
It would appear that the
Grand Vizier's messages
have been effective.
The spacecraft has landed approximately
four farks into the wetlands.
I humbly request permission
to represent our government
in greeting the crew.
Excellent,
take one of my guards,
go and see whether they can
be interacted with safely
and assess their titties for viability.
Yes, Your Majesty.
(FUTURISTIC AMBIENT MUSIC)
So far this planet seems
like a safe environment,
would you agree, Fonda?
I suspect everything, Captain.
These plants are alien life forms,
we do not know what the
primary sentient life form is.
These rocks
could be life forms.
I don't think that rock
sent us a series of notes
and a set of coordinates, Fonda.
Rocks may be living things
and even musically
inclined on this planet.
That exterior could be a exoskeleton.
They may communicate
with music.
I know it seems safe,
but chances are pretty
slim that we'll encounter
a recognizable bipedal
form on this planet.
We must be prepared for
everything, Captain.
Fine, you're the one that studied
theoretical extraterrestrial biology.
Rocks transmitting sounds, right.
♪ Do Re Me Fa So La Te Do
(CALM FUTURISTIC MUSIC)
Oh my god, Fonda, look!
Greetings.
We are visitors,
do you have spoken language?
Do you understand us?
Greetings, Humans. I have been sent
to welcome you to our
planet and escort you
to the palace immediately.
Your cooperation would
be greatly appreciated.
Your hospitality is greatly appreciated,
we would like to learn
more about your culture
before we travel from within
the vicinity of our ship.
How far is the palace from here?
We are so happy to meet you.
I have been sent to
welcome you to our planet
and escort you to the palace immediately.
Your cooperation would
be greatly appreciated,
only the Queen can share
information with you.
We don't know their ways,
culturally, this could be a huge misstep
to let the Goodwill
Ambassador speak with us first
before the Queen does.
This could be the only way
to precede with our mission.
Very well.
We will need more
information on the distance
of the palace from our
ship and a guarantee
that we will returned to our ship safely.
Thank you for your cooperation.
If you'll follow me this way
and I am not the Goodwill Ambassador,
I'm the Captain of the Guard,
what you would call military.
(INTENSE FUTURISTIC MUSIC)
Welcome, you must now
submit for examination.
We must make sure you're safe before
we take you into the
presence of Her Majesty.
I can see that you
are only doing your job
and as a gesture of
goodwill, we will allow this.
(VIZIER CLAPS)
Bring out Platypus.
(INTENSE FUTURISTIC MUSIC)
(DEVICE BLEEPS)
Alright, that's enough,
you must be able to tell that
we aren't carrying any diseases and that
we have no hidden weapons.
This is ridiculous.
Very well,
I can tell that you are both healthy
and your titties appear to
be viable candidates for
heavy production.
You must be very proud of
this physical superiority.
I will take you to our Queen.
(CALM FUTURISTIC MUSIC)
Your Majesty, I have brought
you the viable human titties.
Now, see here.
Greetings, Human.
Please forgive the eager
declaration of my military leader.
She is understandably moved
by this historic moment.
You are dismissed, Captain.
Uh, well, yes,
the Federated Allied Government of Earth
sends their greet, did she say titties?
I-I think she said, I
know she said titties.
Misinterpretation and miscommunication
is very common with two
cultures that have first met.
I'm sorry, Your Majesty, but,
in our language, a titty
is a part of the body.
Yes.
The breast, the teat,
you are both blessed with
functioning mammary glands.
How joyous for you
and for us, my people are
in great need of your milk.
My Grand Vizier will be looking forward
to meeting with you and
she will give you more
information about your future with us.
Our future?
I see discussions have begun.
Vizier, you will speak
with these breast bearers?
Which is a fascinating
cultural anomaly, really.
I'll get this sorted out, ladies.
You're the leader?
Yes.
Come with me.
(INTENSE FUTURISTIC MUSIC)
You should know that
our government will not
negotiate with a government
that uses aggressive tactics.
We will not have our milk taken forcibly.
Calm down, we're just here to talk.
Hypnotized subjects
don't respond well to milking and
the milk spoils.
We thought about milking farms,
but humans are so unwieldy.
Oh, that's true,
we make terrible cattle,
we are much more excitable than most...
Fonda!
Grand Vizier, we will need to know more
about your planet and the resources that
you have to offer.
Earth requires additional
fuel sources and food.
We also need some new techniques in order
to clean our air and environment.
Yes, our research has shown us that your
natural environment is quite damaged.
We don't have the same
problem here, of course,
but we cannot, due to our long lifespan,
long life is a tremendous motivator.
Long lifespan,
I would love to study your species,
that sounds really fascinating,
do you have any scientists
that I could talk to?
Um, I mean like, just sit down for a day
or something.
Well, unlike your precious milk,
our own green breast nectar
has only horrible side effects.
We try to minimize skin
contact with it, of course,
but it's difficult.
As a side effect, extends our life
and makes us invulnerable to
fine lines and wrinkles.
Your breasts
prevent aging and extend life?
Yes.
Woo.
It's terrible.
We have to minimize reproduction.
My grandmother and I seem
to be about the same age.
Our Queen is about 800
of your Earth years.
I think we can arrange
a trade agreement.
(RELAXED FUTURISTIC MUSIC)
(SHIP HUMS)
I look forward to their return.
They were nice for humans.
They had nice titties.
(SHIP HUMS)
Captain's log, January 9th, 2092,
so much has happened.
We've made contact with an alien race
and developed a new trade partnership
that will most likely benefit
all the peoples on Earth.
The imports will change
our entire way of life
and the circumstances, well,
I think that's something
better outlined in person.
Hey, hey, hey.
We're gonna live forever.
(FONDA LAUGHS)
Oh, okay, that's weird.
♪ Space boobs
♪ Don't you leave me walking
♪ Don't you leave me hungry
♪ Don't you leave me stranded
♪ Don't you leave me empty handed
♪ Space boobs
(GIRLS CLAPS)
(GIRLS LAUGH)
(FONDA GROANS)
I think I like it.
(FONDA GAGS)
To living forever.
Yeah (LAUGHS).
[DIRECTOR] Cut.
(APPLAUSE)
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome back.
I hope you enjoyed Space Boobs In Space.
We are here with the Earth director,
human Earth Director, Andrew Shearer?
That's right, that's right, yeah.
He is a beautiful Earth man
and he directed this very
important, historical
dramatization, I love drama.
Tell us, tell us what was
the most important part
of making this film?
Boobs.
Well, thank you so much for
this enlightening interview.
We have so many other
interviews coming up.
Would you like to introduce them?
Sure.
A guy we had to do the interviews,
he shows up to the thing, he's drunk,
he's throwing up behind the couch,
made everybody sick, it's terrible.
So, um,
but what I got is some Foreign Press.
Some Foreign Press?
Yeah, he's a guy and I can't really
understand what he's saying but
the actors were great.
Everybody's gonna love it.
Okay, well get ready
for this enlightening
interviews and we'll be right back with
the lead actress and the
Grand Muff Tit is still
coming, she will be here too.
See you soon.
(APPLAUSE)
[REPORTER] I'm here on the
set of Space Boobs In Space.
I am here with the Coquette De Jour.
Bonjour.
[REPORTER] And she's sewing
her own costume, it appears.
Ms. De Jour, do you not have an assistant
who will make this for you?
You must do your own work
on the set of this movie?
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
[REPORTER] What is it like to make
a movie with the Americans?
Oh, um,
it is good,
they always ask me to do
ze American accent, so,
which I think is very weird but...
[REPORTER] I don't, I don't like it but,
what can you tell us about the character
that you are playing in
Space Boobs From Space?
Um, I am a scientist.
I study theoretical
extraterrestrial biology.
I get very excited
about culture and plants
and singing rocks.
[REPORTER] Do you say
something to your fans in Brazil?
Uh, I do not speak Brazilian.
I just gitsem.
(APPLAUSE)
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome back,
I hope you enjoyed it, the interviews.
I love hearing when people talk about
what they did on the film and on the set.
It just makes the film so much better.
Now, tell us, what did you think about
what they were saying,
what do you think about what actors
reflect on what they did with you?
Eh, I mean, no disrespect
but they're a bunch of assholes.
I see, assholes, I've heard of this.
Coming up next we have some of,
in honor, in honor of
this historical moment,
between our cultures,
when they integrate.
This historical era in film,
we have earthlings from your country.
Hey, great.
Earth.
(LAUGHS AND COUGHS)
And we will be viewing,
ladies and gentlemen, enjoy.
(APPLAUSE)
(UPBEAT DANCE MUSIC)
♪ Quickzilla ghost
♪ Electric air
♪ Up on clouds
♪ Sky ocean shield
♪ Through the vision
♪ Rise of wheels
♪ Within the fields
♪ That will always be the big ones
♪ We'll flow our geyser of life
♪ These are only very wild
♪ There's too many inside
(MUSIC SLOWS AND FADES)
Okay, so, you're sure
this is what you want?
Yes, absolutely.
Okay, alright.
Well, is this okay for you?
Oh, yeah, this is um,
well within the range of things
that I'm comfortable doing.
Okay.
Okay, good.
Woo (LAUGHS).
Alright, sweetie, now,
okay, you tell me if
I'm doing things right,
you tell me what feels good, okay?
Alright so, tell me if you like this.
Give me some response so I know, you know,
what's feeling right for you.
Okay, feedback.
Okay, yes, okay.
So we're gonna try this.
Okay.
Okay, this is what you want?
Yes.
Okay.
Alright, let's give this a try.
How does this feel?
(DEVICE HUMS)
Does that feel good?
Yeah?
Is that right?
Maybe a little deeper?
Okay, okay, I can do that.
Like that?
Uh-huh.
(DEVICE HUMS)
Okay.
(GAME HUMS)
(WOMAN IN BLUE SQUEALS)
Alright.
Yeah.
♪ Through the night it
♪ Night it comes
(GAME HUMS)
(WOMAN IN BLUE COUGHS)
So,
per your instructions,
you know, we pulled a couple of properties
and we're looking for
things that were near,
a summer camp
but there's not really
anything on the market
like that right now.
You know, it's the wrong time of year.
But,
there's a really nice lake nearby,
it's good stuff.
Do you like water?
(PLAYFUL GUITAR MUSIC)
That's real wood.
That's value.
As you can see,
this lot features gorgeous, mature trees.
They're really nice actually
but should you decide to, you know,
clear some of that away
and if you wanted to build,
that would be lovely too
or you could leave it natural
and undisturbed.
Yeah, people do that too.
You know, the way the
office described you,
I thought you'd be taller.
(PLAYFUL GUITAR MUSIC)
Now, it is a fairly private location.
There is a neighborhood nearby but
you may get the occasional jogger.
I don't think they're
gonna disturb you too much.
It's nice though.
Hey.
That's nice, isn't it?
Jogging, getting that heart rate up.
It's good stuff.
Do you jog?
Anything?
Well, other than that,
it's a lovely, lovely location.
You know, you've got your trees,
you've got your leaves,
you got your grass,
yeah, close to a neighborhood
but not too close 'cause finding that
balance between privacy and
being part of a community, it's wonderful
but it is, it's really challenging
to find the right thing.
So, what do you think?
(PLAYFUL GUITAR MUSIC)
(SIGHS) Okay.
Yeah, no, I don't know where the office
is finding these new clients.
Apparently, since we've got all these
Hollywood types coming into town,
a lot of them are looking
for properties now
but this is ridiculous.
Yeah, this guy just walked away while
I was showing the
property, just walked away.
Uh-uh, right, you remember
the one from last week,
the one with the stripey sweater
and that skin condition?
He just wanted to see properties
that had boiler rooms.
Who does that, right?
Uh-uh, no, I don't need
the commission that bad.
No, Mr. Walksaway, he can find his
own way out of the woods.
(PLAYFUL GUITAR MUSIC)
This property features
gorgeous, mature wooded trees,
that's not a word.
Close to the hustle and bustle
but far from the hustle and bustle.
Woo, it's real trees, yeah,
you don't just get that anywhere,
you get that here, out in nature.
This is nice, I like this.
Outdoor activities or a summer camp,
but, you know, there's
nothing like that (LAUGHS).
(PLAYFUL GUITAR MUSIC)
(APPLAUSE)
(LAUGHS) Welcome back
ladies and gentlemen.
I hope you enjoyed these
true depictions of life
on the country of Earth.
Why do real estate transactions
on your planet require use of face guards?
Oh, it's very important,
it's dangerous work,
extremely dangerous work.
Yes?
You know,
when you're out there in the woods and
you know, a neighborhood,
anything like that,
you gotta cover your face,
gotta cover your face.
You, you couldn't walk around like this.
No, no.
I couldn't walk around like this.
I mean, look at me.
Now, the other question I have,
the prominent question is
do all your sexual proclivities include
the use of children's
games based on surgery?
Ah, what's a sexual,
what'd you say, sexual what?
Proclivity.
What is that?
Your needs.
Is that that thing that goes in the...
Your desires.
Okay, what did you say about kids?
We're about to go to
one more interview with
one of the cast members
of this historical dramatization.
Would you like to introduce them?
Yeah, I know this one really good.
This person um, yeah,
things were missing all around the set
after the shoot.
Missing?
Yeah, people's keys were
gone, jewelry was gone,
a lot of things were gone
and this person stole a lot of things
from a lot of people.
We had to make a full prostitution.
Oh, goodness, well thank you for
that introduction.
Absolutely.
Here's that interview
with that cast member.
(APPLAUSE)
[REPORTER] Tittiana Sprinkles,
the Pandora in both say
that you are difficult
and that you spit on the
face and I just want to know,
is this true and if so,
do you have message for them?
I think they better back themselves up
and check it 'cause
this right here, uh-uh,
no, you just gotta get
outta the way of this,
it's not my fault that I need, you know,
exactly eight inches of mirror
but they only gave me seven.
[REPORTER] Do you say
they have body odors?
Well, I wouldn't go that far.
I mean,
so,
yes.
[REPORTER] I want to watch the season
of the Dukes of Hazzard where the original
stars do not play Bo and Luke
and it's probably not as good
but I imagine this is, your
family is like Hee Haw?
My family?
Horrifying.
You can tell when it's someone...
We have loved having Earth
director Andrew Shearer
here with us today.
You are just beautiful,
I want to lick your wrinkles,
they are so gorgeous.
Take a number, you know.
Thank you so much
for have me on the show
and having us talk to you, bye bye.
(ANDREW SHOUTS)
Now, ladies and gentlemen,
we have a huge treat for you today.
The one and only, descended
from the royal family
of Iralane, the member of parliament,
the illustrious, the
ancient, the gorgeous,
Grand Muff Tit, Grand
Muff Tit, come, darling.
(APPLAUSE)
Oh, hello, thank you for having me.
So good to see you.
It's wonderful to see
you, Zee Zee, my dear.
You look so old.
Oh, are you on AARP,
which is a human, Earth word.
I heard of this, I know this thing too.
I feel like you could be on Medicare
and no one would bat a lash, my darling.
Oh, you are too kind.
You're too kind (LAUGHS).
Now, Grand Muff Tit,
you are descended from the woman,
the pioneer who discovered that
we could trade the breast
nectar to the humans
for the milk of the titty.
It was your great, great,
great, great, great,
great grandmother?
Yes, that's correct,
may she rest in peace.
I didn't kill her, just in
case anyone was wondering.
No, no, no, no.
We will now see more interviews
from this historical dramatization.
Yes, they kicked me off the lot.
They, they kicked you off the lot?
I don't wanna talk about it.
It's a court thing.
Oh, I see.
Very well, let us go to these interviews.
(APPLAUSE)
[REPORTER] Ms. Izzie Popp,
tell us, what is the meaning
of Space Boobs In Space
for the artistic statement,
what you are making
from this film?
We have something to do with
I guess, interplanetary exploration.
[REPORTER] So it is a
metaphor, what you are saying,
from the outer space is
to speak from interspace.
That is correct.
[REPORTER] Could you
tell me a little bit
about your character,
it appears as very smart
for what I would assume
is American astronaut?
That's right.
I am a ship captain and
I am skeptical at first.
It's fascinating to think of what it
would be like in the
future when we do finally
discover alien life.
[REPORTER] I think this
is why I will consider you
a worthy thing for the
science fiction genre.
Oh definitely.
[REPORTER] Mostly they
are transforming or they are
Captain America and they are not...
I think they will be breaking ground
with this film and
all audiences, whether they're American
or international will greatly appreciate
how realistic and...
[REPORTER] Pandora Disaster?
Yes?
[REPORTER] I would like to know,
first, how is it like to work with the
behavior problems of Coquette Du Jour
and of Izzie Popp?
They like sitting around on the floors
and do this bump and grind thing,
I don't quite understand.
In my country,
it's no acceptable.
You would be beheaded.
[REPORTER] Space Boobs From Space,
why are they talk about the breasts
and do you think the America
is ready for the boob?
I think the American needs to understand
that boobs, the tits, are glorious, yes.
They are multi-functional and they are
very pleasing to the eye.
[REPORTER] Do you think
that the violence is too much
in the America, do you
think there is not enough
of the bare exposed anus
and things like this
instead of the bullet and the gun?
I think the American needs to
expand their mind, yes.
They need to grow up,
stop that stupid nonsense,
their ridiculous politics.
They needs to understand
that art comes first.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(FUTURISTIC UPBEAT MUSIC)
(DOOR HUMS)
(APPLAUSE)
Welcome back.
Now, Grand Muff Tit,
I must know, I must ask you,
why were you not included in the film?
What happened, tell us everything.
Well, you see,
I'm not supposed to talk about it.
I know, but you must, we're dying.
I feel like you and
I are such close, close
bosom buddies, if you will.
Oh!
That I can share it with you
and your wonderful audience,
despite the court gag order.
The gentleman who was just
here earlier before me?
Andrew Shearer, yes.
That nefarious director,
yes, Andrew Shearer.
Yes, yes, what did he do,
what did he do, tell us Grand Muff Tit,
my breasts are heaving with emotion.
Oh, speaking of heaving breasts,
that is where the story begins.
Imagine it,
a closed Paramount lot,
heaving breasts as far as the eye can see
and me with my wizened, yet still
appreciated by traditional
Earth custom titties,
in the audience, waiting to meet that
nefarious director.
Our eyes locked from
across the crowded lot.
I approached him.
I was very afraid, you see.
You see, I hadn't had any of that
delicious breast milk yet that day
and I said, no, I don't
need that courage right now,
I see him.
We started a passionate, passionate tryst
and by tryst I mean planning murders
while eating Triscuits.
But then, in the manner of all men,
he left me for a Wheat Thin (CRIES).
Oh, oh.
I was irate, naturally,
as you can imagine.
Of course, of course.
What did you do?
Oh, I went back to the
lot the very next day
and I said, where is that Andrew Shearer
and they said, we don't know
what you're talking about,
please leave.
Well, I burned down the whole studio
and it wasn't until later I realized
I burnt down the Fox lot
and not the Paramount lot.
That's a common mistake, yes.
Yes, it was very sad.
Common mistake, yes.
So, I was no longer allowed
to be a part of that movie.
Oh.
Thank you so much for
sharing Grand Muff Tits.
Of course, thank you
for being here for me.
Oh, you're welcome, you're welcome,
your aged self.
You're beautiful and old.
Oh, thank you.
Why don't you introduce
the next set of films?
Well,
you all watching are
in for a special treat.
We are going to get some
actual human Earth people
depictions of the real
life in the 21st century.
You won't believe what they get up to,
number seven's a shocker.
(APPLAUSE)
(PHONE RINGS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
[CALLER] I'm in the basement.
(PHONE RECEIVER THUDS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(KILLER FARTS)
(DISEMBODIED FART)
(SULTRY JAZZ MUSIC)
(APPLAUSE)
And then I just cut off his head.
(LAUGHS) Oh, you know I love murder!
I know, I know.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is Zee Zee Poof
and we have had a wonderful time with
the Grand Muff Tit, it has been an honor,
a true honor for your aged
face to grace our presence.
The honor is all mine.
To be here with you, one of
my closest bosom buddies,
in front of all of you, the viewers.
I just, I couldn't be happier
and I hope you'll have me here again soon.
Oh, anytime, anytime,
we'd love to and coming up next we have
Beryl Peep here now, yay.
(APPLAUSE)
Yeah, you're looking rather young.
Beryl Peep, hello.
Hello, dear.
How are you, it's good to see you.
Thank you, thank you so much.
I am loving this exotic outfit,
can you tell us about it?
Oh, this.
Yes.
When I was doing research for my
highly critically acclaimed
turn in Space Boobs In Space,
I did research on that period
of time in Earth history.
The 1990s, yes.
Reagan years.
And I learned that Earth humans,
they would wear dead animals
draped across their bodies,
it was very popular.
Oh, goodness,
well, did you kill this thing?
No, I didn't kill this one.
This is a vintage piece
but the humans, they raise the animals,
it was a special breeding program
and they were raised to
have depression issues
and they would kill themselves.
Oh, I love all of this, it's beautiful.
Thank you, thank you.
So we actually are about
to watch some human films,
some human sort of
documentary educational films
that humans make...
About nature?
Yes, yes, for other
humans to learn about
the place where they live.
I find Earth nature,
just, it's fascinating.
We should really,
I mean, the same planet that produced
the milk from the titty.
Oh, milk from the titty.
We really, we owe it to ourselves to
learn as much as possible
about their natural habitat.
Yes, habitat.
Let's go to the film.
(APPLAUSE)
Hi, I'm Andrew and I
make really cheap movies.
I am very interested in
the idea of real monsters
because then I don't have to come up
with the makeup for it.
They've already got it on
'cause they're monsters.
My only problem really is that,
will they kill me
and all I've heard about
the Sandy Creek Mud Monster
is that she kills people.
I kind of need
to know if there's a female
swamp monster around here,
'cause if there is,
I don't want somebody
else filming her first.
I should be the one to do it.
I mean, that makes total sense.
So, I'm on my way to
the Sandy Creek Nature Center
and I'm gonna go way off the beaten path,
gonna go really far,
back to the parts where
it's a little dicey and no one ever goes
because if she's gonna be living somewhere
and everybody with their
phones and all that stuff,
and never gotten a picture of her,
there's gotta be a reason for it.
It's gotta be a place where
it's not safe to bring
your beard and you PBR,
so that's where I'm going.
(UPBEAT ROCKABILLY MUSIC)
♪ I've been inside them
♪ Like fish in your life
Hiya, Mud Monster.
Hey.
[ANDREW] How you doing?
I'm doing great.
How y'all doing?
[ANDREW] Oh, we're good, you know,
just thought we'd come and say hey,
find out if you were real,
et cetera, et cetera.
That is so refreshing because usually
it's an opposite, usually
I'm dealing with people,
you know, running, screaming.
You know, that's okay, that's who I am
and I just want other people to know that.
I want other people to realize what
it is to be a mud monster.
[ANDREW] Well, I heard that
you like to rip arms
off, suck out eyeballs,
that kind of thing but so far, so good.
Basically, everything that you see here
is couture, I made it myself.
Everything that you see me wearing,
I found here in the woods.
It's actually three bags,
is that I braided and used some,
you know, another campers shoelaces.
[ANDREW] So are those
people still alive or
how's that working?
Um, I mean, define alive.
[ANDREW] Now they're included
in fashion, which is way
more important than
just a mortal existence.
Fashion is forever.
[ANDREW] Certainly.
So, uh, I was camping and
you wouldn't know it now, but
I was a bit of a princess,
wasn't into
being in the woods, I was a bit
of a, you know, city owl and
well, I was out there camping and you see,
I heard a sound and I
went to investigate and
I saw the mud monster
and I was attacked but
not killed.
So, uh, he kind of retired.
He just left the woods.
He went to Reno.
Since I was already, you know, afflicted,
I decided to go with it.
I like being in the woods, you know and
sometimes I think the
call of Broadway might be
somewhere in my future but
you never know, you know?
Mud monster one day.
[ANDREW] Yeah, stranger
things have happened.
Yeah, the internet.
[ANDREW] Is this where you live?
This is my place, this
is where I keep my things.
You know, all my wearable art.
[ANDREW] That's nice,
where'd you get that,
do you remember?
I think it was a sorority group.
They ran so fast, I didn't get the chance
to find out, I guess.
[ANDREW] I remember
them, 'cause it was like,
they had trouble
identifying them as missing
because they all looked the same.
I mean, it doesn't
get any finer than this,
I mean, what's luxury?
[ANDREW] Exactly.
Sleeping under the stars.
[ANDREW] Yeah, yeah,
well, where do people go
when they wanna get away, anyway?
You're already there.
That's right, I'm already here,
waitin'.
♪ Great green gobs of
greasy grimy gopher dust
♪ Little dirty birdy feet
♪ French fried eyeballs
♪ And I forgot to bring my spoon
I'm available for parties.
[ANDREW] Sweet, well,
thanks for not killing us
and maybe we'll see you around.
Hey, you know, the night is young.
[ANDREW] Oh, shit.
♪ Like fish in moonlight
(APPLAUSE)
Oh, goodness, that's very educational.
Nature, Earth nature,
I didn't know monsters
were even real there
and I believe that...
Like the Yeti.
Like the Yeti, which I
believe lives in the ocean,
isn't that correct?
Yes.
Yes?
I did a lot of research on human culture
and Earth history and I
found some interesting things
about them, like it is a little known fact
that humans are obsessed
with their own anus.
Their anus?
Yes.
They, at that point in history,
they took all these
photographs of their buttocks
which is where the human anus is located.
The anus is in their buttocks?
How do they sit on the chairs?
I know.
Oh, Shearer was sitting
there with his anus,
you realize this?
Yes.
Oh, horrifying, horrifying.
It's very distasteful.
We're better not thinking about it.
So humans, at this point in history
were obsessed with their
own anus and knowing that
gave me an understanding of
how the Queen would have felt
interacting with these primitive humans
who were so stupid and so obsessed with
their own defecation.
Have you had any sort of
strange interactions with the illustrious
Grand Muff Tit,
who was descended from the
Queen you have portrayed?
I really feel very fortunate
that Grand Muff and I have always had,
I feel a cordial relationship, really.
Ah.
Considering everything.
The keyed car, the burned studios.
I mean, I have a long history
of reliability on set.
Ah, yes.
I never try to
show my Triscuits to the director.
So, you are a lady, you are.
You know, I feel that things
should be kept professional,
you know, I just,
and I think that's served me well but
everybody has their
own approach, you know.
That's very true.
I don't bring matches to set.
I think that has been instrumental
in the furthering of my career.
Well, it's been wonderful
for you to enlighten us all
into your film career and your friendship
with the illustrious and honorable
and beautiful, dear
friend, Grand Muff Tit.
Now we are going to go to some interviews
with your cast members from the film.
Oh, good.
Enjoy.
(APPLAUSE)
[REPORTER] Diego Wolf, thank you
for coming to the Foreign Press.
I just wanted to know if you could tell us
why you are participated
in the movie about breasts
when you could be possibly,
maybe, a political statement
or a social statement or save the whale,
why you are doing the movie instead?
Why can't I save the whale
and play with the boobs?
[REPORTER] Do you know what
your character motivation
is supposed to be in the filming
of the Space Boobs, what you are saying
with the artistic statement
of this character?
I like to scan the boob.
[REPORTER] Your friends in
Brazil would like to know,
Diego, what is your favorite color
and who were your
favorite member of Menudo?
Oh, what, Menudo?
[REPORTER] What is
your favorite ice cream?
We would like to know,
the co-star of your film have
a trouble with each other,
there are many scandal and many rivalries.
Very many, yes, very many scandal.
[REPORTER] Can you say why do they say
Coquette Du Jour and Tittiana Sprinkle
are going to fight each
other out in the street?
I don't know.
[REPORTER] You do not want to say
or are you afraid of them?
I am forbidden.
[REPORTER] Ms. Jenny Haniver,
will you talk to the Foreign Press
about your work in the
Space Boob From Space
and how do it relate to the plight of
the aboriginal in Brazil?
I don't know what you said, mate.
I'm high as a kite right now.
[REPORTER] Right, right, right,
what is your favorite pizza toppings?
Uh.
[WOMAN] Milk, milk.
Milk, yeah, milk.
[REPORTER] How do you
feel about the baby cow and
how the milk is only for him and not
for the human consumptions?
You know, I never really
thought it before but
it's kind of fucked up, eh?
[REPORTER] Do you know
Steve Irwin per personal
and how do you feel he, Paul Hogan
was affected by his untimely passings?
What is your favorite color?
We have report that Coquette
Du Jour have murdered
Tittiana Sprinkle or Tittiana Sprinkle
have murdered Coquette Du
Jour in the dressing room.
Have you heard about,
can you confirm these
for Brazil?
I thought that was a dream I had.
(APPLAUSE)
Ladies and gentlemen, I am Zee Zee Poof
and we are here with the
late actress Beryl Peep.
Now Mrs. Peep, we have
just seen some of your
illustrious cast mates
talking about the film.
It was a joy to work with, really,
almost all of them.
I can tell.
Now we are going to go
straight to the next film
because it is one of my personal favorites
in which you play a dead human,
which is just fascinating.
It was a lot of work, you know.
The extensive prosthetic make-up
that had to be put on me.
Oh.
Really took a long time,
they had to cover my age spots,
which was very uncomfortable.
I don't know that I could do that.
It felt odd to be so ugly, you know,
and to look so human.
They're so strange looking.
They're very ugly.
What sort of method
did you have to go into
to play a dead human,
did you think about your
anus the entire time?
Well, I talked to the other
humans because, you know,
some of the roles were
played by actual humans.
Yes, had they been dead before?
I talked to the other humans on set
and they told me that the dead humans
don't utilize their anus.
At all?
No.
How bizarre.
So they just stop when they die
and they just, odd.
So it was very strange because I had to
both be this human character who remembers
being obsessed with my own anus.
So coming up next.
Yes, this film that I play in.
Can you give us a little bit
of an introduction?
(SIGHS) Well, I felt like this was a,
a deeply emotional role for me,
being able to get in touch with, you know,
like my inner, my inner...
Boobs.
Dead human, so, um.
Can they go back and forth?
Can dead humans come back?
No, they just stay that way.
They're very strange.
That's so weird.
Yeah.
Alright, well, let's go to the film,
we'll be right back, ladies and gentlemen.
(APPLAUSE)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
Okay so,
I wanna get serious for a minute.
Everything's fine, but I have to.
Don't do that, you'll ruin everything.
I know I'm not the best at,
at telling you how I feel sometimes, but,
you're making it take longer...
(SNORES) Huh, oh.
I wanna give you something.
It belonged to my grandmother.
She was my best friend and
whenever I forget what true love is like
I just look at it and remember.
I, no, oh my god, no, I can't take that.
That's too much.
You have to.
It's safe with you
and you're safe with me.
Now when you look at it
you'll know every time.
(GIGGLES)
No, I think a few months
is perfect timing,
it wasn't like creepy or like,
desperate, you know, but,
it was like something out of
a movie, it was really sweet,
only, you know, it
wasn't cheesy or anything
because it was happening to me.
Oh, um, well, it's gorgeous.
I sorta don't wanna take it off (GIGGLES).
Um, no, I can't tomorrow actually,
he's cooking me dinner, so.
Oh, you'll find somebody else
to go out with and be jealous
of, don't worry about it,
bye.
(PHONE THUDS)
(SIGHS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
Thank you for doing this and
especially for telling me no
when I asked if I could help.
That's okay, I know you hate cooking.
I do feel sorta guilty but
I would feel worse
burning your house down.
Tell you what, you finish that
while I go get the good dishes.
And I can set the table if you trust
me with those.
We'll see.
(RELAXING PIANO MUSIC)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
So, who's this hot
mama in the picture here?
Really?
Well, she's got on your
grandmother's ring,
so you can't say she's no one.
No,
she was definitely somebody,
was.
Oh, come on, we never
talk about your exes.
I'll trade you stories,
I got a couple good ones.
I do too,
just not about her.
Ooh, well now you have to.
Nah.
There was this one girl...
Who is not in this picture and
who I don't care about.
The girl in the picture died.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
Oh my god.
I-I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm not weird about it.
We weren't together that long,
we broke up long before it happened, so.
That's horrible,
I didn't realize, I
wouldn't have said anything.
It's really okay.
She gave me the ring
back before we split, so.
None of my exes ever really
liked talking about exes
so I guess I just got into the habit of
not doing so.
That's probably a good habit.
The present is way more important.
I'd rather talk about you.
Well, we can do that.
(SHOES CLACK)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
Ow.
(BLONDE GIRL SCREAMS)
Oh, I know who you are.
I, fuck, go away.
Oh my god, please go away.
I don't even know if I love him yet,
I just, I think I might but,
you know what, you can
have him, just have him,
just, you can't have him, you're dead,
what am I saying (SOBS)?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
I don't know what you want.
Just go away, just go away.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
Oh.
What are you doing way over here,
tired of our usual spot?
There's just too many people, you know?
I wanted a little more privacy.
Well, you better be careful because
privacy can lead to sexy really quickly,
sexy picnic.
I really should have
told you about Candice.
Well, at some point you
were bound to find out
how nosy I am (GIGGLES).
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
Things didn't work
out for me and Candice
for the same reason they never work out.
I just need you to trust me
and if you need to know
everything, I'll tell you
and you're right,
you are nosy.
So if you wanna know how she died,
I'll tell you right here.
Right here it happened.
Right here.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
[DIRECTOR] And action, Kate!
I know who you are and I'm not okay
with you being here
and you need to go and you can have him
but maybe not today,
maybe sometime next week
but you're a ghost, so
really can't have him at all.
Mother wanted me to come down in a kimono,
we had an awful fight (LAUGHS).
(APPLAUSE)
Ladies and gentlemen,
hope you enjoyed that
very interesting film
that I love, I love, I
watch it all the time.
You really encompass all
the nuance of a dead human.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, stop.
It's wonderful to see,
it's emotional and moving
and just, you capture
their ugliness so well.
You're too kind.
So, would you like to introduce
this film that I heard was
also a favorite of yours
and was instrumental.
I did watch this human film
when I was doing research
for playing a human.
Yes.
This film, I felt was,
for me and my research,
was something of a turning point
in really seeing that
all parts of human life
related back to the buttocks and the anus.
Yes, yes.
And so, I felt like
I could really see that
coming through in this particular picture.
You saw the anus coming through.
So, I mean, but it
was really enlightening
and it helped give greater insight
into the way that humans really work
when interacting with them.
That is a fascinating, fascinating...
I think it's important.
Perspective on human culture.
Let's see it.
(APPLAUSE)
(UPBEAT DANCE MUSIC)
He's been watching us,
I told you they was watching us.
So, it does not mean
that they are vampires.
Now the hell it don't.
They did the same thing to my cousin Angie
a couple weeks ago.
These bitches stayed out at
the club late all night long
and then they gotta go
steal somebody's car
so then they can get home in the morning
before the sun come up.
So they steal cars, that does not
mean that they are vampires.
Uh, yeah it do.
Alright look, I told you we could go home
if you were too scared.
I am afraid of nothing,
plus, my phone is in the car.
Well, we should go do this real quick
before we burn up too, let's go.
(PULSATING DANCE MUSIC)
They got the keys
and your phone is gone too.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Well, it looks like we're going in.
Okay, okay.
Let's do this.
(PULSATING DANCE MUSIC)
Wait.
What is your brilliant plan?
(SIGHS) I don't know,
drink a bunch of holy water
and I'll piss in their face,
man, I don't know, I thought the keys
would be in the car.
Okay.
[BOTH] Okay (grunts).
Okay, let's go.
(PULSATING DANCE MUSIC)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Yeah.
Yes?
If you are through playing around
we would like our car back.
Yeah and I drank a
whole bunch of holy water
and I gotta real bad, know what I mean?
Holy water?
I know y'all some vampires too.
All that dirt on your neck and stuff
and if you don't quite playing around
and give me my car keys,
I'm gonna come in there
and I'll pee on everything,
I'm gonna kill everybody.
(SPEAKS FRENCH) Psss.
Uh, follow me,
ladies, follow me.
(GLASS BREAKS)
Look man, I just want my car keys,
we'll just wait right here.
Uh-huh.
Oh yes,
the keys.
The Master has the keys
and the Master has your phone too.
I told you they had my phone.
Alright yeah, well, you tell Master
that we'll wait here and they can bring
the keys and the phone here.
Um,
I must stay here but
please go, the Master
wants much very, very much
to meet you.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(STAIRS CREAK)
Ugh, what's that smell?
That is the smell of
cocaine pornographies.
I don't know, I mean,
hookers fart dicks, vampires fart blood
and I know the difference
between dicks and blood.
Thank you for telling me this.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(KEYS RATTLE)
Don't look so frightened, my darlings,
you are both far too beautiful.
I do not fear you,
I do not feel fear your
collective titties.
I fear nothing.
That's not true, you're
afraid of skeletons.
She's afraid of skeletons.
Now, why would you
say that, that is a lie.
(GIRLS ARGUE)
You, my dear, have the
skeleton inside of you,
right under your skin.
Oh my dear, she's right.
She's right, oh my dear.
It's alright, everybody has one.
Why would you say that?
Because it's science.
It's okay.
(VAMPIRES LAUGHS)
Angie?
Oh yes, your cousin,
she came back for her car, just like you,
but she decided to stay,
lucky us.
Angie.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
And she has told what a
fantastic dancer you are.
This is true.
All we ask is one dance
and then we'll gladly return your keys.
With you?
You see, today is Ingrid's birthday.
Last night, we went out to celebrate
and had to make a quick
getaway to beat the sun.
Why ain't y'all just fly home,
why y'all got to steal people's cars?
Miranda learned that one the hard way.
Have you ever heard the sound a drunkin'
bat makes when it burns it's chocha?
(BAT SQUEAKS)
Ew.
Would you believe that poor Ingrid
has never had a lap dance?
Damn,
they're talking now, put
out a chair and everything.
(KEYS JINGLE)
What do you say?
Where is my phone?
Oh yes,
she quite likes these when they make
with the vibrating.
(PHONE HUMS)
Darlings,
sweet lovely darlings,
shall we dance?
And this is not a
cocaine pornography, eh?
What?
(SULTRY DANCE MUSIC)
(TEETH SQUISH)
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
(VAMPIRES LAUGH)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Meg, are you alright,
you don't look so good.
I'm so hungry.
Can we go to ze Waffle House?
Meg, I'm about to pass out,
been up all night and
all this vampire stuff.
Meg, I got some beef jerky back there
if you can't wait till we get home.
Meg?
(WOMAN WITH HAT SCREAMS)
(PULSATING DANCE MUSIC)
(GIRL SINGS PLAYFULLY)
[CREW MEMBER] Good god, that's enough.
(VAMPIRE LAUGHS)
(APPLAUSE)
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is Zee Zee Poof,
thank you so much for joining us tonight.
These are my wonderful
guest, Ms. Beryl Peep,
big round of applause,
the honorable, the Grand Muff Tit
and the bizarre looking, Andrew Shearer,
Earth man and director, yay.
Thank you so much for joining us
in the cinema to give views
of Space Boobs In Space.
See you tomorrow, mwah.
(UPBEAT FOLK-STYLE MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(ALARM BUZZES)
(LASER BLASTS)
Oh, zerpluck, pardon me, hello,
I didn't see you come in.
I'm afraid your puny Earth vocal chords
couldn't properly translate my name so
I will grant you the ability to call me
by my initials, but also
my title (CHUCKLES),
I am Grand Muff Tit.
Tonight I will be giving you
the very inside scoop into the
Iralanian state dinner we'll be having,
and all the proper customs and history
as we celebrate the
Tricentennial from when
my species met you tiny, tiny folks
on that pale blue dot we
call Earth (CHUCKLES).
Now, allow me to break down for you
the three basic of Iralanian customs
we'll be going over today.
Pleasing physical appearance,
greetings
and dining etiquette, which,
there needs to be more
than just one desert spoon,
at least three dessert spoons
or else, why bother (CHUCKLES)?
Now, you might notice
upon my lovely cheekbone
you will find some
wonderful emerald freckles.
The Iralanians don't mind
them being called freckles,
we prefer the term ginnyinni dots.
You lowly humans might
have these weird little
facial folds called wrinkles.
I'm sorry to tell you but
these are disgusting.
In order to alleviate
those unsightly wrinkles,
what I might suggest is
laying back and letting your saggy skin
just kind of, let gravity
just kind of take it's,
take it's hold and then
if you could get your skin
in the very back and just
pull it as taut as possible.
I wouldn't say a staple gun
but if that's what you have on hand,
don't let me stop you and
just go (IMITATES STAPLE GUN),
right down the neck to hold
that loose skin in place.
Wrap a cosmetic, I believe
you call them, scarves,
scarf around your neck
in some pleasing fashion,
perhaps like this, with my hair,
but you don't have hair like this, I do,
so you would have to find a scarf
and now onto subject
two, personal greetings,
because hello won't cut it
and for this, I will have to bring on my
production assistant, (SPEAKS GIBBERISH)
or as I affectionately
refer to her as Boob.
With Boob here as my guest,
we will now do the
official, proper state way
of saying a Iralanian hello
followed by an Iralanian goodbye (LAUGHS)
and so, what you want to do is
move your hands up to your titty
forming titty fins, then
in an alternating motion,
move your hands up,
down, up, down, up, down,
then lock eye contact
with the other Iralanian,
up, down, up, down, move into position,
up, down, up, down,
approach the other Iralanian,
up, down, up, down, make titty contact,
up, down, up, down, now
shimmy, up, down, up, down,
up, down, and then break.
You did it.
Now, onto the official state-sanctioned
Iralanian goodbye
and for that, we will move our hands
back up to titty fin position
and then quickly move them
to our buttocks, like so
and this is mimicking our
squid ancestors and just move this way
until you're out the door.
If you can ink, by all means, do so.
Now, thank you, Production
Assistant, Boob,
that will be all.
Proper Iralanian dining etiquette.
Yes, I have equipped with me
the three proper dessert spoons
because if you don't have
three, what's the point?
You have to use one, um, nom, nom, nom,
two, um, nom, nom, nom, nom,
and three and you have
to hold them this way,
slurp, slurp, slurp, slurp,
slurp, it's delicious.
If you were to mix all of the traditional
Iralanian desserts on one spoon,
when combined with the
oxygen and the metal alloys
in the spoon, you would
die a very painful death,
very slowly over the course of 20 minutes
to 15 years, there's just no telling.
I know I just dismissed her
but I must bring her back again.
My production assistant, Boob,
will be coming to show us the
next proper dining etiquette.
Thank you, Boob.
Okay, goodbye.
Some lovely Earth titty milk
and it will always be served
in a glass like this and we will always
take a sip of it like this.
It's wonderful what our two
cultures can do when combined.
We will remain looking fresh till death
and you, when consuming
our lovely titty nectar
will avoid the certain
death that all of us
must receive by one more pleasant day,
unless you eat all the
desserts on one spoon,
then your death will last
anywhere from 20 minutes
to five years.
Yes, we Iralanians will
drink your human titty milk
because we need it to survive.
If we don't, we'll turn back into squids
and if I turn back into a
blessed squid one more time
because of a trade embargo,
I will go Cthulhu on all
of your major cities,
towns and tourist destinations,
specifically Panama City Beach,
you know what you did,
PCB, you know what you did.
If I may call my lovely
production assistant Boob
here to reclaim this container from me,
there's only so much of human titty milk
I can take in one day,
despite being delicious
and we do thank you for your trade.
We do, I hate being a squid.
It's just the worst.
Alright, goodbye, Boob.
(LAUGHS) And thank you
so much for joining us
on this Earth Public Broadcasting System.
Remember, they need your
donations to help us
make this happen (LAUGHS).
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Oh, and who could that be?
Why, it's my boyfriend,
Tom Cruise, Jr., Jr., Jr.,
Jr., the second (GIGGLES).
He's human, I'm so progressive
and remember, the next time you're invited
to an Iralanian state
function of some sort,
I have taught you all the
basics you need to know
to not look like the wrong kind of boob.
Come.
(FUTURISTIC AMBIENT MUSIC)
Subtitles by explosiveskull