- Room service.
- Come in.
- Where would you like it, sir?
- Oh, on the table there.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Oh no, thank you.
Ok, let's shut him down.
- Ok, Ok, let's break it up.
- All right, bring it in.
Too much stress in areas HK3 and HK4.
There's an irregularity
in the electrical impulse.
Damn hand again.
How much further behind
does that put us, Doctor?
I don't know until I've
done a full analysis of him.
- Try an educated guess.
- I don't know. A couple of days, maybe.
Need I remind you, our budget
is up for review in seven weeks.
And need I have remind you, Dr Heller,
that if that hand in there can't play piano
without setting itself on fire.
We'll all be working at the corner
auto shop rebuilding transmissions.
Dr Simmons, Eve Vlll is being made
ready for a test run in lab number 4.
Oh, I love this jacket.
It's a wonderful jacket.
I think I need a purse, thank you.
Feels very good.
How do I look?
So, where are you from?
New York? Chicago?
You look big city to me,
you know, classy. Right?
No.
But thanks for the compliment.
You staying here long?
No.
Quick in-and-out, eh?
This stop Embarcadero.
Embarcadero station this stop.
- Everybody freeze. On the floor.
- Freeze, asshole. On the floor.
- Get down, you want to wait for die?
- Help.
Down. Get down. Freeze. I said get down.
Lady, what's your problem?
Are you deaf? Kiss the fucking floor.
Hit the floor or you're dead.
You want to die? Are you stupid?
Fuck you, lady.
What the fuck?
OH, lets do it.
- Who are these guys?
- Come, everybody out.
All right, let's go. It's time to go. Come
on, move it, move it, move it, come on.
- Let's go.
- Look out, he's one of them.
Right, move out. Come on.
- Come on, let's go, let's go.
- Move it, move out.
Hurry, hurry. Come on.
Go.
Hurry. Come on.
Come on, hurry. Get in there. Hurry.
Shit.
Line up.
- Let's go.
- Come on, Smith. Hurry up.
Webster, Harris, Des Moines, Saperstein...
Carter, you're all dead.
- Jesus.
- And each would have an epitaph...
He died for his country
because he didn't fucking listen.
You know, I wonder how many times I'm going
to have to tell you guys, you never relax.
You never let down your
guard, not for one second.
Fix that up. Things are
not always what they seem.
So now, just to show you men
who's really God around here,
I'm going to miraculously
bring you all back to life.
Poof.
So we try it again.
Only this time, we don't fuck up.
- Right?
- Yes, sir.
- What the fuck is that?
- Orders, sir.
To get the hell out of
here and onto that chopper.
What you do, pack for me?
- All right. Carter, take charge.
- Yes, sir.
Guess there's somebody
even bigger than God. Fall out.
- Mam, can we go over this.
- One second, Tim.
Tim, what are you doing? Hey.
- Come on, let me see.
- This is a man. This is a woman.
- This is a vagina.
- What?
Mom, there's nothing to be embarrassed about.
You're right.
Hello.
No, I'm sorry. Dr Simmons cannot be disturbed.
- Those are tits.
- Who told you?
- Not Daddy, I swear.
- Tim, they're breasts.
- The other word is not nice, Ok?
- Ok, breasts.
- Do you know what those are called?
- Those?
- You tell me.
- Balls, Daddy tell me that.
- Dr Simmons, you have a telephone call.
- Maria, I told you no calls.
I'm sorry it's Dr Heller.
He says he must speak to you.
- We have to talk some more, young man.
- Ok.
You'd better have a darn good
reason for calling me today. What?
Ok, Ok, I'll be there.
Give me an hour. Yeah. Bye.
Oh, I have to go.
You'll have to take Timmy to
the airport, it's an emergency.
Maria will take you to the airport, Ok?
Now, I'll call you before you leave.
And Tim, we'll go to the
aquarium another time, I promise.
I want a kiss. Oh, my sweetie.
Oh, and remember,
they're called testicles.
Bye, sweetie.
Jim, this is Bill Schneider from the NSC.
- I've heard a lot about you, Colonel.
- Sir.
- Have a seat.
- Thank you.
Look, I know you're pissed...
and it's understandable giving
all the hard work you've put in.
But this hostage crisis
is just going to have to wait.
Sir, we don't get those people out soon,
they're not coming out.
At least, not alive.
Colonel...
The hostages are no longer our top priority.
The plain fact is we
have a more pressing problem.
Jim, you're about to be brought in
on this country's best-kept secret.
The following message
has the highest classification.
This is Project Rob, 25 years ago.
The aim was to design a robot
that could pass as human.
As you can see, the state of
robotics then was very primitive.
Today, this is Eve Vlll. State of the art.
To enable her to pass as
a convincing human being,
she has been programmed with the thoughts
and feelings of her inventor, Dr Eve Simmons.
Please be aware...
Dr Simmons was also used as a model
for Eve Vlll's face and body structure
and her memory programs.
Eve Vlll has been
designed for surveillance work
but can also be used
as a cover battlefield weapon.
Eve Vlll is currently completing a
series of test runs in the Bay Area.
Message ends.
- This thing for real?
- What do you mean?
Well I...
I knew we were doing some
robot research, but this thing is...
Is incredible.
Incredible is not a strong enough word, sir.
Incredible is not
a strong enough word, sir.
She was on a test run in the
bay area this morning.
These were taken by the
bank's security cameras.
As you can see, Eve Vlll got herself shot.
The point is, when she was shot...
somehow and we have no idea,
screwed up her internal workings.
- Now she's on the loose.
- And armed.
Oh, and armed, you bet.
Ok, so let me ask some
maybe stupid questions here.
You know where she is now?
No, our trace on her was knocked out
at the time of the shooting.
- So there's no way to communicate with her?
- That's affirmative.
When we eventually do find her,
how do we switch her off?
It's not as simple as that, colonel.
She's more human than machine.
See, she's just like a regular soldier.
You give her instructions
and she carries them out.
How dangerous is she?
She could be highly dangerous
if she's locked in battlefield mode.
What's that?
Battlefield mode
is Eve Vlll highest state of readiness.
It's mean, she's a split second away
from using force to protect herself...
from what she perceives as terminal harm.
So I guess that means she's no longer in the
mood to accept orders from a superior officer?
That's correct.
Well, this is quite some toy you have
yourself here, gentleman.
I suppose you want me
to put it back in its box?
It's not a toy, Colonel.
Dr Simmons, I'm glad you
could come at short notice.
- I was offered little choice, general.
- Bill Schneider you know.
This is Jim McQuade. Eve Simmons.
- Something wrong?
- No, you just look kind of familiar.
- Don't worry, she's quite human.
- That's not what my staff say, General.
Jim is been briefed on the situation, I hope
you two will be able to work together on this.
Doctor, I'm told that Eve Vlll is been
programmed with a lot
of your own life experiences.
Does that mean you think exactly alike?
Yes, she was programmed with much of my life
experience, but we're not exactly alike. No.
Just exactly what are
your qualifications, Mr McQuade?
What's your specialty?
Well, to tell the truth Doctor,
my specialty is a spinach lasagne.
In a very light tomato and basil sauce.
Actually Doctor, Mr McQuade is highly trained
and fairly knowledgeable in all aspects...
of counter-insurgency and anti-terrorism.
He's our very best field man.
He will neutralize Eve Vlll.
So your specialty is killing.
Which brings me to my next question,
Doctor, how do I kill this thing?
One seriously wounded and a customer, also
believed wounded, mysteriously disappeared
after overpowering one of the robbers.
This just in...
Her areas of vulnerability naturally are
approximate to those of a real human.
All the motor signals that control her limbs
come down the backbone which...
has a strong protective coating.
- What's that cylinder?
- That's just part of her protection.
Ok, what about the heart?
Will a bullet there stop her?
No, her heart, in fact her
whole blood system is cosmetic.
They're designed to let her medically pass
as human but have no real function.
It's tiny electrical currents that power her.
She'll bleed but she won't die.
So upper or lower
body are not good for a kill?
Correct.
The skull is very protected.
A good place to aim would be right or left eyes.
Those are both vulnerable areas.
A bullet through either eye
should terminate all motor activity.
I guess the eyes have it then, eh doc?
Your call sight Seeker. We'll be Homer.
We're also getting a chopper
with civilian markings.
Now, as far as the rest of the world is
concerned and that include press and police,
we'll simply be searching
for a dangerous female terrorist.
This will tell you if we're
dealing with the unthinkable.
If she goes nuclear,
you'll hear a high-pitched tone.
- He doesn't know?
- He doesn't need to.
The less people who know, the better.
Don't worry.
I'm told he's our very best
marksman, he's been fully briefed.
He'll aim for the eyes.
Sir, Eve Vlll's rented herself a car in
the Bay Area, a red 1990 Mustang.
She's also got herself
250 rounds of ammunition.
This say, she also specifically requested and
was given a detailed map of Northern California.
Pink lady.
That's nice.
- That's very nice.
- Very nice.
- Hey, Cal. Don't go getting greedy on us.
- Don't worry.
The same old line,
One for all and all for one.
Go to it, man.
What are you looking for?
Maybe I can help?
Get it while you can, Janis Joplin.
Janis Joplin?
Not on this machine, darling.
Dear Janis was dead
before this box was even built.
What you say you
and me step into the 90s?
Why don't we just go
and take a room, eh?
♪ Something you might want to know ♪
♪ Every time I see your face.
Oh, this feeling grows ♪
♪ I've been watching you for some time now
I know you've seen me too ♪
Sir, we're going to sweep to the
right and head north on US-1.
Roger. Copy that.
So Doctor, will start telling me
a little bit about yourself?
See, because I figure
the more I know about you,
the better my chances of
catching up with your mechanical double.
- Didn't you read my file?
- I read your file.
You're 33 years old...
you got a five-year-old son lives in
New York with his father, your ex-husband.
A former UN diplomat turned
writer, journalism mostly.
You probably have more qualifications
and letters behind your name...
than our friend the
general got ribbons on his chest.
But, that hardly gets me to first base
with what I'm dealing with here.
What about your file, Mr McQuade?
My file is classified, but then you don't
need to read my file to know I'm a great guy.
So you're the guy the government calls
when they don't want congress to know.
Sometimes.
Don't get me wrong, I'm not
some crazy right-wing extremist.
- So what do you believe in?
- Me, I believe in a strong defense.
I also believe we should show a little bit
more backbone when dealing with some...
Of the evils of this world,
international terrorism been the primary.
Also, automated bank tellers,
junk mail and cars that talk back to.
They don't like machines.
Is that why you seem to
have contempt for what I do?
- It's not contempt. It's disbelief.
- Disbelief?
I find it incredible that
someone as clever as yourself
spends billions of the taxpayers
dollars, years of hard work,
and you come up with something that
don't even have a fucking off-switch.
It's a little late to get cold, isn't it?
Excuse me.
You want your pearls?
Come here.
Come on.
Come here. Come on.
You want to play?
Come on. Show me how you play.
Easy.
Nice. Nice.
This is Napa 372. We found that
Mustang, will you send us some backup.
Now for the big surprise.
Come on, it's not a gun.
Come on. Come on.
Say hello.
Come to me.
- Come on, you bitch.
- Please, don't say that.
- Oh, no?
- I'm very sensitive.
I'm sorry, I didn't know
you were a sensitive bitch.
Cal?
You little bitch.
Come on up, get up.
- That bitch is crazy, that bitch is crazy.
- Where is she? Which room she in?
- I don't know.
- Which room she in?
- Put him in that car right there.
- Jack.
No. No. Let me go.
Easy.
Freeze.
Show us your hands, lady.
Show us your hands.
The motel is ten miles north
of Hopland, just off US-101.
How many dead, Homer?
Five. It's five cops, Jim.
- God.
- Stay right here. I'll deal with this.
We don't want to confuse these people.
Take it easy, friend.
You must be the Fed they're
squawking about, McCall?
- McQuade.
- Yeah, whatever.
I ain't had more than one shooting
here in the last three years
and that was a clown that went
shot himself in the foot.
Now I got myself a fucking war zone.
You know, I want to know
why some broader comes here,
brush away a bunch of my people.
And suddenly it's out of my jurisdiction.
- Captain, I understand how you...
- What are you doing, man?
Maybe you'd like to explain that
to the families of those troopers?
Excuse me.
- Homer. This is Seeker.
- Go ahead, Seeker.
It's not good sir, looks
like a bad night in West Beirut.
This thing is going to take some stopping.
Plus we have our friends
from the media crawling around.
This one is not going to go away quietly, sir.
Look, we got to bring in
more firepower to stop this thing.
Our story stands, general.
This is got to be low profile.
That's what Washington wants, sir.
Ok Ruby, I need a description.
Ok, she was blonde, curly blonde hair.
Wearing a tight black dress,
red leather jacket with zippers on.
- How tall?
- Five six, five seven, something like that.
Yeah, she made it real plain what she
was after as soon as she walk in the door..
What was that?
She was looking to
get laid, plain and simple.
Ok Ruby, let's go over it one more time.
- Didn't I say stay put?
- I know this place.
- Been here before?
- Not exactly but I know it.
- I think I know why she came here.
- Let's find someplace we can talk.
- Ok guys, in here.
- Right behind you.
Come here, we talk in here.
I lived near here for a while.
My friends and I drove
by this place all the time.
We never had the guts to come in here.
It's the local hooker joint.
But I...
- I used to imagine what it might be like.
- What what might be like?
What are you trying to say? What?
What?
I think Eve Vlll may have acted
out some kind of fantasy.
That's what I'm trying to say.
Now, wait a minute,
let me get this thing straight.
You're saying this device of yours acted
out one of your teenage sex fantasies?
Yes.
Incredible as it may seem.
Incredible is not a strong enough word, Doctor.
So this device of yours is horny
as well as psychopathic, eh?
It's quite a combination in a woman.
Look Doctor, what would you do
if you were her, seeing that you she
seem to be her and she seem to be you?
I don't know what she's
going to do next, Ok?
I can only give you some
clues after the event.
Yeah, well there might be a few
more events before she's through here.
Get out, get out.
Get the fuck out, get out..
Shit.
It's not going to help you
getting uptight with me, McQuade.
You have to realize this is my
life's work and is all going to waste.
Ok, Ok.
- Where were you born?
- In Santa Rosa.
I went to high school near here,
in Ukiah. I moved around a lot.
- Where your parents?
- My mother is dead.
- Your father?
- I don't know.
What you mean, you don't know?
Where's your father?
I don't know.
My mother died when I was six years old and
I went to live with my grandparents in Europe.
I didn't come back until I was 16.
Haven't spoken with my father in years.
He used to live in Gunerneville.
I have no idea where he is now.
- What's his name?
- Bill, Bill Simmons.
Have you got any other teenage
fantasies I should know about?
- What?
- Oh, shit.
I said, have you got any other teenage
sexual fantasies I should know about?
God.
Am I supposed to put myself for
analysis with some guy who's
probably never read anything more
complex than an army field manual?
Oh, get over it, lady.
Look, there's five dead cops out there
thanks to your surveillance device.
And along with that comes grieving
widows and their fatherless children.
And I don't think all that pain and loss
can compare to any embarrassment that you
might feel because you got to talk to me.
And you got to talk to me.
Look, we got to work together on this, Ok?
I want the names of all the places you lived,
all the schools you went to, friends, enemies,
acquaintances, good memories and bad.
And I want the names
of your favorite television programs,
your favorite food and,
if necessary, how you like it done to you.
We think Eve Vlll may visit
some of her inventor's old haunts.
I have a list of these places, Homer.
Think we should get on
stake out of some of these locations.
Copy that, Seeker.
Also, I want you to check the whereabouts
of one Bill, as in William, Simmons.
Used to live at 2331 South Harper, Gunerneville.
We also knows he served as an army
engineer in Germany, back in the 60s.
- Sir, we need put back to refuel.
- Roger, copy that.
Damn.
Fuck you, don't touch me, lady.
You aren't going to get
nothing in the car, I'm sick.
Please no, please no.
I'm sick and tired of hearing
you griping all the time.
Daddy...
Stop it. No.
What the hell are
you looking at, little bitch?
Come on.
Come on, get out of the way.
It's great, never fucking
get there. Come on, lady.
Fuck.
Hey lady, what is your
fucking problem? Stupid bitch.
There you go, lady.
Think about that one.
You just shut up and listen to me a second.
You and I made a deal, right?
Don't fuck with me like this. It's
business, business are business Charlie.
Friendship had nothing
to do with it, all right?
No listen, shut up a minute,
will you? And listen to me.
Are you with the program or you're
not with the program. Now, which is it?
And when I get in I want everybody
smiling, spit polished, All right?
What the...?
Wait.
Shit.
God.
Jesus Christ, she got a short fucking fuse.
Jesus.
- What's that?
- Oh, my God.
What the fuck is that?
- She is activated.
- Activated? What do you mean, activated?
- I need the radio.
- What do you mean is activated?
I need that radio.
Homer, this is Seeker. Come in, please.
- Homer, this is Seeker. Do you hear me?
- Seeker, this is Homer.
Target appears to be activated.
Repeat. Target appears to be activated.
What the hell is going on?
How the hell this happened?
We don't know. It appears
target sustained a severe impact.
She's put herself on a 24-hour clock.
Well, listen...
She's a battlefield
nuclear weapon, McQuade.
She's designed to
be deployed in hostile countries.
She's our answer to their space shield.
And if we don't find
her in the next 24 hours.
She'll explode with enough
force to take out 20 to 30 city blocks.
Your superiors thought
there was no need for you to know.
I was following my orders
like you're following yours.
She can only be activated by a complex
series of pre-arranged signals.
She's designed to be fail-safe.
You people are too much, you know that?
I mean, you really do think you're God.
Except that, when God created his Eve,
he did it to shake us up a little bit.
Now you've gone one better and
designed her to blow us all the fuck away.
May I?
- Homer, this is Seeker.
- Come in, Seeker.
Homer, just got some real interesting
news from the good doctor here.
You want to bring me up to speed on this?
You Ok, lady?
- I need your jeep.
- Well, you can't have my jeep.
Sir, Napa County Sheriffs have just
given us a location for a traffic accident.
Grid coordinates are Echo Golf
Niner Niner 45432. End transmission.
Seeker, we have a report of a jeep
being stolen a mile north crash site.
The owner was severely beaten.
Jeep is color red,
California license 2PX S822.
Yes, I'd like to speak to
the owner, Mr Victor Montoya.
Have an address for Bill Simmons:
29 Tompkins Lane, St Helena.
State police have been notified.
Backup is on its way.
Hello, Dad.
How did you find me?
Victor Montoya.
Victor Montoya, you know Victor?
Yes. He said, say hi.
I didn't know you've know Victor,
that's quite a memory you've got.
Well, then, I guess you'd better, come in.
Oh, there you are. Bill Kleinow.
We set up a briefing for you. Come this way.
Well, that's 29 Tompkins Lane.
The red jeep report stolen from
Russian Gulch is parked in the driveway.
- The householder's name is Simpson.
- You mean Simmons, right?
All right, the neighbors thought Simpson.
Now, they could be wrong,
apparently the guy is some kind of recluse.
- Well, that sounds right.
- Where's your man?
At the end of the
street, but I can get him to...
No, just tell him to stay out of
sight, this is my show, Captain.
- Who the hell are these guys?
- Your new deputies.
Listen, if this thing gets away from us we
may need to create some plausible deniability.
Perhaps you guys at Langley
could help us out on this.
Yeah, what you got in mind?
A little diversionary blame. Perhaps the Iraqis
or Libyans, whoever is top of your shit list.
- You recognise this place?
- Never seen it before.
- Lieutenant.
- Excuse me, ma'am.
- Sir?
- If she gets past me, hold your fire.
If she fires at you, take cover. Do not,
I'll repeat, do not fire back, understood?
- But sir...
- Understood?
Yes, sir.
Your job lieutenant, is to keep
track of her, not take her out.
- Got it?
- Yes, sir.
If things don't go my way you start
talking to General Curtis at the proceed.
- The call sign is Homer, you got it?
- Yes, sir.
Right, that ought to get
you through. Open channel.
It's Ok., lie still. Lie still.
Homer, this is Seeker.
Seeker, this is Homer.
Come in Seeker. Seeker, do you copy?
Homer, this is Frankel,
what you want me to do, sir?
You have your orders, lieutenant.
Stay where you are.
I saw you. I saw what you did.
What you see me do, Eve? Eh? What I do?
I saw what happened.
What did I do, Eve?
What did you see me do?
- I saw you.
- Eve. Don't.
Don't do it. He didn't kill her.
It wasn't him.
Ma'am. Shit.
- Are we going in, sir?
- Stay right here, soldier. Right here.
He didn't do it, Eve.
He didn't kill her. It wasn't him.
I saw you.
I saw what happened.
Eve, can you hear me?
Eve, listen to me.
He didn't kill her. It wasn't him.
Eve, do you hear me?
Eve?
Eve, it's Ok.
He's your friend Eve, don't harm him.
Eve please, don't harm him.
Oh, my God.
Eve, don't.
Get out. Get out.
Seeker, this is Homer.
Jim, goddamn it, where are you?
Come in Seeker. Come in Seeker.
- Yeah, I'm Ok.
- Outside.
Yes sir, I'm Ok. But we've got three
dead marines and a dead civilian here.
The target is still at large, repeat.
Target is still at large. Seeker out.
Your boy fucked up, General.
We had her. Fucking had her.
Eagle, this is Seeker. I need you to
make a sweep north of the Simmons' place.
Copy that, Seeker.
What did you mean when you said
I didn't kill her? Kill who?
The truth is, I've kept it
hidden away for so long that...
now I've begun to wonder
if it ever really happened.
- Bill, please.
- Don't touch me.
I was five, almost six years old.
It was raining hard that day.
We'd gone to pick up my father.
He'd been drinking at a local bar.
He liked to drink sometimes.
I'm not going to calm down.
That day he was very
drunk, too drunk to drive.
Get very angry when my mother
wouldn't let him have the car keys.
They were out of the car,
arguing by the side of a busy road.
- Come over here, give me the keys.
- Get in. I'll drive you home.
You aren't going to get
nothing get in the car. I'm sick.
- Give me the keys, you bitch.
- Don't call me a bitch.
Go if you want to drive one,
bitch, now give me the goddamn keys.
- But you're drunk.
- I'm not drunk, I'm happy.
Don't give me any more shit about, give me
the damn keys, bitch. I've had enough of this.
Get out of my face, bitch.
- Jesus, Jesus, Catherine.
- What happened?
I don't know. She just ran out.
Catherine, talk to me.
Fell or pushed or slipped, he was guilty.
He'd been killing her for years
and now he'd done it for ever.
We hardly spoke after she died.
Time didn't improve things.
I got more angry about what had happened.
Where you think she'll go now?
- I think she'll go to New York next.
- New York? Why New York?
To see Timmy, my son.
- You're sure about New York?
- I know what she's doing now.
It sounds crazy but she's
going back through my life.
Only there are no barriers, no stop signs.
Whatever damage she sustained
destroyed all her inhibitions.
She's doing things I might think about
doing but would never dare to do...
or have the courage to do.
We got to be right about New York.
Otherwise we're going to be in the wrong place
at the wrong time and a
lot of innocent people are going to die.
Wait, what really matters to me
is to be a good mother for Timmy.
And I know that's what she's feeling right
now, she'll go to New York to get my son.
- I got to be sure that...
- McQuade, I know I'm right.
We've dispatched hit teams
to La Guardia, JFK and Newark.
Do we know what flight she's on?
We're checking sir, there's
lots of permutations.
I'm afraid, gentleman,
it's true confessions time.
The president will have to be told, the
New York mayor's office have to be alerted,
so they can put evacuation plans into operation.
Look, you got to give us more time.
If we shock-up the streets with thousands
of panicked residents we'll never get her.
The general is right
sir, it's do or die now.
Jesus, then do it.
Seeker, Eve Vlll may had
a few hours head-start on us,
But we will have surveillance
in place in New York.
- This must all be routine for you.
- What's routine?
Dead bodies, people getting killed.
I've seen a lot of my friends put
in plastic bags and shipped home.
It's not routine.
Look, look, we believe in something.
We do what we do because we think
it'll help people, maybe stop a war.
We don't set out to destroy.
We set out to preserve a way
of life that we think is important.
The point is your intentions are good...
even if you did forget to
put in the fucking off-switch.
Thanks, McQuade.
Jim.
Eve, I hope you know I'll do everything
possible not to harm your son.
- But this may come down to some hard choices.
- I know.
What the hell he's doing?
I think he's learning
Russian or some damn thing.
Shouldn't we get the husband
and kid out of there?
If we move them, she may not show.
Unit One, this is Condor.
This is Unit One.
All clear.
Unit Two.
- All quiet round back.
- Unit Three.
He's down in the street.
Condor, this is Unit Three. All clear.
Condor, this is Seeker.
We're about 15 minutes away from you.
We copy that, Seeker.
Unit Three, where's that woman's dog?
She hasn't got her dog with her.
Unit Three, come in.
Come in, Unit Three.
Unit One, we've got trouble.
You trying to get killed, buddy?
Condor, this is Unit One. Unit Three's dead.
The target is in the building.
I repeat, the target is in the building.
Eve? What are you doing here?
- I miss something here?
- Timmy is here, isn't he?
Well, sure, it's the weekend.
That's a different look.
Is there raining now?
What's the matter? What's wrong?
- Where's Timmy?
- Are you Ok?
I need to see my son.
- Where is he? I need to see him now.
- Hold on here. What the hell is going on here?
- Hi Mom, what are you doing here?
- Hey, Timmy.
You miss me, don't you?
You do miss me, don't you?
Timmy, I love you, you know that I,
I'm sorry we don't spend
more time together, Timmy.
Look Eve, you're upset, Ok. Maybe we
should just sit and talk about it, Ok?
- Please, I...
- Eve, let's talk, Ok?
- Please...
- Come on...
We'll sit-down and
have some coffee, right?
Come on.
Timmy, you want help me
make your mom some coffee?
Ok, come on.
- Is Mommy going to be Ok?
- Yeah, she's going to be fine.
Hello?
- Peter?
- Yes.
- This is going to be difficult, it's Eve.
- What?
- The woman in your apartment is not me.
- Who the hell is this?
- Look through the window.
- What?
Peter, please. This is not a joke.
Look through the window.
It's me.
Oh, my God.
Listen carefully...
your life and Timmy's depend on
how you act in the next few minutes.
You know what I've been working on.
- Peter.
- Yeah, yeah.
She's one of my robots, Peter.
And she's very dangerous.
- Shit.
- What's wrong?
What am I supposed to do?
Tell to get Timmy out of there, come down in
the elevator and we'll meet him in the lobby.
Hey, are you still there?
- Peter?
- Yes.
You got to get Timmy out of the apartment.
Somebody will meet you in the lobby.
- Do you hear me?
- Yeah, I hear you.
But then do it now, please.
- Where's your mom?
- I don't know.
It's good now, we're
going to go out for a little while.
- But, Dad...
- I want you to be very quiet, Ok?
Get in here.
He's still alive. Get an ambulance.
- She's used the emergency exit.
- Get my back.
Get out of the way.
- Mommy.
- Timmy.
No, put me down.
Get back. Get back.
- That's my son, McQuade.
- Get back.
Let me go. Let me go.
Help, help, help.
- Let me down.
- I'll take care of you.
- No, put me down. Please, let me go.
Hey, what's your fucking problem, bitch? Why
don't you watch where the fuck you're going?
Subject has gone into
subway, 53rd and Fifth. Look out.
Copy that, Seeker. Project the area damage.
Dear God...
Look out, get out of the way.
Homer, this is Seeker. Dead
and injured on 53rd and Fifth station.
Target believed headed for
Lexington Avenue. Am in pursuit. Stay down.
Please don't shoot.
Wait.
Evacuate Lexington
Avenue and stop the trains.
And you better tell the New York Police
Department to stay the hell out of this.
I don't want anybody taking a pot shot.
Please, get help. Please.
Sir, the transit authority say
their computers are going haywire.
- They can't stop the trains.
- It's her.
Get out of there, motherfucker.
Fuck you, lady. Fuck you, lady.
What the hell are you looking at, bitch?
Bitch, bitch, bitch...
No one will ever shut a door on you.
Mommy will protect you, I promise.
- Eve.
- Mommy. Mommy.
Eve, throw him to me, please, throw him.
Eve, please.
Please throw him. Eve, please.
It's Ok.
Run. Timmy, run.
Hey, bitch.
Hey Doc, you want to give me a hand here?
Guess you finally found the
fucking off-switch, eh Doc?