Man: You know, you
want me to tell you
something really
interesting, man?
I was gonna wear a suit
in this interview,
but I thought it would
have been too much,
so I might as well put
these nice sweatpants on
and this nice shirt on.
It's a little too--
you know, too much, I think.
But next time, when we
have a good interview,
I'll wear a suit, OK?
Woman: One thing I
will mention is that
at times, you know,
if you ask a question,
there may be oc-occasions where
I--it may take me a little while
to respond, um, but that's
only because, um, it's--
I'm just trying to process
the--the incoming speech,
and then I'm trying to verbally
process the answer.
So you may hear a pause,
you know, at times, so...
Man, voice-over: I'm
from St. Paul, Minnesota.
I--I like living in St. Paul.
Different man, voice-over:
I never knew for sure
if I was gonna get married
or not, so that is something
that, um, I never was really
fixated on doing.
It's always been important to me
to have somebody in my life,
but whether or not I was
married to that person,
I wasn't sure about.
So, what kind of questions
you got to ask me?
Good. I feel good
about documentaries.
I'm comfortable
with looking at--
anywhere on the camera,
actually, so...
Hello? I'd like to
buy a cigar.
Yeah. Just one?
Let me see that
big one up there.
Hey, I got something
to ask you.
Did you hear about that
one basketball coach
that lived a long
time ago?
What happened to him?
The bask--the Celtics
coach...
Uh-huh.
Red Auerbach.
Did you ever
hear about that guy?
No.
I'll tell you
what he did.
Tell me what you
think about this, OK?
Every time--OK. He was
stubborn, arrogant,
and he was a jerk, OK?
All right.
And every time
he won a big game--
he won 9 championships--
OK.
Every time he won
a big game, he would--
He'd smoke a cigar.
He would smoke
a cigar, and--
It's a celebration.
Hold on.
He would rub it
in the other team's
face.
Well, it's
a cele--
No, he would, like...
He was--
It's a celebration.
How much is this thing?
That's $9.80.
Out of $10.
[Cash register beeps]
20 cents back.
Would you like a bag?
I'm good.
Have a great
weekend.
You, too.
Woman: I knew that there
was something special
with Lenny right away.
And he would always, like,
move his hands, like,
he would, like, get excited
and move his hands,
and he was very--always really,
really meticulous about stuff,
even when he was little,
like where it needed to be.
He just--when he wouldn't talk,
I knew that there was
something going on.
It's been hard.
You've got this kid that doesn't
really want to be autistic,
and Lenny's smart enough to
know that he's different,
and he doesn't like it.
That's a big, big struggle.
Lenny, voice-over:
Sometimes in my life,
I try to pretend
I was never autistic.
I felt like I had to
hide it from people
because if they heard
you were it,
then they would kind of...
kind of laugh at you
a little bit.
People would think to me, like,
you know, "He's cool,"
and when they found out I was
in that situation,
they would be like,
"Oh, he's kind of a weird kid.
We shouldn't be
hanging out with him."
Sometimes I feel
a little bit scared
because let's say you go--
you see a girl
and she likes you
and all this stuff,
and maybe if you admit
that you're autistic,
maybe she'll be like, "I don't
want to be with you no more
because you're autistic."
I don't know. That could be
a little hurtful, a little bit.
I'm single, by the way.
I've been single
for a long time.
Had one girlfriend, but it
didn't quite work out that well.
I don't want to talk about that.
Is that OK?
It's just, you know,
bad memories.
She was really not very nice,
and I know that sex
was a really big issue
because she had wanted
to have sex
and Lenny didn't want to,
and, um,
they split up for a while,
and then when he got back
together with her,
they ended up having sex,
and it wasn't, like,
a good thing.
Like, I really didn't realize
how little Leonard knew
until recently.
Like, he didn't know anything.
I just want to tell those young
kids, "Don't have sex yet."
You know, you're gonna
get screwed one day.
Well, you can have sex
with the girl or the guy
for both of you when--I feel
like it doesn't have to happen
the first day.
No way. You're jumping the gun.
You're shooting
the gun right away.
You've got to do it
when it's, like,
a couple of months
into it, man.
Or maybe a year.
When you get married.
That's what I think.
Don't have sex
on the first date.
That's not love right there.
That's just--that's not love
when you do it
on the first date,
when you meet someone
for the first time or--
that's called reckless love.
That's called reckless.
Kathy: He's lonely.
He wants a girlfriend.
And his dad's not around,
and he just doesn't have
that positive male role model
to kind of tell him, like,
"This is how you do it.
This is what you do.
"This is"--you know,
he's got me.
He's got Mom.
[Indistinct voice on TV]
Dave: I met Lindsey at
a national autism conference
from the Autism Society
of America
in Nashville, Tennessee,
in July of 2005.
We started calling it
a relationship
in the fall of that year,
maybe 3 or 4 months later
when we met up
at another conference,
and I asked her,
"How would you feel
about being in
a relationship with me?"
She said, "Well, I'm confused,
but I could see if this maybe--
this may work."
She was confused at first,
but she could see this working.
"We'll give it a try."
[Door opens]
Hi!
How are you?
I'm good.
Welcome home.
Thank you.
Lindsey, voice-over: I think
that autism definitely
presents unique challenges
to our relationship.
Our particular routines
and rigidities and our--our
particular comfort zones and...
we're so fixated on--on that
that it's sometimes difficult
to communicate to each other.
Love your necklace.
Oh! Thanks.
Do you know--
did I ever tell you,
um, one bene--
one reason I love
jewelry so much is
because it gives me
a, um--a sort
of a sh--a shield
to sort of protect
myself from sort of
vulnerable elements?
That's--that's news
to me, actually.
I didn't know that.
Oh, really?
Vulnerable elements.
Yeah. I kind of
discovered that
after wearing
necklaces
for the past
several--you know,
the past--especially
the last 10 years.
I've really been into
wearing heavy jewelry,
and I discovered
a reason why it was--
that it kind of makes
me--because I feel
so vulnerable and feel
so, um, shy and...
Mm-hmm.
you know, introverted
that wearing the jewelry
kind of makes me feel
that sort of false
sense of confidence,
and it kind of makes
me feel less vulnerable.
It makes me feel like
it's sort of a shield,
sort of protect myself
from feeling, um,
more--more vulnerable.
Well, it looks like
the weather just came on.
I was gonna, like,
catch a glimpse here
and see what he says
about the--
Oh, of course. I can't
ever interrupt you
from the weather.
Well, you can always s--
be near me,
but I may not
talk to you as much.
Yeah, but--
[Increases TV volume]
Man on TV: 47. Not gonna
fall that fast tonight.
Winds are still
gonna be a factor.
Northwest at 16.
I'm gonna go.
I'll be right back.
OK.
Man on TV: And it should
all be finished
tomorrow night,
which is a good thing.
Satellite picture...
Man on TV:
and lots of sunshine
and 64 on Monday.
Chance of showers
and rain Monday night
into Tuesday...
[Music box playing]
Should we go rock
in your rocking chair?
Shall we?
Man, voice-over:
We tried to treat her
as normally as
we possibly could,
all the time making allowances
in our own mind
for the fact that she might not
be able to do everything
quite as fast or quite as well
or something like that
but just trying to raise her as
normally as we possibly could.
Here we go. Ah!
Here we go.
Come on. Lindsey?
Gordon, voice-over: We all,
evidently, come equipped
with a social antenna that we
don't even realize we have.
We know instinctively
when we are getting
too close to someone physically,
when we seem to be pushing them
a little further than
they want to be pushed,
when maybe we should back off
and not be quite so bossy
or controlling.
Lindsey didn't have the antenna.
Gordon: Lindsey,
can you wave?
Say--Lindsey.
Here's the water.
Lindsey.
Woman: She just asked
me to put the hat
back on her.
Different woman: Cute.
Gordon: Lindsey.
[Toddler crying]
Gordon: Can you wave?
Can you wave?
Child: Yeah.
Gordon: Yeah.
Gordon, voice-over:
It's sort of mystifying,
but the absence
of that antenna,
very hard.
That was very
challenging for her.
She wanted to fit in.
Man: Oh. Has anybody
seen Lindsey?
Group: Where is Lindsey?
[Laughter]
Woman: There she is!
There she is. Yeah.
Woman: Lesser-known names
for 600, please.
Alex Trebek: Senator Robert
Wagner sponsored the act--
Man: What is the National
Labor Relations Board?
What is the National Labor
Relations Board?
Alex: Rob.
Rob: What is the National
Labor Relations Board?
Alex: Correct.
Rob: Compound words
for 400.
Alex: Motorcyclist
Evel Knievel
is called this
on his tombstone...
What's a daredevil?
Alex: and by
the Smithsonian.
Man: What's a daredevil?
Alex: Joshua.
Joshua: What is
a daredevil?
Alex: That's it.
I did very well,
huh?
You did very well.
Thank you.
I'm proud of you.
Woman on TV: Monday
at 6:30...
Matt: What are you having
for dinner tonight?
Uh, sole--fish
with mashed potatoes.
Have you got
mashed potatoes?
Woman: Not yet.
Matt:
Are you cooking?
My mother
is cooking.
Matt: Oh, OK.
Do you ever cook?
I cook hot dogs
every Sunday.
Matt: When he was young,
did you think
that he would be capable
of a romantic relationship?
[Sigh]
No. I didn't dare hope.
I didn't dare hope.
Man, voice-over: Although, uh,
his expression was not there,
but he had knowledge.
[Stephen reading
prayer in Hebrew]
Mother: But of course,
he still does not elaborate
and doesn't express himself
too--too well about
his real feelings.
His language is still
not up to the way
it should be.
He talks, and he
communicates, and...
But in
a certain way.
In a certain way.
Matt: So tell me more
about your job, Stephen.
Well, I was doing
assembly work,
and I was working
in stamps,
and I worked on trays.
What's trays?
Trays just means
to fold for the U--
for the United
States Postal Service.
Oh, OK. And so
when you do stamps,
what--tell me what
you have to do for stamps.
To put them
in envelopes.
How many do you do
a day, would you say?
Uh, 500.
Wow. That's a big
workload.
Yes.
Wow.
And how many hours
a day do you work?
8 hours, from 7:00
until 3:00.
OK. How do you get
to work?
By bus.
Do you take one bus
or more than one?
Just the bus.
Just one bus.
Yes.
Oh. Do you like
the bus?
Yes.
Edith, voice-over: Our aim was
he should become independent.
He should be able to
hold down a job.
That, thank God,
we accomplished
without him being
institutionalized.
Lenny: He's a bad man, this guy.
Kathy: What's up,
dude?
Lenny: What's up,
Mom?
Let me finish up
the game first.
Come on.
So we talked about
a dating website
a little bit.
Yeah. I think I might
want to do that.
What would you put if you
were, like, putting, like--
I don't know.
It's hard to say.
I like to keep it
private
to me and you only.
I'm gonna be serious.
I'm not gonna be
no joking around.
OK, if you were gonna
put on a dating website,
like, your interests--
Sports.
OK. What else?
You wouldn't put--
how come you wouldn't
put any of, like,
the Comic-Con stuff?
Do you think
that's silly?
Nope. I won't
do it.
How come?
Because I don't
want to.
OK.
That's you. That's--
But why don't you--
you don't want to find
somebody that likes
that kind of stuff, too?
Nope.
So, what other interests
would you put?
I don't know.
I'll be taken
more serious.
So you want, like,
a serious girl?
Yeah, a little bit.
OK. A businesswoman?
No, not completely,
but I pay
for the dates.
Me. That's the way
it goes.
OK.
That's the way
the show goes.
I'm not gonna let her
pay for everything
and me, you know,
I got to be the one
that...
is the more independent
one than her.
But I don't think
that that's fair.
No, it is fair.
Kind of chauvinistic.
No, it's not.
I think a little bit.
I mean, what if there's
a woman out there
that is perfect for you
but she makes more money
than you do?
Nope.
I won't take her.
I'm serious.
Kathy: He does not want
to be different.
He just wants to be
like everybody else,
so then he goes above
and, like, kind of goes
beyond trying to fit in,
and everybody--
I can see they're like,
"Why is he acting like this?"
Like, we all know
Lenny's special,
so he just needs to be
who he is, and he's not.
He tries to be
something different.
Lenny: I need to
be the one
making more money.
I hear so many
things about--
YouTube videos
about women.
By men. OK--
No. It's a woman
saying,
"Don't be
with broke-ass men."
Wow.
These are the kind
of women--
No, they're trying
to inform the women
not to be
with broke men,
and I don't want
to be--
I don't want to be
a broke male
with a woman.
I don't want her
paying for everything.
I need to be the one--
You don't have to be
paying for everything--
or she doesn't have to
be paying for everything.
You could be paying
for stuff,
but when you get into
a relationship with somebody,
you're supposed to be
their partner. Partner.
Well, I need to be
the one doing more.
That's the way
it goes.
I don't think
that's the way it goes.
I think that you're
being misinformed
by people that are just
not really great people.
I think you're
being misinformed.
I'm not.
I think you are.
What if you find
somebody--
and I'm just saying
if you love somebody,
it shouldn't matter.
It should be, like,
you just love her,
and maybe one day you'll
be making more money,
and you guys just
support each other
in that good kind of
like foundation and--
It's just hard.
It's just hard
to believe that.
Why?
It's just about being
the more independent one.
But you will be
independent.
You're going to
be independent.
That is gonna
happen, Lenny.
Sometimes it takes
a minute for people.
It's hard. That transition
from fricking--into manhood?
That thing, that's hard.
I know.
I couldn't even--
it was hard--
I'm good,
though, Mom.
I'm trying
to be good.
Well, trying to be
good how?
I want you
to feel good.
I'm just going
through
a little bit
of a struggle.
I'm down on myself
too many times,
and it's too tough
because I feel like
I should be accept--
doing more in life.
Do you think--
do you consider yourself
like less sometimes?
That's kind of what
I get.
Sometimes.
Why?
I feel different.
I feel better than being
autistic sometimes.
Let's get past this.
Let's get over this
and get on with it
because you're
fricking awesome.
I know. I know.
I don't think you do.
I know.
I think you don't
and you need to know.
OK.
I love you.
Kathy: He's really
down on himself.
I think once he starts working,
he's gonna feel
better about himself.
He's gonna feel more productive,
like he's out there
doing something.
Because right now he doesn't
feel like he's doing anything.
Man on TV: Some points
in Massachusetts
and Rhode Island could see
up to a foot of snow,
and in New Jersey,
well, the storm is certainly...
Lindsey, voice-over: I always
knew I was different,
even before I was informed
of my diagnosis of autism,
though I always felt like
I was an odd character
outside of my--my peers.
But I didn't really
understand why.
I would often get turned away,
or people would ignore me,
and I--I thought,
"Well, what am I doing wrong?"
And even after learning about
my own diagnosis,
I still, for several years,
struggled to figure out
why I couldn't, um,
maintain and keep friends,
why I couldn't fit in,
why I couldn't be accepted.
Unfortunately, I think the first
impressions I received, um,
when I was learning about autism
were quite negative,
and as a result,
I felt incredibly ashamed
of being autistic.
Every morning when I get ready,
I look in the mirror
before I step outside the house,
and I think to myself,
"Well, I look OK.
I look OK today."
And the moment I step
outside the front door,
I immediately become
self-conscious.
I've recognized pretty quickly
that the way I perceive myself
in the outside world
is drastically different than
the way I perceive myself
in my own world.
In some aspects
and at some times,
I do feel like I have found
that personal happiness
within myself,
or that personal peace.
But it's still very
difficult for me
to find acceptance
of myself.
I have just learned how
to be a good actress.
Woman: I remember when
you first started at work,
and, um, I wasn't sure--
I wasn't necessarily sure
what to expect
because, you know,
everybody on the spectrum
is different, and...
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
you never know if
somebody is going to be
very outgoing or--you know,
kind of the classic
description of someone
on the spectrum
is not--you know,
unfortunately,
not interested,
empathetic,
you know, not into--
I always had this fear
people would be
staring at me, that...
people can see
right through me.
I think it kind of
relates to
my frustration I've
had over the years
of...
being pressured to fit
into the social norm...
that I'm not good enough
if I don't fit in.
Have you ever dated
somebody
who was on
the spectrum before?
Actually, all--all
the guys I've dated
prior to Dave were--
yeah, were not
on the spectrum.
So Dave is the first.
And how is it
different?
Dave: For me, it boils
down to 3 things.
I have a formula here.
It's L plus P plus two T.
So each part is 25%.
So you have 25% of the P and L,
and you have 50% of the T,
which results to what that
person's grade would be
in terms of relationship
and dating potential.
Now, you're wondering,
L is how they look physically--
physical appearance
and attributes.
The second--the P
is personality.
What is their lifestyle like?
And most importantly is T
is how they treat you.
Treatment towards you.
If--let's say, for example,
that the person
is relatively ugly.
Then they get, like, a 50%
category in the L category.
But they have, you know,
like a perfect personality
and nearly perfect way
they treat you,
they're gonna score pretty well
in the overall scheme of things.
So the T has greater weight.
It's twice as much weight
in the formula
than the personality and looks
is how they treat you.
[Playing piano]
Lindsey: You know,
it's funny with Dave.
He--he's much more scientific,
and I'm much more artistic.
I think Dave is trying his best
to understand me.
I think he always has
tried his best to understand me.
I think it's still
difficult for him to--
to really have that grip,
though, of understanding,
of why I have
my particular issues.
[Playing piano]
You know, it's
a very good question
whether someone can love you
without truly understanding you.
I still think it's
absolutely possible. Yeah.
You know, obviously
we have, from time to time,
talked about marriage
and, um, if we were
to get married someday
and kind of
some of the fears
we have with that.
Um, uncertainties.
Yeah, and idea of
whether Lindsey
would take my name
or keep her own name.
And talk about, like,
prenuptial agreements
and how they would
be written out
and, uh,
financial matters,
how they'd be, um,
managed.
Um, things like that.
Yeah.
And where the wedding
would take place.
Yeah, well, I think
that's not really fears.
I think that's just
more of, you know,
listing the pros
and cons
and kind of--
it's the whole idea
of whether marriage
is going to dictate
that our identities
are lost.
That's kind of
my main fear.
I'd still support
keeping
our own identities.
I mean, marriage is
just a--kind of like
a social title
we would have,
but we'd still have
our own identities.
Yeah.
Of course. I would
insist upon it.
I mean, Dave has--has been
through a lot with me,
and he's still around,
and that to me is definitely
evidence of--of love.
Dave: I love it when she shows
me physical, um, appreciation,
when she holds me, hugs me,
kisses me, smiles at me.
I always love it when she comes
to tuck me into bed at night.
But I feel like she puts me very
high up on her daily list.
I feel like I'm very much
important to her
and that I'm a big part
of her life.
But the T score also
ties in very much
to how important
that person makes you feel.
If you don't--if you get
the impression
that person doesn't think
you're important,
that hurts your T score.
When I was first dating her
and first meeting her,
I never had stronger feelings
for anybody else ever before.
The fact that they lasted for 8
years I think is a good signal
that things were on a very
solid course here.
Man on TV: ...the winter
we get in Memphis
in the Midwest region.
Different man: [Indistinct]
boring car interiors forever,
and that's how you do it.
...well-qualified lessees
get a low-mileage lease
on the Dodge Dart SXT
for 149 a month...
Different man: If you have
been diagnosed with lung cancer,
you may be entitled
to compensation.
Even with a history of smoking,
you may still qualify.
Asbestos trusts have
been established,
and millions of dollars have
been paid to people
with lung cancer
or mesothelioma.
To learn more, contact us now
for a free consultation.
Call 1-800-950-MESO.
For nearly two decades,
we've been fighting
for people with lung cancer
and mesothelioma.
Call us at 1-800-950-MESO.
[Chatter]
[Music playing]
Man: When Stephen
first saw Gita,
he was introduced to her.
Stephen said,
"I'm going to marry her."
[Laughter]
And after a few days, Gita said,
"Let's set a date."
[Laughter]
Well, the date is here,
and this is the couple,
and we hope that
this marriage is from God.
It's going to be a lasting
marriage and a happy marriage.
Stephen, voice-over:
I met Gita 20 years ago.
It was on February 7, 1993.
Matt: What day of
the week was that?
It was on a Sunday.
What did you say
to her
when you first
met her?
"Hello."
And what did you think
when you first met her?
It's nice. It was beautiful.
Are you in love
with Gita?
Yes, I'm in love with Gita.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
It means to fall in love,
to give a kiss
and a hug.
How do you know
when you're in love?
I don't know.
Max: Somebody suggested
they knew of Gita.
They said, "Maybe
these two together--
"these two will
get together.
Maybe they'll make--
they'll make a couple."
Edith: They were kind of
complementing each other.
Gita is very verbal.
That's what Stephen is lacking.
Stephen has other qualities
that she was lacking,
so they really
complemented each other.
Max: They lived happily
for almost 17 years,
and then unfortunately,
Gita got ovarian cancer,
and she's fighting with
it for the last 3 years.
Remember 3 years ago,
Gita had chemo?
3 years ago.
Matt: What is chemo?
I don't know.
It's a disease.
Is that bad?
It's bad.
So, what happened
after chemo?
I don't know.
She went to the doctor.
She went to the Mayo
Clinic in Rochester.
What happened there?
Uh, she had to go--
yeah, she had tests
for her cancer.
She had tests.
And what did
the tests say?
Uh, her condition
is, uh, I don't know.
Edith, voice-over:
Stephen is very hopeful
about her sickness.
He says, "Gita's
not gonna die.
She'll be all right."
[Indistinct
voice on TV]
Hi, Marlena.
I feel a little better.
I'm getting better.
Hello.
Hi, honey.
Gita, voice-over:
The thing with Stephen
is that he is...
I find that
he understands me
in his own way.
I have a learn--a mild
learning disability,
and, um--ahem--
so but still and all,
I feel in a way that
I can understand him
because he can--because
we both have something
we cannot do
and things we can do,
but being that
we have disabilities,
we can...
we can relate all the more.
Tell me what else
is new.
Nothing.
Nothing? Well,
I--I relaxed all day...
That's good.
trying to feel better.
Uh-huh. That's nice.
Yeah.
I don't know if this is
the right thing to say,
but I feel bad that he's
not able to express himself,
and I'm--and I try to
encourage him,
to make him feel
as if he can,
and you know something?
He has improved a lot.
How was your day?
It was excellent.
What did you do?
Well, I worked--
I worked on towels
today at MBI.
Towels? What do
they look like?
Well, they look
like, uh--
they look like
wash towels.
They look like
dish towels.
Oh, nice.
What colors were they?
They were purple.
Oh, nice. What's
your favorite color?
Blue.
Blue. And my favorite
color is red.
Well, that's nice.
You have a nice hat,
huh?
Yeah. Just look at me.
Yes.
Relax.
It's always difficult.
It's always difficult,
but I got used to it.
I got used to it.
It's extremely difficult,
but I think if I were married
to someone who it--
wasn't disabled
or who isn't disabled,
I'd have more of a problem
because that person might
be--be--ahem--demanding
and want more out of me.
So tell me more.
Well, I'm going to
eat dinner
at my parents'.
Oh, that's good.
Well, I hope
you'll feel better,
and I'll see you
later.
See you later,
honey.
Thanks for dropping by
and wishing me well.
You're welcome.
Matt: How do you
know that Stephen
is in love with you?
Gita: Um...
it's in the way
he looks at me.
I can tell.
He gives me
such loving eyes.
Dave: Love is a very
abstract concept
that many people with autism
have a hard time grasping,
and it's one of those things
that's not concrete.
As a scientist, I wish I could
put it into perspective
as a type of subatomic particle,
but it's not.
Love is basically
more like a force.
Like, in physics,
you have forces--
forces of attraction--
and I have a feeling
that love is--the best way
to describe that
is a force of attraction
between two people
that is neither visible,
measurable, or heard.
There's no way to quantify it.
Lenny: I'm feeling a little
down about myself right now.
Matt: Why is that?
I've just been down lately.
I've been a little...
sometimes you go through
hard times in your life.
I feel like I can't
get a girl.
I don't--there are
no girls at my school.
Everywhere I go,
it's something about guys.
I go home,
I see my stepfather,
and the only women I see
are my good friends
or my--my--my sister, like,
girls are sort of
like my sisters
or my home girls,
and that's so annoying.
You don't see women
anywhere.
It's like--I feel like
if someone came up to me
and said, "Would you--would you
want to go to a women's prison
for a week?" I would
probably say yes.
"Would you--would you go
to a women's jail for a week
and be the only man there?"
I'd probably say yes.
Lenny, voice-over: I feel like,
you know, if I had a girl,
maybe--maybe I'll be
happy right now.
Maybe I'll be--
feel good about myself.
You know what, Matt?
I'm gonna admit
something to you.
Do you want me
to tell you something?
I like girls that are black.
I like them a lot.
What do you think about that?
Do you know what interracial--
interracial relationships are?
Inter--interracial
relationships?
It means when different race
people go out with each other.
I was reading something
on the computer
that...
black women are really
independent,
and it said that
they're lucky girl--
that they're really
intelligent women,
and I feel like that, you know,
I want a girl like that,
but I feel like I can't.
Matt: Why do you think
you can't?
Because, you know,
they're too independent.
I need to be more
independent.
I need to get a good job
and make good money.
Dave, voice-over: You get
married for love, too,
but for me, there's more of
a practical component as well.
Probably 60% practical
and 40% emotional.
I'll always love her.
That won't change.
But for the specific
reasons for the marriage,
that's what it'd boil down to.
Lindsey, voice-over:
I had told him a few years ago
that whenever he was ready
to take that next step,
that I would be
willing to--to accept.
I've--I've yet to hear
any kind of indicator
that that next step
may be taken.
Um, I know that we kind
of brushed over this,
like, when we chatted
about it.
I do believe you
and trust you
when--when you've
told me that
you were in it
for the long haul.
Oh, yeah.
And I do believe you,
and I do--you know,
I do trust you,
and I--I, um, you know,
I definitely am in it
for the long haul
for us, too, and I--
I wouldn't--you know,
I wouldn't be here
if I wasn't.
Well, I know that.
Yeah.
I guess I'm just--
I was just still
kind of just figuring
out, like--
That was a conversation
that made me
a little bit
uncomfortable, too.
Oh, you mean
at the time?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Well, it's
uncomfortable
for me, too, but...
it's important.
It's important.
Sometimes I think
there's conversations
that are uncomfortable
for us, but they're
really important
to have or at least
to address them
in order to us
to understand
where each other
are coming from.
So I--I'm not gonna lie.
So...
But having this on camera,
I don't like at all.
I don't like the idea
of having this conversation
on camera at all.
OK.
It's one of those things
that's best left
off camera, I think.
OK. We can stop
talking about it.
Yes.
All right.
Thank you for--
thank you for
letting me know.
I think--yeah, I just
feel better that way.
OK.
I just feel
uncomfortable
being on camera
talking about it.
All right.
No, thank you
for letting me know.
But you know how
I feel,
so don't worry
about it.
Lindsey, voice-over:
There's been times
that I have questioned whether
he really wants to be with me.
Gordon: Within yourself,
you think you can communicate.
You think you've
said something.
You think it should be
obvious to somebody
that's this, this, and this,
but again you go back
to the antenna.
Maybe you are, but maybe
they haven't picked that up.
Stephen, voice-over: Yes,
this is my apartment with Gita.
Uh, this is our bedroom.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Gita moved here with me, uh--
that was 15 years ago.
[Door closes]
And this is our bathroom.
Stephen, voice-over: She moved--
she had to go--she had surgery
on--in May 2010.
That was 3 years ago.
Stephen, voice-over: I'll take
a shower tonight at 7:00.
Edith: OK, maybe at 7:30
if you go later to Gita's.
I'll go--I'll go see
Gita right now.
I think they're
eating, still.
They're eating--no,
they're
still eating dinner.
They're eating dinner.
Yeah, because Erica
was making it late...
Yes.
because Gita wasn't
feeling well.
I hope Gita
will feel better.
I hope so.
She threw up.
She felt nauseous.
Yeah. Did she
tell you that?
Yeah, she told
me that.
When you were there?
Yes.
I'm trying--I'm trying
to be positive, man.
I'm just--
it's been kind of hard
the past couple of weeks.
Last week I did
something to a girl,
and it wasn't right.
It felt--it felt
kind of stupid, what I did.
I was bored. I wanted to see
what women felt like.
It felt good for a little bit.
Maybe for, like, 20 minutes
it felt good, but it just
felt like you--
two things.
It felt like you wanted
to do it more times,
but it just felt like
whatever at the end
because it just--
that wasn't--
I don't--
I don't know that girl.
I don't love her.
I just--
it felt like,
I kind of felt bad for
her a little bit.
People told me that--
I talked to 2 or 3 people.
[Whispers] I kind of
want to say it
when there aren't
that many people around.
I kind of want to say it softly
because it isn't good.
People tell me that, "Oh"--
p-people, they tell me,
"Oh, you got ripped off
for just touching her ass."
People told me that "you
could have gotten a ha--"
People told me that I
could have gotten a ---.
People--you know
what this stuff means?
People told me that
I could have gotten a ---.
People told me that I
could have gotten--
could have ---.
People told me that
I could have...
had --- her.
That's what people told me--
those 4 things,
People told me
people told me that I could
have done those 4 things
with--with the 20 bucks,
that "you got ripped off"
and "delete her number."
She told me
her name was Diamond.
That--that doesn't sound
like a real name, does it?
Dave, voice-over: I've been
together with her for 8 years,
and a lot of people
are wondering,
"Why are you still
just boyfriend/girlfriend?"
A lot of people are asking,
"When are y'all
gonna get married?"
That's, um--that's always a big
step for a guy to take,
and got to make sure
it's the right one.
When we talked about it,
she made me feel like,
"Oh, I do want to marry you,
but maybe now's
not the right time."
That's--it's not likely,
but it's possible
she might say that.
Uh, I--sometimes what she thinks
is different from what I think,
so...
Lindsey, voice-over:
I think before I said yes,
I'd want to ask him...
what in particular
had been holding him back
the past few years,
since when I first
brought it up.
Gordon: Nobody was exactly at
the same place at the same time.
I hope, for her sake, that--
that they will eventually
make a--a firm and formal
commitment to each other.
OK, maybe it's just
a few simple words
or something like that.
Maybe it's just a little
formal ceremony,
something like that,
but it means something.
It makes a difference.
It--it gives a base for someone
to feel self-confident
about giving everything of
themselves to the other person
without restraint
or without holding back.
But I think that's just one
of the challenges
that they've had
to work through.
[Indistinct]
So do you still, um,
continue to think
about the future?
Like next steps
and stuff like that.
Well, I--I thought
we had that conversation
recently about how
I wasn't reading your mind
and I wasn't sure.
Yeah.
And then you--you
reassured me
that, um, you...
that I--I shouldn't
be worried about anything.
Just I was gonna see
if still--
everything is still
the case.
Is that still
the same thing?
You wouldn't be
hesitant
to the idea of
marriage, would you?
I don't think you've
ever been so candid
about this
conversation before.
I guess you've been
thinking about it.
I have.
[Chatter from
other tables]
Well, I--I'll be
honest with you.
I think regardless,
I'm always going to be
afraid of anything
that involves, um,
major life transition.
Right.
Right? And marriage
is one of them.
Is what? I'm sorry.
Marriage is
one of them.
Yeah, it is.
We seem pretty
happy, though,
as a couple,
don't we?
We seem pretty happy
as a couple, right?
Well, the question
is, do we feel happy?
I do.
I--I feel similarly.
Lenny: I am high class.
You know that?
What? You calling me stupid?
I'll call you stupid.
You know what?
Let me tell you something, Matt.
I didn't know what
the hell happened, man.
Let me just tell you
what happened.
I wish I was not autistic.
There. I'm gonna
say it right now.
I don't like it.
It makes me different.
I wish I could have
been a normal person.
I wish I could have been
a normal, regular person.
My mom says,
"Be autistic. Accept it."
I tried accepting it.
It's hard.
Can I be honest with you?
If I could change something--
if I could--
I'm gonna try to change it,
but I told my mom this
right now
because of how
disappointed I was.
I would rather be
a normal man
than be an autistic person
with a million dollars.
There. If God came up to me
and says, "What do you want?"
I don't want to be
autistic anymore.
I wish you can give me
a new li--me.
I could start my life all over
again and I wasn't autistic.
There. Let me be
a normal person.
I bet you all the damn people
I knew in middle school
and high school, they're all
in fricking college now.
I'm not in college.
That's what I wanted
when I was in high school.
I dreamed of going to college,
and I'm not in college.
I wanted to go to college.
I wanted to go to college!
I don't--I think now I should
have graduated college!
I should have been
in college right now.
I should have
graduated college right now.
I know so many people
that went to college,
and they're done right now.
I can't hang out
with people like that.
I can't.
Matt: Why not?
Because they're higher--
they're higher than me.
Look. They're up here.
I'm down here.
They're--I'm all
the way down here.
They're all the way up here.
That's what I think.
Lenny: I want to get a girl
that's kind of lower than me.
That's what I want.
If I found a girl that
had a job, had a car,
had her own home,
I can't be with her.
She deserves to be with
somebody better than me.
She's up here. I'm down here.
That's the way I see it.
It's hard, man.
It's really hard
to accept it, man.
Yeah, this is--
this is hard, man.
This is tough.
This is--this is probably
one of the hardest things
I have to go through
in my life.
Don't cry, man. Let me cry.
I don't want to see
a tear come out of your eye.
It's hard.
What do you think
about me crying?
What do you think the peop--
the viewers could think
about this?
[Crying]
It's emotional.
I can't let that happen.
I got no job. I got no car.
I'm living with my parents.
I should be doing something.
I'm a good person, man.
I'm not a bad person, Matt.
I'm a good guy.
That's just--
It hurts. It hurts, man.
He once told me that...
that, um--he said, "You ever
walk into a room...
and you know everybody's
talking about you?"
And he said that's how
he feels every day
when he leaves
the house, you know?
So, um...
I just want my son
to be happy.
And, um, I think he needs
to come to terms
with who he is
because he's not comfortable
with who he is,
and if he's not
comfortable with who he is,
I don't know how he could
ever expect anybody else
to be comfortable
with who he is.
Stephen, voice-over:
I feel sad about Gita.
She died last April.
She had cancer. That's sad.
She was laying down.
She was laid to rest.
I miss Gita. I miss Gita.
When Gita died, we went
to the--to work
to tell him.
It was on a workday,
and he was there,
and when I told him,
he just turned white
like a sheet.
He put his head
down on the table.
I could tell
he was very upset.
She was gone.
Matt: Do you feel like
you're still
in love with Gita?
No. I stop loving
someone--they die,
because they die,
because Gita died
on April 9.
No longer in love.
Max: It is a big help
for him to go back--
go back to work.
Edith: We encouraged
him to pick up life
like...
normal, sort of.
Stephen, voice-over:
I fell in love with Gita
for the past 20 years.
And then gave--I gave
Gita a hug.
I gave Gita a hug.
I--I put my arms around her.
Dave: In physics, we have
something called
electromagnetic spectrum--
how much energy
a wavelength has.
You go from radio waves to light
to ultraviolet,
x-rays, gamma rays.
And then how I feel
towards someone
is kind of on a similar scale.
You have different wavelengths
going from just physical lust,
then you go--graduate from
a general interest
in the opposite sex.
Then you graduate from having
a specific intense crush
on a specific person.
Dave: And after that,
it kind of evolves into
another stage, which is
the true love stage
and not having that deep crush
where you're thinking about her
24/7 and you have
a hard time sleeping
because you're so much
in love with her,
but it kind of graduates
into a more subconscious form.
Let's say you're going
from light waves
that you can basically see
to ultraviolet waves.
They're still there,
but you can't see them.
But they're stronger.
Is that making sense?
Lindsey: Are you sure
that was--
are you sure that was
the spot
where we did
that photograph?
I want to say
it was taken
somewhere
around here.
Very--this is
nostalgic, isn't it?
Almost 8 years ago.
It's always amazing
when you look back
in time, how things
have grown and how
our relationship
has grown
and what we've
been through
has been really
amazing.
That says something
when you go
for a relationship
that long,
that is a very
strong signal
that the relationship
is meant to be.
And at first, um, you
were kind of confused
as to where
we were headed,
and I remember
you telling me
you were--you would
have been totally happy
just pursuing
your career
and being a single
woman,
and then...
Remember that slide
you kind of show
on your presentation--
is it the
physics-related slide?
Yes. Yes.
Where you have...
the wavelengths.
The alpha and the beta
and the gamma?
And the delta.
The delta.
And I think how I
viewed our experience
and our adventure
together
is that our wavelengths
might have been different
at different times--
It was a mutual thing.
And I think
having those different
wavelengths
at different times
may have been
a significant
reason why
we both may have
struggled
to...
really understand where
we may be seeing ourselves
in the far future.
But now I feel like
our wavelengths
are in sync.
I feel like
we've grown.
We have.
And I want to
only go
by what's in here...
Absolutely.
In here, too.
and what's in here.
And trust me,
it's in here.
It's in here
and always will be.
And I say that
from the bottom
of my heart.
[Sigh]
[Laughs and cries]
And it's OK to blush
if you want to,
but, um, understand
if you do.
But, uh, this has
been a remarkable
journey, and somebody
as beautiful as you
deserves the very best
and a life of happiness
together.
And I would very much
be honored...
to have you as my wife.
Will you marry me?
Yes, I will marry you.
There you are.
That's why I wore
my vest--
to conceal that.
I--I was wondering
about that.
But definitely
in the delta region
where it's true love.
That's the wavelength
we're both in.
"Your task is not
to seek for love
"but merely to seek
and find all the barriers
within yourself that
you have built against it."
That quote really
resonates with my life.
All the negative things
that I heard on autism
growing up, it definitely made
me feel worthless or less.
I had consistently
set up barriers
to protect myself.
It's very easy to not feel like
that you can trust people.
I thought that perhaps
Dave was holding back
more than I was.
But what I discovered
through a lot of introspection
is that I was really
holding back, too.
Alex Trebek: This
author's losing entry
in a 1948 literary
contest--
Who was Arthur C. Clarke?
Alex: ...2001? Lars.
Lars: Who is Clarke?
Alex: Arthur C. Clarke.
You are right.
Lars: U.S. Cabinet, 200.
Alex: Which Cabinet
department,
the Transportation
Security Administration...
Lenny: I'm gonna throw
a penny in the water,
make a wish.
When I make my wishes,
I make it clear
that I don't tell anybody, OK?
Hey, by the way, there's
some more ducks over there.
Why don't you go
film them all over there?
Lenny: Got one minute
left, by the way.
When that one minute's
over with, I'm gone.
I got to go back.
I like to get there early.
I don't know.
It's kind of fun doing this.
6 weeks I've been
working here at Flora.
Here. Here's your--here's
the one right here.
A famous person that had
a job like this
when he was a young man
was Kurt Warner.
You don't know who
Kurt Warner is?
He's the--he's
the football player--
he's the quarterback who played
for the Rams a long time ago.
You don't remember how
that Super Bowl happened
where it was the last
second on--
they were one yard
short of winning it?
Well, he was the quarterback
of that winning game.
All right. I got
to go back now. Sorry.
Got to go.
Sorry. Got to go back now.
I'm back now. May I have
a drink of water, please?
OK, ready?
OK.
All right.
[Plays note]
So it starts
here, OK?
Ready?
Mm-hmm.
[Playing "Heart and Soul"]
Don't pound it.
Just gently.
["Heart and Soul" continues]