[electricity crackling]
[birds chirping]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
- [sirens]
- [phone ringing]
[man]
Hello?
[man 2]
Child, is that you?
[man 1]
Yes, Father. I'm listening.
[man 2] I have great news.
Today you will strike.
Get your team ready.
[man 1]
And my target?
[man 2] Senator Bob Jeffers.
Make it messy.
Our benefactors want
to cause an outrage.
[man 1]
I will not fail you.
[man 2]
Go with God.
[man 1]
God is good.
[crowd chanting]
BS! I call BS! BS! I call BS!
[woman on megaphone] Senator
Jeffers, stop the madness.
[chanting continues]
Senator Jeffers,
they're sending in
a Delta team to extract you.
There's been a bomb threat.
Really think you should
leave the interview.
- Would you look at that?
- [exhales]
- I got it. All right.
- Okay. Okay.
You were saying, my dear?
Aren't you nervous your
presidential platform could crumble
if the U.S. Supreme Court votes
against the right to bear arms?
That vote won't take place
till after the election.
And when I am president of this
great United States of America,
I will uphold individuals'
rights to bear arms.
Now, that's a right
that was solemnly confirmed
by the Second Amendment...
ratified in 1791, by the way.
[Kyle]
This is not a real car.
Why'd they give us
this piece of shit?
I feel like a damn clown
in this thing.
You know what I think?
I think Mama fed you too well.
Hey, I'm from Michigan. Us boys
like our cornbread, a'ight?
[heavy metal music on radio]
Shit. Didn't mean to turn
the radio on, dude.
I can't even hit the brake
without hitting the damn radio.
- Oh, you think that's funny?
- [laughs]
That's funny?
That was my request.
I wanted to see you
all cramped up in this thing.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is ridiculous.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're too tall, dude.
- You're just too tall.
- Oh, yeah. You're real funny.
You know, you're the reason why my
nuts are in my throat right now.
Too bad. So apparently, this guy's
sitting in an interview right now.
Okay. And?
Question is, which one of us
gets to go in there
and pull his crusty ass
out of the chair?
Okay, well, you know what?
Seeing that you had your fun already,
I'm thinking I should go in.
Ah, nah. I'm gonna
flip you for it.
No. Not doing that, bro.
I'm not doing that. Nah. Not doing it.
- Too late.
- Hold it up. Hold it up. Let me see.
- Call it.
- Heads.
- Tails!
- Shit.
Come on, man.
- No, no, no.
- [laughs] Yeah! Yeah!
- All right. All right.
- Tails.
You a cheatin' motherfucker,
you know that? You cheatin'.
- [Kyle] Go have this one.
- [Vic] Oh, I will.
[rock music] ♪ I'm about to be
the last one laughin' now... ♪
Enough is enough!
[crowd]
So I acknowledge, support,
and abide
by our God-given right
of self-defense
against any and all enemies,
be they foreign or domestic.
You believe there's a domestic
threat I should worry about?
You don't have to puddle-jump
to some godforsaken country
to find someone
willing to kill you
under the guise of revolution.
Now, if it was up to me,
I would arm every man, woman,
and child in this country
who is a true patriot and
defender of our constitution.
And I would strike first.
Sir, we gotta go. Now.
Oh. All right.
- Now, as I was saying...
- We have a bomb threat.
- Sir, we have to move. Let's go.
- All right.
When this is over, I'd like
to see you again, though.
Mm-hm. No. No.
[laughs]
No, definitely not Benson.
He's a pattycake. [laughs]
No, he's soft on security,
soft on crime.
[sucks teeth] He's a
marshmallow son of a bitch.
Couldn't win an election if
it hit him in the face, okay?
[elevator bell dings]
Alrighty, now, I gotta go.
Bye.
♪ The last one laughing... ♪
[news show theme playing]
[crowd shouting on TV]
[newscaster] ...L.A. We recently
discovered a report of a bomb threat
made against
Senator Bob Jeffers
during a Second Amendment rally
outside his Los Angeles office.
[computer chimes]
He is an outspoken
proponent of the NRA,
and the frontrunning
Republican candidate.
The rally is in response
to a school shooting
that killed CIA director
Mike Phillips's
12-year-old daughter
Stephanie
and nine other students.
Director Phillips has become
a vigilant spokesperson
in support of gun control,
stating he will do whatever
it takes to stop the madness.
[dry-fires pistol]
[Vic sighs]
Package is secure.
Somebody want to tell me
what the hell's going on?
Your name is on a list, sir.
What list?
A list of dead politicians.
Bunch of assholes.
Next time I want the nice car.
[chuckles]
Low profile.
We're rollin' low profile.
[chuckles]
[Kyle]
John, remind me again,
how long are we stuck
on this detail?
Four days, three swing states,
two outdoor speeches.
Yeah, and a partridge
in a pear tree.
I knew better than to answer
your phone call.
Pay's not bad.
How's Shawn?
Eh. He doesn't call much.
He's busy with his... play.
Ah. As in theater.
Yep.
[phone rings]
Hello?
- [beeping]
- Ahh! Damn!
They're tracing your call!
- Tracing who?
- Get off the phone!
[grunts]
[all groaning, shouting]
Let's move!
[gunfire]
[screams]
Just get behind me,
and stay low.
[shouting]
[grunts]
Aaah!
Keep moving!
Aaaah!
Get him out of here!
Unhh!
Aaah! Unhh!
Aaaah!
Oh, shit! Unhh!
All right, man, easy.
Easy there.
Your man for the senator.
Take the shot, Vic.
Let him go!
Vic, take the shot.
Vic, you take that goddamn shot!
No, Vic!
[screaming]
["Thoughts and Prayers"
by Filter playing]
♪ Day starts out the same ♪
♪ Another day to try and live ♪
♪ Killed some kids
at school today ♪
♪ And I got some blood
to give ♪
♪ Young man has
a trigger finger ♪
♪ And sharp plastic shiv ♪
♪ Blocks the exits,
checks his '15 ♪
♪ And stops the will
to forgive ♪
♪ Just another day
in the haven ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! ♪
♪ Just another day
in the haven, baby ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! ♪
♪ Just another day
in the haven ♪
♪ Just another day ♪
♪ Thoughts and prayers ♪
♪ Pulsing shouts ♪
♪ Bleeding out of open wounds ♪
♪ Another day
that no one cares ♪
♪ Thoughts and prayers ♪
♪ Pulsing shouts ♪
♪ Bleeding out of open wounds ♪
♪ Another day
that no one cares ♪
[newscaster on radio] The Supreme
Court has returned to their homes
around the country to celebrate
Christmas with their families
after four long weeks of hearing
the case of Connor vs. Harper,
a case that directly impacts
the right to bear arms,
- [phone ringing]
- and some say could change the Second Amendment forever.
We expect to receive their
opinion shortly after the holiday.
Argh.
Ohh. Damnit, not again.
[Olivia]
You sure you're up for this?
Don't I look up for it?
[sighs] You really need
all that stuff?
I'm not taking Shawn to the
cabin to sit for five days.
Would that be so bad?
What, so we can get in touch with
how well we don't know each other?
You know, I also lost my mom
at a young age.
It's not what he's doing
that's important.
It's who he's doing it with.
You really are my better half.
Better two-thirds.
- At least.
- Hmm.
Do not forget to lock the house,
even during the day.
I won't.
And set the alarm.
Okay. Will you call me?
Uh, yeah,
but from Shawn's phone.
Mine's acting kind of funny.
Right.
Bye.
[chatter]
So how many Russians will
you find in South Africa?
If you're asking me
if you are like
any Russian I've met,
you are one of a kind.
You know how many South Africans
there are in Russia?
How many?
- Three.
- I believe it.
It's too cold.
Fencers ready. Allez.
[foils clashing]
[both grunting]
- [Tessa] Halt.
- Come on.
[laughs]
[Tessa]
Fencers ready.
[both]
Yeah.
Allez.
[both grunting]
[laughs]
[groans]
- Gotcha.
- [sighs] Come on.
Yup. Okay.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Mm-hm.
Fencers ready.
Oh, yeah.
Allez!
[both grunting]
[buzzer sounds]
[sighs]
Thanks.
- Lucky flick.
- [mutters]
[instructor] Erin takes
the last round of the semester!
- Good job, girl.
- Thank you. Thank you!
That's it for class.
Have a good break, guys.
What are you smiling about?
You lost.
Did I, though?
- All right, that'll be $85.
- Pay up.
You cheated.
No, I hustled you.
There's a difference.
Pay the woman.
Me?
Yes. I'll get you back.
Come on.
[Neal] All right, people!
All right, let's go! All right.
Okay, dorm is closed
for the holiday season
due to construction,
so everybody out.
Okay? I'm not saying
you gotta go home,
but you can't stay here.
Hey.
Um, when's your dad
picking you up?
Oh, Olivia said
he broke his phone,
so I guess when he gets here.
- [scoffs]
- How about you?
Oh, he's way too busy with his
opinion on the Second Amendment,
so he's sending a driver.
Right.
That's a really big deal, right?
Yeah.
Like world-changing.
Do you pay attention
to anything?
I, uh, I haven't talked
to him in a couple weeks.
Hey! You three all packed up?
All packed and ready to go.
Yeah. I mean,
I'm like 80 percent there,
but my car doesn't get here
till 6:00.
5:00, Erin. 5:00 PM
is the last person out.
All right, well,
I don't get to choose
when the Secret Service
comes to pick me up.
Okay, you get a minor exception,
all right, but you,
- you're out, all right?
- Of course.
Thanks. You're the best.
Yeah, don't forget
to sign out with Charlie.
- [Erin] Uh-huh.
- Hey, Erin.
Maybe I could call you
over the break?
Sure, I guess.
Cool.
[chuckles] She's way
out of your league, bro.
I mean, [imitates jet].
Hey! 5:00 PM!
Out, all right?
Not coming in. When you left,
you can't come back in.
That's it.
[sighs]
[rock music on radio]
[phone ringing]
Hey, hon.
[Olivia]
You're not there yet, are you?
No, this traffic is just
a nightmare...
[honks horn]
Watch it, dickhead!
Sorry, sweetie.
Well, they closed
the dorm at 5:00.
I told Shawn
you're running late.
Yeah, thank you. I'll call you
as soon as I get there.
Okay. Bye.
[turns up radio]
Nice car.
I'm here to pick up Erin Walton.
I'm gonna need
to scan your license.
- Do we need to do this every time?
- Nope.
But you're not Ms. Walton's regular
driver, and we have protocol.
- I'm impressed.
- I never forget a face.
[horn honks]
[silenced gunshot]
[alarm sounds]
[knock at door]
Make like Michael Jackson
and beat it.
So I need a huge favor.
No.
Thing is, I have to catch
a flight to Calgary.
Charlie.
You don't have
to keep pretending
your Canadian girlfriend
is real.
Bro, do you want me to show you
the Instagram messages?
No. [chuckles]
What do you need?
So, I'm not supposed to leave
until everybody's signed out.
And everybody's gone
except for you... and Erin.
I see what you're doing,
and no, she's on ice, dude.
If I do one more thing,
I'll come across desperate.
"She's on ice"?
Bro, come on. You owe me.
- [sighs]
- 85 bucks.
Okay. Fine.
- Sweet. Thanks, man.
- Yeah.
Just leave this with Neal
before you go.
Sure. [sighs]
And don't cry when Erin
lets you down, man.
Like, she's political royalty.
Put the cane down.
Who the hell are you?
The driver.
[gasping]
[muffled pop music]
[clears throat]
[both] Hey.
How's it going?
Um, I am here to check you out.
I meant check you out
of your room.
Right. Yeah. Um,
I need to finish packing and stuff, so...
Well, you need to sign this.
Yeah, we're actually the two last
people in the building, I guess, so...
Should I be worried?
Why?
No reason.
- [clears throat]
- Okay.
Mission accomplished, cowboy.
Hm? Oh.
- Right, the, uh...
- All of it.
- The cowboy hat, right.
- Yeah.
Uh, I'm actually
on the way to my cabin.
Uh, it's, like,
in the woods.
We have dirt bikes and horses and
a bunch of cool stuff like that.
Oh, you have horses?
Yeah. Yeah, two of them.
I've never been
horseback riding.
What?
Come on, never?
No, never.
Well, I mean...
I don't know if you'd...
you'd want to, but I...
I could, uh...
I could take you?
Mayb... cool.
- Sure. Yeah, maybe. Maybe.
- Maybe. Um..
Yeah, here's this.
I have to finish...
- I need to finish packing, so...
- [clears throat] Right.
I'm just gonna go back
and do it.
Uh, Erin, actually, I have
to make sure you leave safely
before I can go.
Okay, um...
I just... I'm sure you have
something better to do
than just sit here
and wait for me.
No. I don't.
Okay, well, um...
maybe could you help me pack?
[clears throat]
Yeah.
Sure. Yeah. Let's do it.
- Great.
- Yee-haw.
[chuckles]
Giddyup, partner.
Nice getup.
Janitorial technician.
Make sure our asset's
on her way out.
Yes, sir.
[guard]
Campus is closed.
I'm here to pick up my son.
- Where?
- MacArthur Hall.
Hm. Why don't you call your son,
have him meet you over there?
Um...
- My phone is...
- Ah.
Eh, I'll tell you what,
make it quick, will you?
Yes, sir.
And you and your son, you have
a merry Christmas, sir.
You do the same.
One coming your way.
Is he a problem?
Nah, he's just here to pick up
his son. Should be quick.
Okay, everyone stay loose
till this guy's gone.
You were aware this dorm
has a perfectly good elevator?
I don't do elevators.
Childhood trauma?
Claustrophobic.
Oh, so repressed memory, then.
[scoffs] What are you,
a psych major?
No. Theater.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
We have the asset.
Wow. Nice car.
- Secret Service.
- Okay, okay. Pretty cool.
Here, let me get that for you.
I got this.
Here you go, sir.
[clears throat]
- Sorry.
- [chuckles]
Um, well, thanks for
everything, and merry Christmas.
- Yeah. Yeah, merry Christmas...
- [Vic] Shawny!
- [Shawn] Hey!
- How you doing, bud?
Um, you should call me.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I will.
- [Vic] Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know.
- How you been?
What's up? [grunts] [laughs]
Hey, you're good.
You know, I'll take a few hours
late over not at all any day.
Hmm. That hurt.
Sorry.
Is that your girl?
Uh, no, it's Erin Walton.
Walton.
Yeah, Justice Walton's
daughter?
Like Supreme Court
Justice Walton?
Yeah, Dad.
[Erin] Where's Steve?
- Sick.
- Oh.
Shit. Hold on.
I'll be right back.
- Hey, where you going?
- I'll be right back!
- Wait, where you going?
- Oh, I-I forgot my laptop.
The new guy's an ass, so...
I'll be quick, I promise.
All right.
Okay, so what's up?
I, uh, I promised Charlie that
I'd make sure everyone was out,
so I gotta... I gotta stay.
Okay.
The asset is on the move.
Heading to her room.
Ready to do some ridin'?
Uh, it's a little chilly,
nah?
Fishing'll be good.
Eh.
Well, I know you want to shoot.
- You love to shoot.
- I mean, I would, I just...
got tryouts for the play
in a couple weeks, so...
gotta start going over
the lines, get the part.
What's the play?
Lost in Yonkers.
Ah, yeah, right, that's...
It's Neil Simon.
Neil Simon, uh,
is the guy who...
Write. Writes.
[chuckles]
How's your bike holding up?
Oh, good. Yeah, she's good.
Needs a carb tune-up,
but, uh...
Oh! Thanks for reminding me.
Gotta cover her up.
So you're sure you're still
all in on this theater thing.
[chuckles]
Uh, yeah, Dad.
If you'd actually been around
last couple years,
you'd know I was good at it.
I don't get to decide
when I come and go, Shawn.
That's part of the deal.
Yeah, Dad.
I know the deal.
Don't get to choose.
Don't need it.
All right? I'm fine.
Seriously.
[sighs]
Your friend say
her driver's new?
[grunts]
Yeah. So?
Who's left inside?
It's just the two of us.
We're the last ones in.
Here. Take the keys,
get in the Jeep,
lock the doors,
and do not move.
Is something wrong?
I don't know. Just chill.
I'll be right back.
Chill.
"Just chill." Chill.
Who taught him that word?
Papa Bear's headed inside.
Keep your eyes on him.
[phone ringing]
Yo, Charlie.
What up?
[chuckles]
Yeah, I told you.
Can't just come on that strong.
Gotta let her cool off
a little bit. [chuckles]
[knock at door]
God, you scared me.
Sorry. Did you say
your driver was new?
Yeah. Why?
Maybe we should call your dad
and make sure.
Got your phone?
Yeah.
[sighs] Shawn said you're
a Green Beret? Delta Force?
Yeah, I am.
Make the call.
- [sighs]
- [ringing]
- [Walton] Hello?
- Daddy?
Erin. I thought you'd be here
by now. Where are you?
[Erin] Well,
I had a lot to pack.
She's called her father.
[Driver, over headset]
Kill the call now.
[Walton] We have dinner
reservations at 9:00.
When will you be home?
Before then, I guess.
Hey. Can you ask
about the driver?
Sure. Um, Dad, uh,
did you send a new driver?
[Walton] A new what?
Driver.
No.
[dial tone]
[sighs] The call dropped.
I know. I know.
That whole class was B.S.
[dial tone]
Hello? Charlie.
Well, what did he say?
He said no.
[Driver] Kill the lights.
[beeping]
- Get down.
- What?
Get down now.
Oh. Okay.
What is going on?
Okay. Follow close
and avoid the windows.
- What about my bag?
- Leave it.
That's strange. Erin just
called asking about her driver.
And?
The line went dead.
Promise me you're not going to
ruin another holiday season.
Me?
The both of you need to leave
your politics at the office.
I'm calling again.
Probably met a boy with dozens
of tattoos and fell in love.
I am not playing referee
this holiday.
Voicemail.
Her battery is dead.
Have you finished
your opinion?
I'm undecided.
This is not a time
for neutrality.
You pick a side,
and you stand by it.
Dad?
[Southern accent]
Ma'am.
Yoo-hoo!
[Russian accent]
The asset is gone.
Move in now. Contingency Delta.
Full extract.
There's
a structural interference.
Wait. They're on level four.
[Driver]
Acquire the package.
Create rows.
Maintain a perimeter.
No one in or out.
What about Papa Bear
and Baby Bear?
Expendable.
[Paula] Now we have
ourselves a little party.
How excitin'.
[Driver] Stay on target.
We have a job to do.
All right, come on.
Stay low.
Come on.
Okay. I'm gonna need you
to stay right with me,
like step for step.
We're gonna move quickly
and quietly, okay?
Okay.
[cell phone rings]
Dad?
[Driver] Is everything all right, Ms.
Walton?
Fine.
Do you need help
finding your laptop?
Nope. I'm good.
We're running a little
behind schedule.
Actually, I'm not on
any particular schedule.
Beg your pardon?
Not to be a bitch,
but I don't remember
telling you that I needed
to be anywhere
at any certain time.
I see subterfuge
is pointless.
Put the asshole on the phone.
Now.
Yeah?
You've become
quite an obstacle, mister.
But we're working on that.
But I can assure you,
you're surrounded
by a team of highly
trained operatives.
All signals... wi-fi, radio, CB...
have been jammed.
I'm giving you five minutes
to exit the building.
It may not seem like
an act of kindness,
but I promise you,
it most certainly is.
You should have had your
package and been out in two.
Fuckin' amateur.
[dial tone]
What'd he say?
We gotta get you
out of here.
Okay.
[whistling]
Excuse me, sir.
Uh, have you seen, like,
a middle-aged guy
around here, bad clothes,
doesn't smile much?
Ring a bell?
[Southern accent]
Sorry, bubba.
But I can help you look
if you like.
Oh, no, that's okay. I don't want to
take you away from your work or anything.
- Don't worry about it.
- Work's not going anywhere.
Cool.
[sighs]
Sorry about this.
You probably must be
antsy to get out of here.
You know, bubba,
I mean, I can't complain.
Guess if I would have
gone to college like you,
maybe I'd be a big shot,
not a toilet scrubber.
Know what I'm sayin',
bubba?
Yeah. I guess.
[both grunting]
[bell dings]
[sharp grunt]
[assertive grunt]
[grunts]
[laughter]
[knife clatters]
[grunting]
[panting]
Goddamn it, Shawn,
I told you to wait in the car!
You know, one of these days,
you're gonna realize
when I tell you to do something,
I'm not sayin' it
just to hear myself ta...
What?
[gasps]
You just killed that guy?
He was gonna kill you.
Look, he's not dead.
[man groans]
Ohh.
Let's go.
Okay.
[Erin muttering]
All right, go on, go.
[1950s-era ballad playing]
♪ We wish you
Merry Christmas ♪
A merry Christmas ♪
♪ We wish you
♪ And a happy... ♪
Justice Walton.
Pardon me, sir.
Director Phillips is here.
He says it's very urgent
to speak with you.
Show him in.
Very good.
♪ ...a merry Christmas ♪
Do you think this has anything
to do with the decision?
Probably.
Ohh. That poor man.
- Thank you. Eva.
- Hi, Mike.
Ken. Terribly sorry
to intrude like this.
Aw, merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas.
- Thank you.
A man carrying a bottle of
Macallan's is never an intrusion.
Grab a cue.
Guests always break.
Well, it's been quite a while.
I'm not sure if I remember
how this goes, but...
I'll give it
the old college try.
Lucky shot.
You're not the first shark
at my table.
- [soft chuckle]
- Well, get to it.
I'm guessing you didn't fly in from
Washington just to keep me company.
Your opinion.
[clears throat]
Is it done?
I have a draft.
You want to see it?
♪ Good tidings we bring... ♪
Yes, I-I would.
Maybe we should
play by the rules.
♪ We wish you a merry... ♪
Hi. Cheers.
Thank you.
Thank you, darling.
To better,
more responsible times.
- I'll drink to that.
- [glasses clink]
[satisfied sigh]
Listen, Ken,
have you ever read
Those Who Walk Away
from Omelas?
It's a short story
by Ursula Le Guin.
Can't say that I have.
There's this town, Omelas,
where everybody's happy.
Not happy.
Ecstatic.
There's no soldiers,
no kings,
no inequality.
It's a Utopia.
And... well,
there's no monsters
who walk into preschools
with assault rifles.
But there's a catch.
In order for this...
Utopia to exist,
an atrocity
has to be committed.
This is part of the deal.
Some of the townspeople
go along with it,
and some don't.
And what is it
they have to do?
They have to hurt a child.
I have your daughter, Ken.
I have Erin.
If you don't do
what I tell you to do...
something terrible
will happen to her,
and it will be your fault.
It's your shot.
Go, go, go.
Get down, get down.
All right. I've got
to find a landline.
There's people I can call
in a situation like this.
There's a payphone
in the gym.
You sure? I've never seen
a payphone in there before.
Yes! Freshman year,
we had a petition to get...
Guys, guys!
That's where I'm headed.
Give me your cell phones.
- Why?
- 'Cause they're tracking them.
How do you know?
Sorry.
- All right...
- Dad!
- We're going with you.
- No, no.
These people
are highly trained.
Yeah, well, so am I.
Well, then take this.
Here.
You guys stay out of sight,
listen for sound,
but do not engage.
They need Erin alive, but you and
I, they'll shoot on sight.
- Okay, we won't go anywhere.
- Yeah, we'll stay hidden.
- Okay.
- Dad.
You're gonna need this.
It's a payphone.
Yeah.
Here. I'll be
back for mine.
[deep sigh]
Cellphone GPS says
they're on the elevator
heading to the ground floor.
[Rodriguez]
I'm on it.
[tones dinging]
[bell dings]
This kid thinks he's smart.
[sharp groan]
Smarter than you.
Let's take a ride.
On your knees!
[pained grunt]
Put the cuffs on,
put your hands over your head.
Now!
[grunts]
Paula,
how we lookin' up top?
Dead still, baby.
They're zipped up tight.
Babcock,
what's your 20?
I'm playing hide-and-seek.
[elevator bell dings]
[Driver]
Rodriguez, report.
[Jade] Driver,
you gotta see this!
[knocks on door]
[tapping keyboard]
All ears, listen up.
His name is Major Vic Davis.
Green Beret at 21,
Delta Force
a few years later.
He's seen action
all over the world...
Bosnia, Somalia, Kosovo.
If there was a major conflict
in the last 15 years,
this guy was there.
He's the current
Delta One team leader.
In Somalia, his confirmed
kill count was over 50.
Deadly, and he will not
hesitate to kill you.
Did you know all that?
Nope.
[Russian accent]
I don't care who you are.
You're dead.
[grunts]
They seem really
nervous about it.
Yeah.
Yeah, they should be.
Oh, my gosh. Shawn,
you're bleeding a lot.
- It's not that bad.
- No, no, we need to get this wrapped up.
- I-I'll be okay.
- No, it's bad.
It's not... it's not
that bad. I'll be okay.
No. Come on.
Let's find something.
We'll wrap you up.
Hey, this is Vic.
I've got a domestic terror
situation,
Macarthur Hall,
Johnson College.
They're everywhere.
[Driver] Major Davis,
I'm hardly paramilitary.
Try harder.
- CIA? Ground Branch?
- Good guess.
Now do you understand what
you've gotten yourself into?
I give you this
one-last-time offer
to leave
and never look back.
Take it.
No.
[exertion grunt]
[Rodriguez laughs]
This is my way, you bitch.
[roars]
[grunting]
Fuck! Stop!
[panting]
[Rodriguez gurgles]
[clears throat]
- [gasps]
- Does that hurt?
[pained sigh]
But... go ahead.
We used to go
to the cabin all the time.
You know, it was
kind of like our thing.
Mixed martial arts,
hand-to-hand,
sharpshooting, dirt-biking.
It's kind of like
what my dad's best at.
That's cool.
And I really loved it, too.
Not what we were doing,
just...
just that we did it together.
So, uh, are your parents
together, then,
or... where's your mom at?
[pained grunt]
Sorry.
Some asshole from Iraq...
he wanted revenge
for something my dad did.
And, um...
they found our house.
But I was at school.
And, um...
...he killed her.
God damn.
[sniffles]
So, my dad
stopped coming home so much,
and, uh, I started to live with
a lot of military families.
And then I went to college.
We haven't spent much
time together since she...
Shawn, I'm so sorry.
Yeah.
[sniffs]
Thank you.
For what?
You waited for me.
[Russian accent]
I find nothing.
No asset. Nothing.
Keep sweeping, all floors.
[faint sound]
[Russian accent]
Be realistic, Erin.
If you come out now,
we will let your friends go.
Keep resisting...
and we will
have to kill them.
You are not that selfish.
Are you?
[chuckles]
Stay the fuck away from me.
Hello, sweetheart.
[hammer cocks]
[exasperated groan]
[both grunting]
[Shawn] The gun!
Hey!
[groans]
This is why...
you don't interfere...
in other people's...
Aaaahhhh!
Ohh!
Stupid suka!
Hey!
Let her go...
or I'll kill you.
[exasperated groan]
Fucking do it!
[hammer cocks]
Think real hard, little boy.
[Erin gasps]
Once you cross that line...
[Southern accent]
...there ain't no goin' back.
Come on.
- Hold this. You okay?
- Yeah.
Let's go, come on.
They'll declare my judgment was under
duress, and they'll toss it out,
doing you a damn bit of good.
My daughter didn't have a choice
when that monster shot her.
But you have a choice
tonight, Ken.
I just hope you make
the right one.
You deviate from my
instructions just once,
and Erin dies.
You got it?
Don't fuck with me, Ken.
I didn't get to be
Director of the CIA
without making sacrifices.
Even men like you
can disappear.
This'll be our
dirty little secret.
[Erin]
There, there, there, there.
[Shawn]
Shit. Damn it! Come on!
It's open!
Go in! Go, Erin!
[panting]
[cocks weapon]
[both panting]
- Shawn?
- Yeah.
I'm really scared.
[soft sobs]
[whirring sounds]
[sighs]
[beeping]
[servo motor whirrs]
Papa Bear is on
the north side of the dorm.
[Paula] Visual acquired.
Copy that.
[Driver]
Paula, engage and eliminate.
[Paula] I don't have a shot.
There's a fuckin' tree!
[Driver]
Krieg, Rose, move it!
Do you have a shot?
[Paula]
Negative.
Clear target.
Permission to engage.
[Driver]
Granted.
[gunshot]
[Paula]
Tango down.
That's bullshit, okay?
She's lying.
Okay, she has to be lying.
Mnh-mnh.
Krieg, confirm he's dead.
[Krieg]
Yes, sir.
[both sigh]
I can't let them hurt you.
We're gonna get
out of here, okay?
I promise you.
No, that's not a promise
that you can make.
I'm so sorry.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I have to go.
I'm sorry, just stay here.
Just stay here
until we're gone, okay?
Erin, no!
Erin, no, wait!
[combative shout]
[both shouting]
Believe it or not,
we're the good guys!
[grunts]
[blade clatters]
[sharp gasp]
[sharp groan]
Hey! I'm what
you want, right?
Come and get me!
I'm giving myself up!
Hey, pretty young thing.
Hey.
We need you alive...
but not necessarily
in one piece!
[Erin groans]
You are gonna spend
the rest of your life
wishing you hadn't
fucked with us!
Hey! Step away.
Kid, you better
use that thing
before I get up
and kick your ass.
You guys okay?
- You okay?
- Dad!
Vic! Here!
You all right?
We heard you were dead!
No, they just
gave me a workout.
All right.
Let's get out of here.
- Yeah.
- [door shuts]
Hold it.
Stop! Hands up!
Please don't shoot!
Please! Okay?
- Neal?
- Erin?
Where have you been?
We're under attack.
Under attack?
What are you...? Bullshit!
Did you not hear
the gunfire?
What gunfire, where?
What do you mean?
- Snipers on the roof...
- You could have died!
Guys, focus!
- You, what...
- Neal.
Neal, is there a way
out of here, a hidden exit?
Yeah, there's a, uh,
an old service tunnel
between here
and the main building.
- How do we get there?
- Actually, it's, uh...
there's an old elevator
right, right this way.
All right, let's go.
Come on.
Right through here.
Come on, go, go,
go, go, go.
- [Erin] Ooh!
- [Neal] Hang on!
Go! Come on, Neal!
You guys get in that elevator
and get the hell out of here!
Whoa!
Go, go, go, go on!
Open the door!
[indistinct nervous shout]
Come on, Neal,
open the door!
Okay!
Go! Go, go, go!
Come on, come on, come on!
[Erin] Shawn.
Get in the elevator,
come on!
- Shawn!
- I can't leave my dad!
- Come on, Shawn! Shawn!
- Just go with Neal!
Goddamn it, Shawn,
I told you to go!
No man left behind, right?
I lost you once tonight.
It's not happening again.
[inaudible]
[bell dings]
I'm sorry, Erin,
this isn't my fault.
What are you talking about?
No.
No, you son of a bitch!
No, no, no, no!
I'm really tired
of chasing you around.
[Erin groans]
Ohh! Damnit!
You said payment
upon delivery.
So I'll take my cash
and I'll leave.
You know, three people
can keep a secret...
Aaah!
...if two of them are dead.
Aaahhh!
- Please don't.
- Neal!
[Neal groans]
No, Neal! [sobbing]
Take care of the rest.
What are you...
what are you...
What are you doing?
What is she doing?
Get off of me!
Shawn! Shawn!
Look out, please!
Run! Shawn!
[elevator bell dings]
[beeping]
Shit! Come on!
[beeping faster]
No! No, please, stop!
No! No!
[message alert whooshes]
Dad!
Dad! Please!
Ow! [grunts] Ow.
[flames whooshing]
[grunts]
[grunting, groaning]
Shawn. Shawn!
Shawn!
[Shawn coughing]
Shawn. Are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- Dad. [coughing]
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Let me get you up.
Come here.
[both grunting]
Thank God you're okay.
- We gotta get out of here.
- Yeah.
- You all right? Can you walk?
- [coughing] Yeah.
- All right.
- Let's go.
[Shawn panting]
All right, come on.
Ya know, I'm thinkin'
about retirin'.
Really.
So, what then?
I don't know.
Finish the cabin. Fish.
Not get shot at.
Honestly, I was thinkin' we
could make up for lost time.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd like that.
- [distant gunshot]
- [Erin screams]
Shawn! There's a sniper!
Aaaaah!
Help! Shawn!
Come on! Shawn!
Ohh!
[Erin] Shawn! Help!
- [gunfire]
- Come on! Come on!
[gunfire continues]
[Driver]
It's time to go. Move it!
[Paula]
What about the kid?
[Sproule]
Kill him!
Sorry, mate.
Nothing personal.
- Uhh!
- [Vic roars]
[both grunting]
[both cry out]
[gunfire]
Unhh! Aaah!
[Erin] Help!
Shawn!
[tires screech]
[engine starts]
[revs engine]
[tires screeching]
Shawn!
- Aaah! Uhh!
- Aaaah!
[Sproule]
I don't believe!
He is on roof!
[grunts]
[tires screech]
Aaaah!
Now! Shoot him!
- There! Shoot him!
- [firing]
Huh? What is going on?
Shoot!
Watch where you're driving!
Idiot.
[growls]
Uhh! Ohh!
[Babcock]
Run him down!
[Sproule]
I am running down!
[growling]
[grunting]
[panting]
[grunting] No!
Unhh!
Ohh!
[tires screeching]
[all grunting]
Yahhh!
Unhh! Unhh!
[thud]
- [bone cracks]
- Aaah!
Ohh! Please stop!
- [Sproule] Arrghhh!
- [Babcock] Get him!
Unhh! Unhh! Unhh!
I ate a man in gulag!
Uhh!
Makes it seem like kindness
compared to what
I do to you!
[choking]
Aaaah!
Dad!
[coughs, groans]
[coughing]
[panting, groaning]
Ahh. Aaaah!
[groaning]
Shawn! Shawn!
[flames crackling]
[chambering rounds]
[cocks pistol]
[TV reporter] The Supreme
Court has indicated
that a decision
has been made,
and the justices are
finishing their opinions.
They will deliver their judgement
tomorrow at 8 a.m., Eastern time.
Who the hell is he?
I lost...
a lot of good people
tonight.
Uh... Implicating me
with an unknown third party
was not part of the plan.
His father is
a Delta team leader.
Major Vic Davis?
And where is he now?
Maybe dead. Maybe not.
Insurance policy.
What about your mess
at the school?
Cleaning crew.
And you're sure that Walton...
did what I asked?
Doesn't matter.
It matters to me.
[glass thuds]
[pours liquid]
[plaintive ballad playing]
[TV reporter] ...unconfirmed
source says that Justice Walton
has submitted his judgement
against the Second Amendment.
There are times
when one must sacrifice a few
in order to save the many.
We all have callings.
I need you to drown the girl
and put her body in the boat.
Get rid of the boy.
Come on, baby doll.
Let's have some fun!
- No, hold on... Stop!
- [Erin] Shawn!
Sit.
Put your hands up.
- He's clean.
- All right, let's go.
Hey, wait!
Looks like your insurance
policy's about to pay off.
I'll handle this.
Aaaah!
Uhhh! Aaaah!
Uhhh!
[intense moaning]
- [gunshot]
- Aaaah!
Uhh! Aaah! Ohh!
Uhh!
Ohhh!
Aaaaah!
[beeping]
[sets down glass]
It's too bad we didn't meet
under different circumstances.
Could've been friends.
Unhh!
[both grunting]
Aaaaah! Unhh!
[grunting, roaring]
- [steam hissing]
- [alarm blaring]
[both grunting]
- [switch clanks]
[alarm stops]
[Driver] Might I
suggest you let me pass?
We're fighting
for the same thing.
Duty, Vic.
To country.
To your family.
It's what we fight for,
and I have a duty
to follow my orders.
It's simple.
You and me are gonna go
on a little boat ride, love.
Ohh! Ohh. Ahh.
[coughing, gasping]
[anchor chain clanking]
Unhh!
En garde, bitch.
[chuckling]
Stay back.
You're not the first one
to wave a sword at me, love.
I'm warning you.
I know how
to use this thing.
Yahh!
Brat!
[sputtering]
Ahh!
[laughs] Oh!
[panting]
[roars]
[both grunting]
This. Is. Not. Fair!
Aaaah! Aaah!
[both grunting]
[roars]
Aaah!
[thud]
[knife clatters]
[Driver]
Hyahh! Hyahh!
[hissing]
[alarm blaring]
Aaah! Ohh.
You know,
I was supposed to drown you.
[sighs]
That's what I have to do.
[gunshot]
Hey. Hey.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I just...
I'm really happy
we're alive.
Yeah, me too.
- Are you okay?
- I think so.
I'm okay now.
[Walton] Erin!
Dad.
Erin.
Oh, Dad. Oh.
[both grunting]
Unhh!
Aaaah!
Ahhhh! Aah!
- [crackling]
- [alarm blaring]
Aaaah!
[stammers] I gotta...
I gotta go help my dad.
That's far enough, Judge.
Let it go, Phillips.
It's over.
You're not the one
calling the shots here.
[Vic]
Director Phillips!
You have three seconds
to put the gun down.
What's your play?
Huh? You gonna execute
the Director of the CIA
of the United States of America?
[chuckles]
Yes.
Two...
one.
You think this ends here?
I'm just the tip of the spear.
[laughing]
[Erin sighs]
- I'm so glad you're okay.
- Me too.
Ow! My arm!
[door closes]
[Phillips]
Genevieve?
Are you here?
[ice cubes clatter]
You survived.
That's good.
Drink?
History won't be
kind to you, Mike.
And that's... unfortunate.
Our benefactor is worried
that Walton will talk?
Because I can assure you,
he won't.
And he won't change
his judgement, either.
He knows I'm watching.
And he's afraid.
All of this will be...
our secret.
Mike....
three people
can keep a secret...
[shell clatters]
[thud]
...if two of them are dead.
[monitor beeping]
Hey. [groans]
What time is it?
Past six.
What's up?
Are you okay?
Did I ever tell you
how I got this watch?
I always figured you just
took it off some dead
terrorist or something.
[chuckles]
[laughs softly]
I-I'm just kidding.
How'd you get it?
President Clinton
awarded my entire unit
the Medal of Honor in '97.
- What?
- Yep.
Holy shit.
You got the Medal of Honor?
How did I not know
about this?
It's classified.
So the president
goes down the line,
by the time he gets to me,
they're a medal short.
But the president,
without missing a beat,
he takes off his Rolex...
this Rolex...
and he hands it to me.
He says, "I can't have a man
showin' up for the Medal of Honor
"and leavin' my office
empty-handed.
"I want you to wear this watch
and remember
the lives you saved."
Son...
once you take a life,
you never sleep
quite the same way again.
You're not really
the same guy anymore.
So I'm gonna tell you
what President Clinton told me.
When you wear this,
I want you to think
about the lives you saved...
not the ones you took.
[sighs]
All that time you were gone...
I want you to know there
wasn't a day that went by
where I wasn't proud
to be your son.
[sniffles]
I always meant
to tell you that.
I'm proud of you, too.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Okay.
All right, that's enough
of the mushy stuff.
[laughs]
Who wants a drink?
Um, I think so.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna leave
you two kids alone.
[Erin, Shawn laugh]
Hi. So...
Oh, uh, Dad.
Yeah?
Merry Christmas.
Thanks, son.
Merry Christmas,
young lady.
Merry Christmas.
Who's the lucky guy?
Stop! I see the meds
are kickin' in.
- Oh, my goodness, it's a twist-off.
- I know, what can I say?
Mr. Vic Davis.
You ready to pay your dues?
Oh, Vic!
[whimpering]
[Olivia crying]
[heavy metal music playing]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ You take my money ♪
♪ You take your drink ♪
♪ You think it's funny ♪
♪ And I hate your face ♪
♪ Yeah, you got your Jesus ♪
♪ And I got my space ♪
♪ You got your reasons ♪
♪ And I got my case ♪
♪ Just gotta
sit yourself down ♪
♪ To contemplate ♪
♪ You get yourself
a nice cold beer ♪
♪ And drink yourself away ♪
♪ You're celebrating nothing ♪
♪ You feel A-okay ♪
♪ To feel ♪
♪ A-okaaaay! ♪
♪ You think you're precious ♪
♪ I think you're shit ♪
♪ I'd kill your father ♪
♪ To destroy his seed ♪
♪ Oh, nothing will ever ♪
♪ Destroy your greed ♪
♪ Ohhh! ♪
♪ Just gotta
sit yourself down ♪
♪ To contemplate ♪
♪ Get yourself
a nice cold beer ♪
♪ And drink yourself away ♪
♪ You're celebrating nothing ♪
♪ And you feel A-okay ♪
♪ And you feel ♪
♪ A-okaaaaay! ♪
♪ Now when you
break yourself down ♪
♪ Go to this place ♪
♪ You give yourself no reason ♪
♪ To get off your case ♪
♪ And when you
break it down again ♪
♪ See through this shit ♪
♪ You give yourself no reason ♪
♪ To live through this! ♪
[guitar solo]
♪ Mama, give me my medicine ♪
♪ The one that
makes me feel taller ♪
♪ Mama, give me my medicine ♪