(MultiCom Jingle)
(dramatic music)
(wings flapping)
- Long ago, before the time of man
there lived a fairy
king whose name was Ar.
Now Ar lived in a land
called the Angel Isle
and he had ruled for 1,000 years
before the first man
set foot in his realm.
Now to the fairy king and his people
men seemed large and loud,
quick tempered and destructive,
beings who had no time for
the gentle ways of fairy folk,
and before they realized what they did
the men drove Ar and his people
from the fields and woods
right up to the edge
of the deep green sea.
Now Ar was trapped and his
people could go no further
so in desperation the
fairy king sent a message
to the Emerald Isle asking for help
from Timish the leprechaun king,
but Timish was powerless to help
as Ar and the fairy folk were
barred from the Emerald Isle,
but still he could not turn
his back on his cousin Ar
and therefor he asked the
giant Fin McCool for help.
- A giant?
- Yes Evie a giant.
- Evie shh.
- Shh yourself.
- Well Fin McCool was usually a bad giant,
but in this case he was pleased
to help the people of Ar
in return for the hand in marriage
of Ar's daughter Tumbeleen.
Tumbeleen was very sad at the
thought of marriage to a giant
but after her father persuaded
her she finally agreed,
so Timish struck the deal with Fin McCool
and as the fairy folk
rejoiced the lumbering giant
ripped up a huge piece of the Emerald Isle
and throwing back his mighty
arm he set the piece of land
sailing through the air across the sea.
- Cool.
- Well when the noise had
settled and the water grew calm
the giant's voice boomed across the sea
telling Ar and his people that
the new land he had created
was to be called the Isle of Man
in honor of the king of the sea,
but that Ar and his
people could live there
for as long as Tumbeleen was his wife.
- Poor Tumbeleen.
- Ah wait and see.
So Ar took his people to the new land
and he made ready for a huge celebration
to which he invited the giant.
Tumbeleen was dressed in fairest silks
with dainty flowers for a crown
ready to be the giant's bride
and waited at the cliff's
with Ar and all his people
as Fin McCool waded from the Emerald Isle
to the new land he had made.
Well the giant's voice booms out,
"Oh fairy king I have done what you asked,
"now I come for my bride,"
and to the amazement of all those around
Ar laughed and laughed.
"Oh foolish giant how can that be?
"You are too large to
live on this little land
"and Tumbeleen is forever
barred from the Emerald Isle,
"where would you live?"
- Hooray Tumbeleen is
safe, she's safe Grandma.
- Well, only partly,
but one day, one can only hope.
- Grandma?
- What?
Oh sorry.
Right, where was I?
Yes here we are.
Now as you can imagine the
giant was not too pleased,
in fact he was downright
furious at being tricked
and in his rage he scooped
up all of Ar's people
in his giant hand and with
the other he tore a large hole
and there he placed Ar and all his people
covering them with dirt, he
buried them deep underground
and his voice boomed out across the sea,
"King Ar, oh treacherous fool,
"the land that I gave you so
that you might live in peace
"shall now be a prison forever more."
(joyful music)
- Look the Fairy Bridge.
- [Nancy] It's so beautiful.
- Remember in the story
when you cross the bridge
you have to say hi to the fairies
or they give you bad luck.
(wings flapping)
(magical swooshing)
- [Children] Hi fairies.
- Evie see if you can see one.
(wings flapping)
- Daddy I saw one.
- Great.
(joyful music)
(magical swooshing)
(wings flapping)
(joyful music)
- Wow look at this place.
- Yeah, where is Hansel and Gretel huh?
(laughing)
- [Kyle] This is Grandma's?
(talking drown out by music)
- Wow this is ares?
- Yeah I guess, I guess it is.
- Cool.
- Hey, what do you say we check it out?
- [Children] Yeah.
(joyful music)
- Kyle, Kyle back up here.
Well nobody's lived here for 40 years,
but everything, the grounds are very neat,
electricity works.
- Well I guess there's a caretaker.
- I wonder why your mother
never, never came back here?
Hello?
- Come on Evie.
- 'Kay, wait for me.
- Hey hey hey careful,
don't break anything.
(joyful music)
(magical swooshing)
(wings flapping)
(joyful music)
- [Rob] Where is everybody?
- It's weird.
- Hey, look at all this old stuff.
Oh, and pots and pans.
(laughing)
It's real alright.
- Water works.
I wonder where the TV is.
Watch out Evie the TV's mine.
Wait for me.
- Hey!
(screaming)
What the hell's going on?
Walk down you, hey.
What the devil?
- What is that?
- Evie?
(crying)
- Stop it.
- Hey, hey hey let them go.
- Who are you? You shouldn't be here.
- Let them go.
This is our house.
- Nobody lives here.
- [Rob] They do now.
- This is my mother's house.
- Elizabeth?
- Who are you?
- I'm Ian, I'm the caretaker here.
- What the hell do you
think you were doing?
- I'm doing my job,
keeping strangers away.
This is a dangerous place,
you shouldn't be here.
- I'm sorry I think you should go,
please, could you take your dog?
Let's go, go on, come on, come on dog, go.
(whistling)
You just stay away from my kids.
- Come on.
- Go on dog.
(barking)
- Only death lives here.
(foreboding music)
Foreigners, oh what are you looking at?
Come on.
(whistling)
- Why do I feel like we just
ended a Stephen King novel?
- What do you say we unwrap this place
like a big Christmas present?
- [Children] Yeah.
(laughing)
(mysterious music)
(banging)
- [Nancy] Hey careful with that.
- [Rob] Slow down guys slow down.
- [Kyle] It's all old stuff.
- [Rob] Slow down, that's
an antique, that's not old.
- Look what's here.
- Look at this stuff Dad.
- Careful we don't know what's
under all this stuff, huh?
Ah, Nancy--
(foreboding music)
- Mom, Dad, look what we found.
It's the fairy.
- Ew, what a horrible picture,
what are those things?
- It's goblins Mom, you
know, wicked fairies,
they live underground.
- It's in Grandma's book.
- [Rob] It's interesting.
- Yeah well I don't like
it, can we take it down?
- Yeah, let me see.
I'm afraid not, looks like
it's bolted to the wall.
- Look what I found.
- Careful.
- Ooh now that's better.
Hey let's take it outside.
(dramatic music)
(swooshing)
(laughing)
There, let's hope they bring us luck.
(clinking)
Oh god it's beautiful.
I wonder how much property there is.
- You know the letter
didn't really say did it?
- Well I love it.
I'm glad we came,
Mom would be so pleased that
we're all here together.
- Well so am I.
- We need this.
(coughing)
Rob we've got to do something about that.
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
(wings flapping)
(joyful music)
(swooshing)
I'm sorry I haven't been there.
- Well you are now.
Hey, who would've thought
someone as ugly as you
would have married someone
as wonderful as me?
- That is an understatement.
(swooshing)
- Kyle look.
(joyful music)
(laughing)
(wings flapping)
Don't worry, we'll save
you, we promised Grandma.
Mom, Dad look.
(swooshing)
- Fireflies.
- Look it right there.
- Incredible.
(joyful music)
(sizzling)
- Smells good.
So what is this?
- An English breakfast.
- Oh, I'm gonna get fat.
Where are the kids?
- They were up and out hours ago.
Oh I made an appointment
for you at the doctors.
- Okay, okay.
(suspenseful music)
- Hi.
You're the fairy, I'm Evie.
(laughing)
Wait for me.
- Evie where you going?
Evie?
- Hey.
Hey what do you want?
- Nothing.
- Well who are you running from, eh?
- We weren't running from nothing,
we were playing.
(swooshing)
- With the fairies.
- Hmm?
With the what?
- Where'd she go?
- Ah she's just being stupid.
- [Ian] Well you shouldn't
be playing around here
and why don't you tell
your mom and dad to leave?
- [Kyle] Why should we? It's our house.
- Is it? Nobody owns this house,
and all the monsters that live in it
and you shouldn't be
playing in these woods.
If you do they'll be watching you.
They like to eat small children.
- Ah you're just acting crazy.
- Oh am I? Hey don't
say I didn't warn you.
Ow.
(dramatic music)
(swooshing)
- Rob, I'm going to take Evie
and Kyle into the village
and do some shopping, I'll
drop you off at the doctor.
- Oh right, yeah I was thinking,
maybe I'll take Kyle with me
and stop off at the church afterwards
and see if they keep any
records on this place.
- Hey take it easy, you alright?
- We saw that--
- Evie met a fairy.
- Really?
- Yeah she lives under the bridge.
- Hey, friends already,
you guys ready to go?
- Yeah I'll meet you
guys in the car, I gotta,
I think my wallet's upstairs.
- Okay, come on, let's wait in the car.
- Why didn't you tell them about that man?
- 'Cause he's crazy,
I didn't want to worry
Dad so he'd want to leave.
- But he said the monsters will get us.
- Evie he's just trying to scare us.
- No you heard what Grandma said.
- Evie it's just a dumb story
in a book Grandma wrote.
Look hasn't Dad changed?
Is it more fun, isn't it better here?
- Yeah.
- We have to keep him here Evie
or else he's gonna go away
and we'll never see him again
just like before.
- We still have to save the fairies.
- Hey come on guys, let's go, let's go.
- We promised Grandma.
(dramatic music)
(wings flapping)
(playful music)
- Was that you?
(wings flapping)
(playful music)
What in the devil?
What the devil?
Now we know, we know don't we Tippit?
Alright we know.
You don't frighten me
with your little tricks.
(barking)
Whoa, hey.
(laughing)
Hey.
- Take that when you need it,
and in the meantime I'll call
you when I hear from the lab.
- Alright thank you.
- And take it easy, no strenuous exercise.
- Alright.
- You alright?
- Yeah.
- Hmm, they don't look very nice.
(suspenseful music)
- Mom?
- I know honey.
You know it's rude to stare.
- Dad.
Firefly.
- Good job, good job.
Here roll that out slowly,
don't want to rip it.
There we are, Firefly
Mine, claim 18, gold.
According to this there's
a goldmine on the property.
- Grandma owned a goldmine?
- That's what it says here.
- Can I help you?
- Yes, we were just
looking for the records
for the Ballaugh property.
- Ballaugh, may I ask who wants to know?
- I'm sorry I'm Rob Preston, this is my,
this is my son, he's the new owner.
- We don't have any information
on the Ballaugh property.
- Well surely there must be something?
- There isn't any, not as far as I know.
Now if you'll excuse me?
- Sure, yeah of course.
Thank you.
(swooshing)
(joyful music)
I don't get it, it's
gotta be here somewhere,
look there's the water right there right?
Well it's gotta be right here somewhere,
we must be standing on it.
- Dad.
- What is that? Come here.
That's gold, Kyle that's gold, where?
Here come here, take the
map, look right around here.
Nancy, Nancy!
(dramatic music)
Nancy, Nancy, Nancy look at this.
- Why what is it?
- Gold, Kyle found it down in the creek.
- Gold?
- Yes.
- You've dug this out of the creek?
- Supposedly there's a
goldmine here somewhere,
we haven't found any trace of it yet,
but we found a map at the
church that said Firefly Mine.
- [Nancy] Firefly?
- Do you remember what your mother said?
Fireflies, remember?
- No I--
- Nancy, she's left us a goldmine.
- No.
- Yeah.
- Dad, I found it, I found the mine.
- You found what mine?
- Where, where?
- [Kyle] Come on follow me.
- Show me where?
- Wait for me.
- What are you talking about?
- Look, look there's the mine.
- Where?
- Right there.
- You're right, right there it is,
Nancy Nancy look come here.
It's under here.
See there it is, it's right under there,
Nancy look it's right
there, we own a goldmine.
- We're rich.
- Yay.
- Can we open it Dad, can we?
- Oh you betcha but
we're gonna need a pump,
there must be some pump around here,
it's probably old or rusted or something.
Nancy you guys check over here
Kyle let's look over here.
- Yeah I've got to see
this mine, where is it?
Is that it?
It's hard to imagine there's
a mine under all this water.
- Nancy, Nancy, can I
have a word with you?
- Oh no, what now?
- Nancy, you don't mind
if I call you that?
I'd just like to
apologize about yesterday.
- Yeah well you scared Evie.
- I know I'm sorry, sorry
Evie I didn't mean to.
It's just that I didn't
know you were coming.
- Well didn't the solicitors tell you?
- No, nobody mentioned it to me.
- Well I'm sorry.
You knew my mother?
- Yes well actually we were cousins.
I supposed that makes us all family.
- Really well I didn't realize. (laughing)
Oh well it's very beautiful
around here, peaceful.
- Yes well don't be fooled,
it may look beautiful on
the surface, but the pond,
the house, it's all
tainted, tainted with evil.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It means that anyone with any sense
will stay well away from this place.
- Really?
- A lot of people have died here.
Please I wouldn't want you to be next.
- Hey, hey hey hey.
What're you doing here?
- No you can't, you must be
mad, you can't drain that pond.
- Yeah here we go again, look
I'm mad, this is our pond,
this is our house, if we want to drain it,
then that's exactly what we'll do
and you better get used to the idea.
- You're making a mistake,
a big mistake, look
Elizabeth knew, she knew,
that's why we took here away from here.
- Knew what, that there
was a goldmine in here?
Yeah maybe that's why you're so keen
to keep people away huh?
So you can keep it all to yourself?
- You know about the mine?
- I sure do.
It's deep huh?
- Please you've got to listen
to me, don't open that mine.
You open that mine,
you'll free the demons.
- Demons?
Please just go away.
Come on Kyle, go away.
- Alright, I'll go,
but before this is over,
you'll be needing me.
- Okay well thank you very
much, we'll remember that,
leave your phone number at the
front door, bye, thank you.
- You okay Mom?
- Yeah, yeah honey, so
where did you find this?
- Oh it's in a box right over there.
In fact Evie I want you to run over there,
see that brown box,
when I tell you to
you'll see a red switch,
I want you to hit it alright?
Hope this is gonna work.
Kyle get ready.
- Ready?
- Go ahead.
(motor running)
- Yay it works.
(wings flapping)
- Alright look this is
gonna take a while to drain,
I'm starving, let's go inside
and get something to eat,
we'll come back in a little while,
and don't you worry there's
a lunatic in every family.
- Yeah well there is in yours.
- Who would that be? (speaking goofily)
(laughing)
(coughing)
(dramatic music)
(swooshing)
- The fools.
God.
Bloody fools.
(dramatic music)
(laughing)
I'll show him.
Then they'll have to
believe me. (laughing)
I'll show 'em, what do
you think about that?
What do you think about that?
Yeah, you're a lovely dog.
(laughing)
- Uh oh it's starting
to wobble, whoa, whoa,
it's going to fall down, whoa.
(laughing)
(coughing)
- Hey quit having so much fun.
- Oh I gotcha girl.
Okay.
- Time for bed Kyle, come on Evie.
- Off to bed, up you go like
a rocket, one, two, three.
- Here you are darling.
- I want a pony.
- We're not rich yet.
- I want one daddy.
- Hey you know there might
not be anything down there.
But we'll find out tomorrow won't we?
Goodnight Kyle.
- Goodnight my little
scrumptious bumtious. (smooching)
- Alright in we go, in we go, in we go.
Big kiss huh? (smooching)
(coughing)
Alright, night guys.
- Night.
- Goodnight Dad.
- Night. (smooching)
(dramatic music)
- They're so beautiful, they
want us to save them Kyle.
- Save who from what?
Who are you waving to?
- [Evie] The fairies, who do you think?
- What?
(dramatic music)
You're so weird.
(swooshing)
(dramatic music)
- What's a matter?
- Oh nothing I guess.
It's just, what if Ian's right?
- What, what that we have
monsters in our garden?
- No, but it could be
dangerous opening an old mine,
and what did he mean when he said Mom knew
and being then being taken away?
- Oh Nancy I have no idea,
but don't let it get to you,
look at this.
- Why are these people so against us,
what have we done to make them hate us?
- They're not against
us, we're just newcomers,
you know that in 20 years,
we're still gonna be newcomers.
- Yeah but I don't think I want
to hang around for 20 years.
- Well do you want to go home?
- No no of course not.
- Want to get under the covers with me?
- Maybe.
- Want some gold?
- Definitely.
(laughing)
Come on give it to me,
I want it.
- Here it is, come and get it,
come and get it.
(foreboding music)
(rubble exploding)
(grunting)
(crashing)
(growling)
(rubble crashing)
(groaning)
(dramatic music)
- [Man] Demons, demons!
- Let go of me, let go, stop it, let go.
Dad!
Dad.
- Kyle, Kyle you okay, what?
- What's wrong Kyle?
- I had a bad dream about
the mine and the goblins.
- Just a dream Kyle, just a dream.
- It's all this talk
of fairies and demons.
Come on darling lie down,
just close your eyes and go to sleep,
think good thoughts, it's all right.
- [Evie] Mom?
- Evie back to bed, come on.
There you go.
Okay back to sleep.
Good girl.
Ian has a lot to answer for.
- You'll be alright okay?
I'll leave the light on.
- Can I sleep with you?
(water pouring)
(suspenseful music)
(swooshing)
(knocking)
(groaning)
- Who's that?
- I don't know, what time is it?
It's six o'clock.
(rooster crowing)
- [Nancy] It's alright,
it's just someone at the door that's all.
- Got you out of bed a bit early have I?
- Yeah, yeah something like that.
- Sorry about that,
early risers around here.
Jim Blythe, local constabulary.
- Hi, hi, Rob Preston.
- Bit early for a cup of tea is it?
Or will that be coffee,
why you being an American?
- Whatever.
- Morning Mom.
- [Nancy] Good morning.
- [Jim] It's only a visit.
(rooster crowing)
- [Rob] Ah yeah sure,
here she is, here she is.
- Thank you Mom.
- So to what do we owe the pleasure?
- Oh just a social call.
We like to know who's moving
in and who's moving out.
- Do you want us to move out?
- What ever gave you that idea?
- Well if you don't,
you're the only one in town who doesn't.
- Oh you shouldn't take too much to store
in what people say around here Mom.
They mean no harm, they're
just suspicious that's all
and this property of yours
has got its fair share of history.
- Well like what exactly?
- A couple of miners were killed
when the mine was closed down.
Way back in 1800's I think it was.
- Why'd they close it down?
- Well one day they opened up a knew gap
and a pile of creatures swarmed out.
- [Rob And Nancy] Creatures?
- Some of the locals think
they're still down there.
- Well you don't believe that do you?
- I didn't say I did, but some
of the folk around here do.
- Well you're aware
that there may be gold down in that mine?
- Aye, so I've heard.
- Are you not from around here?
- No, Lanchester lad,
been here for 15 years,
but I'm still an outsider.
- Do you think maybe that,
maybe these people are
trying to frighten us
so they can get their
greedy hands on the gold?
- No Mr. Preston I don't.
Things go a lot deeper
than that around here.
I'm afraid you're into
something far bigger than greed.
Well you'll call me if you need me?
- Will I, need you?
- Not if you leave your mine alone.
Nice to have met you Mom,
thanks for the coffee.
I'll make me own way out.
(laughing)
- What ever happened to,
"hi nice to meet you,
welcome to the community,"
I think it rains too much on these people.
- Are we gonna leave?
- No, no, 'cause I
don't believe in demons,
I don't believe in goblins and
I don't believe in fairies.
No we're not going anywhere
until we decide to.
Now, why don't we get dressed.
I think I want to check
out that gold mine.
- It's the fairies from Grandma's story.
- What?
- You know Tumbeleen and
the fairy folk of Ar,
they're trapped underground.
- Evie you're so stupid.
(glass smearing)
(playful music)
(wings flapping)
(shouting)
- Right, I've got you now,
let's see you get out of that. (laughing)
(magical swooshing)
(shattering)
What, where, where'd it go?
(swooshing)
(wings flapping)
(playful music)
(groaning)
(wings flapping)
(playful music)
(groaning)
(shattering)
(playful music)
(wings flapping)
(banging)
(playful music)
(crashing)
(wings flapping)
(swooshing)
- [Rob] Firefly Mine.
(splashing)
- Cool.
- Hey Kyle careful.
Oh Rob I don't like this, I
mean nevermind the legend,
but I think you should
leave this mine alone
it's old and dangerous.
- Relax we're gonna be fine.
- Can I go with you?
- No, I think I better go first huh?
- Okay.
- Hold still.
- Mom, Dad!
- Kyle!
(shouting)
- Dad! (shouting)
(splashing)
- Kyle!
- Dad!
- [Rob] Kyle!
- [Kyle] Come on Dad.
- Kyle!
- Dad help.
Dad!
- Kyle, Kyle!
- Dad.
(splashing)
- Come here, come here,
it's okay, it's okay,
I gotcha, I gotcha, I gotcha.
- Something got my foot.
- No you just caught it on
something don't worry, come on.
You alright, you okay?
Look at me you alright?
Okay, let's get out of here,
over here, over here.
(splashing)
Oh hold on, easy easy,
easy, that's it, careful.
Look at me, are you alright, you sure?
Alright.
Oh man.
Check this out.
(dramatic music)
- Whoa. (laughing)
- Wow.
- Is that?
- Gold?
- Dad.
(foreboding music)
The gateway to hell, September 22nd 1887.
- Whoa. (nervously laughing)
(coughing)
- Now come on come on let's get
warm, we can come back down.
- Mom's not gonna believe this.
- No she's not.
Here take my hand, take my hand.
Be very careful now, wait wait wait wait.
Alright, watch where you're walking.
Now hold on, hold on, we'll
get this hose back down there
and we'll drain the rest of this.
Here take this, take.
(splashing)
- [Nancy] Rob?
Kyle, are you okay?
- Be careful.
- Rob?
- Nancy!
- Mom!
- [Nancy] Kyle!
- [Kyle] Mom.
- [Nancy] Hey, hey, are you alright?
- [Evie] Are you alright,
what'd you find down there,
what'd you see?
- There's gold everywhere down there Mom.
- Nancy it's the most unbelievable thing
I've ever seen in my entire life.
- Can I see, can I please?
- Evie not now.
- A bit later Evie,
come on let's get you
into a nice warm bath.
- [Nancy And Evie] Careful.
- Look at you, come on darling,
you'll catch a cold Kyle, come on inside.
(coughing)
(dramatic music)
- [Evie] Come on.
(coughing)
(swooshing)
(wings flapping)
(heavy coughing)
(crashing)
(dramatic music)
- Dad.
- Daddy.
- [Kyle] Dad.
- Call 999, get an ambulance.
- Daddy?
- Hurry.
- Mrs. Preston we've got the
results of the test we did.
I'm afraid there's no
easy way to say this,
your husband's very sick Mrs. Preston,
but we'll know more in a couple of days,
but there's not much we can do
except help him stay as
comfortable as possible.
- Well what are you saying?
- With rest and medication, he
may have two or three months.
- He's going to die?
- I suggest you take him home.
He'll be better off in the States there.
They're better equipped
for, this sort of thing.
I'm sorry.
(dramatic music)
- When is Daddy coming home?
- They said he could come
home in a couple of days.
(dramatic music)
- What does Dad have?
- Come here.
Your father,
he's very sick.
- Is he going to die like Grandma?
- I want you to do
something for me right now,
I want you to pray, I
want you to pray to god,
and ask him for a miracle.
(dramatic music)
(magical swooshing)
(groaning)
- Let go, let me go.
Let go.
(magical swooshing)
(thudding)
(grunting)
No!
(exploding)
(screaming)
(gasping)
- Help us Kyle.
Evie?
Where are you?
- Kyle!
- Evie, my god Evie,
are you alright?
(crying)
- I hurt my arm.
Ow, ow.
Ow, ow. (crying)
Ow my arm hurts, it hurts.
- Look we gotta get you out of here.
You stay here and I'll go get Mom okay?
- No don't go.
- I have to.
(swooshing)
Evie.
Stay back don't come any closer.
Stay away, stay away.
Don't come any closer, don't hurt Evie,
please don't hurt Evie.
- It's alright Kyle, she'll help us.
- No don't hurt Evie please.
(electric buzzing)
(magical swooshing)
- Evie,
Evie.
- I want to go home, I feel so tired.
- Don't worry, I'll take you home,
you'll be okay, don't worry, come on.
Evie.
Evie,
Evie?
- What?
- Your fairy friend can help Dad Evie.
Make him well.
- No Kyle she can't.
- But your arm, she cured your arm.
- This is different,
only the fairy king has
enough power to save Dad.
- Then we have to set him free.
- What's wrong?
- What if Ian's right, I
mean what if they're evil
and they start killing again
because we opened up the mine,
then what?
- They won't.
- What if they do, what if they're demons?
- We gotta take a chance.
- Yeah, come on.
(laughing)
- Kyle?
What do you think you're doing?
I've been looking for you everywhere,
I thought something might
have happened to you.
Now I don't want you to
ever come down here again
this mine is dangerous
and I don't want you anywhere near it.
- But Mom they could
save Dad if I open it.
- Who can?
- You know, Evie's friend the fairy.
- Kyle?
- Really, really Mom.
- Kyle, I know you're frightened, so am I,
but I need you to be strong for me Kyle.
- Remember E.T., his finger?
- Oh Kyle.
That was just a film, a film.
Now look I don't want you
to come down here again,
it's dangerous down here okay?
Promise me Kyle, promise.
- I promise.
- Okay, come on now.
(wings flapping)
(dramatic music)
(swooshing)
- I'm sorry, we tried,
we promised Grandma we'd help you
and we're doing all we can.
Now Mom won't let us in the mine,
no one will believe us.
(gasping)
And Grandma's not here to talk to,
what are we going to do?
- Shh.
(swooshing)
- I don't know what I'm going to do.
Daddy's very sick, can you help him?
(magical swooshing)
(barking)
(crashing)
- Well, what, damn, missed
the little blighter.
- Don't hurt me, please don't hurt me.
- It's alright.
- Keep away!
- It's alright I'm not going
to hurt you, calm down.
- It's those little devils that I'm after.
Hey, you shouldn't be down here with them.
I mean you shouldn't be here
at all, they're not good.
(swooshing)
(wings flapping)
- Keep away.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey I
didn't mean to frighten you.
(barking)
Oh.
Alright don't be like that,
didn't mean to scare her.
Come on.
- He almost got me.
- Ian?
- What are we gonna do?
- I'm gonna go into
town and get some help.
- Can I come too?
- No, you stay here.
(dramatic music)
(foreboding music)
- Thanks Gladys, see ya.
- [Kyle] Excuse me.
- Yes?
- I was wondering, do
you have a bulletin board
where people put there wanted ads?
- Yes, what is it you need?
- Yeah, I live above the Ballaugh house
and I was wondering if
somebody could help me
work up at the mine.
- Ballaugh, oh my god.
Are you mad?
Go, get out of my shop, go.
(suspenseful music)
- Let's go.
- Let's go, come on.
- Excuse me, excuse me.
I was wondering if you could
help me open up the mine?
I live up at the Ballaugh house.
- No, no way, I've got
no time to waste on ya,
get out of here, go on, clear out kid.
(suspenseful music)
(crashing)
(chattering)
- [Kyle] I live up at the Ballaugh house
and I was wondering if
anybody could help me?
I could pay.
- I told you and your sister to leave,
before the monsters get ya.
- Stay away from Evie
Mister, leave her alone.
- Or what?
I told you to leave and you wouldn't
and now you father's sick,
see he's paying the price
for meddling in things
he doesn't understand.
- You're a liar.
(laughing)
- Give me another one of those.
- There was no call to frighten the kid.
- Ah well,
everyday they're up at that place,
we're in more danger here.
I'd just like to see them go
for their own good as well as ours.
- Has it ever occurred to you
that we're far too old to
believe all this nonsense?
- What are you talking?
I've seen them.
But what would you know?
You don't belong here
anymore than they do.
- That's it isn't it Ian,
that's what really scares you.
Anyone who's different,
anyone who doesn't fit in with
your limited knowledge world.
And the rest of you,
you're all just as bad.
All of ya, prejudiced,
it doesn't matter if
they're demons or people,
if they're different they scare ya,
and what scares ya, you destroy,
even a little kid.
You're pathetic.
(dramatic music)
- [Boy] Get him!
(suspenseful music)
- [Boy] Come on let's go.
- Get out of the way.
(suspenseful music)
- Get him.
(crashing)
- [Boy] Come on let's get him.
(suspenseful music)
(quacking)
Now we got him.
(suspenseful music)
(crashing)
(splashing)
- My bike.
(grunting)
(crashing)
- Kyle?
Kyle?
- No one will help us Evie, no one.
- Then we'll have to do it ourselves.
- We can't.
- We got to Kyle.
- We promised Grandma.
- Hey, hey what's all the shouting about?
- Dad, dad,
it's true there are goblins in the mine,
they're trapped, they're really fairies.
Can't you see, they can help you Dad,
all we've got to do is
open it up and let them go.
- This is ridiculous.
We should've stomped on this nonsense
right at the beginning.
- Please Dad believe me, help
me open it, help me save them.
- Please Daddy.
- No we need to get your father home
where he can get the treatment he needs.
- Nancy.
- Rob I'm not gonna let you do this.
- I've got to, it's important to them.
Just for a couple of days.
A couple of days.
(dramatic music)
(banging)
(coughing)
Alright there it is.
Now Kyle take these and hang
them on the tree next to you,
there you go.
Thanks.
(electrical popping)
Alright.
(laughing)
Alright, let's go save
us some fairies huh?
- Yeah.
- Hit it.
(motor running)
Here we go.
(wheels squeaking)
(joyful music)
Are you alright?
- Yeah.
- Okay watch it.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Okay, you guys ready?
- Yep.
- Yeah.
- Evie I want you to roll up
the rest of that hose alright?
- [Evie] Alright.
- Here take this.
(groaning)
(crashing)
Alright, here we come.
(cracking)
(joyful music)
(coughing)
Watch out Kyle, just a bit.
(coughing) Alright.
Alright that's good I think
that's enough for today.
Evie I want you to do me a favor
I want you to grab-
(banging)
When I tell you to I
want you to go up top,
I'm gonna give you a
little tug on the line,
you'll start the winch okay?
Go on, take a shovel.
Watch out.
(banging)
(coughing)
That's good.
Alright Evie get ready.
- [Evie] Okay Dad.
- Alright, hit it.
(wheels squeaking)
(joyful music)
(coughing)
That's good, Kyle grab
that shovel would you?
(coughing)
(thunder cracking)
Good days work guys.
Bright and early tomorrow morning.
- Yeah.
- Hey what's wrong?
- Nothing.
I mean what if we open the mine
and the goblins are evil, then what?
- Well, you know sometimes Kyle
you just gotta go with your feelings,
you gotta take a chance
in what you believe in.
Do you think they're evil?
- No,
no.
- Well then we have to help them.
Alright Evie come on, why
don't we get cleaned up?
Kyle I want you to turn off these lights
and secure the ore cart alright?
- [Kyle] Sure.
(dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
- Hey.
You never listen,
hey you think you know
everything don't you?
- And you don't?
- I've lived here all me
life I know about them things
and I can prove it to you.
- What do you mean?
- You come with me I'll show ya.
- [Kyle] Dad, dad!
- Come on, move along, go on.
- Help.
- Come on get on with it, move on.
- You're pushing me, stop it, quit it.
- Do you think we're making it all up?
Do you thing we're kidding
about things in that mine?
Look see for yourself, there.
Look at the face of a demon.
(screaming)
(thunder cracking)
- You're crazy, just a crazy old man.
They're not demons, they're
the ones dead aren't they?
If they're so evil how
come they're the ones dead,
how come they're the ones lying there?
- Hey.
- You're the ones that are evil not them.
You are, you killed
them, they were trapped,
all they wanted to do was to
escape and you killed them,
you, you and your stupid town.
(mysterious music)
You've packed.
- Hey Kyle.
- Yeah well I'm sorry but we
need to get your father home.
- We can't go, not now.
- Hey hey hey hey.
- Look I'm not going, I'm not giving up.
They can cure you Dad.
- That's enough, we're
leaving and that's final,
I've had it up to here
with these stupid stories.
Your father's sick and we're going home.
- Nancy.
- No Rob what do you expect me to do,
just sit here and watch you die?
We're going home.
- You're gonna die and
it's gonna be all my fault,
only if I could've opened the mine.
- Hey Kyle, Kyle you did
everything you could do son.
Come here.
Come here Evie.
I love you guys.
I love you so much.
- I love you too Daddy.
(coughing)
- Rob I'm sorry,
I'm just trying to do
what I think is right.
- I know.
We have to make plans.
- If only it were true.
If only there were fairies,
E.T.'s with the power of healing.
- Ah shh.
- I don't want to lose you.
(rain pouring)
(thunder booming)
(swooshing)
Rob.
(magical pulsing)
(magical swooshing)
(wings flapping)
Thank you.
- Stop it Kyle stop it.
Kyle stop it, stop, Kyle stop it.
Stop Kyle, stop it, stop
it I tell you, stop it,
Kyle stop it, stop it,
Kyle stop it, stop it Kyle.
Mom.
(banging)
- Kyle please.
- No.
Why, why my Dad, why?
I can save him Mom I can save him.
- Oh I know Kyle I believe
you, I believe you, I do.
(dramatic music)
(thunder cracking)
(groaning)
- [Ian] I'll show 'em.
I'll flood that mine again.
Oh come on.
(wheels squeaking)
(suspenseful music)
- Mom!
- Evie!
(shouting)
(screaming)
Evie!
(crashing)
- You alright?
- Yeah, yeah are you okay?
- Are you okay honey?
- It's open we did it.
(distant groaning)
(crashing)
(coughing)
- Nancy?
(distant shouting)
- Gotta fill that mine in.
(shouting)
Let's close them down.
- Send them home.
(shouting)
- [Woman] Shut them down.
(coughing)
- Come on, oh, there
you go, are you alright?
Where's Kyle?
Kyle, Kyle?
- Kyle?
- Mom help.
- Kyle.
(banging)
- Mom help.
- Wait wait there.
- I'm slipping Mom.
- Oh my god.
Kyle it's okay, here grab my hand.
(crashing)
- Mom help.
- Grab onto my hand.
- I can't.
- Yes you can.
- [Evie] Mom.
(shouting)
You can do it Kyle.
(groaning)
- Come on, you can do it, come on.
- Mom I can't I'm stuck.
I can't I'm stuck.
- Come on, get your neck up.
There you did it, you did it,
you did it, you clever boy.
We're safe, we're safe.
(coughing)
- Hey, what's going on here?
- I tried to warn ya, you got
the whole place stirred up.
- Look this is our mine, it's on our land,
we're gonna do what we want
and nobody's gonna stop us.
- That's right,
but you gotta understand
how these people feel.
I haven't got the manpower to
provide you with protection.
- Protection, would you--
- This legend of there's
isn't a joke Mr. Preston,
it's real to them, they know
it's true, they're frightened
and fear makes people
do things they regret.
- Look I want everybody out of here now.
- [Jim] Just calm down.
- I want everybody out!
- Just calm down.
- [Nancy] Careful Evie.
- Come on.
- Careful Kyle.
Okay let's get out of here.
- Everybody out of here.
You're all on my land,
you too I want you out--
- Hey you're making a mistake,
you're making a mistake,
don't go down there.
(crashing)
(shouting)
(coughing)
- Nancy?
Nancy, Nancy?
- Daddy.
- Rob, Rob Kyle's in there.
- What happened?
- Kyle's in the mine.
- Calm down calm down.
- He's in the mine.
- Would somebody take her? Take her.
- Just try, just hey let me go.
- Get Kyle, no my son is in the mine.
- Calm down, just calm down and wait here.
- Kyle!
- Wait,
Tippit, Tippit.
- Kyle!
- Tippit, Tippit, Tippit come here.
- [Rob] Kyle!
- [Nancy] Kyle!
(barking)
- Somebody help me please!
- Somebody help him!
- Kyle we're coming!
We're coming Kyle we're coming!
- Tippit, Tippit, here
boy, here boy, good boy.
- [Rob] Can you hear me?
- Dad!
- I'm coming.
Tippit.
- Somebody help me, please help me.
- Help him please, please!
Why don't you help him?
- I can't believe this,
your stupid superstitions
are going to keep you from
saving a child's life?
- Let me go for god's sake.
- Ian let him go.
- There's a kid down there.
- Let him help us.
- It's just a kid.
- No Jim.
- Kyle!
- Let him go.
- All you fools, alright
look a tragedy happened here,
it was a long time ago,
but you're making a worse one right now.
That's the evil of this
place, not what's down there,
but here in your hearts.
Please, please help me.
- Oh please, please help us.
- Help my dad.
Please, please.
Somebody.
Please Ian,
please?
(dramatic music)
- We're coming Kyle just stay there.
(music drowning out voices)
(dramatic music)
(crashing)
Kyle, Kyle!
(dramatic music)
- [Ian] There's a big one there.
- Kyle!
Kyle!
- [Kyle] I'm down here.
- Careful.
- Dad help.
- Kyle.
Watch it, watch it.
Kyle.
- Dad, Dad I'm trapped.
- [Rob] Kyle!
Hold on, hold on.
Let me get this out of the way, watch it.
Hold still, hold still.
Alright, are you alright?
- My leg it's stuck.
- Okay hold on, let me see, let me see.
- Look we're gonna have to
move this log very carefully,
on three.
- Okay.
One, two, three.
- [Ian] Go.
- [Ian And Jim] One, two.
(crashing)
(barking)
(coughing)
- [Kyle] Look Dad, over there.
- Whoa listen.
Listen
(distant groaning)
- What is it?
- [Rob] It's moving.
- Dad?
- I told you, I told you it's demons.
- Let's get out of here.
- We gotta get out of here now.
- [Ian] Tippit.
(distant groaning)
(coughing)
(barking)
Tippit.
- [Man] Demons, demons.
(barking)
(groaning)
(suspenseful music)
- Kyle.
Kyle.
- Thank god.
- Mom.
(coughing)
- Are you alright?
- I'm okay Mom.
(swooshing)
- Move it they're coming.
(growling)
They're coming out.
- Rob.
- [Kyle and Evie] Dad!
(gasping)
- Daddy.
- Okay get back, make room for him,
give him some room please.
Rob speak to me, Rob?
- Please, please Dad hang on.
- Oh my goodness look.
(swooshing)
- Look.
- They're going to kill us.
- No no, that's the
mistake the miners made
the first time they tried to escape.
- [Ian] You're wrong
they're going to kill us.
- They just want to be
free, they won't hurt us.
- I hope you're right.
(wings flapping)
(swooshing)
(heavy breathing)
No.
- No Mom, they'll help us.
(resonating)
(magical pulsing)
(dramatic music)
- Nancy.
(swooshing)
(wings flapping)
(magical swooshing)
(swooshing)
(dramatic music)
- Bye Tumbeleen.
- You did it,
you did it, they're free.
- Oh honey.
- [Kyle Narrating] We
stayed on the Isle of Man.
Dad takes me and Evie
fishing a lot with him.
Tests found no sign of
the sickness in his body.
Ian turned out to be just
one of Mom's cousins,
seems she has a lot of cousins here.
I'm glad we freed the
goblins so they can go home.
So Evie says she still
plays with the fairies
at the bottom of the garden,
I guess it's nice to know
that there's still a little
magic left in the world.
(magical swooshing)
(dramatic music)
(MultiCom Jingle)