And with this Kreitech
miracle micro battery,
we will power the world...
together!
Thank you.
I'll take it!
Uh, you there,
you shouldn't be in here.
But don't worry, the battery
will be available soon
for purchase.
Did I say "purchase"? Ha!
-Hey!
-Ha!
Pretty sure I said "take it."
Ow!
-Ha!
-Aha!
Juniper, what are you
doing here?
Could you please tell Barb,
who I'm not speaking to
because she betrayed
our mother-daughter bond,
that I am taking the battery.
Mother?
I don't believe you.
Yeah, I feel the resemblance.
Young lady,
you give me that right now!
No, Mother!
Not after what you did.
This battery's mine!
Not that you care about that.
Just what is that
supposed to mean?
You know exactly what it means.
Juniper, cut the sass
and give me the battery!
Never!
but you do realize there's
another battery right there.
Ha!
This is not how I raised you
to steal things!
I'm my own
crime-dancer now, Mother!
It'll do for now.
I should call my mom.
Hello, I am Baymax.
♪ Whoa-oh
♪ Whoa-oh, whoa-oh
Bad news, San Fransokyo.
Infamous mother-daughter duo,
High Voltage,
broke danced
out of jail
and are making
a crime-dance comeback.
I get the crime.
I don't get the dance.
See, I get the dance.
I don't get the crime.
Let's just get them
back in jail.
Guys, Richardson Mole.
He can't know that we're--
-Big Hero 6.
-What about Big Hero 6?
Because if there's
something you want to know
about Big Hero 6,
I'm the one to ask.
I'm kind of an expert.
Right.
I see I piqued
your interest, Dream Girl.
I'm not just a superhero expert.
I know villains too.
High Voltage, Glooby--
Globby! I mean, um-- I--
I mean, I believe
it is pronounced "Globby."
Stay in your lane, Fred!
It's definitely Glooby.
Uh, no, it's not.
The man's a giant glob.
Thus, his name is Glob-by.
He's not a giant "gloob."
You don't know what
you're talking about.
Oh, I know exactly
what I'm talking about.
-No, you don't!
-Yes, I do!
You're ruining
my lunch serenity, guys.
Yeah, move along, Richardson.
This is my side of town.
You have sides?
Not for long.
I'm buying
the lot next door.
It will soon be home
to the Mole Museum
of Superhero History.
A superhero museum?
That was my idea!
-Was not!
-Uh-huh!
Stop. Just stop.
Sure, anything
for you, Dream Girl.
I wouldn't.
Some day.
Ugh!
I hate that kid.
Yeah, you really shouldn't
let him get to you, Freddie.
He's just trolling you.
Do not engage.
Hi there.
Ma'am, you can't be in here.
I'm so sorry
to bother you, officer,
but my little ol' GPS here,
well, it just conked out,
and I'm all turned around.
Could you be a sweetheart
and point me
in the right direction?
Uh, okay.
Where you trying to go?
Well, thank you, darling.
I'm trying to get...
...here.
Got it.
Come to...
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no!
Having a bad day?
Too bad. Because it's about
to get worse.
Who's having a bad day now?
Still you!
And me.
Yeah. Sorry about that.
Buh-bye!
Great. High Voltage got away.
Well, technically half
of High Voltage got away,
since they're clearly not
working together anymore.
So maybe we should
call her Half Voltage or--
Ooh, ooh, I got it--
Low Voltage. Eh? Eh?
-Right?
-Look.
- It's empty.
- Huh.
Why would Low Voltage--
going with that name--
want an empty box?
She didn't want the box, Fred.
She wanted whatever
was in the box.
Their energy orb.
Ah. Interesting theory,
Go Go.
This requires research.
The mother-daughter
supervillain section is so vast.
Uh, here to start.
What do you want?
Just wanted to make sure
you weren't soiling
my comics
with your finger dirt.
Yeah. Well, I wish
you weren't soiling
my life with your face.
Oh, witty retort. Not!
What? No! You cannot mock
with a "not!"
That's just-- Wait.
What is this?
What does it look like?
Wait, "Lizard Guy"
isn't even my-- his name!
Yes, it is!
For your information,
I am a close,
personal friend
of Big Hero 6.
-No way!
-Or yes way.
We hang out all the time.
Brunch, kayaking.
Last weekend,
we went apple picking.
It was delightful!
That is a bushel
of lies, Richardson!
I know Big Hero 6,
and they would never
pick fruit with you.
-Ever!
-Oh, please.
There's no way
you know Big Hero 6.
They're big-time superheroes,
and you're just a big...
...old...
...nobody.
I definitely know Big Hero 6
because I am Lizard Guy!
Except that's not my name!
It's Fredzilla, baby.
Fake.
Yeah, I guess
this is fake too?
Ha!
Oh!
Uh... Uh...
Forget you saw that!
Oh, no.
He's eating crackers.
This is bad.
I detect heightened stress.
Indicated by cortisol
and crackers.
-What's with the crackers?
-He's a guilt eater.
What did you do?
I told Richardson that
I'm a member of Big Hero 6!
Ah! Crackers on my face!
Crackers on my face!
Wait. You what?
I know. I'm sorry. I broke
superhero rule number one.
I'm a disgrace,
and I deserve to be punished.
I don't deserve
a cushion, Baymax.
Wait, wait, wait. Fred, what
exactly does Richardson know?
Oh, I know a lot of things.
If Fred's in Big Hero 6,
that means so are you.
You. You.
-You.
-Hello.
And you.
Dream Girl...
just got dreamier.
Ugh. Dream on.
Yeah, we're not--
You're not going
to tell anybody, right?
If people knew,
it would be dangerous.
"If people knew,
it would be dangerous."
Seriously, Richardson,
you have to keep it a secret.
Sure, sure, a secret.
My lips are sealed.
-But...
-I knew there'd be a but!
-I want something in return.
-What?
To go on a date with--
No way. Not happening.
Go ahead. Tell everyone.
Fine. It was worth a try.
-But...
-Ooh, I knew
there'd be another but!
Oh, there are
a lot more buts, Fred.
"I want Fred's first edition
of   The Human Fist,
"his entire
Captain Fancy collection,
and his limited edition
Dr. Slaughter action figure."
No way! You can't--
-Done.
-Fine.
-Take it.
-Okay.
Wait, what?
Okay. You can have
all of Fred's stuff
as long as you keep
our identities a secret.
- Wait!
- Goodbye.
No wait, Fred.
You make a mess,
you clean it up.
I hate when you're right!
Hello, Juniper.
Don't "Hello, Juniper" me.
Where is it?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Tell me where it is. Now!
You wanna dance?
Ah!
♪ You might think I'm done
Let's dance.
I think that song's
a little tired, don't you?
♪ You choke up on the phone
♪ You end up all alone
It's a classic!
Classic's just another word
for old, Mother!
Did you just call me old?
Hey!
Mind your own business, buddy!
This is my business!
I'm Joe!
If you think for one minute
that I won't get to it
before you,
then you're wrong.
So wrong!
It's cute that
you think so, little girl.
What a mess.
But what a performance.
Mmm.
Release attention.
All right, Richardson.
You got everything you wanted.
Now just leave us alone.
Actually, I thought
of something else I want.
I want to be one of you.
What?
A member of Big Hero 6.
-What?
-Bad idea.
-Uh-uh.
-Nope.
Ha-ha. No.
Fine.
Wait, what is he doing?
Who is he calling?
Hey, Bluff,
Richardson Mole here.
Yeah, I've got
a big scoop for you.
I know the real identities of--
Yeah, sorry about that, Bluff.
I got cut--
Hey, Bluff--
Yeah, sorry about that--
Richardson Mole here--
Okay, fine.
I'll make you a battle suit.
That's what I thought.
Hiro, no. You can't make Mole
a battle suit.
I don't have a choice.
People can't know
who we really are.
What power do you want?
Hmm? I want to breathe fire.
But that's my thing!
Yeah, well, I think
I can do it better.
- Cracker?
- Thank you!
Check it out, everybody.
Much better than Fred's suit,
thanks to a few changes
I dictated to Hiro.
-I changed the color story...
-Uh-huh.
...increased the force and
trajectory of the fire blast,
and I added cup holders.
Whatever, mine's still--
Should have thought
of cup holders.
Oh-ho-ho.
Mole power punch!
Hyah! Ho!
I am awesome.
Battle cry!
Just be careful, okay.
It's a powerful suit and--
Please. If Fred can do this,
I can certainly do it.
- Fire blast!
- Richardson, no!
Not the topiaries!
Fire.
Please step back.
Okay, that's it--
High Voltage.
- We've got to suit up.
- Yes!
My first superhero mission!
We are Big Hero 7!
How you doing
back there, Richardson?
This is really high!
Right there!
Wasabi, you see her?
Yep.
Nuh-uh. No buttons.
Go Go!
♪ Come on, here we go
♪ We're headed to the show
Wasabi, watch out!
Okay, that button I like.
♪ Wow!
♪ Wow! Wow!
This is real.
This is happening.
It's Big Hero 6!
Seven!
Ugh! Get off me!
♪ What do you need to know?
♪ Bubble-up, bubble-up
♪ Come on, here we go
Oh, no.
Baymax!
♪ What do you need to know?
♪ Bubble up, bubble up
What was that?
Five, six, seven, eight!
Oh, hello, Mother.
Guess they made up.
Or not.
I thought I told you
to stay out of my way.
You also told me to make my bed,
and I didn't do that, either!
Got it!
Oh, no, you don't!
- Comic book store!
- My store?
Why are they going in there?
I don't know. But we still have
a lot of problems out here.
Fred and I are on it.
All right. Be cool, okay.
Out of my way.
Who would do
such a horrible thing?
Villains, that's who.
Filthy villains!
-Wait, I don't like you.
-I don't like you either!
Boys, focus.
We need to find High Voltage.
The Mole Hole.
Oh, no, you don't.
Juniper, give me
the orb right now!
After the way
you betrayed me! Never!
Ha!
Guess we know
what they're looking for.
Hey, Go Go,
you were right. Wait--
- Why do you have that?
- For the museum!
Obvi!
I will not ask you again.
And I will never
trust you again!
That move is mine.
You stole it!
Gotta be honest, your tap
is a little sloppy, ladies.
Richardson!
Never insult the bad guys
in an enclosed space.
Especially you.
Shuffle-hop-step?
More like shuffle-hot-mess.
For your information,
the move is called
the "Power Surge,"
and Juniper does it perfectly.
Whoa!
Oh! That could have been me.
Yeah. So stay down.
You really think
I do it perfectly?
Of course I do.
But then, why did you steal it?
Because... I can't do
my move anymore.
My extension just isn't
what it used to be.
Aww, you could
have just told me.
I was embarrassed.
And I thought you wouldn't want
to crime-dance with me anymore.
But we're a team.
Every move I have,
I learned from you!
Oh, come here.
I love you, Mom.
I love you too.
♪ But always in my heart
♪ Whoa, whoa
♪ This time is forever
♪ Forever together...
That's why I think it's time
we got the team back together.
♪ Let's get our acts together
♪ Never say never
♪ But forever together
♪ We could be
♪ Together forever
♪ Together forever...
What are you doing?
Not... crying.
Get it together.
We need a plan.
They're charging up
to full power with that thing.
I've got an idea.
Um, what are you thinking?
Cut them off from the orb.
-Ah.
-Ready?
Ready!
Together, we're High Voltage!
Power Surge!
♪ High Voltage
You probably should've kept
these as backup.
Oh, Mom, are we
going back to jail?
At least we'll be
together, baby.
Woman up.
Fred, wait!
What now, Richardson?
I just wanted to say thank you.
For saving me.
You've never been nice to me.
I'm not sure what
I'm supposed to do here.
Ugh, don't make it awkward.
Okay. You're welcome.
Ah.
Does this mean you're going
to keep our secret?
No way. I'm totally
going public with this.
I've already got
an exclusive interview tomorrow
with Good Morning,
San Fransokyo.
Now if you don't mind, I'll be
taking the orb to my new museum.
Richardson, don't!
Hello.
On a scale of one to ten,
how would you rate your pain?
I'm not in any pain.
Why are you guys here?
High Voltage attacked
your store...
Wait, was Big Hero 6 here?
W-W-Where are they?
-You don't remember?
-Remember what?
Fred revealed to you that
we are all members of Big--
Uh-- Uh-- Big, uh--
Big nothing.
One big nothing!
He doesn't remember.
Perhaps the unique
nature of the orb's power
caused memory loss.
Okey-dokey,
let's go with that.
Hey, buddy.
Need a hand?
Pfft. Not from you, loser.
Excuse me, but I just--
Staying calm.
- You just what?
- Do not engage.
Do not engage.
Anyone have any crackers?