NARRATOR: When a
travelerin north central Louisiana
takes a wrong fork at
thejunction of Boudreaux Road,
just beyond Thibodeau's
Corners, he comes
upon a lonely, curious country.
[music playing]
Here sits the Whateley house,
a cold, desolate place.
Hundreds of years ago,
whenthe talk of voodoo and Satan
worship was commonplace,
thelocals would warn strangers
to stay far, far away.
It was here, 10 years ago,
that the unimaginable happened,
the unspeakable.
Athena Whateley.
She was 35 years old.
She did nothing to
hide her pregnancy
to others in that small town.
She never spoke of
the child [inaudible]..
Some conjectured that OldMan Whateley,
her father,
was responsible
for her pregnancy.
Those wounds were too sinister,
even for this small town.
Any reference to such
a strange family.
[screaming]
I see it.
Here it comes, Logan.
[screaming]
[baby crying]
It's a boy.
He... he beautiful.
Yes, dear.
[music playing]
[screaming]
[inaudible]
[cackling]
[music playing]
[thunder]
[woman crying]
WOMAN: Why is this happening?
I want my baby back.
It's gonna be OK.
[crying]
Father?
PRIEST: It's all right.
It's all right.
The cut isn't bad.
I'll go.
PRIEST: No way.
It's too... too powerful.
If I can't do anything,
there's little that you can do.
I can try.
[knocking at door]
PRIEST: Dr. Alridge, thank God.
It's much worse
than when I called.
This is my
associate, Dr. Morgan.
Good evening.
May I ask you how long
you've owned this house?
Two months.
She started acting
strangeright after we moved in.
She's home on a
break from college,
and we were just hoping
tospend some time with her.
Can you help us?
Her room... was it
always a bedroom?
Or was it an attic?
WOMAN: It was an attic.
We just added a wall and
made it into her room.
How much renovation?
Uh, we added new
flooring and dry wall.
What does all of this haveto
do with what's going on?
This house was built
by a Silas Brown,
a well-known practitioner of
theoccult and a demon worshipper.
DR. MORGAN: Chances
are good that he
built something into the
roomto assist in his sorcery.
DR. ALDRIDGE: And he
left something behind.
Does the entity have a name?
Yes.
[inaudible]
Splendid.
And give us 30 minutes.
If we don't come out,
spread the contents of this
over the entire doorway.
What is it?
Just do as I ask.
PRIEST: Dr, you may want
to keep that jacket on.
I'm just a simple girl.
I just want to be left alone.
I just want to
play with my toys.
I'll handle this.
Try and find it.
So what's your name?
Caitlin.
DR. ALDRIDGE: Oh,
well, that's a quaint
name for a 60,000-year-oldalien demon.
The gates are about to open.
And I'll be the
first [inaudible]..
Well,
don't get toocomfortable because you're
going right back.
[laughter]
Almost.
Got it.
No!
[pounding noise]
[music playing]
Sumerian ritual pyramid.
5,000 years old.
[child laughing]
The pyramid!
[music playing]
Ipsil.
You all right, Faye?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
Top section always clockwise.
Got it.
Won't happen again.
Sure hope not.
Someone or something
has opened a portal.
We have to close it.
So after reviewing
chapter 10, what
is the difference
between the Cthulu
cults of ancientMesopotamia in comparison
to the other polytheiticreligions
of similar cultures
during the Iron Age?
Ms. Badish?
No?
Mr. Jones?
Bryce, the only person
who seems to care.
The Cthulhu deities
were all evil,
unlike the Egyptians
and Greeks, who were
benevolent and malevolent gods.
That's correct.
Also, in James
Garland's book, he
hypothesizes that
these gods were
actually extraterrestrials,
and primitive man...
Yes, but that conversationis for next week.
Also,
most cultures wentto their gods in the sky
or on mountains, whereas
the Cthulhu [inaudible]
living under the ocean.
Thank you, Bryce.
And that's what they
called [inaudible]..
Bryce, that's quite enough.
Thank you.
Well, I guess it's
about that time,
so as our friend
Bryce alluded to,
let's discuss chapter one
ofDr. Garland's book next week.
Thank you.
Have a good day.
Pardon me, Dr. Rice...
Bryce, office
hours are on Tuesday.
I have an appointment today, OK?
I'll have your schedule
by 10:00 AM tomorrow.
All right.
That is not dead
which can eternal lie.
Strange eons even death may die.
Yeah.
It's so good to see you.
Same here, my good friend.
It's been too long.
Yes, it has.
We should grab a
coffee... catch up.
What brings you all
the way up here?
Oh, well, we brought
you another piece
for the collection.
We?
Hello, Walter.
Hi, Faye.
So you want to see the piece?
WALTER: Definitely Sumerian.
I'd put this at about 2000 BC.- 3000.
Look at the markings.
I did.
These markings are
consistentwith pre-Babylonian,
late first dynasty.
But at first glance, at
the second tier glyphs...
He's the linguistic expert.
Let him do the analysis, Faye.
And just as Dr.
Garland suggested,
articulated subsections.
Have you tried to move them?
No!
No, stop!
[music playing]
[SINGING] If it's broken,
please don't fix it.
If it hurts, then
you can kill it.
Gotta stretch my legs.
Wow, these are old.
There's not even a
credit card terminal.
I'll go pay inside.
All right, baby.
Hey, I'll probably get a soda.
You want something?
- Yeah, sure.
Just a water.
OK.
Hey, let's go ahead and fill up.
We've still got three
hours to Houston.
You got it, hot stuff.
Do you have a bathroom?
Thanks.
Hey.
Bathroom.
Save me that key, baby.
Now I gotta go.
[muffled shouting]
Yo.
[laughter] Yeah, man.
We got about three
or four hours left.
Yeah, it's brutal, man.
The I-10's all torn up.
Yeah, we'll be seeing ya.
Well... Yeah, all right.
That's great.
With all due respect,
weare all far too educated
to believe that this mythology,
this archeology that we've
studied our entire
lives is real.
You don't have to believe.
Obtaining the book and
helping us translate it
would be quite the
feather in your cap.
It's because of truebelievers
like the two of you
that securing the Necronomicon
would be extremely
difficult, if not impossible.
It's hidden.
And wherever it's hidden,
it's protected by cultists
and religious fanatics.
So even if you
did find it, you'd
probably be killed beforeyou
could ever bring it back.
A portal has been
opened between our world
and the realm of the old.
With them come chaos
and destruction.
Why do you need it?
There are several translations.
I have one.
There's one in BuenosAires,
there's one in Paris.
All of them are incomplete.
Page 751.
Every copy,
every translationis missing page 751.
That page contains
theincantations needed to open
the portal, and to close it.
Only the original has page 751.
But I just don't see that...
At the very least,
it's animportant piece of history.
Whoever retrieves it willbe
showered in accolades.
Not to mention all
the research grants.
And the press.
OK.
I see where the two of
you are going with this.
We'll have to compare notes.
Nobody's even seen the
original since John
Dee translated it in 1603.
Then we start at 1603.
[static]
We're gonna have a party, Agnes.
It's my boys' birthdays,
and they're coming home.
[laughter] We're gonna
getpretty pretty for my baby.
[laughter] I can't
wait to see my baby.
Shut up!
Just shut up!
Wilbur's home.
Wilbur!
Wilbur's home!
[laughter]
Hello, Mother.
Oh, whatcha got there?
A present for your brother?
Yes.
[laughter]
[screaming]
Well done, boy.
Take care of your brother.
Shh.
Soon it'll be all over for you.
[demonic whispering]
[screaming]
[demonic screaming]
This indicates that
Dee gave the original
to the Anglican church.
Well, that would explain this.
An unnamed book with
great significance
kept by the Knights
Templar in Scotland.
Well, that was until
theylost that in a fire in 1789.
A fire that was most
likely a diversion
to steal the real book.
Well, where'd it go?
America.
Taken here by a group
knownas the Black Brotherhood?
Oh.
Olas Wormius.
The Dutch alchemist?
Yes.
He translated the book
beforeJohn Dee translated the book.
What are you thinking?
Ask him.
He'll know.
And how do we do that?
A seance, or a psychic?
According to my calculations,
he died 700 years ago.
He explained to me thetrue
history of the old ones.
The secret cults that
have existed forever.
He claimed to have been
bornduring the Shang dynasty.
Please.
That would make him
over 3,000 years old.
OK, far be it for me to guessthat
he's really in his mid 60s
somewhere.
Where?
Well, the last time I sawhim
was in southern Louisiana.
He was overseeing
avoodoo cult in the Bayou.
What would he know?
He knew about the brotherhood,
and for a time he was a member.
Yeah, he knows their secrets.
Well, it sounds like as gooda
place as any to start to me.
You're gonna need this.
I'm going to stay behind
andtry and figure out who or what
is behind all this,
sowhen you obtain the book,
well, we'll know
where to use it.
Pick me up?
10?
Mm.
Same place?
Do you live alone?
I'd hate for it to
be awkward, and all.
Wait outside.
I'll come out.
You two kids are
going to be fine.
Six years is a long time.
You know, people move on.
Sometimes.
Are you going to be all right?
Dealing with him?
Well, our personal
history is just that.
History.
I'm more concerned
aboutinvolving him in general.
Well, he's the only one that can
translate the original text.
But he doesn't believe.
His believing is irrelevant.
Once he translates it,
I'll perform the ritual.
But they... they
prey on nonbelievers.
Remember what
happened to Darelith?
Well, before longhe'll see it for himself.
Then we'll be glad to
have him on our side.
Let's just hope he doesn'tgive
up before we get that far.
The time is close, boy.
Seven days until
your 10th birthday.
You know what that means?
Yes.
You been practicing
for the big day?
I will be ready.
Henry paid me a visit yesterday.
Henry Armitage?
In the flesh.
Was she with him?
Yes.
She was.
What do they want?
Shame I missed them.
I would have loved
to have said hello.
- You would have?
- No.
Not really.
What did they want?
Well, they brought me
anew piece for the collection.
It's a Samaritan ritual pyramid.
It's quite nice, really.
And they also asked
for me to help
them find the Necronomicon.
Well, what did you tell them?
I said I would help.
Why?
I don't know.
You're just feeding
their delusions.
It's not healthy.
- I know.
I know.
It's an important
piece of history.
Yeah, well, some relics
are best left buried.
The missing pages.
There is a copy at the
University in Arkham.
I will steal it.
Good.
Henry was going on abouta portal,
or something.
He said that all thecopies
of the Necronomicon
are missing page 751.
Only the original
has that page, so...
And page 751 contains the spells
and incantations necessary
toopen and close said portal?
Precisely.
Why do you know that?
We took a trip
to, uh, New England.
To a small town called
Innsmouth, I believe.
A seaside village.
The trip seemed innocuousenough at first,
but I soon realized thatHenry
was up to something.
You should go.
Fetch it now.
Yes.
Who is going to feed him?
He needs to grow.
I'll Have your worthlessmother
do it while you're away.
Give her a reason to
continue to breathe.
There was a cult there,
that Henry was trying to stop.
A cult attempting to opena
portal between our world
and the world of the old ones.
It was a very complex
and detailed ritual.
It was quite the big deal.
Here, you see... first theyhad
to find a willing female...
A woman to give
birth to these twins.
One of the twins would
be human, the other
would be an inhuman
manifestation
of the god Yog-Sothoth.
[chanting]
It means for the twins,
10 years shall be 40.
Yes.
One of the cultists
was going on about how
these twins would age rapidly.
So if you run into
any40-year-olds with the intellect
of a child, you be careful.
Wilbur?
Yes, Pa?
We have many enemies.
Mankind cannot
comprehendthe new world order.
I know.
When the planet
isliberated by the old ones,
only the true believerswill
prosper in the new age.
Mind your steps, boy.
I'll find a way, Grandpa.
Or I'll make a way.
Once this inhumanchild grows large enough,
it holds open the portal for thelarger,
more powerful old ones
to enter our world.
And thereby starting
the apocalypse.
The original cult was lookingfor
the Necronomicon, as well.
They were trying
to find a man named
Olas Wormius to help them.
That's interesting.
Henry set up an
appointment for me
to meet with him
later this evening.
I tried to tell him
that the real Olas
has been dead for
over 700 years,
but he didn't believe me.
It's also quite
convenient that he only
lives four hours north of here.
But they're convinced
that he's legitimate.
Those two areconvinced of quite a bit.
Indeed, they are.
Do me a favor.
Be careful.
These cultists,
they... takethis stuff very seriously.
You're quite
cavalier with people,
if you don't mind me saying,
so just watch your step.
I'll be careful.
Ah... can I borrow these?
Well, they're part of
my private collection.
[inaudible] I will
take care of them.
I'll guard them with my life.
All right.
Just be very careful with them.
Thank you.
- Lunch on Monday?
- Yes.
Yes, yes.
[footsteps]
Where is she, freak?
Where is she?
Who?
Amanda!
You were the only other
personthere when she disappeared,
man.
Where is she?
Stop!
She's inside.
I will take you to her.
Brandy?
Oh, good!
Company!
[laughter]
Shut up!
Upstairs.
After you.
The both of you!
Now!
[laughter]
God!
No!
[screaming]
Go upstairs, boy.
She's waiting for you.
What the...
[screaming]
You're late.
I'm sorry.
I thought I was early.
Well, when we were together,
you were never ready on time.
You were usually a
minimumof 15 minutes late.
So I gave you the
benefit of the doubt
and showed up 10
minutes after we agreed.
This is going to be
a long drive, isn't it?
I never said that.
If you didn't,
why wouldit be burned into my memory?
I don't know.
Overactive imagination?
Delusions?
You're brilliant, Fay.
You're brilliant.
Dr. Armitage is a
wonderful man, and I
think he's a great
teacher, but you're
following him into his cult.
It's not a cult.
It's not?
I thought you were
smarter than that.
You haven't seen
what we've seen.
You turned your back
on us before the truth
could be revealed.
The truth?
It's mythology, Fay.
It's legends and storiesfrom
prehistoric dreamers
and science fiction authors.
It's not real.
- Believe what you want.
I know...
I know what's out there.
I know what we
must do, and I know
the consequences if we fail!
That's why we didn't work.
You lost all
respect, because you
think you're smarter than us.
I just always found
your relationship
with Dr. Armitage...
Atypical.
Do you think we slept together?
Me and Henry?
WOMAN: Ah... uh-uh.
I can't do it without you.
Grandpa said you
would have to do it.
WOMAN: Ah... I'm...
I've been here
since you were born.
You can't leave
me here with him.
I'm afraid!
There's nothing to be afraid of.
This is it.
This is where we start.
[bell ringing]
Can I help y'all?
We're here to see Olas.
Ah.
No Olas here.
I sell bait and crawfish,
when the season is right.
Armitage sent us.
He gave me this to give to you.
It's, uh...
I know what it is.
The question is do
y'all know what it is?
Where y'all asking to go?
What y'all asking to see?
We have a question for Olas.
We need to speak to him.
Olas answers allquestions with the truth.
Look within.
You'll find all the
answers you need.
Please.
We've given you what
you need to take us.
Out back there's a little boat.
Take it.
Paddle upstream.
North.
How far north?
You'll know.
OK, great.
Thank you.
Oh, Christ.
I think that Yoda back
therewas a little over-dramatic.
Well, you said yourself,
people believe in this.
They'll protect it.
Try and scare us away.
When I was six, I
stopped going to church.
I told my mother that I was
sickof hearing about virgin births,
and burning bushes,
and a godthat would condemn a good man
who doesn't believe
while welcoming
a mass murderer who repents.
Some blind, Creole
crawfish peddler's
not going to change my mind.
Sometimes you have to
believein things you can't see.
There are higher truths.
Fay, as much as I love you,
you can't convince me, either.
What?
I don't think in the sixyears
that we were together,
you ever once said
that you loved me.
Of course I did.
Didn't I?
[suspenseful music playing]
Dr. Rice.
Dr. Morgan.
We have been expecting you.
Pick up.
Come on, pick it up.
This is Henry.
Now listen...
There's a connection
between the girl's
family from the exorcism
and a Puritan era
cult near Dunwich.
And the girl is a
direct descendant.
She's coming down
here to meet with me,
so call me with an update...
Can I help you?
Dr. Rice?
No, I'm Dr. Armitage.
Dr. Rice.
Is away on business.
Can I take a message?
Maybe you can help me.
Dr. Rice is the curator
ofthe Antiquities Collection,
is he not?
Yes.
I'm looking for a
book in his library.
A book?
Which book?
I'll know it when I see it.
Well... I'm not
really very familiar
with the surroundings here.
Uh, books... book, book, book.
Would it be one of these?
No?
Uh...
Uh... What's your name, friend?
Whateley.
Wilbur Whateley.
Oh, yeah.
OK.
I think I might
know where they are.
Why don't you follow me?
Please enter.
Sit.
The master shall be here soon.
I think we're wasting our time.
Shh.
The master OlasWormius will see you now.
Oh.
Good.
There are a great manybooks here,
Mr. Whateley.
It might help if you
could describe it to me.
[sigh]
[sniffling]
[inaudible]
[sniffing]
There.
You're not going to find it.
That's a copy.
Like yours.
There's no page 751.
Where is the original?
I don't have it.
It's you.
You opened the portal.
What do you know of such things?
You summoned Yog-Sothoth.
He holds the door
open for the others.
Yes.
It grows.
Grows strong enough to
holdit open for the old ones.
Where?
Help me find the book.
I'm like you.
I'm a member of the brotherhood.
Then... you will help me?
Brother.
Where is it?
I will not tell you.
I will take you.
[wheezing]
Air.
I need my air.
All my life you've been
telling me I'm no good.
I can't do anything.
I need my air.
Boy needs to be fed.
Boy needs to be fed!
I can't leave!
What's wrong with you?
Well, he's gonna get fed!
What are you doing?
Come and get it, boy!
What?
Oh... no, no, no!
No!
[shouting]
[screaming]
[roaring]
[laughter]
[sigh]
Welcome.
It's quite the entrance, sir.
Olas.
Dr. Armitage...
I know why you are here.
You seek the book.
The book that is hidden.
The book that should
never be found.
[inaudible]
That's right.
With the old ones comes chaos.
They are not of our world.
They lie in sleep,
waiting to return.
To plunge mankind into madness.
Someone has opened a portal.
The old ones are attemptingto
come into this world.
Now.
We must stop them.
I know.
I have seen them.
Cthulhu.
Speaks to me in dreams.
Warns me of the
impending apocalypse.
Begging me to unfree him.
Did he happen to mentionwhere
we might find the book?
For centuries the book
was in my possession.
It was stolen from me by
the Black Brotherhood.
Later it fell into
the hands of a witch.
A witch who escaped
persecutionduring the Salem Witch Trials.
That witch's descendant...
a man came Ward...
Now holds the book.
100 Prospect Road.
Do you have a zip code for that?
So I can type it
into my MapQuest?
No, never mind.
I'm sorry.
Can we go?
Thank you.
The house is not
what you expect.
I'm not surprised.
Thank you.
You do not believe, Dr. Rice.
No.
Good.
Remember that when
you are inside.
[laughter]
I can't believe you
were unaffected by that.
I can't believe that you were.
I've seen much better
acts on the Vegas strip.
The man levitated into the room.
That's called a parlor trick.
You know, using
rational thought, Fay,
you can explain the most
extraordinary things.
You're very cold.
I'm very practical.
Very practical.
Do you have faith in anything?
Yes.
Nothing from Armitage.
I hope he's made some progress.
I hope we make some progress.
I have this strange
feeling we're
going to run into anotheridiot
speaking gibberish
with grave seriousness.
What?
What time do you have?
I don't.
It stopped.
Mine, too.
He is here.
Yog-Sothoth knows the gate.
Yog-Sothoth is the gate.
Yog-Sothoth is the
keyand guardian of the gate.
Past, present, and future.
All are one in Yog-Sothoth.
He knows where the
oldone broke through a void.
And there they will
break through again.
This one looks rather inviting.
It's charming, really.
Don't bet on it.
Shall we?
Hello?
OK, let's split up.
You should take upstairs.
No.
We should stay together.
OK.
What did he say to you,
right before we left?
He said that it was
goodthat I didn't believe.
I wonder what he meant by that?
Nothing.
He meant nothing.
It was actually meant tobe
more spooky mumbo jumbo.
Well, we're wasting
a lot of time.
Old relics are found
buriedin caves and dig sites,
not sitting in an empty
old bed and breakfast.
It's not what we expect.
Oh?
Mr. Ward?
[shouting]
Well, that's going to takeme
a little longer to explain.
Who this?
He's here to help us.
I like him.
Quiet, Mother.
What... happened to Grandpa?
He, um... he, um...
He gave himself to
feed your brother.
He would not do that.
He... he... he did.
That was not the plan.
He... he changed the plan.
He said you'd understand.
You...
I didn't have a choice.
I can't leave.
How dare you?
He was gonna kill me, Wilbur.
He was gonna kill your mama!
[shouting]
We've already gone
up three flights.
I know.
I swear this house only
hadtwo stories when we came in.
Look at this hallway.
It goes on forever.
I see a light.
I don't need you.
You will be next.
[shouting]
Al Hazared.
The author of the Necronomicon.
Remarkable.
Come here.
Help me.
The door's not there anymore.
We're trapped.
[inaudible]
[shouting]
Don't come any closer, boy.
I am not afraid.
[shouting]
[gunshot]
Wilbur?
[roaring]
Oh, Wilbur!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean it, Wilbur.
I'm so sorry.
Wilbur!
[gasping]
[shouting]
[pounding]
[gasping]
I'm so sorry!
Mama didn't mean it.
I'm so sorry, baby.
Mister, you ain't gonna
shoot me now, are ya?
[gunshot]
[shouting]
I'm sorry.
It's OK.
I shouldn't have left you.
Walter... I love you.
[inaudible].
Wait.
[laughter]
We never left the bayou.
Wait, wait, we never
left the bayou.
It's not real.
Focus.
Think!
OK.
It's not real.
So why are we still here?
He said that the old onesspeak
to him in dreams, right?
Right.
We're in a dream.
The book is hidden
in this house.
What?
We can't just make it
appear in front of us.
No.
We can't take the
book from the dream.
The book doesn't exist.
It never did.
That's why there
isn't an original.
The house is the book.
The house the book.
Help me.
[inaudible]
Go.
Over here.
It's gonna be over there.
It's over there.
[coughing]
[groaning]
Hm.
So, Dr. Rice,
now do you believe?
Ask me when this is over.
[laughter]
[ringing]
Fay?
Henry?
We have it.
We're on our way to you.
Are you still at the university?
It's... it's worse
than we expected.
I'm going to try and
dosomething to slow it down.
I'm still here.
I'll wait for you.
Right.
We're on our way.
[creature groaning]
[creature roaring]
[roaring]
Henry?
Dr. Armitage?
He said he would be here.
Call him.
Find out where he went.
Ah!
Straight to voicemail.
Hello?
Caitlin?
What are you doing here?
Dr. Armitage called me.
He said he had some
questionsabout my great grandfather.
What's your last name?
Bowers.
[roaring]
[shouting]
This makes no sense.
I mean, it's not
like him to do this.
Something is amiss.
He fully intended to be here.
Someone or something
drew him from here.
Yeah, but where?
I don't know.
Amelia?
Can you bring me the
security log, please?
Anyone after hours,
anybodywho listed me as a contact.
Uh, just one.
A Whateley?
Whateley.
[whispering] Does the
nameWhateley mean anything to you?
No.
Should it?
This is a list of the occultists
and the families tied to
theold ones over the centuries.
So a Mr. Whateley
came to the office
last week to visit Dr. Armitage?
No.
He came here to see me.
To get this.
Grab your things.
Let's go.
Directions.
Wow.
He's good.
Yeah.
He is.
[creature growling]
[rattling]
I need you to drive
while I study this.
You got it.
What is she doing here?
Well,
the old ones speakthrough family lineage.
They spoke through
her grandfather,
and now they speak through her.
Yeah.
And it could be useful.
Are you sure you
want to do this?
24 hours ago I
was convinced this
was all a big heaping pile of...
Nonsense.
I felt that way 24 hours ago.
So?
I've seen things
that I can't explain.
I've experienced things
faroutside the realm of normal,
and if any of it is
true, or even if it's
partly true, what we're
about to experience
is not for the squeamish.
Dr. Rice, I was possessed.
Now, I don't remember much ofit,
but from what they told me,
I had bat wings
growing out of my back.
So I'm down.
Fine.
I've got shotgun.
You remember anything, Caitlin?
Not a lot.
I mean... I rememberthings
before it happened.
Such as?
CAITLIN [VOICEOVER]: Well,
I started sleepwalking.
I would walk outside,
into the yard.
I drew things on the ground.
Circles.
Circles with symbols.
The... the symbols
alwayspointed towards the east.
And I remember the night
before it happened,
I made circles in myfront yard,
and something
happened that never
happened before And I
remember a poem... a song.
Yom sureth, yom
azereth, yom belereth.
Yom turkis, yom derth. OK,
that's enough of that.
But remember that.
The poem is an incantation.
We're going to need it.
It says there's a road0.2
miles up on our left.
But... I don't see it anywhere.
MapQuest is never wrong.
Maybe it's a private road?
There!
[shouting]
Doctor!
Henry!
I saw it.
I saw its face.
Can you hear me?
- It looked at me.
- It's OK.
It's... No, it was inside my head!
We're here.
It showed me everything.
He's in shock.
[coughing]
I know.
Oh, god, I know.
Come on, Henry.
Let's stand up.
Caitlin, get a blanket.
Henry?
Henry.
Where did it go?
Oh, it's gone.
To the world.
What is it?
I can't say.
I can't speak its name.
When you first
came to me, you said
that a portal had been opened.
Yes.
The guardian.
The gate keeper is Yog-Sothoth?
Is that who you saw?
Yog-Sothoth controls and
holdsopen the gates for the others.
He has to grow until
he's large enough
to hold open the gates for
eventhe greatest of the old ones.
Did you see that ceiling?
I mean, it looks pretty big.
No.
You're not getting it.
He can't open the portal.
Someone from our
world has to open it.
That's why Whateley
wanted the book.
He was going to open the portal.
So the question
is where did he go?
Well, maybe he went home?
He can't.
The woman said it...
Was Wilbur's brother.
Her son.
He can't go home.
He is home.
[thunder]
No.
Now it's home.
We're going to open the portal.
What?
Just long enough for
it to take its position.
Try and hold it open.
Walter, if we open the portal...
I know what the book says.
That's why we have to close
itbefore anything else comes out.
If we open the portal, then...
Then the older,
stronger godsare gonna come into our world.
We'll be powerless.
I was wrong not to believe you.
I should have trusted
youand Henry this entire time.
I was arrogant, and jealous.
And I don't know what else,
but it blinded me to something
that I always knew was true.
Now I'm asking you...
Believe me.
We can do this.
How?
Henry isn't strong
enough to fight.
I mean... he knows
the ins and outs.
The incantations.
He has experience.
And I've spent my
entirelife alone in a library,
obsessed with their books.
I know them, too.
I know they can be defeated.
He's right.
We have to try.
Caitlin!
Do you remember those
circle drawings?
- Yeah.
- Good.
As soon as we get
outside, I need
you to make one large
enoughfor all four of us to stand in.
As long as we're in thecircle,
we should be safe.
[warbling]
Yog-Sothoth!
Yog-Sothoth, tu ra nan.
Yog-Sothoth, tu ra nan!
Yog-Sothoth!
[roaring]
Help me!
Don't let it take me!
I'm not gonna let it take you!
Help me!
Don't let go!
Dad!
[chanting]
[roaring]
Now...
[chanting]
Fay?
[shouting]
[chanting]
Don't let go, Fay.
[shouting]
[chanting]
[screaming]
[creature roaring]
Oh, god.
Excuse me?
Professor?
I was wondering if I
couldschedule some time with you
during your office hours?
Actually,
my office hoursare all booked up this week.
Dinner tonight, perhaps?
Oh... I don't know.
It hardly seems professional.
No, I guess it's
not very professional.
7:00?
Hm... Perfect.
I'll see you at 7:15.
Today we're going
todiscuss the concept of faith.
Faith is a belief
in power or powers
that can actually
alter human destiny.
What?
Dr. Rice, do you
believe in such a power?
Yes.
Yes, I do.
[music playing]