- Boss...
- Something happened.
What's wrong?
You'll have the item today,
just like we agreed.
It's as good as in your hands.
- Nothing can go wrong.
- You contemptible canine.
Don't call me canine.
- Do you know what patience means?
- Silence!
As long as dogs are involved,
anything can go wrong.
I'll take that as a no.
Jeez, what a hothead.
Eh... Keep your quarter.
I am proud to present this
special token to our dear...
Only in heaven
can a bunch of squeaky-clean angels
get awards
for being extra squeaky-clean.
And now, our final honoree,
voted Most Rehabilitated
by our heavenly jury.
He's a dog who is...
Wouldn't be caught dead wearing
one of those merit badges, eh, Carface?
Hey. Sh!
A dog who's lifted himself up
from the depths of depravity,
who proves that every dog deserves
a second chance in heaven.
Now I know why they call it eternity.
- Everything here takes forever.
- Sh!
Charlie, show some respect.
For making the most
of what he's had to work with,
this first-class, diamond-studded,
angel-wing pin goes to...
- ...Carface Caruthers.
- Huh?
What an honor. You're too kind.
I don't know what to say.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Bless you.
I only hope
that our other angels,
who have yet
to distinguish themselves,
soon follow your shining example.
Hey, remember, Charlie,
it never hurts to play the game.
Halo polisher.
Whoa, I'm late.
That feels good.
Yah!
Sorry. Lousy brake pads.
Have the newcomers
touched down yet?
No, not yet.
Put on some weight, huh, Fluffy?
Check. Go ahead, 15.
Check. Move along.
Sorry, sir.
Check. Check. Check. Move along.
That's it. That's all dogs.
Hold it, hold it, let me see that list.
There has to be more.
I'm expecting company.
Uh...
Asta, Bandit, Bowser, Fido, Fifi,
Hound of Baskerville,
Pavlov's dog, Rex, Rover, Rufus,
Shatzi, Spot and...
Itchy! Ho-ho!
Oh, yeah. Right.
He's right here on the list.
- Where am I?
- You old fleabag, you.
Charlie, is that you?
Charlie, it is you. Charlie.
Gee, Itch, you shouldn't have.
Sorry, sir, you can't take it with you.
Wait a minute, ain't you dead?
Oh, yeah,
as a dog that eats chicken bones.
Oh, so that means...
Uh-oh!
Welcome to paradise, Itch.
Come on, I'll show you around.
You can mark your territory.
Hey, wait. Charlie.
Oh, this is...
Well, I never would have imagined.
Look at this.
Hey, Charlie, wait a minute.
I'm not itchy.
That's funny, you sure look like him.
No, I mean...
...for the first time in my life,
I don't need to scratch.
This is heaven, Itch.
Fleas go to the other place.
Hey, Bubba, how about we go down
to Hog Heaven and get us some ribs?
Everybody's flying.
Does that mean me too?
Oh, yeah,
it's all part of the basic package.
I'm gonna like it here,
Charlie.
Believe me, it gets old fast.
Yeah, sure. Ha-ha-ha.
Whoa! Yah! Hoo!
- What do you mean?
- It's hard to explain, Itch.
This joint is supposed
to have everything, to be the best,
but it's just too...
I don't know, it's...
It's too...
♪ It's too heavenly here
♪ It's too peaceful and paradise like
♪ Straight and narrow
and much too nice like
♪ Endlessly sunny and clear
♪ It's too heavenly here
♪ It's too blissful to bear
♪ Calm and quiet and much too mellow
♪ All my brain cells
have turned to Jell-O
♪ Every day feels like a year
♪ It's too heavenly here
♪ I need some action
I need some juice
♪ That crazy kind of feeling of
Playing fast and loose
♪ Some razzle-dazzle
and a little stress and strife
♪ I gotta get some life in my life
♪ But it's too heavenly here
♪ There's no way you can be a sinner
♪ Roll the dice
Everyone's a winner
♪ It's so legit and sincere
♪ It's too heavenly here
♪ What good's a hustler without a scam?
♪ I'm wasted talent
That's all that I am
♪ But this operator
is at the wrong address
♪ 'Cause there's nothing to finagle
♪ And no one to finesse
♪ It's so heavenly here
♪ Pure and perfect
Sublime and shining
♪ Every cloud has a silver lining
♪ Everyone's full of good cheer
♪ It's so heavenly here
♪ They're all so saintly
I just can't relate
♪ There's gotta be an exit
through that pearly gate
♪ Behold a canine
who's been cut down in his prime
♪ I may have done the crime
♪ But I can't do the time
♪ 'Cause it's too heavenly here
♪ All hallelujahs and hosannas
♪ It could drive anyone bananas
♪ I'm going out of my head
♪ This joint is deader than dead
♪ I'll give you eight to three
It's too heavenly
♪ Hallelujah!
Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
♪ Too heavenly
♪ Here ♪
Charlie, you gotta see a doctor.
Hm...
Ah!
Ooh!
Baby, you're my ticket
to fame and fortune.
This is not good.
Whoa!
Oh-ho!
Charlie,
you're wrong about this place.
The flying alone
is worth the price of admission.
That's perfect for you, but for me,
there's still something missing.
Ooh! Charlie, look, look.
Quiet, quiet, quiet, everyone.
- I've got terrible news.
- Oh, yeah, the flying nun.
Gabriel's horn has fallen from heaven
and landed on Earth
in the heart of San Francisco.
But without the horn,
the Pearly Gates can't be opened.
- And no more dogs will get into heaven.
- Lucky dogs.
Reginald,
you're our most-decorated angel.
I need you to go back to Earth
- to retrieve it.
- Go back?
Anabelle,
I would consider it a great...
Whoa, time-out.
- I beg your pardon.
- You can't send Reggie.
Just look at him, for heaven's sake.
They got rats down there
bigger than this.
He's right. I'll go.
We're talking the mean streets of Frisco
here, Ace, not Mount Happy-Go-Lucky.
Send me, Ana...
Anabelle, you're gonna need someone
who can zip down there and back
before Big Gabe
finds his horn missing.
Someone who knows the ropes
and the dopes.
- Someone who's...
- Just like you.
Me? Well, I don't know.
I'd have to check with my people
and get back to you.
Aw, what the heck. I'll do it.
Maybe you can do something
besides make a nuisance of yourself.
- Right, right, right. I'll be in touch.
- Hold it.
To find the horn, follow your ears.
It gives off a steady, heavenly tone
that only angels can hear.
Only angels. Got it.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
You're on your own.
I can give you one miracle
to be used only in an emergency.
One per customer. Got it.
Charles, Charles, Charles,
this is serious.
If the horn falls into the wrong hands,
it could mean disaster for us all.
You can count on Charles.
Uh... Just to make sure,
I'm sending Itchy along with you.
Oh, no. But I just got here.
Wait just a sec.
I still have death lag.
I remembered,
I have flying lessons after lunch.
Bring back the horn, Charles,
otherwise there'll be heaven to pay.
Got it.
Look at this mess, Itch.
Trash, exhaust fumes, graffiti.
We are home.
Whoa!
You're telling me.
Halo. Double chili cheeseburger
with onions and pickles.
Charlie, stay.
Look, we find Gabriel's horn, and then
it's straight back to heaven, okay?
What's the hurry, Itch?
- Let's have some fun.
- Charlie, wait. Wiener dog here.
Oh, my legs are short.
Now, let's hear it
for Kiko and his Jazz Mongrels.
They're great, aren't they? Yeah.
- ID?
- I don't need no stinking dog tags.
Oh, a classy place.
They check for worms.
Nice toss, big guy.
♪ Wasn't lookin' for love
but fate throwed me a bone
♪ She walked into my life
like the princess she was
♪ And she didn't have even
a half inch of fuzz
♪ My pals call me crazy
but I couldn't care less
♪ 'Cause I've fallen hard
for an Afghan hairless
Full house.
- Guess that's why they call me Lucky.
- All right, boys, name your game.
Poker, double deuce, 52-card pickup?
I'm just yanking your leash.
Hold that thought.
♪ And she loved my singin'
Said it sounded just... pretty good
Hey, bartender, how about a frosty one
for the Chuckmeister?
Root beer, Itch?
Oh... Huh?
Yo, Sparky.
Hey, what am I, invisible?
I'll just help myself.
Yee-ha!
What?
Charlie, look, we ain't... Ooh!
- We're ghosts.
- Anabelle.
Of all the rotten tricks.
Charles, you've been down
there for almost half an hour.
We're waiting.
Thanks, Jingles.
You really knocked them dead.
And now, let's have a warm round
of applause for our next contestant,
Miss Sasha La Fleur.
♪ If you've got romance on your mind
♪ If you'd like to stroll hand in hand
♪ If you want to cuddle in the moonlight
♪ And whisper, "Ain't love grand?"
♪ If you want someone
♪ To buy that sweet talk
♪ That you guys all love to spout
♪ Baby
♪ Count me out
♪ If you want to dance cheek to cheek
♪ Then go home and talk all night long
♪ If you want to send somebody flowers
♪ And share a stupid song
♪ If you want a woman
♪ Who believes that
♪ You're what her life's all about
♪ Baby
♪ Count me out
♪ I've been there
♪ I've done that
♪ It's nowhere
♪ It's old hat
♪ Forget those thoughts
♪ You're thinking, mister
♪ And just regard me
♪ As your sister
♪ If you want to send valentines
♪ If you want to write poetry
♪ Here's a little change
♪ Go call somebody
♪ Who doesn't look like me
♪ And if you've got plans
to fall in love
♪ Without a shadow
♪ Of a doubt
♪ Baby
♪ Count me out
♪ That's what I said
♪ I said baby
♪ Count me out
♪ Hound dog ♪
Itch, my heart is beating
a million miles an hour.
- I can hardly breathe.
- Maybe it was the change in altitude.
Ooh! My ears popped.
Did your ears pop?
Now I know what I was missing
in heaven.
- I gotta meet her.
- But she can't even see you, Charlie.
- You're an angel.
- Quit reminding me.
You're back in circulation,
huh, Charlie?
Oh, yeah, my circulation's fine.
Hello, Carface. Carface?
I heard you was in the neighborhood.
Yeah, I got time off for good behavior.
What are you doing here?
Missionary work.
Hey, I'll take one of them.
- She can't hear you.
- That'll be two bits, Carface.
- Put it on my tab.
- Huh?
As long as I'm wearing this baby,
I'm flesh and blood.
- Where'd you get it?
- A buddy of mine has them.
- Maybe you could introduce us.
- Charlie, you can't trust Carface.
He shouldn't have got into heaven
in the first place.
My mistake.
I just thought you'd like to meet
the lovely lady.
Hold it, Carface, hold on.
- What about the horn?
- Hey, we'll get it later.
Lead on, pal.
Charlie, wait. Short legs, short legs.
Charlie.
Charlie, wait for me.
How much further here, Carface?
We're... We're almost there.
Charlie. Charlie.
Itchy, you're out of breath
and the fun hasn't even started yet.
Charlie,
I got a bad feeling about this.
Relax. I got it under control.
Boys, we're here.
Hey, Red!
He must be in the back.
Have a look around.
Ah! Whoo!
- Ooh!
- Ah!
- You trying to scare me to death?
- Don't sweat it, pal.
You're already dead.
Itch. Come here.
I want to read your fortune.
- I see you going for a long walk.
- Yeah, on a short leash.
You're in the wrong seat. Move it.
Carface, that's no way
to treat customers.
Red, I'd like you to meet
a couple of friends of mine.
Charlie Barkin, Itchy Itchiford.
- Welcome.
- Wait, wait, how can he...?
Red sees all and knows all.
You got cats around here or what?
Cats? Good heavens, no.
The boys have come
to do a little shopping.
Carface tells us you've got
some special collars.
Collars? Oh, yes.
They're going to be the next big thing.
- Here. Enjoy.
- What's the catch, old man?
No catch. Any friend of Carface
is a friend of mine.
- There is one small thing.
- I knew it. We're out of here.
Right, Charlie?
The collars are only good
until sundown tomorrow.
After that, you'll be, shall we say,
insubstantial again.
By then, I'll have Sasha begging for me.
Yow! Hey! Oof!
Ah. Perfect fit.
Feels great to be back in the flesh.
Infested again.
Ooh! Get off. Everybody, off.
Now, don't forget, sundown tomorrow.
- Hey.
- Hey, Red, I owe you one.
You'll owe me one, all right.
They fell for it!
When we get that horn,
we can open any safe or bank vault
in the world.
Silence!
I didn't recruit you for such
entry-level wickedness.
You have so much to learn.
♪ Now I know you've been malicious
♪ Spiteful and a trifle vicious
♪ It's no secret that you cheated
and you've lied
♪ And you've done some double dealing
Scheming, swindling and stealing
♪ You're an amateur
But heaven knows, you've tried
I answered your ad, didn't I?
"Money, power, stature,
call 1-800-BRIMSTONE."
Good boy. And very soon,
your efforts will be rewarded.
♪ You'll develop so much faster
♪ Now you're working with a master
♪ Who will help you
cultivate your darker side
♪ You'll discover wicked ways
♪ You've never known before
♪ And you'll find that when
you're really rotten to the core
♪ It feels so good to be bad
♪ So delicious to be a despicable cad
♪ It's just so thrilling
and so fulfilling
♪ To give somebody
the worst time they've ever had
♪ It feels so good to be bad
Case in point.
♪ Charlie doesn't know it
but he's in my power
♪ He's gonna wish
that he was never born
♪ I promise you that by the sunset hour
♪ I'll have Gabriel's horn
Boss, why can't I get it for you?
♪ 'Cause you had your chance
and blew it
♪ I entrusted you to do it
♪ But you bungled it
and threw your chance away
♪ It's a problem you created
If the horn can't be located
♪ I'm not naming names
But someone has to pay
I can try again, boss.
You'll never find it. Only angels
can hear its heavenly tone.
- But I'm an angel.
- Not anymore.
- You work for me now.
- Hoo!
Ah! Oof!
♪ Though you gave me cause
to doubt you
♪ There's a loathsomeness about you
That attracts me to you as a protégé
♪ And when you've learned every
creepy crummy thing I know
♪ You'll taste the joy that comes
when you're the lowest of the low
♪ It feels so good to be bad
♪ So delightful to be a deplorable cad
♪ It's so appealing to have the feeling
♪ That what you're doing
gets trouble brewing
♪ And drives everybody mad
♪ You've got my guarantee
♪ It feels so good to be bad
- So exciting!
- So inviting!
♪ So good to be bad ♪
A-ha!
Whoo!
♪ If you got romance
♪ On your mind
- You sing pretty good for a stray.
- Can I have my prize now?
What? You advertised a meal
for the winner.
If it's a meal you want, honey,
I'm off at 10.
Honey, I'd rather eat
out of the garbage.
Hey, that's what I had in mind.
Bonsoir, Frenchie.
It's your lucky night.
Pedigree? You show me yours
and I'll show you mine.
What do you serve
with that shake, baby?
Ah!
This is gonna be fast, right?
We got a horn to find.
Ah. Take notes, Itch.
Ah!
You're about to watch a master.
You must hear this all the time,
but you sing like an angel.
- Excuse me.
- The name's Barkin, Charlie Barkin.
- And you are...?
- Not even remotely interested.
- Oh, that's a mouthful.
- Down, boy.
- Let me help with that.
- I don't want a scene.
- Give me that. No, please.
- It's no problem at all.
Whoops!
Hey, sister.
No free eats.
I'll take care of it.
- Put it on Carface's tab.
- Okay.
Now, where were...?
Huh?
Hey, Charlie,
I noted how you swept the lady
off her feet.
So I'm rusty.
Let's make a little home delivery.
I'll never get back to heaven.
Oh, shucks.
Something tells me
you're forgetting the horn.
Would you take it easy? There's
plenty of time for that. Come on.
Anabelle is not gonna
like this, Charlie.
Hey, nice digs, huh, Itch?
Ah!
- You again? What do you want?
- You left your doggy bag.
Oh, right. Thanks. Thanks a lot.
There's more than enough.
If you want some company,
we could stick around.
- Sorry, I've got a kid.
- Uh...
Yeah, well, I'm good with kids.
Whoa, she's got a "kid" kid.
Thanks, girl.
What did he do,
follow you home?
- Ah! You can talk?
- Ooh! Please don't encourage him.
Whoa!
He can understand you?
- Of course he can.
- Holy cow.
Holy dogs, actually.
I'm Charlie, he's Itchy.
What's going on here?
And I want the truth.
The truth?
I'm an angel.
- Oh, boy.
- Come on.
- Somebody's playing a trick.
- Okay.
Okay, if I'm not an angel,
how can I do this?
Ooh!
Oh!
Wait a minute. Run, jump, fly.
What did I forget?
Of course. Watch this, kid.
- Ah!
- Please...
...hold your applause.
- Ta-da!
- Wow!
That was the best trick
I've ever seen.
- Trick?
- I do magic too.
Give me the ball, boy.
Wow, that was... That was... More. More.
- The kid's good.
- Listen.
- I could help him with his technique.
- Houdini, that little boy is lost.
If you really wanna help him,
why don't you ask him where he lives?
- Charlie, look. It's a miracle.
- Why not ask him yourself?
- Now, that would be a miracle.
- One miracle coming up.
Ugh! Of all the arrogant, presumptuous,
egotistical mutts I've ever met...
Now you talk.
You must be an angel.
Hey, Charlie, you used up your miracle.
And that was supposed to be
for an emergency.
- Seemed like an emergency to me.
- You must be my guardian angel.
- Your what?
My mom told me
everyone has a guardian angel.
You're here because
I ran away from home, right?
Uh, sure, right, kid.
We're gonna make some team, huh?
- You mean you're not lost?
- Not anymore.
I got my guardian angel.
Hold it.
I wanna know why you ran away.
- You tell her.
- This ought to be good.
It's, uh... Um... Uh...
You're having, uh...
...kid problems?
- Yeah, with my stepmom.
- Knew it. Yeah, I knew it.
She wants me to call her Mom,
but she's not.
I'm never going home again.
So, what do you plan to do,
live on the street?
Yep. And do my magic
at Cannery Square.
- Tourists give you money.
- Now, you know that's silly.
- Come on, tell me where you live.
- No.
Okay, don't listen to me.
Listen to your guardian angel.
David, Cannery Square
sounds like a good plan to me.
- What? Don't listen to him.
- He's not ready to go home.
- Come on, he's 8 years old.
- That's 56 in dog years.
David, with your talent,
there's no telling where you'll end up.
- Oh, please.
- No, no, you must have faith.
Guardian angels move
in mysterious ways.
- So we're off to Cannery Square?
- Not Cannery Square.
- Easy Street.
- Yes!
You with us, Sasha?
I don't know what you're up to,
but I'm gonna keep my eye on you.
I wouldn't want it any other way.
Charles!
We've got a traffic jam up here.
New arrivals can't get in.
We need that horn.
Put them in a holding pattern, okay?
I'm really onto something down here.
You're gonna love this place,
boss. It's got everything you wanted.
Beachfront location, fenced yard,
tight security.
The joint's been home
to some great pedigrees.
Capone, "Machine Gun" Kelly,
the Bird Dog of Alcatraz.
Ho-ho-ho!
Ah!
All that and ratatouille too.
Then I did good?
Have a bone.
Which way to Cannery Square?
Uh, just follow your nose.
So is there a Mr. Sasha?
No, and I'm not taking applications.
Okay. Okay. But if you were,
what, uh, what qualities
would you be looking for?
- Oh, I don't know.
- Of course you do.
Hm...
Well, loyalty, strength, breeding...
- I'd be good at that.
- ...humility,
- Compassion...
- Oh!
...and, of course, style.
Charlie, you okay?
- Boy, are my ears ringing.
- Yeah, you're right.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
That's not your ears, Charlie, that's...
Oh, that's gotta be the horn.
Look, Charlie, there it is.
Go get it, Itch.
I'll stay here with Sasha.
Uh-uh. That's your job.
I'll stay with Sasha.
Okay. I'll be back
before you can say "Hallelujah."
- Where's he going?
- Confidential guardian-angel business.
You dogs have enjoyed
a state of grace for far too long.
- Wouldn't you agree, Carface?
- Uh, yeah, whatever you say, boss.
All these cells filled with dogs.
- Can you see it?
- Huh? Oh, yeah, yeah, sure.
And me playing Gabriel's horn.
- Can you hear it?
- Oh, sure.
Just, uh,
put your lips together and blow.
And then the grand finale!
That ain't...
That's not coming in so clear, actually.
Oh, it will.
And all thanks to Charlie Barkin.
- Make sure he doesn't disappoint me.
- You got it, boss.
♪ It's all so stirring
I feel like purring
♪ It's deeply pleasing
to be the reason
♪ So many will be so sad
♪ Three cheers for treachery
♪ It feels so good to be bad ♪
A-ha!
Let's go.
- All right, step through.
- Good boy.
Hey, nice little dog there, isn't he?
Get this, McDowell:
"Man finds genie in his vacuum cleaner."
And last week, you believed
that scientists
created intelligent lunchmeat.
That's why everyone's afraid
to ride in a car with you.
Hey, sarge,
you got a lost and found here?
- Room 112, through the squad room.
- Ten-four.
I'm telling you, McDowell, there are
some mighty weird things in this world.
Any ideas why he ran away?
- It could only be one thing.
- We're having a baby.
And David got very upset
when I told him.
Hm!
Huh?
Oh! Whoo!
I can't believe this.
Where'd I put that lost-and-found list?
Come on. Come to Charlie.
- Oh! Ah!
- Huh?
Oh...
Of course it couldn't be Gabriel's flute
or Gabriel's kazoo, no.
- Thanks, Officer Reyes.
- Don't worry,
we'll find your little boy.
Itchy, where is he?
And what's this all about?
Sorry, can't.
Charlie and I are sworn to secrecy.
My lips, these lips right here,
see these lips? Well, they're sealed.
Itchy.
- Miss me? Ooh!
- Charlie.
- So where's the you-know-what?
- Minor setback, Itch.
We're just gonna have to bust it out.
- It? What "it"?
- Charlie, no.
- Well... Yah!
- Charlie, don't give away the "it."
You ever hear of Gabriel's horn?
All right, here's the plan.
Just keep moving. Doing great.
Act like you belong here. That's right.
Just through the door on the left.
I don't think this is gonna work.
Nobody even sees us. No eye contact.
Am I good or what?
Ah!
Don't you...
Don't you do that on those papers.
Uh-oh. Plan B, guys.
Doughnuts, fresh off the truck!
- Somebody get those mutts!
- Hey, hey, come back here.
Hey. Whoa! Get over here.
He's headed for the... Whoa!
Oh, no. Excuse me.
Ooh!
I'll just file this.
Whoa!
Oh! Oof! Ah!
- Oops! Sorry, officer.
- Ha! We got you.
Okay, son, give me the keys.
- You heard him, little man.
- Nothing up my sleeve, sir.
- What?
- Officer, what's that behind your ear?
Thank you, thank you.
You've been a great audience.
Mission accomplished. Come on.
- Ah!
- Oof!
Oh, my gosh, David. David!
Freeze. Sit. Stay.
What the...?
Move, move, move.
- Stop that kid!
- What are you doing?
- And those dogs on the scooter!
- Kick it, Charlie.
You don't have a license!
- Hey, short legs.
- Come back here!
Ah! It's the dog pound for sure.
Whoa!
Jump, Itch. Now!
Yahoo!
Whoa! Aren't guardian angels
supposed to protect people?
Hey, it's my first day on the job.
Ah!
Whoa!
I'm gonna barf.
- Yee-ha!
- Having fun, are we?
You finally got your flying lessons,
eh, Itch?
I'm gonna get you
for this, Charlie.
Aw, what do you mean,
we're not gonna go back yet?
Look, we got the horn, don't we?
Come on, let's get out of here.
I still need to take care of David.
I am his guardian angel.
Oh, yeah, sure,
and Sasha has nothing to do with it.
- Well, uh...
- Charlie, you're making me crazy here.
Just a little more time.
The horn'll be safe here.
No. Charlie!
Wouldn't you rather
be home right now, David?
Uh-uh. Not that again.
I'm going to Cannery Square.
- Don't you mean Easy Street?
- Yeah. How far is it?
A lot closer than you think.
- Nervous?
- A little. And sweaty.
Well, don't be.
- Excited?
- You bet.
- Now, Charlie...
- It's okay. All set. Let's go.
Ah!
♪ Outta his way, he's coming through
♪ The kid's makin' his showbiz debut
♪ You'll be amazed, amused, enthused
♪ And bowled over
♪ I got the moves, I got the tricks
♪ Been practicing since I was six
♪ His dues are paid
He's got it made
♪ Soon we'll be in clover
♪ Easy Street
♪ Where the sun's always shinin'
♪ Not a cloud in the sky
- ♪ Clear and sunny
- ♪ Milk and honey
♪ Life is sweet on Easy Street
Charlie, I hope you know
what you're doing.
Relax, enjoy the show.
It ain't over yet.
Hm!
♪ When you're a big celebrity
♪ Fans are like a family
♪ Abracadabra, poof
I'll be a sensation
♪ And I'll be there
through thick and thin
♪ Watchin' the dough come rollin' in
♪ A couple of shows and then we'll close
♪ And take our vacation
♪ On Easy Street
♪ Where the sun's always shinin'
♪ Not a cloud in the sky
- ♪ Good time livin'
- ♪ It's a given
♪ We'll all meet
♪ On Easy Street
♪ Where we'll be together
Best friends till the end
♪ I'll be applauded and admired
- ♪ There's easy pickin's
- ♪ And boneless chickens
♪ Wishing is all that's required
♪ On Easy Street
♪ Where the sun's always shinin'
♪ Not a cloud in the sky
- ♪ Clear and sunny
- ♪ Milk and honey
- ♪ Good time livin'
- ♪ It's a given
Ah!
♪ Easy Street
♪ Where the sun's always shinin'
♪ Not a cloud in the sky
- ♪ No goodbyes there
- ♪ No one cries there
♪ You can't beat
♪ Life on Easy
♪ Street ♪
Come on, let's get you out of the rain.
One, please.
- Thank you.
- There you are. Come here, hon.
I'm so hungry, I could eat a shoe.
How about you?
I thought so. I'll be right back.
My mom used to do that.
Charlie, can she see me from heaven?
- Of course she can, kiddo.
- David, remember,
you still have
your dad and stepmom here.
My stepmom doesn't want me.
She's having her own kid.
But parents can love
more than one pup.
Maybe she didn't know
how to tell you that.
Maybe you should give her
another chance.
You know, I ran away from home
when I was little.
- That make your parents sorry?
- I don't know.
I never saw them after that.
Guess I could've used
a guardian angel, huh?
Charlie, I'll go home
if you promise to take me.
- I promise.
- Really? It'll be great.
You can sleep on my bed
and we'll play in the yard.
We'll be one big family.
Uh, David, hold on, hold on.
I can't promise that.
We struck gold.
Egg foo yung, mu shu pork, won ton,
and I hope you like potstickers.
Napkins?
Ah!
Ge... Wha!
Nice work, Charlie Barkin.
You really are an angel.
No, I'm not.
Not a guardian angel, anyway.
- What you did for David was wonderful.
- I'm not his angel.
I'm just an errand boy
sent to fetch Gabriel's horn.
Sasha, my whole life has been about
making and breaking promises.
- And now I'm gonna do it again.
- You can't take him home?
I have to go back,
and just when I finally found
someone special.
Oh, Charlie.
♪ I will always be with you
♪ Makes no difference
♪ Where your road takes you to
♪ Even if we're apart
♪ Now we're joined at the heart
♪ Though our moment may be gone
♪ You and I will still live on
♪ I will always be with you
♪ I'll be by your side
whatever you do
♪ Other memories may fade
But the ones that we made
♪ Are eternal as a star
♪ Now I'm part of who you are
♪ And I'll be there with you
in the sound of your laughter
♪ I'll be in the tears you cry
♪ 'Cause the way you and I
have touched one another
♪ Doesn't end with goodbye
♪ I will always be with you
♪ Like a guardian angel
Constant and true
- ♪ When you're lost in the night
- ♪ Lost in the night
- ♪ And you can't see the light
- ♪ Can't see the light
♪ My love will see you through
♪ I will always be there
♪ You'll have me there
♪ I will always be with
♪ You ♪
- Charlie?
- Mm-hm?
Oh, no, no, not now.
Sasha, I can't find Itchy.
Where's Charlie?
- David, I'm here, right here.
- He's gone.
He wouldn't leave.
He's my guardian angel.
- We gotta do something, Itch.
- They'll be fine, Charlie.
I promised David I'd get him home.
Short legs.
Short. Charlie!
Hey, you got any sixes?
Go fish.
- Red. Red.
- Ah!
I gotta... I gotta ask a favor.
Anything, Charlie, just name it.
- I need a new collar.
- You enjoyed it.
- I knew you would.
- Oh, thanks. You're a pal.
- Can I have it now?
- Oh, I am sorry.
You misunderstood me.
If you want another collar,
you must pay.
Oh.
You caught me a little short.
How about an IOU?
I don't think so.
Carface will show you out.
There must
be some way to make a deal.
Charlie, he might take a trade.
- Wait, wait.
- Goodbye.
Red, I have this horn.
Sorry, I'm not musical.
No, this is much more than a horn, Red.
There's nothing like it
in the whole world.
Let me sleep on it.
I don't have that kind of time.
I like your spirit, Charlie.
Bring me this horn
and you can have the collar.
Great. Uh, I need the collar to get it.
Oh, really?
- Come on, Red, you can trust me.
- This isn't about trust.
A deal with me is binding.
- Charlie, no!
- Deal?
Huh?! Ah!
Ah!
Guess the cat's out of the bag, eh?
You tricked me.
Oh!
Now, be a good little bow-wow,
and fetch me my horn.
Oh, Charlie!
Follow him.
Where you going, Charlie?
The train station.
Oh! Charlie, are you nuts?
- You... You gave away the horn.
- Get out of my way.
You shook on it.
You made a deal with him.
You promised Anabelle
and you promised me, Charlie.
Itch, I know that, but right now,
I've got to find David. Move.
- Come on, David. Which train?
- Where's Charlie?
He wouldn't leave me.
Huh?
David? David?
A-ha!
Bring the item to Alcatraz
in one hour,
or junior here doesn't have a prayer.
Charlie!
Where is he? The hour's up.
You know what they say, boss,
"Patience is a..."
Oh!
Uh... Maybe he's stuck in traffic.
What kind of dog are you,
selling out to some mangy old cat?
- Quiet, or I'll have your tongue, boy.
- Red.
Charlie.
The horn.
Let me, boss. I'll fetch it for you.
Gabriel's horn is finally mine.
- Boss, they're hitting the bricks.
- Let them. I have what I want.
Silence!
Huh?
Charlie, what's happening?
Don't worry about it.
Let's get out of here.
- Come on. Jump.
- Ah!
- Charles, what have you done?
- Charlie, we gotta do something.
No, Itch, it's my fault.
I'm the one who's gotta do something.
- Get David home safely.
- Charlie, no!
Ah!
Red, Charlie's coming back.
That puppy's into punishment.
- Oof!
- It's a cat's world now.
- Let him go!
- Run, David.
Huh?
- No!
- David.
- All right, you, I'm coming. Ah!
- Huh?
Which do you want,
the horn or your friends?
Itchy, help us!
Everyone, scatter!
Come back here.
Play the horn, Charles. The horn.
Charlie.
This should cool him off.
Take a bath.
Enough stupid pet tricks.
Ha!
Ah!
Huh?
Here, kitty, kitty.
I like your spirit. Oops!
- Hope you can dog paddle.
- Charlie!
Ah!
Halo.
Double chili catburger
with onions and pickles.
- Everyone okay?
- Think so.
- I'm fine.
- I'm good.
Me too.
- Where's Red?
- His boss yanked his leash.
Ah! Good riddance.
Charlie, I hope you didn't
take any of that personally, you know?
I was just, you know,
playing the game.
Sure, Carface.
Say, what did you trade Red
for your collar?
He wanted the bottom of my
shoes or something.
I don't even wear shoes,
that stupid cat.
Stupid dog. It was your soul!
Let me go.
This is not good. Hey! Not the flames.
What do you know.
And I thought all dogs go to heaven.
Anabelle?
- Come on, Charlie, time to go.
- Already?
David, can Sasha take you home?
Charlie, don't go.
Hey, I'll always be your guardian angel.
Okay.
Sasha, I love you.
I love you too, Charlie.
Hey, what's wrong?
Is this thing stuck between floors?
- I'll take the horn from here, Charles.
- What, you afraid I'll drop it?
Ah! Whoa!
There's someone who still needs
to go back where he belongs.
- I already took care of David.
- Not David. You, Charlie.
For what you've done,
you deserve a second chance.
Claim this in, oh, say, 20 years.
- You mean...?
- Mm-hm.
Itchy, you hear that?
We're going back.
Nah. Not this wiener dog.
See, when you can fly...
...short legs don't matter.
I'm gonna miss you, pal.
I couldn't have done it without you.
Take care of yourself, buddy.
What is it, girl?
Can you believe it?
- Charlie.
- Charlie?
I got a weekend pass
for the rest of my life.
- Oh, Charlie.
- David?
- Thom, it's David.
- Davey!
Oh, David.
You're all right.
I've been worried sick about you.
- You worried about me?
- Of course.
Having this baby doesn't mean
I don't love you.
- I know that now, Mom.
- Honey, we're a family.
That's right, just a bigger one.
Dad, Mom,
speaking of bigger families, you think
we have room for a pet or two?
Now, tell me the truth, Charlie Barkin,
why'd you really come back?
And don't you con me.
Actually, I kind of like the idea
of being Mr. Sasha.
Hey, guys, I worked a little magic.
♪ Now that you're loving me
♪ It's so heavenly
♪ Hallelujah, hallelujah
Hallelujah
♪ So heavenly ♪
♪ I will always be with you
♪ Makes no difference
♪ Where your road takes you to
♪ Even if we're apart
♪ Now we're joined at the heart
♪ Though our moment may be gone
♪ You and I will still live on
♪ I will always be with you
♪ I'll be by your side
whatever you do
♪ Other memories may fade
But the ones that we made
♪ Are eternal as a star
♪ Now I'm part of who you are
♪ And I'll be there with you
in the sound of your laughter
♪ I'll be in the tears you cry
♪ 'Cause the way you and I
have touched one another
♪ Doesn't end with goodbye
♪ I will always be with you
♪ Like a guardian angel
Constant and true
- ♪ When you're lost in the night
- ♪ Lost in the night
♪ And you can't see the light
♪ My love will see you through
♪ I will always be there
♪ You'll have me there
♪ I will always be with you
♪ Like a guardian angel
Constant and true
- ♪ When you're lost in the night
- ♪ Lost in the night
♪ And you can't see the light
♪ My love will see you through
♪ I will always be there
♪ You'll have me there
♪ I will always be with
♪ You ♪