[female operator] 911. May I help you?
[fake Chinese accent] I
think it's a fight maybe,
And there could be a gun there.
That's right!
Can you give me a location?
This, uh, disturbance
at Wang's Fu restaurant
at 84 Paradise. Yes. At...
Can I have your name?
No. No, no. My name is not important.
I think you guys should
be there pretty quick.
That's right.
Good. Thank you.
Our ass is covered like a diaper.
[police radio] 1051, Chinatown.
Disturbance at 84 Paradise Road.
Wang Fu restaurant.
Unit 18 responding. Roger that 1051.
We're on it, 84 Paradise.
[sirens]
[radio] In the vicinity...
Let's back those guys up.
No, they'll be okay. Just stay out of it.
What's the matter with you, man?
Cutting down on your MSG or some shit, huh?
What's the matter with you, Roadie?
You want to do some ching-chong recruiting?
Hey, now that's a good idea.
We need Chinese cops in Chinatown.
In fact, my brother,
you can pass out the fucking applications.
We're cops, man. We back each other up.
That's what we're supposed to do.
Come on, man. Those guys can handle it.
Have a heart.
[siren] Come on.
[busts door open]
Out of my way! Come on.
Let's go! Move it!
[screams and crashing]
Move! Come on. Move!
Get out!
[thud] Out of my way!
[speaks Chinese]
You guys forgot to
support your local police?
You don't support us,
how can we support you? Huh?
Huh? Huh?
[man with Chinese accent]
Why you do this? Huh?
Thanks for the contribution.
[cop] Put your hands up.
Get back, buddy. Put 'em up! Put 'em up!
Move. Move!
Go watch the door, huh?
Hey, Grant. Yeah.
Report this to the bank. You hear me?
[laughs]
Break it up. Break it the fuck up.
Fucking ping pong! You
got a fucking problem?
Rhoades. Rhoades. Relax, man, relax.
Out of my way, man!
Fucking...
Asshole. What the fuck is he doing here?
He was driving! What was I supposed to do?
Hands on the table. Eyes on the floor.
Don't look at me. What are you looking at?
Look out! You're killing him, man.
Get off him! Come on, get up.
Come on!
Now! Come on, man!
Son of a bitch.
Ugh!
Come on. Come on!
Get up! Get up!
Come on! Come on!
[camera shutters clicking]
Lieutenant,
we were responding to a disturbance call.
We just stumbled on this shit.
Did any of our boys get hurt?
No. But Rhoades almost got dead.
Got a good shot in the coconut,
but Beckstrom saved his life. Right,
Jensen?
It's true. Put a call in to the Mayor.
Maybe you can squeeze
a medal of valor out of him.
He deserves it.
You okay?
Yeah, I'll live.
Take care of him, okay?
Yeah.
Good job.
Everybody's here now.
The whole damn circus.
Moose has got his story fixed.
I warned you.
You fax the Feds, you watch your back.
Hey, I need to find...
Do me a favor. Check
with the Watch Commander.
Tell him it's not my problem.
Hey, Mirk! We missed you at the ball game,
buddy.
[bangs locker]
[spits]
[all chuckle]
You're a real fucking comedian, Moose.
When are you gonna learn to relax, man?
How long have you got? A month?
A week.
29 years, 11 months,
and 3 weeks, and counting, huh?
Mirk, buddy, you're not gonna make it.
It's that last week,
that's when the ax falls.
[mutters] Shut the fuck up.
Take it easy on them doughnuts.
Shut you mouth.
Tough night. It happens.
I ain't gonna lie,
Mirk. I've seen better, man.
Want some aspirin?
Want something to wash it down with?
How old is this coffee, Mirk?
I don't know. Four, maybe five days?
Good. I hate it when it's fresh, man.
Are you still on that?
I can't...
You were working with Rhoades.
Lieutenant, listen to me. Mirk is retiring.
You've gotta rearrange the assignments.
Just let me work with the Moose.
Beckstrom, you just saved your partner's
black ass. You know what that means?
That brutality complaint is bullshit.
Yeah, but...
Listen, just listen to me, okay?
You were a brave cop who was
protecting his Afro-American partner.
Now, that other complaint's gonna
be bullshit. You want to mess with that?
No...
No. Good boy! Good boy! Huh?
Best face for the Grand Jury.
You're a good cop. Clean as shit.
Colorblind cop. Hell! They'll probably
put you on the happy news tonight.
[whispers] But Moose wants me to...
Not another word. No more. That's it.
I don't want to hear about it again.
And get your paperwork all squared away,
but in the meantime,
I know the skipper will want to meet you.
Have you taken Jesus Christ into
your life as your personal Savior yet?
Hey, Sagamaki,
are you trolling for choir boys again?
You can come to church this Sunday
and we can all pray
together. What do you say?
Hey, Red, don't let him get you alone
at the prayer meeting, huh?
Hey, Lieutenant. This is our new man.
Perfect timing, Mochizuki San.
One more minute and I'd be
over at the crapper taking a shit.
I never would've had the opportunity
to meet this new man, Really, thank you.
You know,
I can wait outside if you want. [chuckles]
Nah. You're older than most recruits.
I was in the Marine Corps 10 years.
Really? What's your MOS?
3125.
You're an RTO?
Hmm.
I can't help the radio.
How did you get around Affirmative Action?
I told 'em my father's real
name was Kunta Kinte.
Look. Suit up and I'll send you on an
orientation ride with Moose and Jensen.
Okay? They'll show you your turf.
All right. Thank you, sir.
I asked him to cut me loose of Rhoades.
Eyler's turned into a fucking old
woman with this Grand Jury shit.
Rhoades almost fucked up that little
surprise we had with the chinkies last night.
They won't try another one of
those gambling den situations
with out cutting us in any time soon,
right?
That's why we need a good man
like you out on the street with him.
God damn it. I mean,
I saved this black ass' life,
and now it comes back to haunt me
I shoulda just let him die...
Beck, hey, hey. You're in
the streets out there, not me.
Anything can happen.
[breathes heavily] Ugh.
One one thousand, two one thousand.
Come on,
man. Enough of this Jane Fonda bullshit.
Come on, get in here. Let's go!
[breathing heavily]
Checked that new dude?
♪ From the halls of Montezuma ♪
[both chuckle]
The fool look like he from
Mark Fuhrman Police Academy.
You can all that with just one look?
Yeah. They all look like they'll
kiss him now, check it out.
You on for tonight?
Yeah, man, of course.
You got your macho jeep all
gassed up and ready to go?
I thought you was gonna drive.
No. I'm drinking, you're driving.
I'm always driving. How
come you don't drive?
Good looks.
By now you're probably wondering,
"Am I gonna piss my panties
at the first sign of trouble?"
Probably. Don't worry about that.
Ms. Jensen here is still pissing hers.
[chuckles] Yeah? Well
you can kiss my sweet ass.
I spent some time on the streets.
Two years I had shore patrol.
That's right. If I were you I wouldn't
wave that Marine Corps shit around Eyler.
Why not? I thought his
kid was in the Marine Corps.
Was. Rest in peace.
No shit. How'd he die?
Granada. Friendly fucking fire.
Ain't that some shit? What
else do you want to know?
Hey. 10 o'clock. Ooga-boogas
at the jungle. What do you know?
[Moose] Make a U. [siren]
[Jensen] Ooh, the boogie man!
That's a number one coming up.
So what's the lesson,
Andre? What are we supposed to do?
You're a fine example, a credit to
your race. Did that work for you?
I got you here, didn't I?
I know. But what about your promotion?
You look like Shaft. Went to college.
It's more than most detectives.
Eyler barely squeezed his ass outta
high school and he's a Lieutenant.
You pissed him off big time.
I don't want to make nobody mad.
Come on. Look at all the minorities.
When's the Department
gonna get with the times?
Hey.
Hi, honey. How are you?
Good. Glad you could make it.
Hi, Rhoades.
Hi, Xeenie.
Looks good.
No, I'm gonna get a taco later.
Adventure feeds the soul.
Tacos feed my face.
Aren't you hungry?
Xeenie made them herself.
Okay. I'll take this one here.
Get down.
Ugh!
You keep your hands on the car.
I got him! get down, man!
That's good. You know I like
diversion with the boys around the hood.
Registration,
everything checks out. They're clean.
See? That don't mean squat to me.
Looks like we got a pair
of hardened criminals here.
How do you want to handle this situation,
General?
You want me to take care of this?
Yeah, show me the jar handle.
You got yourself a jig on shore leave,
so you need to give 'em the DWA test.
Come on, I didn't do anything.
DWA, what's that?
Attention. Stand still.
Put your feet together.
All right now.
All right. Bring your right
forefinger and your thumb up,
and hold on to your right earlobe.
Come on, man. Come on.
Forefinger and your thumb
up to hold your right earlobe.
Okay?
The right.
[cops chuckle]
Go on. Grab it on. Grab it on.
That's very good.
[laughs]
I want you to take your left
forefinger and your thumb,
and hold on to your left earlobe.
Right here. Very good. Now,
you've done this before?
You've done this before?
No, no, you're very good. It's okay.
Okay. Push your jaw out.
Push out your jaw.
Push your jaw out!
Push it out. Good.
Breath in and out
through your mouth rapidly.
[cops chuckle]
[both breathe] There you go.
Now say, "Uh!"
Uh. Come on.
Say, "Uh!"
Uh. Uh. Uh.
[chuckles]
You're DWA, you matched it.
Driving Wild Aboriginal.
Good boy, you passed it,
chief. Now go on. Get outta here.
Go ahead, go.
What about Speedy Gonzalez here, huh?
[in Spanish accent] Hey, you try to run,
we're gonna teach you a lesson.
What do you say, Colonel?
What do you want to do with this one?
Well, we got a lot of work tonight now.
All right. Now listen, you use
your feet and you're gonna get beat.
Okay. Hm?
Wait a minute. These
wetbacks got hard heads.
I don't want you to bruise your knuckle.
[chuckles] Oh, ho, ho.
Oh.
"X" marks the spot.
Now I just realized, this could
be construed to be police brutality.
And we sure don't want to
be doing anything illegal here.
[In Spanish accent] Hey, Paco,
you got a free pass tonight
Get outta my world!
[chuckles]
What you say,
muchachos? It's a big world out there.
What is the use of working your tail off
at the FBI if they only
give you a little dinky shield.
You need a real cop shield,
a master shield.
Accepted the world over.
Hi, Michael. Nice badge.
Thank you. Fancy meeting you here.
Really? I thought this was
more my thing than yours.
I may have changed since you last saw me.
I could've gone through
a cultural metamorphosis.
Hm. I don't think so. Your
baseball hat kinda gives you away.
No. I could change.
I read somewhere that
women like to mold us like clay.
Hm. I'm sure you'll make
some lucky girl a nice ashtray.
[both laugh]
Alright. Enough bad jokes.
How come you don't return my calls?
I received the files, but, uh,
I haven't had a chance to look at them yet.
Okay. I'm gonna save you a little time.
Now listen to this. 25
homicides within the last 8 years.
All unsolved. With circumstances
that point to police vigilantism.
Michael, please...
From a racist group of cops
that happens to be in my division.
Now when I go to pull the files,
the forensics, the lab reports, all that,
they're gone. They turn up missing.
This is not the time...
Wait, hold on, one second.
Now all that's left of the ballistics
reports are the first five killings.
And they match. It's the same gun.
If we get that gun, we can nail these cops.
Michel, I'll look into it.
You look good.
Turn around.
Oh, please. [chuckles]
How's your mom?
She's fine.
Okay, I gotta go. I promise I'll
look into as soon as possible.
Okay? Bye.
Go Andre. Go Andre.
Why not? Why not?
I better get outta here, man.
Okay. Hey, Xeenie, we're taking the cut.
Bye, Dad.
Bye, Xenia.
Sorry, I didn't know Anita
Bayard was gonna be here.
You mean to keep me away?
Damn. She's stuck up. What'd
she have to say about the files?
She said she's been
busy but she'll get to it.
Yeah. Mm-hm. Sure!
First of all, you keep your
mouth shut and your eyes open.
The faster you learn that,
the faster you get your own car.
Hey, are we gonna get some food any time?
Are you hungry?
Here. Why don't you
have half of my sandwich?
Why don't you come meet the guys?
Nah, I don't want to be born again.
Aw, they're not Christians. Only
Mochizuki's a Christian. [chuckles]
They're just regular guys.
Moose is a regular guy?
Yeah.
Hey, don't even talk to that old fool, huh?
He's counting the days
until he pulls the pin
thinks everyone's out to dig 'em a grave.
[chuckles]
Hey, rookie. You might want to think
about carrying a second gun out there,
something small, easy to get at,
a .38 snubby.
Now me and most of the boys,
we use dumb dumb hollow points.
They ain't regulation,
like Mr. Rhoades uses,
but it'll tear a perp a new
asshole every time, I guarantee.
[all laugh]
Regulations bullets work real well, Moosey,
if you know how to shoot straight.
Is that right?
Yeah, baby, that's right.
It's straight when you
shoot it towards your head.
Hey, uh, give me that.
Hey, Rhoades,
you batting fifth on Saturday?
'Cause I was thinking,
maybe you ought to lead off
with your natural speed and all.
[all] Oh, ho!
Whatever's right for the team, man.
Well, what a fine attitude, my man.
Because once we get out there,
you are one of us.
You are a Phantom.
[all] Yeah!
[Rhoades] Speaking of baseball,
I'm talking to this new
brother from Union High,
Bat enough, plays first base...
Whoa! I play first...
Don't yank my chain, huh?
And don't be recruiting no more brothers.
I don't want to have to change
the name of the team to The Spooks.
[all] Woo. [chuckles]
You know why I like white girls?
[mimics female voice] Because
you get all that screaming!
And you never meet the parents.
[all snicker]
Leave them white girls alone, boy.
Did you pull strings to
get this flat top rookie?
Hey, Rhoades, you want to tell me why you
always got some fucking bug up your ass?
Them big innocent watery blue eyes, huh?
But you fast tracked that
fresh Gestapo meat, don't you?
You know why you're brown?
You're so full of shit.
Hey, Becky.
Come on, Mirk. Let's give it a try. Come
to my church and we'll all pray together.
Hey, guys. How does that thing go? Uh,
Nam yoho renge kyo,
Nam yoho renge [chuckles]
New guy's a nice kid.
I'd hate to see him get into any trouble,
Bill.
Well, he's not.
Ugh.
[radio] Becky, what's your twenty?
Southwest 126. What's up, Moose?
We're dead in the
water. we got a flat tire,
we're not going anywhere for a while but we
got an 1124 coming up. Can you take that?
You got it, Moose.
Roger that, thank you very much, buddy.
That's Disciple's territory, man.
It's a suspicious brand of vehicle, man.
What's your fucking problem?
Let Moose cover his own area.
Hey, we're cops, we help each other out.
That's what we're supposed to do, right?
Don't fucking tell me how to police, man.
I tell you how to slam dunk?
[Rhoades] Something
ain't right. This is bullshit.
Yeah, yeah. Come on, let's check it out.
Call for backup.
Come on, man. It's a pussy move.
Becky, call for backup.
Okay. Whatever you say.
All right. I'll go in here,
you come round the side.
What am I, a rookie?
No, you're not a rookie, dude.
I got your backup. [snickers]
You know what I mean?
See this stuff right here?
Yeah. You know?
[meow]
[rat squeaks]
What's that?
[gunshots]
[unloaded gun]
Oh, Rhoades,
what did you step into this time?
Don't let him get away.
[panting] Calling 30 Upper West Park Way
by the Old Mill, officer needs assistance.
Officer needs a coroner.
Oh, shit.
Okay, clear guys. Clear guys.
Get this goddamn shirt outta here.
Gimme that shirt.
You want to tell me what happened here?
Gimme that fucking shirt!
Come on, man. Come on.
Come on,
you got your partner killed, Rhoades.
You unloaded my fucking gun.
You want to pin this on me, huh?
I'll kick your fucking ass.
Come on, let's get some Affirmative Action,
you fucking monkey.
I'll chop your head.
Are you crazy? You're putting yourself
and all of us in the fucking politics.
I thought you'd finally
be in the fight. Come on!
Get your hands off of me.
There's more of them than
us. You'll just end up dead.
Get your hands off me. You hear me?
Come on, man. Fuck!
Look, I'm not saying, "Let it go."
You just gotta be smarter than them.
There's gotta be an investigation, okay?
I don't know why Becks was
carrying loose rounds in his pocket
but I'll look into it personally.
Not loose rounds. My rounds. In my gun.
Looks, Rhoades, I don't think you had
anything to do with Beckstrom's death.
I need a new partner.
Yeah, well, psss,
we're a little thin right now.
I'll take the new kid.
DeBruler? No way, I got plans for him.
It's gonna take me about a week and I'll,
um, redo the schedule, okay?
I need a new partner now.
Are you trying to tell me
how to run my station?
I request permission to contact Personnel
Division for a hearing to determine...
I need a rat. Like you've been going to IA,
huh?
You leave me no choice
but to go to the press.
You? Go to the press? No! You are a cop!
What did you do going hooking
yourself up with that rookie?
Will you be my partner?
No way. Your partners die.
I spent 15 years on the street
to get my cushy day, man.
No sweat, man, my partners don't die.
Yeah, I know. I know.
All right, first of all,
if DeBruler doesn't
grade out in my evaluation,
you got yourself in the
spot that much earlier
for my mankind.
See? There he goes again,
looking for ways to piss them off.
You fellows go ahead. All right?
See you later, man.
Get that thing outta your ear.
Okay, check this out.
If I'm his training officer
it's up to me to ask his TO
to ground him in investigating techniques.
Mh-hm. Like looking through all the files
and using his name on the paperwork
so as not to raise any red flags?
Someone's gotta do it. man.
Look, you'd better start growing
eyes in the back of your head, son.
That missing bullet stint.
That was just a first step.
That's the whole thing. Now,
see this rookie
he's my best chance to staying alive.
He's too green to put a bullet in my back.
Yes, weak.
Listen. He's too naive to know
what I'm doing. He's my best shot.
Okay.
Just keep looking for shit to step in.
Go find yourself some nice fresh turd
and don't forget to take off your shoes
and let it get all up between your toes.
I give it up to Jesus, boy.
[bagpipes] Sniffs.
[Commander] Honor guard.
Load!
Arms!
Honor guard. Volley!
Honor guard.
Aim!
Fire! [gunshots]
Honor guard. Fire! [gunshots]
Thanks.
So it was your idea, huh, Moose?
I don't think I know
what you're talking about.
The Rhoades thing without my permission.
We got a nigger problem...
We don't use that kind of
language here. Understand?
You're not doing a damn thing about it.
So you were gonna do
something about it. You moron.
If you're gonna be a decision maker
you better look at the big picture.
There's a Grand Jury out there
and you just got their attention.
So now Rhoades is a problem.
A problem I gotta deal with.
Hey, FBI lady.
Can I give you a lift?
I'm with my boss and
friends. Now's not a good time.
Anita.
I need someone to talk to.
Just for a minute.
I'll give you a ride home. Okay?
Michael, it's starting to rain.
When are you gonna get a
real car? I mean there's no roof.
Who do I contact considering
that another cop is trying to kill me?
It's not my department.
I tried going through channels,
they got the whole system rigged.
I get no support. They
draft all the Hitlers they want.
They brought a new one this week.
Michael,
you can't go off like a loose cannon.
You do more harm than
good. You're not looking at...
At the big picture. Yeah. Yeah.
If you won't even give me backup,
what am I supposed to do?
Okay. Now let me ask you a question.
Where the hell are we going?
[Keith] Who are those guys?
They're ours, cops, downtown around.
I'm glad you could make it, Keith.
Thanks for inviting me.
You're putting him with Rhoades?
Can it, Moose.
Trying to find out how
the other half lives?
Back off, Tavola. It was my decision.
If I was running this outfit...
Well you're not running this outfit. Okay?
Why don't you go help those guys, son?
[Moose] Bon voyage, Becks.
So what do you think of all this?
I feel like I belong here.
That's why I became a police officer.
To find people like myself.
Every last one of these
guys proved themselves.
They proved people.
Proved it. Not just talk.
I want to prove myself.
I'm stuck with Rhoades.
Well, you'll get the chance.
Troublemakers like your new partner
and all that Affirmative Action bullshit
it's on the way out. We still have to
tolerate minorities, but not for long.
How long do I have to wait?
Something happens to Rhoades, pffff.
He'll get a full Department funeral,
just like Beckstrom got,
we'll all be there.
[Eyler] You remind me of my son.
[Keith] I do?
Yeah. He would've done the right thing,
too.
Hey, Moose!
That is for Beckstrom.
I don't think he's gonna miss it. Do you?
Yeah, you're real big on
tradition. Aren't you, Moose?
Huh?
He's a piece of work.
Yeah, but he's a good cop.
Yeah.
All right, here we are. Come on.
Thank you. Wow!
Yup. Check it out.
You never climb this thing, do you?
Yeah. Let's go. [chuckles]
[Anita] Whew!
Isn't this this a trip
down memory lane here?
Yeah. [chuckles]
Michael, I need to get back.
Hey, we just climbed, we're already here
come on, you're here.
And I'm enjoying the view.
Yeah, I bet you are. [chuckles]
With the power of this badge
backing up the might of this gun,
we pledge to carry on the
work of our fallen comrades.
Good bye, Joe.
[Anita] Oh! [chuckles]
[sighs] I can't believe
this place is still here.
[thunder]
It's worth the climb, isn't it?
Yeah.
Remember the first time?
Yeah. It was my first time,
not yours. [chuckles]
That's not what I was talking about.
♪ The coming of the Lord
♪ He is trampling out the vintage ♪
♪ Where the grapes of wrath are stored ♪
♪ He hath loosed the faithful lightning ♪
♪ Of His terrible, swift sword ♪
♪ His truth is marching on
♪ Glory! Glory! Hallelujah! ♪
♪ Glory! Glory! Hallelujah!
[glass breaks]
[kids mimic] ♪ His truth is marching on
Is it my imagination,
or has this wine improved with age?
[both chuckle]
[sighs]
You know something?
Hm?
You looked good before I had this wine?
Now you look like some "Lord have mercy",
"Save me Jesus".
Shut up. [chuckles]
[thunder] It's starting to rain again.
[raindrops fall]
I have to go.
[Grant] Let's go, Moose.
You want to go, go. What the
fuck you hanging around here for?
Look at that shit. God damn I hate that.
Fuck them goddamn niggers.
They got no respect.
They piss on the whole world,
they rule the whole fucking city.
Leave them alone,
they're not doing nothing.
We'll fuck 'em.
You want to?
It's okay by me.
[Anita screams] Ah!
Sh Sh Sh.
[kiss]
You're late.
I need to take a shower. I'm wet and dirty.
You know I like it like that.
Okay.
Mm-hm. [chuckles]
How am I doing?
Hey, what's the matter?
It's okay. It's okay.
[Anita] Look, we have to do something.
What about?
We can't have Michael
Rhoades as your partner.
[chuckles] Why not?
Shit. I can work around him.
The important thing is that Eyler bought
your whole setup about the Marines.
These guys are going for
everything. The accent. Everything.
They really think that I'm one of them!
They actually think that I'm one of them.
I mean, this Eyler, he acts like,
like I'm his son back from the dead.
You know I don't like playing
that card. I'm fucking in.
I don't know yet if it links
to the ballistics in those files
but these guys make a
big deal about the guns
and badges of their dead buddies.
Keith.
Listen to me.
You don't know what Michael's capable of.
Why is this such an ordeal for you?
Huh?
What's the problem?
Remember that guy that I told you about?
That I used to go out with, the cop?
Yeah.
Are you shitting me?
I had to do it that way.
If Franklin had known he
would've taken me off the case
and somebody else would be running you.
But you coulda told me.
How could I know you
were gonna be partners?
I didn't know he was
going to be so aggressive.
Putting himself in
the line of fire like that.
I'm supposed to be on
your side. Remember that?
Do you remember that?
I know, I know, it's just that you
know how bad I want these guys.
I mean, how many chances
are we gonna get like this?
They had me running license plates scams.
Oh.
Fuck it. What's the difference?
All right? [growls]
You know what? It's nothing.
[thunder]
Ah. I love this adrenalin.
Hm. That worries me.
[both chuckle]
Hey, Moose, How you doing this morning?
Oh, no, rookie. First day I gotta get
your coffee for ya. How do you like it?
I can get my own coffee.
You sure?
Don't you like it black?
Black is beautiful. No? Okay.
Moose, look at you. Sunglasses?
Must have been a rough night, huh?
Who was the lucky fella?
That's Phil Ericsson. My Rabbi.
He adopted me when I was
a rookie cop. About your age.
Yeah? What happened to him?
Ambushed.
He went after some drug
scumbags on his own time.
Five of them jumped him, cut him to pieces,
dumped him in a playground,
took his gun and badge.
Damn. No shit.
Next day they were flashing
him around the jungle like a trophy.
Did they ever get caught?
You mean arrested? No.
We turned the heat up,
we had this town by its balls.
But no proof, no case. Nothing.
And then somehow,
uh [chuckles] they started turning up dead.
One by one by one.
All five of them.
What happened?
Depends who you listen to.
If you ask some of the people around here,
they'll tell you Ericsson did it.
Ericsson? You mean, like his ghost?
Well, they say he came back from the grave,
hunted them down,
and took his gun and badge back.
It's bullshit.
It's a legend.
Come on, you gotta be kidding me.
I'm dead serious.
You listen to me, son,
those are the people that
you're dealing with around here.
You know,
that banana seems to fit with you.
Oh, man,
let me know if you're interested, baby.
I got it in for you.
[chuckles]
Hey, hey, rookie man.
Banana? Apple?
No.
No cholesterol. You sure?
How about a Tic Tac to
keep your breath fresh?
My breath's fine.
How do you get your hair flat like that?
Now here's the vehicle. Yeah,
mine. You're going on a soul patrol.
Looking good.
All right. Hey, Moose. Right on,
brother. Stay black.
So where are you from?
Hm, from Tennessee.
Well, Tennessee,
not everybody's right for this job.
Yeah, but you'll give me
the benefit of the doubt, right?
Absolutely, baby.
So it's not just me you're
messing with here, right?
It's more of a, a what, a rookie thing?
It's you if you can't do the job.
Sounds like you expect me to screw up.
I expect everybody to screw up.
Maybe my being here's a mistake. Hm?
Personally, I think it's a mistake
to send inexperienced, rookie, redneck cops
into patrolling minority
neighborhoods. Yes.
But your folks make the rules,
not mine. Right?
[hip hop music]
In this blue uniform, we become a target.
Doesn't matter if you like Garth Brooks,
I like Snoop Dog,
we don't back each other up, we're dead.
Hm.
Beckstrom got killed. He didn't back me up.
So now Beckstrom's a dead mother fucker.
And I'm alive.
Which way are you gonna go?
[Rhoades] We could be black
man and boy white. Right?
What's this?
Got a call.
What call? There was no call.
Then stay in the car.
[radio] Hey, Rhoades. What's your twenty?
Yeah, he's outta the car.
DeBruler? Hey, you wash up real good. I
don't want to see any charcoal on your car
[both chuckle]
Man, I told you before,
it's chocolate, not charcoal.
[loud heavy metal music]
All right. Hands up. Touch your head.
[Neil] What the hell...
Get the fuck up.
You have no right...
I've the right of my gun and night stick.
On head. How old are you?
14.
Shouldn't you be at school?
I'm late.
32 days of truancy is pretty fucking late.
Oh, my God. What's happening?
Back off, lady! This your daughter?
Yes. Her name is Marsha.
[Neil] You can't bust
somebody for skipping school.
How about contempt of a cop,
huh? Or disorderly conduct?
Uh-oh. Possession of controlled substances.
Man, those are my cigarettes.
No. My field test tells me when I get these
bad boys back from the lab, they're pot.
You're in a world of
trouble. A world of trouble.
Everything okay?
I'm on parole.
Oh, great.
Then you shouldn't have close encounters
of the third grade. ain't that right,
DeBruler?
That's right.
Please, let him go. Mother, please.
Hey, hey, girl! Look at me.
Now Mom can't do anything for you.
Come on, you'll never see me again.
Neal!
Look, man, you know her idea totally, okay?
She told me she was 18.
Come on, man.
Officer, come on, I mean,
maybe he's telling the truth.
Yeah, man, no shit. That's the truth.
I'm gonna let you got this time, all right?
[removes handcuffs]
Come back for seconds, and I'll...
Yeah!
Now you.
What time is class?
8:30.
No! Class is gonna be 8:27 for you.
I want your ass there every day.
Early! In that class, you got me?
Now you're late,
or you miss one more class,
you come in late,
you even fart in study hall,
and I'll send you to a foster home at the
Born Again Missionary. Do you understand?
Yes.
Am I clear?
That's enough. That's enough.
Come on.
Button up your shirt.
Christ.
For a second, I thought you weren't coming.
I told her to keep that
prick out of the house
and get back to school
and she tells me to fuck off.
She doesn't listen to me any more, Rhoades
like, do you think she's having sex?
I haven't had a man over in 17 months.
Listen, come by the diner and I'll
bake you a hot apple pie. Okay?
This is my partner,
DeBruler, he loves hot pie.
DeBruler?
Yeah, he's new in town.
What an exotic name.
Listen. You like home cooking?
Yeah.
Come by the diner, I'll fix you up.
I'll bring him by.
Thanks, Rhoades.
You come by!
Nice to see yourself
bonding with the community.
You wanted to put your big nose into the
mix, I didn't want you to feel left out.
Oh, we gotta watch each other's backs,
right?
Exactly. You're learning. Right.
Uh-oh. Flowers?
Let me guess. Could this be for
a certain Anita Bayard of the FBI?
Why don't you take
you're old ass back inside.
Leave me alone. Why don't you?
Listen to me. Take it real easy.
Go slow. Women like that shit.
You know what I mean,
you sort of move in...
You know what I'm saying?
I don't think that's her thing.
I'm not talking about
that. I'm talking about...
You know... doo, da, da, baby.
Look, why don't you go home and
dance with that big woman of yours
and quit giving the kid love talk.
I am the Master of Love.
Just because there's snow on the roof don't
mean there ain't no fire in the furnace.
Andre,
ain't that much snow up there on the roof.
Well, you know grass don't
grow on a busy sidewalk.
[laughs]
Come on, now. Remember. Barefoot.
Hm? Real slow. They like that shit.
Counter. Huh? Brother Andre,
he's your tit man.
Get the action going. All right?
Go, Andre. [chuckles]
All right.
Hey, pretty lady.
I got something for you.
Michael.
What do you say, uh, no baseball hat,
no pressure and um,
thanks for being there the other day.
Bye. Bye.
Hey,
Moose. What's that? You had then do two?
Yeah.
No. No. I got two.
Listen to me, Dopey.
There were three of them,
I got two of them.
What are you arguing about?
Who's got the most flea bites?
[Moose] Hey, why don't you
mind your own business, all right?
Fuck you. I got two.
[laughs]
[hip hop music]
Call backup.
We need backup at South Drive.
[cars roar and sirens]
[cop] Freeze!
Let's get outta here.
[shouting]
Everybody freeze. Lift your hands.
Down! Down!
You motherfucking asshole!
Hands behind your head. Now!
Put your hands up.
[cop] Get down! Get down! Down!
Come on, get down!
Get your ass over here.
Come on. Get up now.
What the fuck are you looking at?
[sprays] Ah!
[cop] Get him. The gun.
Mirk, get back to the fucking car.
You only got a couple
days. Go back to the car.
I know you, don't I? You're the
brother that did Beckstrom, huh?
DeBruler!
[cop] Freeze!
[gunshots]
The next time, let your spear
chucking partner do the running.
That's what they're good at,
besides, who knows? You lay back,
let Rhoades do the chase
and maybe Junior there puts a round
in them before he gets plugged. Let's go.
He's just a kid. He's only what,
12 years old?
No. He's a fucking animal. They're all are.
That's the way it is.
Don't you trust nobody.
They hate us, and we hate them. All right?
At least we got that punk
who killed Beckstrom.
Fuck! who said? Look,
Rhoades doesn't get in the way
of the shine who killed Becky. It's simple.
I see what you mean.
Your partner turned his back on you
the same way he did on Beckstrom.
And that's the bottom line. Look,
Rhoades is one of them.
If he had his way he'd badge any of
those goddamn animals over you any time.
You understand me?
You guys waiting for him to expire or what?
Hey, DeBruler! Power to the people, right?
[nurse] All right, fellas,
you're outta here.
Out that out. Damn!
I thought I was being released.
The Doctor Bayard wants to talk to you.
Hey, momma, there's nothing wrong with him.
Look. I'm serious. Come on.
Hey, rook.
Thank you.
I'm sorry if I let you down.
Look, just get better. Okay?
You scare me like that again and
I'll send you that nurse for a month.
All right.
Thanks for coming.
Yeah. Get well.
[Rhoades] Hey. What's happening?
What are you doing here?
Came by to see how bad
your big-ass square head was.
You okay?
Yeah.
Nowhere they're going.
Listen, you know what? I'm a little tired.
Cool. Cool. I'll leave.
I'll tell you something, though, man.
My first shooting,
a little Mexican girl got killed,
about the same age as that kid today.
Look, I'm fine.
All right?
I don't even know why the fuck you're here.
Why are you doing this?
Doing what?
Acting all buddy buddy
with me around the guys,
why are you doing that?
Afraid they're won't let
you into their little clan?
That's why you're doing it, isn't it?
Kicking me out.
I guess I made a mistake.
Yeah.
Doctor Bayer here for your checkup.
Shit!
You want to tell me about this?
Huh?
Come on, man. What about you?
Can you tell what this FBI lady do?
I'm FBI.
You couldn't tell me that?
Stay out of it!
You guys after the Phantoms?
That's privileged information.
Now why would you cut me outta that?
I've been trying all this
time to get the FBI involved.
Man, I was running a cover.
You were messing with it from the word go.
I didn't know who you were, motherfucker.
Do we understand something here?
My life is on the line.
They're not trying to kill you or you,
They've been after me!
I don't know whose
battle you think this is.
It's mine!
Bullshit.
No. It is mine!
If you jeopardize my agent's cover...
Why would I do that?
Is that logical? Huh?
I don't even know what to say to you.
Alright then, Michael.
What you gonna do?
You could blow this sky high.
I think we can try real hard,
we can pretend we don't get along too well,
huh?
For how long do you know Anita?
I like you hick accent better, man.
Look, my Mom's really from Tennessee,
so you can stop with all
the fucking insults, okay?
515 responding.
Get your fucking foot off the dash.
Honey, look at this.
Mommy will be right back.
[children talk]
Over here!
Thank God, you're here.
There's something down
there. You gotta do something.
All right. We got it. Okay. Thank you.
[children play and giggle]
I said go back!
Aw, look at this, brand-new fucking shoes.
Oh, man. Check this out.
Oh, God. [sighs]
This is a handcuff mark.
That's for the coroner for to decide.
No, that's for the coroner to
confirm. It's a handcuff mark.
This kid was beaten to death.
We got two more over here.
Same thing.
Fucking Tavola.
What you got?
Fucking Moose.
Flip top.
Tavola always breaks
the flip top off his beer can.
The night of Beckstrom's funeral
these kids were hanging around.
Then you're a witness.
No. It puts them at the scene.
Just can't tie it... Son of a bitch.
What?
Tattoos.
Moose and Grant, I heard them
argue over who got credit for the kills.
They said that exactly?
The bastards keep score.
You know what? We ain't got
shit. Nothing in a court of law.
All we have is three
dead kids and a flip top.
Moose didn't beat them
to death with a beer can.
We have nothing!
[train roars by]
[singing "For He's A Jolly Good Fellow"]
♪ For he's a jolly good asshole ♪
And now he's on the street
[laughing and cheering]
Come on. Come on.
[chuckles]
[Jensen] Hey, Ernie, baby.
Jesus. So, Ernie,
still working Personnel down at jail, huh?
Ray got all fucking month.
Yeah, we got one of your guys,
DeBruler, good man.
Who?
DeBruler. Over there,
playing pool, with the flat top.
Ah.
Never seen him before in my fucking life.
What? You've never seen this guy?
No.
I'll catch you later, Ernie.
Hey, sweetheart!
What are you gonna do?
Maybe go out to the race track,
do a little fishing.
I got no big plans.
No. No. No.
I mean about the Grand Jury.
Grand Jury?
I don't know nothing about no Grand Jury.
Look. Why don't you just tell them
the Phantoms are a softball team?
Bill. You know that
that's what I will tell them.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're right, Mirk,
just forget about it. Okay?
You want some cake?
[train]
[Jensen] [muffled] Hey, Moose!
[clinking of keys]
[Jensen] [muffled] Moose!
[Moose] What?
Hey, Moose. Check this out.
You won't believe this shit.
[turns TV on]
[Moose] I admired you once.
Moose.
[gasps]
[breathes heavily]
Hey, Moose.
What's happening?
You should never have
agreed to talk to the Grand Jury.
I'd never tell 'em nothing.
I know that gun.
That's Ericsson's.
[breathing heavily] Did I upset you?
No.
[ominous drone]
[sound of trigger] I'm glad to hear that.
Holy shit! Moose!
Fuck.
[clattering sound]
Hey. He coulda got us all hanged.
Eyler wasn't gonna do anything.
Somebody's gotta take charge.
Why don't you wait outside?
I'll be down in a minute.
[buzz]
[radio] Rhoades.
Yeah, Andre.
A call just came in something's
up at 4732 Fair Oaks.
That's Mirk's address.
Right. I though you might want to get there
before the circus arrives.
Officer! Over here! Over here!
Yeah. Right over here.
[postman] Right over there.
[Rhoades] Don't touch anything.
[Rhoades] Shit!
Rhoades. Check this out.
Mirkovich was a Phantom?
Yeah, a long time ago.
What's wrong with the inscription?
I don't know. Disciples time.
Yeah, but in "Disciples",
the "L" goes backwards.
This one goes forwards.
So what do you say this is? A setup?
We might have the Phantom gun.
Let's hope.
[sighs]
He was a friend of mine.
A good friend.
Stand up!
[Eyler] Show some respect!
There are no words when
some scumbag kills your partner.
I want you guys to hit the street,
pick up anything that moves,
and squeeze them until they squeal!
Is that clear?
[all] Yes, sir.
[drone]
Alright, then, let's go!
Got something to show you.
So, uh, Mirk and Eyler were partners, huh?
Yeah, they were partners.
Boy, even after Mirk gave up the group.
Hey, who told you to bring him, huh?
Who told you you could decide
who comes in to my fucking office?
I say DeBruler's all right.
If there's a problem...
There is no problem. I
still call the shots here.
[louder] Right?
Okay, Tavola.
What is it? What do you want?
I organized a little
party tonight at the jail.
Tonight?
That's right. For Beckstrom.
The jig who killed him is in there.
What about Mirk, huh?
You given a second thought to
Mirk? Potter ain't going nowhere.
The animal who killed Mirk
is still in the fucking street.
So? Let's send a message to
the fucking jungle loud and clear.
Am I right, fellas?
Yeah.
All right.
That makes sense.
So you're coming with us, huh?
That's good.
Let's see what you're made of.
[phone rings] Hello? Records.
Hey, Pearline! Yeah?
Thanks a lot. 5 gets you 10
you're having pot roast again.
Oh, yeah?
[suspense music]
You were right with your crazy ass self,
just like you suspected.
Those arrogant assholes used the same
gun to kill Mirk. The ballistics match!
What do you do when the gang goes blue,
huh?
That's right.
We get the Phantom gun and
we nail these motherfuckers.
I think I know where they keep
it and to prove it I'll get a warrant.
Whoa. You said, "We"?
Don't I get a vote? I got
almost 25 years on the force
you go out with this information
and my ass is on the line with yours.
We ain't good to nobody dead, Rhoades.
Are you sure you want
to trust the white boy?
The little FBI girl?
Don't make no check with
your mouth that we can't cash.
It's your call.
[engines roar and radio walla]
[metal clanking and buzz]
Potter.
Who killed Mirkovich?
Aw, man. How am I supposed
to know when I'm locked up?
Who killed Mirkovich?
All right, listen. I'll check
with my boys on the street.
It wasn't us. Me and my
crew don't know shit about shit.
Have it your way.
[ominous music]
What are you doing?
What's the deal? What are you doing?
What the fuck do you do that for?
I didn't do it. You did it.
When you tried to jump me asshole.
[blows whistle]
[alarms set off] No. No!
[jailer] You're hurting
me. He's attacking me.
[alarms and jailer yelling]
[Potter] No. This is s set up.
I didn't do nothing. It's a set up.
Hey, yo'll. I didn't do anything. Nothing!
[Potter] No. I didn't do nothing.
[clanking]
[Potter] I didn't do it! Agh!
[general shouting and swearing]
Go!
Come on, will ya? Take a shot.
[alarms, shouting and blows]
Come on!
Agh! Ugh.
[yelling stops]
Hm.
What's this word? E - X - C - A...
What are you,
nuts? It's not an "X", it's an "S".
"Escape". Come on.
Oh, yeah. [chuckles]
"Prisoner fell downstairs
attempting escape."
So this how it goes down,
nobody's gonna question it?
Don't worry about it.
You'll get used to it.
No one's gonna question a sworn
statement from all these officers.
Excuse me, can I borrow you a second?
Yeah, sure.
Where are you going?
It's no problem, a little police business.
Hey, Kojak,
why don't you watch your back, huh?
Tell the Lieutenant what you told me.
Bring me the log.
Tell the Lieutenant, not the whole room.
[Ernie] Okay.
Every rookie officer that came
out of the Academy is in here,
where they did guard duty, how long,
their final assignment...
Ernie, cut to the chase. Show
him what you showed me.
I checked the log.
DeBruler's name was put in
there in the Warden's office.
So what are you getting at?
It's a fake. The warden
doesn't make entries in the log.
So I look around, checked around.
That guy never worked here.
So how does the name get in the book?
Someone with clout
must've called the warden's
and said they want it to look like
this guy did his jail assignment here.
But who?
What the hell's the difference?
IA, prosecutor's office.
The point is this bastard is under cover.
And he's taking a long hard look at us.
So Bill, maybe I'm not such
a stupid moron after all, huh?
Relax, Moose, will ya?
So what you gonna do about
this? What more do you need?
Look, I'll take care of it. Alright?
Thanks.
Fellas!
I think it's time for
a little trip to Code 7.
I thought we were going out
in the street to find Mirk's killer.
Short stop. Gotta get the right
weapon for the right job, right fellas?
[all] Right!
[knocking on door]
Keith, did you forget your keys again?
[gasps]
Waiting for DeBruler in your church dress?
What are you doing here?
I came about getting a warrant,
but maybe you don't have
time for business right now, huh?
Are those my files?
The ones you pretend not to read?
Yes.
You based your operation on my work, huh?
Or is that none of my business too?
We wanted to tell you.
I know, I just don't really
see the big picture too well
You two put a whole new meaning
in undercover work here now.
Is this about your file or is
it about who I sleep with?
It's about being used.
I don't mind being useful.
I mind being used. There's a difference.
Micheal, wait.
You wanted the FBI to get
involved? We got involved.
You deal with these
pigheaded fools everyday?
Do you think the feds are in a hurry
to rush in and bust a bunch of racist cops?
I've had to plot to make this happen.
I sent the man that I love undercover,
not for the promotion
but because I care about stopping them.
Because I care about you.
That's the truth.
[pager]
Oh, shit.
What's wrong?
They're on to your boy.
Thanks for letting me known.
Keith's cover's been blown.
The quickest we can mobilize is an hour.
If the Phantoms are on to DeBruler,
he may not have an hour.
Well, maybe they won't do anything.
Now they know he's FBI,
maybe they won't mess with him.
Now they killed Mirkovich.
He's one of them and they blew
his ass away with Ericsson's gun.
The best shot is to get
me that warrant. Okay?
I'm going to Code Seven. Get me the
warrant now. I need it now. Right away!
[suspense music]
[crack]
[hammers]
[sound of train passing by]
Lieutenant. Moose.
[Jensen] Isn't that the Rhoads' car?
Son of a bitch, it is.
Go!
There comes a time in every man's
life when he has to take a stand.
Hey, Moose. What's the deal, man?
Get the hell outta here.
[male] Go. Go. Go.
[male] Move! Move!
[Moose] Rhoades?
[Moose] Whoa! Hold your fire!
[Moose] You shouldn't be here.
You know that, don't you?
[pulls trigger]
The jig is up.
[sniggers]
Hey, come on.
[Rhoades] Huh?
Hey!
Come on, bitch, I'll treat you like a king.
Get up, fucker.
Come on, Moose.
That's right, I'm right here, baby.
Let him free.
Come on! Agh!
Get up, man!
Get up, Moose!
We got your boy with your own boy.
Come on.
Oh, you motherfucker.
Whoa, Moose.
It's all right. He's my partner.
I'll deal with it.
Not here. Not smart.
Well,
there's no time like the present, son.
Check him.
Don't fucking move.
What's this about?
He's clean. There's no way.
It's about honor.
About a sense of responsibility.
We have all taken a test,
and we have passed.
Me, Mirkovich, everybody.
Is this about Mirkovich's ghost story?
Mirk had a bad habit of leaving
out some parts of our story.
You see these five guys here?
These five bastards killed Ericsson.
The Phantom ghost who avenged
him were me and Mirkovich off duty.
We found the first one
over here just by luck.
Big dumb coon,
flashing Ericsson's badge and his gun.
So we just turned it on him, you know?
We held it right up to his head. Pissed
his pants and gave up all his partners.
Boom! [all laugh]
See? Then we pick them up, one at a time.
One at a time.
We got 'em all.
That was the beginning. Me and Mirkovich.
You started the Phantoms.
It's about history, Keith, and tradition.
That's what binds society together.
That's why when the Phantoms strike,
we use Ericsson's gun.
That's right.
When we find the nigger
that killed Mirkovich,
Ericsson's gun's gonna go boom again.
Yeah, it's a duty, it's an honor
to carry out that tradition, Keith.
So why don't you just step up?
Join us.
It's not right. He's my partner.
Yeah, well.
He brought all this down on his own head.
Come on.
Show us what you're made of.
Go on, General.
If you don't kill that nigger right now,
I'm gonna do it.
Step right up.
No. No. No. Put it right up to his head.
Go on.
That's it.
[Eyler] Now pull the trigger.
Do it nice and easy though,
so you don't miss.
Do it!
No.
I'm FBI.
FBI! Now we're fucking screwed!
You motherfuckers.
I'm gonna put you in a
hole so deep and dark,
they'll never find your fucking bodies.
Anything happens to us
and the Feds will rain down
on you like you've never seen.
Sometimes a brave
officer dies in the crossfire,
specially when his bad black partner's
been caught dealing drugs
to brothers in the hood.
Man, that bullshit will never fly.
[laughs] Well, I got a magic pencil.
Don't I, fellas?
Right on!
Besides, who's gonna convict us?
We're the thin blue line
that keeps the animals back.
We got dirt on half the officials
in this county in those files!
We have affiliate groups, we got contacts,
In every single state.
You have no idea what you're up against.
You piece of shit.
[chuckles]
Yeah. Uh-huh.
Do it. Do it.
Hey.
What about tradition?
Why don't you kill us with Ericsson's gun,
huh?
The way Moose did Mirkovich.
[All] What?
Shut your fucking nigger mouth.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You blew him away, didn't you, Moose?
Huh? You blew Mirk away.
That's why Ericsson's gun ain't there,
right?
You fucking piece of shit...
Hey, hey. Shut up.
Go check it now. Go!
Check fucking what? What
the fuck are you talking about?
Shut up. Please. Shh.
It ain't there.
What do you mean?
What are they talking about?
Look,
I don't know a thing. I swear to God...
Jensen, shut up.
No, you shut up.
Grant.
Lieutenant, I don't know what's going on.
Moose. Moose, I saw something in your bag.
No, Brad, no. You didn't
see a fucking thing in my bag...
This fucking nigger can't
prove a fucking thing.
Yeah, that's bullshit. You know that.
The ballistic report shows Mirk
was killed with Ericsson's gun, Moose,
and you fucking did it.
Where is it, Moose. Huh?
Where is it?
He was passed it, Bill, you know that.
He was way past it.
He was gonna sing to the Grand Jury.
I did the right thing.
He did. Come on.
Bill, you wouldn't do it. He
was your fucking partner.
I did what I was supposed to do, Billy!
Shut up, Moose.
Just shut the fuck up!
Billy, come on.
We're in this together.
You did it!
[train passes]
You killed Mirkovich! [gunshot]
DeBruler! Go! Come on, man!
No ammo.
There. There!
[Rhoades] Come on. Move in on.
Rhoades!
What the fuck we gonna do?
We got enough shit here
to hang us ten times over!
There's more of us than there are of them,
okay?
So go out! Go wide! Go, go!
We'll get 'em round the back way. Come on!
[gunshot]
Agh!
Thanks for the tip,
Moose. [breathes heavily]
Stand up. Come on.
How many people did you kill with this?
How many fucking
people did you kill with it!
What difference does it make. Huh?
Your people kill each other
quicker than we ever could.
You're finished, you piece of shit!
Maybe not today, but we'll get ya.
[chuckles]
You're a dead man.
[spins barrel]
Then don't spoil the moment for me.
Come on!
You pansy-ass chicken shit! Come on,
pull the fucking trigger!
Shut up!
Fuck!
Look at me, Eyler.
I'm the man you hate. Look at me.
Put it down, son
Stay the fuck back,
Andre. This is between me and him, man.
[Rhoades] Stay the shit outta this.
Over here. Come on,
Stay back.
What's going on?
Don't fuck up your life.
But I've been fucked up.
The moment I want to get
these motherfuckers, man!
We both want to see it's through.
Wrong! This ain't about black,
it ain't about white.
It's about right, man.
Chicken shit.
Come on, brother.
Don't become them.
God.
[Andre] The guy then turned to the Feds,
and the Feds are pissing
on each other's uniform.
Ericsson's gun is gonna be here
to go to the FBI Ballistics Center.
And the Grand Jury's getting a special
prosecutor to go after the Phantoms.
Anita wants to be named
FBI Director by morning.
But she'll settle for a
Supreme Court Justice.
You weren't exactly
going through the channels
but I guess you opened a
few spots down the road.
I'm proud of you.
You got me here, Andre.
I mean it, son.
I'm really proud of ya.
Hey!
They kicked your ass.
Partner.
[chuckles]
Congratulations, Agent Bayard.
Agent DeBruler,
we're looking at
arraignments in the morning.
[Anita] I was so worried.
[Rhoades] DeBruler!
Ahh.
Rhoades.
Fucker shot my partner.
It's over.
[breathes heavily]
Go to him.
Go on. He needs you. Go. Let's go.
Keith.
I'm here.
[Anita] I'm here.
Hang on.
Closed-Captioned By J.R. Media Services,
Inc. Burbank, CA