Forgive me, baby.
Please don't go away.
You'll never have to worry,because I'm here to stay.
You've got to believe it.
Baby, please don't leave it.
Forgive me, baby.
Please don't go away.
From now on, baby, I wantto be right by your side.
Yes, from now on, baby, I'mgoing to be right by your side.
You've got to
forgive me, baby.
Yes, you've got to
Please promise me you'll stay.
If you can stick aroundmore than a month or two,
you might be able to
finish this thing.
They're moving your
brother up north today.
The god damn death penalty--
I suppose it doesn't
matter where you go.
Well, you know, I think Joe chose
that road a long time ago.
DAD: I guess Joe shouldhave taken care of business
in one of those
third-world countries,
got a license to
kill like you, huh?
I went to visit him lastweek, and he asked about you.
How's Joe's head?
Well, you know Joe.
Nothing seems to botherhim except being locked up.
Mm.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you look great.
Your husband is going tofall in love all over again.
Tracey, we out of here?
Definitely.
Let me just clean
up around here.
And I'll meet you
outside in five.
Did you hear Alanis
is coming to Dallas?
Girl, the show is
sold out already.
Well, what do you expect?
Nobody ever comes to Fort Worth.
Plaza-- Fort Worth
Shopping Plaza.
We're under attack!
Everywhere.
This ain't a joke.
I'm telling you.
POLICE: Get him out of there.
Stay together.
Settle down.
All right, I got us here.
Now get us out.
Time for a party.
We got to have a party.
Let's try not to hurt anybody.
Yeah, right.
All hell broke loose.
Your brother and some
others busted out.
Well, I never did see Joeletting the goddamn state
put him to sleep.
Killing a drug
dealer is one thing.
This time, there'sinnocent people involved.
What are you going
to do about it, son?
When you get there,
if there is a decision
to be made about yourbrother's future, you make it.
Don't let them.
I haven't been there
for Joe in the past.
This time, I'm not walking away.
He's my brother.
I'm going to get
him out of there.
What the fuck is this shit?
I'm delivering you
21st-century quality.
And you talk to me
like a Neanderthal.
Do you know who I am?
Do you know who I
know, like, globally?
Think yourself.
The last time I saw hardwarelike this was in Kuwait.
Where'd you get this shit?
So you in?
I ain't got nothing
else to do, so.
M16-203 with a grenade
launcher underneath.
Imagine a gun that's
smokeless, near
silent, with case-less ammo.
It means there's nothing
flying out where it
shouldn't-- the case
converting inside
the chamber into
rocket propelling
for its armor piercing rounds.
Get them while
they're hot, boys.
Billy?
Yeah.
Can you handle that?
Oh, yeah.
I can take care of things.
WOMAN: I don't want to die.
I don't want to die today.
I want to go-- let me go home!
Oh, I don't want to die.
I don't want to die!
I want to go home!
I don't want to--
Shut the fuck up!
I don't want to die!
I want to go home!
That's one less
fucking cowboy.
NEWSCASTER: Officials speculatethat one of the escapees
from the bus, convicted moneylaunderer Howard Daniels,
may have been
behind the breakout.
Daniels' corporate
headquarters is
based in the same
mall where the hostage
crisis has taken a deadly turn.
So, what do you
got back there, Wood?
I mean Hardwood-- just
joking, just joking.
Jesus, Mac, they're fortifyingtheir whole position here.
Yeah, what with?
I don't know what that is.
Here's your profile, sir.
Oh, thank you.
Damn, I don't know
he was on the bus--
Wallace Black.
Last minute thing.
Multiple contract
killings, a rape,
murder he got acquitted for.
Then he takes out that
casino owner in Reno.
God damn-- 20 pieces
in a dumpster.
Makes the rest of theseguys look like Boy Scouts.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
But Joe Ray didn't just
kill that drug dealer.
He took out his whole operation.
He did away with thecompetition, so to speak.
Boy, this thing can get messy.
Well, I'll be dipped.
Rudy, I didn't
know you were back.
They'll be a triage
unit set up right here.
Let's keep clear of this area.
Let's keep clear now.
How the hell did
you get in here?
I learned from you, man.
Well, I obviously didn't
teach you very well.
You wouldn't-- you know,they got me running things,
at least for now, anyway.
The feds will be here
soon enough, though.
You bet your ass.
You let the feds
in here, you're
going to have anothergoddamn Waco on your hands.
Shit, man.
Don't even think about that.
I mean, I suppose you
know how to handle this.
I know my brother.
Yeah.
How much time can you give me?
Aw, Rudy, we don't workthat way around here no more.
Oh, man, this is pathetic.
It's just pathetic shit.
Now he has some militaryhardware, and all we've got
is a bunch of pissant
9 millimeters.
Rudy!
Shit.
What's up with
the suit, Howard?
Prison blue not your color?
It's the party
that never ends, Joe.
Step inside.
Step outside.
Please, enter.
Make yourself
extremely comfortable.
Sit anywhere.
Sit anywhere you like, anywhere.
Sit there.
It's a gorgeous chair.
It's Michael Graves.
It's very comfortable.
I paid $70,000 for that chair.
It better fucking
be comfortable.
He wanted 20.
I talked him down--
prick.
So this is my little playground.
You like, hm?
I run all of my
operations out of here.
No one asks any questions,fabulous loading dock,
perfect front, very legitimate.
You look like a
drinking man, Joe--
very passionate.
Shall we?
MAN: There's a lot
of fire down here.
That's enough.
We had an agreement.
You put up the money.
I hired the guys
to break us out.
Then you fly our
ass out of here.
So where's the
helicopter, Howard?
It'll be here, Joe.
What about the boys on the bus?
Now, they weren't part
of the plan, were they?
Shut up.
What was I supposed to
do, leave them there?
As far as I'm concerned, we alldeserve a chance like anybody
else, except for maybe Wallace.
I'm starting to haveserious doubts about you.
Trust me.
The only possible delaycould be a weather condition.
He said he'll be here.
He'll be here.
Get us out of here.
The feds show up, the
negotiations stop.
And they will kick
our ass, Howard.
HOWARD: On the
country, my friend.
It'll be fun, actually.
Because I'm going to distractthem with our demands.
What demands?
We don't have any
fucking demands!
I can be quite demanding.
Welcome to the big time, kid.
Nice clothes.
Mm.
You smell good, so good.
Sh, sh, sh, sh, sh.
Don't move.
Sh, sh.
No!
Sh!
Hey, fat!
You're breaking
my concentration.
Sh, sh, sh, sh, sh, sh.
I know you want to do me, bitch.
But first, we get
to do my friend.
Uh, uh, uh.
Yeah, yes, yeah, yeah, oh, yeah.
OK.
Oh, yeah.
Now for something real special.
Oh, god.
Sh, sh, sh.
What the hell is this?
These demands are a
bunch of shit, Howard.
It's called creative
confusion, my friend.
Take care of the men, Collum.
What the fuck are you
guys doing down there?
Oh, Jesus Christ, Wallace,put your Dick in your pants.
I got cobwebs on my nut sack.
And homeboy here
wants to be a hero.
This will take
your mind off it.
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
BILLY: Hey!
We got a problem.
You know this could
quite possibly
go down as the stupidest goddamn jailbreak known to man.
A guy gets caught 20 feet away,and you don't see anything?
Hey, I didn't hear anything.
Well, if the big chief herewasn't so busy trying to get
himself a goddamn blow job.
How about I do a blow job onyour brains all over the wall?
JOE: All right, all right, allright, enough with the blow
jobs.
I didn't bust my ass out ofthe penitentiary to start
a babysitting career
with you guys.
Come on, Wallace, why
don't you try and take
it easy on these people?
Call it a hunch, we just
might need them later.
Look here.
I didn't ask to be, right?
But I'm here now.
You give me two of
your boy, all right?
Then we'll find
this son of a bitch,
and I'm going to kill him.
Cover me.
Unbe-fucking-lievable.
You, to the left--
to the right.
HOWARD: No, no, no this is-- no.
This is how we're going to play.
See, you're the
genie in the lamp.
And what I'm going to do isI'm going to rub the lamp.
And you're going
to
pop out, and give
me three wishes, OK?
Doesn't that sound like fun?
Tell me your name,
Mr. Policeman.
This is Sergeant Hardwood.
Ha- Hardwood?
Sergeant Hardwo--
I'm sorry.
Get the fuck off the phone.
Give me that damn phone.
Two people are dead so far.
Do we understand each other?
OK.
I want three fully-fueled,fully-outfitted 747s.
I want one at DFW.
I want one at Houston
Intercontinental.
And I want one at San Antonio.
I want new ones, none of
those crappy retreads.
Are we understood?
Right now, I'm--
I'm getting a bit of a migraine.
So I'll have to call you back.
Son of a bitch.
This guy's good.
Hey, I could use a bump.
What do you got?
I said, what do you got?
Oh, shit.
What are you
eyeballing, cop killer?
You want to taste that?
You want me to slice
you off a chunk?
Ignore him.
He's an idiot.
Son of a gun!
Don't worry.
It will be OK.
Will it?
I hope.
What are you doing
with these guys, anyway?
Don't-- please.
It's just hard
for me to believe
you're a cold-blooded killer.
I'm no killer.
I'm not.
Anyway, what does
it matter to you?
Nobody gives a shit.
I caught some bad luck.
I had a good job.
I was playing in a
band in New Orleans.
I was good.
So I came on here trying
to find another job.
But no job, no money rightnow, sleeping on benches.
I was starving.
I was desperate.
I got a hold of
this little gun I
found in the park, no bullets.
So I went to this
convenience store.
I stuck this gun
in this man's face.
All I wanted was
some goddamn food.
I grabbed the keys to histruck, ran out of the backdoor.
All I could think of was eatingthe shit I'd just stolen.
I turned the corner
a little too fast.
I had some cops on my ass.
God, I was scared.
I couldn't see anything.
I smashed into another copcar and killed two of them.
I got death sentence.
Hell, maybe I deserve it.
No, no.
My name's Tracey.
Hi.
SONNY: He's a killer.
Watch your ass, partner.
Because that's what I'm goingto be doing from here on in,
looking out after my ass.
Where the fuck is Wallace?
We got every cop in
Texas outside, Wallace.
You think you could be a
little more productive?
What in the fuck
are you doing?
Well, you got a problem?
Don't start, guys.
We got shit to
take care of here.
Come on, Mama,
let's take a walk.
Can you hear me, cops?
Do I have attention?
Now, if you don't get
your men out of here--
What are you doing, baby?
That's going to
become a habit!
You scared, kid?
Yes, I'm scared.
Everybody's scared.
Who did you kill to get here?
I killed a man.
17 years in the Marine Corps--
I joined up straight
out of high school.
I've been everywhere
I loved my job.
I loved it every day.
I married my--
married my sweetheart
on her 16th birthday.
The first time we ever laideyes on each other, I was--
what-- in the fourth grade.
She was in the second.
After my discharge, I
had this new business.
One day, I'm fighting this--
this bad flu I had.
And I forgot themedication the doc gave me.
So I had go on back
home and get it.
And I couldn't
believe what I saw.
It was like a goddamn nightmare.
But there was my CO gettingdown with my old lady.
It's kind of funny when
I think about it now,
that little old Marine
Corps tattoo on his ass
going up and down, up and down.
And there he is,
standing up, butt
naked with a hard dick talkingabout, wait, wait, wait,
you don't understand.
You don't understand!
I understood.
I understood all too well.
I just grabbed that sonof a bitch round the neck.
And I squeezed.
And then I stabbed him 14 times.
I put my knife in him.
I twisted it until I wassure his heart was hamburger.
I cut this throat--
Randall, model number 14.
I carried that knife
through three campaigns.
I finally found a
good use for it.
Are you in charge here?
I wondered when you'd
boys come rolling in.
San Antonio?
Yeah.
Say, aren't y'all the onesthat handled that Waco deal?
Ouch.
Now, we understand
you let a heavily-armed
mercenary walk right in there.
Say you couldn't stop it.
He was one of mine.
Well, that's very
touching-- for bullshit.
Born in El Paso, Texas, June,1960, former Marine service
in the Far East, contractcivilian mercenary
in Afghanistan and El Salvador.
El Salvador, right.
'88 to '89.
Indicted in '91, NeutralityAct, charges dropped,
turns up in Africa in SierraLeone, military advisor
to government, bailed out--
Do you mean want whatreally interests me here?
No.
What's that?
Is this boy of yours wasa Texas Rangers for three
years right here in Fort Worth.
And I'll be damned.
He walked off the job.
He was my partner.
Not anymore.
Later.
HOWARD: I want 3 milliondollar bonds, 2 in Swiss francs
and 2 in Deutsche marks.
I want the money wired
to the Credit Suisse
then to Grand Cayman.
I'm going to have
to call you back.
While you've been
in here dicking
around accomplishing nothing,we've just lost five guys.
Now you do what you
gotta do, and you
get us the fuck out of here.
I'm done playing
with you, Howard.
You got an hour.
Oh, dear, that wasn't
very nice, now was it?
Excuse me?
I really need to
use the ladies room.
I'm going to have to
come with you, though.
Hey!
Where are you going
with my bitch?
Don't worry.
I'm ain't going to
rape or kill her.
I'm just letting
her use the can.
Oh.
I think it's the other one.
Yeah.
Sh.
Can I still pee?
Knock yourself out.
You know what to do.
Careful-- wouldn't want
to leave without you.
Well, I missed you, bro.
I had a feeling I'd
be seeing you here.
You're wasting
all my guys, Rudy.
I'm just doing
what I gotta do, Joe.
And you do it good.
So what do we do
now, kill each other?
How do you want
to handle this?
How do I want to handle what?
I'll get you out of here.
You're my brother, Joe.
I ain't going to
let nobody kill you.
The state's already
gonna kill me.
Your friend's hurtinga lot of innocent people.
I can get you out of here, bro.
Go home, Rudy.
OK?
That fag is just fuckingwith your head, bro.
I know.
An electrician, yes.
So you're the one I come
to when I feel dark.
He's safe.
Get it?
Ooh, a wet one.
Yes.
Mm.
Darling, fix this.
Yes, much better.
Well, I'm about to make anotherfew requests of our friends
on the outside.
If anyone needs anything
special, now's the time.
Don't be shy, old man.
Is this Sergeant Hardwood?
How are you, darling?
Guess who?
Well, um, I just need a fewmore requests if you don't mind.
I'm feeling sort of like,well, some chocolates, Godiva--
fucking decadent.
I fucking love it.
Yeah, because-- well, I knowit's not very good on a figure.
But I have terrible sweet tooth.
What the hell?
You only live once.
And, uh, make sure it's the goodstuff, none of that cheap crap
or I'll fucking Van Gogh
someone's fucking ear.
Do you hear me?
No requests?
Three bottles of wine, halfpint of whiskey, and a case
of beer.
Ooh, we're having a party.
Any particular brand?
Yeah.
Enough of the games, Howard.
Your hour's up.
I"ll have to call you back.
Let's kick some serious butt.
Excuse me.
But I think that's
a terrible idea.
Maybe ought to stop thinking.
Start taking notes.
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe his ass.
I saw him moving
through the promenade.
Have a ball, fellows.
What?
What the hell is that?
Where'd that come from?
Welcome to the Alamo, boys.
We're fucked.
Howard's rigged thewhole damn mall the blow.
This shit's all over the place.
How are we going
to get out of here?
Maybe we're not.
Dose somebody got a quarter?
Bruce fucking Lee!
I just want you
to know one thing.
I love you.
And I have never, ever,
ever stopped loving you.
And I never, ever will.
Hey, now, calm down, baby.
Calm down, will you?
What's the matter, huh?
What's the matter, baby?
I want you to get thesepeople out of here, Billy.
We're running out of time.
Who the fuck are you?
Nobody.
Well, you've got
to be somebody.
Joe's my brother.
It's your movie, soldier.
I ain't looking forward tospending the rest of my life
in no cage, mister.
Oh, shit!
No shit.
Hurry up!
What's the matter, baby?
Who's the bad baby?
Who's the bad?
Ow!
God!
What you doing, Howard?
Leaving without me?
Of course not, Joe,
for Christ's sake.
We thought you were dead.- Shut up.
Just shut up.
Oh, Joe, Joe.
Joe, I know you're probablyafraid of dying here.
I certainly am.
I ain't afraid of dyinghere or anywhere, Howard.
I am afraid of doing
it without you, though.
HOWARD: Oh, god, Joe, Joe.
I have a little surprise.
There's a tunnel, a tunnel, Joe.
It lead to the old stormdrains about a mile away.
Leaving without me, Joe?
That wasn't very nice.
Howard, old man,
pick up the phone.
Pick it up.
Pick it up!
Howard, yes, send someonedown here, please.
Howard, please--
oh, fuck you, you
fucking-- put that on the line.
I don't know who.
Someone's trying to kill me.
Oh, Christ, do something.
Do something.
I'll call you back.
You'll be unconscious in 20seconds, dead in three minutes.
Joe.
Sh.
Hey, Rud.
I'm right here.
I should have stayed
on the bus, huh?
RUDY: Sh.
Hey, it's OK, all right?
Yeah.
Tell the old man
I'm sorry, yeah?
He knows.
I'd sure like to smoke a joint.
I got a joint, Joe.
Where the fuck
did you get bud?
I got it in your
glove compartment.
You're driving my car?
Man, I had me some
fun in that car.
How's it running, Rud?
Hey, Joe, it's fast.
I'm here, Joe.
I ain't feeling too hot, Rud.
I love you, Joe.
I'll always love you.
I love you.
Joe, I'm right here.
There's a kid in there.
The state's going to kill him.
He ain't bad, Rudy.
You set free, yeah?
Yeah.
You bet your ass, Joe.
I love you, bro.
I know you do.
I love you.
I know you do, Joe.
Yeah.
Joe, Joe.
I love you, Joe.
I love you.
Hey!
What are you doing with
my fucking hostages?
The party's over, pretty boy.
Yes!
What did I do?
Hold your fire!
We've got hostages coming out.
Come on.
Let's go!
You go.
Drop the guns.
show up?
Everybody on the bus beenaccounted for except one,
that kid, Billy Cobb.
You wouldn't happen to knowanything about that, would you?
Sonny, he saw the
other one go down.
They all been accounted for.
You know, you
never did tell me
why you just walked in oneday, and laid down your badge,
and never come back.
I didn't feel good.
It didn't have anything to dowith your brother, Joe, did it?
It had a lot to do
with my brother, Joe.
You know, Rudy, you
both ran the fast track.
You got off.
And he just kept going.
You've done everything
you could for him.
Maybe I could have done more.