[phone ringing]
♪ BA-DA BA-DA ♪
♪ BA-DA BA-DUM ♪
♪ BA-DA BA-DUM BUM ♪
♪ TO TELL US WHAT TO DO ♪
♪ BA-DA ♪
- ♪ BUM BA-DA BUM ♪
[cranes calling loudly]
♪ ♪
♪ BUM BUM ♪
♪ BA-DA ♪
SHIT, MY WALLET.
- UH...
IS THAT OKAY?
[distorted guitar music]
NO, I DON'T NEED
TO GO TO A HOSPITAL.
- YOU'RE DRUNK.
"WHEN IT IS A DAMP, DRIZZLING
NOVEMBER IN MY SOUL,
"IT REQUIRES A STRONG MORAL
PRINCIPLE TO PREVENT MYSELF
- NO.
- LISTEN.
- YEAH.
- I DON'T KNOW.
I CAME TO AMERICA
TO MEET A GIRL.
- GREAT; WHERE'S THE GIRL?
SHE WAS REALLY PRETTY.
SHE HAD THIS
KIND OF CHEERLEADER HAIR.
FOR SIX HOURS,
LIKE A SPOON.
AND THEN SHE SHOWED UP
WITH HER BOYFRIEND.
HER EX-BOYFRIEND.
- I NEED TO TAKE YOU SOMEWHERE.
HE SAID HE LIKED TALL GIRLS,
AND SHE WAS LITTLE.
SHE'S A LITTLE GIRL.
- NO.
- OH, OKAY.
- DO YOU HAVE A PHONE
THAT I COULD USE?
YOU WERE MY HUSBAND!
I AM NOWHERE!
I'M NOWHERE!
I'M NEVER GONNA FIND--
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA FIND ME!
NO!
I--YOU--
I CAN'T--I LITERALLY CANNOT
BELIEVE THAT YOU FUCKED HER.
I AM--I--
I'M MARRIED TO YOU.
AND EVERYTHING,
AND I--
SHUT UP!
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NEVER GONNA--
I'M NOT.
IT'S UH, UH, UH--
ENJOY IT NOW, FUCKING ASSHOLE!
EMMA!
ARE YOU IN THERE?
[grunting]
YOU HIDING FROM ME?
LET HER KNOW
THAT I WILL BE BACK!
AND--
- DOESN'T MATTER.
EXCUSE ME.
- EMMA HICKS DOESN'T WORK HERE
ANYMORE.
SHE--VERY RECENTLY,
SHE HAD TO LEAVE OUR COMPANY.
- DOES ANYONE KNOW WHERE SHE IS?
SHE'LL NEVER WORK HERE AGAIN.
- ARE YOU 21?
- HE'S 21.
WHAT WE CALL THE CELLAR
TO THE BREWERY.
- [echoing]
AH!
WHAT WERE YOU GOING TO DO
TO HER IF SHE WAS HERE?
- WE INVENTED HANG...
"A."
"D."
- "O"?
- "K."
"T."
"L."
- KILL THE BITCH.
♪ ♪
IT'S UPSTAIRS.
[melancholy music]
- LIBYA.
♪ ♪
- EMMA.
EMMA, ARE YOU IN THERE?
[car engine rattling]
DID YOU KILL HER?
AND DEDICATE THEM TO ME.
YOU LOSE YOUR TURN.
IN SCHOOL, I WAS A STAR GYMNAST.
AND MY EVENT WAS THE FLOOR.
AND ONE DAY, IN A COMPETITION,
I WAS TUMBLING.
AT 16, I WAS THE ONLY BOY
IN SCHOOL
TWO.
I CAN END THE GAME.
[sighs]
DON'T TOUCH MY SIDE.
GOOD NIGHT.
WAKE UP.
- [groans]
- ♪ SLEEP IN HEAVENLY PEACE ♪
♪ SLEEP IN HEAVENLY... ♪
- OH.
EXCUSE ME?
DO YOU HAVE ANOTHER ONE
OF THESE FLYERS?
[geese calling]
♪ ♪
YOU KNOW, WHO THE FUCK
DID YOU EXPECT?
FROM YOUR FUCKING GIRLFRIEND?
I WILL KEEP CALLING YOU,
MOTHERFUCKER.
I WILL FUCKING TIE YOU UP
EXACTLY.
LIKE A FUCKING BEDTIME STORY.
GO!
UH-HUH.
OKAY.
OKAY, THANK YOU.
BYE.
[wind blowing]
- WHAT?
- A LITTLE MORE IN THAT ONE.
- THEY FEEL LUMPY.
- YES.
- WHOA.
CHEERS.
- DO YOU LIKE IT?
OKAY.
- SURE.
AND I'LL CALL YOU BACK.
THINGS HAVE BEEN A BIT CRAZY
AROUND HERE.
YOU KNOW,
MY FUCKING WIFE IS, UH--
SHE'S CRYING ALL THE TIME.
BUT I DON'T WANT YOU TO THINK
IT'S YOUR FAULT, BABY.
MY WIFE WAS CRAZY--
CRAZY BEFORE THIS EVER HAPPENED.
AND, YOU KNOW, AND THE STUFF--
IT WAS DISGUSTING.
YOU TEACH YOGA.
YOU'RE HOT.
YOU'RE LITTLE.
AND I NEVER DID LOVE ROSE;
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT.
MY WIFE WAS--
WAS A MISTAKE.
I LOVE YOU.
I HOPE MY WIFE IS DEAD.
- ♪ DON WE NOW OUR GAY APPAREL ♪
- ♪ WE PACKED
ALL WE COULD PACK ♪
♪ I STOPPED ON THE WAY ♪
♪ TO HAVE ME OLD HALF QUARTEN ♪
[cheers and applause]
- OH.
- WHY ARE YOU TAKING--
- NOTHING.
NO, I NEED TO KNOW, UM,
IS EMMA HERE?
OR...
- THERE'S ONE LATER.
- SHE'S NOT HERE.
- AND I CAN COMP YOU GUYS,
IF YOU WANT.
- I'M GONNA GO WAIT OUTSIDE.
- OH.
- WELL, IF SHE WANTS
TO SEE EMMA, SHE--
WE'RE GOING
TO THIS DANCE ON SUNDAY.
IT'S REALLY CRAZY.
AND DANCE WITH OLD PEOPLE,
AND IT'S REALLY FUN.
- IT'S SUNDAY.
- WHERE?
WHERE--WHERE IS IT?
IT'S RIGHT ON THE MAIN DRAG.
- YEAH, YEAH.
IT'LL BE REALLY FUN;
YOU GUYS SHOULD COME.
- BYE; GOOD-BYE.
18.
THE PLAN IS,
IT'S JUST YOU AND ME.
- THAT'S THE PLAN.
- [sighs]
THAT WE'RE GONNA CATCH A FISH.
- ALL RIGHT.
CAN YOU PAY?
[reel clicking]
NOW, KEEP YOUR FINGERS
OUT IN FRONT
SO YOU CAN FEEL THE EEL MOVING,
AND YOU FEEL THE BOTTOM.
- YEAH.
GET A BITE.
FLIP YOUR LEVER DOWN.
GIVE IT A LIFT.
PUT YOUR HAND RIGHT HERE.
AND THEN YOU JUST
GIVE A NICE EASY LIFT.
- WHOA, SOMETHING'S HAPPENING.
SOMETHING--
SOMETHING'S HAPPENING.
- COME ON, COME ON!
YOU GOT IT.
- START WINDING, START WINDING.
- WIND WHAT?
TURN THE HANDLE.
KEEP WORKING HIM.
- I CAN--
- I'M WINDING.
- OH, MY GOD!
[all yell excitedly]
THAT'S WHERE YOU WANT TO BE.
- OKAY, BECAUSE THAT WAY,
YOU WON'T HAVE ANY MEAT LEFT
- RIGHT HERE?
- KEEP IT DOWN LOW.
POINT DOWN LOW.
THERE YOU GO.
- LOOK, I DID THIS.
- THIS IS ALL YOU WANT
RIGHT THERE, OKAY?
- NO, WE DID.
- WHAT?
AND IT WAS A MUTUALLY BENEFICIAL
RELATIONSHIP.
AND WHEN NEEDS CONFLICT,
MOST OF THE TIME
ONE PERSON GETS WHAT THEY WANT,
AND THE OTHER PERSON DOESN'T.
BEFORE ANY OF THAT HAPPENED,
WHEN EVERYTHING WAS GOOD.
- BUT HE DIDN'T
HAVE DINNER WITH THE JEWS.
- NO.
[glasses clink]
- [sighs]
I'LL--IN MY BODY, BUT THEY
SHOULD ALL LOOK LIKE YOU.
AND TEN OF YOUR MOUTH
AND YOUR EYES
AND YOUR HAIR
AND YOUR FINGERNAILS
AND YOUR TEETH.
[longing cello introduction]
- SO, UM,
I WANT A WEDDING DRESS.
- CAN I LOOK AT BOTH?
THAT ONE...
DO YOU WANT TO TRY IT ON?
- OKAY.
AND LIFT YOUR HAIR FOR ME.
GREAT.
OKAY, BRING YOUR CHIN UP
A LITTLE BIT, SIR.
PERFECT.
[shutter clicks]
WONDERFUL.
- THANKS.
DO YOU MIND WAITING HERE
FOR THE PHOTOS?
COME SEE!
- YES.
YOU WON'T HURT ME, WILL YOU?
[sighs]
- 18th CENTURY,
THAT WOULD BE COLONIAL.
- I'LL KNOW WHEN I SEE IT.
- OKAY, THE COSTUME ROOM IS
RIGHT BEHIND YOU, TO YOUR LEFT.
YOU'LL FIND THEM ON THE RACK.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- MM-HMM.
- WOULD YOU PLEASE SIGN IN?
- THANK YOU.
SO HANDS FOUR FROM THE TOP
TO IDENTIFY YOUR INITIAL SET.
ALL THE WAY AROUND.
IT'S A COUNT OF EIGHT.
SIX TURN ON THAT CLOVER LEAF
AWAY.
FOR A STAR LEFT,
AND GO THE OPPOSITE DIRECTION.
AND, VOILA, YOU HAVE GONE
EXACTLY NOWHERE.
OKAY, YOU'VE WORKED VERY HARD
LEARNING THE STEPS,
SO WHY DON'T WE ALL
TAKE A BREAK NOW?
- HEY.
- HI.
WE GOT MARRIED.
- THAT'S GREAT.
THAT'S GREAT.
- YES.
[fife music]
♪ ♪
AH--QUIT IT!
GET OFF.
- [panting]
- [gasping and coughing]
I CAN TAKE YOU ANYWHERE,
AN AIRPORT OR...
- I DON'T KNOW
WHO THE FUCK THIS IS.
YOU'RE BACK.
I'M GOING INSIDE.
ARE YOU OKAY OUT HERE?
♪ AND YOU'LL SAY ♪
♪ ARE YOU? ♪
♪ FOREVER ♪
♪ I HAVE PLANETS ♪
♪ I DO NOT PANIC ♪
♪ DON'T BE AFRAID ♪
♪ I'M MADE OF IVORY ♪
♪ I'LL TIE YOU UP ♪
♪ I WILL ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH ♪