How my Reds looking this year, Joe?
Sucking hind teat.
Yankees re-signed Ruth.
Thirty five thousand dollars,
you believe that?
A man can work ten lifetimes
and not earn that kind of dough.
I could grow old on that.
Amen.
Hamilton!
Where you been? Get your ass over here!
Crowson, Hamilton's out of group again.
I'll take him back. Ray, come on!
Drop your rifle.
Drop it.
Joe!
Wait!
Ah!
Care to comment on the escape, Governor?
Morning, boys.
Ma, no one's ever
broken out of your prison.
Bonnie and Clyde break in?
They've been on the run for two years, Ma.
Never say die, boys.
Say damned, never say die.
Some folks are saying that
Parker and Barrow are heroes,
calling them Robin Hoods.
Are they Robin Hoods, Ma?
Did Robin Hood ever shoot
a gas station attendant
point blank in the head for four dollars
and a tank of gas?
We will capture Clyde Barrow
and his paramore.
Write that down and underline it twice.
One more question?
If today was a fish,
I'd throw the son-of-a-bitch back.
- How did it happen?
- Clyde did a nickel at Eastham.
He knew the the system, planted guns,
ran it like a military operation.
Where are we on this?
Hoover and the FEDS are proceeding...
- Dallas Detectives, Highway Patrol...
- My Ferguson agents.
Same as the past
six months with no end in sight.
Busted into your facility, Lee.
You're right, they did.
Wounded one of my guards, killed another,
died in my arms apologizing
for letting me down.
I'd like a say and how we handle this.
Fine.
Let's hear it.
Was a time, we'd put a pair of man killers
on the trail and let them do their job.
Texas Rangers.
Was a time
and that time's past.
This is 1934 Lee,
and you want to put Cowboys
on Bonnie and Clyde?
Is that what you're selling?
Frank Hamer.
That's what I'm selling.
Well, sure.
Why don't we just go dig up Wyatt Earp.
Wild Bill Hickok.
Legislature disbanded the Rangers, Lee.
And you're right proud of it,
aren't you, Mrs. Governor?
Damn right I am!
They took orders from no one,
and they left me to answer for the blood.
Seems like you're answering for it again.
Governor,
Bonnie and Clyde have been
on the road for two years.
Cold-blooded killers who are
more adored than movie stars.
This has to stop.
Well.
Where is he?
This sure don't look like
no famous gunfighter's house.
Well, most gunfighters end up
living in a pine box,
but Hamer married well
and did just fine
in private security
with the oil companies.
Doesn't sound like he needs a job, sir.
No, Luther, I suppose it doesn't.
What in the good holy hell?
- Porky!
- No.
He ain't going to bite.
Frank.
Lee.
That's quite the watchdog
you've got there.
He's a gift.
Widow in Alpine, too tough to eat,
wouldn't run off,
Glady hates him, but
he's my friend not hers.
Go on.
Back in the house.
Speaking of...
How's Gault?
Speaking of what?
Friends.
Don't know. No idea where he is.
Lubbock.
Maney’s in Lubbock.
What bring's you?
You may have heard
there was a prison break. Huntsville?
Well, Ma Ferguson pardons
a hundred convicts a month.
They could've signed her a check,
saved themselves a lot of trouble.
It was the Barrow Gang.
Bonnie and Clyde.
Nobody can put a net over them.
A thousand men in the field right now.
Must be good.
Got the drop on six peace officers so far.
What can I do for you?
Put them on the spot.
Well, don't...
Don't mention that idea
inside the governor's mansion,
not unless you want to be laughed at.
I did and they did,
but she'll back me up on this.
She gonna bring back the Rangers?
No, never.
What capacity then?
Special highway assignment.
Highwaymen?
What's it pay these days,
$150 a month?
A hundred and thirty. It don't matter
what badge you got, Frank.
We just need you to
put them out of business.
I thought you and Maney.
He's killed six law?
You know you're gonna
have to put this man down.
The Governor says you'll have full
authority to do whatever's necessary.
Those are her words.
I'm sorry, Lee, but I...
I made a promise.
Well, Lee Simmons, as I live and breathe.
Live in the same town, never see you.
Hello, Gladys.
You look lovely as always.
What, are you feeding an army?
- Yeah.
- Ladies Auxiliary.
Look at my new Henry Ford, Lee.
Eighty-five horses, ain't she fun?
Yes, ma'am, she certainly is.
What brings you out?
Oh, come by say hello.
Lady Governor's offering me
130 dollars a month, Glady.
To do what?
Hunt down Bonnie and Clyde.
I'd best get back to my office.
I think you'd best, Lee.
Something you want to say?
I'm gonna repaint the kitchen.
- That's what's on your mind, huh?
- Mm-hm.
Yellow, I think.
Dear Lord.
How about your fried egg? Is it too small?
No. It's big enough.
It's a hen's egg.
But if it's too small
I'll get the rooster over here
and squeeze one out of him.
We interrupt this broadcast
to bring you a CBS news report.
Told you it looked like tornado weather.
Police in Reed Springs Missouri
report a harrowing shootout
between gangsters Bonnie and Clyde
and officers of the law.
The lawless lovers fired hundreds
of machine gun rounds
at the out-numbered officers.
No report yet
on the number of a fatalities.
We now return to your
regular scheduled program.
You boys work for Ol' Salazar?
Yes, sir. Mend fence,
cut Johnson grass,
I think I've seen you before.
He sent me out here
to give you boys a break.
Come on, fellas.
Which one of you has an arm?
I do.
You take them bottles out of there
and see if you can get a couple
up here high for me.
All right, and just...
How about every one I hit,
you get a nickel?
Let her rip.
Yeah, let's do another one.
For pity's sake.
I'm a goddamn old man!
All right.
Let her go.
You got a piece of that.
Yes, I did.
Just a piece.
Go ahead.
Take it, boys.
It's for keeping your mouth shut.
Yes, sir.
You bring me that bag there?
Hey, mister.
Was you really Frank Hamer?
Yep.
You boys best get back to work, okay?
Go on.
The look on his face.
Gladys is lovely,
but Captain Hamer is such a grump.
- Mrs. Hamer, may I help you with anything?
- Keep Leanne from spiking that punch.
Nice turn out.
Where's Porky?
Locked in the spare bedroom.
I don't suppose there's any chance
you want to take him with you?
Don't pretend
you didn't just hide this from me.
I suppose you're going to
want to take my new Ford.
I could tell you you're too old for this,
or that it's not your affair,
or that you hadn't held a gun
in quite a while.
I know that's all a waste of time,
so I won't.
And I appreciate you
not telling me any of that.
I'm sorry, Glady.
Don't be.
I knew what you were when I married you.
Oh, I packed sandwiches.
They're in the icebox.
Thank you.
Something else.
If you're covering miles, keep oil in her.
Yes, ma'am.
Those two scare me, Frank.
You tell me.
I'll come back.
Too good to come to my office?
All the same I'd rather
keep this low-key.
Files.
Here's your authorization right there.
Your jurisdiction technically ends
at the state line on the border.
Technically.
- I guess this is my badge?
- Yep.
You will keep me posted.
Call me from the road?
I'll call you when.
Where you headed to first?
Texarkana? El Paso? Dallas?
Lubbock?
Wake up, Pop-pop.
Yeah.
Mama says you should get up for breakfast
even if you don't have a job.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
I've got to take Dan over to see
a man about some work.
Can you make sure Nate
gets off to school on time?
Thinking about adding another bay
down at the garage.
Pete said to call him in a few weeks.
We're okay, Daddy.
Really.
No, I aim to pull my weight.
Thank you.
Coming!
Thanks, Pop-pop.
That's a dang good biscuit, right there.
You fix cars, so you could fix Daddy's?
I could if he'd ever let me near it.
But you used to be famous, right?
Who told you that?
Timmy Hess,
he said you shot lots of crooks.
Oh, yeah, what else did Timmy have to say?
Nothing, just that
you might go to hell for it
Go on.
Morning.
Can I help you?
I'd like to have a look at that Thompson
sub-machine gun.
And the Colt monitor machine rifle,
one up top there
with a custom pistol grip.
Carter.
Colt automatic pistol
and 1917 Smith right behind it.
And I want to see that B-A-R 30 aught six.
And the aught three Springfield
with the glass up top there.
That Remington
Model 11 Right Gun over there.
You want the 28 inch, or the 20 inch?
No sir. I want the short barrel.
- Is that the 12?
- Yes, sir.
Let me see that older Winchester
you got there, that 30-30.
No, I'll take it.
I'll need one gun that won't jam.
Would you be wanting the
stick or the drum for the tommy?
- How may in the stick?
- Twenty rounds.
I'll take a dozen,
and two of them drums.
And a handful of them half-moon clips for
this Smith if you've got them.
Do you have this in black
instead of nickel?
Too damn shiny.
I believe I do, sir.
Alright then that'll...
that'll do it.
Which will do it?
All of 'em.
All of 'em?
Yes, sir.
Along with four cases of 45 lead,
same for the 30 aught six and, say,
an even hundred each of the others.
What all you going after that you need
all this firepower?
If you don't mind me asking?
No, sir. I don't mind at all.
How'd you know it was me?
Between the suit and the car,
I thought you was the bank
'til I saw how poorly you drove.
All them guns have anything
to do with that
jackass and his girlfriend?
It as bad is the headlines?
Yeah.
You came all the way up to the house.
What changed your mind?
I don't know, maybe seeing you
move like you're 85.
Well, that's honest.
Maybe a little too honest.
You could've asked me, let me decide.
That would have been
the polite thing to do.
Like you said, I changed my mind.
Besides, what would your...
What would your daughter say
if you ran off?
That a weight's been lifted.
Well, you know how it goes,
I got to live the way they do, Gault.
This case, that means sleeping in the car,
driving thousands of miles a week.
I don't sleep much anyway.
When I do,
I most always dream about dead Mexicans.
I think I'll look up Ledbetter.
He's dead.
Or Cuthbert.
Dead too. So is Alvarez
and if you go any further down the roster,
I'm gonna be gravely offended.
Dammit, Pancho, I'm above ground
and ready to go.
Unless you...
think I'm useless.
You in good spirits?
Pretty polite way
of asking if I'm drinking.
Well, are you?
I'm not.
Not...
holding.
I could help with the driving.
No.
Or not.
Ah, Judas Priest. Get in.
But no singing.
I raised taxes to pay for my
new law enforcement program
and the last thing
this administration needs
is for a couple ofhas-been vaqueros
make that program look anything less than
stellar during this economic crisis.
Nod if your ears are working.
We'll get your gangsters, Ma.
You don't, John, you're gonna be on guard duty at Easham
Prison Farm. Get Barrow off the damn road before they do.
There she is.
Why, here you all are.
I'm so glad to see you.
Get your checkbooks out!
♪ ...to the boss to get my roll ♪
♪ He figured me out,
Nine dollars in the hole ♪
♪ Ki yi yippee yippee yi yippee yay
Yippee yi yi ♪
- ♪ Yippee yippee yay... ♪
- Mount Ayr, Iowa. Mount Ayr, Iowa.
Huh.
Hey, you're getting tired.
I could always...
dr...
Just saying.
Hey, uh, you think it was them
robbed that Armory up there?
Huh. It's a good chance.
Stole a car in Illinois.
Shot their way out of a roadblock.
They've been following the same loops now
for three years.
North to Kansas or Iowa,
east to Illinois or Indiana,
South to Arkansas.
Then right back to Texas
to start over again.
We've got no jurisdiction
north of Red River.
Maybe Hoover will take them up there.
Carthage,
Carthage.
Carthage, Missouri
Hell, I don’t remember a saddle being
as hard on a man’s ass as these seats.
I never shot a girl before, Pancho.
If we can take Clyde long range she'll...
she'll surrender.
We’re gonna shoot a man
without fair warning?
Well, Lord knows he does.
Yeah, well, Lord knows that’s what
separates us from him.
Clarksdale, Mississippi.
- Where next?
- Where they're headed.
Home.
West Dallas viaduct.
The Devils back porch.
And I thought my circumstances were bad.
Let me see the file.
Bernal street.
That's her mamma's house right there.
They're real close to one another.
Should be the Barrow's up on the corner.
Eagle Ford Road.
Mm.
Says here the two families
talked on the telephone once a day
until about a week ago.
How the hell they know that?
Federal wiretaps.
Huh?
G-Men can hook up to the party lines
and record conversation.
No.
I'll be goddamned.
Poncho.
What's this kid up to?
Whoa, Poncho!
Got to grab him quick.
Were youchasing someone?
Jim Thorpe, who are you?
John Quinn, State Ferguson Agent.
This is Kendale, US Bureau of Investigation.
We heard you were on
special assignment, Sir.
Director Hoover sends his regards.
He also sends a tip
by way of his contacts down south.
What's going on?
Ask him.
You okay?
Thought you had my back.
I would have been dead by now.
You ran one more block we'd both be dead.
Our information tells us that Barrow
might be hiding out down in Brownsville.
You probably weren't aware,
but this is
a highly-coordinated operation.
That said, we're happy
for any help you two might give us.
Down in Brownsville.
You ever hunt wild horses, Quinn?
What?
God!
Jeez!
They hunt a big range.
But they always come home.
Got a thousand person dragnet
in full operation.
Roadblocks, air surveillance.
Don’t think the Barrow Gang’s
gonna be coming back to the neighborhood
any time soon.
No, sir. Outlaws and mustangs
they always come home.
Maybe you gentlemen
should go home too.
This isn't Llano County.
Be a shame if either of you
got hurt in retirement.
Be a shame if anybody got hurt.
Sir, if I could,
I think what detective Quinn means is
the Barrow gang just hit an armory.
They're armed to kill.
That's called a double-band system.
Didn't have one
in your saddlebags I imagine.
It's essential in a dragnet.
Without it you might as well be
in Timbuktu.
Or down in Brownsville,
following your bullshit tip.
I hear ya, understood.
I've felt more welcome.
Yeah.
Maybe we ought to make some new friends.
Smoot Schmid, gentlemen.
No need to introduce yourselves,
I know who you are,
but I’d be honored
to shake your hands anyway.
Hey.
Bob Alcorn there, and deputy
Ted Hinton holding up the Cola machine.
Have a seat.
Damn.
Hamer and Gault.
You know how many times
I have told my grandson
the Candelaria story?
Every night before he goes to bed.
That's what he wants to hear.
And I mean every night.
How's he sleep?
Sheriff, we're involved
in the Barrow Manhunt...
in a very private way.
Well, it's not too private.
Word gets around.
Yes, it does.
We heard that Clyde
put a price on your head.
And I keep my front door unlocked in case
that son-of-a-bitch ever wants to stop by.
We're going to take him down.
But we need your help.
I would be honored.
We're looking for a confidence
in the neighborhood.
Someone who knows the families
and willing to talk.
Well, how about a boy
that grew up with him?
That worked with Clyde
known Bonnie ever since you was girl.
A boy that can give you a positive
identification on them from first sighting
He's got the mental range
of a windshield wiper.
But he's reliable.
Where can we find him?
Holding up the Cola machine.
Tough place to grow up.
Clyde was always mischief.
You know, me and him
used to play cops and robbers.
Let me guess.
You was the cop.
All I ever wanted to be.
That, or short stop
for the Cleveland Indians.
And Bonnie? You, uh...
you know Miss Parker?
She grew up on the backside of the porch.
Near Cement City.
No daddy.
Must be one hard lady.
To the contrary, Sir. Little-bitty thing.
Can't weigh but 90 pounds.
Smartest girl in school.
She was in all the plays.
Won the spelling bees.
- Yeah.
- Wrote poetry.
Yeah.
I mean, attractive girl.
Taffy-colored hair
Sounds like the short-stop was
maybe a little sweet on her?
Any boy she ever waited on
at the Courthouse Cafe was sweet on her.
How'd she fall in with
an outlaw like Barrow?
Bored to tears.
Along come Clyde in a fine car.
By the time she found out
the car was stolen,
she was already in love.
Ain't that romantic.
I met my wife she was milking
a prize Devon at the Oklahoma State Fair.
I can't imagine anybody writing a ballad
about that encounter.
You know, the files say they ran
two of your roadblocks.
Well, they ran roadblocks in Oklahoma too.
Kansas, New Mexico.
Also said you had a clear shot at 'em.
They say Clyde is some sort
of Fu-Manchu
You know, can't be touched.
Time magazine called him superhuman.
Y'all see that?
Maybe you weren't able
to pull on her, Ted.
Sir?
Couldn't pull the trigger on a nice girl
who used to serve you pecan pie
at the Courthouse Cafe.
You're not able to do it.
Well, I won't have to.
I'm stationed here in West Dallas.
Be a cold day in hell
before they show their faces
on the back porch.
Well, they're on their way, Ted.
According to the wiretaps,
Mrs. Parker is cooking red beans
and cabbage Easter Sunday.
Sir, I don't understand what you mean.
Ted, you don't know what wiretaps are?
Of course I know what wiretaps are!
I just don’t understand what
red beans and cabbage have to do with it.
Whenever Bonnie’s mama says
that she has red beans and cabbage
on the stove, those dates,
they match up to sightings or shoot-outs
in the general Dallas area.
Red beans and cabbage. That's code.
Means the kids are coming home.
So, do I just ride with you boys?
No, sir. We'll meet you in two days,
Easter Sunday.
You meet us first thing in the morning,
a block from Eagle Ford road.
I'll need you to make
the ID on Barrow and Parker.
I'm your man.
They're afraid to shoot the girl.
Gives Clyde the one second
he needs to get the drop and
Toothpick there knows it.
You've read the story
of Jesse James,
and how he lived and died.
Still in the need of something to read,
here's the story of Bonnie and Clyde.
Used to be you had to have talent
to get published.
Now you just have to shoot people.
What is this place?
They were sighted
a month or two ago camping...
camping somewhere out here.
Somebody's a damn good eye.
That or they just walk right up to it.
Look at it.
Every shot right through the same hole.
When's the last time you fired that thing?
You know what we're up against?
Hm? Any idea?
Ain't nothing we ain't seen before,
Pancho.
It was a shootout in Joplin.
Over a thousand rounds were fired.
What the hell is that?
It's a Colt monitor machine rifle.
Fires a twenty-round volley
at 3,000 feet per second.
Our boy Clyde, he prefers
a Browning automatic 30 cal.
Pretty much the same gun
except now the little shit uses a...
...welded under clip
that can fire 40.
Well, he ain't met old lucky.
Shit. I ain’t that lucky.
Hey, got one of them for me?
You folks all right?
Happy Easter.
Gotta pee.
Yeah, might be something left
after the 40 times you were up all night.
Yeah, well, there's a place in heaven
for Gladys, the way you saw wood.
When did you start that?
Hurry up.
Why don't you go inside and wait there?
Barrows and Parkers stayed put
and no one's really seen Clyde around.
Don't be surprised, Ted.
You wouldn’t think Clyde would’ve noticed
a little metal man leading a circus
through his old neighborhood?
I hear there's red beans and cabbage
over at the Parker house.
If you’re hungry, Captain Hamer.
Maybe they rode in on their mustangs
and then rode back out again.
Shots fired over near Grapevine.
Officers down.
I didn't say anything.
Get in the car, Ted.
How's the view from up there, Mr. Hoover?
You high flying sissy.
The car was parked there all morning.
The two officers pulled up...
- Hold on.
- You explain it to him, Ted.
What do you make of that?
Kid didn't get 'em into the gun.
Get that to field office, too,
for finger print analysis.
Careful where you step, cowboy.
This is an active crime scene.
Kiss my ass.
You were right, came back.
Came right back to Dallas.
Hm.
Lettuce.
Check the goddamn fence line.
- What the hell you doing?
- You still got two.
Third gun who fired; we think it's either
Joe Palmer or Raymond Hamilton.
We'll run ballistics
and then maybe we'll know something.
No, tracks are too big
and deep for Palmer.
These are driver side.
It may have to be Raymond
who shot that B-A-R then.
Yeah, heavy.
I reckon' Clyde used
a ten-gauge scattergun.
Little girl used a sawn-off twenty.
You see that?
She drags her left leg.
She gimped?
Well, Clyde missed a detour
a month or so back.
Got her leg burned up in the wreck.
Why does Bonnie have a pet rabbit?
Maybe a present. For Bonnie's mama.
Or Billie Mace.
You know, she's generous like that.
Yeah, she can light up a rainy day,
can’t she, Ted?
Little-bitty ain’t but 90 pounds.
But she could shoot a patrolman
in the face, point blank, while he's down.
- You can tell that from her tracks?
- See that heel scrape?
He was on his side.
She used her foot to push him over
so he could see what was about to happen.
Those kids you grew up with
aren’t human any more. Look at me!
You remember that at the next road block.
You okay, son?
Yeah.
We'll be in touch.
Red River.
State line.
Oklahoma.
- Just thought I’d point that out.
- Thank you.
It's open range now.
Well, where the hell are they?
I'm not sure.
Why not?
They work for you.
They were in Dallas three days ago.
That's as much as I know.
You promised to keep
Hamer on a short leash.
Didn't you?
If they make a fool of me,
there's going to be hell to pay.
Do we understand each other,
Marshall Lee Simmons?
Yes, ma'am.
Good.
Never seen 'em.
Never seen 'em?
Well,
there hasn't been
another filling station for...
a hundred and sixty miles, you know.
You never saw blue sedan with black tires.
Nope.
Two men and a woman,
headed northbound?
If it's Bonnie and Clyde you looking for,
I didn't see 'em.
And if I did,
all the luck to 'em.
They only taking from the banks
that are taking from the poor folk,
like me.
Well?
Oh, Lord.
Now what? I done told you all I'm gonna
tell you about Bonnie and Clyde.
There's a peace officer
died in the puddle of himself
back in Dallas.
He was trying to get the shells
out of his pockets
when his head was blown off. Easter Sunday morning.
His family will be on the breadline next week.
All luck to ‘em?
Huh?
Poncho!
- Is that really all you have to say, son?
- Poncho!
They come through here yesterday.
Asked me
where the nearest migrant camp was.
Showed 'em on state map.
Black tires,
blue sedan,
the woman was carrying
a white bunny rabbit.
Gas prices these days
got everybody a little riled.
- What?
- Well, you’re the more sociable type.
Meaning, I’m more full of shit.
You boys hiring?
I was gonna ask you the same.
My partner and I,
been on the road a long while.
Business went under in Fort Worth.
Foreclosed. Damn banks.
It says so in the Bible.
The banks is the Devil.
Say, my daughter
and her boyfriend been moving
camp to camp, looking for work.
Would've come through in a new Ford sedan.
Wouldn’t have happen
to see them, would ya?
Two boys and a red-haired girl.
Tiny thing.
They didn't come through here.
Oh, uh...
Trade for some pump water?
Much obliged, Mister.
Good luck to you.
They like me.
Well, those are some first-rate mud pies
right there.
I had a little girl like you.
She's all growed up now.
Got a baby of her own. A boy.
Hey.
Can I ask you something?
Have you see these two come around here?
Dressed up real nice.
Huh?
These are bad folks,
they hurt other people.
And if we don't find them,
they're going to hurt more people.
Have you seen 'em here?
Okay.
Masterful.
Well, why don't you just get out
and beat the hell out of everybody?
The lady gave it to me.
Still warm?
Butts over here, spread out.
Hand-rolled Durham.
She puffs Camels, right?
Yeah.
Clyde smokes Luckys.
Always has that third man on watch.
Usually near the car, away from ‘em.
Which one is he?
Well, three broke out,
only one still with ‘em.
Hamilton maybe, like you said.
Well, maybe I was wrong.
I’m sorry, I didn’t catch that.
You were what?
Hamilton, he’s a…
he's a front-runner, a peacock.
Old Durham over there, he’s a follower.
I suppose you got all that
from their file?
Well, you track a wolf, you track a dog,
pretty soon you know the difference.
Our third man over there,
that’s Clyde’s watch dog.
You know, he may not drink but...
She sure does.
Little girl’s in serious pain.
Laudanum.
I love Clara Bow.
Stuck in the...
You folks need some help?
Oh, Lord, help me.
Hi, sweetie.
Kansas or pan handle?
Check the file, see if any...
of the escapees have family nearby.
You know you got a radio in this thing?
That ain’t factory.
How much that set you back?
You’d have to ask Glady.
Just an intrusion
on a man’s peace and quiet.
Not that I've had any since Lubbock.
Oh, yeah, that's a good'n.
This is an emergency alert.
Police are not yet releasing any details,
but it has been reported
that two officers have been shot
on a country road in a rural area
just north of Commerce, Oklahoma.
How far is that?
Twenty miles.
This don’t look promising.
How are we today?
Well it's never good when
a peace officer goes down in the line.
We need to get through, Sir.
Now.
Only the Bureau has
multi-state jurisdiction.
We need to stay the trail.
This paper is worthless up here.
So, unless you’re government agents,
or Oklahoma police officers,
you’re not passing this roadblock.
Turn this vehicle around.
Goddammit.
Hey! What the hell do you
think you're doing?
They need dope for the girl.
What’s the closest large town?
You know what, Poncho?
Maybe I should drive.
What town?
What's that?
Expense report.
It's how much we...
How much we cost.
How many bullets you got in you?
Hell, I don't know.
Sixteen, I think.
You know, a man can't
pass bullets through him like he can kidney stones.
Might be good to have a doctor look at you sometime.
Might be good to have a doctor
look at you sometime.
I ain't got no bullets in me.
Because I was covering you.
Clyde’s ahead of us on the road.
How long we gonna just sit here?
I don't know. You got a better idea?
I don’t know if it’s better.
The file said
there was one convict
tried to make that Eastham escape,
but missed the bus.
Wade McNabb.
Why?
If you were a free man, wouldn't you
try to meet up with your friends?
McNabb's only in for firearms,
he's not a killer.
Lee Simmons could get him furloughed.
Lady Governor would have to sign for it.
I’d wager she’s not too happy
about us expanding our jurisdiction.
Just saying.
Maney.
Bonnie Parker.
I've seen ten of them today.
Yeah, it's the...
- It's the fashion.
- All the rage.
Where you going?
Nature calls.
Jiminy Christmas. Ya just went!
Is that Bonnie?
Get in the picture now.
Bonnie and Clyde!
It's them, around the corner.
Grab a shotgun.
I’m gonna back us out of here. Come on.
They parked in the back.
One of ‘em went in.
Wasn’t Ray Hamilton either.
It was Henry Methvin.
- The third man in the jailbreak.
- I know, I saw him. You let him go?
Well, I had my eye on Clyde.
Clyde? You had your...
You had your eye on Clyde?
You had a shot?
Why didn’t you take him?
Too many people.
God damn fan club.
Right there! Right there!
I can’t see ‘em!
Yeah.
Damn.
They stopped
for a nice breakfast this morning.
French toast and coffee.
Clyde ordered himself a soft boiled egg
off the a la carte menu.
Cute little diner in Amarillo.
- Amarillo?
- Yeah.
Clyde drove 400 miles last night?
Four hundred and fifty.
Did you ever think, maybe...
Maybe it ain't in us no more?
Oh.
He got through a thousand-man dragnet
to deliver a bunny to mama.
What do we do now?
I just had the one idea.
Pancho!
CLYDE SENDS LETTER TO HENRY FORD
"YOU MAKE A DANDY CAR"
Thank you, sir.
They tell me
you're from the highway department, but...
I know who you really are.
I know a killer when I see one.
I’m sure you would, Mr. Barrow.
Look, mister.
I know y'all going to have to
kill my boy.
It ain't your fault.
He's gone past the point of redemption.
There's something I want to say.
Here.
He wasn't born that way.
He wasn’t born with no dark soul.
My little Huck Finn.
That’s what me and Cumie called him.
He loved bicycles.
What he really wanted to be
was a musician.
I mean, sure, he liked to dress fine
and get the girls and all like that but...
You know, he wasn't a bad boy.
I had high hopes.
People don't always know who they are...
...until it's too late.
Oh, you mean one turn on the trail, huh?
That what you mean?
He stole a chicken.
He stole a goddamned chicken, Mister.
and the law took him for a bad seed
and from that day forward,
he was dogged by the law.
- Dogged him?
- Yes, sir!
Dogged him or watched him?
I guess it’s all the same to you.
You’re a cop.
Yes, I am.
Growing up all I ever…
all I ever wanted to be was a preacher.
Preacher?
You expect me to believe that?
I was saving up for the seminary.
Working for a sharecropper in San Saba.
Word got out
that I was pretty handy with a pistol.
The owner, McSwain,
called me up to the porch one day
and wanted to know if I
wanted to make $150.
I laughed and said,
“Who do I have to kill?”
And he kept staring at me.
That's when I knew
he wasn't talking about killing
a coyote or a polecat.
He was talking about
his business partner he wanted dead.
I told him I was going to
tell his business partner.
That wasn't too smart.
Well, I was 16!
Like I said, I was
saving up for the seminary.
Couple weeks later, he...
asked me to put some groceries
in his house.
Before I could go in,
he pulled a scatter gun.
Shot me in my head,
my back,
my leg.
For whatever reason I still don't know,
he stepped right over me and went inside.
Maybe to reload.
I don't know, but I...
I scrambled away.
Hid in an irrigation ditch.
I would’ve died there
except for a colored field hand.
Came along found me.
Carried me home.
My momma took care of me all summer.
Come fall, I...
I packed up for the seminary.
At least that's what I told them.
And on my way out of town,
I rode over to McSwain’s.
Rang the yard bell. He come out.
And I shot that son-of-a-bitch dead
right there on that same porch
and there went my calling.
Turned out
McSwain was a wanted man himself,
and I became the law.
One turn on the trail, huh?
Yes, sir.
One turn.
How come you telling me all this?
You ever think maybe there was
something in Clyde
made him steal that chicken
in the first place?
Maybe he was hungry.
Maybe we were all hungry.
I won't argue that.
He ain't going to surrender.
You just going to hang him anyhow.
Hmm. He'd rather be brought down
on the run.
You know, your boy may not have been
born with a dark soul, but he has one now.
You're not hearing me, mister.
I'm trying to say something.
It ain't easy for me to say.
I know there's only one way
that this thing is ever going to end.
And I'm asking you, please
just end it now, damn it.
End it for my family.
You call Lee Simmons.
Get him to furlough Wade McNabb.
What a fine idea.
I couldn't believe it when
Billy Mays said he was letting you out.
Sixty days. And if I get a job
and I do good behavior in that time,
it could be full parole.
But it ain’t good behavior
I got on my mind tonight, sweetie.
My kind of place.
How are you, darling?
So, is it true?
You really know Clyde Barrow?
I knew his brother Buck, too,
before they shot him dead.
What are we gonna do with you?
- I can think of a few things, darling.
- Oh, yeah?
Good to be off the farm, Wade?
They wouldn't tell me your name.
Don't need it.
I dig.
Say, you owe me a do-over, slick.
Or not.
Where's a water closet?
So, what do y'all need me to do?
Say, you bringing the cattle market, dad?
I swear, big man,
they’re plannin’ to skin out for Mexico.
That is the word.
What do you know, Joe?
Son, suppose you cut
the junior gangster act and get serious.
Otherwise, there's
nothing you can do for me.
I'll have Lee Simmons give you a ride
back to the farm tonight.
Yes, sir.
Let me tell you somethin’, Mister.
You come to the wrong place
to dog Wade boy.
That's right, old man.
You see, Wade Boy runs with Clyde
and around here, Clyde is king.
Watch those fancy shoes.
It’s a real mess, you get it point blank,
but I’m happy to do it for you.
A lot of nerve you got tryin’ to...
...rob a fella while he’s
havin’ himself a pleasant relief.
Get yourselves in that stall.
Stay in there till I come back
and tell you different.
Clyde might be king,
but I'm a Texas Ranger, you little shit.
Billie Mace is set to fix Bonnie’s hair.
- When?
- Tomorrow.
Dinnertime.
Might look like two girls.
Clyde sometimes wears a ladies wig.
He done got y'all chasing
your own tails, don’t he?
Son, if you're telling the truth,
you’ll finish out your term
in a nice, civilized federal pen.
But you do wrong by me, you’ll be
back on the farm, breakin’ rocks,
and getting your teeth stove in.
What took you so long?
There’s a fella in the toilet.
Are you Billie Mace?
Must be Billy Mace.
Hey, grand-dad.
Wanna race again?
Didn’t your mama teach you
to tie your shoes?
Uh-uh.
- We gonna see each other again?
- No, sir.
Git!
"Git." Down right poetic.
Uh, "headed for greener pastures,
see you next time around."
McNabb warned them.
McNabb! Open up the goddamn door!
Goddamn animals.
Did I get that boy killed?
No, sir.
You did not.
He would have been out
in nine months on his own.
Fella did not
have to die.
Maybe so, but that fella
made his own choices.
See, Frank,
that’s the difference
right there between you and me.
You could always hide
behind some notion
of right and wrong. Me,
I never particularly liked the weight
of the deciding
who gets to live and who doesn’t.
There’s differences between us, Maney.
But hiding behind something
ain’t one of ‘em.
You know, counting McNabb,
they’ve killed 13
and people call ‘em heroes.
- Who cares what they call...
- I care!
People idolize them.
We need to end this.
It's never easy,
it's never pretty.
But there's always blood
at the end of the road, you know that.
You know that the same as me.
I seen a lot a blood,
but it ain’t theirs.
Goddammit, Maney, why the hell…
Why the hell you even come?
I had to come.
Though I don't exactly know why.
It's going to look like
we set McNabb up to be killed.
Ma finds out,
I don't think
I can protect you or myself.
You need to come back to Austin
so we can sort this out.
I understand, Lee.
If you're ready to go home,
I'll drive you.
Take me to greener pastures.
I’ll just get a bottle and set there
and wait for Clyde to show up.
Does that mean anything, you think?
Headed for...
greener pastures.
Is he headed for a state
he hasn't hit yet?
Could be.
What states have warrants for him?
Mm.
No, better still.
What states don't.
New Mexico,
uh,
Colorado,
Louisiana.
Outlaws always go home.
Maybe we just been looking
at the wrong home.
Methvin, where’s he from?
Kansas.
He still have family there?
No, his dad
lives in Bienville Parish.
East of Shreveport.
Owner lets folk squat
in exchange for labor.
Henry’s daddy hauls wood for ‘em.
That's his truck right there.
Ivy Methvin.
They're playing house.
She’s a little bitty thing.
So's he.
Huh.
You all right?
Yeah.
Fix the room back.
Probably best they weren't home.
We got no jurisdiction
to arrest in these parts.
Now, we weren’t there
to arrest them, Maney.
Well, then I suggest we bring in
a local sheriff next time.
Okay, what if he's in on the hand?
A corrupt sheriff down this way
isn’t exactly remarkable.
One way to find out.
- You said you seen Clyde.
- Yes, sir.
Where? North highway?
- Most recently two miles from--
- How you know it him?
My name is Flavius Kern.
I am the Barrow family parson. May I?
Thank you.
Now, nobody knows I’m here
and you never saw me.
But, the family is grateful to you
because the kids,
they’re good kids. They're...
They got in a little over their heads,
but word is there’s some heat on ‘em
down here
and I know you never saw 'em,
and you never heard they was
in your parish,
and we’d like to keep it that way.
Clyde will try to show
his appreciation to you, but the family
would like to show theirs.
Call it a contribution
to the Parish church.
Now, I won’t take up
any more of your time.
Your boy use a shotgun on that gator or...
No, we use a gig, like this here.
Listen to me, papere. I see these dogs
in Bienville, I shoot ‘em dead.
Take your bribe and go home,
or I shoot your ass, too.
We’re not crooks down here.
Well, then, you are just the gentleman
we're looking for.
Timber!
Mr. Ivy.
Some men over there lookin’ for somebody
to cut and haul wood.
Say they’ll pay fair.
You need some more hands,
me and my boy, we needs the work.
Work right here.
Get to it.
Yes, sir.
What the hell is this?
I’m Sheriff Jordan.
This is my deputy, Mr. Oakley.
Well, who are you fellas?
Doesn’t concern you.
All you need to know is Bonnie and Clyde
are going down hard, Mr. Methvin.
If not by the gun, then by the chair.
- And your boy Henry is going with them.
- My boy didn’t kill nobody.
Killed a highway patrolman
near Grapevine, Texas.
We have a witness,
ballistics, the whole book.
Wiretaps.
We know sooner
or later they’ll be coming to see you.
We’re gonna give your son
a chance to live.
How?
Well, he’s gonna have to
put ‘em on the spot.
He does, we’ll put him
on the ground, instead of in it.
- Meaning you’ll let him go.
- As far as Texas is concerned, yes, sir.
They might be by in a day or two.
When you get your boy alone, you tell him
to get separated first chance he gets.
They'll come right back to see him.
We'll be waiting.
Why should I trust you?
Because I said.
That's just how he's built.
Well, they got a rule.
If they get separated,
they wait a couple days
for the air to clear
and then meet up back at my house.
Clyde won’t be taken alive.
Neither will your boy, sir.
Unless he takes his one chance now.
I like my house.
- Excuse me?
- I like my house!
Clyde bought it for me and I don’t want
y’all shootin’ it up none.
Now they’ll be around for Henry.
There ain't but one way in one way out.
That's Ringgold Road.
Ringgold Road.
Once my boy gets clear,
well, you can kill ‘em there.
All right.
Take two.
There you go.
Looks like we outnumbered
by a Texan, Sanderson.
Yeah, well, we need
these Dallas boys, the only ones
who can make a positive identification.
Mm.
Old Ivy said their car loaded
with fire power.
They got machine guns,
hand grenades, thousand round of shells.
Said it’s like an armory on four wheels.
- Well, we'll find out.
- Gonna have us a hunt.
Gonna skin us some deer.
Dang, If I don't have
an Arkansas Straight.
Dallas paper gave me a camera
to film it when it happens.
Said he’d pay me.
Y’all believe that?
What the hell is this world coming to?
Well, here we go.
- Three sevens?
- Mm-hmm.
Maybe we should put six bills in the pot,
Homme, make it more interestin’.
No. Cap says no money in a game,
nor drinking on Sundays.
Can't be much fun.
Yeah, well, there's a place
for me in heaven, I'll tell you that.
What's he doing out there?
He likes to be alone sometimes.
Sheriff Smoot said you and Hamer killed
more than fifty men between you.
Killed more than that one evenin’.
I didn't mean to pry.
It’s all right, kid. Ante-up, gents.
I was young.
Younger than you.
South Texas place called Candelario.
Ranger Company C. Had about sixty bandits
pinned down in a dry wash.
These fellas burned half a dozen ranches,
killed a dozen,
raped just about as many.
Anyway, every time we’d ride in there
to take ‘em,
we’d yell out, manos arribas.
You know, hands up.
Well, they'd fire on us
and we’d lose a man.
Went on like that for two days.
So, they sent down
young Captain Hamer.
My friend, Pancho.
Cap says,
"What's going on out here?"
Any time we yell out, manos arribas
like the Law tells us to,
they open up on us.
Cap says, “Well, we’re going in there
'afore dawn and, this time,
don’t no-damn-body yell out
manos arribas.
Just shoot ‘em
Well, that night
them bandits were celebrating. Drunk.
Most of them asleep by the fire.
We went in.
Some of the boys refused to go.
Refused to just start shooting men.
But I went with Frank,
like I said, he's my friend.
He gave me the nod.
We let 'em have it.
We shot that arroyo all to hell
before most of them fellas even woke up.
I was
jittery.
A mule come out
from behind a cactus and I,
uh, shot the man riding it
half dozen times.
Turned out to be a
thirteen-year old boy just
trying to run away.
I still see his face.
Whole thing was over in five minutes.
Counted 54 dead.
Counting was over, Cap sat on a rock,
holstered his gun and said,
"manos arribas, you sons-a-bitches."
Came back,
Governor gave us all medals.
My boy got loose.
When he comes,
he's going to be coming from the south.
Which will bring him right by you.
Well, I figure
you fellas got it from here.
Ivy.
Turn your truck around,
park at the wrong side.
What?
You're staying with us.
No, that wasn't part of the deal.
The deal ain’t done ‘til it’s done.
Now, park it.
Jack up the front right bumper
and take off your tire.
Clyde’ll slow down and help him change it.
- What?
- Stash these cars. How do I know I ain't going to get shot?
You okay?
Yeah. Yes, sir.
We need you to identify these two.
Nobody said nothing about
having to pull the trigger.
Which means, you don't have to.
I'll be all right.
Sure?
Yeah.
When they get here, y’all
stay behind the blind.
If I present myself,
you fire on my command.
We stay in the blind.
Yeah.
You walk out there?
That’s an order, Gault.
Maney,
for the record, you only
move like a 75.
The reason I passed your house
that day was 'cause I
I wanted to spare you this.
That said, I’m...
I’m real glad you’re here.
Me, too, Pancho.
Me, too.
Ivy!
Get out there!
Hurry up.
It's them.
Ford V8.
Ted?
- Yeah.
- You better look.
Yeah. It’s Clyde.
This is it.
- Hey, Ivy. Need some help with that?
- Yeah.
Stick 'em up.
Manos arribas.
H. J. SMITH'S SONS
GENERAL MERCHANDISE
ARCADIA, LOUISIANA
Mr. Hamer?
Excuse me, Mr. Hamer,
there’s a fella on the phone
from the Associated Press in New York.
He says he’ll give you $1000
for a phone interview right now.
Got him on the line in the back.
Mr. Hamer?
Shame on you.
The nation has been freed
from the worst killing rampage in history.
Retribution has been served
and J. Edgar Hoover
has issued a formal announcement
that the crime spree
of Bonnie and Clyde...
Would you care to comment on your role
in the apprehension of Bonnie and Clyde?
I knew Hamer and Gault
would get the job done.
That’s why I chose ‘em.
Bottom line.