Where are you going?
The Jeffersons's about to come on.
Damn! Taking this role-playing thing
a little serious, don't you think?
Shut up. You talk too much.
For real, where the hell is my TV?
Your ass is ringing. You want me to get it?
Just keep it hot. Wait. Talk to me!
Pier 16, half an hour.
- What?
- You wanted to come to the Player's Ball.
Here's your invitation.
I'm sorry.
That was the President.
Puffy remixed the national anthem.
They need me.
Mr. Miyako is expecting you. Follow me.
Thank you. Do I sense an accent?
- Yes, I'm from the Bahamas.
- Really? I know Rick Fox.
Do you know him? Turn around, girl.
Vanessa Williams!
I'll be back.
Hey, what's up, Miyako? My man.
Relax.
What's going on with your boy here?
My man needs a girlfriend.
He's just doing his job.
Boy, you....
You never cease to amaze me. Look at all
these fine women sitting around you, boy.
What's cracking, man?
This is what you've been waiting for.
Hang out.
Maybe you'll learn something tonight.
One of my dogs is fighting next.
I didn't come here to watch dogs fight.
I came here to get paid.
This is a party. Relax. Enjoy yourself.
I just got a page from Smokey Robinson.
I need to call him.
He's deaf in one ear
and there's a lot of noise here.
I'll go call him outside. I'll be right back.
If your guy keeps looking at me
the way he's looking at me...
tell him I'll throw him a fucking beating...
where his mother won't know him
when she see him.
His fucking face will look
like a fucking pizza pie or something.
I'll be right back.
Get him some ass.
Captain...
get down to Pier 16.
They're shipping the cocaine in liquid form.
And get this: They're shipping it in dogs.
- I don't get down like that, brother.
- Who you calling?
I'm calling my girlfriend,
that's who I'm calling. Damn cell phones.
Just bad reception, man.
All I keep hearing is....
Gunshots reported at Pier 16.
All harbour units respond. Code 3.
How're you gonna
just leave the party like that, man?
I missed The Jeffersons to be here.
Fuck you, cop.
I knew you were gonna wanna fight.
All right.
Did I thank you
for inviting me to the Player's Ball?
All right.
By the way, I am not a cop!
- Your money's in the regular place.
- Beautiful.
- Who's gonna get credit for this one?
- I think we'll give this one to Boston.
He's worked hard,
hasn't had a bust in a while.
- Boston needs to lighten up.
- That'll be Lieutenant Boston after this one.
Ain't that something?
- Anything I can do for you?
- Think I can keep the car another day?
You're pushing it.
How about your niece? All right.
I'm just kidding.
- I'm thinking about it, though.
- Everybody else hit it.
This was the shit, man!
We gotta do this again sometime.
When are you getting out? 30, 40, 50 years?
What, you got something in your eye?
- This ain't over.
- I'm scared.
Yo, Rad! Get in the car.
Move, motherfucker! Move!
You've got the wrong guy, brother.
I've been looking for you, motherfucker.
I ain't gonna be
but too many more "motherfuckers."
Shit!
- What's up, bitch?
- What's up, baby?
- Hold this.
- What's good, daddy?
- That's my man, Tico.
- Tico almost got fucked up.
Good to see you. It's been too long.
What's popping? You missed me?
It's hard to miss a brother...
when you see a poster of him
on Sunset Boulevard every day.
- What's up? When the album dropping?
- Next week.
In fact, we're on our way
to a listening party now.
- Wanna roll out?
- Ain't nothing to talk about.
Let's do it. Yo, driver, we off, baby. Let's go.
Y'all make some motherfucking noise...
for New Freedom Records'
multi-platinum artist...
Benjamin, a.k.a. Killer Ben!
This is for my niggas doing biz
hold ya head
Mix tuna fish with the squid, hold the bread
For those getting hit at the board
got to get a reward
Park at the gate with incredible doors
This is D block, daddy
We touch dudes with Kalis
Give bricks to D, does juice from Cali
Do it for the adolescents wildin'
In the O.G.'s on the tail
with silk shirts at Bally's
So what did you think?
You were putting it down.
That's what I like to see.
Ain't nothing. You ain't heard the half.
I got some more real fire for you to hear.
Heard me?
You know I gotta hear it.
Yeah, definitely.
Check it out, Dre. I really gotta roll.
- I'll catch up with you later.
- All right.
- One love, baby.
- What's cracking, Andre?
- What's up, B.?
You know, I find it very disrespectful...
that you're talking to my artist
while he's under contract with me.
I'm gonna tell you this one time,
and one time only.
- Don't be fucking with my ones.
- I was being friendly with him, that's all.
You want to be friendly?
Buy yourself a motherfucking poodle.
This P.I. thing
must have really worked out for you?
What's your ball game now?
You still coaching down--
You know I'm still coaching.
We're going to the championship.
Hard to believe, with a ball hog for a coach.
Since you my dog and all that,
look how I'm doing here, baby.
What? You got married?
Last week in Vegas. Just me and her.
- Who is she?
- Her name is Venus.
She out of town right now,
but she's fine. An angel.
- You serious?
- I hope my mum likes her.
- They're gonna meet up tomorrow night.
- You know mas is a tough critic.
- That sounds real good.
- I gotta get out of here.
- Meet me at Stevie's, Ventura, Friday. 7:30?
- Do that. Well done.
Bring the car around back, dog.
You're getting your coat put on you
like you're James Brown now.
- I'm gonna see you on Friday, all right?
- Good seeing you.
- Stay up.
- You too, man. Don't stand me up, man.
No, never that.
Will that be all, sir?
Actually, Rhonda,
I was hoping I could get a--
It's on your napkin.
Benjamin. Coincidence
running into you over here.
What's up?
I'll kick it straight with you,
'cause I'm a businessman and all.
Funk U Up Records know about
your contract with New Freedom.
Basically, we ready to do whatever it take
to make you a part of the team, player.
I'm straight, you know.
What do you mean?
Think you're too good for us?
The last album you all put out
was called Garbage Truck Juice.
If I didn't know better, I'd think
your bad-boy ass is trying to insult me.
- Get the fuck out of here.
- I ain't even going to trip off that, man.
Just sign this letter of intent,
and we're good, baby.
- I'm straight, dog.
- Kid, I'm not asking you.
- Who the fuck are you?
- I'm the one who'll make you reconsider.
Hey, fellows. What's up, man?
- We got a problem here?
- You bet your ass we got a problem.
I ain't got no problem
kicking somebody's ass your size.
That's factory equipment for me, baby.
But him, you may have a problem.
- Go on. Get the fuck out of here.
- Get your big hamburger-ass out of here.
Get the fuck out of here.
Fake-ass suit. Get in the damn car!
Just remember what I said, Benji!
I'm gonna see you, man.
- This is your life, right here!
- Whatever.
- Where's your bodyguard, man?
- I don't know.
- My bad, man.
- Yeah, all right. Whatever.
- What's that all about?
- It ain't nothing, you know. Just business.
- What's up, Rad?
- What's going on?
How cute!
Yeah. I finally found a man
that won't leave you.
- Check yourself.
- What's up? What you got for me today?
Now, mind you,
this is a bit generic for my taste...
- but it's definitely your steelo.
- Boy, I can't wait.
I love you.
- Did you just turn that on?
- Yeah, why?
- Give me the doll, Rad.
- No, I like it. What?
- Give me the goddamn doll, Rad!
- Lisa, what is your problem?
Give me the goddamn doll,
or I'm gonna jack your ass off.
Too late.
- What the fuck was that?
- I call it the Tracy Doll.
- Like in your ex-boyfriend Tracy?
- Made sense at the time.
You got issues.
- I live in L.A. Don't blame me.
- Oh, my goodness.
- You know what the problem is?
- What?
You sell all your good stuff
to Sharper Image.
- Then you give your boy the bullshit.
- Sharper Image pays me.
- You're gonna take it there?
- Yeah. And, Rad...
how about letting me go out with you?
I'm tired of being huddled up in here.
You know I can do it. I'm practicing Tae Bo.
- That was a good move. Do that again.
- What?
Let me see that move again.
Yeah, okay. Lisa.
- Let me think about it.
- Think about it.
No.
Tell me, what's up with this Wild Wild West?
Don't touch, all right? See this one here?
This one can knock out a 300-pound man
100 yards away.
I call it Magilla.
And this one, here.
I'm not exactly sure what this one does,
because I haven't used it yet.
What is it supposed to do?
Inject adrenalin into the sexual glands...
thereby causing deep passion.
I call it Thriller.
Okay. Why the hell
would you need something like that?
You're kidding, right?
- You keep the love potion.
- Okay.
I'm gonna see you later.
- Call me if you need me, Rad.
- No!
Inject some adrenalin into your ass.
Compliments of Miyako.
I'm Chinese, motherfucker!
You know, I'm hurting right here, too.
Need a little bit of touching. Yeah.
Right there, too. Another peck.
Right there.
Here. Right there, too.
Okay, now, I really need you
to concentrate...
because this region, right here...
it's just in bad shape, okay?
Damn it! Just keep it hot.
Talk to me.
What's up, Captain?
Right now?
All right. I'll be there in 10 minutes.
Make that 11.
This better be good because
I was just giving this waitress a massive tip.
You don't need to be here, Conrad.
Just let it be.
- Get the fuck out of here, man!
- Everybody, let's go.
Can everybody get the fuck out of here?
Make sure your report reflects that we have
evidence to support a murder-suicide here.
Most of these rap guys
are unstable, anyhow.
Captain, this wasn't a suicide.
- What do you need?
- Time.
You got 36 hours.
After that, it goes into the system.
Whatever evidence we have
is how we'll designate the case.
I know that's shitty,
but we're backlogged like crazy...
and Benji did have a rap sheet.
I'm real sorry, kiddo.
That's the best I can do.
Amazing grace
How sweet
the sound
that saved
a wretch
like me
I once
was lost
but now
am found
We are live and exclusive
at the funeral for rap superstar Benjamin.
As you know, there has been a tremendous
amount of secrecy surrounding his death.
Thousands of people
are still in a state of mourning...
over the recently deceased singer.
But here at the Balboa Street Cemetery,
only close friends and family...
have been allowed
to say their final goodbyes to the artist.
- You gonna be okay?
- I'll be okay.
I still can come by on Sundays
to get my pie?
You know it.
Go on.
All right, it's okay.
Mr. Freeman!
- My name is--
- I know who you are.
- You're Benjamin's boy Conrad, right?
- That's right.
- I'm investigating Benji's--
- You haven't been watching the news?
- The media said it was suicide.
- That's what they say.
I'd like to talk to you as soon as possible,
if you don't mind.
This is a funeral for your friend,
and you come at me, playing detective?
Why don't you respect a brother?
I mean, you're coming at me
like I'm some kind of suspect.
- If you got nothing to hide--
- Fuck you!
Benjamin was a friend of mine.
Shit! I made the motherfucker rich.
What the fuck did you do for him?
That's what I thought.
How about 12:00 p.m. tomorrow...
if you can wake your big ass up?
Our time is gonna come soon.
Trust me on that.
You must be Venus.
Conrad McCrae.
Benji talked about you all the time.
He didn't kill himself.
What was he like?
- What do you mean?
- I mean...
would he have wanted any children?
I never got a chance
to talk about any of that stuff.
I may not have known everything about him
I could've known...
but I know he didn't kill himself.
I know it.
Do you know about B. Free?
Yeah, I just met him.
Do you know
that he has three of the same cars...
so that his enemies
won't know which one he's in?
What record company CEO does that?
One that's in a whole lot more
than just selling records.
I need you to help me find out...
what really happened to Benji.
- You know you're rich, right?
- What?
My mum used to tell me that all the time.
We would sit in the backyard
on a clear summer night.
She would look up into the sky,
smile, and say, "We're rich."
You see, she grew up in the inner city...
and ain't never got a chance to see the stars
'cause of the streetlights.
Then one night,
she was visiting the suburbs...
and she saw them.
Right then and there, she realised
why people in the suburbs are rich.
That's why she worked so hard
to move us out there.
Just so her family could see the stars.
- You miss her.
- Every day.
When she got ill, there was nothing
I could do but watch her die.
But now with Benji, you can do something.
You can make things right, Rad.
You know, Lisa...
I really do value our friendship.
I love you, too.
- Damn, fool!
- You don't kick nobody.
- Let go of me.
- No, I've got you.
What you gonna do? Come on!
- I'll take you--
- Chill! What are you guys doing?
You're on the same team.
- He won't pass the ball. I was wide open.
- No, you weren't!
- Ball hog!
- Shut up!
That's enough.
Do you two want to play
in the championship game?
The only way you gonna do that is if
you beat Duran and J.R. in the two-on-two.
- No problem.
- Yeah, we'll smoke 'em.
Then we'll make it interesting, okay?
The game is seven. Duran and J.R. has six.
You guys have nothing.
- What?
- That's not fair!
"That's not fair." Okay, then I suggest
you pass the ball, all right?
Everybody else, on the baseline.
Kyle and Randall lose this game,
everybody else is running laps.
So you better root for your team-mate.
Pass it back.
Come on!
Talk to me.
Yo, motherfucker,
you better watch your back.
Stay out of grown folk's business,
or your ass will end up just like Benji's.
Come on, Randall, pass it!
Dag, man!
- Play some defence.
- What?
- Who the fuck is this?
- Venus.
Conrad, I need you to come over right now.
- I just got a crank call. I'm really scared.
- Where are you?
I'm at the Regency Building.
- Room 302.
- All right, I'm on my way.
- Who is it?
- It's Rad.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Just a little freaked out.
Somebody don't want me to find out
who really killed Benji.
We need to get you out of here.
Get your things.
All right.
Shit!
Shit! Come on!
- You okay?
- I'm fine. What are we gonna do?
- You afraid of heights?
- What?
Do you feel the spirit?
Do you feel? Do you feel the vibrations?
All right. We are praying to the gods.
I call on God, Jesus, Baal,
and everybody else to bring Bobby here!
Feel his presence! It was an untimely death.
Do not mess up the move.
Send us our son!
It's all good. Keep....
Mama, please! This is not the time
to be talking about this right now.
I got to go. I got to work.
Demise?
What the fuck!
Come on, let's go.
- Give me your keys.
- I don't have them. I left them upstairs.
- What the hell is that?
- Lisa. You'll meet her.
- Are you okay?
- I'm getting there.
You must tell me everything you know
about Benji's business dealings.
- I don't--
- Think.
- I don't know anything!
- Think!
- Lady, I want you to think!
- I don't fucking know anything--
- Come on, now!
- Think.
- Call his lawyer.
- His lawyer would know something.
- What's his name?
David Rabinovitz.
- You sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
I saw the tape.
Look, they're saying she's 14.
I saw you jack off. I can't fucking help you!
I saw you piss on her,
and then you jacked off!
David Rabinovitz?
Ted, let me get right back with you.
I have some blacks in front of me. Great.
I'm Conrad McCrae, Private Investigator.
This is Venus Hatchett.
- You have a minute?
- Venus, yeah.
I was just discussing your husband's death.
Talented guy. He could rap.
- Could you clear a few things up for me?
- Anything you guys need.
- First, do you have a copy of Benji's will?
- Benji's will.
I know that there's a Bentley, the Rolex....
Where's the Platinum....
It was right under the Platinum account.
- Here it is, right here.
- Thank you.
Can you guys hold for a second?
Pam, can you get...
- Reggie Fiess' number?
- All right.
Anything unusual happen with Benji
the past few weeks?
Not really. The usual contracts,
new album coming out...
- getting ready for that video shoot.
- A video shoot?
Yeah, Paul Williams
is shooting Bitch, Shake That Ass.
It's gonna be phat. All the things
the blacks do with the videos...
with the girls and whatever.
Hold on.
Pam, can you please get Line 7? Shit!
- Who's Armageddon?
- Silent partner.
It says here that...
this guy Armageddon is to receive
the bulk of Benji's royalties...
and all his publishing rights.
What would that be worth?
- Millions.
- And no one knows who this cat is?
That seems a little suspicious,
don't you think?
Of course, Venus, you receive
50 percent of the estate once he passed.
Goddamn.
Talk to me. Hi, Sister Karen.
No, you can tell the boys
I will be at the championship.
All right, bye now.
Where are we going?
It's time to take you to a safe place.
Coming up is the first single
off of Benjamin's never-heard-before album.
Rest in peace, Benji.
This is for my niggas doing biz
hold ya head
Mix tuna fish with the squid, hold the bread
For those getting hit at the board
got to get a reward
Park at the gate with incredible doors
This is D block, daddy
We touch dudes with Kalis
Can I just stay with you? I'd feel much safer.
Trust me. She'll keep you safe.
She's got more firepower than Waco.
- What's up, Rad?
- What's up, Lisa?
Lisa, this is Venus. Venus, Lisa.
- How you doing?
- Okay.
So, you come up with a name for him yet?
- Kaboom! Yeah, that's it.
- He's adorable!
I should have known.
Lisa, I was just telling Venus
how much I trust you...
and that you got my back,
and I was just wondering...
if she could stay here
until I could figure out a few things.
Sure. Why don't you go
make yourself at home?
- Thanks.
- I told you.
Thanks.
Kaboom is heavy.
So, Rad, wassup?
You're turning me into a baby-sitter.
The girl, the dog.
When will you let me
get out there with you?
Come on, Lisa, you know your place is here,
designing all this crazy stuff.
- This shit ain't that crazy, though.
- Come on, now, it's a little crazy.
Plutonium-laced tampons?
Statistically speaking, there are
more and more female terrorists every day.
You'll see. Them tampons are gonna pay off.
Just give me a call
if something strange happens, okay?
No doubt.
And try not to kill Venus by accident.
- I will.
- You promise?
- I'll try.
- All right.
- Got you.
- Thank you.
We need her on the set now.
Now I can send you on your way
or just split your knot
And you can talk to Pun,
and kick shit to Pac
Tell Big you dig city spit the hot
I got you feelin' for this R&B kid to drop
Keep it locked, push mad hits
I'm R&B but got a thing for this rap shit
You think I ain't touching
don't stop the madness
I got a deal, I got dough, I got a bad bitch
Cut! That was nice!
I like all that, when you grab the ass.
That was nice.
Remember to do that every take.
- We can wrap that.
- Yeah, like that's hard for you.
I'm Conrad McCrae, Private Investigator.
I'm looking into Benjamin Hatchett's murder.
- Yeah, Benji.
- I talked to David Rabinovitz.
He said you spent a lot of time with Benji
for the new video.
- Right, we were trying to close that deal--
- Have you ever heard of Armageddon?
No, I do not know him personally.
But my partner, who produced Benji's
album, said he was a writer or something.
What can you tell me about Demise?
Yeah, I'll tell you that...
that Garbage Juice Truck,
or whatever it is, Garbage Truck Juice...
was one of the shittiest songs
I've ever heard.
What about that record label, Funk U Up?
Mr. Williams? You have a call on Line 3.
Yeah, give me a second.
Listen, I don't know
how much you know about this...
but anybody who knows anything
knows not to ask those kinds of questions.
- You wanna build on that?
- They don't sell any records.
They got Beverly Hills offices,
gold-plated desk...
and they pay for $100,000 videos in cash.
You didn't hear that from me.
Now, that was the one, right there.
Playback. Check this out.
This is Conrad. He's a private investigator...
checking out Benji Hatchett's case.
Listen, I'll be right back.
I heard you guys were kicking it a lot
before the incident.
Was he stressed out?
Can you tell me anything?
I haven't really seen too much of him,
'cause he was like....
- He was caught between his girl and school.
- School?
Some community college up north.
But he was keeping it on the low.
Did he ever mention Armageddon to you?
- Like the ending of the world?
- He's talking about Armageddon.
The writer, Armageddon.
He's high. He's been smoking that shit.
I never heard of him, man.
Want some of this?
- No, dog, I'm on a diet.
- Sure?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Look, I know you brothers are busy.
I appreciate your time.
But anything comes up, could you....
- Sure.
- Okay, peace.
- See you.
- All right.
Okay, my people, let's recap.
Jean Baptiste Pointe duSable.
Black pioneer, trader,
and founder of the settlement...
that later became known as
the city of Chicago.
He and his Native American wife...
took up residencies on Lake Michigan...
at the mouth of what became known as
the Chicago River.
It is his residency here...
that established his name as
the Father of Chicago.
Some of you may think
Michael Jordan was the Father of Chicago...
but actually it was Mr. duSable.
There are four chapters of Mr. duSable
in your books.
I want you to read them,
learn them, know them.
For tomorrow you will be richer for it.
Have a blessed day.
He was spiritual and enlightened
in contrast to most of his peers.
He also had a great interest
in history and philosophy.
I suppose that's what made him
such a great writer.
He had a writing partner.
Is that a question or a comment?
His name was Armageddon.
Did he ever mention him to you?
- No, I think I'd remember a name like that.
- I see.
You know,
it's a shame that such a good guy...
could be killed over money.
We don't know he was killed over money.
Well, it is the great motivator, isn't it?
I guess you're right.
I'll be in touch, Professor.
Mr. McCrae.
- Send my condolences to his family.
- No doubt.
What's up, B.? You know...
we had a hundred ways of saying goodbye:
"Later," "holler back"...
"Audi 5,000"...
"peace, peace out."
But we were never prepared...
to say goodbye forever.
How do you say that?
...evidence to support
a murder-suicide here.
Time!
What's going on?
You're acting like you're not team-mates.
Coach, he won't pass the ball.
We don't have time for that.
This is for the championship.
I want you to bring the ball home.
We got 10 seconds.
I want a good shot. Can we win it?
Let's go. Ready?
One, two, three, play!
Pick up the phone!
Lieutenant. The gun was in his right hand.
- So what?
- He couldn't dial with his right hand.
He couldn't shoot a basketball
or pull a trigger.
That's a good start, but I need more.
I'll be in touch.
Excuse me, Lieutenant. We have
a civilian here to see you: Conrad McCrae.
Thank you.
I think I want to drop and give her 50.
I see the government
is recruiting fine these days.
And I see some things never change.
What's up, Lieutenant?
It's been a long time.
- Too long. Should I take that personally?
- I would.
Okay. To what do I owe
the honour of your visit?
Come on. Why are you playing me like that?
You know I miss you guys.
The camaraderie we used to have,
the system, the fly uniforms.
Okay, what do you really want?
I need some information
about Benji Hatchett.
Federal?
You know I could get fired for this.
You know if anybody can do it, you can.
I'll make it up to you.
I'll do it because I'm a fan.
I didn't know you like rap.
I meant a fan of yours, Conrad.
Does the government know you're a freak?
What exactly are we looking for?
Anything. I've been on a wild-goose chase
since this thing started.
Looks like his promoter bought him a limo.
He bought his mum a house.
He bought a gun.
- This is kind of strange.
- What is it?
Bank statements. See all these deposits?
They're pretty regular over the past year.
All withdrawn from the same account,
all basically the same amount.
Until last month, he makes this
huge deposit from a cashier's cheque.
It sticks out like a sore thumb.
- Where's it come from?
- Hold on a sec.
There it is. New American Music.
Andre Haus, guarantor.
You're the best.
That's it?
- Janet called and....
- All right, go.
- What's up, man?
- How're you feeling?
- Thanks for seeing me.
- No problem.
You wanted to know
about this cheque, right?
$500,000, man.
Why?
'Cause Benji was about to sign
with New American Music...
after his contract with New Freedom ran out.
That's why.
- And B. Free found out about it?
- Apparently so.
I did everything in my power
to keep it from him.
Bobby Freeman isn't exactly the type
of brother whose shit list you want to be on.
Half of Benji's royalties
is going to a guy by the name of--
Armageddon.
- You know him?
- Yes. Good writer.
- What's his real name?
- That I don't know. Benji never told me.
So let me get this straight.
B. Free finds out
that you want to sign Benji.
Then he figures Benji is worth more to him
dead than alive, so he kills him.
Tell me,
what's the deal with this Demise guy?
Demise works for Funk U Up, man.
Funk U Up is a dummy corporation
owned by Bobby Freeman.
Demise and them were supposed
to get Benji to sign with them...
but they were too stupid to pull it off.
Benji's now dead.
Armageddon gets half of his royalties.
All B. Free has to do
is strong-arm Armageddon...
get him to sign over his half...
and he owns damn near
the whole smash, man.
I guess I gotta find this Armageddon first.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Hello, Lisa? What you got on, girl?
What's up? This is Rad. What's going on?
What?
- Lisa, what happened?
- When I woke up, she was gone.
- She didn't leave a note or anything?
- Nothing.
- Where's your keys?
- In the car.
What do you want me to do?
Get in.
I'm telling you,
girlfriend was just gone. Straight.
So Demise worked for B. Free
the whole time?
That's why he tried to kill me.
Venus told me about that.
So, who is this Armageddon?
That's the $10 million question.
I don't know, Lisa. This shit is crazy.
My best friend is dead.
Lady Wu Tang kicks my ass.
The worst rapper in the history
of the business tried to smoke me.
This just ain't my week.
- You didn't, Rad.
- What're you talking about?
That's cold. You mean you didn't know
that Tracy's the manager here?
- I didn't.
- You're lying.
- I swear to God--
- I know you're lying.
- What's up, Trace?
- What's up, man?
You didn't! You know
you're not supposed to be in here.
- I got a restraining order against you.
- Yes, you do.
I'll be in the car.
- Let me get the key, Trace.
- What key?
Don't play dumb with me.
The key to Benji's room.
I don't know what you're talking about.
- You don't know what I'm talking about?
- No.
Okay. You're talking about that key?
I thought you meant the key to life.
That key.
Give me the fucking key.
- Benji's key?
- Yeah, Benji's key.
She's supposed to stay
100 yards away from me.
You know, there's a bird in Africa
called the Whitetop.
A beautiful bird. It hunts smaller birds.
And when it catches it, it decapitates it.
And then it takes the bird's head
and hangs it from the branch for all to see.
You're lucky
this bird ain't hungry right now.
- What happened to you?
- Give me the surveillance tapes.
I don't know what you're talking about.
This ain't the time to be fucking with me.
I'll tell you, just like I told those detectives.
The tapes were gone
before the police even got here.
Breathe.
Whatever he said, he's lying.
I didn't know shit about them midgets.
Remind me to bring that up later.
But for right now,
I need you to run this invoice I found.
- What's it for?
- It's for a shipment of CDs.
- Benji was in the music industry.
- I know that, Lisa, but look at the total.
- That's a lot of money for 250 records.
- $52,000?
Okay, I'm on it.
- What are you going to do?
- I'm about to pay a visit to a little friend.
Take this.
- What is it?
- It's me looking out for your ass.
You call me if you need me, okay?
- Be careful.
- No doubt.
8619 Lankershim.
This is it?
This isn't Funk U Up Records.
...Lady Wu Tang kicks my ass...
Hey, Rad, this is Lisa. The address is fake.
I've got a lead that I'm following.
I'll fill you in later.
I'm Tammy Wong.
Here's a sample of what we do.
Come on, baby.
I know my CD player's working.
Oh, my God!
Baby.
I've got to go.
I've got to tell you something.
I'm pregnant.
You can't have that baby, baby.
I got a woman.
So?
I love you.
You know what?
Let me think about this for a second.
Are you seriously trying to tell me
you think Ginger's finer than Mary Ann?
You're fucking stupid?
What the fuck was that?
Go and see if the window's open.
Might be them damn mosquitoes again.
Damn!
What the fuck is this?
I don't know what I'm thinking...
but I want to ask you if....
Do you want to give me a massage?
Yes, I do.
All right!
I saw the way you were looking at me, boy.
I was like, yeah.
Them shoulders are soft.
- Like them tats?
- I like them tats, too.
You make me feel like a man!
Fuck it.
What was that? A.9?
That shit sounded like a.45 Grizzly.
- Fuck the guns.
- You know what I'm saying?
We are into non-violence tonight.
- You know, nigga?
- You bet.
Wait right here.
I love you.
Now! Go!
Do it, daddy.
Hell, no!
- Wanna sit here?
- Yes.
You want me to sit down?
Go get B. Bring him back here.
- Like this?
- That's right.
Too late!
Are you okay?
- Is your ass hot, too?
- Hell, yeah!
Come on.
You okay?
What are you doing?
It's just that I feel like
you're Benji's guardian angel.
I feel like you're mine, too.
How did they get you?
Fuck, I'm sorry.
I left Lisa's because I wanted to help and....
Shit! I guess they were following me
or something.
- What is it?
- I don't know, but it's Lisa though.
- I don't get it.
- I do.
Benji's pager.
It's Armageddon.
- What?
- I gotta go.
All right, take this.
- You know how to use one of these?
- No.
- Just point and shoot.
- Okay.
All right?
Lock the door.
I got to Armageddon before you did, Rad.
If you want to see him alive,
warehouse, Pier 27 at 6:00 a.m.
I'll give you what you want,
you give me that tape.
Oh yeah, this tape is blowing in 10. Out.
Blackie Chan up in this motherfucker.
Fucking door was open.
Where's Armageddon?
Where are my tapes?
Them nuts is clean.
No, they're not.
Asshole.
Go check them out.
Where's Armageddon?
I hope you ain't trying
to get smart with me, Rad.
Make a few copies for the boys
down in the squad room.
- No time.
- No cops outside waiting for me, right?
You destroyed the evidence.
I was smooth, wasn't I?
I mean you gotta gimme that.
But I tell you, if you're lying...
- he's dead.
- I feel you. Now what?
Just so we're clear.
I mean, you know, just so we're clear.
I tell you,
you really should be working for me, Rad.
- I mean, we'll make a hell of a team.
- Fuck you!
You kill my best friend,
and you want me to become your partner?
You still think this is about record sales?
Maybe. Maybe it's about heroin.
That's your real business, right?
Imprinting heroin on CDs.
Selling heroin on CDs make this whole thing
legal for you, don't it?
Now you got accounting records
and everything.
You see the beauty of the whole thing?
It's just supplied to the entire West Coast,
and nobody thinks a thing.
Your shit was hot...
till I took out your main supplier.
Those dogs were doing pretty good
until you came along.
Almost fucked up my whole operation.
Looks like she's getting ready
to whup your ass, my brother.
My momma always taught me
to never hit a woman.
But, bitch, you ain't got your papers.
I'm about to fuck you up.
I need to ask you one question
before I take you in.
- Why did you do it?
- So, we're back to this?
Why I killed Benji?
You're smart, Rad. I'll give you that.
See, I knew if you took the case...
and got your little emotions involved...
the last thing you would be thinking about
was drugs.
Benji's dead for one reason,
and one reason only:
- because he was your friend.
- Shut up!
Nice and easy, Aaron Neville.
It's good. That's the tape.
You're the man.
Just out of curiosity, Rad,
did you have a look at the tape?
And what did you see?
- I saw you leaving the scene of the crime.
- You did?
- So you're positive I killed Benji?
- You tell me.
I would...
but then that would ruin the other surprise.
- What the hell is this?
- You don't even know, do you?
This is Armageddon.
What, you don't believe me?
Rap, motherfucker!
I got bitches on my dick
'cause I rock the hits
drive the whips, stack the chips
I'm a professor of Philosophy
of sexual veracity
Your big black ass is history
Fuck you, motherfucker!
See, change up a few things...
add a sample or two, and you got...
a hit.
Drop the gun, B.
No, motherfucker. I think you got it wrong.
I think you're the motherfucker
who needs to drop the gun.
Bet you didn't see this one coming.
Venus, what are you doing?
I should get an Oscar for that acting job.
I mean, the tears, and I was crying.
Baby, I think he was
starting to fall for me a little bit.
- Hey, baby.
- Hey.
So, what are you gonna do?
You pull that trigger, he dies,
and so do you.
You know, I actually can't believe
you made it this far.
It's too bad and so sad
I can't say the same for Lisa.
What about Lisa?
Caught that bitch
slipping outside her garage.
I shot her.
Two shots, point-blank range.
Pulled the trigger on Benji, too, didn't you?
Yeah, I did, but that was easy.
I fucking hate rap.
See? I told you, Rad.
I ain't no killer.
I'm a businessman.
But this bitch right here, this bitch is crazy.
I thought you loved him.
Loved him?
Baby, I didn't even fucking know him.
What?
Where did you get your P.I. license?
In a cereal box?
Bring her in.
Venus, this is Rad.
Baby, what are you doing?
Let me break it down for you.
With you gone, I can run the whole show...
and the Asians will deal directly with me.
So I just don't think
there's any room for you anymore.
Bitch, you've done lost
your motherfucking mind!
- Shit!
- Oh, look. I'm sorry.
I'm fucking with you.
Why are you running?
Come out, it's your turn.
Take it like a fucking man!
Now look at this shit.
Big, bad Rad just killed an innocent man.
Get out here!
Nobody ever had to look for me.
- You're messing with the wrong cat now.
- You having a party without me?
I knew I should've checked your vitals,
gadget bitch!
Would have, should have, could have, bitch.
- Follow my lead.
- Better know what you're talking about.
So smart. See now, that was easy.
I just want to have a good view, that's all.
- View for what?
- This.
Sometimes PMS can blow your mind.
That little slut shot me twice
when I wasn't looking.
Shocked me a little bit,
but that was all right.
It gave me a chance
to try out my new bullet-proof vest.
It was something about her ass.
I never trusted her.
Woman's instinct.
How the hell did you get a bomb on her?
Girls borrow stuff from each other
all the time.
- Not the--
- Tampons!
- What?
- I'm done with you.
I told you they would work.
What have we got here?
- You all right?
- Yeah. How did you like my flow?
- I don't know what to say.
- I'm just glad you're okay.
- Anything she needs, okay?
- Thank you.
We'll be in touch.
Is it over?
- Did we win?
- At the buzzer.
Why did you shoot me?
It was the only way I could save you.
Don't worry, I didn't hit anything important.
Thanks for--
Save your strength.
You're gonna need it later.
Benji would be very proud.
- Hey, man, I'm just doing my job.
- All right.
To the Batcave, Alfred.
I'm a professor of Philosophy
of sexual veracity, 'cause I rock the hits
So, what now?
Got a championship at the Y
in a couple hours. I mean, right now.
Thanks.
Ain't nothing to talk about. See you later.
I'm catching a cramp in my leg and my hand.
Do you know
how to ride one of these things?
Of course I do. The question is
do you know how to ride one of these?
Can't believe you're still doing
that high school shit. Catchin' a cramp.
Yeah, but it works.
I prefer a stick, but I guess this will do.
Hop on.
- Get on the bike.
- All right.
- Eight seconds.
- I'm up here. Go get 'em.
- Okay, eight seconds.
- Nice of you to show up.
Look here. This is what we're gonna do.
Kyle, I need you to bring the ball up.
J.R., I need you to set a pick right here
on the free throw line.
Randall, I need you to come around,
come off this screen.
Kyle, I need you to give him a good pass.
We win the game, okay?
Coach, I've been off today
and Kyle's been filling it up.
Can I bring up the ball
and he run off the pick?
All right, you guys swap positions.
Randall, I need you to give him
a good pass, okay?
- Done.
- All right, good.
On three, together.
1, 2, 3, together!
Come on.
You can do it.
Make me proud. Come on, now!
Randall, I need you
to make that good pass for me!
The ball-hogging coach...
won a championship for the Y.
Yeah, that's right.
I brought you a little something.
'Cause as long as there's a me,
there's a you.