[instrumental music]
[dramatic music]
[music continues]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[crickets chirping]
[music continues]
[solder hisses]
[jeans ripping]
[music continues]
[cellphone ringing]
- Yeah.
- 'The plane's leaving Miami.'
(Wilcox on phone) 'Landing at 9 a.m.
with six Ki's of fentanyl.'
- 'Is the meeting confirmed?'
- Looks like it.
(Wilcox) 'I need confirmation.
Lots of strings to pull.'
Yeah, tell me about it.
[cellphone ringing]
- It's them.
- 'Stay cool.'
'It'll all be alright.'
[cellphone ringing]
[speaking in foreign language]
[chuckles] Crazy Heaven Club.
Looking for wife.
You wanna join? Huh?
Thanks, I got one already.
Hey, listen...
(Stazek) 'Why we never go out
together, my brother?'
'Wh-why you don't have
good time with me?'
[speaking in foreign language]
Hey, listen. Uh,
the plane's landing at 9:00.
So you gotta sober up, okay?
All good?
Six passengers.
(Stazek)
You're a fucking genius, man.
Tomorrow we sit down with him.
Six passengers would get
my uncle's attention.
Alright. Hey, girls,
you tell him to go to bed. Okay?
- You need to fucking sober up.
- 'Ugh.'
I'll pick you up in two hours,
okay? I need you sharp.
(Stazek)
'I was born sharp, my friend.'
'Born sharp
as the fucking razor.
[Peter laughs]
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I'm sorry, sweetie.
Was I talkin' too loud?
You just tell him there's
no bad words in the house.
You're so right, baby.
You're so right. Heh.
[keys clacking]
Hey, hey, you know
that camping trip
that we were
talking about before?
- The one with me and mom?
- Mm-hm.
It's tonight.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You wanna go wake up mommy?
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, go wake her up.
Mom, wake up!
Mommy, mommy, wake up!
'We're going camping!'
It's happening.
'You got 20 minutes.'
Just keep the lights off.
[dramatic music]
[siren wailing]
[cellphone ringing]
- 'Yeah.'
- Boss.
(Wilcox)
Koslow is taking us
to The General in the a.m.
We're moving in.
I sent you the ops plan
and we need verbal approval.
Give me a sec, Wilcox.
- How many bodies you got?
- 'Eleven.'
(Wilcox) 'Four surveillance,
seven arrest team.'
You did good.
Koslow was your idea.
'You're gonna get credit
for this.'
[horns honking]
'Conquer.'
- 'You're good to go.'
- Thank you, boss.
[door opens]
[music continues]
[tires screech]
Alright, ladies and gentlemen,
thank you all for coming.
This is Ryszard Klimek.
His gang known as Vojtech
is one of the major
importers and distributors
of fentanyl.
'The new dope sensation
among junkies'
also known as Pink
or synthetic heroin.
We're going after him.
We have a source inside.
His top drug runner,
who'll receive the drugs
and take them to The General
at his factory
providing all the evidence
we need to move in.
Please make a visual note
of our source.
And when we move in,
go easy on him.
I'm gonna hand over
to the tactical team leader
for the layout of the meat
factory and final brief back.
[water splashing]
[dramatic music]
[door opening]
Pete, I'm not gonna need
that key.
Hey.
You don't open the door
to anyone.
And if I'm not back here
by 1:00...
Pete, stop it,
I don't wanna hear this.
1 p.m., baby. Okay?
You gotta promise me.
This time tomorrow,
we'll be on the road.
All this will be over.
[door squeaking]
[metal clanging]
[siren wailing]
[dramatic music]
[water splashing]
[door opens]
Alright, same as usual.
This is recording now and
will be recording
the whole time.
All your private numbers
are in there.
Mother, Cousin Jackie,
and dad, it's me.
If I need to communicate, I will
send you WhatsApp messages
using one of these names.
If I call you,
don't be surprised, just answer.
Right before you meet
The General, they'll strip you
of all electronics. This one
needs to enter the room.
- No. The wire's in place.
- Today you need to wear mine.
Hey, it's my ass
that's gonna get pat down.
The wire's in place.
[train screeching in a distance]
Alright, let's test it.
You wanna turn around please?
Of course, sorry.
Oh, and if you feel
your life is in danger
ask to smoke a cigarette,
we'll come get you. Okay?
Might buy you more time.
Yup. Done.
Riley. Let's test it.
Say something.
Those Pollock's
won't give a fuck
if I wanna smoke a cigarette.
(Riley)
'Sounds great.'
Alright, let's stamp it.
Alright, it's June 12th, 2017,
at 0500 hours.
This is FBI special agent
Erica Wilcox.
The following recording will be
a cooperating witness
1-2-4-5 X-Ray-8
regarding case number
9-Alpha-N-Y-1-4-5-7-7-4.
The recording will be a
consensually recorded meeting
between C-W-1-2-4-5-X-Ray-8
and Stazek Kuzek
and Ryszard Klimek.
[dramatic music]
- There's our man?
- Good.
[airplane droning]
[speaking in foreign language]
[car horn honking]
[music continues]
[speaking in foreign language]
[brakes squeak]
[siren wails]
Jeez, guys. A bit obvious
in that damn van.
[car horn honks]
Okay, guys, we gotta go.
The parade is moving.
[traffic bustling]
[music continues]
[speaking in foreign language]
Let's stop at liquor store.
Uh, I wanna buy a bottle
to my uncle, okay?
My God. This guy has no clue.
[music continues]
[speaking in foreign language]
Whitey Fisk, do you know him?
- Yeah, we did time.
- Trust him?
Yeah, he's a straight guy. Why?
We have a buyer.
We're going to Techniska Bar.
Wait, wait, wait.. What do
you mean, you got a buyer?
How'd you find him?
I checked. He's good.
Fuck.
[dramatic music]
[keys clacking]
[cellphone dings]
[speaking in foreign language]
[car door opens]
I really want to see
my uncle face
when we show up with cash.
Jesus Christ. My cousin's one
annoying bitch.
Hook me up.
(Peter) You don't want any of that..
Her face..
It's a problem, believe me.
He needs to stick to the plan.
He'll fuck everything up.
What, we follow
the Little Poland?
[music continues]
Guys, there's been
a change of plans.
Source was ordered
to take drugs to a buyer
on his way to Klimek.
(Montgomery) 'Okay,
if the exchange takes place'
'arrest the buyer,
recover narcotics.'
Copy that.
We follow the Little Poland.
[car engine starts]
'Guys, we follow,
you stay close by.'
(male #1)
'Copy that.'
[intense music]
[music continues]
(Stazek)
Sit here.
[sighs]
I'll take think everything
you got, cabron.
- Whatever we've got?
- Yeah, that's right.
(Daniel)
'All of it.'
What are we talking about? Hmm?
You got a half Ki,
or a Ki, okay.
Six.
[laughing]
Motherfucker, six Ki's?
[laughing] You got a bunch
of Polacks walking around
with six fucking Ki's
of fentanyl?
[laughing]
I fuckin' love it.
Y'all niggers crazy, man.
I ain't got the cash for six,
but I'mma get that shit though.
You're not good for six?
No, no, no. I-I'm good.
I'm good for three, okay?
Just give me a couple hours.
I'll bring back the cash. Bam.
[sighs]
Huh?
Relax.
I'm cool, Polack.
You look a little nervous.
Are you the money guy? Hmm?
You guys want
the fuckin' money or no?
[sighs]
Three Ki's, it's 85k.
Yeah, I can fuckin' count.
You'll get that in two hours?
I guess you motherfuckers don't
know who the fuck I am, huh?
- No. I don't know who you are.
- Ah.
You did time at Bale Hill?
- That's right.
- Whitey Fisk?
Yeah, 0-5-2-0-9.
- Ah, I did time in Bale Hill.
- Oh, yeah?
Whitey, he was over there
in section three, right?
D section. Right?
'Cause they don't got numbers,
they got letters up there.
Who else you do time with?
[scoffs]
Well, fuck you guys. Fine.
Fine, just give me half a Ki.
I'm good for that right now.
Fuck it.
I thought you said
you want three?
Yeah, I want half a Ki now. Hmm.
[intense music]
What the fuck is his problem,
man?
His problem is
you didn't answer my question.
Yeah, question is that, cabron?
Who else you do time with?
Kantro and Delray,
and go fuck yourself.
- Go fuck myself?
- That's right.
[chuckles]
Delray he's murdered.
And Kantro, he's scratchin'
walls up in Austin County Mental
which means that you picked
two guys we can't check on.
What the fuck
are you tryin' to say?
I'mma ask you one more time.
How the fuck is a spic junkie
gonna raise 85k in two hours?
Spic junkie, huh?
[speaking in foreign language]
You got a nasty fuckin' mouth,
you know that?
You don't even know me, man.
You a cop?
[scoffs]
Fuck you.
I'm no fucking cop.
How can you say that, man?
You're a cop.
(Daniel)
'Fuck you.'
(Peter) 'If these guys
find out you're a cop'
'you're a dead man.
You understand?'
(Daniel)
'Stop saying I'm a fuckin' cop.'
'It's a serious accusation,
homie.'
(Pete)
'You'll die here tonight.'
Who are you, cabron?
I'm a drug dealer,
you dumb fuck.
'But I don't wanna go down
for being a cop killer.'
- How far is rescue?
- Five to seven.
Call them, now.
Move it in, guys. Yeah, now.
Put your money back.
Put your fuckin' money
in your pocket.
Fuck it. You guys don't want
my money, fuck you then.
You got one chance.
And I'm gonna give it to you
in a few seconds.
You fuckin' understand me?
[breathing heavily]
Get the fuck outta here. Can you
believe this fuckin' guy?
You waste my time again,
I'll fuckin' kill you.
- Ooh!
- Don't fuckin' touch me, huh?
I said get the fuck outta here.
Unh! It's no deal.
Fuck you. Fuck you.
Waste my time again,
I'm gonna fuckin' kill you.
Hey! Shut the fuck up!
Shut the fuck up! Alright?
'Yo, freeze.
Put your fucking hands up.'
Hands where I can see them.
NYPD.
Chill the fuck out.
You too, motherfucker.
I'm wired fuck.
Huh?
[gunshot]
[dramatic music]
- What the fuck?
- 'Whoo-hoo-hoo.'
Burrito on the floor.
Don't.. Fuck, fuck. You don't
fucking kill cops in New York.
[indistinct chatter]
Get some garbage bag.
Come on.
[speaking in foreign language]
(Stazek)
'You need to clean this shit.'
[men laughing]
[speaking in foreign language]
Gotta smoke a cigarette.
Call off rescue. Let's make
this fucking car disappear.
SO is two minutes away.
(Stazek)
'You're smoking now?'
A cop just got killed.
Call them off.
Calling it off, guys.
[car alarms blaring]
[tires screeching]
[engine revving]
[dramatic music]
What the fuck
are you looking for, man?
[siren wailing in a distance]
Come on. I need you inside.
[speaking in foreign language]
[intense music]
[indistinct chatter]
[music continues]
[brakes screeching]
[birds squawking]
[upbeat music on speaker]
[indistinct chatter]
[speaking in foreign language]
[music continues]
Get up. Hey.
[man screams]
[indistinct yelling]
[man groaning]
[man screams]
Okay.
[man groaning]
[speaking in foreign language]
[intense music]
[man groans]
[groans]
[speaking in foreign language]
When did you understand
the buyer was a cop?
Earlier in the conversation.
Well, I thought
he was a rookie who..
...got into more than
he can handle, I don't know.
I felt he might take advantage
if I gave him an exit.
You thought by kicking
and pushing him to the ground
he would take advantage
of such polite exit?
I-I was trying to avoid
bigger problems for Vojtech.
An NYPD cop just got killed
in New York.
Do you know
what that means, Piotr?
'Bad business.'
'They will shut down
all illegal activities'
'until they find
their cop killer.'
'Now, Stazek
doesn't have documents'
because Stazek doesn't exist
but you? NYPD will come for you.
'The best drug runner
in Vojtech.'
Oh, Piotr..
This is bad business for me.
I'm sorry, Mr. Klimek.
(Klimek)
Oh, no. Don't be sorry.
That feeling
doesn't take us anywhere.
We were talking
about business here.
Please, sit down.
[intense music]
Stazek tells me that
the cop was pointing the gun
i-in your face. Correct?
So, Stazek saved your life.
You now owe the price
of your life to Vojtech.
How much is your life worth?
I don't know.
Two words.
Closed market.
Bale Hill is a holding unit.
It sends prisoners
all over the state.
Hub.
We control the product
inside the Hill.
We control the supply
to prisons all over New York.
You did four years
at Bale Hill, right?
[Klimek sighs]
So if anyone
can get drugs inside
that's, that's you?
You, you want me
to control the supply inside..
I mean, how would I do that?
Oh, you're a resourceful man.
With fentanyl, we can have
tens of thousands hooked
on our product.
They will work off their
debts to Vojtech.
Not only in prison,
but afterwards on the street.
I will own a fucking army.
[intense music]
[slurps]
[gulps]
[sighs]
You'll break your parole.
My lawyers will convince
the judge
to send you back to Bale Hill.
With good behavior, you'll
be released in five years max
and our debt
will be extinguished.
[music continues]
My life ain't worth that much.
[sighs]
How much are the lives
of your wife
and daughter worth to you?
'We found them'
'driving around your house.'
So frightened.
Suitcase filled with clothes.
[music continues]
You informed them
what happened at Techniska.
I-I just, I told them
to get out of the house.
Where-where are they?
(Klimek)
'Outside.'
'Waiting for you.'
Oh, don't worry.
Sofia and Anna will be okay..
...while you're inside.
[music continues]
Now..
...fuck off.
[dramatic music]
[indistinct chatter]
[siren wailing]
[music continues]
[tires screeching]
[dog barking]
[phone ringing]
(Wilcox)
'You safe?'
You guys left me
in the fuckin' lurch.
You were supposed to take us
directly to The General.
(Pete)
'I can't call those shots.'
I'm only a soldier. I do
what I'm told. You understand?
Only a soldier? You just
brought in six Ki's for them.
It would've raised suspicion.
They would've stripped me naked.
(Wilcox) 'Look,
meet me tonight and hope we can'
salvage something,
otherwise four years
of hard work just
went down the fuckin' drain.
What the fuck you talkin'
about..
Are you fuck..
(Nina) 'Anna,
do you wanna come and play?'
[exhales]
Do you wanna go play with Nina?
- Listen, sweetie...
- She's fine. Don't, now.
(Nina)
'I can see you.'
[sighs]
- 'Hi.'
- 'Hi, Nina, You wanna play?'
- Yeah.
- Go ahead.
- Come on.
- Go the the backyard.
[door closes]
Why didn't you do
what I fuckin' told you to?
Just one sec.
Why didn't you fuckin' leave?
Pete, you've got blood
all over you.
Answer my question.
Why didn't you protect Anna?
I wanna know what's going on.
- I'm sorry, I'm...
- I don't wanna hear sorry.
I don't wanna hear
fuckin' sorry.
You were supposed to take Anna
away from there, 1 p.m.
You think these people
would have a fuckin' problem
in killing the both of you?
[yells]
We tried.
[crying]
We fuckin' tried!
We kept driving around the block
hoping you'd be back.
Fuck you!
[intense music]
[sniffling]
Come on.
[water splashing]
[music continues]
[footsteps approaching]
[speaking in foreign language]
[foghorn blares]
[dramatic music]
[speaking in foreign language]
[laughing]
Yeah-hoo-hoo!
[siren wailing]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[music continues]
Driver's license says
it's Carlos Harrera.
His real name was Daniel Gomez.
Who the fuck are you?
Detective Edward Grens,
organized crime.
- He was one of mine.
- 'What happened here?'
He was supposed to be
a low-level buy
off the street tip.
They cut his throat,
pulled out his tongue.
They knew he was a cop.
'What'd you say his name was?'
[siren wails]
[dramatic music]
[music continues]
[siren wailing in a distance]
[indistinct chatter]
- Hey.
Thanks for takin' me here.
It's so romantic of you.
Yeah, dig in.
[indistinct]
Shut up and eat, girl.
Homicide talk about anything?
Like what?
I think Daniel's connection
was Polish.
Entire NYPD force
in this manhunt.
You don't see to sharing
this little fuckin' detail?
I gotta check my sources
before they get spooked
by the stampede.
You heard of Ryszard Klimek,
aka "The General."
Hmm. Polish crime boss, right?
Came over from Poland
after serving 20 years
in some shithole
Eastern European dungeon.
Now he's moving pieces
all over the board.
You think he has something to do
with Daniel?
[bike revving in distance]
Gomez was killed in this bar
in Little Poland.
'It's impossible
to trace its owners'
'the street's link it
to The General.'
'Security cameras across
the street record Gomez'
entering at 11:09,
then at 11:27 this guy pops up.
Look at his body language. This
is a man who's just done bad.
- What do you need?
- Your badge.
IAS comin' after me.
Christ, Eddie.
I sent a man
when he wasn't ready.
This is on me.
[train brakes screeching]
Hold on a second. Watch my six.
That girl over there
was Daniel's source.
Shit.
Shit. Help, help,
help, help, help!
'I'll give anyone $20
who stops the puto behind me!'
- Whoa!
- Help me out! Help me out!
- 'Move! Nigga, move!'
- Hold on.
NYPD! Get the fuck back!
(Grens) Tell me what happened to Daniel?
Tell me what happened to Daniel?
- Daniel...
- I don't know nothin'! Okay?
You got Gomez killed.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, Grens, you wanna talk to me
for a second?
Hey, Ed. Hey, Eddie,
you wanna talk to me outside?
Ed, outside, please?
Right now. Ed?
You're gonna be down.
What are you doing? You wanna
get these motherfuckers?
Oh, this bitch better talk.
You are scaring
the shit out of her.
You wanna calm down,
you wanna be professional
and let me do this, alright?
- Do what you gotta do.
- You stay here.
Hey, honey, you wanna
scooch over for a second please?
Stazek carved him up like that?
You think I'd fuckin' do that?
I'm just trying to find
a professional way to say this.
- Say what?
- You're fucked, Koslow.
- Wait, who the fuck is he?
- 'He's my boss.'
We tried to close the case
on The General
and bury this whole mess.
But Washington labelled
the case as weak
and took the embassy
off the table.
W-w-with all due respect, sir,
what the fuck you talkin'
about taking the embassy
off the table?
You just watched me
smuggle a dozen Ki's
through Polish diplomatic
pouches.
Deal was to give you enough
evidence so you could
indict The General,
which I have fuckin'
over-delivered at this point.
'Look, I've done my part.'
I-I want out.
Agent Wilcox here has a plan
to keep your status alive.
You should listen to her
and hope I like it
'cause in my book,
you're old news, my friend.
(Wilcox) 'Pete,
I think there's a way out of this.'
We go along with
The General's plan.
Evidence of fentanyl being
methodically distributed
inside a state prison
buries Ryszard Klimek for good.
And if that happens,
you're a free man.
[intense music]
The fuck you talking about?
Go back to prison?
That was never part of the plan.
And where is the part
of the plan where you become
an accessory to the murder
of an undercover policeman?
How am I an accessory
when I try to help him?
I mean, it's all on the tape.
And you guys put me there.
If I inform the NYPD
that I'm working with a witness
to Officer Daniel Gomez's murder
you will be exposed.
If you're exposed,
General's case falls apart.
If I say no?
Prosecutor will have
you serve the remaining
twelve years of your sentence
and then tack on
whatever the NYPD pins on you.
[music continues]
[scoffs]
Some fuckin' bullshit.
I tried to help him.
You're a convicted felon who was
present when one of their own
was nearly beheaded.
You should think
of your family, Pete.
Look, once you're in charge
like The General wants
you just build a list
of all the inmates
and COs distributing for him.
'Everyone's a potential nail
to crucify'
'that son of a bitch.'
I need to know you're in.
[music continues]
And let me guess,
if I fuck up and bail
then I'm alone, right?
Don't fuck up.
[scoffs]
[dramatic music]
[car engine cranking]
[music continues]
(Wilcox on tape) 'Look, once you're
in charge, like The General wants'
'you just build a list
of all the inmates'
'and COs distributing for him.'
'Everyone's a potential nail to
crucify that son of a bitch.'
'I need to know you're in.'
(Peter on tape) 'And let me
guess, if I fuck up and bail'
'then I'm alone, right?'
(Wilcox on tape)
'Don't fuck up.'
[music continues]
(Kat)
'Yeah. Thank you.'
'Alright. Thank you.'
Yeah. Thank you.
Buh-bye. Buh-bye.
Okay. Got a couple
hits on the names.
First's a Pole,
street name's Stazek.
Real name unknown,
whereabouts unknown.
Unfortunately, that's it on him.
He was probably
recently imported.
Well, what about the American?
This is where
it gets interesting.
- Peter Koslow, he's a..
- What?
"Complex. Born here,
parents immigrated from Poland.
"Gulf War vet, sniper.
"Served an additional
four tours in Iraq.
"Medals, medical history,
post-traumatic stress disorder..
"Crashed and burned
a few years ago.
"Manslaughter, got 20 years for
killing a guy in a bar fight.
- Then it's weird.
- Weird, how?
Well, the file looks like
it's been redacted.
"Paroled from Bale Hill
after four
pending the full investigation
of new evidence."
Doesn't add up though.
Well, who could fuck with
his jacket like that.
Feds is my guess.
Can you dig into this Fed angle?
You can't just fuckin'
poke around the Feds
like they're one of your
junkie hookers, Grens.
Look, I-I think this is the guy
who shot Daniel.
You said Bale Hill, right?
Bale Hill was part
of Daniel's cover story.
He liked it because
his old man served time there
but that was years ago,
if this guy was fresh out
he could've tripped
the kid up on something.
[indistinct chatter in distance]
Let me see what I can do.
Oh, shit. Got a breakfast date
with my sweetheart.
Wait, this guy you're runnin'
to, is this somebody special?
[chuckles]
You jealous?
I'm just hoping his name
ain't fucking Logan
or-or Chad or Brett.
Laila. Her name is Laila.
Laila?
Kat, why didn't you
tell me that?
[Kat laughs]
La.. Yo, I-I should come with
you and Laila!
Y'all want a chaperone?
[knocking on door]
- What are you doing here?
- We have to talk.
Important stuff.
Don't ever come knocking
on my fuckin' door.
Go to the garage.
[speaking in foreign language]
[sighs]
All night awake, fuck!
What happened?
I had to do some sweeping.
They guy you did time with.
- Whitey?
- Yeah, Whitey.
We found him 30 minutes ago.
Why don't you fuckin'
listen to me?
I told you, the cop
just used his name.
He's a straight guy.
[chuckles]
You can complain to my uncle.
He wants to see you.
- Your wife good cook?
- Why?
It's an old tradition to invite
boss home before prison.
You sell two of this
to break your parole.
Rest until Bale Hill.
Yeah, I still gotta figure out
a way outta here.
Figure it out fast, Piotr.
Detective sniffing around
Little Poland.
Monday you need to be inside.
Kalash told me you went out
last night, motherfucker.
Where did you go?
It's none
of your fuckin' business.
Come on, I want to know.
Where did you go?
My wife's next door.
You have kurba?
[chuckles]
She good fun?
Huh? Who is she?
Come on, tell me,
you mind if I bonk her a while
when you're inside?
You touch any of my things
when I'm inside
and I'll carve
your fuckin' eyes out.
[dramatic music]
[door opens and shuts]
When?
Tomorrow? In a month?
Two days.
[sniffles] If you go back
inside, you'll never get out.
You know that, do you?
[intense music]
[birds squawking]
Are you happy
to spend the day with daddy?
Uh-hmm.
What are you doing?
You see that down there?
That's where I'll be going
on my business trip.
But I don't want you to go.
I know, sweetie, but what if I
told you this was the last time.
[phone beeps]
Okay. Gotta go.
[dramatic music]
[exhales]
(Wilcox) New warden's
name is James Leonard.
He's been briefed.
You give him the list,
he'll put you in solitary
and then in 24 hours
the appellate court judge will
put you back on the streets.
Daddy, you're too loud.
I can't hear my movie.
Uh, I know.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
Yeah, j-just watch your movie.
Sofia and Anna will be
in a FBI safe house
before Klimek evens knows
what happened.
You have my absolute word
on that.
Uh, look, um,
I'm gonna need three favors.
First, I'll need a major drug
sweep day after I get there
to dry up the competition.
And second,
have, uh, Warden Leonard..
...put me on program
post detail.
And third, in six days..
...courier these beautiful
yellow wonders
to a Deputy Superintendent
Reseda Johnson
compliments of the bureau
so the prison receives
them on Founders' Day.
And, there's got to be a
government seal on the package...
I can't do this, Pete.
You know, if the prosecutor
finds out that I helped
people get high, he'll destroy
me, you, and the case.
You..
You gotta fuckin'
help me out here.
I can't do it.
It won't come through, if
it don't come from you guys.
Hmm.
Have Leonard assign me
to roof and yard maintenance.
That I'll do,
the drug sweep I'll also do
but the rest you're on your own.
[siren wailing in a distance]
How's Sofia holdin' up?
Just fuckin' great.
[phone vibrating]
- I'm sorry. I gotta take this.
- Yeah.
One second, boss.
I gotta go.
You'll be fine.
[car engine starting]
[indistinct chatter on tablet]
[engine cranking]
[indistinct chatter]
[speaking in foreign language]
Pete, you should have told me
we have friends coming tonight.
They brought me so many presents
to keep me comfortable
when you're away.
You have such an adorable
wife, Piotr.
- Beata. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
(Klimek) 'We should get
this little creature in bed'
then we can celebrate.
Let's go. I will help.
- It's okay, I got it.
- No, no, no, no. Please.
Piotr, I insist.
'After you.'
I don't have kids, Pete.
I regret it.
Must be wonderful.
It is.
Beata wants them,
but I'm afraid..
I would suffer too much
if something happened to them.
Imagine someone hurts them.
In the honor of bravery of
Pete's, his courageous wife
here is a Polish song entitled
"I Used To Be A Rose"
which talks about the love
we give to our partners.
- Na Zdrowie.
Na Zdrowie.
[Klimek sighs]
[singing in foreign language]
[intense music]
[singing continues]
- Bye.
- Goodbye.
Yeah.
You need more reason to dig?
The General just left
the Koslow residence.
(Sofia) Honey,
you want to go to the zoo or not?
Let's go to the zoo, come on.
'We'll be back
in a couple of hours.'
- Okay.
- Be a good girl, okay?
(Pete) You know daddy
loves you very much.
(Anna)
I know. Can I go now?
- 'Anna, come on!'
- Pete?
Pete, come on.
Give me a kiss, eh?
- Mwah!
- See you later, guys.
- Bye! Have fun.
- Bye! Love you!
- Send me photos!
- 'Yeah, of course!'
[indistinct chatter]
[car engine cranking]
[engine revving]
[dramatic music]
Those kids with a drone.
Better call them today.
Pete, don't worry.
I don't want you to worry.
- I'll take care of it.
- You still got the key?
It's right here.
It's gonna be fine.
[music continues]
(woman on phone)
'911, what's your emergency?'
Please, I need help.
My husband's going crazy!
He wants to kill me.
Please send someone fast!
(woman on phone)
'Just hold it right now, ma'am.'
'Ma'am, is he armed?'
'Do you have any children
in the house?'
Please send someone fast.
[music continues]
[bat clatters]
[siren wailing]
[dogs barking in distance]
[indistinct chatter]
[gates rattling]
Second time around, huh?
I want you to stand
right there for me.
Oh, what language is that?
I don't know.
I was drunk when I did it.
Maybe Chinese or something.
You're not gonna tell me, huh?
'Okay, now show me your arms.'
- Are you affiliated?
- He is.
Last term you become a courier
on behalf of the Poles.
Look at you. They gave you
the white shirts, Slewitt.
- His bed been assigned?
- Not yet.
I got this.
Welcome back, Koslow.
Let them know he's here.
Follow me.
[buzzer blaring]
[clamoring]
(Slewitt)
Stand right there.
[intense music]
Okay!
[indistinct chatter]
Hey! Come here, boy! Yeah,
you see me talking to you!
Don't walk away from me!
Hey! Hey! Pssh!
- Mornin'.
- Mornin', boss.
Mornin', gentlemen.
(male #3)
One time, one time!
Wake up, sleepyhead.
Hey, big man.
(Slewitt)
Carlos.
(Smiley)
Hey, yo, fellas!
Looks like we got us
a new white boy.
- What up, Slewitt?
- Smiley, this is Koslow.
Your new celley.
Try to make him feel at home.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, don't be scared.
They'll be gentle.
Won't you, boys?
The Prodigal Son returns.
I need two extra mats.
You and you, roll it up.
It's your lucky day, dickheads..
[speaking in foreign language]
Each and every business that
takes places under the roof
of this facility
runs through me.
Comply or I crucify you.
- Get back to your block.
- Yes, sir.
[indistinct chatter]
[speaking in foreign language]
[dog panting]
(male #4)
'Rise and shine, ladies!'
[clamoring]
It's time to get the fuck off.
Name?
Koslow, Pete.
Previous term
you kept yourself busy, huh?
Roofing, HVAC maintenance?
We should get you
on the program, Mr. Koslow.
I appreciate that, warden.
Name?
That guy.
- This guy.
- Hands up. Legs spread.
- 'Next. Hey.'
- 'You.'
[indistinct chatter]
(male #5)
'This dumb fuck.'
[indistinct chatter]
They swept the whole place..
Bone-dry.
That's a lucky break for us.
Product will be here soon.
[speaking in foreign language]
Under the table.
[dramatic music]
[indistinct chatter]
[phone beeps]
- Who?
- K-O-S-L-O-W.
Comma Peter.
- I'm sorry, I don't...
- Uh, don't apologize.
Me, I'm old-school,
I knock on doors
get-right-there-in-your-face
type of cop.
Wilcox, we gotta go.
Sorry. You are?
Detective Edward Grens
from the NYPD.
- Everything good?
- Yeah.
We're just having a conversation
about somebody named
Peter Koslow.
'Decorated vet.'
Driver slash security
for the Polish Consulate.
Fast-tracked almost smells
like a bogus parole violation.
Back into Bale Hill.
Same prison he was serving
20 years for murder
before somebody pulled him out
pending the investigation
of new evidence.
Anyway, I want to know
why your subordinate's name
keeps popping up around
this admittedly suspicious
motherfuckin' file.
I'm sure that, uh,
Agent Wilcox's name pops up
on a number of case files,
detective.
You should check with the DEA.
They just sent me here.
(Wilcox) 'Look, if I was involved
in the kind of pro-active operation'
that you are suggesting,
I would be intimately acquainted
with, uh, Peter,
what was his name again?
Koslow.
- Koslow.
- Hmm.
Our organizations may not
see eye-to-eye, detective
but we've extended you every
professional courtesy we can.
There's Koslow
right after Gomez was killed.
That Prius screamin',
"We're the FBI!"
'That's y'all leaving
the scene.'
And here, even though this
picture may be hard to read
that person looks very much
like you, Agent Wilcox..
...drivin' away
from the crime scene.
You want to pitch
your field office
against the biggest police
department in the world?
Let's do it.
We love us a good fight.
[intense music]
Have a good day.
[music continues]
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
[sniffles]
What perfume you wear?
Smells expensive.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
[drone whirring]
[seagulls squawking]
Alright. Now, get
this shit cleaned up.
[dramatic music]
[indistinct chatter]
(male #6)
'Okay, that's enough.'
(Grens)
'It must be tough on you.'
- We'll get through it.
- 'Like you did the last time?'
I checked the old visitor logs
at Bale Hill.
You and Anna never missed
a visitors' day.
That's how
you kept him strong, huh?
You let him see
how much he had to lose.
[sighs]
What do you want?
Someone killed a friend of mine.
I used to think
your husband did it
but now I'm not so sure.
This FBI thing has gotten me
thinkin' otherwise.
[chuckles]
Look, I'm here
to help your husband.
But you got to give me
something to work with.
You know, five years ago
we walked into a bar
looking for a jump start
for our car.
Some bikers inside started
making comments about me
so Pete asked them to stop
and then he was fighting
three of them.
That night
I went from being the wife
of a great father
and a loving husband
to the wife of a convict killer.
And since then,
every time someone tells us
they wanna help
they end up doing
the exact opposite.
So unless you wanna
buy something..
With all due respect
to you and the NYPD
get the fuck out of my store.
I'm not like all the others,
Mrs. Koslow.
I hope you don't learn that
the hard way.
Stay safe out here.
[indistinct chatter]
[intense music]
And here we go.
[indistinct chatter]
[music continues]
[cheering]
Let him through.
(Grens on phone) 'The Knicks
hardly get that exciting, huh?'
Who's this?
Motherfucker, I'm the hangman.
And I just put a tight noose
around your neck.
In a few hours, you're gonna be
alone on this yard
it'll be the scariest moment
of your life.
'Your only way out
is that man in front of you.'
'His name is Vermin.'
'When you're ready to talk
about Officer Gomez's murder'
'tell Vermin
to call the hangman.'
[intense music]
[indistinct chatter]
[ominous music]
Here I am, dead man.
Present and fucking
accounted for.
We need to talk.
I got a fuckin' present for you.
Why're you selling fuckin'
product on my patch.
To get your attention.
You have it. I don't think
it's on you want.
Slewitt.
That's for not respecting
the system.
That's for not following
our rules.
[grunting]
Smiley, listen,
listen, listen.
Please, listen!
You gotta listen to me.
I'm here to take out
The General.
I'm here
to take out The General.
I need, I need his Bale Hill
distribution chain.
I need all the names.
I'll take him down.
I'll fucking help you..
Make it look like a suicide.
Clean up after you're done.
[choking]
You think Mick is important?
Six Ki's of fentanyl per week.
[groaning]
What are those names for?
[Peter gagging]
I'm a... snitch.
I'm a snitch.
Let him down.
[gasps]
[coughs]
It's their fault, Ben.
[gasping]
[coughs]
Are you alright, dead man?
You're a snitch?
I made a deal with the Feds
to take down The General.
Look, you're on top now.
But The General's coming for you
harder than ever.
If you gimme that list
I'll bury
that Polish cocksucker.
That's all, huh?
So, what's it gonna be?
If you're alive in three hours..
...you fuckin' own my ass.
[indistinct chatter]
[intense music]
You can wait here.
Grens went to Bale Hill.
Shit.
- I'm sure Leonard blocked him.
- He did.
But it's only a matter of time
before he gets to Koslow.
He's already got Washington
on the fucking phone
asking me why an NYPD cop
is trying to subpoena a file
on an FBI informant
who shouldn't exist.
Look, we just need
to stall a few days.
Koslow is so close to delivering
and then it won't matter.
What? What are you thinking?
- Burn him.
- No.
He has a family, I mean,
we, you can't make this call.
The Bureau can't afford
the luxury
of your precious feelings
right now.
We looked him in the eyes.
We made him guarantees.
You took a convicted killer
out of prison
you run him off the books
and you stuck him in a room
where a cop was murdered.
If you don't see how this is
about to blow the fuck up
and tear you apart with it..
...you're not the agent
I thought you were.
How fucking dare you?
I was operating
under your authority.
You will not throw me
under the fucking bus
if I don't burn an innocent man.
I don't have to throw you
under the bus.
I didn't know anything
about this operation.
You were trying
to impress a superior
and you went too far.
We'll make an example of you.
You will serve jail-time.
I guarantee it.
You know, I started
on this floor 23 years ago.
My desk was right there.
Burn him.
It's an order.
[snoring]
[coughing]
[instrumental music]
I had you, white boy.
Smiley Phelps
was right behind you.
Like a nigger angel.
[chuckles]
Mmm.
[coughing]
[birds squawking]
[alarm buzzing]
Hey, warden?
I just wanna shake your hand.
Come on, leave the warden alone.
Oh, no, it's okay.
I just wanna thank you
and congratulate you
for running this place
the right way.
I now request a solitary.
I can't do that, Pete.
If you leave me out here,
I'm a fuckin' dead man.
I'm sorry, Pete,
they were very clear.
Who was clear?
Look, this wasn't the deal.
Just get Wilcox here right now.
Escort the inmate back
to his block.
- Yes, sir.
- Lenon, Lenon? Come back here.
(male #7)
'Come on.'
[intense music]
[indistinct chatter]
(male #8)
Time is up!
Come on, guys.
Get off the phones.
Next in line. Six minutes.
[cellphone ringing]
- Wilcox.
- It's me.
Hey, it's me.
I did it.
I drew you the picture.
(Pete) 'Why aren't
you sayin' anything?'
I did what you told me,
and I drew the picture
and now I need
to show it to you.
'I need to show it
to you right now.'
You promised you'd come see it.
You fuckin' promised.
'Fuck, you did!'
'Hello?'
Hello? Hello?
[dramatic music]
Eh, eh, how much time I got?
Two minutes and 15 seconds.
[telephone ringing]
[sighs]
[ringing continues]
- Hello?
- 'It's me.'
Pete?
Are you okay?
The key, you gotta use it
right now.
Why?
They fucked me.
- I'm not gettin' out of this.
- 'No, no. You shut up.'
'You listen to me.'
There is a detective.
He, he asked about the dead cop.
He knows about the FBI, okay?
'You don't fucking give up now.'
Okay. Alright.
Give him the tapes.
Tell him there's information
about Daniel Gomez.
He'll know what to do,
but you gotta
you gotta make him promise
to protect you too.
'You gotta do it right now.
You and Anna you ain't safe.'
'You gotta get outta
the house right now.'
'Okay, baby. You gotta get
out of the house right now.'
Promise me.
Promise me right now, okay?
- Now.
- 'I promise you.'
(Sullivan)
'Time is up!'
Pete.
[intense music]
[indistinct chatter]
I have some information
that might
interest your biggest client.
[music continues]
(Wilcox)
Move away from that box.
Sit on the chair.
How'd you find me?
Your phone. We heard everything.
We tracked you here.
Now, you and Anna
need to get off the grid.
You need to go somewhere
the Pols won't find you.
Take those tapes
and get the fuck
out of our lives.
(Pete on tape) What the
fuck you talkin' about?
Go back to prison?
That was never part
of the plan.
[tape fast forwards]
(Pete on tape) 'How am I an
accessory when I try to help him?'
'It's all on the tape
and you guys put me there.'
(Montgomery on tape) 'If I inform
the NYPD that we're working'
'with a witness to
Officer Daniel Gomez's murder'
'you'll..'
(Wilcox on tape)
'I was always close by, Pete.'
'I was never gonna let
anything happen to you.'
[tape fast forwards]
(Wilcox on tape)
'How's Sofia holding up?'
(Pete on tape)
'You just scared my daughter.'
'Stop trustin' me..'
(Wilcox on tape) 'Sofia and Anna
will be in a FBI safe house'
'before Klimek even knows
what happened.'
'You have my absolute word
on that.'
[intense music]
[indistinct chatter on TV]
[bed creaking]
[grunting]
[both grunting]
Your time is closer.
[grunting]
[groaning]
[choking]
[grunting]
[panting]
[indistinct cheering on TV]
[groaning]
[dramatic music]
[panting]
[indistinct chatter]
[alarm blaring]
[whistling]
[alarm blaring continues]
[indistinct chatter over radio]
[intense music]
[grunting]
[screaming]
Get the fuck back.
Stay the fuck back.
Stay back.
- Back the fuck off.
- Everybody, on your knees!
Face the wall!
Hands on the wall!
- Back the fuck up.
- On your knees!
- Face the wall. Hands on wall.
- 'Stay right there.'
I'm gonna run this
in his fucking brain.
Back the fuck up! Just take me
to talk to your boss.
Koslow, tell him.
Don't do anything stupid now.
Get the fuck back.
Back off!
I will kill him right now.
Back the fuck off.
(Slewitt)
Do what he fucking says!
Just stay away from him.
Stay down there.
Get the fuck away.
Get the fuck over there.
It's okay. We're here..
I'll drive this into his fucking
brain. You hear what I'm saying?
- Get the fuck over there.
- Ah!
I will fucking kill him
right here.
'Back the fuck up.'
It's alright.
[screams]
You tell Lenon,
I wanna talk to the press.
I want a phone to call my wife.
He's got 15 minutes to comply
or I'm gonna fucking
kill this guy.
- Take it easy.
- Gimme the keys.
Stay there.
[screams]
You stay right there.
- What color?
- Black.
[screams]
[grunts]
[indistinct chatter over radio]
What color's the next door?
Ah! Blue.
[groaning]
[alarm blaring continues]
[screams]
You fucking..
[indistinct radio chatter]
[thudding]
[intense music]
[indistinct radio chatter]
I think we should put, um, the..
Girls, don't leave
the bikes outside.
- Take them in the backyard.
- Okay, mom.
Thanks so much, sweetie.
The biggest prophet must be
out..
[indistinct murmuring]
- Czesc.
- Hi.
You're so sweet.
Anna.
Anna, come with me.
What the fu.. What the fuck
are you doing here?
Go inside. Go inside.
[singing in foreign language]
Get away from us.
[indistinct]
Fuck you.
[panting]
[phone ringing]
[glass shatters]
[screams]
[singing in foreign language]
(Grens on phone)
'Ms. Koslow?'
'Ms. Koslow?
Ms. Koslow, is that you?'
Surprise.
(Grens on phone)
'Ms. Koslow?'
Everything is ready, sir.
[cellphone ringing]
- Hey.
- I just got word from Leonard.
Koslow has taken a hostage.
- He wants to talk to the press.
- 'I know.'
(Montgomery on phone) 'Aideg
has granted me his authority.'
I'm going out there.
This ends now.
[alarm blaring]
[glass shatters]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[grunts]
[intense music]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[siren blaring]
[indistinct shouting]
NYPD, freeze!
[gunshots]
[gasps]
[muffled grunting]
Where are they?
[gunshot]
[muffled scream]
[gunshots]
Stand up.
[mumbling]
Shut up or I'm gonna kill her.
Shut up.
Now, we're gonna play a game,
okay?
Where is he?
'Where's our friend?'
[grunts]
[intense music]
Sit down.
I will cut your tongue out
like I did with your friend.
[gunshot]
[grunting]
(man on wireless) 'Hey, Jim,
federal authorities are still proceeding'
'local chains of command.'
'10-9, federal authorities
are still proceeding'
'local chains of command.
Over.'
'Local authorities
are coming in.'
Get ready.
Move! Move! Move!
Get back. Get back.
(man #2 on wireless)
'Lead two moving into position.'
[helicopter whirring]
[siren wailing]
(male #9)
'Hey, Pete?'
'Pete?'
'It's only me.'
'Everything's cool.'
I got the phone
so you can call your wife.
Welcome.
Ray Barnes, H-I-T supervisor.
Get me up-to-date.
Where are we?
Inmate Koslow is holding
CO Slewitt
up there in the HVAC room.
There are three shooters
in position.
One to the north.
We got two more.
South of these towers.
They're the one with eyes.
What decision do I need to make
in the next five minutes?
Well, right now
we're buying time.
Breach will be through
in 15 minutes.
H-S still stuck in the traffic.
(Ray) 'Warden Lenon is giving
Koslow one of our phones'
so that he can call
his family.
If he calls the press,
cut the call.
Copy that.
[cellphone ringing]
- Hello.
- Hey, Sofia, it's me.
(Sofia)
'Baby, what's happening?'
Hey, baby, are you safe?
Tell me what's happening?
Everything is gonna be alright,
sweetheart.
Just, I got this.
Don't worry.
Are you and Anna safe?
(Sofia on phone)
'Yes, we're safe. We're safe.'
Um, Anna's here,
you wanna talk to her?
- 'Alright, put her on.'
- Yes.
Talk to your dad.
Are you coming home, daddy?
I'm trying, my love.
I'm trying.
It's just, uh,
I got held up here. But, um...
Please, daddy,
come back home. I'm scared.
I'm trying, my love.
I'm doing everything I can
to get home to you
as soon as I can.
I just, I just want
to tell you that.
Daddy loves you very much.
I love you very much.
Cut the call.
Put mommy back on.
Babe..
[dramatic music]
[grunts]
[music continues]
(man #3 on wireless) 'I have a
visual of inmate with a shiv'
'in the officer's throat.'
[music continues]
Reds, what you got?
(man #4 on wireless)
'Zero movement, sir..'
- Three?
- 'Negative, sir.'
'Lost the visual.'
Slewitt. Wake up.
Hey?
[indistinct chatter on radio]
God dammit!
What the fuck is he doing?
Come on.
[grunts]
What the fuck?
[grunting]
[screams]
There you go.
- Come on.
- Hah!
That's all you got?
[grunts]
[dramatic music]
Red 3, you have the shot?
(man #4 on wireless)
'Negative. No clean strike.'
'Repeat, no clean strike.'
[grunts]
(man #4 on wireless)
'I have a clean shot.'
'Repeat, I have a clean shot.'
- Hostage's clear.
- You're clear hot.
[gunshot]
[tank hissing]
[explosion]
[indistinct chatter]
[siren blaring]
[dramatic music]
(man #5 on wireless)
'We got a survivor.'
We got somebody. Let's go.
Give me an ID on the survivor.
I need an ID on the survivor.
(man #5 on wireless)
'Slewitt. S-L-E-W-I-T-T.'
Well done, Agent Wilcox.
Good job.
Get the door. Coming through.
Go, go!
(male #10)
'Alright. Let's go!'
[dramatic music]
(male #10)
'Alright, we're loaded!'
'Let's move it out!'
I'm coming with you.
[indistinct chatter on radio]
[dramatic music]
[gun firing]
You cuff yourself
to his leg.
[dramatic music]
[panting]
I recognized him
on the stretcher.
Where is he?
In a motel upstate.
Address?
If you shield me from the O-P-R
investigation
on the Gomez murder...
You think I'm here to negotiate?
Who else knows about this?
You and me.
You need to fix this.
No one can save you
from the Gomez investigation
while Koslow is alive.
Sunnyside Motel Northern Ave.,
Murray Hill.
Room?
3-0-4
You know what to do.
I can't.
If you can't I will.
Keith, I'm so sorry.
- I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
- Keith Montgomery?
I'm special agent Barbara Lee
with O-P-R.
We have a federal warrant
for your arrest.
Please put your hands behind
your back. Thumbs together.
Yeah, we have our target
in custody.
Meet us at peer 11, Wall Street.
Don't it just warm your heart
to see the FBI
and the NYPD finally cooperate.
[dramatic music]
[music continues]
Koslow, it's from Wilcox.
She couldn't get rid
of the tail on your family.
We need you to lay low
for another month till it gets
all worked out with
the corrupt prison investigation
the FBI is conducting.
She promises you're gonna see
your family soon.
But you need to go now
before they catch you.
[dramatic music]
[music continues]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[instrumental music]
[music continues]