MAN: All right,
we gonna set this off,
you know what I'm sayin',
for this
New Jersey Drive joint.
All right!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GATE UNLOCKING)
OFFICER:
How you doin'?
(INMATES SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
Third one on your left.
Enjoy your stay.
(BANGING)
(INMATES CLAMORING)
JAY: I remember when my mom
used to always talk about
how she wanted
to live in peace somewhere.
For her, it wasn't about
cars, money or a new house.
She just wanted to be
able to live somewhere
where it was quiet,
calm and peaceful.
That was
a long time ago.
I remember
when me and Midget
was just little kids.
We used to watch
his older brothers go
out and snatch a car
just for joyrides
around the block.
(CAR ALARM SOUNDING)
We couldn't wait
'til it was our turn
to get behind the wheel.
(ALARM STOPS)
(ENGINE STARTING)
It didn't matter
what it was.
It could've been
a Lexus, a Camry, a Ford.
Didn't matter.
It was all good.
NEWSCASTER: It's become
a tradition in this city
of half a million souls.
The reasons are many.
But whatever the reasons,
the port of New Jersey
has become the car-theft
capital of the world.
On a nightly basis,
you'll find
the streets alive
with the sounds
of engines screaming
and carloads of
kids in flashy imports
racing down the avenues
acting out their anger.
JAY: By the time we got
back on Hawthorne Ave.,
everybody had a ride.
Jamal, Ritchie, P-Nut,
Tiny Dime, everybody.
We was just out there
puttin' on a show.
Blowin' up the spot.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
GIRL: What's up?
(GIRLS SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
You ain't called me
last night, what's up?
(HIP-HOP SONG PLAYING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(POLICE SIRENS WAILING)
JAY: It was about
3:00 in the morning when
I hooked up with Ron Q.
We had nothing
special in mind.
Just a stereo and
a .440 under the hood.
She was live, right.
Right.
Motherfuckers hadn't
seen years out of
their record shit, boy.
Turned out phat, though.
Hell, yeah. Yeah.
I told you
them niggers
is buggin'.
Tell the motherfuckers
against 'em on all
four sides and shit.
I definitely
had to bail out.
Motherfuckers
tried to roll up on me.
Had to show them
motherfuckers mad skills, boy.
Left the motherfuckers
in the dust.
(LAUGHING)
OFFICER: Heads up,
heads up, fellas.
Here we go.
You heard about
that nigger, Troy?
What, that
he got sent up?
Yo, that man
gonna do mad time, B.
OFFICER:
Look lively, you're up.
Let's get ready, guys.
OFFICER:
Roscoe, that's your car.
Motherfucker!
If I ever see another judge,
my ass is out. I might as
well start packin' it up.
Don't be sweatin' that.
It ain't no thing.
They send you up,
you do your time,
that's all.
OFFICER: Front left. Go!
(GUNSHOT PUNCTURES TIRE)
Oh, shit.
What the fuck
was that, man?
RON Q: Hold on.
Let me pull this shit over.
OFFICER: That's
a bull's-eye, buddy.
(OFFICERS LAUGHING)
OFFICER:
One for the good guys.
(GUN FIRES)
Oh, shit!
(YELLING) Holy shit, man!
Come on!
(SIRENS WAILING)
Get up!
I'm shot, Jay.
RON Q: Oh, shit, man.
OFFICER 1: One of 'em
went this way.
OFFICER 2:
Get a light down there.
RADIO DISPATCHER:
Units 5 and 6, we have reports
of shots fired in your area.
Units 5 and 6,
please respond.
You all right, man?
You all right, right?
They shot me.
They goddamn shot me.
We got to go upstairs.
Look at this shit.
I'm fucked! (SOBBING)
Aw, man, you got
to go upstairs, man.
No, man, chill!
Come on, let's go upstairs,
man. Get real.
No, shh, shh!
Come on, man!
Let's go! Get up, man!
Get up, man!
You got to go to
a hospital, man!
I can't.
Where are the keys at?
What the fuck
happened to you?
They shot him, man.
Who shot him?
Police.
The police!
For what?
We was just walkin'.
And they shot you
just for walkin'?
What the fuck!
(SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Get him up!
Get him upstairs!
Get him...
Pick him the fuck up!
Pick him up!
JAY: They hit Ronnie
with something nasty.
He kept telling me
he didn't want to
go upstairs.
'Cause his mom would
kill him for gettin' shot.
NEWSCASTER: ...the ongoing
tensions between police
and Newark car thieves.
Last night,
17-year-old Ronald Lambs
was shot and
critically wounded
while sitting in
a stolen car in Newark.
The police statement
claim the officers
were fired upon first
after they ordered
the youth to surrender.
There have been reports
that the car belonged
to a Newark policeman.
Many residents
in the area
are convinced
that the police
shot Mr. Lambs
out of revenge.
No weapon has been found.
(ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
So they was squattin'
up there waitin' for us.
I'm tellin' you, man,
shots was goin' off,
glass was flyin'.
Shit hit the fan, man.
I'm tellin' you.
I don't know how my man
got by. That nigger was out.
Straight up cold.
'Cause them motherfuckin'
police put a bullet
in that nigger's ass.
You know what I'm sayin'.
That's my man. We need to go
check that nigger out.
Let's check
that nigger out today.
You know what I'm sayin'?
I'll bring the Buddha
and we'll get that nigger.
Look what they did to Pico.
They put caps in that
nigger's back for no reason.
They hit my man
off some mess.
Black man.
You know what I'm sayin'?
Talking about
my man had a gun.
My man didn't have no gun.
You know what I'm sayin'?
It's open season on
the black man out here.
Kid, I'll tell you.
Fuck all that
open season shit.
You know what I'm sayin'?
Fuck that.
You got to be quicker
than them motherfuckers.
You know what
I'm sayin'?
You're quicker
than a Smith & Wesson,
ain't you, motherfucker?
Fuck the motherfucker
Smith & Wesson.
By that time, they start
cappin' niggers anyway.
You know what I'm saying?
That's what
you're gonna do?
I thought you knew.
My heart don't
pump no lemonade.
(ALL CONTINUE SPEAKING)
Yo, here come Coreen.
Hey.
Yeah, yeah.
So come here
for a minute.
Oh, you ain't gonna say
nothin' right now?
It's like that?
You go, girl. Keep going.
I'm talkin' to you.
Where you goin'?
All right.
JAY: Next day,
they put on a little show
of their own for us.
Flexing their muscles.
Trying to let everybody know
who's in charge.
You're always coming around.
It's like a little war
we got right here in
our own backyard.
Why don't you go back
to your own neighborhood?
And there was always one
who seemed to like his job
a little bit too much.
I know him.
Roll him.
Let me see his face.
Let me see his face. Roll.
What's goin' on, man? Yo!
What the fuck
is wrong with you all?
Why you stressin' my man?
TINY: Yo, what's up
with you police?
Why you pullin'
on him like that?
You all like
shooting people, right?
Why don't you
shoot one of us?
OFFICER: We might.
You might?
Yo, you're gonna have
to shoot us all, punk ass!
Sellout motherfucker.
OFFICER ON RADIO:
We're holding them now.
Please check for warrants.
Over.
I thought that they were gonna
snuff you or somethin'.
You know what's up
with him, right?
That nigger know
he saw me.
Fuck, man.
Put some money on it.
That's the motherfuckers
shot Ron Q.
JAY: I hadn't seen my mom
since the day before.
What's up, Mama?
So I knew she'd be angry.
My little sister was good
in lettin' her
know my business.
Now, sit down,
will you?
I didn't say go in there.
I said, sit down.
What's up, Ma?
Sit down.
What's up?
What's up with you?
Don't eat all of them.
I ain't.
I ain't?
I'm not, Ma.
You know Ronnie Lambs is
in the hospital?
Yeah, I know.
You know what
happened to him?
Yeah, I know about that.
Of course you do.
Were you with him?
No, I wasn't with him.
Oh, you weren't there?
Then how you
know about it then?
He told me about it
last night.
Oh, you just
heard about it?
I heard about
something too.
These police aren't gonna
play with you anymore.
You know, they shot
that kid for no reason?
Oh, you need a reason to
get shot nowadays, Jason?
I don't think so.
Look at me.
I don't wanna get
that call, okay?
Now, you stay away
from those police because
they will use their guns.
What the hell
happened to you?
You want something?
Nugget said you was with that
nigger when they shot him.
Fuck Nugget know?
You see that ring
he bought her?
Yeah, I saw it.
He better not
try and marry her.
He will.
Well, I ain't
livin' with him.
Are you done already?
Am I done? You got that
magazine there actin' like
you can read or something.
Am I done?
I can kick your little ass.
Go upstairs.
What's wrong with you?
Yeah, okay, whatever, Jason.
Fuckin' sticks and bones.
I'm about to break that ass.
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
Hello, young lady.
And what would your name be?
Ma!
RADIO DISPATCHER:
We have the description.
Plate number
Robert-Harvey-Thomas, 3-3-9.
Driver is a male black,
late teens.
Red hoodie, white pants.
Last seen in the vicinity
of North Irving.
Did you know
he had stolen the car?
I knew
it wasn't Ron Q's.
Did he tell you
he had stolen it?
No, we was just ridin'.
If it was stolen,
it was stolen.
Made no
difference to you?
No.
Now, did you hear
any gunshots?
Yeah, I heard gunshots.
And how many did you
think you heard?
I didn't think.
I know I heard four shots.
Now, did you see
anybody shooting?
I mean, anybody actually
firing a weapon.
Did I see
the police shoot him?
Did you?
The police was
the only ones out there.
Was there a gun?
Who had the gun?
Ain't nobody had no guns.
What about Ronnie?
You didn't see him with a gun
earlier in the evening?
No.
Were you with him
earlier in the evening?
Yeah.
Well, no. I don't know.
Listen, I know
ain't nobody had no gun
and the police shot him.
But he might've had one
and not told you?
You all can say
what you all want,
but ain't nobody had no guns.
That's all I got
to say about it.
Now, do you think
you can identify the officer
you saw firing his weapon?
JAY: So they had me
in there all morning.
Asking me questions.
Talking like there's gonna be
an investigation or something.
Come on, man.
What they gonna do?
Lock up some cop for me?
(CAMERA SHOOTING)
MIDGET:
Look at this brother.
You think he's sleeping, man?
My man ain't
even breathing, man.
Wake up. Hey, Ron.
This nigger's dead.
Word up, yo.
(GROGGILY)
Nah, man.
I'm alive, motherfucker.
What you think, man?
Yo, how you feel, Q?
You feel all right?
Yeah, man, I'm all right.
I'm all right.
Did that shit hurt, Q?
I know that shit hurt.
It felt like a truck
and shit, man.
Except now they got me on
heroin or some shit.
(ALL LAUGH)
TINY: You look
high as hell, right?
You know you made
the news, right?
True.
MIDGET: Word up.
To tell you the truth,
I don't give
a fuck about all that.
All I wanna do is get
the fuck out of here.
Straight up, B.
JAY: My court dates were
so backed up that week,
I hardly had any time
left for school.
(INDISTINCT)
Sometimes you had to
stand around all morning
when you got there.
And you always
run into a familiar face.
JUDGE: Okay, Counsel.
I have to tell you.
I don't see any circumstances
in this particular case
that would warrant me
to dismiss these charges.
Any other investigations
and pending legal action
has no bearing on the charges
presented in this court.
Mr. Petty, you're now going
to see more of Mr. McHenry.
I sentence you
to two years probation.
If you come before me again,
I'll have no choice
but to send you
to the Franklin James
Burke School for Boys.
Have you heard
about that institution?
Yes, sir.
I thought so.
In a year, you'll have
the privileges of an adult.
Now, if you continue
on this trend,
I'll have no choice
but to sentence you
to serve time there.
Now, let me just add this.
I've seen far too many
young men such as
yourself come before me
in these last 12 years
since I've had the privilege
of sitting at this bench.
Far too many young men.
Now, society tells us
that these young men
are criminals,
hoodlums, animals.
What I see every day
are confused children
trying to find their way
through a harsh and
unforgiving world.
JAY: Back at school,
I had to wait outside
a half an hour
because the metal detectors
weren't working.
Then somebody
pulled the fire alarm.
At that point,
I just called it a day.
So what are they doin'?
Fuckin' with me.
Givin' me the runaround.
The police
tried to smoke me.
Tryin' to lock me up.
Well,
you know it ain't
the first time.
You should see Ron Q.
You lucky you ain't
in the hospital
right with him.
Lucky I ain't dead, man.
Fuck the hospital...
(CAR BRAKES SCREECH)
What's up?
MIDGET: What happened to you?
Just stay away from them.
What's up, girl?
Hey, Tiny.
How you doin'?
Ain't nobody
avoiding you, Midget.
I see in that top
you got it goin' on.
Yeah, and you can't do
nothin' with it, Tiny.
I want to get with you,
girl.
Stop playin' yourself.
Why don't you come
for a ride with us?
I ain't goin' with you.
Come on, man.
TINY: Yo, I'm just sayin'...
I don't believe you're
gonna leave me for them.
TINY: I'll let you
sit on my lap.
You comin'?
COREEN: No.
You're gonna leave me
and go with them?
TINY: Motherfucker's in.
COREEN: I don't believe you.
Yo, Midget.
TINY: Midget,
get in the fuckin' car!
(RAP MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
What's up? What's up?
You're comin' through, man.
What's up
with that party?
I understand, I understand.
This shit is butter.
You should've seen it.
You know what I'm sayin'?
This nigger was like,
yo, pow, pow, pow!
Hey, yo, 5-0, you all!
MAN: Shit, 5-0.
Fuck that shit.
Come on!
(ALL CLAMORING)
(LAUGHING)
Asshole!
(TIRE BLOWS)
Yo, yo, yo.
Yo, what's up, man?
Yo, yo, Midget,
check that shit, man.
Shit! Man, come on!
(SIRENS WAILING)
Let's move!
Let's be out of here!
RADIO DISPATCHER:
They're on
Grant heading north.
JAY: Yo, yo, yo, look
at Robert slingin'
that shit for Bo.
What up, fools?
P-Nut in the house!
What's up, baby?
Yo, what up, K?
You can't drive.
MIDGET:
That boy ain't got no skill.
Can't drive.
Motherfucker can't drive.
Can't drive, baby.
ROSCOE: Okay, I've got
a live one here.
Headin' south on 14th.
Gray Honda Accord.
RADIO DISPATCHER:
Roger. Do you have
plate I.D. on that?
ROSCOE:
All right, I'm comin' up.
Comin' up.
Plate A-G-B-8-3-2.
RADIO DISPATCHER:
Apple-Gary-Baker, 8-3-2.
I copy.
Oh, shit,
we got fuckin' 5-0 on
our back! Come on, you all.
All right,
he's bailin', he's bailin'.
I'm goin', I'm goin'.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
South on 14th.
(SIRENS WAILING)
Yo, that's that Moscow cat.
Be out, be out, be out!
(SIRENS WAILING)
TINY: Sucker's stayin'
on me. Shit.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
RADIO DISPATCHER:
Unit 6 is in pursuit.
(LAUGHING)
(CAR HONKING)
Yo, yo, yo,
get down!
JAY: Go, go, go!
Oh, shit!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SHOUTING)
Yo, is that your
fuckin' brother,
man? Huh?
(WHOOPING)
MIDGET: Come on, come on!
Yo, be out, be out, man!
They're comin', man,
comin', man!
Shit, man!
(LAUGHING)
MIDGET: Shit,
motherfucker, man, shit!
Ah, shit.
Goddamn.
(ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
You owe me money.
Come here.
Nah, nah, don't be tryin'
to pal me up, nigger.
Where's my money?
What's up?
This is not a fuckin'
drag strip, you understand?
This is my groove.
Don't fuck with
my groove, nigger!
I'm tired of you punks
comin' down with
this bullshit.
This ain't
no fuckin' car race.
Take that shit back
to Avon Street, faggot!
Yeah, bounce, motherfucker.
Bounce or get bounced, punk.
Broke-ass niggers!
You watch yourself and
your trick-ass bitches.
Yeah, all right,
all right.
Why don't you get
a job, motherfucker?
Be all you can be.
(ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Bingo.
Yo, I'm going
to get the Buddha.
Who's comin' with me?
MIDGET: We'll be
right here, man.
You gonna be here?
ROSCOE: (ON RADIO)
Okay, Phil, I got 'em
in front of the Chinese joint
on the south of town.
Roger that.
I see 'em.
All right,
who got loot?
Come on, man.
Here, here.
Five dollars?
What am I gonna get
with five dollars?
Fuck more you want?
You all wanna get the Phillie?
Two of 'em.
Here, here.
Go feed your
family while you're at it.
(MUTTERING)
You never got
no money, man.
You'll be here
when I get back, right?
MIDGET: Where we gonna go?
Just be here, all right?
Don't front.
Five fuckin' dollars.
What the fuck is
wrong with this nigger?
(SIRENS WAILING)
Holy shit!
OFFICER:
What are you doin'?
Get out of the fuckin' car!
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
Fuck you, nigger!
(SIRENS WAILING)
OFFICER: Stay back!
ROSCOE: Get them back.
Get back! Get 'em back!
Keep the fuck away!
Get them back.
Joe, get over here.
Come on.
Is he all right in there?
ROSCOE: Shit.
I'll call it in.
Get an ambulance down here.
RADIO DISPATCHER: Send
an ambulance to the corner
of State and Ocean Avenue.
Damn!
What up?
What up, you all?
JAY: What's up, man?
Chillin'.
Why'd you get out
of there so early?
I couldn't take lookin'
at him like that, man.
I couldn't.
I couldn't see him
like that, man.
You seen Tiny, man?
That shit ain't even
look like him, bro.
Word up.
No bullshit.
Yo, what?
I'm tellin' you...
Why you buggin', man?
I ain't buggin',
I'm just sayin'...
Show some respect, kid.
Man, his family
right here, man.
I got love for
the critter and all,
but he just looked messed up.
RITCHIE: Like he just...
People is out here, man.
Man, come on, man.
I'm just sayin' he looked
messed up. I'm just sayin'
he looked like
he got fucked up.
JAY: Something is
wrong with you.
Stop cursing out here.
Something is seriously
wrong with you, man.
RITCHIE: Hey, whatever.
I'm just sayin'...
JAY: Ritchie,
what's your problem?
MIDGET: Here comes
Tiny's mom.
Don't worry about it, man.
Don't worry about it.
I'm gonna
miss you, Tiny.
(ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Much love, homie.
Much love.
Shit shouldn't
have happened, man.
Should not have happened.
(SIRENS WAILING)
What's up, man?
Don't move, kid.
(GRUNTS)
What the fuck
is this, man?
(HANDCUFFS CLICKING)
Shit.
Let's go.
Fuck.
(INDISTINCT SPEECH OVER RADIO)
Yo, my man.
You be the lucky one.
(CHUCKLING)
You're the wrong
black male.
Too bad, too.
I was kinda lookin'
forward to spending
a little time with you.
Maybe become friends.
You know what I mean?
These things
on kinda tight, huh?
Yeah.
Usually you people start
hollerin' holy hell, huh?
Shit, look at that.
(HANDCUFFS UNLOCKING)
They cut through your
skinny little wrists.
Are you done, man?
Can I bounce?
No, you can't bounce.
Let me ask you something.
You know what a grand jury is?
You ever hear of a grand jury?
Nah, I don't know
what a grand jury is.
Well, when questions come,
and questions will come,
just remember who
your friends are, okay?
That's you, right?
Yeah, that's right. That's me.
Now I can bounce, man?
Yeah, get out of here.
Hey, Jason.
Oh, shit, man.
That's so you
stay the fuck away
from grand juries.
You've been fightin'
with somebody?
No.
Somebody hit you there?
The bruise just didn't
crawl down on its own.
How you know that?
Excuse me?
(SIGHS)
Slappin' me in the back seat
of the car, man.
(SCOFFS)
Yeah, man.
Get out of the car
and this fool ass tried
to snuff me, man.
Yeah.
What's up, Clean?
Yeah. Hold on.
What's up?
Your moms wanted me
to talk to you.
Yo. You're coming
over here, right?
Get off the phone.
Listen, I'll see you
when you get here.
What's up, man?
What you want?
Your mom told me
to talk to you, man.
About what?
We're not no fools.
We know all about you
and your boys and
your activities.
You ain't got to worry
about that, not even
if it was your business.
No, now it is
my business.
I am makin' it my business.
You got a problem with that?
You're funny, man.
No, I'm not funny
and I ain't laughin'.
This ain't
no damn game.
I ain't playin' no game.
I ain't either.
And if you think
you can live here,
run in and out
as you please,
get locked up in and out
of jail all the time,
then you expect us
to come and
get your ass out?
(SCOFFS) You got another
thing comin', man.
No, man, you can just stop
the bus right there, man.
I ain't tryin'
to hear that, man.
I'm not tryin' to hear that.
Listen, man,
I don't need no daddy,
all right?
I got my own life.
Just know that, all right?
Yeah, right.
(HONKING HORN)
Yo, Jay!
What's up, nigger?
MIDGET: Hey, yo!
Get up out here, boy.
What's up?
There he go.
There's my boy.
What up, man?
Jay.
Lookin' great.
Ah, get out
of here, man.
What's up, man?
What they do to you?
He snuffed me, man.
Blindside.
Sucker, man. For real.
Yeah, I told you.
Try to lynch a black man out
in this motherfucker, son.
I'm tellin' you, man.
MOTHER: Jason!
Ah, shit, mom's gonna
ding that ass.
She's tripped up.
MOTHER: Kyle.
Get that damn car out of here
or I'm gonna call
the police on you.
JAY: Mom, I'm just
talkin' to them.
No, you can get inside!
And you, you can get the hell
out of here with the car too!
JAY: Can I chill with them
for a minute?
No, you're not
just chillin' with nobody!
I don't see you movin'!
Excuse me. Excuse me, Mom,
I'm talkin' to my friends.
Can I talk to my friends?
No, you ain't
talkin' to no damn body!
Get inside, God damn it!
You all ain't
fuckin' goin' nowhere.
What's the matter with you?
What's the matter...
Oh!
Boy, don't you
ever use that kind of
language with me.
You still here?
Nah, nah, we out.
Whatever, we out.
Whatever, okay.
MIDGET: Put some
ice on that, baby.
We see you
on the block, baby.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, shit.
You're worried about Roscoe?
You better be
worried about your mom.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(RENE AND LIONEL ARGUING)
JAY: I crashed at Midget's
crib a couple times before.
It's all right when it's
just him and his grandmoms.
But when all his brothers
are out of jail
at the same time...
House motherfuckin' rules.
...it's a different story.
All pushes go to the
motherfuckin' dealer.
Five-card draw.
Let me tell you what the rules
is 'cause I don't want to
bust your ass in your house.
And every time I win,
I fuck somebody
in your family.
Ah, shit, nigger,
that ain't fair.
(LAUGHING)
Look at these
motherfuckers.
Yo, Mighty.
MIDGET: Yo, what up?
Loan me five dollars?
Who the fuck do I look like?
I ain't got no money.
Man, the whole motherfuckin'
family is broke.
Didn't I tell you this
motherfucker look like alien?
Yo, Wonder Woman called.
She wants her
sweat pants back.
(LAUGHING)
Yo, fuck you all, man.
MAN: Ah, man, stop clownin'.
Who's these motherfuckers?
Yo, what the fuck
is this, man?
"Auto..." what?
That's the shit
I read in school.
You got to read this?
Think I'm gonna be
on the street with you
the rest of my life, man?
I don't know what
you be thinkin', man.
I don't know.
Who do you think you're
gonna be workin' for, man?
Some white motherfucker
driving a Lexus while your
ass is still taking the bus?
Yeah, man.
Can I put this here?
Yeah, right down there.
I seen one of
them motherfuckers
just yesterday, man.
That motherfucker
popped the locks on his Benz
as soon as he seen me coming.
I'm thinkin' that motherfucker
don't even deserve that car.
You should've took it, man.
I know, man. I felt like it.
I know more about that car
than that old man did.
You know everything, man.
That's the kind of
motherfucker you're
going to be working for.
And they're going
to be making mad loot off
your sweat and your knowledge.
What you doin', man?
Say what?
I'm lookin' for my scissors.
In my bag you're
looking for your scissors?
Nigger, I wasn't
in your bag.
You was in my bag, man.
I wasn't in your bag.
You calling me a liar,
black man?
Don't call me no
motherfuckin' liar,
all right?
All right, man. Fuck you.
Just get out of here, man.
Fuck you!
Look, I'm lookin' for my shit
and it was up in here.
All right, man, just bounce.
Get out of here, man.
(KICKS BAG)
Punk-ass bitch!
This nigger thinks
he's going outside?
Oh, boy, something
ain't easy, man.
What's up, dude?
What up?
Chillin'.
What the fuck
is this you ridin' on?
It's a little somethin'.
Is this how you're livin'?
What's up?
Why are you
talkin' that shit?
Oh, shit. Look at
this motherfucker.
You're walkin', motherfucker.
I wouldn't ride
this bullshit. (LAUGHING)
What's up, man?
You can haul ass.
Out here slingin'
your thing, man. Who you
out here slinging for?
What you say? What's up?
You know what I'm sayin'?
I gots to get mine, nigger.
Motherfucker,
get a real job.
Get out of here.
You niggers
don't know what's up.
You know what I'm sayin'?
I gots to get mine.
Bullshit.
You know what
I'm sayin'?
(GUN FIRING)
(ALL CLAMORING)
(ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Gonna get me some harmony.
JAY: Yo, where we at?
Where we at, man?
That's a good question.
Where the fuck are we?
What the fuck are we
looking for anyway?
Yo, yo, yo,
there we go.
Yeah, there it is.
Right there.
RITCHIE: Oh, no.
(LAUGHING) You ain't gonna
get no money for no cop car.
It ain't about the money,
you ignorant motherfucker.
RITCHIE: Hurry up.
Yo, man, fuck that.
Let me drive
this motherfucker.
That's why
these motherfuckers
can't catch us, yo.
I'll make this shit go.
You motherfuckers want me
to make this shit go?
Go, motherfucker.
Don't talk about it,
be about it.
All right. Motherfuckers
get the fuck out of
my way right the fuck now.
(SIRENS WAILING)
(IMITATING SIREN WAILING)
Get the fuck
out of my way.
(ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
MIDGET:
Shit. Yo, yo, check this out.
Look at these motherfuckers.
Ah, you gonna mess
with them kiddies, you all?
I'm gonna fuck
with these motherfuckers.
All right, watch.
Check this out.
Check this shit out.
(SIREN CHIRPS)
RITCHIE: Get on the speaker.
(IMITATING WHITE COP)
All right, pal.
Pull it over.
MIDGET: (NORMAL VOICE)
Watch this.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(IMITATING WHITE COP)
I see the beer there. Don't
try to throw them out now.
It's too late.
All right, guys,
put your motherfuckin'
hands in the air.
Get 'em in the air.
Now, damn it, now!
You, driver, step away
from the car, please.
Step away
from the car.
Come on, come on, that's it.
Come on out, come on out.
Don't look at me.
What are you looking at?
Get your hands up now!
Look like they're
from Happy Days and shit.
Okay, all of you,
get out of the car.
Come on, get those
hands in the air!
Reach for the sky,
bucko!
(ALL LAUGHING)
Oh, shit!
Hey, hey, hey!
Put that beer down.
Get those hands
in the air now.
Get 'em up! Up!
You guys are in
a whole heap of trouble.
Put your hands
on the car now.
Put 'em on the car!
Come on.
Okay, okay.
You have
the right to be stupid
ass geek motherfuckers.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Okay, guys, carry on.
Have a nice day.
RITCHIE: Stupid motherfuckers.
(LAUGHING)
Look, baby, you ain't got
nothing to worry about here.
Look, you don't need
to be chasin' after the boy.
I'd give him some room
if I was you.
Where you goin'?
I'm going to get
something to drink.
No, no, no.
Go back to your room.
I'll bring it to you.
See, Ma? That's what
I'm talkin' about.
Every time I want
to do something,
you got to be
all in my business.
Every time Jason
does something,
it's okay.
He's out on the street
doing whatever and you
don't even know where he is.
Do you?
Jackie, shut up and
go back to your room.
Why do I have
to go to my room?
I'm the good one.
Shut up.
I'm the one in the house.
I'm always in my room.
If you look for me,
I'm in my room 24/7.
Anybody want Jackie,
Jackie's in her room.
That smells like
borrowed cheese.
You crazy?
That's my dough, man.
What's up?
Yo, yo,
crazy nigger's down.
MIDGET: What up, what up?
What's up, man?
Is you all niggers
crazy, man?
Is you all
motherfuckers crazy?
What you talkin' about?
I'm talkin' about boostin'
that cop car, kid.
Don't act like you
don't know about it,
motherfuckers.
Who told you that?
Tell this motherfucker.
That big-head nigger,
Ritchie, told us.
Ritchie been talkin'
mad shit. Mad shit.
That's all right though.
We still cool.
We cool, but you all gots
to watch the fuck out,
if you gonna play
that rebel outlaw shit.
You know what I'm sayin'?
Rebel outlaw motherfuckers.
We see all you niggers.
Peace out, baby.
Let's bounce, man.
Chill, y'all.
JAY: I told you that
nigger had a big mouth.
MIDGET:
I'm gonna tell that
motherfucker myself.
Still fuckin' with
these toy-ass niggers.
I'm sayin, man...
Oh, shit!
What the fuck
is this, man?
Freeze, motherfucker!
Hands! Let me see your hands!
Get out of the car!
Shut the fuckin' car off!
Get out and eat some dirt!
Get on the fuckin' ground!
All right,
down on the ground!
Eat some fuckin' dirt,
peckerhead!
Get up, fat boy!
OFFICER 1: Come on.
All right, let's go.
OFFICER 2:
You fuckin' like takin'
cop cars, huh?
Get in the car.
Get the fuck in the car!
NEWSCASTER:
Police in Newark were
out in full force today
rounding up
suspected car thieves.
Next time you fuck with me,
I'll blow
your fuckin' head off.
They were trying
to find out
just who it was
that stole
one of their cruisers
the night before last.
(CLAMORING)
Word up, man!
I know my rights!
Yo, I want my
fuckin' lawyer now!
OFFICER:
Down the stairs!
Come on!
MIDGET: I want
my motherfuckin'
phone call
so I can have
my lawyer here!
Listen, let's keep it down.
Let's try to keep it down.
We'll get this over with
quickly as possible.
Don't worry about it.
Listen.
Cooperate with me and
we're out of here a little
sooner than a little later.
All right,
let's start with you.
Can you hurry
this up, man?
What's your name?
Deez.
Deez what?
Deez Nuts, man.
Spelled, N-U-T...
Thank you very much
for your cooperation.
Thank you very much.
You look a little
brighter to me, son.
Let's not play any games.
What's your name?
Yo, Charles.
Charles what?
Charles Manson.
You're a game
player, huh?
That's what you like
to do? Waste time?
If that's all this is,
I can I.D. you in a second.
All it is is a pain in my ass.
Tommy, ring a bell?
They all look
the same to me.
Richie,
he look familiar?
Never seen him.
Why do you want to play it
like that, my friend, huh?
All I did was
ask you your name.
Do you want
to play games?
All right,
we'll play games.
Play my game.
Have a nice day.
Ha-ha.
(OFFICERS LAUGHING)
What's up?
Why you got to fuck...
I want a fuckin' lawyer.
Get the fuck off me!
ROSCOE:
Hey, Sarge,
do me a favor.
Give this to Lenny.
I left it here the other day.
All right.
Oh, listen, Roc.
You may recognize
this package in the back.
Hey, hey!
Look who it is.
My little man.
What's up
with you, man?
What's this?
You've been
tellin' us lies?
Hey,
you have any idea
how much trouble you're in?
Hmm?
I mean, has anyone
come by and told you
how much trouble
you're in, huh?
You gonna tell me,
right?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah,
I'm gonna tell you.
Want some?
(SIGHS)
Come on, man.
Come on.
What's that, man?
That's what that is.
You know
what your problem is?
I'm gonna tell you
what your problem is.
You got nobody
watchin' your back now.
That's your problem.
And that's not good.
Not fuckin' good.
'Cause anything, anything
can happen in this big,
bad motherfuckin' world.
So when people come around
and start asking you
all kinds of questions
about a fuckin' grand jury
and shit like that,
you gotta remember one thing.
And what is that, huh?
What is that one thing?
Come on, tell me.
What is that
one thing, huh?
Sorry,
I didn't hear you.
Fuck you, man.
Keep in touch, kid.
Damn.
Another day in jail?
What?
You spend another night
in that place?
Where you hear that?
I got my connections.
Oh, you do?
I'd like to
think I can find out
when I got a son in jail.
It wasn't that.
They just pack a whole
bunch of us just for show.
Except they added another
court date to your collection.
They told you that?
They sure did.
It don't mean nothin'.
Doesn't mean anything.
Have you kept
your word, Jason?
Have you?
Have you been goin'
to school?
I can't hear you.
Have you?
Look, this is not what I had
in mind for my family, okay?
Yo, what up, girl?
What up, Midget?
What you doin'?
Nothin'.
Yo, I'm on the road,
you know.
Why don't you come
take a ride with me?
With you?
Yeah, with me.
That's right.
What would I look like
ridin' with you?
Why, what's up?
What's up?
I ain't gettin'
in no stolen car...
That ain't no stolen car.
That's my car.
You still think you can lie
to me and tell me anything.
"That ain't no stolen car"?
Boy, please.
Yo, what's up?
I wanna get back up with that.
You know what I'm sayin'?
I know you ain't
sayin' that.
(SIGHS)
I know you ain't
sayin' that.
What are you
talkin' about, Midget?
You know what
I'm talkin' about.
That was
a long time
ago, Kyle.
I like when you say
my name like that.
Well, I'm sorry.
Yeah, all right.
(CAR HORN HONKING)
Yo, what up, what up?
So don't you think
you should go
with your boys?
Nah.
You know,
you're still beautiful,
you know.
You got my heart
whenever you want it.
See you later, Midget.
All right.
Yo, I'm out.
(ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
Get your ass over here,
motherfucker! Yo!
(SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Hold it, hold it, hold it!
Look, Jackie! Jackie!
Man, what you
doin' in here?
What you doin'
in here?
Come on, get out.
Hey, what you doin'?
MAN: You act like it's
my fault she's in here!
Would you mind your
business, please?
Come on, get out.
What, Jack?
Don't get out!
Man, we gonna...
Fuck that nigger!
Come on.
What, Jackie!
What you in here for?
What you doin'?
You not my father, okay?
Why are you stressing out?
I'm not stressing!
You just mad because I got
a better ride than you.
Next time I catch you
in another stolen car,
I'm gonna make it my business.
Come on, just go home. Go!
Yeah, whatever. Don't touch
me when you on the street!
See ya! Take that
thataway, out of here!
Go ahead!
All of you, just go on!
Goddamn!
(ALL JEERING)
Shut the fuck up.
This kid is not walkin' home,
you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, right here...
Yeah, whoa, whoa!
It's that
nigger Roscoe.
Yo, what's up?
Hey, little brother!
What's happening, baby?
Fuck you lookin'
at me for?
How you feelin', man?
I've got five
of 'em down...
Aw, shit.
So, what's up?
You want some of this?
What some of what?
What's that?
You want some of this here?
Yeah, some of this!
MAN: Oh!
(ALL SHOUTING)
(LAUGHING)
Man, what made you do it?
I'm glad you did it!
That was the one!
Yo, I know that shit.
I'm telling you,
he was tryin' to
hit me off!
Yo, I hate those
motherfuckers, man!
Excuse me.
Can I ask you fellows
what you're doin'
over here?
You're drinkin'?
We ain't doin' nothin'.
Oh, shit. We goin' home.
Could you pour it
out for me, please?
I ain't got nothin'.
Shut up. I'm not going
to say it to you again.
Ah, come on, man!
Pour it out.
Don't pour
that shit out!
Fuck her, man!
What did you say?
JAY: I didn't say nothin'.
Listen, you let me
pour this out.
Can I ask you
to repeat yourself?
Listen, I ain't say nothin'.
You want me to drop this?
Would you repeat yourself?
(SIREN WAILING)
What did you say?
You done call backup
on us, huh, bitch?
(GLASS BREAKING)
(SIREN WAILING)
Grab him!
(CRASHING)
MIDGET: Oh, shit!
(SCUFFLING)
(COUGHING)
Somebody lose this?
(CHUCKLING)
Hey!
Save anything
for me?
(GROANING)
(SIGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
(GLASS RATTLING)
Shit.
Ah.
Oh.
What's up?
What's goin' on?
You all right?
Yeah.
JAY: So, we fuckin'
left them niggers.
We was elegant!
You all sit there
for five minutes.
That shit was
five seconds long.
Hey, son,
what you gonna do
with that, son?
Yo, I'm sayin'...
The track stage
is right there.
(CONTINUES
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(GUN FIRING)
Shit! What you doin'?
P-NUT: What's wrong
with this kid?
(ALL CLAMORING)
You're crazy, man!
You are trigger-happy!
(CONTINUES
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Yo, put that
gun away, man.
It ain't gonna
bite ya, man. Chill.
You put that
shit away, man.
You know
shootin' at cops...
Shooting at cops
ain't all good.
It ain't all good.
That shit ain't
no thing, man.
I'll be right back.
(MACHINERY WHIRRING)
(WOMAN SPEAKING OVER PA)
Yo, my man!
Why you bring
that car in here?
The what?
Did I tell ya not to come
on my property with no rides
unless you call me first?
Your phone was busy,
all right?
Did I tell you that?
Don't put your
hands on me, man.
Excuse me! Excuse me!
I don't need any
fools on my property!
Can you understand that?
You say you have
something for me, though.
No, wrong! You told me
you had something for me,
okay?
You wanna do yourself a favor?
You wanna do me a favor?
Go and get me something
to look at.
Don't be bringing no shit...
That shit looked...
Don't bring no shit-box
you're usin' for joyrides.
I don't need them.
Okay?
Now go on the street
and earn some money.
Yeah, fuck you!
Do what I tell ya!
Earn it for a change!
We in it?
We in there, son.
You're sure we in it?
What I say, man?
We in there.
We got the money.
Yo, we in there, man!
We hook?
Yeah, we hook.
JAY: How long to wait?
All right, man.
Yo, where we at, man?
What's up?
Yo, chill, chill, chill!
Let's go home, man!
I wanna wear something.
I'm riding on damn tires!
Yo, what?
You see that,
right there?
MIDGET: You're dead!
JAY: What you
talking about,
that Lexus?
What are you gonna
do with that, kid?
Hey, man,
leave him!
Let's follow
this guy.
What about?
No, I'm takin' that shit.
What the fuck
are you doin'?
Yo, I'm takin'
that shit, Jason.
What? What the fuck you...
My man, let's talk
for a minute! Yo, yo!
Come here!
Fuckin' dumb!
MIDGET: Don't fuck with me!
Get the fuck out of here!
MAN 1: Hey! Come on!
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
MAN 2:
He's stealing his car!
Okay, okay.
Shit!
(MIDGET WHOOPING)
Shit, what the fuck
are you doin'?
Man, what you doin'?
You piece of shit, come here!
Come here! God damn it!
Son of a bitch!
(TIRES SQUEALING)
Yo, Grammy, close this
up like this, you know?
You don't wanna
catch a cold.
Can't have you
leaving me, too,
you know
what I'm sayin'?
Let me get this.
Here, eat your carrots.
Go ahead, go ahead,
go ahead.
Take some more.
What's up, man?
Yo, what's up,
man?
Yo, where
you been at?
Why you fuckin'
with me, man?
Watch your mouth!
Can't you see
what I'm doin' here?
What you think?
Just tell me what
you was thinkin', man.
Yo.
I told you
I was gonna make
my move, all right?
I'm sayin', you was gonna
just leave me out there?
What's in your head?
I did what I had to do.
I got bills to pay.
Oh, you did
what you had to do.
Yo, I told you
I was gonna
make a move,
so I did what
I had to do!
I got bills, kid!
I'm your right-hand man.
This is me, man!
You ain't tell me nothin'!
No, I ain't waitin' around
for you to catch up with me.
You know
what I'm sayin'?
You playin' me, man!
All right!
All right.
Yo, man, I hope you got
your money's worth.
Boy, I hope you got
You know I did,
motherfucker.
Excuse me, Grandma.
Eat that right there.
Eat your carrots.
(ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Just 'cause your man
is trying to get between
his homies and all that...
What a bod.
...a party!
What, I met this guy
with a BMW, named Sean.
Girlfriend,
he was too fine!
What! I know...
Can I talk
to you for a minute?
Talk for a minute.
(CONTINUES SPEAKING)
Come on, stop playin'.
Can I speak to you?
You're pulling
on my clothes!
I asked you
not to come here.
You're embarrassing me!
Why are you here?
'Cause I'm chillin'
with my friends,
is that all right?
You know how Mommy is,
and you're blowing
the spot up.
I know how Mommy is,
and she ain't sayin' nothing!
You blowin' the spot up!
You got to stop this.
I'm doin' this shit
for you!
You know what...
Come here,
you're gonna go home!
What's up, my own?
I asked you not to deal
with my sister, man!
Just chill!
Yo, man, chill out!
Chill out, man!
I'm telling you.
Why you in my business, man?
This ain't no
business of yours!
(CROWD CLAMORING)
Get the fuck out
of my face!
(BOTH ARGUING)
JACKIE: No, shut up!
Mind your business!
JACKIE: Yo! What the...
Get off of...
Jason! Jason!
(CROWD SHOUTING)
JACKIE: Jason!
Big fuckin' mistake!
(BOTH ARGUING)
Guys!
207!
Afternoon, ma'am.
My name's Lieutenant Roscoe.
How are you?
Fine.
Would you mind if I ask
you a couple questions?
Why?
Would you mind telling us
what your last name is?
Petty.
Petty. Are you
Jason Petty's mom?
Yeah!
Does he live
here with you?
Yeah, he lives here.
Is he here now?
No, he's not here now.
We just have a couple
questions for him.
Uh-huh.
He's from around the way,
you know what I'm sayin'?
You want me to let 'em
bring it to me?
Nah, but I got to
smooth that shit
out now.
You ain't
got to do that.
Nah, I do.
Don't do that.
I'm telling you.
I told you that nigger
my people, kid!
Fuck these niggers, man!
Straight up and down!
All right.
What's the matter
with you?
What you talkin' about?
Oh, you're gonna stand
in my face and lie to me?
They came to my damn house.
What you talking about?
You know what
they gonna do to you?
They gonna lock
your nigger ass up
and throw away the key!
Why are you blowin'
up the spot?
Shut up!
Oh!
What the hell you laughing at,
with your bald-headed ass?
Through with you!
Why you coming down
here blowin' the spot up?
(LAUGHING)
Oh, shit!
God!
Yo, your moms is crazy...
Why you laughing
at my moms?
Nah, I'm not
laughing at your moms.
Why you laughing at my moms?
I'm not laughing at
your moms, I'm saying!
(LAUGHING)
Oh, she need to get
her oil checked!
I'm tellin' you,
this shit's gonna work.
Oh, shit.
Hey, you!
Come over here!
I ain't going
over there, man!
Yo, I live here. What's up?
I ain't going nowhere!
JAY: It was starting
to feel like the walls
was closin' in on me.
You keep running forever,
you run out of places to go.
Yo, Jason!
Let me talk to you
for a second, man.
Come here.
I wanna talk to you!
(CAR ALARM BEEPING)
(GUN FIRING)
(COUGHING)
(PANTING)
P-NUT: Fuck that shit.
Yo, clean.
I'm saying, what's up?
You're gonna pop
the nigger, right?
I hope so,
'cause yo, he did try
to decapitate your ass!
(MIDGET LAUGHING)
Fuck you.
I got this.
My man was, like...
(MIMICS GUN FIRING)
He almost took
your ass out.
What the fuck you
laughing at, man?
That shit funny to you,
right? Shit funny.
I ain't...
(LAUGHING)
I ain't laughing!
He almost had you!
Motherfucker.
You tryin' to
trip on me, man?
Oh, yeah...
Fuck you, man!
What's up? Why you
got to take it there?
I can take it
where the fuck
I wanna take it.
Bouncing on me in
the parking lot
and all that shit!
That ain't got
nothing to do with it!
That's my problem
with you!
Now you're tryin'
to instigate some
Ritchie shit, man?
If that's what you want,
let's go get it, man!
Let's bring it
to this nigger, man!
That's what you want!
Fuck it, man,
let's go make it
real for this nigger.
Come on, man, I'm out there
dodging bullets and all
this shit, man, you jokin'?
(SCOFFS) Some crap
friends, man!
Crap friends.
(ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(LAUGHING)
That shit is cream.
That is a phat ride.
Right, Clean?
MIDGET: Yo, we gonna
make mad loot off of
this motherfucker.
P-NUT: Fuck the dough,
nigger. We keepin'
this motherfucker.
Come on, yo!
Are we coming here, man?
We coming here for this shit?
Will you shut up?
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
Fuck you, man!
I got shit on my mind,
and you come here
for this shit!
Come on,
come on, come on!
Don't rush me, man!
(ALARM CONTINUES)
(SCOFFS)
Motherfuckers
is crazy, man.
I got this!
One more!
Come on!
(ALARM CONTINUES BLARING)
(INDISTINCT SPEECH OVER RADIO)
OFFICER: Look at 'em,
look at 'em, look at 'em.
Just like fuckin'
candy over there, huh?
Fuckin' mutts.
MIDGET: Come on,
hurry up, man!
Just move out
of my fuckin' face,
'cause I'm about
to get this shit!
Come on, man!
Chill, motherfucker!
(GARBAGE CANS RATTLING)
(ALARM STOPS)
(INDISTINCT SPEECH OVER RADIO)
OFFICER 1:
Hey, don't fuckin' move!
OFFICER 2: Freeze!
(OFFICERS SHOUTING)
Get out of the car!
Out of the car! Hey!
Don't fuckin' move, asshole!
Don't even fuckin'
think about it, you hear me?
(SIREN WAILING)
Freeze! Freeze!
OFFICER 1:
He's gettin' away!
Get your fuckin'
hand back!
Put it down!
OFFICER 2:
Move it! Move it!
(GUN FIRING)
OFFICER 1:
Hold your fire!
Turn around!
Turn around and get
the fuck on the car!
Turn the fuck around!
Get up against here.
You like runnin'
over cops, you fuck?
You're goin' away!
You hear me,
motherfucker? Away!
You tell
all your little friends
what happens to people
who like to run over
fuckin' cops!
(SIREN CHIRPS)
Hey, my man.
You're out of luck
this time.
I got you cold.
You look good on video,
you know that, kid?
(LAUGHING)
(SIREN APPROACHES)
NEWS ANNOUNCER:
Outrage in Newark tonight,
as angry residents
took to the streets
after a 16-year-old
suspected car thief
was shot and
killed by police.
This after he allegedly
tried to run down
an officer in a stolen car.
After news of
the shooting spread,
angry residents
overturned cars,
and showered the cops
with rocks and bottles...
(CROWD CLAMORING)
(GATE UNLOCKING)
How you doin', Bill?
Hey, Brian.
How's the kid?
Great.
(GATE LOCKING)
JAY: That's how
they got me.
It was the one time
I didn't run.
I just got
tired of runnin'.
Somethin' had to change.
So be it.
I'll take the time
they gave me.
I can handle it.
(INMATES SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
What's up?
What's up, kid?
What's up, nigger?
What's up?
You didn't hear
about your man?
What man?
What you talking about?
Your man, Midget.
Fuck you talking about?
It's like you ain't
hearing me.
You deaf,
motherfucker?
You trying to bring it
to me or something, man?
What's up?
What you want, nigger?
You better say good-bye
to your man, Midget.
All right.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
RENE: You doin' okay?
JAY: I'm doin' all right.
You know,
I was wondering when
I'd be taking this drive.
We could've talked
over the phone,
but, it's kinda hard
to get to the phone.
(LAUGHING)
Yeah, I bet.
I don't mind
driving up here.
You're not gonna get
rid of me that easy.
Yeah.
You brought me
something?
What, I'm not enough?
Come on, Ma,
I know you brought me
something.
You do?
(CHUCKLING)
Wait, let me
get this straight.
I'm supposed to go
shopping for you now?
It is funny, isn't it?
You the one in jail!
Well, I'll be out of here
in a little while. Okay?
I know.
Then what?
Then what? I don't know.
School, I suppose.
I don't know.
But then
after that, what?
Look, we'll find you
something, okay?
I hope so. It ain't
nothin' out there.
You know, I...
Come on,
don't talk like that.
There's nothin'
out there, Mom.
What's all the more,
I just feel...
I feel terrible. I mean...
(SIGHING) I feel like
I let you down.
I disappointed you.
No, no, you didn't
let me down.
This thing with Lionel...
You didn't let me down!
I know I did, Mom.
We gonna make it.
I don't care
what it look like,
we gonna make it.
You hear me?
You be strong.
Be strong, okay?
GUARD: Time's up, Petty.
I love you.
We got to go, Mom.
I'll be back
really soon, okay?
(WHISPERING)
I love you.
I love you too.
GUARD:
Petty, time's up.
Let's go.
All right, come on.
Callin' us.
I know.
NEWS ANNOUNCER:
In Newark today,
investigators are hoping
to uncover some more
clues in the shooting
of 17-year-old
Ronald Lambs.
He was allegedly shot
by police a month ago,
here in Newark.
At 9:00 this morning,
the first witnesses
were brought in
to testify
before a grand jury.
JAY: Ronnie was
still in the hospital
when they finally
brought me in on
that grand jury.
So much has happened
since then,
it was like talking
about ancient history.
No way could you
bring any of it back.
There has been
lots of speculation
since 17-year-old
Ronald Lambs was
shot last month.
He was critically wounded
here in Newark after
stepping out of a stolen car
that apparently belonged
to one of the officers
involved in the shooting.
Oh, ow! That's that beast
that bagged me, man!
Check this nigger!
MAN: That's the nigger
that bagged me, too!
The officer has admitted
that there was some
wrongdoing on his part.
He has admitted that
he was not correct...
Shit in the barrel, boy!
You're comin' home, boy!
The officers involved
have been suspended
from duty pending
an investigation.
And one officer,
Emil Roscoe
of Glen Ridge,
is now facing
criminal charges.
Aw, it's the bomb, son!
Faggot motherfucker!
(LAUGHING)
I missed you!
Man, how you doin'?
Oh, I'm so glad
to see you!
I missed you!
You look good, man!
You look good!
Look at you! You got
your weight up in there.
I been filling out.
You're so stupid!
If you wouldn't have been
in in the first place!
You shouldn't
have been there!
Aw, man!
You gonna take me
to see Midget?
You know,
he's up there on Avon.
He didn't even come
see me once
in that joint. Once!
I know you wasn't
looking for that
nigger to come up there.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
It's like, "Bam, bam!"
I hit that
motherfucker, yo!
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
What's up, man?
Where you been at, yo?
I been waiting
for you, kid!
Hey, you couldn't
come see me
up in the piece?
Come on, man! Yo,
why I wanna come see
you up in there, man?
You know that shit depress
the hell out of me, yo!
You're my right-hand man!
You're gonna leave me to rot?
Yo, come on, man!
What's up?
Not even once, man!
Yo, come on, man! Yo!
Yo, so how you do
up in there, son?
You do all right?
Did all right.
You know, represented.
But, yo, I heard
shit was crazy out
here altogether.
Shoot, it's been hectic
up around here, yo.
They been lockin'
everybody up
in the small bunk.
Ever since that night that
they took out P-Nut, man...
Shit's been
getting real, yo.
Shit crazy?
Yeah. Yeah, I know.
Yeah, I know how that is.
I know how that flow.
Yo, they still ain't
figured out a way
to catch your man!
You know what
I'm saying?
MAN: Let's go, yo!
Yo, I'm gonna get up
with these kids, man.
It's time
you started thinking
about what you gonna do!
You know
what I'm saying?
MAN: Come on, man,
let's go!
(HORN HONKING)
I been thinking about that
for the past three months.
You don't need to be
around here, man.
You got a big old life
to lead, you know?
Fuckin' activity.
Man, let's go!
You gonna get
with them, or what?
Yeah, I'm gonna get up
with them, yo.
(HORN HONKING)
We gonna be at the park.
What you gonna do?
I might roll through.
Well, get up later, man!
Come on, man!
Man, let's go!
All right, man.
Yo, hold up, man!
Stay real, kid!
(SIGHS)
Coreen, I been thinkin'.
I been away
for a little while,
like 90 days!
I'm sayin', what you been
doin' while I was gone?
You know what I been doin'
all the time you been
talkin' to me. You know.
I'm sayin', what do you
think of our friendship?
What do you mean,
"our friendship?"
Bitch, get out the car!
Get out the car, nigger!
You think I'm bullshitting?
Get out of the car!
Get out!
Yeah, nigger,
I should clap your ass!
MAN 2: Get your ass
up out the car!
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
COREEN:
The fuckin' car!
Shit! No!
Don't fuck with me!
That's my mother's car!
Damn!
COREEN: Jason, I knew
I shouldn't have...
What happened?
Fuck you, Jason!
I shouldn't have never went
with you in the first place!
What happened?
They jacked
the shit, right?
(ALL ARGUING)
That was my mother's car!
Let's go get that shit!
Fuck you, Midget!
I don't need your help!
Fuck it, I ain't even
gonna try to help you!
(SIREN WAILING)
Let's go get that shit!
What you doin', man?
Yo, what's up, man?
What you gonna do?
Do about what?
Just chill!
You mind your
fuckin' business!
Go with me, man!
Don't go there!
Don't go there, man!
Oh, you got your hand
in my face now, right?
Just chill!
You got something
to say to me?
Say it to me! What?
What? What, man?
Good, I like that.
Good to see you there, son!
Pardon me, Coreen.
My bad.
All right. Yo.
Welcome home, black.
I'm out.
Leave me alone!
Leave me alone.
All of you,
just leave me alone!
(ENGINE STARTING)
Welcome home!
MAN: Yo, man,
why don't you turn
the radio on, nigger?
Fuck the radio.
Some fuckin' sounds
or somethin', man!
Check this, check this.
(LOUD RAP MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALL LAUGHING EXCITEDLY)
(ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
MAN: You all bad, yeah!
(POLICE SIREN WAILING)
I can show you
how to escape
the motherfuckers!
(CAR ACCELERATING)
(ALL SHOUTING)
(INDISTINCT SPEECH OVER RADIO)
NEWS REPORTER:
In the news tonight,
a high-speed chase
from Newark to Hill Vale,
New Jersey, turned deadly
after police opened fire
on a stolen van filled
mostly with teenagers.
The chase began in Newark
after police
officers spotted a van,
which had been stolen
at gunpoint a day earlier.
The van took off
at high speed.
Newark police followed it
to Hill Vale.
At a bridge on
North Brown Street,
a police car blocked
the van's path,
but the driver
did not stop.
What happened next
is unclear.
Police won't give details
until their investigation
is complete,
but they say
some 30 shots were
fired at the van.
When it was over,
two people were dead,
and three others had
been hit by gunfire.
One of the dead was
a pregnant teenage girl.
In all, six people
were in the van.
Police also say they found
a starter's pistol
on the floor of the van.
It was not, however,
the weapon used
when the van was stolen.
Police are preparing
a long list
of charges now.
POLICE OFFICER: At this point,
I guess some of them will be
armed robbery,
conspiracy to
commit robbery,
auto theft,
aggravated assault
on police officers,
eluding police
and resisting arrest.
What's up?
What's up, nigger?
(LAUGHING)
JAY: I guess
the house
is quiet now.
And up and down the block,
you don't see anybody anymore.
It's almost like
we were never there.
We was just tryin'
to make our mark
in the world,
find something
we can call our own.
And if
I've changed at all,
it's only because
I've seen too much.
It's only because my life
can't go back the way it was.
Even if
I want it to.
There's no goin' back.
I can't forget
New Jersey
Don't let no one
get close to you
except the chosen few
Stick with the ones
who meant the most to you
when you were broke and blue
That's how a fan do
That's how you stay
True around the snakes
that freakin' smile
when they hate you
I'm quick to take a ride
down far in town
Just another day
living on the dime
My experience legit
my rhyme is on hit
It's mad truth to the rumor
we the shit I can't forget
I can't forget
New Jersey
I used to work
at Burger King
but after takin' orders
I used to take the path
to Latin quarters
cross the waters
When I learned to do the wop
yo, I couldn't stop
I brought it back
around the way to show
the people on my block
Teacher, teacher
tell me how you do it
It looks so simple
like there is nothin' to it
So we meet in Irvington
Hi Ho's and after school
I'd run
To the Willowbrook
Mall boostin' with Sulamun
I had a talent
for gettin' up a gear
Petty thief
small-time crook
of the year
But I chilled 'cause I had
bigger dreams than to steal
And Ramsey came for me
and Patchy to put
our voices on a reel
And now I could
hear myself
on the radio
45 King Special
Red Alert Show
'Cause that's what
life was all about to me
All E.E. flavor unit
representin' Jersey
I can't forget
New Jersey
I think about my moms
and my brothers
when I'm on swole
Shakim
My baby sister
when I'm on swole
Holsted
Illtown
when I'm on swole
Chilltown J.C.
Irvington, Newark and so on
when I'm on swole
Recognize the home
of my soul
Hey, we got Naughty,
the Lords, we got Nicki
We got Redman,
the Artifacts,
and Whitney
Bon Jovi,
they're my homies
Bruce Springsteen
and Das EFX
Shaquille O'Neal
oh, he'll catch rack, huh
Tisha Campbell
Jerry Lewis, Tony Bennett
Back spin, we'll spin it
Thursday peppermint I'm in it
Shadows
I knows no foes
in the spot
'Cause them
peeps is my peeps
and my back is got
'Nuff respect
to your borough
your block, ya black
I love to see ya
smooth as a flock
Unstrapped
against each other
no body armor
Nobody harms
a hair on a head
everything's calmer
And we cool
the ghetto stars and fools
We paid the dues
we made the blues
So come on with the,
come on
get down with the
Get down, I'm down
with my hometown sounds
I can't forget
New Jersey