You're 40 minutes late
What's her story?
I don't know.
She came from up in New England somewhere.
Some witch trial protector of women nonsense.
Was it late 1600s?
Do I look like a curator? Check the file.
Make sure you lock up when you're done.
[Quiet, distant screams.]
And if you even think that you can just waltz in here tomorrow-
Okay. See you then,
[Door closes.]
You're a beauty, aren't you?
Ow.
[Inessa Gasps.]
Goddamnit, Inessa.
Please Ted, what are you doing back?
Do you have any idea how expensive this stuff is?
I can explain-.
That's the problem with you.
Even if you knew how expensive it was, I don't think you'd give a shit.
Relax, Ted. Check your attitude.
What?
What did you just say?
Check my attitude?
Oh, that's rich. That's real rich coming from you.
Look. I don't know what you did to defile yourself, to permanently put yourself in
Mr. Granville's good graces, but I am your direct supervisor, and I have had enough!
You don't respect my authority, you don't respect my time, and you certainly don't respect my equipment!
I'll be damned if you aren't gonna respect me enough to look me in the eye when I fire your ass!
What?!
[Rock shifting, sound of breathing from the statue.]
[Soft breathing from the statue, Inessa panting.]
[Distant voice speaking indiscernible words.]
[Wind howling.]
Rebecca.
Leave me alone Tim.
You're hurt.
I'm fine. Just please leave me alone. I don't need this today.
You're not as alone as you think.
Come to worship to Sunday. You'll find that no situation is beyond God's reach.
Is that right?
So tell me, where was he last night around 11:30? Maybe could have used some help then.
If you feel that God is ignoring you then perhaps you should spend some more time on your knees.
No class again this week?
It's okay. Let me see.
[Sigh.]
He was drunk.
I shouldn't have pushed it. It's my fault.
Rebecca, look at me
This is not your fault. Don't ever let me hear you say that again.
I don't know what to do.
Pack your things. You're coming with me.
What are we doing here?
There's something I want to show you.
Come on.
Follow me.
Watch your step.
Watch your head.
What is this place?
My sister used to bring me here when I was about your age.
She used to work in a museum.
she discovered something amazing before she died.
I've tried to keep it safe for her.
Until I find the right person to give it to.
Give what?
What is that?
(Distorted voice.) A power.
[Discordant sounds, indistinct yelling.]
(Same distorted voice) To fight men like him.
Come to me.
[Rebecca gasps.]
[Grunting in discomfort.]
[Tim whistles.]
Goddamnit Tim, just leave me alone.
You sick?
Stop following me.
Come on. Sit up.
No. [Rebecca slaps Tim.]
Why is it so difficult to make you people understand?
[Muffled cries. Tim shushing.]
You know, someone really should have taught you some manners.
On your knees
[Bone snaps, Tim cries out in pain.]
Please. Please please don't, Rebecca.
Six atom, Dispatch, repeat last? Some kind of interference.
[Radio static] We have a-
[Cut off by static.]
[Crow sound, followed by a thud.]
What the hell?
Hey!
Hey, wait! Come here, hey!
Hello?
It's okay, don't be afraid. I'm a police officer.
[Door creaking, then clicking shut.]
[Sudden radio interference. Indistinct words over radio.]
Hey! Wait!
Stop!
Hey!
[Girl screams.]
[Continued screams.]
(Distant voices.) Answer me!
I'm sorry!
Where are you?
Come out!
[Girl screams.]
Where are you?
[Sounds of whipping.] I'm sorry! Stop! Please, Daddy!
Don't you talk back to me! (Said between strikes.)
What the fuck?
Look familiar?
Rebecca?
Baby, what are you doing here?
I'm here to give you a message.
What are you talking about?
What's going on?
I want to tell you that it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter,
how many criminals you catch.
It doesn't matter that you pretend to quit drinking.
That you get to dress up,
and play hero.
You see, deep down I know who you really are.
Alright, Rebecca whatever this is, this is over.
You and I are going home you understand me?
No.
I'm not afraid of you anymore.
Rebecca.
Rebecca! Come here.
Re- ...Rebecca?
Rebecca.
Who is that behind you?
I hated you.
So much.
Rebecca, who is that?
[Bones snapping.]
You can only beat a dog so many times before it learns to bite.
[Rebecca screams.]
Watch new scary vids every Tuesday, Thursday, and Friday.