MRS. CHRISTIE DAWSON?
YES, UH, MRS. DAWSON WOULD
BE IN HER CHEMISTRY CLASS.
IT'S 306.
[ KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
MORNING.
GOOD MORNING.
WE'RE LOOKING
FOR JOSHUA GAINES.
I'M JOSH.
FOLLOW US, PLEASE.
WHAT?
NOW.
[ CLASS MURMURING ]
ONCE YOU BALANCE
THE EQUATION,
OXIDATION REDUCTION
IS A NO-BRAINER.
[ KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
ONE MOMENT.
FINALLY.
YOU NEED ME FOR MORE
QUESTIONING?
CAN YOU JUST GIVE ME
15 MORE MINUTES?
I'M SORRY.
IT CAN'T WAIT.
OKAY, I WANT YOU TO
BALANCE THAT EQUATION.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ BELL RINGING ]
[ ALARM CLOCK BUZZING ]
[ GROANS ]
FINISH YOUR
PAPERS, TEACH?
BUSTED!
WHAT WAS THAT SOUND?
AH, OUR SUBTLE
ALARM CLOCK.
NO. THAT AGONIZING SQUEAK.
MY FELT-TIP PEN?
MENTAL CRUELTY.
OH, ONE MORE.
ONE MORE AND I'M YOURS.
OKAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
ONLY CHRISTIE DAWSON
COULD MAKE
MARKING CHEMISTRY TESTS
LOOK SEXY.
♪ THROUGH YOUR EYES
I SEE A WORLD ♪
♪ OF INNOCENCE AND GRACE ♪
♪ AND ALL THE MYSTERIES
OF YOUR SOUL ♪
♪ ARE MIRRORED IN YOUR FACE ♪
♪ I SEE A LIGHT SO CLEARLY ♪
♪ WHERE IT COMES FROM,
I DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ I'LL NEVER KNOW ♪
♪ MY LOVE ♪
♪ I'LL NEVER NEED TO KNOW ♪
WE NEED TO BE MORE CAREFUL
ABOUT GETTING PREGNANT.
WE SHOULD BE
LESS CAREFUL.
IT'S JUST THE TIMING.
CHRISTIE, CHRISTIE,
THERE'S GONNA BE --
OKAY, NO SERIOUS
TALK BEFORE COFFEE.
WHAT IS THAT, IS THAT
GROUNDS FOR DIVORCE?
DON'T TEMPT ME.
AH!
AH AH AH.
OW!
SO ARE WE GONNA WAIT
10 YEARS TO HAVE A KID?
OH, THIS THING
IS LEAKING AGAIN.
YOU CAN'T AVOID HAVING THIS
CONVERSATION FOREVER, CHRISTIE.
I CAN'T TAKE
A MATERNITY LEAVE NOW.
DOESN'T YOUR UNION
COVER STUFF LIKE THAT?
I'M JUST STARTING OUT.
IT'S MY FIRST YEAR.
I LOVE MY JOB!
YOU ALREADY HAVE A JOB,
YOU'RE A DOCTOR'S WIFE.
ISN'T THAT
EVERY WOMAN'S DREAM?
ABOUT THAT DIVORCE...
[ LAUGHS ]
♪ WHO CAN TAKE YOUR PLACE ♪
BYE, MOM!
♪ I'VE SEEN IT ALL
AND IT'S NEVER ENOUGH ♪
IS THAT LIFEHOUSE?
YEAH, IT'S "TAKE ME AWAY."
I LOVE THAT CD.
DO YOU HAVE IT?
NO.
I'LL SEE YOU IN CLASS.
OKAY.
♪ TAKE ME AWAY ♪
♪ I'VE GOT NOTHING LEFT TO SAY ♪
♪ JUST TAKE ME AWAY ♪
OH, HI!
HOW ARE YOU?
GREAT BOOTS!
YOU COULD KILL
SOMEBODY IN THOSE.
AREN'T YOUR FEET
GONNA HURT?
WE'LL SEE.
HOW'S JUSTIN'S
BRONCHITIS?
OH, ALL BETTER NOW.
IT'S JUST A GOOD EXCUSE
FOR HIM TO SKIP SCHOOL.
HEY, MS. DAWSON.
HEY, JOSH.
THERE'S TWO FUTURE MEMBERS
OF THE UNWED PARENTS CLUB.
[ LAUGHING ]
NO, I'M SERIOUS,
I MEAN,
IT'S LIKE A SIMMERING
CROCK-POT OF HORMONES
AROUND HERE.
WHAT ARE THESE
GIRLS THINKING?
DO THEY WANT
TO GET PREGNANT?
COME ON, YOU REMEMBER
THAT AGE, DON'T YOU?
OH, AROUND HERE?
ONLY ABOUT
1,200 TIMES A DAY.
I'LL CATCH YOU LATER.
YEAH.
HEY! WHERE DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE GOING?
OH, MRS. DAWSON, I'M SORRY.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE A STUDENT.
HAVE A GOOD DAY,
MR. FISKE!
THANK YOU, YOU TOO.
YEP.
MAKE SURE YOU NOTE THE DECREASE
IN THE MASS OF COPPER OXIDE.
THIS LAB IS 10% OF YOUR MIDTERM,
SO TAKE YOUR TIME.
YOU CAN DO IT.
IT'S NOT AS HARD
AS IT LOOKS, OKAY?
REMEMBER TO MEASURE
THE MASS BEFORE AND AFTER.
HEY.
TURN IT UP.
JOSH, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING?
AH!
GREAT!
THAT WAS OUR MIDTERM, JOSH!
IT'S OKAY, EVERYONE!
DON'T WORRY, JUST DO NOT
REMOVE YOUR BURNERS.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THE ONE THING NOT TO DO
IS REMOVE HEAT
DURING THE TRANSFER.
I KNEW THAT.
IT WAS HIM, I SWEAR.
OKAY.
GOOD JOB, GUYS.
JOSH.
DID YOU STUDY?
YES!
MS. DAWSON,
I GOT TO DROP CHEMISTRY.
IT'S KILLING MY AVERAGE.
WE'VE BEEN
OVER THIS ALREADY.
HE KNEW THE DEADLINE
FOR DROPPING THE CLASS.
YOU'RE NEW TO THE SCHOOL,
MRS. DAWSON.
OUR SON'S BEEN ON THE HONOR
ROLL HERE FOR 3 YEARS.
LIZ...
WHY DON'T YOU
LET ME HANDLE THIS?
SHE'S RUINING HIS RECORD.
SHE'S TREATING CHEMISTRY
LIKE A COLLEGE-LEVEL COURSE.
AND IT WOULD BE SUCH A SMALL
EXCEPTION TO MAKE, MS. DAVIS.
I'M SORRY, I SEE
NO GROUNDS HERE.
AND IT'S NOT FAIR
TO THE OTHER STUDENTS.
MAYBE JOSH NEEDS TO CUT
SOME EXTRACURRICULAR
ACTIVITIES.
THEY'RE VERY IMPORTANT TO HIM.
HE'S NOT ABOUT TO CHANGE HIS
LIFE COMPLETELY TO SUIT YOU.
DAD.
WHAT, JOSH?
OKAY, I THINK
OUR BEST OPTION HERE
IS FOR JOSH TO
ACTUALLY PASS CHEMISTRY.
SO HOW ABOUT SOME
AFTERSCHOOL TUTORING?
ARE YOU GAME FOR THAT?
TOTALLY.
MR. AND MRS. GAINES?
AH, THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
AS LONG AS HE PASSES.
MS. DAWSON!
SORRY ABOUT MY DAD,
AND THANKS FOR SAVING MY ASS.
HEY!
LANGUAGE.
SO WHEN DO WE START?
TODAY?
AFTER CLASS, TOMORROW.
AND NOW YOU GOTTA DO
YOUR PART AND WORK HARD.
YOU'RE ON.
MS. DAWSON?
CAN I OFFER YOU
LIKE A, I DON'T KNOW,
A TRIPLE CHEESEBURGER
AT THE HAVEN
INSTEAD OF THIS JUNK?
TO SAY THANKS.
WELL, THAT'S A BRIBE,
AND YOU CAN'T BUY YOUR WAY
INTO PASSING CHEMISTRY.
AND TEACHERS DON'T DO
31 GRAMS OF FAT.
IT IS NOT A BRIBE, JUST
A PURE AND SIMPLE THANK YOU.
COME ON, I GOT A COUPLE
QUESTIONS ABOUT IONIC SOLUTIONS.
IT'D REALLY HELP ME OUT.
VEGGIE BURGER?
LET'S GO.
LOOK, IF YOU KNEW
MY DAD, YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
IF I DON'T GET
INTO BUSINESS SCHOOL
AT AN IVY LEAGUE
COLLEGE LIKE HE DID...
HE PUTS A LOT OF PRESSURE
ON YOU, HUH?
YEAH.
PLUS I FEEL BAD.
I MEAN, I'M TAKING UP
YOUR PERSONAL TIME
'CAUSE I'M AN IDIOT
AND CAN'T GET CHEMISTRY.
NO, JOSH.
JOSH, DON'T PANIC, OKAY?
A LOT OF PEOPLE BLOCK
ON CHEMISTRY LIKE YOU.
JUST KEEP WORKING AT IT.
YOU'VE GOT THE BRAINS FOR IT
AND I'LL HELP YOU.
IF I DIDN'T WANT TO DO THIS,
I WOULDN'T HAVE MADE THE OFFER.
REALLY?
ABSOLUTELY.
SO YOU ACTUALLY
LIKE CHEMISTRY?
YEAH!
IT'S REALLY HARD AND I'M
GOOD AT IT, SO...
YEAH, WELL, I GUESS
SOMEONE HAS TO BE.
SOUNDS LIKE MY HUSBAND.
YOU MEAN HE'S NOT
A CHEMISTRY TEACHER?
NO, NO.
HE'S A DOCTOR.
I ACTUALLY WORKED
FOR A FEW YEARS
BEFORE GOING TO
TEACHER'S COLLEGE
TO HELP PUT HIM
THROUGH MEDICAL SCHOOL.
WOW!
YOU MEAN,
YOU SUPPORTED HIM?
YEAH, WELCOME TO
THE NEW MILLENNIUM, JOSH.
YOUR MOTHER DOESN'T WORK
OUTSIDE THE HOUSE?
WELL, PART-TIME.
BUT SHE MAINLY STAYS HOME.
CHECK!
I MEAN, YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE DIFFERENT.
NOT TOO MANY PEOPLE WHO LOOK
LIKE YOU ARE SCIENCE GENIUSES.
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO OFFEND YOU.
I MEAN, YOU'RE
A GREAT CHEM TEACHER.
IT'S JUST, YOU'RE
ALSO LIKE A...
BABE.
SO ATTRACTIVE
WOMEN ARE STUPID?
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID.
I GUESS I JUST NEVER
MET ANYONE LIKE YOU.
JOSH, LET'S JUST STICK
TO THE WORK, OKAY?
I GOTTA GO.
OH, UM, 3:00 P.M.
TOMORROW.
MY HOMEROOM.
DON'T BE LATE.
SURE.
HYDROGEN BONDS ARE POLAR
WHEN HYDROGEN BONDS
WITH OXYGEN.
BUT WHAT HAPPENS
TO THE HYDROGEN NUCLEUS?
IT'S SHORT
OF ELECTRONS?
YES!
YES, LIKE WATER, H2O.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND IT NOW?
ALL RIGHT, I THINK I GET IT.
BUT COULD I DO IT ON MY OWN?
I BET YOU COULD.
NO!
ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S IT FOR TODAY.
I'LL SEE YOU WEDNESDAY.
VEGGIE BURGER?
UH, NO THANKS.
THAT WAS A ONE-TIME DEAL.
SURE, OKAY.
I JUST THOUGHT MAYBE
BEING THE WIFE OF A DOCTOR,
YOU MIGHT --
WHOA, WHOA!
JOSH, OUR CONVERSATION GOT
A LITTLE BIT PERSONAL YESTERDAY,
SO LET'S NOT PURSUE
THAT ANY FURTHER.
SORRY.
NO OFFENSE MEANT.
I JUST THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU GUYS ARE SO BUSY
YOU DON'T GET OUT MUCH.
LOOK, YOU'RE SWEET,
BUT I'M DOING YOU
A REALLY BIG FAVOR HERE,
SO DON'T BLOW IT, OKAY?
HEY.
YOU WANNA HANG OUT?
I GOT TOO MUCH HOMEWORK.
NO, YOU DON'T.
OKAY.
YOU WANT TO WORK
AT MY PLACE?
MY PARENTS ARE OUT OF TOWN.
AND MY LITTLE BROTHER'S
GOT SOCCER PRACTICE.
[ CAR ALARM CHIRPS ]
♪ SHE'S SLEEPING GENTLY ♪
♪ IN HER HEAD ♪
♪ YOU KNOW ♪
♪ NOTHING'S
GONNA WORK OUT RIGHT ♪
YES, I'M STILL HOLDING.
I'VE BEEN HOLDING
FOR, LIKE, 5 MINUTES.
DREW!
DREW, FINALLY!
WHERE ARE YOU?
THE MOVIE'S STARTING.
WHAT?
YOU JUST DID
A DOUBLE SHIFT.
IT'S YOUR WEEK OFF.
OKAY, FINE, I JUST WISH
YOU WOULD LET ME KNOW.
♪ UNDERWATER
I WROTE DROWNING ♪
♪ I USED TO BE SUCH
A GOOD, GOOD SWIMMER ♪
♪ BUT FOR NOW MY HEAD
IS IN THE CLOUDS ♪
♪ I'M A SILLY LOVE SONG ♪
♪ A TWISTED-ELBOW CRUSH SONG ♪
♪ I WOULD GO TO JAIL
WITH ONLY BOYS ♪
♪ JUST TO PROVE
I WAS AS TOUGH AS YOU ♪
♪ AND WHEN I GET OUT
FOR GOOD BEHAVIOR ♪
♪ I'LL BE WRITING LOVE SONGS ♪
♪ SILLY BANGING-KNEE SONGS ♪
♪ I'M A CAR CRASH BUT
I HAVE TO GET UP ♪
♪ AND EVERY MORNING
THERE'S A CLEANUP ♪
♪ ALL I NEED IS TIME ♪
[ JOSH CHUCKLES ]
♪ TIME TO LOVE YOU ♪
HOW ABOUT HEADING TO
THE CABOOSE FOR DINNER?
HEY!
HOW ABOUT HEADING
TO BED INSTEAD?
NOT IN MY PARENTS' ROOM.
LOOK, I WANT TO GO OUT.
WE NEVER GO ANYWHERE.
HEY, I'M HUNGRY.
YEAH, ME TOO.
STOP!
JOSH, YOU CAN BE
A REAL JERK SOMETIMES.
OW!
LET GO!
WHAT'D YOU CALL ME?
A JERK.
DON'T YOU EVER!
YOU NEED TO LEAVE.
YEAH.
JENNA?
I REALLY NEED
YOUR CHEM HOMEWORK.
20 BUCKS?
I JUST REALLY NEED
TO PASS CHEM.
IT'S NOTHING PERSONAL.
CAN WE BURY
THE HATCHET FOR LIKE...
30?
NO.
WHATEVER.
SO THESE ARE SOME EXAMPLES
OF HOW COVALENCE WORKS.
JOSH?
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
ANYBODY HOME?
I'M FINE.
YOU'RE CATCHING UP.
YOU'RE WORKING HARD.
YOU'RE GONNA PASS CHEM.
I KNOW IT.
YOU STILL WORRIED?
NO.
I'M JUST THINKING.
ABOUT COVALENCE?
ABOUT A GIRL, ACTUALLY.
GO HOME, JOSH.
I SAID YOU'LL PASS, BUT ONLY
IF YOU KEEP DOING THE WORK.
OKAY.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
[ CAR ALARM CHIRPS ]
[ ENGINE TURNING ]
DAMN!
[ DIALING TELEPHONE ]
HI!
HI, THIS IS
CHRISTIE DAWSON.
YEAH, AGAIN, UM...
I'M IN THE SCHOOL PARKING LOT.
OH, THAT LONG?
OKAY, OKAY.
[ ENGINE TURNING ]
TROUBLE?
HI.
UH, NO...
I MEAN, YEAH,
I CALLED A GARAGE.
WELL, LET ME TAKE
A LOOK UNDER THE HOOD.
I MEAN, MAYBE I CAN'T TELL
A PROTON FROM AN ELECTRON,
BUT, UH, CARS ARE MY TURF.
GIVE ME 2 MINUTES AND YOU WON'T
HAVE TO WAIT FOR THE GARAGE.
OKAY.
GO FOR IT.
ALL RIGHT,
JUST POP THE HOOD.
OKAY.
START TURNING IT OVER.
[ ENGINE TURNING ]
OKAY.
STOP!
[ LAUGHING ]
IT'S NOTHING.
IT'S JUST AN INJECTOR PUMP.
JUST TRY IT AGAIN.
OKAY.
WAIT.
HERE. HERE, PUT THESE ON.
YOUR HANDS WILL FREEZE.
RED GLOVES?
I THINK
I'D RATHER FREEZE.
THANKS ANYWAY.
OH!
HELLO, JOSH.
MRS. DAWSON.
WHAT A TIGHTASS.
JOSH!
ALL RIGHT, GO FOR IT.
OKAY.
[ ENGINE TURNING ]
ALMOST.
AGAIN!
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
IT'S FIXED.
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
YOU'RE AMAZING!
WELL, THERE'S NOTHING
I WOULDN'T DO FOR YOU...
CHRISTIE.
WHAT'D YOU TELL HIM?
THAT, THAT KIND OF
FAMILIARITY IS INAPPROPRIATE,
AND A STUDENT CALLING ME
BY MY FIRST NAME IS WRONG.
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOUR PROBLEM IS?
YOU'RE TOO DAMN HOT
TO BE A TEACHER.
[ LAUGHING ]
AND IF HE TOUCHES YOU,
I'LL KILL HIM.
GET DRESSED.
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE.
I THINK CLARK TAKING YOU
TO THE CONTINENTAL
IS AS GOOD AS A PROMOTION.
WELL, NOTHING IS DONE
UNTIL IT'S DONE, OKAY?
HOW DO I LOOK?
LOVELY...
DON'T WORRY, OKAY?
I'M GONNA BE RIGHT
THERE WITH YOU.
OKAY.
UH...
I MISS MY HUSBAND.
I MEAN, IS THAT
ASKING TOO MUCH?
NOT IN THE SLIGHTEST,
CHRISTIE.
GO AHEAD AND ASK ME
TO SUBVERT
TO HOSPITAL ADMINISTRATION
AS WE KNOW IT.
WHY NOT?
GEORGE REMEMBERS
HOW WE STRUGGLED THROUGH
DOUBLE SHIFTS, CHRISTIE.
IT'S JUST THAT NOW
HE GETS TO BE THE ONE
TORTURING YOUNG DOCTORS
AND THEIR WIVES.
EXACTLY.
DID DREW GET YOU TO
DO HIS DIRTY WORK?
NO, NO, IT WAS
ALL MY IDEA.
LOOK, DR. CLARK,
I'M THE SORT OF GUY WHO
WILL WORK UNTIL HE DROPS.
WELL, THAT WON'T DO.
WE CAN'T HAVE YOU
DROPPING IN THE O.R.
NO, NO, NO.
WHAT I MEANT WAS THAT --
THAT --
I'M SORRY.
YOU KNOW, I SHOULDN'T
HAVE OPENED MY MOUTH.
I JUST...
I MISS MY HUSBAND.
I'M SORRY IT CAME OUT
A LITTLE WRONG.
BUT YOU'RE SO UPTIGHT
AROUND HIM.
I MEAN, HE'S JUST A HUMAN
BEING -- YOU CAN RELAX.
HE'S GOT A SENSE OF HUMOR.
RIGHT.
AM I GONNA GET THIS
COLD SHOULDER ALL NIGHT?
LOOK, IT'S SIMPLE.
I'M TRYING FOR A PROMOTION,
YOU'RE LOBBYING
FOR SHORTER HOURS.
IT MAKES ME LOOK
LIKE A SLACKER.
YOU'RE PARANOID.
IT'S FREEZING IN THIS CAR.
I GOTTA TAKE IT IN.
A STUDENT OF MINE
JUST FIXED MY CAR.
MAYBE I CAN GET HIM
TO FIX YOURS.
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
NOTHING!
I'M SORRY I SCREWED UP
YOUR DINNER.
CLEAN IT OFF.
SCREW YOU!
DON'T TOUCH MY STUFF!
STOP IT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
STOP IT! THAT'S ENOUGH!
COME ON, YOU TWO!
SHE STARTED IT!
GET TO YOUR CLASSES!
LET'S GO.
COULD YOU TAKE MONICA
TO THE PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE?
THAT'S NOT FAIR!
SHE'S THE ONE THAT STARTED IT!
JENNA?
JENNA!
JENNA, WHAT IS THIS?
THIS ISN'T LIKE YOU.
SHE HATES ME.
WHY?
JUST SEND ME TO
THE PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE!
HELLO?
HI!
HEY!
HOW WAS WORK?
UH...
NOT THAT GOOD.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
UM, DID YOU SEE CLARK?
YEAH, I SEE HIM EVERY DAY.
AND...DID HE
TALK ABOUT DINNER?
AT THE TIME WE WERE
STABILIZING A KID
WITH COMPOUND FRACTURES
AND BONE SHARDS
IN HIS FEMORALS.
I'M STILL WORKING
DOUBLE SHIFTS THIS WEEK,
SO I GUESS YOUR LOBBYING
DIDN'T WORK.
CAN WE DROP IT?
WHAT?
THIS PASSIVE-AGGRESSIVE
STUFF DOESN'T WORK FOR ME.
FINE.
I'M -- I'M SORRY.
ME TOO.
I'M SORRY.
SORRY!
YOU GUYS ARE THE ONLY
SENIOR HOMEROOM
WITH PERFECT ATTENDANCE.
AND THAT IS VERY COOL.
THREE LARGE
PEPPERONI PIZZAS!
THE LINE FORMS
TO THE RIGHT, PEOPLE.
OH, COME IN!
THERE'S MORE THAN ENOUGH
PIZZA FOR EVERYONE.
NO, THANKS.
JOSH, COME IN.
YOU'RE INVITED TOO.
TAKE A PLATE.
YEAH!
THANKS, MS. DAWSON.
OKAY?
THAT'S SO CUTE,
BY THE WAY.
CONGRATS AGAIN!
JUST THROW OUT ANY RANDOM
PARTY STUFF ON YOUR WAY OUT.
OKAY, YOU GUYS?
BYE!
THANKS.
JENNA!
UM...
I GOT THE NEW
LIFEHOUSE CD FOR YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DID THAT.
WELL, TAKE IT.
IT'S YOURS.
YOU WORKED REALLY HARD
THIS SEMESTER.
THANK YOU, MS. DAWSON.
THANKS A LOT!
OH, JENNA, UM...
I DON'T MEAN TO PRY, BUT...
YOU KNOW, IF YOU
EVER WANT TO TALK ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED WITH YOU
AND MONICA, I'M HERE.
I MEAN, YOU'RE MY BEST STUDENT
AND I DON'T WANT THAT TO CHANGE.
THANKS, MS. DAWSON.
YOUR PIZZA PARTY'S THE TALK
OF THE FACULTY LOUNGE.
GOOD.
GLAD TO SHAKE THINGS UP
A LITTLE BIT.
WELL, IT'S JUST NOT
HOW WE DO THINGS HERE.
YOU CAN HAVE
A CHRISTMAS PARTY,
AN END-OF-YEAR PARTY,
BUT THE KIDS ARE SUPPOSED
TO BRING THE GOODIES.
DID YOU TREAT?
THE KIDS LOVED IT.
30 BUCKS WELL SPENT.
SOME FACULTY THINK YOU'RE
TRYING TO WIN POINTS
THE EASY WAY.
THE BATTLE-SCARRED
AND MENTALLY FRIED?
DO YOU THINK THAT?
OH, NO!
I MEAN, I KNOW YOU
BETTER THAN THAT.
MMM-HMM.
THE KID WITH THE COMPOUND
FRACTURE WENT HOME TODAY.
OH, NICE JOB, DOC!
I BET THAT GETS YOU BACK
IN CLARK'S GOOD BOOKS.
YEAH.
FIXED THE CAR HEATER, TOO.
COME ON!
AND THE BEST PART...
THE BEST PART IS?
I MADE UP WITH
MY INCREDIBLY BEAUTIFUL WIFE.
HOW DID YOU PULL THAT OFF?
YOU WANT TO...
PULL THAT OFF?
IT WAS EASY, THOUGH.
WE JUST MADE LOVE,
AND IT REMINDED US OF...
HOW INCREDIBLY NUTS
WE ARE ABOUT EACH OTHER.
WAS IT GOOD FOR YOU?
IT WAS AMAZINGLY GOOD.
CONDOM.
SKIP IT.
NO!
CHRISTIE.
JUST DO IT FOR ME, OKAY?
STOP ASKING, FOR ME.
ONCE YOU'VE MEASURED THE pH,
THAT'S IT FOR TODAY.
DON'T FORGET
TO SHUT OFF THE GAS.
AND LEAVE THE CRUCIBLES
FOR MR. DI ORIO.
GOOD WORK, EVERYONE.
DON'T FORGET YOUR LAB REPORTS.
THAT WAS ROUGH.
THANK YOU.
ARE WE STILL ON
FOR TUTORING?
YOU KNOW WHAT, JOSH?
LET'S SKIP TUTORING FOR TODAY.
WE'LL RESCHEDULE TOMORROW.
I DO SOMETHING WRONG?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S NOT IT.
YOU OKAY?
YOU SEEM KIND OF
OUT OF IT TODAY.
SOMETHING WRONG AT HOME?
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
YOU HAVE A FIGHT
WITH YOUR HUSBAND?
JOSH.
WE'RE FRIENDS, RIGHT?
FRIENDS CAN TALK.
WE'RE TEACHER-STUDENT FRIENDS.
IT'S A SPECIAL CATEGORY.
IT DOESN'T INCLUDE
PERSONAL CONFIDENCES.
SO IF I HAD A PROBLEM,
I COULDN'T COME TO YOU?
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
IF YOU HAD A PROBLEM,
YOU COULD COME TO ME
OR YOUR GUIDANCE COUNSELOR.
THEN IT WORKS BOTH WAYS.
ACTUALLY, NO, IT DOESN'T.
LOOK...
I'M NOT A KID.
OKAY?
WELL, YOU ARE TO ME.
YOU'RE MY STUDENT.
WELL, I'M SORRY.
I JUST THOUGHT
YOU LOOKED A LITTLE UPSET.
JOSH, HOW I LOOK
OR DON'T LOOK
IS NOT AN APPROPRIATE
SUBJECT FOR DISCUSSION.
TUTORING IS.
SO LET'S RESCHEDULE
FOR TOMORROW, OKAY?
ALL RIGHT.
HOW'S THE CHEMISTRY GOING?
GREAT.
TEACHER LOVES ME.
BECAUSE NOW SHE'S
INVESTED IN YOU.
YOUR SUCCESS IS
A REFLECTION ON HER.
IT'S ALL ABOUT
THE RELATIONSHIP, SON.
SHE GETS HER EGO STROKED,
YOU GET GOOD MARKS,
AND EVERYBODY
GOES HOME A WINNER.
GOOD WORK.
[ WHISTLE BLOWING ]
Man: TEACHERS SWIM!
STUDENTS OUT OF THE POOL!
SORRY ABOUT THE PERSONAL
QUESTION YESTERDAY.
I WAS OUT OF LINE.
IT'LL NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
WHAT ARE YOU
STILL DOING IN THE POOL?
IT'S TEACHERS' SWIM.
EXCUSE ME, MS. DAWSON.
I GUESS EVERYTHING
I DO IS WRONG.
WAIT.
JOSH!
THAT'S IT, OKAY?
OUR TUTORING
SESSIONS ARE OVER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOUR PROBLEMS
ARE, BUT IF I WERE YOU,
I'D TALK THEM OVER WITH
YOUR GUIDANCE COUNSELOR.
YOU'RE IN BIG TROUBLE.
[ SIGHS ]
I AM VERY DISTURBED
BY WHAT YOU'VE JUST SAID.
BUT FRANKLY, I AM NOT
TOTALLY SURPRISED.
ARE YOU AWARE OF THE RUMORS
CIRCULATING THROUGH THE SCHOOL?
RUMORS?
UM, MS. DAVIS,
I VOLUNTEERED TO TUTOR JOSH
TO HELP HIM WITH CHEMISTRY.
I SEEM TO REMEMBER YOU THOUGHT
THAT WAS A GOOD IDEA.
I DID INDEED!
YOU'RE A FIRST-YEAR TEACHER,
AND I THINK YOU'RE GOING TO
BE A DAMN GOOD TEACHER.
YOU'RE FULL OF
ENTHUSIASM, BUT...
SOMETIMES THAT
CAN LEAD TO TROUBLE.
WAIT, I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M HEARING THIS.
I HAVE DONE NOTHING
TO BRING THIS ON.
JOSH GAINES NEEDS HELP!
WHAT SORT OF HELP
DOES JOSH GAINES NEED?
WELL, I THINK HE NEEDS
TO BE SEVERELY REPRIMANDED.
I MEAN, MAYBE EVEN SUSPENDED.
HE WAS WAY, WAY OUT OF LINE.
WHAT'S THE SCHOOL POLICY
ON SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
POLICY?
ON A TEACHER BEING KISSED?
THERE IS NONE.
WELL, IS THERE A POLICY
ON ASSAULT?
WELL, CERTAINLY THERE IS.
BUT DO YOU ACTUALLY THINK
THAT THIS IS THE BEST WAY
TO GO WITH THIS?
AS AN ASSAULT CHARGE?
I MEAN, IT'LL LEAD TO
AN INVESTIGATION
WITH WITNESSES, REPORTS,
AND ALL OF THAT.
WE'RE JUST GOING TO LET HIM
GET AWAY WITH THIS?
DEFINITELY NOT.
BUT DO YOU HAVE A WITNESS
TO THIS ASSAULT?
NO.
WELL THEN,
DON'T YOU THINK
HE MIGHT JUST DENY THE CHARGE?
HE SAID, SHE SAID.
WHERE ARE THOSE DIFFERENT
VERSIONS GOING?
I'M A TEACHER.
ISN'T MY WORD
WORTH MORE THAN A STUDENT'S?
ABSOLUTELY!
IT'S JUST THAT YOU'RE
VEERING OFF
INTO LEGAL TERRAIN THAT I...
LOOK, YOU COULD LODGE
A FORMAL COMPLAINT,
OR YOU COULD SIT DOWN
WITH JOSH GAINES YOURSELF,
AND DEAL WITH IT.
WANT MY ADVICE?
I THINK I JUST GOT IT.
HE'S A LITTLE PUNK!
WHERE DOES HE GET OFF?
YOU KNOW WHAT HE NEEDS?
HIS BUTT KICKED!
DREW, DON'T EVEN
THINK ABOUT THAT!
DAVIS SHOULD'VE HANDLED IT.
THE WAY SHE WAS
LOOKING AT ME
WAS LIKE I WAS SOME SORT
OF FAILURE OR SOMETHING.
I'M THE TEACHER, I SHOULD
NEVER HAVE ALLOWED IT.
I MEAN, TALK
ABOUT ZERO SUPPORT.
SHE BLAMES ME.
HOW LOUSY IS THAT?
SHE'S A BUREAUCRAT.
IT'S NOT HER FAULT.
SHE'S HARD-WIRED
TO AVOID PROBLEMS.
FORGET DAVIS, WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO ABOUT THE KID?
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU GOTTA DO?
TELL HIM LOUD
AND CLEAR THAT YOU --
WHAT, SMACKING HIM
ACROSS THE FACE
ISN'T LOUD AND CLEAR
ENOUGH FOR YOU?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE LUCKY.
HIS FATHER COULD'VE
COME AFTER YOU FOR ASSAULT.
THESE ARE SERIOUSLY
SCREWED UP TIMES, HONEY.
EVERYONE THINKS
I CAN'T HANDLE JOSH.
I CAN HANDLE JOSH.
HE'S A KID!
BUT I CAN'T HANDLE
EVERYONE ELSE, EVEN YOU!
HEY...
I'M WITH YOU, OKAY?
I'M JUST WORRIED
ABOUT YOU, THAT'S ALL.
WHY DON'T YOU, UH...
WHY DON'T YOU
STAY AWAY FOR A WHILE?
CALL IN SICK.
LET EVERYONE COOL DOWN.
NO, NO WAY.
ONE KID GETS FRESH
AND I CAN'T DEAL WITH IT?
NO WAY.
HEY, YOU'LL BE FINE.
BUT IF YOU NEED ME TO
TEACH HIM SOME MANNERS...
JUST SAY THE WORD.
OKAY.
BI-POLE BONDING, CLASS.
WHAT IS IT?
JOSH?
EXCUSE ME?
GIVE ME AN EXAMPLE
OF BI-POLE BONDING.
A GAY WEDDING?
[ CLASS LAUGHING ]
NO, ACTUALLY, THAT'S WRONG.
JENNA, COULD YOU PLEASE
HELP JOSH OUT?
UM, BI-POLE BONDING
OCCURS WHEN...
POLAR MOLECULES ARE
ATTRACTED TO EACH OTHER.
THEY'RE SIMILAR TO, BUT
WEAKER THAN, IONIC BONDS.
THANK YOU, JENNA.
THAT'S CORRECT.
JOSH, FOR TOMORROW, I WANT
FIVE EXAMPLES OF BI-POLE BONDS.
THAT WILL BE OUR
INTRODUCTION TO POLYMERS.
SCREW YOU, CHRISTIE.
PARDON ME?
NOTHING.
SEE ME AFTER CLASS.
ANY TIME.
DETENTION.
WHATEVER.
[ KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
COME IN!
SIT DOWN.
IS THERE AN ISSUE BETWEEN
YOU AND MRS. DAWSON?
I DON'T KNOW.
IS THIS THE FALLOUT
FROM YESTERDAY'S INCIDENT?
SHE TOLD YOU?
PERHAPS YOU SHOULD TELL ME
YOUR SIDE OF THE STORY.
WELL, WHAT DID SHE SAY?
IT WAS NOTHING, REALLY.
I MEAN, SHE KIND
OF CAME ON TO ME--
ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S QUITE ENOUGH.
TO BEGIN WITH,
I'M GOING TO CANCEL
YOUR TUTORIALS
WITH MRS. DAWSON,
EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY.
SHE ALREADY DID THAT.
GOOD.
AND IN THE FUTURE, YOU WILL
STEER CLEAR OF MRS. DAWSON,
WITH THE EXCEPTION OF
YOUR ATTENDANCE
IN HER CHEMISTRY CLASS.
YES, MA'AM.
ANYTHING ELSE?
NO -- I INTEND
CALLING YOUR PARENTS
TO DISCUSS THIS
SITUATION WITH THEM.
MS. DAVIS,
PLEASE DON'T DO THAT.
I THINK THEIR INTERVENTION
IS GONNA HELP YOU
FOCUS ON YOUR STUDIES.
NO.
I DON'T THINK YOU UNDERSTAND.
I THINK I DO.
THIS DETENTION IS OVER.
[ WATER DRIPPING ]
OKAY...
[ DOOR CLOSING ]
DREW, I'M IN THE KITCHEN!
JOSH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU TOLD DAVIS.
THAT HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH HER.
THAT WAS BETWEEN YOU
AND ME.
JOSH, GET OUT OF HERE!
I BROKE UP WITH
MY GIRLFRIEND FOR YOU.
YOU'RE VERY CONFUSED.
NO, I THINK YOU'RE
THE ONE WHO'S CONFUSED.
NO!
JOSH, DON'T!
GIVE ME A CHANCE.
GET OUT OF HERE!
SHH, SHH.
STOP IT!
[ CLOTHES RIPPING ]
OW!
STOP IT.
OH!
WAIT, WAIT!
PLEASE STOP.
I DON'T...
OW! OW! OW!
CHRISTIE, I DON'T WANT,
I DON'T --
[ Crying ]
GET OFF ME!
I LOVE YOU, I LOVE YOU.
DR. PHILLIPS, CARDIOLOGY,
DR. PHILLIPS, CARDIOLOGY.
NO, I'M OKAY. THAT'S OKAY.
I WANNA SEE DREW.
CHRISTIE, DO YOU WANT TO
REPORT THIS TO THE POLICE?
YES.
OKAY, WELL, WE NEED
TO LOOK YOU OVER.
I WASN'T RAPED,
I WAS ASSAULTED.
I KNOW, BUT WE STILL
NEED TO EXAMINE YOU.
CHRISTIE!
WHAT DID HE DO TO YOU?
I'LL KILL HIM.
NO, DREW.
I'M OKAY, I JUST WANT
TO SEE THE POLICE.
SON OF A BITCH.
CALM DOWN, DREW.
I NEED YOU.
I'M HERE.
JOSH?
WHY ARE YOU SITTING
IN THE DARK?
I HAVE A PROBLEM, MOM.
Christie: YES, ASSAULT.
HE ASSAULTED ME -- I DEFINITELY
WANT TO PRESS CHARGES.
ALL RIGHT, WE UNDERSTAND
THAT, MRS. DAWSON,
BUT FOR NOW, WE JUST
WANT TO HEAR YOUR STORY.
WHAT DO YOU
MEAN MY "STORY"?
WE DON'T MEAN ANYTHING.
WE'RE GONNA TAKE YOUR STATEMENT.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
IT'S FINE.
GO AHEAD.
SO YOU KNEW THE BOY?
YES, HE WAS ONE
OF MY STUDENTS.
DID YOU HAVE PRIOR INDICATION
HE MIGHT ASSAULT YOU?
WELL...
YEAH.
YESTERDAY MORNING,
IN A SCHOOL HALLWAY,
HE FORCED A KISS ON ME.
SO, YOU DIDN'T WANT
HIM TO KISS YOU?
OF COURSE I DIDN'T
WANT HIM TO KISS ME.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
HONEY, THEY'RE JUST
DOING THEIR JOBS, OKAY?
AND HOW DID YOU REACT
TO THIS UNWANTED KISS?
I TOLD HIM TO STOP.
AND I SLAPPED HIM.
AND THEN?
HE LEFT AND I REPORTED
IT TO THE PRINCIPAL.
WHAT'S HER NAME?
HELEN DAVIS.
ALL RIGHT!
UM...
HOW OLD IS JOSHUA?
I DON'T KNOW, 17, I GUESS.
THANK YOU, MRS. DAWSON.
THAT'S ALL WE NEED FOR NOW.
THAT'S IT?
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
ASK ME HOW IT HAPPENED?
WE GOT ENOUGH.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
ARREST HIM?
THAT'S THE D.A.'S CALL.
THEY'LL BE IN TOUCH.
THANKS.
THANK YOU.
YOU OKAY?
UNREAL.
HOW'S JOSH DOING?
JOSH IS DOING FINE.
THIS IS A VERY
DELICATE SITUATION.
I CAN APPRECIATE THAT.
HAVE THEY PRESSED
ANY CHARGES?
NO.
LISTEN, MAKE SURE HE
DOESN'T TALK TO ANYONE.
AND WHAT WAS THAT
TEACHER'S NAME AGAIN?
CHRISTIE DAWSON.
I'M GONNA CALL THE D.A.
GOOD.
DR. KRAVITZ, YOU HAVE
A VISITOR IN THE MAIN LOBBY.
DR. KRAVITZ, A VISITOR
IN THE MAIN LOBBY.
I NEED A DISCHARGE FORM
FOR CHRISTIE DAWSON.
DREW.
HEY, HOW DID IT GO
WITH THE DETECTIVES?
AHH...OKAY.
WELL, YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT
THEY'RE ASKING FOR CHRISTIE'S
MEDICAL AND PSYCHIATRIC HISTORY.
OKAY.
GOOD LUCK.
THANKS.
HAVE YOU BEEN
INTERVIEWED YET?
NO.
THEY'RE INTERVIEWING EVERYONE.
I KNOW, THEY'RE
ALL OVER THE SCHOOL.
YEAH, SHE'S CHARGING
HIM WITH SEXUAL ASSAULT.
AND THE COPS BOUGHT INTO THAT?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO TELL THEM?
I HEARD THEY DID
ECSTASY TOGETHER.
AND YOU BELIEVE THAT CRAP?
ISN'T THAT WHAT YOU
AND JOSH USED TO DO TOGETHER?
THAT'S WHAT HE SAID.
NO.
YOU DON'T HAVE A CLUE WHAT
HAPPENED BETWEEN JOSH AND ME.
I THINK I HAVE
A PRETTY GOOD IDEA.
MS. DAWSON
IS THE BEST THING THAT
EVER HAPPENED TO THIS SCHOOL.
RIGHT, I JUST WISH
I'D GOT A PIECE.
[ Chuckling ]
YOU'RE ALL LOSERS!
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
[ RING ]
HELLO.
CHRISTIE?
LORRAINE.
OH...HONEY,
HOW YOU DOING?
LOUSY.
I'M SO SORRY.
IT'S BEEN THREE DAYS.
I'VE BEEN WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
NO, DON'T.
HAVE THEY CHARGED HIM YET?
NO.
OH!
IS DREW HOME?
HE'S ON HIS WAY BACK.
HE, UM, HE'S WORKING PART-
TIME SINCE THIS HAPPENED.
THAT'S BIG OF HIM.
[ EXHALES ]
LISTEN, DO YOU WANT ME
TO COME OVER THERE?
NO, NO.
OKAY...
THEN YOU COME HERE.
WHAT?
COME TO SCHOOL,
FACE THESE JERKS.
THAT'LL SHOW 'EM.
[ Exhales ]
NO, I DON'T THINK I CAN.
I'M NOT FEELING GREAT.
OH, HELLO!
WHERE IS THAT SCREW-THE-WORLD
ATTITUDE WHEN YOU NEED IT?
OH! COME ON, CHRISTIE.
COME DOWN HERE AND SHOW 'EM.
I'LL BE HERE.
I'LL HELP YOU.
YOU'RE A GOOD
FRIEND, LORRAINE.
YEAH, ARE YOU COMING
OR DO I HAVE TO DRIVE THERE
AND DRAG YOU DOWN MYSELF?
I'M COMING.
HI.
WHERE YOU GOING?
TO SCHOOL.
WELL, THAT'S A REALLY,
THAT'S A REALLY STUPID IDEA.
I'M GOING TO SCHOOL.
OKAY, OKAY, JUST, UM,
LET ME DRIVE YOU,
WE'LL TAKE MY CAR.
DREW, DREW.
JUST STOP WALKING
ON EGGSHELLS WITH ME, OKAY?
I'M FINE, AND IF IT FEELS WEIRD
AT SCHOOL, I'LL COME HOME.
OKAY.
BYE.
HI.
HI. LISTEN, UM...
HE JUST SHOWED UP.
WHAT?
I SWEAR I DIDN'T
KNOW WHEN I CALLED YOU.
WHAT, HE'S JUST
RUNNING AROUND LOOSE?
THIS WAS ONE OF MY DUMBER
IDEAS, WASN'T IT?
I'M SO SORRY.
NOT EVEN A DETENTION
FOR AN ASSAULT?
WHAT, ARE THEY GOING TO
MAKE HIM VALEDICTORIAN?
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET ME TAKE YOU HOME.
YOU DON'T NEED THIS,
HONEY.
NO.
Woman: REMEMBER
THAT OXIDATION IS
THE GAIN OF OXYGEN,
LOSS OF HYDROGEN,
OR LOSS OF ELECTRONS.
YES?
THIS IS MY CLASS.
I'LL TAKE OVER, THANK YOU.
WHAT?
I'M CHRISTIE DAWSON.
YOU CAN SPEAK WITH
MS. DAVIS, SHE'LL EXPLAIN.
OKAY.
THANK YOU.
OKAY...
OXIDATION REDUCTION.
FOLLOW US, PLEASE.
NOW.
ONCE YOU'VE BALANCED
THE EQUATION,
OXIDATION REDUCTION
IS A NO-BRAINER.
[ KNOCKING AT DOOR ]
ONE MOMENT.
FINALLY.
YOU NEED ME FOR
MORE QUESTIONING?
CAN YOU JUST GIVE
ME 15 MORE MINUTES?
I'M SORRY, IT CAN'T WAIT.
OKAY, I WANT YOU TO BALANCE THAT
EQUATION. I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ CLASS MURMURING ]
MRS. DAWSON...
YES -- HAVE YOU
ARRESTED HIM YET?
YOU'RE UNDER
ARREST, MRS. DAWSON.
WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU CRAZY?
HE'S THE ONE
WHO SHOULD BE ARRESTED.
YOU HAVE THE RIGHT
TO REMAIN SILENT.
TO AN ATTORNEY.
IF YOU CANNOT
AFFORD AN ATTORNEY,
ONE WILL BE
APPOINTED FOR YOU.
KID, RELAX, IT'S
JUST FOR QUESTIONING.
ARE YOU GOING TO
HELP US OUT?
YEAH.
GOOD. YOU ALL RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
THIS IS SO INSANE, BRIAN.
I KNOW, I KNOW, WE'LL GET YOU
OUT OF HERE IN A FEW MINUTES,
AS SOON AS
DREW POSTS BAIL.
I MEAN, I CAN'T
COMPREHEND IT.
HOW COULD THEY ARREST ME?
HE ATTACKED ME.
WHY AM I HERE?
BECAUSE THE POLICE BELIEVE
THE GAINES' STORY AND NOT YOURS.
THEY ARE SAYING
THAT YOU INITIATED
A PHYSICAL RELATIONSHIP
WITH JOSH.
THAT YOU INVITED
HIM TO YOUR HOUSE.
WHAT?
THAT'S OUTRAGEOUS!
OF COURSE IT IS.
THAT'S WHY I NEED
TO KNOW EVERY DETAIL.
I NEED YOU TO BE CALM,
I NEED YOU TO HELP ME
PREPARE YOUR CASE.
OKAY, SEXUAL ABUSE OF
A MINOR IS A HEAVY CHARGE.
IT CARRIES A MINIMUM
5-YEAR SENTENCE.
ARE YOU TRYING TO FREAK
ME OUT OR CALM ME DOWN?
CALM YOU DOWN.
[ EXHALES ]
THIS IS A NIGHTMARE --
I HAVE BEEN ARRESTED
AND THE SCHOOL BOARD
SUSPENDED ME.
I KNOW, AND THE ONLY WAY
WE CAN DEAL WITH THIS
IS IF YOU TELL ME EVERYTHING.
SO, LET'S START WITH
THE SIMPLE FACTS.
HOW OLD ARE YOU AGAIN?
27.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
HEY, BRIAN.
HEY, DREW.
SO, UH, BAIL'S ALL TAKEN CARE
OF, WE CAN LEAVE ANY TIME.
OKAY, 27, BUT, UH, YOU
COULD PASS FOR YOUNGER.
UH, I'M SORRY,
WHAT'S THE POINT HERE?
WELL, SHE'S YOUNG,
ATTRACTIVE,
THE KIDS PROBABLY LOVE YOU...
COULD THE BOUNDARIES
HAVE GOTTEN BLURRED?
YEAH, YEAH, I
WOULD SAY THAT, UH,
SEXUAL ASSAULT IS A BLURRING
OF THE LINES, OKAY?
NO, HE MEANS DID I
BLUR THE LINES, DREW.
NO.
OKAY, BUT WE HAVE TO
DEAL WITH THE FACT THAT
THE D.A. HAS GATHERED
SOME PRETTY DAMAGING
TESTIMONY AGAINST YOU.
UH, YOU THREW A HOMEROOM
PARTY DURING SCHOOL HOURS
IN WHICH JOSH WAS INVITED,
EVEN THOUGH HE'S NOT A MEMBER
OF YOUR HOMEROOM CLASS.
NO, NO, NO.
HE SHOWED UP.
I DIDN'T INVITE HIM...
UNTIL HE SHOWED UP.
AND THEN YOU DID.
INVITE HIM.
YEAH, OKAY, UH, SOME OF
THE STUDENTS HAVE SAID
YOU SINGLED HIM OUT FOR
SPECIAL ATTENTION.
I QUOTE, YOU WERE SEEN
IN "INTIMATE SETTINGS."
I WAS TUTORING HIM.
QUOTE, WITH YOUR
"HAND ON HIS SHOULDER."
YOU'RE WORKING HARD, YOU'RE
GONNA PASS CHEM, I'M SURE OF IT.
Fiske: I'M SORRY, I THOUGHT
YOU WERE A STUDENT.
"SHE DRESSED LIKE A KID,
IN TIGHT JEANS."
QUOTE -- "SHE WAS TRYING TO
BUY HER STUDENTS' AFFECTIONS."
Student: THANKS, MS. DAWSON.
QUOTE -- "ONE DAY
DURING TEACHERS' SWIM,"
"I SAW JOSH AND MRS. DAWSON
HORSING AROUND
TOGETHER IN THE POOL."
HE WAS SEEN "TOUCHING
HER ROMANTICALLY."
HELLO JOSH,
MRS. DAWSON.
AND SO ON AND SO ON...
IS THIS SOME KIND
OF WITCH HUNT?
YEAH.
YEAH, IT IS.
I MEAN, PEOPLE ARE ON HIGH
ALERT FOR SEXUAL PREDATORS.
WAIT, I'M NOT
A SEXUAL PREDATOR.
HEY, YOU WATCH YOUR MOUTH.
OKAY, WHOA, WHOA.
I'M IN TROUBLE, AREN'T I?
[ EXHALES ]
LOOK, LOOK...
THE GOOD NEWS IS
ALL OF THEIR EVIDENCE
IS CIRCUMSTANTIAL.
I CAN BUILD A REALLY GOOD
REASONABLE DOUBT CASE.
I REALLY THINK I CAN
GET YOU OFF HERE.
THINK?
WHAT IS THIS "GET
YOU OFF" CRAP, OKAY?
I MEAN WH-WHOSE
LAWYER ARE YOU?
YOURS. OKAY? YOURS.
BUT YOU NEED TO CALM DOWN,
YOU NEED TO GO HOME.
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF WORK
TO DO TO PREPARE.
NOW LISTEN TO ME, THIS
IS A RUNAWAY TRAIN
AND IT IS COMING
STRAIGHT AT YOU.
HOW COULD YOU NOT KNOW ABOUT YOUR SON'S
DANGEROUS RELATIONSHIP WITH HIS HIGH SCHOOL TEACHER?
Mrs. Gaines: WELL, WE COULD
TELL JOSH WAS TROUBLED,
WE JUST DIDN'T KNOW WHY.
Mr. Gaines:
WE WERE TOO TRUSTING.
OH, THAT IS SUCH BULL!
PUT THAT BACK ON.
YOU DON'T NEED
TO HEAR THIS CRAP.
THEY ARE PLAYING THE MEDIA
AND WE JUST SIT HERE LETTING
THEM GET AWAY WITH IT.
LET BRIAN HANDLE
YOUR DEFENSE, HONEY.
FINE.
I'LL HANDLE THE OFFENSE.
FIRST THING TOMORROW,
I'M GOING BACK TO SCHOOL.
SCHOOL?
THE LAST TIME YOU
WENT TO SCHOOL --
I'M GOING TO SEE DAVIS
AND GET REINSTATED.
SHE CAN'T REINSTATE YOU.
YOU'VE JUST BEEN
ACCUSED OF A FELONY!
FINE, I'LL
CALL THE UNION.
NO, NO.
LEAVE DAVIS ALONE, OKAY?
DON'T STIR HER UP.
STIR HER UP ABOUT WHAT?
TO GO ON TV AND SAY
MORE BAD STUFF ABOUT YOU.
PERCEPTION IS
ALREADY BAD ENOUGH.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING, DREW?
THAT...
OBVIOUSLY, THERE'S
A PERCEPTION OUT THERE,
THAT THIS IS YOUR FAULT,
THAT YOU LED HIM ON.
IT'S WHAT YOU REALLY
THINK, ISN'T IT?
NO. NO.
IT'S THE PERCEPTION.
WHAT HAPPENED TO, "DON'T
BLAME YOURSELF, CHRISTIE"?
SOMETIMES YOU PUT OUT SIGNALS,
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW IT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT
SIGNALS, DREW.
YOU WANNA KNOW WHAT SIGNALS
I'M GETTING RIGHT NOW?
A MAN -- A BOY --
ASSAULTS A WOMAN
AND HE GETS A FREE PASS,
EVEN FROM HER HUSBAND.
HEY!
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
AND THE WOMAN?
SHE HAS ONLY HERSELF TO BLAME
FOR NOT SEEING IT COMING FIRST.
I DIDN'T SAY THAT!
NO, YOU SIGNALED IT.
OHH...GOD, I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE I DID IT WRONG.
I JUST WANTED TO BE
FRIENDS WITH THE KIDS.
I CARE ABOUT THEM.
I FEEL -- OH, GOD.
CHRISTIE...
CHRISTIE?
[ COUGHING ]
[ VOMITING ]
CHRISTIE, ARE YOU OKAY?
DREW, I'LL BE OUT IN A MINUTE.
UH...
I'M SO SORRY, BABE.
A BABY...NOW.
WHAT A MESS.
LOOK, DO YOU WANT THE BABY?
[ Whispering ]
Do you?
Yeah. Yeah.
WE'RE GOING TO
BEAT THIS, DREW.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO TOLD ME
NOT TO START AN OFFICIAL
INVESTIGATION.
YOU TOLD ME TO JUST
WORK THIS OUT WITH HIM.
WHERE DID THAT LEAD?
HE ASSAULTED ME, MS. DAVIS.
IN MY HOME.
I'M REALLY
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I INSIST UPON
BEING REINSTATED.
I LOVED MY JOB.
I WANT IT BACK.
I WISH I COULD HELP.
I DEFENDED YOU LAST
NIGHT, MRS. DAWSON,
IN FRONT OF THE SCHOOL BOARD.
IF IT HADN'T BEEN
FOR MY INTERVENTION,
YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN DISMISSED.
I AM CERTAIN WHEN
YOU GO TO COURT --
WILL YOU TESTIFY?
WELL, IF THEY ASK ME,
OF COURSE I'LL TESTIFY.
I'LL TELL THEM WHAT YOU SAID.
BUT I'LL ALSO HAVE TO TELL
THEM WHAT JOSH GAINES SAID,
AND THAT IS THAT
YOU CAME ON TO HIM.
GREAT. GREAT. SO HAVE
THAT ON MY DESK BY 3:00, OKAY?
WHAT EXACTLY ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
I WANT YOU TO TAKE
YOUR SON TO THE POLICE
AND HAVE HIM TELL THEM
WHAT REALLY HAPPENED.
JOSH DID SOMETHING
TERRIBLE AND YOU --
GET OUT OF HERE
AND STAY AWAY FROM MY SON.
I NEVER WANT TO SEE
YOU AROUND HIM AGAIN.
YOU'RE LYING,
YOU KNOW WHAT HE'S DONE.
THIS IS MY LIFE AT STAKE.
I'M CALLING THE POLICE.
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
[ RING ]
Josh: MS. DAWSON.
HOW THE HELL DO YOU HAVE
THE NERVE TO CALL ME?
LOOK, I WISH NONE
OF THIS HAPPENED.
I REALLY DIDN'T MEAN
TO GET YOU IN TROUBLE --
NO, STOP IT!
YOU THINK
YOU CAN APOLOGIZE TO ME?
YOUR LIES...
WOULD YOU LET ME EXPLAIN?
HAVE GOTTEN ME
ACCUSED OF SEXUAL ASSAULT.
I MIGHT GO TO JAIL
FOR WHAT YOU DID TO ME.
THAT'S NOT FAIR. OKAY?
Y-YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND,
I REALLY THOUGHT THAT
YOU WERE IN--
NO, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOU'RE A SICK KID, JOSH,
AND YOU NEED HELP.
BUT RIGHT NOW, WHAT YOU
NEED TO DO IS GO TO THE COPS
AND TELL THEM THE TRUTH.
I DIDN'T WANT YOU
TO GET IN TROUBLE.
IT WAS MY PARENTS.
MY FATHER WAS THE ONE WHO LIED TO THE COPS.
THE HELL WITH YOUR FATHER!
GO TO THE COPS AND TELL THEM
YOU ASSAULTED ME,
TELL THEM TO DROP
THE CHARGES!
NO.
NO...YOU WANTED IT.
I KNOW YOU DID.
'CAUSE I KNOW WHAT GIRLS THINK, CHRISTIE.
GIRLS ARE ALWAYS LIKE THAT.
[ EXHALES ]
WHAT GIRLS ARE
LIKE THAT, JOSH?
SCREW YOU.
HE'S NEVER GONNA CALL YOU AGAIN.
YOU TRUST ME, OKAY?
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
NO, HE IS NOT THE PROBLEM, OKAY.
NO ONE BELIEVES ME,
DREW, NO ONE.
GAINES HAS THE MONEY
AND THE LAWYERS AND THE PR.
I MEAN, I COULD LOSE.
I COULD GO TO JAIL.
YOU WON'T, OKAY?
BRIAN IS ON TOP OF IT.
WE NEED TO BE
ON TOP OF IT.
I'VE BEEN ON THE WEB --
GUYS WHO COMMIT AN ASSAULT
ARE LIKELY TO HAVE
DONE IT BEFORE.
IF WE COULD GET SOMEONE
ELSE TO TESTIFY...
THAT'S GREAT, WE'LL GO SEE
BRIAN IN THE MORNING, OKAY?
[ EXHALES ]
HEY...
HOLD ON.
WHAT IS THIS?
JUST OPEN IT.
OPEN IT!
OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW,
I THOUGHT WE'D, UH,
GET A HEAD START
ON THE DEBATE, THERE.
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
I GOT SOME NAMES FOR YOU.
YEAH?
FOLSOM, ATTICA.
THAT'S VERY FUNNY.
THANK YOU.
[ COMPUTER BEEPS ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
HI, MRS. HOBSON.
I'M SO SORRY TO DISTURB
YOU SO EARLY, BUT...
I REALLY NEED TO SPEAK
WITH YOUR DAUGHTER.
JENNA DOESN'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO TELL YOU.
HER LIFE IS GOING REAL GOOD.
LET IT BE. PLEASE.
COME ON!
JENNA!
I'M HERE BECAUSE
I NEED YOUR HELP.
I'M REALLY SORRY
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU'RE THE BEST
TEACHER WE EVER HAD.
I WISH.
JENNA, DO YOU THINK THAT
JOSH GAINES ATTACKED ME?
YES.
WHY?
CAN I ASK YOU
SOMETHING PERSONAL?
I WASN'T HERE LAST YEAR.
WHY WERE YOU OUT OF
SCHOOL FOR SIX WEEKS?
I WAS SICK.
I'M NOT HERE TO LECTURE YOU
OR TO JUDGE YOU, OKAY?
I JUST REALLY NEED
SOME HELP.
I WOULD.
BUT I CAN'T.
YES, YOU CAN.
I'M GONNA TAKE A WILD GUESS,
AND IF I'M WAY OFF BASE,
JUST TELL ME, OKAY?
[ SIGHS DEEPLY ]
YOU USED TO GO OUT WITH JOSH.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT.
I'M GUESSING THAT THE SIX
WEEKS AWAY FROM SCHOOL
HAD TO DO WITH HIM.
DID JOSH HURT YOU?
DID HE RAPE YOU?
I DON'T WANT THIS TO
HAPPEN TO SOMEONE ELSE.
IF YOU TESTIFIED
IN COURT,
THEY WOULD BELIEVE
BOTH OF US.
SWEETIE, I DON'T
WANT TO HURT YOU.
I KNOW YOU'RE
GOING TO DARTMOUTH,
AND LIKE YOUR MOM SAID,
THINGS ARE GREAT NOW.
SO IF YOU CAN'T DO IT,
IT'S OKAY.
I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND.
[ CRYING ]
I CAN'T.
OKAY.
YOU WANT TO LEAVE?
DO YOU WANT TO LEAVE NOW?
IT'S OKAY.
[ SIGHS ]
HOW'D IT GO?
JOSH RAPED HER.
[ SIGHS ]
OKAY, UM...
I'LL CALL BRIAN.
SHE'S NOT GONNA TESTIFY.
DO WHAT?
WHAT? SHE HAS TO.
JUST LEAVE IT ALONE, DREW.
SHE'S HURT.
LOOK, I TALKED TO
BRIAN THIS MORNING,
HE SAID THE JUDGE WANTS
TO PULL THE TRIAL UP.
WHAT? WHY?
I DON'T KNOW, HE SAID
THE GAINESES ARE BEHIND IT.
THEY WANT THE TRIAL TO GO ON
WHILE THE PR THEY'RE
DOING IS STILL FRESH.
I TOLD HIM ABOUT YOUR HUNCH.
HE SAID WE COULD REALLY
USE THAT TESTIMONY.
AND WHAT ABOUT THAT
REASONABLE DOUBT CASE?
HE'S NOT SO SURE ABOUT THAT.
MAYBE --
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE JENNA JUST
DOESN'T REALIZE
THAT IT'S YOUR WHOLE LIFE
THAT'S AT STAKE RIGHT HERE.
SHE CAN'T TALK.
I'M NOT FORCING HER TO.
CHRISTIE, WE NEED THE HELP.
CHRISTIE, YOU NEVER TOLD ME
YOU INVITED JOSH TO DINNER.
WHAT? I NEVER
INVITED HIM ANYWHERE.
YOU WERE SEEN TOGETHER AT
A RESTAURANT AWAY FROM SCHOOL.
NO, HE INVITED ME
FOR A HAMBURGER
TO THANK ME FOR
OFFERING TO TUTOR HIM.
HE HAD BEEN HUMILIATED
BY HIS PARENTS
IN FRONT OF ME AND
THE PRINCIPAL, OKAY?
I FELT SORRY FOR HIM.
HE INVITED ME.
THAT'S NOT THE STORY
THE GAINESES ARE TELLING.
CAN'T WE STOP
THEM FROM LYING?
I WARNED YOU BOTH, OKAY?
A CASE LIKE THIS,
IT'S ABOUT PERCEPTIONS,
IT'S NOT ABOUT REALITY.
I'M GONNA LOSE, AREN'T I?
WHAT ABOUT THIS JENNA GIRL?
NO, NO, SHE'S
NOT GONNA TESTIFY.
SHE'S BEEN THROUGH TREMENDOUS
PRESSURE, AND SHE'S HAD ENOUGH.
IT'S NOT JUST
ABOUT US ANYMORE.
I WON'T HURT THE GIRL!
YOU CAN'T GO TO JAIL.
LOOK, THERE'S
ONE OTHER OPTION.
OKAY? ONE --
YOU'RE NOT GONNA LIKE IT.
SIT DOWN, PLEASE.
WHAT?
ALL RIGHT.
[ SIGHS ]
PLEA BARGAIN.
I CAN'T PROMISE ANYTHING,
BUT WE CAN TRY.
TO GET WHAT?
YOU MIGHT BE ABLE TO GET
PROBATION, NO TIME SERVED.
WHICH MEANS?
YOU'D BE CONVICTED
OF A FELONY,
BUT YOU'D PLEAD GUILTY
TO A LESSER CHARGE.
NO JAIL. NO TRIAL.
PLEADING GUILTY?
FOR HIS CRIME? NO WAY!
ABSOLUTELY NOT!
FORGET THAT!
I KNOW IT SOUNDS UGLY,
BUT I'M AFRAID WE REALLY NEED
TO START THINKING ABOUT THIS.
THANK YOU FOR
COMING, MONICA.
THIS IS REALLY
WEIRD, MS. DAWSON.
I KNOW.
WELCOME TO MY LIFE.
IT'S PLENTY WEIRD,
BELIEVE ME.
IT'S ABOUT JOSH, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
HE ASSAULTED ME.
I DIDN'T ASSAULT HIM.
I CAN BELIEVE IT.
HE'S A TOTAL HORN DOG.
I MEAN, WHEN HE
DOESN'T GET IT...
HE GETS VIOLENT?
HE EXPECTS IT, I MEAN,
HE KNOWS WHAT A BABE HE IS.
HE...GIRLS PRACTICALLY
THROW THEMSELVES AT HIM.
AND IF A GIRL REFUSED HIM?
HE WOULDN'T THINK IT WAS,
LIKE, VIOLENCE OR ANYTHING.
JUST, YOU KNOW,
CUTTING THROUGH THE CRAP.
WOULD YOU BE
WILLING TO TESTIFY?
AT LEAST WITH MY LAWYER.
AND YOUR PARENTS
COULD BE THERE.
[ LAUGHING ]
LIKE I'M GONNA TALK ABOUT
SEX IN FRONT OF THEM!
LOOK, I REALLY...
I DON'T THINK I HAVE ANYTHING
TO SAY THAT WOULD HELP YOU.
I MEAN, HE NEVER
REALLY HURT ME.
OKAY.
I'M SORRY, MS. DAWSON.
I BETTER GO.
♪ I WALK THESE STREETS ALONE ♪
♪ AND I DON'T KNOW
WHERE I'M GOIN' ♪
♪ LIFE BURNS FAST AND BRIGHT ♪
♪ AND IT SHOWS
NO SIGNS OF SLOWIN' ♪
♪ I TAKE THESE DREAMS OF MINE ♪
♪ AND I TURN THEM TO THE SKY ♪
♪ I TAKE THESE SCREAMS OF MINE ♪
♪ AND I BURY THEM ALIVE ♪
♪ I TAKE THESE DREAMS OF MINE ♪
♪ AND I SPREAD
THEIR WINGS TO FLY ♪
♪ I TAKE THESE SCREAMS OF MINE ♪
♪ AND I LET THEM TESTIFY ♪
Drew: TELL US ABOUT
THE PLEA BARGAIN.
OKAY, IF I CAN GET IT, WE PLEAD
GUILTY TO A LESSER CHARGE,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT, BUT IT
WILL HAVE TO BE A FELONY,
AND A FELONY WILL
FOLLOW YOU FOREVER.
YOU'LL DRAW SOME
KIND OF SENTENCE
WHICH WE'LL GET
COMMUTED TO PROBATION.
THEN YOU START
YOUR LIFE OVER AGAIN,
AS FAR AWAY FROM
HERE AS POSSIBLE.
I AM SO SORRY.
I'LL, UH...
I'LL WAIT OUTSIDE.
I CAN'T DO THIS.
I KNOW.
BUT WHAT ELSE CAN WE DO?
WHAT CHOICE DO WE HAVE?
WE FIGHT. WE GO TO COURT.
I'M INNOCENT, DREW.
WE WIN THE CASE.
BRIAN SAYS OUR CHANCES
ARE LESS THAN 50/50, OKAY?
WHAT IF YOU LOSE?
ARE YOU GONNA HAVE
THAT BABY IN PRISON?
NO. NO WAY.
EXACTLY.
THEY WANT ME TO ADMIT
I'M A CHILD MOLESTER.
HOW CAN I POSSIBLY SAY THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT LOOK, OKAY, LET'S IMAGINE
WE TAKE THE PLEA BARGAIN.
I MEAN, WHAT REALLY HAPPENS?
WE MOVE. WE START OVER.
WE HAVE A CLEAN SLATE.
YOU DON'T GO TO PRISON.
THE BABY IS UNTOUCHED
BY ALL OF THIS CRAP.
I MEAN, ISN'T THAT
THE LEAST OF ALL EVILS?
I DON'T KNOW.
I WANT TO FIGHT.
YEAH, ME TOO...
BUT UNLESS JENNA TESTIFIES...
NO, DON'T GO THERE.
I'M NOT GONNA DO THAT TO HER.
THEN WE'RE STUCK.
YEAH.
IN THE INTERESTS
OF THE GAINES FAMILY
AND OF THE COMMUNITY AT LARGE,
THE OFFICE OF
THE DISTRICT ATTORNEY
HAS AGREED TO A PLEA BARGAIN
WITH MRS. CHRISTIE DAWSON.
THE DEFENDANT HAS PLEADED
GUILTY
TO THE LESSER CHARGE
OF CHILD ENDANGERMENT
AND HAS AGREED NEVER TO WORK
AROUND CHILDREN AGAIN.
NOW THE GAINES FAMILY
WOULD LIKE TO PUT
THIS INCIDENT BEHIND THEM
AND MOVE ON WITH THEIR LIVES.
WE FEEL THAT IDENTIFYING
CHRISTIE DAWSON
AS A SEXUAL PREDATOR
BOTH PROTECTS OUR COMMUNITY
AND TAKES INTO ACCOUNT
THE SPECIAL NEEDS
OF HER VICTIM.
THANK YOU.
[ REPORTERS SHOUTING ]
UH, IS MS. DAWSON HERE?
WHAT, JENNA?
YEAH.
COME ON IN.
COME ON IN. SIT DOWN.
THANK YOU.
YOU MUST REALLY HATE ME.
YOU MUST BE REALLY MAD AT ME.
NO, NO, WE'RE NOT.
UM, CHRISTIE IS JUST
DOWN AT THE SCHOOL
PICKING UP A FEW THINGS.
UM...WE'RE LEAVING.
I FEEL LIKE PART OF
THIS IS MY FAULT.
NO, NO, LET'S GET ONE
THING STRAIGHT HERE, OKAY?
THERE'S ONLY ONE PERSON TO
BLAME HERE, AND IT'S NOT YOU.
AND IT'S NOT CHRISTIE.
YOU HEAR ME? GOOD.
UM, CAN I GET YOU
ANYTHING, A DRINK?
SOME WATER, PLEASE.
SURE.
[ SIGHS ]
[ TAP RUNNING ]
JENNA!
COME IN.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HERE ON A SATURDAY?
YOUR HUSBAND TOLD ME
YOU WERE HERE.
I CAME TO TELL YOU HOW SORRY
I AM I COULDN'T HELP YOU.
NO, JENNA, DON'T FEEL BAD.
I WON'T ALLOW IT.
BUT YOU'RE SUCH
A GOOD TEACHER.
WHEN I HEARD THAT THEY
WON'T LET YOU TEACH ANYMORE,
I FELT SICK.
THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW, I HAD A CHEMISTRY
TEACHER IN HIGH SCHOOL
WHO COMPLETELY INSPIRED ME.
HE GAVE ME THIS PERIODIC TABLE.
TAKE IT TO DARTMOUTH.
I DON'T DESERVE THAT.
YES, YOU DO.
I AM SO PROUD OF YOU.
THANKS, MS. DAWSON.
YEAH...
I'M READY NOW.
I WANT TO TESTIFY.
NO, JENNA, NO, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO DO THAT.
I'M FINE WITH MY DECISION.
REALLY, I'M READY NOW.
I CAN DO IT.
I WANT TO DO IT.
DON'T.
DON'T THROW AWAY DARTMOUTH.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I KNOW HOW EXPENSIVE
THAT SCHOOL IS.
AM I RIGHT THAT THE GAINES
WERE GONNA PAY FOR IT?
I SAW IN YOUR RECORD THAT YOU
DIDN'T HAVE A SCHOLARSHIP.
IT WAS WRONG.
I KNOW IT.
MY MOM DIDN'T WANT TO
PUT ME THROUGH A TRIAL.
SHE SAID I WAS TOO SICK.
BUT SHE WANTED THEM
TO PAY SOMEHOW.
OH, THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
NO, NO,
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
DON'T EVER SAY THAT.
YOU DIDN'T INVITE
JOSH TO RAPE YOU.
NO, BUT I DIDN'T
STAND UP TO HIM EITHER,
NOT FOR YOU OR FOR ME.
BUT I CAN NOW.
PLEASE DON'T STOP ME.
WHEN YOU ASKED
ME TO TESTIFY,
YOU SAID THAT TOGETHER
WE COULD BEAT JOSH.
DON'T YOU BELIEVE THAT
ANYMORE?
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE
READY FOR ALL THIS?
POSITIVE.
YOU'RE GONNA BE A GREAT MOM.
THANK YOU.
♪ RUNNING IN CIRCLES ♪
♪ LOST IN THE WORLD ♪
♪ SO HELPLESS AND ALONE ♪
♪ I WAS AFRAID ♪
♪ I COULDN'T MAKE IT
ON MY OWN ♪
I AM SO PROUD OF YOU.
♪ BUT THEN YOU REACHED FOR ME ♪
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
♪ AND EVERYTHING CHANGED ♪
I'M NOT TAKING YOUR MONEY.
WHAT?
I'M GOING TO THE COPS.
GOD, THAT FELT GOOD!
I WILL BE DISCUSSING THIS
NEW INFORMATION WITH THE DA.
GREAT, BUT I REALLY
THINK YOU SHOULD CONSIDER
PRESSING CHARGES
AGAINST THE GAINES BOY.
ONE STEP AT A TIME.
FAIR ENOUGH.
♪ NOW I CAN SEE THE LIGHT ♪
♪ AND I NEVER
HAVE TO BE AFRAID ♪
♪ AND MAKE EVERYTHING
ALL RIGHT ♪
OKAY, CLASS?
SO DEPENDING ON THE DIRECTION
OF THE HYDROGEN-ION TRANSFER,
SOLUTIONS CONTAINING
HYDROLYSING SALTS
MAY BE EITHER ACIDIC OR BASIC.
WHY IS THE PROCESS
CALLED HYDROLYSIS?
RICK?
UH, BECAUSE ITSPLITS A HYDROGENN
OFF OF A WATER MOLECULE?
EXACTLY!