Okay.
Billy Moore!
- No, no, no.
- I want to fight! I have to fight.
I have to fight.
- Got the money?
- Yeah, man.
Nice.
You there?
Okay.
I don't know what you're saying!
I don't know what you're fucking saying.
I don't understand.
- William.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
I have something special for you.
I have something special.
Take it.
It's heroin.
Take a seat.
You okay?
Okay?
You okay? Hey.
You...
We are the same.
I...
Yeah.
You!
You.
Look at me.
Look.
Dead.
Come on...
I'm your friend.
I am Tiffany.
My name is Tiffany.
I am so beautiful inside.
You're sick.
If the guards find anyone gambling,
smoking, or tattooing,
you'll be punished.
Understand?
Stand up.
Walk to the dormitory.
Stay in line. No talking.
Get off me!
Get off! Get off!
You want to fucking fight?
Your name?
Billy.
- Billy.
Surname?
Moore.
- Billy Moore.
- Moore.
- Police?
You police?
Yaba.
You sell yaba?
- Yeah.
- Yaba. You sell yaba.
Sit down!
You have money?
- No.
- No?
You work?
Boxer. Boxer.
Boxer?
You understand? Listen.
You understand?
More...
Yes, I understand.
No, no cock.
- No cock?
- No cock.
No cock. No more?
No more.
Stand up, Billy! Stand up!
Twenty.
Listen. Twenty.
One.
No.
Go on.
- Eleven, 12, 13, 14, 15.
- Quick! Quick! Quick!
Stand up!
What are you doing now?
Don't fucking touch me!
Fuck off!
Yeah.
You! Don't speak!
Okay?
You...
Sit down!
All right?
I need painkillers.
I don't have.
What do you mean you don't have?
You're an infirmiry.
I'm told you do tramadol for free.
Not free for you.
What do you mean, it's not free? I've just
seen you give it to five people in a row.
You need to pay.
No, I've got no money.
I've got no money. I've been told it's free.
You have cigarette for me?
I don't have no...
I have no cigarettes, okay?
I've got no pull here.
And I just want tramadol.
This is not right.
Give me the... no, fuck you!
Who wants to fucking go next?
You love ladyboys?
Hey.
Yes.
You remember me?
I just wanted to...
say thank you...
for the other day.
For what?
For helping me when I was in a bad way.
Okay.
And I wanted to ask as well
if I could get some cigarettes.
Your family put money in your account, right?
I've got no family.
No family, no money, no cigarettes.
I'm gonna get some money
next week, okay? In my account.
I need you to borrow me some
cigarettes. I'll pay you back.
I give you only one.
- Which one?
- Red ones.
Tell me your name, please.
Billy.
- What's your name, by the way?
- My name is Fame.
- Nice to meet you, Fame.
- Nice to meet you, Billy.
Can I just get one more packet, please?
Why is the fan blade missing?
- Cell Boss! Where is the blade?
- I don't know, sir!
How the hell don't you know?
Everybody! In the yard!
Someone got killed.
I found yaba, sir.
It's not mine.
Confess, Billy.
Look, this is mine.
That's mine. That's my top. That's my top.
This is definitely not mine, I swear to God.
That's not my shirt! That's...
No, that's fucking not mine!
Look, it doesn't even fit!
It doesn't even fucking fit.
Look! It's fucking too small.
I swear, it's not mine.
I promise you, it's not mine.
Hey. Hey, the heroin.
Get inside.
Hey, you.
Yaba.
My yaba.
It's from a ladyboy.
Ladyboy?
You got the stuff, man?
Step back.
Fuck you!
Where is your fucking heart, man?
Where is your fucking heart?
You just pay me.
If you don't have money, the Muslim guys...
just beat them for me.
Smash them.
They're not good for my business.
I'm not gonna beat up
some fucking Muslims, all right?
You're a boxer, man. Don't be scared.
I'm not fucking scared.
I don't give a fuck about that.
I'm not scared. I'll beat up everyone
in this fucking prison if I have to.
I'm saying to you I just need a hit now.
If you fucking give me a hit now,
I'll fucking do whatever you want, man.
I'll do whatever you fucking want.
They almost died.
Take it.
I told you, just beat them,
not try to kill them.
Take it.
Billy!
Family visit...
for prisoner William Moore!
You see me?
I'm happy to see you.
Are you okay?
I had a fight.
I won.
Number one.
I'm sorry to see you like this.
It's all right.
Take care...
Billy.
Stop!
Sit down!
Why don't you care about each other?
You eat together.
You sleep in the same room.
You do activities together.
Don't you have any sense of unity?
Prison is for men,
not for dogs!
Can't you speak to one another?
Why do you fight?
What is there to gain?
I'm here to train.
I want to train!
Go!
I'm a boxer. I can show you I can fight.
I need to fight.
Let me in.
Come on, just...
Just let me show you, all right?
Same, same. I'm a boxer.
Go!
Come on, man. Let me in.
Hey.
How are you?
Look, I'm sorry about not bringing
the cigarettes back.
I've had a fucking rough time.
And I was wondering maybe
if I could get some more cigarettes.
Join the boxing team.
I want to fight again.
Just give me this one chance
and I promise I'll pay you back.
I sear to God, Fame.
I'll prove to you.
I'll make it up to you.
Hey.
I've got the cigarettes.
Your turn.
Okay.
You fight?
- Boxing.
- Oh, boxing.
I want to bet.
Cigarettes.
- How many?
- Two packs.
My fish won. Hey, two packs.
- Cigarettes.
- No.
- My fucking fish won.
- It wins every time.
My fish won.
Give me two packs of cigarettes.
I fucking won, man.
I fucking won.
Fucking...
The rule is the rule. He won.
No, boss. This prick is tricky.
Follow the rules. How much did he bet?
Hey.
It's from your girlfriend?
No, no, no. Fighting fish.
- Okay.
- I won a bet.
No girlfriend, no family.
No, no girlfriend.
I wanted to apologize, actually.
Because...
I lied to you about my dad.
Not having a family.
I've got a dad, I've got brothers.
They don't know I'm in prison.
It's okay.
Why are you in here anyway?
I killed my father.
Why?
He beat me.
He was not happy with who I am.
Sorry.
Put 'em up, man. Put 'em up.
Put 'em up!
Put 'em up.
William.
Just fucking do it.
See and decide.
You... No! Okay?
Again.
Strong.
Okay.
Hey.
78.
Hey!
Fucking go!
Your fight at Songkran was a fucking mess.
You will be transferred.
You're going to move to the boxing team cell
and share their privileges.
You're the first foreigner to compete
to qualify for national tournament.
Consider this an honor.
The tournament will take place
in another prison.
You have only two months to train.
If you don't want to represent
our prison, say now.
I can.
- I want to fight.
- Good.
Thank you, sir.
Wait.
From your father.
Thank you, sir.
William Moore.
See you later, man.
Look after yourself, all right?
When I was arrested,
I pleaded guilty for my girlfriend.
I got five years.
When I realized I was gonna
be in for five years,
I went wild.
I killed three people
in prison, stabbed them.
Three. Three people.
He killed three.
It's been 13 years now.
Seeing people leaving this prison
makes me want to go home.
So I joined the boxing team,
trying to be a better man.
You know what you get from being a boxer?
Your life inside here is better
than any regular prisoner's.
Sometimes, you can fight outside
and see your family.
Even if it's just for a few minutes,
it warms your heart.
Me...
South Thailand and Bangkok.
- I killed...
- Two people.
My family is poor,
so I decided to be a hitman.
Life sentence for a hitman.
William.
You...
No good.
You start here.
- Okay?
- All right.
Go, William.
Fame.
Hey, sorry, I'm busy now.
I'm busy now, okay?
I'm not talking to you.
I'm not fucking talking to you!
Come here!
I fucking want to know!
I want to fucking know!
Come over here. You're a fucking liar.
You're a fucking liar!
I said fucking hit me!
Fucking hit me.
Come on. Fucking hit me.
Come on. Fucking hit me, man.
Fucking hit me then, okay?
Fucking hit me!
Hey! Fucking hit me.
Hey!
Hey, I'm sorry, okay? I fucked up.
- I made a mistake.
- Sorry?
Look, I'm fucking sorry.
This song is about a woman
who is ready to wait forever
for the man she loves.
Okay. One more!
Hey, Billy.
Money!
I'm gonna get your money, all right?
I'm gonna get it.
I've got a fight coming up.
I'm gonna win, okay?
I'm gonna win. I'm gonna fight.
I'm gonna fucking win, all right?
I'm gonna fucking win, okay?
I'm gonna get the money for you,
all right? I'm gonna win the fight.
No.
I got AIDS. You want?
You lose...
I'm okay.
I've got to tell them I'm coming up.
It's all I've got.
The reason you have a rupture
is because of boxing
and the massive abuse of drugs and alcohol.
Any more trauma and frankly...
you could bleed to death.
Look, Mr. Moore.
I'm sorry.
I'll keep my guard up.
William Moore.
Okay.
Okay?
- Billy!
Billy!
Hello?
William Moore.