This is a bad address.
Did you see that, man?
Damn, boy.
Why do you have to park
this raggedy-ass piece of shit...
...in front of us like that, huh?
Move.
No shit, man.
Where you going, boy?
Man, I know that dude from somewhere?
On your knees I say, slave.
Stay.
Hey, good looking. Can I help you?
I have the wrong number, sorry.
Let's sex and...
Beg more. Beg me. Beg me.
-Yes, yes. You love it.
-Great.
You are my slave. Yes, you are my slave.
You like licking my... don't you?
I know. Yes. Come on.
I'm gonna get this dude, man.
Come on. Let's go.
Should I begin to...
Hi.
I was just wondering maybe if you know...
Thanks.
Go ahead.
Hey, Jorge. Wanna play?
Hey, chica. What's happening?
Howdy, Jorge.
-Thank you.
-Okay, Jorge, you've been a bad boy.
-You are in the wrong address.
You can't just walk into my home.
Where is your warrant?
I don't have one. I don't need one.
You skipped on your bail.
-Now, you've been a bad boy.
-That's bullshit.
I know my rights, man.
This is none of your business.
This man is a fugitive.
Ain't we all? Unlock him.
Unlock him, motherfucker.
Come on!
Okay.
You do it.
Shit.
You're dead, mister.
This is definitely a bad address.
-He's at the roof.
-Come on.
Go. Go. Go.
Wait. Let's talk about this, okay?
Is that a no?
I'm getting too old for this.
Yeah.
Shit.
Remember me? Trey. Trey Washington.
I did eight years because of you!
Yeah, I remember you now.
I remember and it should have been 20.
I'm gonna kill you the right way.
I'm gonna kill you.
Boy, that's good. That's real good.
-Oh, you want the keys.
-I just trying...
Be right back, cowboy.
Hey, Sonny, my boy. Good to see you.
Come on in. Come on in.
How you doing, Murray?
Where's the doughnuts?
What do you mean? There's no doughnuts.
Fine.
Here's the docs on Jorge,
I brought him into county yesterday.
Put them down.
Everybody puts them on the pile.
They know I'm good for it.
They know I'm gonna get to them.
Except you.
You're just like your father.
All right, all right, all right.
Okay, okay. Perfect.
One, two, three, four. Four hundred. Okay.
You got to sign for it.
Excuse me.
Sorry. We are looking for Mr McLaine.
It's McLaine. Sonny McLaine.
I am Lazlo, this is my wife, Eva.
Is bad time?
No, what can I do for you?
We have restaurant,
"Best Russian food served."
Okay? So?
Our son, Jonish, is wild boy.
He always in trouble with the police
ever since we come here.
He steal cars. Go to jail.
We put up our business for bond,
and he run away.
Now we will lose our bond
if he for not come home...
...for to face judgment.
Look, I'm not a private detective, okay?
I don't work on a direct basis. I'm sorry.
But people in the neighborhood,
our friends from old country,
they told us to come to you.
There's really nothing I can do.
I'm sorry.
Please Mr McLaine,
we do not know where else to go.
We pay you 20 thousand dollars.
More if you need.
No, no, no. It's not the money, okay?
It's not the money at all.
You are our only hope.
If Jonish does not come back home
for to go to court, we lose the bail.
We lose everything we work for.
Everything.
Now, we think he go to cabin.
We have in the hills.
Map and directions,
here in your hands now.
Look. You should call the police. Okay?
They'll gather him up for you.
I'll give you a name
and a person to contact.
Okay? You just tell them
that Sonny McLaine sent you.
He will hurt someone.
Or someone will hurt him.
We think it is better to
stay away from police.
It is for the best.
Half the money now.
Half when Jonish is back.
My wife, she make the Russian dessert
for restaurant,
best Russian you,
for you have ever get eaten.
God bless you.
-I'm home, babe.
-I'm up here!
How's my boy?
No. You mean, how's your little girl?
-Okay. As long as it's healthy.
-It could be a girl.
-It could be a girl. I know.
-As long as it's healthy, right?
Hey, Sonny.
When are you gonna learn how to duck?
Let me go get some ice. Here. Hold this.
Wait a minute. You missed a spot.
-Where?
-Right here.
Oh, that's a good spot.
Have you talked to Murray?
No. Not yet.
Are you gonna talk to him?
What am I suppose to say?
I have nothing to offer him?
Well, you know
Murray's not getting any younger.
I'm sure
he'd love to have you in the office.
You know the business? You could run it.
It's a hell of a lot better
than almost getting killed everyday.
Case, I'm a bounty hunter,
just like my father.
-I don't know anything about office work.
-Yeah.
-I'm not sure I even wanna.
-Yes, I...
You know, all I want, is to be with you.
To be a good mother.
And to teach a few computer classes,
you know?
And, that is gonna be
a hell of a lot harder...
...if you go and get yourself killed.
I mean, you know, is it too much to ask...
...for you to do something
a little less dangerous?
No. I mean, I don't know.
I don't know.
-I love you, Sonny.
-And I love you too.
Nothing is gonna happen. Okay?
Nothing will ever happen.
I won't let that happen to you.
I love you.
-Hey, Tony.
-Hey, Sonny. Have an apple.
-Thank you. Everything okay now?
-Good. Better now. Thanks. Yeah.
Thanks. Okay. Gotta go.
So, how's Lisa?
-It's Casey.
-Yeah, I knew that.
-She's pregnant.
-Hey, hey, hey.
Hey. Salud.
To fatherhood.
The best thing any man can do
with his life.
How would you know that?
You don't have any kids, Murray.
-I had a father.
-Father.
So, he's a big guy?
He's a dump truck with feet, Murray.
Come on.
With the brains to match.
You're thinking "can I take him?"
Time to change tactics.
You're getting too old to duke it out
with these guys anymore.
You gotta outsmart them.
I'm not doing it.
Not for five percent anyway.
Ah, five percent? Now we're getting
to the heart of the matter.
Well forget it.
That's all I can pay on this one.
Here. Take a look at these.
You can have any job you want. All right?
-What?
I mean, you got something on your mind.
Come on. What's bugging you?
Nothing. There's nothing bugging me.
Here, Casey made you a salad.
How about that, huh?
Salad, shmalad.
In the old days we used to go
out for corned beef sandwiches.
Eat like gentlemen. Rabbit food.
Rabbit food.
Thank her for me, okay?
She's a wonderful girl.
-Bye, Murray.
-You hear me?
-Hey, Zeke.
-Hi, Sonny.
Here, throw me the ball,
I'll give you a pass.
He's going and he's going.
-Whoa, you all right?
-Yeah, nice pass.
-Hey, honey.
-Hey, babe.
-What's all that?
-Nothing.
Well, it doesn't look like nothing to me.
What have you got another case?
It is, isn't it?
You know, Sonny, you promised me
one more case and that was gonna be it.
It's always the same story with you.
Again and again.
Another case. Just one more case.
Just another case.
You know, being a bounty hunter...
...and having a family
just doesn't mix, honey,
it didn't work for your family
and it's not gonna work for this family.
Because you won't let it.
You won't compromise.
No, I won't compromise.
Not when it comes to our child.
You have a family to think about now.
It's different.
Well, I like what I'm doing.
Honey, you know, your dad died...
...doing what you do
when you were 10 years old.
I don't want the same thing
to happen to our child.
Hey. Well, look who's here.
Hey, guys. How are you doing?
As your father used to say,
"None of your damn business."
How are you doing, baby?
I was just talking with old Jake here.
-You know what Sonny?
-What?
I had the distinct pleasure
of working with this man,
the best fucking cop.
I told you before, Racine.
You try to kiss me...
...and I'm going to paste your lips
to another part of your body.
That's funny.
He did it again. He did.
Shit. Oh, shit.
Come on. Come on. Oh, shit.
Come on. Right up there. All right.
Tell me something Jake.
Why does this guy
look so familiar to me anyway?
-I don't know. Never saw him before.
-You never saw him?
Then can you do me a favor?
Without getting the cops involved.
Not even Rass, okay?
Hey. Okay, okay, okay. All right. So...
What else has been happening
in your life, youngster?
Well,
besides constantly fighting with Casey?
Let me guess.
She wants you to change your life
for the baby, right?
You don't get married four times
without learning something.
I'm gonna tell you
the same thing I told your old man...
...when he came to see me 35 years ago,
with that same weeping hang dog
expression on his ugly mug.
You're not getting any younger.
You're not beautiful, you're not smart,
you're not rich.
It's a miracle
Casey sees anything in you she likes.
So, you better do
whatever she wants you to do.
-And thank God she...
-Garcon.
Garconette.
Give me one more round
for me and my friends.
No. That's enough. Thanks.
Come on, Rass.
-Jake, Jake. I'm taking him home.
-Yeah.
-Rass, you've had enough.
-Wait a minute. I'm having some fun here.
Yeah, I know you're having fun...
My toe!
-I'm sorry.
-Gosh!
Jake, you got anything
on that Jonish character?
Yeah, his name turned up
in four separate files,
but each one had nothing in it.
-Aw, come on. What do you mean nothing?
-Empty. Zero. Zip.
Somebody swiped everything
or deleted everything.
Be careful on this one, Sonny.
-Thanks, Jake. I'll be in touch.
-Okay.
-Pizza man.
-Pizza...
-What?
Pizza man!
-Hi.
-Who ordered a pizza?
I don't know. Ugly guy, long hair.
He said deliver it up here,
and you'd pay me.
-Well, what's on it?
-What's on it?
Well, looks like we got some pepperonis,
some little black olives.
Any anchovies?
Anchovies? Yeah, looks like
there's some anchovies right there?
Double on the cheese, too.
And we got your basic...
Nice, huh? Can I come in?
-Who sent you to kill me?
-Kill you? Nobody.
Your parents want you home, that's all.
My parents? My parents are dead.
I buried them both 10 years ago.
Any idea why someone sent
a bounty hunter to collect you?
Oh, P-38, nice.
I don't know.
But if you leave,
maybe you'll live to find out.
What's that suppose to mean?
"Jonish Kukoc."
You damn, pig.
To much pizza. So there, pretty go.
You piece little shit.
Three hundred pounds.
This is a set up.
You're going to get me killed.
Oh, shit.
Go to that side.
-Who are those guys?
-They're gonna kill us both.
Who the hell are they?
Hey, are you listening to me?
They're going to kill me,
and they're going to kill you, asshole!
Will you calm down?
-You're dead man.
-Yeah, I do get that feeling.
Now let's find out why.
Yeah, Rass, this is Sonny.
Can you do me a favor.
I need you to run a name
through the computer for me.
Yeah. Yeah, I'll check for you.
-What's his name?
-Jonish Kukoc.
Jonish Kukoc. Jonish Kukoc.
Is he a client of Murray's or what?
Jesus.
Go around!
Ah, Jesus.
You trying to outrun them in this...
this cowboy Yankee piece of shit.
What, you got a better idea?
-Give me a gun!
-I can't give you a gun.
They're gonna kill both of us.
-Give me a gun!
-Under the seat.
Get off of me! Get off! Get off!
Hurry! Run!
You bastard!
This is your lucky day, Sonny McLaine.
I guess we'll talk a little later.
How do you get into these jams, junior?
-Anybody want a beer?
-Yeah, I want a beer.
They beat you up pretty good there,
Sonny-Boy?
Yeah, one of them
had this big old ring on.
So you said.
Yeah, that's what I said.
What? You doubting my word?
No. No. It's just that you got
a lot of questions to answer.
You left a trail of bodies out there.
Yeah, well, one of which was almost mine.
Keep on pushing, and it will be.
Hey, look. I believe you,
but you got to convince the DA.
It was your gun at the scene.
And your bullets in that guy's back.
Stop being on my side, will you, Rass?
You got yourself
right in the middle of it.
At least we got a picture of the bruise
before it spread out too much.
That's a solid lead.
Too bad
he didn't hit you a few more times.
All the better
for making a lasting impression.
Uh-oh, here comes trouble.
-What?
-It's Casey.
Casey?
I called her at the school.
All I told her
was that you were in an accident...
...and you wrecked your truck.
-Yeah, but she's gonna be all upset now.
-Aw, man. Give me a break.
-What break?
-What happened?
Oh, he's all right, Casey.
He just got a concussion.
-A concussion!
-Here's his medication.
-This is great. What have you been doing?
-I'll see you later.
You have medication and everything?
-What did the doctor say?
-It's Jake's fault.
-Good-bye, guys.
-Good-bye, champ.
It's Jake... Honey don't do this.
Don't do this.
She's crazy to marry that girl.
Yeah, and he's crazy not
to quit this line of business.
Especially with a kid on the way.
Are you sure you're okay
driving around with that?
Yes, I'm fine.
I mean, I'm just worried about you.
I know, but I'm gonna be fine.
Really. I'm going to be okay.
Okay.
Now, we will take better care of my truck
than we did your truck, won't we?
Right.
Please?
This is a set up.
We got friends from old country,
they told us to come to you.
Who sent you to kill me?
My parents are dead.
I buried them both 10 years ago.
Any idea why someone sent
a bounty hunter to collect you?
They're gonna kill us both!
They're going to kill me
and then they are going to kill you!
You're a dead man.
He's in there.
-What did you do, lose your wallet again?
-Oh, yeah, well, yeah, yeah.
Uh, yeah, thanks for coming by.
I wanted to talk to you.
Sit down. Sit down.
Okay.
What?
Uh, well, it's one of those
good news, bad news things.
I'm being charged with murder right?
What's the bad news?
The good news is
I've been assigned to the case.
Good.
Good. Here.
-No, no, no...
-Please, Murray, I know...
I know, Sonny, we were lucky
that they granted bail.
I'm gonna have to take your house
as collateral, all right?
-Yeah, right.
Now, listen to me, the bonding company
would never let me...
...have something this big on
the books without collateral.
They'd shut me down.
-You're serious.
-Yeah, I'm serious.
-What's worrying you? Casey?
-Yeah.
Mom's the word. She'll never know.
Okay? My hand to God.
-Yeah.
-All right.
Come by this afternoon
to sign the papers, all right?
We'll order in a corned beef sandwich.
Mr Tuzla wants to see you.
Who?
Sonny McLaine.
You big ox.
-Mr Tuzla.
-Sit down.
If you don't mind, sir,
I'm a little confused.
What the hell am I doing here?
Do you know who Jonish Kukoc was?
One of your people?
He was my sister's child.
I raised him like my own son.
I didn't kill him.
Then who did?
Answer my son.
Two people hired me to find him.
A Lazlo and Eva Kukoc.
-They said they were his parents.
-I know of no such people.
-Quit fucking lying!
-I'm not fucking lying!
-Did you kill Jonish?
-No!
Liar! The police charged you with murder.
Enough, Danny! You have people to meet.
I don't want you to be late.
-Liar!
-Enough!
I know.
You say you didn't kill Jonish,
but he was in your responsibility,
in your custody. Drink.
I will give you only a little time
to bring me the killer.
If not, I promise,
you will join Jonish in his grave.
Mr Tuzla? I didn't kill your nephew.
You know me and you know my family.
Men change, Sonny McLaine.
It is not the same world at dawn
as it is at dusk.
Even if I did believe you, Danny will not.
Go.
Sonny.
Bring me proof.
You turned up nothing, Sonny.
No information. No leads.
No evidence. Nothing.
Pack it in cowboy,
leave it to the professionals.
-Oh, like you?
-Yeah, like me.
-You got a problem with that?
-No, I do not have a problem with that.
Look, you're the DA's number one
with a bullet suspect.
Which makes me even more motivated
to find him.
Oh, listen to me, please.
You can't be involved
with this investigation. Cannot.
As in illegal, as in against the law.
Do you read me?
Okay.
Kukoc was a nephew of Greg Tuzla's.
There.
How the fuck did you find that out?
-Because he told me.
-When?
Never mind when. Does it matter?
Oh, fuck.
We better put you into protective custody.
No, way. No.
All right. Wait a minute, wait a minute.
If you're determined to do this,
ask yourself this one question first.
What was it Jonish Kukoc
doing in that cabin?
Pretty professional, huh?
Another beer, John.
You know,
Casey won't let me eat this stuff at home.
You sound like you already married guy.
Look.
This took more goddamn spade work
than you have dick hairs.
Here it is. The arrest report is a phony.
Where ever that old couple got it,
it wasn't from the police department.
-What about Tuzla?
-He's dangerous, man.
Maybe Racine should put a 24 hour watch
on your house.
Tuzla's old school.
He's not gonna mess with family.
What about Kukoc?
He's wanted by immigration
for being illegal in this country.
Illegal?
He's got a New York drivers license, Jake.
And a green card.
But as part of the information exchange
with the former Soviet Union,
his criminal records caught up with him.
The INS labeled him undesirable.
He appealed and lost.
Before they could deport him,
he disappeared.
Where the hell you get all this?
I mean Rass doesn't even have it.
Unless he's not saying.
Rass is a good cop.
Look, I was a cop for 40 years.
I still have my connections, you know.
Hey, wait a minute.
You're not gonna eat it?
It doesn't taste as good as it used to.
-Hey, Sonny.
-What?
-Be careful.
-Yeah. Thanks.
Talk to me, you fuck. Come on.
Come on. Come on. You gonna talk to me?
Talk to me you piece of shit.
-Big Shot, you scared?
-You fuck.
Look I can make this quick,
or I can make it slow.
Tell me what you know,
and I'll make it quick.
Make it fast.
Fuck you.
Danny!
Put the gun down!
I'm doing what you should have done!
You'll kill him,
when I tell you to kill him!
Put the gun down! Put the gun away!
You, you, out.
Andre will take you where you want to go.
Just do me a favor Mr Tuzla,
you keep your son off me.
I can't do any good
while he's jacking me up...
...in the back of warehouses.
-What happened to you?
-I had a run in.
Do you want to fill me in
on what's going on between you and Tuzla?
Otherwise, what is this doing here?
When I figure it out, you'll know.
You'll be dead before you figure it out.
What about the ring?
I'm gonna get forensics
to enhance the details of the ring.
-Can I have this one?
-No, it's evidence.
Why? What's up?
I'm getting close, Rass.
I'm getting close and this could help.
-See you later, Sonny.
-All right, Rass.
-Say hi to Casey for me.
-All right. All right.
Hey, Jake! You owe me a brew.
Thank you.
-Yeah.
-Sonny, it's Jake.
So, what's up Jake?
Come to 1704 Mission Street.
Apartment 206.
I got some people here
I want you to meet.
Who?
For a little cash,
they'll be whoever you want them to be.
Recognize them?
Yep. The grieving parents, I presume.
Meet George and Bridget McCully.
Blacker Irish souls you never saw.
Fuck you. Thank you very much.
-What happened to your accent?
-I shoved it up your ass, pal, okay.
I want you both
the fuck out of this apartment, now.
You ain't the cops,
so you ain't got a warrant.
Shut up!
I busted these two several
times back in the '80s...
...doing the same gypsy Russian grift.
I thought I'd check them out.
You set me up and I want to know why.
The man who was killed
was Gregor Tuzla's nephew.
Do you know what that means?
It means your buddy's ass is in a sling.
-So is yours, pal.
-Oh, I don't think so.
Why not? You think
you got a guardian angel or something?
Something like that.
That guardian angel wouldn't happen
to be Danny Tuzla, now would it?
You know, Mr Tuzla's not gonna like
the fact that you set up his nephew.
We were in Cleveland last week.
Right, dear?
So fuck off and get out of my home.
The last person that did
that to me, I bit it off.
Real good.
They ain't gonna talk. Call Racine.
You need them on the record
to convince the DA to drop
the charges against you.
It's not the DA I'm worried about.
Yeah, Tuzla will find out about it too.
I'm sure I can beat it out of them.
Right. Leave that to the cops.
-Shit!
-What?
I got Casey's car.
She needs a ride home from school.
Can't someone else take her?
I really don't want her going home alone.
Okay. I'll take care of these two.
You call Racine, pick up Casey.
Come meet us at the precinct.
-Are you gonna be okay?
-Sonny, I was a cop for 40 years.
-Forty years?
-Yeah.
I thought it was 30.
God, whatever. Just get going.
-You should buckle up.
-Next stop light, I'll buckle up.
Is there any way
to make that image clearer?
-To... To what?
-To make it clearer.
Well, you could dither it, I suppose.
-Sonny!
-What?
I thought you were gonna get out of this.
You said you were going to quit.
-I'm gonna quit. I will.
-This is not quitting.
What took you so long?
Over there.
Hold it right there.
I got to go out again, babe.
Hey, what do you mean
you have to go out again.
I have to go out again.
Well,
I was just gonna make you some dinner.
-Well...
-Who's gonna rub my tummy?
Maybe if I stay,
I can rub more than your tummy.
-Good idea, huh.
-Gotta go.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
-Bye.
-Yeah?
-Where are you, Sonny?
I'm just leaving the house.
Did you catch up with Jake?
Yeah, you better get your butt over
to the Lady of Mercy Hospital right away.
Jake's gonna be okay.
He'll be out of op in an hour or two.
Just a shoulder wound.
Go get some rest.
-What happened, Rass?
-I don't know for sure.
One gunman came in,
popped the old couple,
put one in Jake.
Jake tagged him and the guy got away.
Do you have any idea
who might have done this?
The two that got killed
were the ones who set you up, right?
And you had Jake track them down, right?
I wasn't trying to keep that from you.
Well, the big problem with that is,
Jake was nearly killed, Sonny.
What did I tell you
about doing things on your own?
-I feel bad enough as it is, okay?
-Well, isn't that fucking terrible?
Jake's in there almost killed
and you feel bad about it.
Yeah.
I feel bad.
Sonny, I admire you.
A lot like I admire Jake.
But you got to stop playing cop.
Acting like you're better at this
and smarter than us...
...simply because you're allowed
to work on a different set of rules.
Shit.
Didn't your father tell you
to back off, junior?
Junior? That's funny, man.
Sonny?
My father wants to talk to you.
Yeah? Well, I'm not in the mood right now.
-Not in the mood? Not in the mood.
-No.
How about this you fuck?
Fucking big shot.
My father taught me how to make vodka.
I taught Jonish. And I taught Danny.
How do you like my vodka, Sonny McLaine?
I thought we had a deal.
Is it because you thought
I was responsible for your father's death?
Is that why you struck at me
through Jonish?
What are you talking about?
Jonish's best friend, Boris,
saw you shoot Jonish! He was there!
He might have been there,
but he's lying about what he saw.
How is it everyone lies but you?
'Cause maybe they have something to hide.
It had to be someone in your organization
who betrayed Jonish.
Yeah? That still doesn't mean
you didn't pull the trigger.
-Oh, what would my motive be?
-What would your motive be?
Revenge.
Or maybe someone paid you to do it, huh?
You know? Maybe you did it.
Or Boris did it?
I would have died for Jonish!
Either Sonny is lying.
Or Boris is lying. Or both.
Look. Just let me whack him.
There's already talk in the street
about how you're getting soft.
If this talk reaches our visitors,
we won't be able to negotiate.
By sunset Friday, I must have the killer.
-You understand?
-Yeah.
You have until then.
God!
You always loved working with pop, huh?
Me, Murray and your father.
What a group we made.
I'd book 'em, Murray bail 'em,
and your father would bring them back
after they skipped.
You got his chin, you know?
Yeah?
Tell me something Jake.
What happened between Tuzla and my father?
Your mother never told you
how your father died?
Well, she said that...
...he was protecting
someone and he was killed.
That's all she said.
I suppose if I was trying to explain...
...what happened to a 10 year old boy,
I'd say the same thing.
Come on Jake,
you telling me my mom was lying?
Your father was caught in circumstances
similar to yours.
He had collared his man,
and someone tried to make a hit.
They shot it out.
He took one in the chest.
The fugitive drove him to the hospital,
but it was too late.
Gregor Tuzla was the fugitive.
Hey, man. That's no way to greet a friend.
Put that thing away.
What? You here to arrest me?
I should.
You'd be a hell of a lot better off.
You think whoever it is,
won't get me in jail?
Well,
they'd have to come through me first.
Come on. Let's go in the house.
It's cold out here. Come on. Move. Move.
Hemmingway said,
"If you live long enough,"
"you'll see everything you love
in the world die or be destroyed."
You don't strike me as a Hemmingway type.
I memorized it years ago to pick up women.
-Did it work?
-But of course.
Checked with a buddy of mine
in the Organized Crime Group.
Bought him a few drinks.
He told me a few things.
It seems pretty plain to me...
...that there's a power struggle
going on in Tuzla's house.
Yeah,
Tuzla did mention something like that.
-When did you talk to him?
-Tonight.
Aw, man, Sonny. What did I tell you
about withholding evidence?
It's not withholding evidence.
I'm under a lot of pressure, God damn it!
I know you're under a lot of pressure!
I can't give you much more time!
Thanks for coming right back.
-I love you.
-Don't...
Are you gonna talk to me?
Where were you all night?
Jake got shot last night.
He's gonna be okay.
Are you in danger? Am I in danger?
No, I would have told you.
Damn you, Sonny. Damn you!
Case, look, I understand
you're anger, okay,
just bare with me.
I'm going to birthing class
this afternoon, room 103.
Are you gonna be there?
Yeah.
Great. I'll see you there.
Sonny?
Clean the car.
Now these are the men
that were killed outside of that cabin.
All illegal immigrants,
and all Russian Mafia.
The American Russian Mafia
and the Mafia from Russia are merging.
And guess who the OCG thinks
has the point man...
...for both sides for the merging?
Jonish Kukoc.
But he had one problem.
Yeah, he was about to be deported.
But there was one particular person
that was against the merging.
His cousin, Danny?
Tuzla was gonna make Jonish
the head of the organization.
-Jonish pissed Danny off.
-Yes.
And Danny's hot headed
and not overly bright.
Everyone, including Tuzla, knows that.
No one from the Russian Organization likes
or trusts Danny.
But despite his shortcomings,
Danny's very ambitious.
So, Jonish is killed.
And the hit's hung on me,
to keep Tuzla from seeing
Danny's hand in it.
You got it. You were the easy target.
History replays itself.
Oh, shit! Time? What time is it?
Ten to 4:00 PM.
Casey.
The most important thing
about birthing is to breathe.
To breathe.
Breathing from the check people.
Good work, Steven. Wonderful.
Diaphragmatic intercostal muscles
feeling the strain.
Yes, Bob. Yes, wonderful. Imaging.
We are three, yet we are one now.
Wonderful.
-The birthing class? Birthing class?
-On your left.
Second door on your left.
No, no. No, no. No.
Hey, hey. Further down.
The next one on your left.
The second door.
Excellent breathing, Casey. Wonderful.
Yes.
And breathing and breathing.
You must be Sonny McLaine?
I see you've already
begun your breathing.
Please, come in and join us.
The breathing and breathing. Excellent.
Continue breathing. Wonderful.
This is getting tougher now.
-Want some juice?
-Yeah, juice would be good.
Okay. Give me a kiss.
Oh, thank you. Hey.
Hey, get up.
Rass, I need some cars
to Hill Avenue School. And I need it now.
Come on. Move. I got to go.
Just do as I said.
Drop it, the helmet, man.
Okay, helmet, man, let's see who you are.
You keep everyone in that classroom,
-you understand?
-Yeah.
-My wife's in there.
-Okay.
I want you to call the police,
Detective Racine.
-Racine, Racine.
-Fifty-two.
-Fifty-two. Okay. I got it.
-Again.
-All right. Racine, fifty two. I got it.
-Go.
Stay in the classroom!
Stay in the classroom.
-You're gonna be okay. Stay in there.
-What's going on?
We're gonna be okay,
he's calling the police.
I'm sure everything is gonna be fine.
I'm sure it sounds much worse than it is.
I'm sure
he's got everything under control.
No, Anna. Don't go. Anna.
Go that way.
Get back inside!
Go! Get back inside!
No!
No! No!
Rass. Rass.
No ID on the bodies. Probably illegals.
At least whoever's after you
is consistent.
So, Tuzla wouldn't hurt anyone, huh?
This wasn't Tuzla.
Hang in there, Casey.
Can I talk to you inside?
I don't want you going back home.
It's too dangerous.
I have no intentions of going back home.
Hand me my car keys.
Hand me my car keys, Sonny.
You lied to me, Sonny.
You put me and everybody in that class
in danger.
-Wait a minute.
-No! Just stop!
Looks like you need a ride.
I'll walk.
Sorry, Noel. Is Casey here.
Just a sec.
Hi.
I came by to get the picture I gave you.
Oh, okay. Just a second.
This is...
This is as far as I could get it.
-It's good.
-Yeah.
-This is really great.
-Oh, good. Good.
-Okay.
-Wait.
I just want you to know
that I'm really trying...
Trying to get out of this mess.
I'm really trying.
Yeah, I know, I know, Sonny.
I guess, I just have to decide
if I can live with what it is you do.
And you have to decide...
...if you can live without me and the baby
if I can't.
But I thought relationships
were about compromise, Case.
-Compromise.
-Yeah.
They are, Sonny.
Oh, Sonny.
Before you say anything, Mr Tuzla.
The police took this photo
right after the attack.
The man who killed Jonish,
hit me without his gloves on.
-You were hit by a man wearing this ring?
-Yes, sir. The killer.
I think it was Danny.
Yeah, that's the ring.
Very interesting, Sonny.
Because this is Jonish's ring.
The police gave it to me
along with his personal effects.
But I saw that same ring
on Danny's finger.
I gave them both one, several years ago.
So perhaps what happened was,
Jonish fought with you.
That's how you got the imprint
in your head.
But when you saw the ring
on Danny's finger,
you saw a good way to blame him.
No!
No, Mr Tuzla.
Look. I did not kill your nephew.
Your son did...
...and I know you don't want to hear it,
but that is the truth.
And you know what?
He's gonna do the same damn thing to you.
-No!
-Yes!
Who has more to lose
if the merger goes through?
-Danny!
-Enough of this!
You expect me to believe
that now you are on my side?
No.
Mr Tuzla, all I'm trying to do
is save my life and your life.
That's all.
Please.
Hold him
until I come back from the meeting.
-Please.
-We all know your father was a good man.
Howdy, Boris.
Tuzla's not gonna like this much, Boris.
Danny's mad. Not Tuzla.
Before I kill you,
let's see what you got tough guy.
Thank you, sir. Thank you, sir.
Hey!
Come on, what is going on?
Yes, yes.
Oh, nice one. Okay.
Jake, you busy today?
Okay, we're rolling.
Hey, Sonny, don't do nothing stupid.
Thank you all for coming.
We have been a part of history today.
To the new organization.
Which you have all had the insight
to participate in.
May our enemies harvest bitter wheat.
Nostrovny.
-Stop!
-No!
Damn! Sounds like a war zone.
Go.
I'm being killed by my own son?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Why, Danny? Why?
You always thought Jonish was so good.
So pure.
You couldn't see it.
He's trying to push me out. Me, your son.
I know he would of eventually
had me killed. So I...
There is no escape for you.
You've started a war that will never end.
I'll finish it.
And in the end,
I will be the head of this organization...
...with no interference
from the old country.
At what cost, Danny?
I never wanted it this intense.
I account you for killing him.
I should have killed you on the mountain.
Yeah, you should have killed me.
Are you gonna take care of his plants?
Yeah.
You know, Jake.
-The only family Rass had was you and me.
-Yeah.
Rass would have been very proud of you.
Yeah.
He would of been proud
of the both of us, Jake.
Don't let that girl walk out of your life.
-Hi.
-What are you doing here?
-What? What's this?
-It's an agreement between Murray and me.
Fifty-fifty partners
in the bail bond business.
Part of the arrangement
is that I still go out on some cases.
Just the big ones. Okay?
Well, I guess it's a start.
-Hey.
-Yes?
Are you busy this afternoon?
What did you have in mind?
A wedding.
Whose?
Yours and mine.