Amazing!
Nitrogen 7/8.
Oxygen, 21.2.
Better than back on Earth.
Alright, we're heading north.
Single file, stay alert.
Harling!
Sir, I'm sorry, I didn't see you!
Holy!
What the?
Keira!
We're coming down!
Rioting over access
to vaccination has
caused the Prime Minister
of the World Congress to
declare a quarantine of Africa,
suspending all travel to
and from the continent.
The Mexican government has announced
that the death toll has now reached 40,000
in Mexico due to the air pollution crisis.
Residents are warned not to go outside
without proper breathing apparatus.
In related news, a gas mask shortage
in Mexico City has triggered
looting with hundreds
of civilians being shot by police.
Today marks the 10th anniversary
of the India-Pakistan nuclear war of 2058.
Scientists have determined
the continuing death toll
from the radioactive fallout
has reached over one billion.
Latest calculations suggest the region
will be uninhabitable for
at least another 200 years.
It's no damn picnic here, either.
Calron has completed its takeover
of Microsphere making
Calron the largest privately
held company in the world.
And its majority
shareholder, James Carlson,
the richest man--
- Radio off.
Go away, Duncan.
How fast can you get here?
You have any idea what today is?
What?
It's the first day of my vacation.
Canceled.
Word came down from high up.
Carlson?
The man himself.
See you soon.
Morning.
There's a communique for me, Randall Cain.
Thank you.
John, Vickers, good morning, gentlemen.
- Hey, boss.
- How you doing, boss?
Check it out, finally arrived.
Valdez 4400.
That's my little baby right here.
Yeah, well, I think I'm
gonna stick with this.
It might be an antique, but
it doesn't take any batteries.
Can you believe it?
The first day off in months.
I was gonna try and
unwind and have some fun.
Yeah, weren't we all?
Weren't you are gonna go off to Vegas,
spend some time with what's-her-name,
that sexy brunette?
- Yeah, well, what's-her-name
went to Vegas on her own.
Said I was too isshy.
Isshy?
Said living with a foreign
military man was, uh.
You know what?
It doesn't matter, let's go upstairs.
She wanted a nine to fiver, anyway.
Let's introduce her to Duncan.
What's he want with us anyways?
It's not Duncan, it's Carlson.
The man himself.
It's the real deal,
gentlemen, Project Ark.
I thought that belonged
to Harling's team?
What happened to Harling?
Oh, he probably
got another migraine.
You know, cold, hangnail,
something like that.
He might be on
vacation, for all I know.
Tight lid on this one,
strictly a need-to-know.
Whatever, I
just hope we get to kick
some ass because I want some fun.
The day
you learn to have some fun
I'll be the happiest man on this planet.
Cain, nice of you to join us.
Mr. Carlson has asked me to bring you
all up to speed before he arrives.
Okay, Duncan, everybody's
bottled up nice and secure.
What's the big secret?
As you're well aware
our planet is dying.
The Earth's resources have
been depleted beyond repair.
If there's going to be a future
for the human race it
will not be here on Earth.
All the major global
corporations are throwing
in their resources for
off-planet solutions.
GSA's building huge ships.
Alcor has purchased exclusive
rights to colonize the moon.
And, as usual, our Mr. Carlson
has aimed a little higher.
Given Mr. Carlson's roots in
aviation and space travel,
he's come up with a solution
that could save billions
of lives and generate billions of profits.
If we can get it to work.
The Oxygen
Project, what is that?
What I'm about to tell you
is known by less than a dozen people.
50 years ago NASA located planets
with characteristics similar to
the Earth's size, gravity
and magnetic field.
The planet we have labeled Oxygen
has the raw DNA of plant and animal life
that would make it possible
to create a single plant
capable of producing
mass amounts of oxygen.
All the other corporations
are focusing on Project Ark.
We're going ahead with Project Oxygen.
So, what you're saying
is you've discovered
a plant that can produce as much
oxygen as the rainforest used to?
Exactly!
It would take light years just
to send DNA through space which is one
of the reasons NASA abandoned the project.
Not to mention the thousands of years
it would take these planets to develop.
Make that millions of years.
Oxygen is our new precious commodity.
Our discovery will save
mankind from extinction.
Allison, welcome to the party, love.
You told them the part about
the advancement in technology?
Well, I was actually just--
What technology is that?
The very heart of the Oxygen Project,
the one and only thing
that can make it possible;
DST, Deep Space Teleportation.
You're joking?
I don't joke about business.
DST, discovered by the late
Chinese physicist, Yan Pow,
secretly purchased and
perfected by yours truly.
It requires massive amounts of energy
and it only works at
extremely long distances.
Which, luckily, for our purposes,
makes it ideal for this very project.
30 years ago.
Here it is today.
Not very impressive, I know.
Project 2, Project 3 and Project 4.
Each planet, same result,
all but one, Oxygen One.
Here it is 30 years ago
and here it is today.
How is that possible?
That's the trillion
dollar question, isn't it?
Duncan headed up the surface
teleportation project.
The results were mixed.
Duncan?
DST technology is still
relatively primitive.
It took us years just
to successfully teleport
a Unibot to Plant Oxygen's surface.
This disc was teleported back to us.
Now, this is what the bot recorded.
Planet Oxygen has 99.9%
Earth's atmosphere,
a wide variety of vegetation similar
to species found here on Earth
and abundant clean and
clear water sources.
Are there any mammals,
any other signs of life?
Sensors indicate nothing dangerous.
I would think that the biggest thing
we're gonna run into is probably rabbits.
Launch is set for 02:30 tomorrow.
Cain and his team will provide security.
Myself, Duncan and Allison
are the science team.
Gretchen will provide medical support.
My lawyer, Mr. Mason, will make sure that
the possession of this planet
and its resources are legal.
And Miss Bertzyk will officially
record the event for posterity.
What, no marching bands?
Maybe on the next one.
Any other questions?
Yeah, one.
What's the objective?
Explore Oxygen and find
and secure this unique plant.
This is lightning in a bottle, people.
We are on the verge of the most
important discovery in human history.
Well, for those who can afford it.
Right?
What's his job, hairdresser?
I'm tagging along in case you need help.
Mr. Alvarez is responsible
for my personal security.
I thought my team was
in charge of security?
My world, my rules.
End of story.
Well, we'll see you all at launch.
Let's make history, everyone.
I'll need DNA from everyone by noon.
Sure.
Those are full of aluminum.
I'm gonna write you a prescription
for something a little
easier on your stomach.
- Oh, thank you.
- Sure.
Allison.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Thanks.
Duncan?
Thank you for including me in this.
I know it must have been a
pretty tough sell to James.
Not really.
We need a biologist, you're the best.
Besides, he was eager for a chance
to spend some time with you.
I know how he feels.
That was in the past.
I'm on this mission because it's
an incredible opportunity, but that's all.
Yeah, well my door's always open
if you ever want to walk back in.
Tell me something.
Why do you even need DNA?
Well, a computer
copies our DNA to a disc,
then when atmospheric
conditions, thank you,
are perfect, we pinpoint a black hole
and we shoot the genetic code to
a receiver hub that's already been
teleported to the destination planet.
There are two discs; one
to go, one to come back.
Do not lose those discs.
Without the DNA we'd be torn to pieces.
So why can't you just use saliva?
Danger of contamination.
You wouldn't want to mix your genetic code
with something you ate for
breakfast, now, would you?
No, especially since I eat
guys like you for breakfast.
What happened to the first team?
What are you talking about?
James and I may be separated,
but I still know him pretty well.
And one thing I know for certain
is that he would not risk his life unless
he was absolutely sure
that the DST worked.
So there must have been another team
that went through first.
What happened to that team, Duncan?
Okay, let's say there was another team.
Obviously, the
teleportation was successful
or James wouldn't risk it, would he?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Where'd you learn that logic?
Physics or business school?
Do your worst.
Just relax.
You know, you can take
blood from me any day.
This should be sufficient, Mr. Stotzer.
No, no, no, John.
You call me John.
John.
You know with me on this trip you'll be
as safe as a babe in
ever lovin' mama's arms.
I think I feel safer already.
Gum?
Biodegradable.
Maybe later.
Having fun?
Dunc, between you and me and the wall,
what's up with Harling?
I'm sorry, what was that?
Come on, this was his project.
Wondering what you reassigned him to.
What's it matter, Cain, you jealous?
Yeah, yeah, that must be it.
Sorry, Mrs. Carlson,
didn't mean to startle you.
I don't startle easily and it's doctor.
What, uh, what're you looking at?
I don't know.
It's just this last bit
of static that bothers me.
Is there a glitch?
There's a technical
glitch, it just cut out.
There shouldn't be any static.
I've been trying to
access the backup files,
except for no luck.
Maybe I'm just being paranoid.
It's just a bad case of the nerves.
Nervous, about being teleported
20,000 light years away?
I'm still trying to wrap
my head around that one.
20,000 light years.
The very idea just staggers the mind.
We are only human.
We are none of us machines.
It's okay to be afraid.
It's what keeps us alive.
Cain?
The first transmission?
Rations, supplies,
weapons and video equipment.
All readings indicate they
made it safe and sound.
I've sent a temporary
receiving hub for myself.
I'll set up a permanent
hub when I arrive safely.
I'll let you know by sending a signal.
When I do that's the all-clear
to start coming through
one at a time, in the assigned order.
No signal, no one comes through.
Clear?
Okay.
We got our atmospheric window.
It's time.
Countdown will start from
five when I hit the launchpad.
Good luck.
See you on the other side.
In five, four,
three, two, one.
Randall Cain.
When I signed on they
said there'd be travel.
Three, two, one.
How you feeling?
Like a sock that just went
through the tumble dryer.
Give it a sec, you'll feel great.
Obviously, we can breathe this stuff.
Yeah, we're acclimated to much worse.
This all the supplies?
Carry-ons may shift during flight.
Yeah, obviously.
Damn!
Welcome.
How do I look?
You're still ugly.
In five, four, three,
two, one.
Allison Carlson.
In five, four, three,
two, one.
Alvarez!
There's a blip
in the teleporter device!
Help me straighten him out!
Don't touch
him, don't touch him!
What the hell happened here?
Bone deterioration, his
torso structure is gone.
It's gone!
What do you mean gone?
It just didn't make it through!
What was that?
My PDA's gone down.
Alright, talk to me, Duncan.
Too much stress on the system.
I warned you about this!
Alright, what does this mean?
Where does this leave us?
Well, it means we're on our own.
Jesus, what the hell just happened?
Stotzer!
Our only mode of transport back to Earth
just turned that guy into hamburger.
How the hell are we gonna get home?
Obviously, his DNA and the
transporter did a disconnect.
Now, it's a terrible tragedy, I'm sorry.
But every experiment has its downside.
I'll fix this.
You have my word on it.
Yeah, that's great.
That fills me with a
whole lot of confidence.
Alright, alright, we all agree
this is a terrible tragedy.
But let's not forget
what we came here for.
We are currently the first human beings
to set foot on this planet.
Prioritize, people.
Opportunities like this
don't come along every day.
So let's just stay focused on our jobs.
He's right.
We're here, we should make the best of it.
We're stranded here, aren't we?
Nobody's stranded, darlin'.
It's just a little technical
glitch, that's all.
You call that a technical glitch?
It's nothing Duncan can't fix.
Isn't that right?
It'll take time.
Yeah!
Here she is.
Yo, James!
Business calls.
The camera's working perfectly.
Alright, let's get set up.
You ready?
It's the most state of the art camera
on the market and nobody else has one.
It's a thousand to one zoom.
Let's do this.
You ready?
We are rollin'.
I'm James Carlson.
I'm currently standing on Project Oxygen
breathing pure, clean air.
Project Oxygen is an unexplored planet
20,000 light years from Earth.
How I arrived here and the purpose of
this journey will be revealed in due time.
But to more immediate business purposes,
I hereby claim Project Oxygen as
the sole property of Calron Corporation.
My witness.
Carter Mason, attorney at law.
Do not assume that
what you see around me
is merely another corporate venture.
This pristine, unspoiled world represents
a new beginning for each
and every citizen of Earth.
God bless you, God bless us all.
That's it.
That sincere?
- Yes.
- Sincere?
- I'd trust you.
- Alright, let's go.
- Excellent.
Most of the gear made it through.
What do you mean most?
My 4400's toast, man.
Two cases of weapons and electronics
are missing and there's only two cylinders
for the Magnum, one for the rifle.
Two cylinders, six shots
each, for the Magnum.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Seven shots for the Winchester.
Well, we'll make do.
Vickers and I, 12 each.
We gotta find shelter to
make camp for the night.
Stotz, take point this direction, will ya?
On it!
Where you headed?
I'm taking the point, too.
This is a brand new planet
and I'm a scientist, remember?
You don't leave Stotz's side.
Okay.
Nutrition, housing, A-okay.
Alright, guys, grab as much cargo
as you can hold and let's roll.
We're already down a man
so you gotta carry extra.
I'm a lawyer, not a pack mule.
Yeah, well now's your chance
to move up in the world, counselor.
There's nothing you could do.
You know that, right?
I'm the medical officer.
I'm responsible for the life of
every person on this expedition.
Well, you didn't design the teleporter.
It was on my watch,
that's all that matters.
Your line of work, I think
you can understand that.
Alright, let's move.
This is amazing.
Mature vegetation, clean water, pure air.
That's what Earth must have been like
before man came along
and messed things up.
Ain't it great to
breathe without a mask?
Yeah.
This place is pretty much paradise.
What is it, what happened?
I was trailing behind you guys
and I saw something
huge, it was an animal!
Yeah, it must have been big.
And it's damn hungry, too.
Looks like we've made
contact with something.
Yeah, the question is, with what?
Alright, let's get outta here.
Everybody stick together, go, move!
Gretchen,
what did it look like?
I don't know.
It was huge, covered in fur.
I've never seen anything like it.
Everything just happened so quickly.
It grabbed the body and
just dragged it away.
What the hell is that?
Something sure did a number on it.
You mean that mother lost the fight?
2.49 meters, crown to toe.
That's a big guy.
Yeah.
Weight, I estimate about 270 kilograms.
Oh, my God.
What?
This claw.
The posterior end is soft.
What does that mean?
It means that this is a very young bear.
You're telling me this thing's a baby?
I'm just as shocked as you.
It's DNA must have undergone some
kind of radical biochemical amplification
including extraordinary growth.
So what are we dealing with?
Well, I'm not certain, but
my guess is Ursus spelaeus.
It's a prehistoric cave bear.
It's been extinct on Earth
for over 10,000 years.
Bear?
No, this is a monster.
It was the most formidable
predator in its day.
So how does an extinct bear
come to get on this planet?
Somehow its DNA sequence regressed.
No modern bear, even full-grown,
has claws this big or a hide this dense.
The beast that did this stands 4.5 meters
and over 900 kilograms.
That's perfect.
So what else?
They're fast, they're tough.
They're very smart, lived
and hunted in packs.
Their only known enemy was man.
Over 100,000 years ago
our two species were put
into direct conflict
over food and territory.
Man won.
Yeah?
Well, I'm not a betting man,
but I don't like our chances in a rematch.
It's one bear, it's dead.
End of story.
We proceed as planned.
Whatever killed this is still
out there so we gotta be careful.
That's why you're here, isn't it?
Good work, trapped on a piece
of rock 20,000 light years from home
with carnivores bigger
than my company car.
Duncan'll fix the transporter.
You do your job and
keep us alive till then.
Alright?
That's gonna be a bit tough
with limited ordinance, don't you think?
Okay, as security officer I'm exercising
my authority to abort this expedition.
Fine with me.
I don't wanna suddenly find myself
on the bottom of the food chain.
Well, we're not going anywhere
without a working teleport hub.
What happened to the backup?
Obviously, it didn't teleport over.
Yeah.
Well, that should make
Mr. Carlson pretty happy.
You think I willingly stranded myself
on an alien planet with these prehistoric,
man-eating bears on it?
I think you like your job,
and I think you'd do just about
whatever it takes to keep it.
What's going on?
Expedition's aborted,
it's too dangerous.
James, you know that no one wants
to find that oxygen planet more than me,
but I think that Cain is right.
We're all in danger here.
We have to fix that
hub and get outta here.
Listen, Allison, when I want
your opinion I'll ask for it.
This isn't some university lecture hall
full of drunken students.
We're on an alien planet;
of course, it's bloody dangerous!
Every mission of great discovery
is full of danger, and
yeah, sometimes death.
But those who die, they go down
in history as explorers and heroes.
We cheapen their deaths
by acting like cowards.
You can talk so causally about death
and yet you know absolutely
nothing about life.
This mission is too
important to stop now.
We're discovering a new planet
and a new hope for mankind!
Just can the speeches, will ya?
You wanna fire me when
we get back, that's fine.
But out here the contract says that I'm
in charge of all matters relating to
the security and the safety of the team.
So, it's my decision.
And I say we're gonna cut our losses
and we're gonna teleport off
this rock the first chance we get.
Who do you think you're speaking to?
You work for me, damn it!
Yeah, so get the hell out of
my way and let me do my job.
Hey, I found it!
I found the backup hub!
It must have transported
to the wrong coordinates.
It's way, way, north of here.
I can find it.
Just give me some time, I'll find it.
About time something
on this planet worked.
Alright, we move out at first light.
We gotta get to that hub before sunset.
Then we go home.
Sounds good.
James is, um, just always James.
Like winter is cold or like the moon
is made of lifeless rock.
Yeah.
Well, there must have been something
about him at one point in time, right?
Yeah, he really believed in me.
He supported my projects,
but he's changed.
I used to think he was so smart.
Well, he can't be that smart
if he's not paying attention
to a girl like you.
It's a lonely planet.
This should take you right to it.
Remember to turn the beacon off when
you get there and wait
for me to contact you.
Only me.
I don't need the others knowing
the reason why we came here.
One problem.
What if I run into one of
those things out there?
I don't pay
you to ask questions.
No, correction, you don't pay me enough.
I'll double your fee.
Not enough.
I want ownership, 5%
and you double my fee.
I don't like greedy employees, Bertzyk.
Not employee, partner.
That's what it'll cost
you, take it or leave it.
Fine, now go.
I'm gonna need a weapon.
You even know how to use one?
I'm not going without a weapon.
Great, guess I'll go check out our planet.
Say, Duncan, let me ask you a question.
The weapons are missing,
teleporter doesn't work,
replacement hub ends up some kilometers
away from our position.
Can you explain that to me?
It's like I told you before,
the technology's primitive--
Oh, come on!
Carlson's not an idiot.
Wouldn't risk his life on a
teleporter that didn't work.
So that only leaves one
other possible explanation
for why everything's getting
screwed up, doesn't it?
You're insinuating I--
I'm not insinuating anything.
I'm standing right in front
of you and I'm accusing you.
I don't trust you, Duncan.
I don't think you're nearly
as incompetent as you pretend to be.
You need to get that damn hub working.
And if any other mysterious
problem presents itself,
then I'm gonna come straight to
the source and I'm gonna eliminate it.
You're threatening me?
No, no, you have my word on it.
It's a promise.
No!
Vick, what the hell was that?
Where's Bertzyk?
James!
No!
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, Lord!
I'm so sorry about Bertzyk.
I know that she was a friend of yours.
Yeah, she was always loyal to me.
What was she doing out
there all on her own?
It's hard to say.
I guess she probably let
curiosity get the better of her.
James, I think that we should talk.
As far as I'm concerned, we
have nothing to talk about.
So that's it?
There's no discussion?
All this time.
Did you ever, ever care about me?
You know what I care about?
I care about people who stand
by me, no questions asked.
Especially when the chips are down.
Right.
So all that talk about--
What the hell?
Bastard.
Where's Duncan?
I can't find him.
He was here last night.
Have you checked the radio?
No answer.
All his things are gone
and the circuit board
of the hub is missing.
Cain, I don't like these readings.
I think this quake was just the first.
There's a major seismic shift occurring.
The planet is experiencing eons of change
at a hyper-accelerated rate.
The entire surface of
the planet is in flux.
It's literally ripping itself apart.
Okay, how long?
There's no way to know for sure.
Any idea?
Hours, days.
Alright, we gotta find
Duncan before he finds the hub.
He's way ahead of us by now.
Alright, Mason, Carlson,
Allison, you're gonna go with me.
We're gonna hit the valley.
The rest of you pack
up and take the bluff.
Well.
Radio contact at all times.
What if we find Duncan?
I'll deal with him.
Try to keep up.
These aftershocks are
getting closer together.
We gotta hurry.
I need to rest!
There's no time.
Move your ass, Mason!
You're endangering all of us!
I need to rest!
Come on, Mason, just
breathe, but you gotta hurry.
- I know.
- We gotta go.
Come on, give it a try.
Okay?
Allison, come up
here and check this out!
- You've gotta try.
- Alright.
If you don't move
you're gonna get left behind.
Let's go.
Stotzer, can you hear me?
Loud and clear.
We lost Mason.
They lost Mason.
Everyone else?
No, everybody else is okay.
Stick together.
If you get separated they'll pick you off.
Okay, gotcha.
Man said stay close, stay alive.
That's Duncan.
We're losing light, I say we camp here.
We've been going for hours.
No, we don't let Duncan get away.
I'm sure he's beat, too.
I say we continue!
Get this through your head, alright?
It's not a scientific mission anymore.
This is a survival mission,
which means I'm in charge.
You got that?
Look, you wanna go, you go.
You got a 50/50 shot of making it.
Good luck to you.
Fine, we'll camp here for the night.
Get us some firewood.
It's safe to assume I'm not gonna
make the Employee of the Month list.
Well, that makes both of us.
Being on James' bad side
is not a nice place to be.
I'm sorry to hear that.
It's been coming for a while.
In a way it's almost a relief.
Do you believe that I actually thought
this trip might be good
for our relationship?
I'm such a fool.
Like I said, any guy let's
a girl like you get away,
gotta be something wrong with him.
What about you?
Any special girl in your life?
The last girlfriend I had said
I was stuck in a permanent combat mode.
I think the exact words she used,
I think she said I was,
I was disconnected.
Said I treated everybody like a target.
I don't know, you know.
Well, I think that's her loss.
Yeah, I guess James and I have a lot
to talk about if we make it back.
Now see, that's the wrong attitude.
When we make it back.
Yes, sir.
I don't know what we would
have done if you hadn't--
There's a bear right behind you.
- Just, just, shh!
- Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, there's one there, too.
Stay here.
Carlson, get these two, I got this one.
For God's sake, shoot!
Carlson!
What was that all about?
Cain!
Cain.
Oh, my God!
Stotzer?
Vickers, do you read me?
Stotzer, over.
It's Allison, Cain is really hurt.
And Carlson's gone.
Okay, how bad is Cain?
He's out cold.
Okay, Vickers is gonna
try and track your signal.
We're on our way.
You do what you can for Cain, over.
Okay.
It's clear, no sign of those things.
The cave must not be big enough.
Let's hope.
It should give us
protection for the night.
One can only hope.
I gotta go get the
rest of the equipment.
Vickers, you stay here with them.
I'm coming.
How is he?
He's gonna be okay.
He's gonna have one screaming
headache when he wakes up.
So, you and Stotz, huh?
Yeah.
He's an alright guy.
Just don't tell him I said that.
You?
I got a beautiful wife, two great kids.
If I didn't have them to think about
I don't know how I'd get through this.
My head.
Welcome back.
How many?
Wait, how many fingers.
There's five.
Glad to have you back.
I'm tired of taking up your slack.
Where are we?
We're in a cave.
Stotzer and I are gonna take turns
covering the entrance till dawn, you rest.
Yeah.
You can boss us around later, alright?
Alright.
Welcome back, boss.
I'll take first watch.
Hey, doc, I think I messed up my ankle.
It's been killing me.
You wanna have a look at it?
Yeah, sit down over
there, I'll check it out.
Hey, you had me worried.
I got a thick head.
Yeah, I'll say.
So he come back yet?
Who, James?
No.
But if he does I'm gonna break his neck.
Drink this.
Thanks.
I don't think I can
go through this again.
I'm gonna go work.
I might as well find out
everything I can about this place.
You rest.
Hi there!
Well, well, well!
- Yes!
Thank you.
Made it just for you.
Well then, I guess I owe you a dinner.
Yeah, when we get back to Earth.
Steak and ribs, I can smell it.
Steak and lobster.
Look, I promise you
I will get us home.
Gretchen!
It's human.
What, are you telling me
humans developed here as well?
The DNA matrix contained all
the basic elements of life on Earth.
Whoa, whoa, so you mean we gotta
deal with Neanderthals, too?
Not unless they
developed cranial surgery.
This skull has a plate in it.
Whoever it belongs to was just here.
What do you think, about six months ago?
Yeah, possibly.
That's when Harling and his team came.
He had a metal plate in his skull
after taking shrapnel in Mongolia.
What, you're telling me that's Harling?
Son of a bitch!
I knew we weren't the
first people through.
Harling must have been a guinea pig.
Even James wouldn't deliberately
send people to their deaths.
It had to be something else.
Something worth dying for.
Listen, Casanova, you should stop
worrying about your love life and start
watching the front of this cave.
You didn't get enough sleep, Vickers?
Hey!
Man, I will put you
to sleep permanently--
Hey, hey, guys!
Now's not the time to fight.
There's bears out there that
want to turn us into pulp.
Come on!
It sounds like they're
talking to each other.
Sounds like they're
doing more than talking.
Maybe they're still hungry.
Well, there's fish here, so why us?
It could be the end
of a hibernation cycle.
The first awake are usually the hungriest
and the most aggressive.
And there's more of
those things waking up?
Easy, Stotzer!
Don't worry about me, boss.
I'm cool, calm and collected.
Good, now get back on point.
Everybody else inside.
Come on.
What's it say?
The remote hub is going
through a power cycle.
So it's been activated?
Well, maybe, or it could
be the battery cycling
because the power core is failing.
Any way to know which one?
Sorry.
Okay, how far?
That way, approximately two kilometers.
Let's grab the gear.
Allison, you're sure there's no other way?
No, it's straight down.
Should be okay.
It doesn't look okay to me.
We'll be fine.
Alright, we'll tie off here.
How we doing this, chief?
This is the way it's gonna work.
I'm gonna go down first
followed by the two girls.
You two are gonna stay on point up here.
When I give you the signal
you're gonna follow us down.
Alright.
Alright, back into me, I gotcha, I gotcha.
Okay.
Go, just go really slow.
That's it, a little further.
Look up.
Look up, don't look down.
Gretchen!
Vickers, I'm going down.
Oh, God!
It looks like she has internal bleeding.
What happened?
The carabiner must have broke.
Stay down!
Wrong day, buddy.
I still owe you a dinner.
Hey, how you doin'?
The pills are kicking in.
I'm gonna be in dreamland soon.
Can I get you anything?
Some French toast and a latte.
My whole life I've taken care of patients.
Now I am the patient.
It's awful.
How do you do what you do?
I've got nothing to lose.
I don't know, maybe it's time you did.
What?
Found something to lose.
- Stotzer?
- Yeah?
I'll check on you later.
What is it?
Movement.
What do you see?
Gretchen!
Wait, you're gonna hit Gretchen!
I'm going after her!
- No, John, no!
- Let me go!
- John!
- Let go of me!
- Too late!
- No, not Gretchen!
- She's gone!
- No!
Come on, stop, come on!
I always believed that there had to be
a scientific explanation for everything.
Science was the only answer.
Since I've been here I'm
rapidly becoming a skeptic.
Oh, it's the hub.
According to these readings there
haven't been any recent power spikes.
So nobody's using it?
So it would appear.
Well, finally some good news.
That's Gretchen, she's alive!
We don't know what that was.
It's her, damn it, Cain!
I know it's her!
John, I know it's awful,
but you can't go out there, alright?
They hunt in packs.
Come on, they communicate,
they lure their prey.
Yeah, we have no idea
where it's coming from, man.
Cain's right, Stotzer.
They could be trying to separate us.
They're bears, damn it!
They could be trying to use her as bait.
John, just relax.
Okay, come on.
Yeah, right, boss.
Gretchen!
Oh, my God!
I'm here now.
I'm gonna get you out.
I'm getting you home.
Oh, God, no!
Gretchen.
I finished packing
Gretchen's medical supplies.
I hope we can find the
rest of the hardware.
As fast as he was moving it's a good bet
he left a trail we can follow.
I don't wanna lose anybody else.
Yeah, we're getting low on ammo.
Make 'em count.
Long time, no see.
Where you headed, Duncan?
It's not what you think.
Oh, you didn't leave us for dead?
No.
Where's the hub, Duncan?
It's near.
Let's go.
My foot!
Can you move?
I'm trying, I think it's twisted.
Use this.
We're almost to the top.
Hub's just the other side.
Let's go!
Come on, it's not that much further.
Cain!
Everybody down!
Nice shootin', boss.
We can't afford to stop again, let's go.
How far are we from the hub?
I don't know, I haven't
been able to locate it yet.
Why should I trust you?
Cain!
Carlson knew that
the planet is unstable.
The telemetry from the
Unibot confirmed it.
He set us up!
What about the oxygen plant?
It was just a con to get you up here.
So the planet's worthless?
That doesn't make any sense.
No, you're wrong in your assumption
that this planet is worthless.
It's got something to do with what
happened to Harling and his team.
We found Harling's skull.
Oh, my God!
What have I done?
You can make peace later.
I need to know exactly
what's going on here.
Six months ago we sent out a recon party
of five to do very much what we're doing.
Explore the planet and establish
a base for future colonization.
The first party soon discovered that
the planet's unstable and
it's developing exponentially.
It will eventually implode.
The genetically mutated bears
are much smarter and stronger
than anything we've ever seen on Earth.
Then, why?
If the planet can't be colonized,
then why come back here at all?
Because first team
discovered something else.
Something that makes it
unnecessary to leave the Earth!
What is it?
The team had missed three check-ins.
Fortunately, one of them
survived long enough
to program the Unibot to return.
It wasn't like
anything we'd ever seen.
Cellular regeneration
on a macro time scale.
What the?
Carlson calls it 'vida
sera', the serum of life.
So is that why he came here, to find it?
With a perfect sample of vida sera
we can replicate it back on Earth.
Can you imagine?
A vaccine capable of rejuvenating cells
that have been ravaged by cancer!
Lung cells that have been
damaged by pollution!
Mankind can evolve and live
on Earth as polluted as it is.
Let's roll!
Why not just send a bot
to collect the sample?
Why put us at risk?
Because we didn't have exact coordinates
and remote surface scans
came back negative.
Well, you should have told us.
You could have at least--
Carlson swore me to silence.
He said he'd make me responsible
for the disappearance of the first team!
And he gave you a share of the profits.
I didn't think I had a choice.
You still monitoring that hub?
Yeah.
Less than a kilometer to go, that way.
Yeah, we're going home.
Wait a minute, wait a minute!
What about the vida sera?
We've come this far!
It's Carlson's problem, it's not ours.
Think about what it
can do for the Earth.
For the evolution of man!
Cain, Duncan is right.
This may be our only chance
to get ahold of this stuff.
We can't really afford to pass that up.
My job is to protect your ass
and get us out of here in one piece,
and that's what I'm gonna do.
The missing cases.
I told you I sent them!
Alright, let's check them out.
They're empty!
Carlson!
It's empty.
Hey guys, over here!
Without the hub we're stuck here.
Where the hell is Carlson?
I don't know.
I swear guys, I'm a victim, too!
Well, we gotta find him.
He's gotta be around here somewhere.
I bet the vida sera's nearby.
Cain!
No, wait, don't go over there!
No, no, come on.
What, come on!
Shoot me!
We gotta get out of here.
They're gonna pick us
off one by one, let's go.
There it is!
Come on, shoot it!
It's too close to the hub.
Hold this.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna run a distraction
while you two fix the hub.
- What?
- That's suicide!
This is insane.
Come here.
Come on.
Let's go!
Come on!
Okay.
That's it.
Okay, okay, okay.
The circuit board's gone!
Pot roast.
Allison!
You bastard!
Didn't think you'd last this long.
By now, I should learn not
to underestimate my Allison.
I think you've done enough damage.
She got to you, you fool.
You know how rich you can be?
Yeah, maybe, but I'm learning
that there's more to
life than money, James.
Who taught you that, Cain?
Where is he?
He died protecting us.
Unlike you, he was concerned about
what happened to the rest of us.
You're making a mistake.
No, I already made one.
Now, you shut it!
It's your fortune.
Will you hold this?
The lady said shut up!
I got it.
I suppose he's told you he's
innocent of all this, huh?
Duncan!
He should have the circuit board.
Cain!
Oh, my God!
How long's it gonna take
to get it up and running?
It's done.
Get on it.
So, is that it?
The vida sera, it was
so important to you.
You risked all our lives and for what?
So you could be even richer?
What else is there?
Something you don't know
anything about; humanity.
You'll all pay for
this when we get back.
No, no, no, you'll pay.
I'll be filing for divorce.
It's not working.
He's done something to the circuitry.
We need the motherboard.
We're running out of time.
The core tectonics are shifting again.
This whole place is going to erupt.
Where is it?
Cain.
I got two shells left.
Get it out of him.
Point it at him and pull the trigger.
Where is it?
You're not gonna kill me.
I'll blow it off.
Where is it?
My pack.
In the cave.
I think it's a trick.
I'll go.
Caves go on forever.
You need me to find it.
I'll risk it.
Let me go.
- No, no.
- Cain, let me go.
A deal?
I'll take you to the motherboard
if you don't say anything about
what happened here when
we get back to Earth.
We all go.
You lead.
Get up.
Come on, get up, get up.
What would we have done if you'd died?
And why would you give Duncan the gun?
You're full of surprises.
Alright, which way?
Left, it's not far.
It stinks in here.
You okay?
Yeah.
- You alright?
- Yeah.
Cain, I don't think this is a rock.
Duncan!
Cain, hold them off!
Allison, get out of here!
I'm not going without you!
It can only take one at a time, go!
I'm right behind you, go!
Allison!
Thank you all for coming.
As the sole inheritor of
the Calron Corporation
my late husband, James Carlson,
has left me a legacy of healing.
And it is with great pride that
I announce to you our newest product;
a cellular regeneration
compound, Vida Sera.
The miraculous properties of
this compound are already being explored.
Regrowth of cells damaged
by cancer and disease.
Even regrowth of entire limbs.
And I am pleased to introduce to you
our first successful test
subject; Randall Cain.
We've barely scratched the
surface of the serum's potential.
And I pledge to you
now that I will utilize
the full assets of Calron Corporation
and its subsidiaries to ensure
that every man, woman and child on Earth
is given a new chance at
a full and healthy life.
May each of us make the most of it.
This way, please!
This way!