Do Not Re-Post This Subtitle!
This subtitle is free.
OK to Translate.
♪ Impossible, ♪
♪ for a plain yellow pumpkin ♪
♪ to become a golden carriage. ♪
♪ Impossible, ♪
♪ for a plain country bumpkin ♪
♪ and a prince to join in marriage. ♪
A slipper made of glass is just a shoe.
And dreamers never make a dream come true.
♪ Impossible. ♪
Sing-along Subtitles By:
MightyMike77020
Come along now girls.
Hurry up.
Move it.
Quiet down, here comes the prince.
Have any of you seem, Lady Gwendolyn.
Wouldn't you tell me where to find her.
What do you think mother?
Mmm...
It's certainly not the sort
of thing you see every day.
I saw it first.
How do you think it looks on me, mother?
Aagh, awful.
I didn't ask you.
How can a mother choose between
two such extraordinary daughters.
Cinderella, Cinderella!
Yes.
What do you think?
Does it look better on me?
Oh??
Or me?
Ooh!
Well, I don't know much about hats but...
I don't think it flatters
either one of you.
What did you ask her for?
She doesn't know anything about hats.
She said so herself.
Give it to me!
It's mine!
Mother!
Words could never express the joy
of holding you in my arms again.
Be my bride Lady Gwendolyn
and I will pledge to you my
love for all eternity.
♪ The sweetest sounds, I'll ever hear ♪
♪ are still inside my head. ♪
♪ The kindest words I'll ever know ♪
♪ are waiting to be said. ♪
♪ The most entrancing sight of all ♪
♪ is yet for me to see... ♪
♪ And the dearest love in all the world ♪
♪ is waiting somewhere for me. ♪
♪ Is waiting somewhere... ♪
♪ Somewhere for me. ♪
Cinderella!
Have you ever seen such
a lazy girl in your life?
Who are you calling lazy?
Not you stupid, Cinderella.
Who are you calling stupid?
♪ The sweetest sounds I'll ever hear ♪
♪ are still inside my head. ♪
♪ The kindest words I'll ever know ♪
♪ are waiting to be said. ♪
♪ The most entrancing sight of all ♪
♪ is yet for me to see... ♪
♪ And the dearest love in all the world ♪
♪ is waiting somewhere for me. ♪
♪ Is waiting somewhere... ♪
♪ Somewhere for me. ♪
♪ The sweetest sounds I'll ever hear ♪
♪ are still inside my head. ♪
♪ The kindest words I'll ever know ♪
♪ are waiting to be said. ♪
♪ The most entrancing sight of all ♪
♪ is yet for me to see. ♪
♪ the most entrancing sight of all ♪
♪ Is yet for me to see. ♪
♪ is yet for me to see. ♪
♪ And the dearest love in all the world ♪
♪ is waiting somewhere for me. ♪
♪ Waiting somewhere. ♪
♪ is waiting somewhere... ♪
Are you all right miss?
Yes, I'm fine I think.
Here you go.
Just like those royals isn't it.
Not caring if there in anybody's way.
Well I'm sure they were going
somewhere very important.
I doubt it.
Thanks.
Thanks for your help.
Wait. What's your name?
Cinderella.
Beg your pardon?
I like to sit by the fire
and the cinders fly and
my face gets smudged.
Oh.
Cinder Ella.
I like it.
It grows on you I-I guess.
Excuse me.
Tell me Cinderella, what would a man have
to do to find himself in your good graces?
Who wants to know?
Let's just say
a charming stranger.
This charming stranger seems
pretty sure of himself.
But he'd have to get
to know me a lot better
than some girl he just met on the street.
Oh, but he'd like to.
Very much.
Oh my!
I'm not sure I wanna meet this stranger.
I doubt he has any idea how
a girl should be treated.
Like a Princess, I suppose.
No, like a person with
kindness and respect.
You're not like most girls are you?
What do you mean?
Oh nothing.. I didn't mean to offend you.
It's alright.
It's just that I've lead
a pretty sheltered life.
So have I.
Really?
Everyday the same old routine.
Until you just wanna run away and..
never..
And never come back.
I thought I told you never
to talk to strangers!
I'm so sorry stepmother.
I hope I see you again..
Cinderella.
Well hurry up with those packages.
What are you doing?!
♪ The most entrancing sight of all ♪
♪ is yet for me to see. ♪
♪ And the dearest love in all the world ♪
♪ is waiting somewhere for me. ♪
♪ Is waiting somewhere for me. ♪
♪ Is waiting somewhere ♪
Cinderella!
♪ somewhere for ♪
♪ me. ♪
Why?
Why the disguise again your highness?
After I begged you.
I had a wonderful time today Lionel.
No one treated me like a prince.
What a relief to be among real people.
Yes yes, can I tell you something.
Real people are not all they
are cracked up to be. Eh?
Look at me. I am a real person.
Does that tell you anything?
Believe me, they are all out
there wishing they could be you.
Because they have no idea
what it's really like.
Help me out here?
You are rich,
you live in a gorgeous palace,
you have beautiful women
throwing themselves at your feet.
Is there something I am not getting?
I have no life of my own.
Everything's decided for me.
Where I go, what I do, and who I see.
Your highness, this disappearing
thing has got to stop!
It is too dangerous!
It's perfectly safe Lionel,
I am not worried about
you, I'm worried about me!
I cannot keep lying to your mother!
They have laws against that!
If he wants to kill me
why does he not trample
me with his carriage
and get it over with.
Eh.
You wanted to see me mother?
Christopher darling where have you been?
Your father and I were
just talking about you.
Your mother was talking I was listening.
Alright, what's going on?
Just planning a little get
together. Nothing fancy.
- Just family.
- A-ha.
- And a few close friends.
-
- A-ha.
And all the eligible young
women in the kingdom.
Mother!
Were only talking maybe
4 or 500 at the most.
Mother you can't keep doing this to me.
What!
Max, what's he saying?
He saying,
he doesn't want to have another ball.
No he's not!
Mmm.
[Squeak]
[Squeak.]
[Squeak!]
Here we go.
Oh.. Max!
My smelling salts.
ᴹᵃˣ.
Chris, it's really very simple.
All your mother and I want
is for you to be happy.
Happiness has nothing to do with it!
I mean of course, we want you to be happy.
But you do have certain obligations.
What your mother is trying to say is,
we think it's time you chose a bride
and produced an heir.
Someday soon this entire
kingdom will be yours.
Not that soon.
Look, all I'm asking is you
let me choose a bride for myself.
In my own way.
And I guess I have this silly idea that
I want to be in love when I get married.
Like you were.
That's all we want for you too son.
Yes darling, but there's nothing saying
that you can't fall in love at the ball.
You haven't heard a word I've said!
It happens all the time.
Now you should go through the menus...
Where is he going!
Could have been something we've said?
Lionel?
Lionel.
Ahem. Yes your majesty?
Proclamation from the prince..
Excuse me your majesty I..
I couldn't help overhearing,
And I have to say I don't think
the prince sounded like..
Lionel.
Take this down.
♪ His royal highness ♪
♪ Christopher Rupert, ♪
♪ Windemere Vladimir, ♪
♪ Karl Alexander, ♪
♪ François Reginald, ♪
♪ Lancelot Herman, ♪
Herman?
Herman.
♪ Gregory James,. ♪
He'll thank us for it later.
♪ Is giving a ball! ♪
♪ The prince is giving a ball. ♪
♪ His royal highness ♪
♪ Christopher Rupert, ♪
♪ Christopher Rupert. ♪
♪ Son of her majesty, ♪
♪ Queen Constantina, ♪
♪ Charlotte Ermantrude, ♪
♪ Gueenavier Mazy. ♪
Mazy?
Mazy.
♪ Margarita. ♪
♪ Is giving a ball! ♪
♫ The prince is giving a ball! ♫
♪ They've spread the
message far and wide, ♪
♪ the prince is giving a ball! ♪
♪ They say he wants to find a bride, ♪
♪ he may find one at the ball! ♪
♪ Oh, if only he'd propose to me! ♪
♪ I wish that he'd propose to me! ♪
♪ Just leave the hair and clothes to me! ♪
♪ The prince is giving a ball! ♪
♪ And now if you please,
the crown decrees, ♪
♪ some fois de soir with frills. ♪
♪ A silky sateen in aubergine, ♪
♪ a red if someone spills! ♪
♪ A surfeit of meat, a side of ham, ♪
♪ a surfeit of meat, a side of ham, ♪
♪ and lots of beef filets. ♪
♪ Some marbleized steaks, a rack of lamb, ♪
♪ and veal you raise to braise! ♪
Ooh!
♪ Limburger, swiss in gourmandise, ♪
♪ cheddar, gruyère, and bleu. ♪
♪ Chunks of swiss in barrels, please. ♪
♪ Make sure that it's 'holy', too! ♪
Your highness.
♪ Puddings, and pies, and rum souffles, ♪
♪ succulent chocolate rounds. ♪
♪ Cream puffs they can chew away ♪
♪ to gain some royal pounds! ♪
♪ The prince is giving a ball! ♪
♫ The prince is giving a ball! ♫
Children!
Oh!
Whoa!
O-ah!
Hey!
Ahh!
Woop!
Hump!
Whoa!
Ohh.
Hoy!
Ooo!
Ha, ha ha!
Ohh!
Hey!
♫ The prince is giving a ball! ♫
♪ His royal highness.. ♪
♪ 200 orchids, 400 poppies,
600 roses, 800 lilies.. ♪
♪ Christopher Rupert.. ♪
♪ 1,000 oranges, 2,000 plums.. ♪
♪ Windermere Vladimir, Carl Alexander.. ♪
♪ Raspberry, blueberry,
strawberry, gooseberry.. ♪
♪ Francois Reginald, Lancelot Herman, ♪
♪ Son of her majesty Queen Constantina.. ♪
♪ Chocolate cheddar and
Charlotte and Mazy.. ♪
♪ Son of his Caviar, King Maximillian.. ♪
♪ Alfred Ladislaw, Leopold Sydney.. ♪
- Sydney?
- Sydney!
♪ Is giving a ball! ♪
♫ Is giving a ball! ♫
The prince is giving a ball.
The prinMightyMike77020.
Thank you.
Cinderella,
the door.
Oh! Right away.
Ahh.
Cinderella, my wrap.
Cinderella, my hat.
Cinderella, my gloves.
Cinderella, have you dusted the rafters?
Not yet stepmother, I've had a busy day.
You've had a busy day!
Uh yes, I've been in the village with you.
The impertinence.
After your father died everyone
said I should have thrown you out,
into the street.
Be a swan Minerva. Be a swan.
But I've kept you on here all these years
and this is the thanks that I get.
Shoulders back Calliope. Back.
I've always been told
I've got too big a heart.
You've got too big a heart mother.
Will take our tea upstairs.
Come girls, it's time to
get our beauty rest.
We want to be our best for
the ball tomorrow night.
I don't know about you,
but I'm exhausted.
I'm tired too mother.
You're tired?
Yes, I'm tired!
Stepmother?
What is it now?
I was wondering about the ball?
All eligible women in the
kingdom are invited..
And I suppose you think the prince
is going to take one look at you
and fall madly in love.
Ha!
I didn't.. I didn't mean that..
Take my advice Cinderella,
know your place and be
satisfied with what you've got.
I promise you,
you'll be much happier.
Well if my f-father were alive..
Well he's not is he?
He's alive in my heart.
Don't cling to the past Cinderella.
It's not very attractive.
Cinderella, hot water!
Cinderella, warm milk!
Cinderella!
Cinderella, hot water.
Cinderella, warm milk.
Cinderella. Cinderella.
♪ I'm as mild and as meek as a mouse. ♪
♪ When I hear a command I obey. ♪
♪ But I know of a spot in my house ♪
♪ where no one can stand in my way. ♪
♪ In my own little corner. ♪
♪ In my own little chair ♪
♪ I can be what ever I want to be. ♪
♪ On the wing of my fancy ♪
♪ I can fly anywhere ♪
♪ And the world will open its arms to me. ♪
♪ I'm a young Egyptian Princess ♪
♪ or a milk maid. ♪
♪ I'm the greatest prima
donna in the land. ♪
♪ I'm an heiress who has
always had her silk made ♪
♪ by her own flock of silkworms in Japan. ♪
♪ I'm a girl men go mad for. ♪
♪ Love's a game I can play ♪
♪ with a cool and confident kind of air. ♪
♪ Just as long as I stay
in my own little corner. ♪
♪ All alone ♪
♪ in my own ♪
♪ little chair. ♪
Cinderella I'm thirsty!
Ooh that girl is slow.
Cinderella where's our tea?!
♪ I can be whatever I want to be. ♪
♪ I'm a thief in Calcutta. ♪
♪ I'm a queen in Peru. ♪
♪ I'm a mermaid dancing upon the sea. ♪
♪ I'm a huntress on an African safari. ♪
♪ It's a dangerous type of
sport and yet its fun. ♪
♪ In the night I sally
forth to seek my quarry. ♪
♪ And I find I forgot to bring my gun. ♪
♪ I am lost in the jungle ♪
♪ all alone and unarmed. ♪
♪ When I meet a lioness in her lair. ♪
♪ Then I'm glad ♪
♪ to be back in my own little corner. ♪
♪ All alone ♪
♪ in my own ♪
♪ little chair. ♪
Cinderella! Cinderella!
Cinderella!
His royal highness
Christopher Rupert.
Son of her majesty.
- Mother!
- Oh!
Listen to me!
You've got to call this
ball off immediately.
Not possible.
It's difficult to cancel once
you got the ball rolling.
Besides what would we tell everyone.
Tell everyone you went behind my back
and you're very ashamed of yourself.
Ashamed!
I've never had to be ashamed
of anything in my entire life.
I'm certainly not gonna start now.
WOW! Woh!
You know, I probably should not interfere.
Probably! Probably!
Probably!
But, let's say the prince
goes to the ball tonight.
- Trader!
- I like the way that sounds.
Well, if he should find a bride,..
That's wonderful.. but.
If he does not..
Lionel you're brilliant.
Mother,
I'll go to the ball
but if I don't find her tonight,
you'll let me fall in love my own way.
[Squeak!]
With no interference.
No matter how long it takes.
[Squeak!]
It does have the ring of fairness to it.
I suppose.
- If that's what you want dear.
- Thank you.
I love you both very much.
Don't worry your majesty's.
He'll meet someone tonight.
I can feel it in my bones.
You'll feel it in your bones if he doesn't.
Waah!
Oww..
Mother!
My girls are going to be the
envy of everyone at the ball.
Do you really think so mother?
Stand still Minerva.
Our family has always been
known for its fascinating women.
Why, I might have marred a prince
if I had had the same opportunities
- that you girls have had
- Ow!
if I had someone to push
me the way you girls do.
Someone to sacrifice for me.
Mo-mother, you're hurting me!
Beauty knows no pain girls.
Now, let's go over this again.
If I've done my job right,
there's no reason on earth
that the prince shouldn't pick one of you
for his bride.
Girls.
Well, first I flutter my eyelashes.
Excellent.
I'm going to start with a curtsy.
Then I'm gonna start with the curtsy too.
Then I get to flutter my eyelashes.
Then I'm gonna flutter my eyelashes too.
Let's! Let's move on.
Tell me, what you're going
to say to the prince,
Minerva?
Well,
you said to show him that there
is more to me than mere beauty.
So,
I thought I might recite a poem.
A poem!
What's wrong with that?
Whatever you do girls,
you mustn't let the prince
know how clever you are.
Men can't stand to be around smart women.
Yes mother.
For heaven sake Minerva
stop scratching yourself!
I can't help it mother.
You know I get itchy when I'm nervous.
Don't... do...
that!
And what are you going to say Calliope?
Well, mother..
I've been working on my
naturally infectious laughter.
Excuse me?
Tonight I'm going to laugh
infectiously at all the princes jokes.
Ha! Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Snort-snort!
Snort.
I beg Calliope whatever you do
try not to snort.
Yes mother.
And Minerva
you must try not to scratch.
Remember girls,
we hide our flaws,..
Until after the wedding.
But shouldn't a man love you for
who you are in spite of everything?
How quaint.
Tell me Cinderella,
what would you say to capture the prince?
I don't know.
Of course you don't.
But whatever I'd say,
we'd know in an instant and
we were meant for each other.
Then he'd smile and
kiss my hand.
That sounds so romantic.
Say it again Cinderella.
Rubbish!
This isn't about love.
It's about marriage!
Have I taught you girls nothing!
♪ Falling in love with love
is falling for make believe. ♪
♪ Falling in love with
love is playing a fool. ♪
♪ Caring too much is
such a juvenile fancy. ♪
♪ Learning to trust is just
for children in school. ♪
♪ I fell in love with love one
night when the moon was full. ♪
♪ I wasn't wise with eyes unable to see. ♪
♪ I fell in love with love
with love everlasting. ♪
♪ But love fell out with me. ♪
♪ Falling in love with love is falling for make believe. ♪
♪ Ahhh ♪
♪ Falling in love with love is playing a fool. ♪
♪ Caring too much is
such a juvenile fancy. ♪
♪ Learning to trust is just for children in school. ♪
♪ I fell in love with love one
night when the moon was full. ♪
♪ I was unwise with eyes unable to see. ♪
♪ I fell in love with love with love everlasting. ♪
♪ She fell in love with love with love everlasting. ♪
♪ But love fell out ♪
♪ with me. ♪
Go to the ball?
Me?
Why would I want to go to the ball?
I would much rather sit here by the fire.
♪ In my own little corner ♪
♪ In my own little chair ♪
♪ I can be what ever I want to be. ♪
♪ On the wing of my fancy ♪
♪ I can fly anywhere ♪
♪ And the world will open its arms to me. ♪
♪ I am in the royal palace of all places. ♪
♪ I am chatting with the prince ♪
♪ and king and queen. ♪
♪ And the color on my
two step-sisters' faces ♪
♪ is a queer sort of sour apple green. ♪
♪ I am coy and flirtatious ♪
♪ when alone with the prince. ♪
Oh your highness!
♪ I'm the belle of the ball ♪
♪ in my own little corner. ♪
♪ All alone,.. ♪
Oh!
I wish..
I wish I could go to the ball.
♪ Fol-de-rol and fiddle dee dee. ♪
♪ Fiddley faddley foddle. ♪
♪ All the wishes in the world ♪
♪ are poppy cock and twoddle. ♪
Who are you?
I'm your fairy godmother, honey.
You?
You got a problem with that?
'Cause if you'd rather have some old lady
in a tutu sprinkling fairy dust on you..
Oh no, no, I'm sorry, I just,
never dreamed..
♪ Fol-de-rol and fiddle dee dee. ♪
♪ Fiddley faddley foodle. ♪
♪ All the dreamers in the world are ♪
♪ dizzy in the noodle. ♪
That's terrible.
You try coming up with a
rhyme on the spot like that.
No no, I mean what you
said about dreamers.
I mean, why shouldn't I dream?
I can see this is going to take awhile.
Aren't you going to invite me in?
Oh forgive me, of course I am.
Cinderella, over here.
Is it just me or is it freezing in here?
How'd you do that?
Practice.
I've always hoped that someone would
come and take me away from here.
Cinderella,
if you wanna get out of here you're
going to have to do it yourself.
The music's in you.
Deep down in your soul.
When you find it,
nothing will be able to keep
you from walking out that door.
You don't know my stepmother.
You wanna know what her problem is?
She can't handle how fabulous you are.
Fabulous? Me?
Do you see anybody else in this room?
Those 3 are all I've got.
Before my father died, I promised
him we'd stay together as a family.
Cinderella,
this can't be what your daddy
had in mind for you baby.
I dreamt about leaving so many times.
That's the problem with most people,
they dream about what they want
to do instead of really doing it.
Oh I wish that,.
but I guess wishing's no good either.
Mmm, everything starts with a wish.
You want to know what I was wishing
before you came here tonight?
That one of those pumpkins in the yard
would turn into a great big golden carriage
and take you to the ball.
Guess I know what you're going to say,
Fol-de-rol and fiddle dee dee.
Fiddley faddley foodle.
You're right.
It's impossible.
♪ Impossible, ♪
♪ for a plain yellow pumpkin
to become a golden carriage! ♪
♪ Impossible, ♪
♪ for a plain country bumpkin and
a prince to join in marriage ♪
♪ and four white mice will
never be four white horses. ♪
♪ and four white mice
wilMightyMike77020 white horses. ♪
♪ and four white mice will
never be four white horses. ♪
♪ Such fol-de-rol and fiddledy
dee dee of course is. ♪
♪ Impossible! ♪
♪ But the world is full
of zanies and fools ♪
♪ who don't believe in sensible rules ♪
♪ and won't believe what
sensible people say ♪
♪ and because these daft
and dewy-eyed dopes ♪
♪ keep building up impossible hopes ♪
♪ Impossible, ♪
♪ things are happening every day! ♪
♪ Impossible! ♪
Wait!
If impossible things
are happening everyday,
then, then why shouldn't I have
impossible hopes and dreams.
Even something as impossible
as going to the ball?
Then go to the ball Cinderella. Go.
No one stopping you but you.
But I have no way to get there.
Mm, you have a point there.
God mother I've been
wishing as hard as I can.
I know you have Cinderella.
Go on stand over there.
Go ahead.
Ahem.
What's the matter with me?
You think after 600 years.
Alright.
Oh my goodness!
Hum, we need some horses..
Let me see.
They’re so beautiful.
Don't you run away from me.
Just like in my dream.
Ahem.
We've got a coachman, we've got footman,
horses, carriage.
Is there anything else I have forgotten.
Spin around. Don't make me do all the work.
Thank you godmother.
Thank you so much.
There's one tiny little
thing before I forget.
You must leave the ball before
the clock strikes 12:00.
It's very important.
Before 12:00?
Look, I don't make the rules.
The magic only last till midnight.
Come on Cinderella its time to go.
♪ It's possible, ♪
♪ for a plain yellow pumpkin ♪
♪ to become a golden carriage. ♪
♪ Its possible, ♪
♪ for a plain country bumpkin ♪
♪ and a prince to join in marriage. ♪
♪ and four white mice are
easily turned to horses.. ♪
♪ Such falder-all-and-fiddle-dee-dee ♪
♪ of course is. ♪
♪ Quite possible, ♪
♪ Quite possible. ♪
♪ It's possible, ♪
♪ It's possible. ♪
♪ For the world is full
of zanies and fools. ♪
♪ Who don't believe in sensible rules. ♪
♪ And won't believe what
sensible people say. ♪
♪ And because these daft and dewy-eyed dopes ♪
♪ keep building up impossible hopes ♪
♪ Impossible, ♪
♪ things are happening everyday. ♪
♪ It's possible, ♪
♪ It's possible! ♪
So many beautiful girls.
He'll find the one he's looking
for tonight I'm sure of it.
And if he doesn't?
This ball will never end!
I don't think we ordered enough food.
What?
I WANNA CHANCE AT HIM!
Look at his face, is that a smile?
It's a wince.
A tiny little smile.
Wishful thinking.
Oy.
Pardon me,
I'm sure you notice my
two beautiful daughters.
Madam,.
Madam for the last time,
his highness will dance with all
the young ladies in due time.
Please, try to exercise some restraint.
Naturally any mother would be eager to
see her daughters dance with the prince
but what I would like to know is
whozz
going to have the honor
up dancing with
h'you?
Excuse me?
There's no need to be coy.
Look at you, that manly physique.
Those handsome chiseled features.
That wonderful full head..
Of skin.
No touching please.
Surely there's no need to pretend.
I know that you felt that certain something
between us.
You know, I honestly wish
there was something between us.
Really?
Yes.
A continent.
Ah!
Do you have an itch?
No your highness why would you say that?
You just scratched yourself.
No I didn't.
Just did it again.
I don't think so.
Ships that pass in the night
and speak to each other in passing.
Excuse me?
On the ocean of life.
- Oof!
- It's poetry!
Oh.
Ships that pass in the
night, that's you and me.
On the ocean of life.
- Don't you get it?!
-  Got it.
Tell the orchestra to speed it up.
I miss something?
Snort!
Oh, your laughter is incessant.
But your highness c'est très amusant
I don't think anyone's ever found me funny.
Snort snort!
Snort!
Snort! Snort!
I thought we were getting along so well.
- Hey, loosen up a little.
- Ooh!
- Faster Lionel.
- Ehh.
I think it's going awfully well don't you?
Cinderella.
Alright now, you're on your own.
Aren't you coming with me?
I got you to the ball,
The rest comes from you.
Don't be afraid.
Just remember, you got to be out of
there before the clock strikes 12:00.
Hello.
How do you do your highness.
Who is that charming girl?
No one seems to know.
She is stunning isn't she.
Like a vision.
My, if I were a young man I'd..
Yes dear..
Well, I'd be younger wouldn't I.
Yes dear.
Where on earth did she come from?
I've never seen her before.
There's something vaguely
familiar about that girl.
You know I have the funniest feeling
I've met you somewhere's before.
Well I'm sure I would remember.
Was it last summer at the lake?
No I can't swim.
Then it must have been this
winter, at the lodge.
Up in the mountains?
You go to the mountains too?
No, I just love looking at them.
They're very beautiful.
Your very beautiful.
Everyone staring at us.
Really?
I had forgotten anyone else was here.
♪ Ten minutes ago, I saw you ♪
♪ I looked up when you
came through the door. ♪
♪ My head started reeling ♪
♪ you gave me the feeling ♪
♪ the room had no ceiling or floor. ♪
♪ Ten minutes ago, I met you, ♪
♪ And we murmured our how do you dos. ♪
♪ I wanted to ring out the bells ♪
♪ and fling out my arms ♪
♪ and to sing out the news. ♪
♪ I have found her, she's an angel, ♪
♪ with the dust of the stars in her eyes. ♪
♪ We are dancing, we are flying, ♪
♪ and she's taking me back to the skies! ♪
♪ In the arms of my love, I'm flying, ♪
♪ over mountain and meadow and glen. ♪
♪ And I like it so well ♪
♪ that for all I can tell ♪
♪ I may never come down again. ♪
♪ I may never come down to earth again. ♪
♪ Ten minutes ago, I met you ♪
♪ and we murmured our how-do-you-do's. ♪
♪ I wanted to ring out the bells ♪
♪ and fling out my arms ♪
♪ and to sing out the news. ♪
♪ I have found her. ♪
♪ I have found him. ♪
♪ In the arms of my love I'm flying ♪
♪ over mountain and meadow and glen. ♪
♪ And I like it so well ♪
♪ that for all I can tell ♪
♪ I may never come down again. ♪
♪ I may never come down to earth again. ♪
♪ Why would a fellow
want a girl like her, ♪
♪ a frail and fluffy beauty? ♪
♪ Why can't a fellow ever once prefer ♪
♪ a solid girl like me? ♪
♪ She's a frothy little bubble, ♪
♪ with a flimsy kind of charm. ♪
♪ and with very little trouble, ♪
♪ I could break her little arm. ♪
♪ Oh, oh. ♪
♪ Oh. ♪
♪ Why would a fellow want a girl like her, ♪
♪ So obviously unusual? ♪
♪ Why can't a fellow ever once prefer ♪
♪ a usual girl like me? ♪
♪ Her face is exquisite I suppose, ♪
♪ but no more exquisite than a rose is. ♪
♪ Her skin may be delicate and soft, ♪
♪ but not any softer than a doe's is. ♪
♪ Her neck is no longer than a swan's. ♪
♪ She's only as dainty as a daisy. ♪
♪ She's only as graceful as a bird. ♪
♪ So why is the fellow going crazy? ♪
♪ Oh why would a fellow want a girl like her, ♪
♪ A girl who's merely lovely? ♪
♪ Why can't a fellow ever once prefer ♪
♪ a girl who's merely me? ♪
♪ She's a frothy little bubble, ♪
♪ with a frilly sort of air ♪
♪ and with very little trouble, ♪
♪ I could pull out all her hair! ♪
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
♪ Oh, oh. ♪
♪ Why would a fellow want a girl like her, ♪
♪ a girl who's merely lovely? ♪
♪ Why can't a fellow ever once prefer ♪
♪ a girl who's merely me? ♪
♪ What's the matter with the man, ♪
♪ What's the matter with the man?! ♪
Oh!
I do hope that son of
MightyMike77020g himself.
mine is behaving himself.
Oh yes your majesty he's
been a perfect gentleman.
A chip off the old block is he?
Yes your majesty.
Clearly he's smitten with you.
I must say, it's as though you
have appeared here by magic.
What's he saying to her?
What difference does it make?
You said you weren't going to find
the girl of your dreams tonight.
- Do we know your mother and father dear?
- Oh!
I don't think so.
Uuh!
You must introduce us. Where are they?
Well m-my father, he..
Yes dear?
Well my mother she..
I'm sorry, will you excuse me?
[Squeak.]
What did you say to her?
[Squeak. Squeak.]
Oof!
I think she's lovely don't you?
- A little high strung.
- A little.
- Who is that?
- Lionel darling.
Oh.
- It's not midnight yet.
- I want to go now.
Oh, so you're just giving up?
I'm not what they think I am.
All their thinking is that you are
the most beautiful girl at the ball.
and you are.
You're still here.
Yes.
I was just..
Please, I don't know what
my parents said to you but
I apologize.
Oh no, no, they were wonderful.
Compared to my family.
- I wanna meet your family.
- No you don't.
- Everyone in your life.
- No no. Really you don't.
That bad huh?
Well, they didn't want
me to come here tonight.
Well I'm glad you did.
To tell you the truth I
almost didn't come myself.
Well how can the prince
not show up at his own ball?
Don't you think that
it's a little medieval?
Everyone circling around as if I were some,
prize bull they were trying to rope in.
Go ahead and laugh but this is serious.
If I'm going to spend the rest
of my life with someone..
Well she's got to be..
Well she's got to be, exciting.
I guess.
- But sweet.
- Not that sweet.
And your devoted servant forever and ever.
Servants I got.
What I need is someone
I can really talk to.
You know what I wish?
I wish..
You know the trouble with most people,
is they sit around wishing
for something to happen
instead of just doing something about it.
You're right.
May I ask you a question?
Of course.
Do you think it's possible to meet someone
and know in an instant that she's the one.
It's very possible.
I feel so strange.
Like I'm not myself , or maybe its
just with you I really am myself.
Not the self that people expect me
to be but the real self that I..
Not making any sense am I.
Actually your making perfect sense to me.
That's what so scary.
Scary?..
And confusing and wonderful.
All at the same time.
♪ Do I love you because you're beautiful ♪
♪ or are you beautiful ♪
♪ because I love you? ♪
♪ Am I making believe I see in you ♪
♪ a girl too lovely to ♪
♪ be really true? ♪
♪ Do I want you because you're wonderful ♪
♪ or are you wonderful ♪
♪ because I want you? ♪
♪ Are you the sweet
invention of a lovers dream ♪
♪ or are you really as
beautiful as you seem? ♪
Maybe you're imagining me.
and maybe I'm imagining it too.
♪ Am I making believe I see in you ♪
♪ a man too perfect to ♪
♪ be really true? ♪
♪ Do I want you because you're wonderful ♪
♪ or are you wonderful ♪
♪ because I want you? ♪
♪ Are you the sweet invention of a lovers dream ♪
♪ or are you really as wonderful ♪
♪ as you seem? ♪
I always dreamed it would happen like this.
And now it really has.
I don't never want this night to end.
Neither do I.
♪ Are you the sweet invention of a lovers dream ♪
♪ or are you really as wonderful ♪
♪ as you seem? ♪
I can't stay!
What do you mean?
I have to go!
Wait, come back!
I don't even know your name!
Your highness what is it?
Chris, don't let her get away.
[Squeak!]
Your highness, you simply must..
♪ Do I want you because you're wonderful ♪
♪ or are you wonderful ♪
♪ because I want you? ♪
♪ Are you the sweet invention of a lovers dream ♪
♪ or are you really as wonderful ♪
♪ as you seem? ♪
Come along girls.
What a night!
What a magnificent affair.
Perfect.
Like a dream.
Well did any of you get
to dance with the prince?
I danced about an hour with him.
- An hour?
- Didn't you?
Well, of course I did.
If you did.
I wouldn't be surprised if the prince
chose one of you for his bride.
Oh, that sounds too good to be true.
Did you know everyone at the ball?
Everyone who's anyone.
Except some Princess
something or other.
I never did quite
catch her name.
A Princess?
Did she dance with the prince?
I didn't notice.
Do you think he liked her?
[Snort.]
And uh..
What pray tell have you been
doing all night Cinderella?
I been dreaming mostly.
What it would've been
like to be at the ball.
She couldn't possibly dream what
it was like unless she was there.
You simply can't imagine.
Well..
I imagine that there's a grand staircase,
candles everywhere,
and an orchestra playing.
♪ It looks that way. ♪
♪ The way you say. ♪
♪ She talks as if ♪
♪ she knows. ♪
♪ I do not know ♪
♪ that this is so ♪
♪ I only just suppose. ♪
♪ I suppose that when you
come into the ball room ♪
♪ and the room itself is
floating in the air. ♪
♪ If you're suddenly
confronted by his highness ♪
♪ you are frozen like
a statue on the stair. ♪
♪ You're afraid he'll hear the
way your heart is beating ♪
♪ and you know you mustn't
make the first advance. ♪
♪ You are seriously
thinking of retreating ♪
♪ then you seem to hear
him asking you to dance. ♪
When you waltz with him
you whirl around so that your
feet never touch the floor.
That's right, they don't.
And it makes you feel like
you weigh nothing at all.
That's right, it does.
And then for a few precious moments
you're the only two people
in the entire world.
♪ A lovely night. ♪
♪ A finer night you know
you'll never see. ♪
♪ You meet your prince. ♪
♪ A charming prince. ♪
♪ As charming as a prince will ever be. ♪
♪ The stars in a hazy heaven ♪
♪ tremble above you, ♪
♪ while he's whispering, ♪
♪ "Darling, I love you." ♪
♪ You say goodbye. ♪
♪ Away you fly. ♪
♪ But on your lips you keep a kiss, ♪
♪ all your life you'll dream of this ♪
♪ lovely, lovely night. ♪
♪ A lovely night ♪
.
How lovely.
♪ A lovely night. ♪
.
How lovely!
♪ A finer night you know
you'll never see. ♪
- How lovely
- Shh!
♪ You meet. Your prince. ♪
♪ A charming prince ♪
♪ As charming as a prince will ever be. ♪
♪ The stars in a hazy heaven. ♪
♪ Tremble above you. ♪
♪ While he is whispering, ♪
♪ "Darling, I love you." ♪
♪ You say goodbye. ♪
♪ Away you fly. ♪
♪ And on your lips you keep a kiss. ♪
♪ All your life you'll dream of this. ♪
♪ Lovely. ♪ ♪ Lovely. ♪
♪ Lovely. ♪
♪ Lovely night! ♪ ♪ Lovely night! ♪
♪ Lovely night! ♪
Stop this!
Worst nonsense I ever heard.
Rubbish and dribble.
But mother!
And you!
listening to her!
Hanging on her every word.
- But mother!
- Enough!
Go to your room it's late.
And you.
Why, the thought of you
dancing with the Prince.
It's preposterous.
Why?
Why is it so hard for you to imagine?
Because!
Your common Cinderella.
Your mother was common, and so are you.
Oh, you can wash your face
and put on a clean dress
but underneath you'll still be common.
And a Prince would even consider
taking you for his bride why,
It's laughable.
- My father..
- Your father was weak.
He spoiled you rotten.
He filled your head with silly thoughts
and dreams that'll never come true.
Never.
Now, clean this place up.
It's a sty.
Father,.
I know I promised that
I'd never leave here,
But after tonight I don't
see how I could stay.
If you only knew how she's
changed you'd understand.
I deserve better father.
I deserve to be loved.
And that's what I found out tonight.
And that's all that really matters.
♪ My dream came true. ♪
♪ Away I flew. ♪
♪ But on my lips he left a kiss. ♪
♪ All my life I'll dream of this, ♪
♪ Lovely, ♪
♪ Lovely night. ♪
Cinderella.
If you really love him why
don't you let him know?
How can I?
Look at me.
Do you really think he fell in love with
your fancy gown and your pretty braids.
I don't know anymore.
And if you hadn't help me..
You didn't need my help.
You just thought you did.
Believe in yourself Cinderella.
and trust him to love
you as you really are.
Chris, you been up all night.
Come and have something to eat.
I can't.
I can't eat or rest until
I found her again.
Chris, they've been searching everywhere.
Not a trace of her.
You may never find her.
Don't say that.
I will find her. I've got to.
Before last night you didn't
know a thing about her.
And you don't know anything about her now.
Except that she's beautiful.
And all the girls last night
were equally beautiful.
I don't want to hear about
anyone else, mother.
She's not like the others.
She's different than any
other girl I've ever met.
How can you know that after one night?
♪ Are you making believe you see in her ♪
♪ a girl to lovely to ♪
♪ be really true? ♪
♪ Do you love her because
she's wonderful? ♪
♪ Or is she wonderful ♪
♪ because you love her? ♪
♪ Is she the sweet invention
of a lovers dream, ♪
♪ Or is she really as wonderful ♪
♪ as she seems? ♪
All my life I've been
searching for something.
And I finally found it.
In her.
Well then,
You must find her.
Keep looking Chris, for
as long as it takes.
Your Highness, I'm afraid I don't
have very good news to report.
No one seems to know who she
is or where she's from.
Lionel she's out there somewhere
and I'm going to search every inch
of this Kingdom until I find her.
A shoe made out of glass?
Who dances in glass shoes?
We're going to try this slipper on the
foot of every young woman in the Kingdom
until we find her.
I'm going to marry her. Do you understand?
Do as he says Lionel.
Yes, your majesty.
♪ And the dearest love in all the world ♪
♪ is waiting somewhere for me. ♪
♪ Is waiting somewhere, ♪
♪ Somewhere for ♪
♪ me. ♪
That's my slipper, I'd know
that stripper anywhere..
You see, it fits perfectly.
[Snort.]
Calliope honestly anyone can see that that
slipper was made for a daintyer foot.
What happened to it!
You shrunk it!
It fit perfectly at the ball!
Miss, his Highness is really weary
and I think it is obvious...
that... he... is.
Are there any other women in the house?
Oh why, yes.
There's one more.
Move over!
I mean, are there any other
"young" women in the house?
How young?
Younger than you.
Uhh! Ah-Ahhh!
My stars!
It fits! It fits! Oh!
Impossible!
Ohh! Oww!
Ahh!
And it's cutting off my circulation!
Get it off me!
Off, off, off!
Pull harder you imbecile harder!
Madam there's no need for name calling.
I'm on it!
On the count of 3.
- 1,.
- Ah!
- 2,.
OHHH!
What's the matter with you people?
A blind man could tell it
wasn't going to fit my foot.
Are you certain there's no one else here?
No, not a soul.
No one your Highness.
Not even a servant girl.
Those doors, where do they lead to?
What doors?
The ones right behind you.
Oh!
Oh, oh.
Doors! These doors.
There the one's you said.
There's nothing
behind these doors.
I'd like to see for myself please.
Oh, it's just like any other kitchen, a
few pots and pans, a couple of mice.
Step aside Madam.
Take one of my daughters your Highness!
I beg of you!
Calliope got charm and elocution!
She's really much smarter than she looks!
And Minerva, that girl
is as strong as an ox!
And culture,
Why she's memorized the wreck of
Hesperus in three languages'.
Four if you count pig Latin.
Madame!
I command you to stop this
foolishness this instant!
Come along Lionel.
ᴴᵒ ʰᵒ.
Just like those Royals isn't it.
Not caring if there in anybody's way.
Well I'm sure they were going
somewhere very important.
What did you say your name was?
Cinderella.
I like it.
It groMightyMike77020.
It grows on you I guess.
May I?
NOOO!
Quiet woman!
♪ Impossible, ♪
♪ MightyMike77020, ♪
♪ things are happening ♪
♪ every ♪
♪ day. ♪
♪ Someone wants you, ♪
♪ you know who. ♪
♪ Know you're living, ♪
♪ there's music in you. ♪
♪ Now you're hearing ♪
♪ something new. ♪
♪ Someone's playing ♪
♪ the music in you. ♪
♪ Now you're living. ♪
♪ You know why. ♪
♪ Now there's nothing ♪
♪ you won't try. ♪
♪ Move a mountain. ♪
♪ Light the sky. ♪
♪ Make a wish come true. ♪
♪ There is music in you. ♪
♪ Now you can go wherever you want to go. ♪
♪ Now you can do whatever you want to do. ♪
♪ Now you can be whatever you want to be. ♪
.
Wait! We're family!
♪ Now you can be whatever you want to be. ♪
We're family!
.
♪ Now you can be whatever you want to be. ♪
We love you!
♪ And love is the song you will
sing your whole life through. ♪
♪ Ohhhh! ♪
♪ Move a mountain. ♪
♪ Light the sky. ♪
♪ Make a wish come true. ♪
♪ There is music ♪
♪ in you. ♪
♪ Ohhhh! ♪
♪ In you. ♪
{\move(400,10,190,270,100,400)\fad(0,1000)\fscx25\fscy25\t(0,6000,\fscx125\fscy125)\c&H000000f&\3c&0000a6&}Subtitles By:
MightyMike77020
Sing-along Subtitles By:
If you would like to comment on
my Read-along/Sing-along subtitles,
or would like to suggest
a movie to subtitle,
I'm at
http://subscene.com/u/759958/subtitles
Good or bad your comments are welcome.