City of new orleans 911.
911. What's
the address of you emergency?
Austin 911. Do
you need police, fire, or ems?
I've always wondered
what actually happens
when we call 911?
Who are the mysterious voices
on the other end of that line?
Tell me exactly what happened.
Stay on the line.
I'm gonna tell you what to do next.
You're doing a great job, okay?
Who are the faceless
strangers that we reach out to
in our darkest moments?
They navigate the unknown,
keep calm in the chaos.
I don't know!
Just send the cops!
- I just heard some gunshots.
- They're trying to hit me.
Oh, my god. Please hurry.
Please help!
They're driven by
a desire to help.
Ma'am, listen to me.
Stay where you are.
I have officers going after him.
You can do this.
We're gonna do this together.
You don't need to be scared.
We have them coming to you.
Take a deep
breath. Take a deep breath.
We have help
heading that direction.
Thank you.
This is what I found.
240 million...
That's how many calls americans
make every year to 911.
Nearly a quarter billion calls
ranging from the absurd
to the tragic
to random butt dials.
Let's not beat around the bush.
This has been a crazy year.
But day in, day out,
pandemic or no pandemic,
911 operators, they answer
the phone knowing anything...
Literally anything...
Could be about to unfold.
Austin 911. Do you need
police, fire, or ems?
Police department.
My neighbor's
smoking crack, man.
- I'm in the restroom now.
- I just smell the
makes me want to come out there
and take a
I think certain people
are meant to be 911 operators.
Certain people are not meant
to be a 911 operators.
You're doing a great job.
Officers are just down
the street now.
Okay, and what kind of vehicles
are involved?
I'm gonna stay on the phone
with you
until the officers get there.
In a single shift,
I could take
up to 100 calls per night.
There's a guy walking around
with a samurai sword
on his back.
Say that one more time.
This is the drunkest
driver I've ever seen.
Okay.
Someone trying to get
into my house
through the back door.
Yeah, I have a cat
stuck up in a tree.
You take so many different
types of calls, it's insane.
My wife is gonna kill me.
I locked my baby in the car.
Whenever I have calls with kids,
that pulls on my heartstrings.
You know, you're human,
so you've got those feelings.
Some of us have weaknesses,
and kids are
definitely my weakness.
This is austin 911. Do you need
police, fire, or ems?
I need 911! Someone took
my car with my baby in there!
Ma'am, what kind of help
do you need? Are you okay?
Do you need an ambulance?
Can...
Okay. How many children
do you have in there?
Okay. Which way did they go
so we can go after them?
I don't know what street.
That's okay.
We still have help for you.
It doesn't matter
which way they went.
Okay, we're sending help to you.
Auto theft. The child
was asleep in the back seat.
What kind of vehicle
did he leave in?
And what kind of vehicle?
A range rover.
I think it's a 2015 range rover.
What color? It's white.
We have help on the way to you,
okay?
You're doing a great job.
Please get my baby back.
Take a deep breath.
Everyone is coming for you.
Everyone, I have a location.
I need missing persons
detective to 21.
Clear a path.
Fell asleep in the vehicle.
Confirm all units.
Resume normal traffic.
How does deb prepare
herself for a call like that?
And even more so, how does she
move on from a call like that?
There's no time
to process emotions,
no matter how much a call may
trigger something inside of you.
Here we go.
Alright.
Let me show you how this works.
So you call 911.
Now, your phone's location,
it determines the call center
that you're routed to.
Austin 911. Do you need,
police, fire, or ems?
As you explain the emergency,
everything you tell the call
taker is logged in a report.
Now, based on the situation,
the appropriate response
is dispatched.
Whether that's
the police department...
...The fire department...
...Or an ambulance.
Maybe all three.
The responding units,
they have access
to that very same information
gathered by the call taker.
So when they show up
on your doorstep,
they know exactly
what they're walking into.
911. What's the address
of the emergency?
Old ridge camp.
Okay, what's going on?
Um, there's a grizzly bear
that's been stalking us.
There's a grizzly bear? Yeah.
Did the bear actually attack you
or come towards you?
It charged twice.
And then it came back, charged.
Sprayed it again.
The bear's coming back to you?
We don't know yet.
How old are you?
19 years old.
How big was it?
12 feet tall.
12 feet?
He's the biggest thing
I've ever seen.
For a brown bear,
you want to play dead,
and a black bear,
you want to fight back.
Did I lose you?
What was that?
What did I just hear?
I just stepped on the dog.
Oh, okay.
You stepped on your dog.
Okay. Good.
Are you able to get back
to your vehicle?
No, ma'am.
The... the bear is
between us and there.
I'm working on getting a ranger
up there to find you, okay?
Oh, thank you so much.
I'm really scared
the bear is gonna come back.
Being scared is
completely natural.
Don't you worry about it.
I'm right here with you, okay?
Okay. I don't blame them.
I wouldn't want to be chased
by a bear, either.
Running uphill, no less.
Are you still walking
that trail?
Alright.
We do have a trooper
on his way to you, okay?
They're looking for you guys.
Get there as fast as possible.
Have you passed the first
or second bench?
Okay, you're past the second?
You're at the top?
Looks like I have two troopers
headed that way.
I'm gonna stay
on the line with you, okay?
In contact with hikers.
Everyone 10-60.
Whoo-hoo. - They made it.
They made it.
No bear attacks today.
- Today.
- Yeah. Happy endings.
They're both okay.
And they learned a life lesson.
Did they, though?
They'll be going and getting
a firearm, I'm hoping.
Life lessons learned, right?
Yeah.
If it's brown, lay down,
and if it's black, fight back.
That's a rhyme I learned
while camping as a kid.
Suddenly, they're the most
important words I've ever heard.
At least it wasn't a polar bear,
because I believe
the rhyme ends with
"if it's white, good night."
City of new orleans 911.
What's the address
of your emergency?
City of new orleans 911.
What's the address
of your emergency?
- City of new orleans.
- City of new orleans 911.
City of new orleans 911.
What is the location
of your emergency?
There's no place
like new orleans.
There's no other people
like new orleans people,
because down here,
we can open our door to anybody.
I have people
that I've worked with,
and we just became family.
I like to be a good wingwoman.
How about I tag along with you
for a change?
I just want to... I just want to
be here for support,
whatever you need.
I think that's what
makes us who we are.
That's what makes us different.
When you're call taking,
you have to have compassion.
You have to have patience.
It's not always easy.
Oh, hang on.
Wait, hold on, ma'am.
You're cutting in and out.
I'm trying to get the
information. Give me one moment.
Because if you have somebody
calling in
and they screaming at you,
you have to be able
to calm them down
so you can get them the help
that they're looking for.
City of new orleans 911.
What is the location
of your emergency?
Um, ma'am, I'm on
carol sue avenue in terrytown.
There's cars all over,
and the water's coming up.
I don't know what's going on,
but I'm about to start floating.
City of new orleans.
Police, fire, ems...
- How may I assist your call?
- Yeah, hi, sorry.
I'm calling about the water
flood in terrytown.
I ain't never seen
the water this high.
Girl, look at
all these flood calls.
I know.
That's what I'm looking at.
City of new orleans 911.
What's the address
of your emergency?
I'm on the superdome exit,
and my car is like
stuck in the water.
I think my engine's flooded.
I can't turn my car back on.
Are you able to see
a street sign, sir,
so you can tell me
what street you're closest to?
I'm just right off the I-10
under the bridge.
And you're inside
of the vehicle?
Yes.
Alright.
I mean, it isn't
raining, but it keeps rising.
Look, I've been stuck here
20, 25 minutes.
Okay. Is your vehicle floating,
or are there just vehicles
in the area?
The vehicles in the area
in front of me
and all around me are floating.
But I'm about to start floating.
Are you able to get out
of the vehicle, sir?
No.
So if you open your door,
your car is gonna flood?
Yes.
Alright, hold on for me
just a minute.
It's raining...
It's flooding over there?
Girl, I don't know.
You know, they working on
the canal over there, so...
Oh, my god.
Damn.
In this job,
you have to want to be here,
and what keeps me here
are the citizens.
New orleans has
a basic foundation
of hospitality and love.
Post-katrina, our callers need
someone that wants to help them.
Okay, I just want...
I want you to be safe.
Well, what do you think
we should...
Do you think we should get out
or something?
Are you able to get out
and step off to the side?
I don't know.
I guess I could, like,
jump out the window or
something. I don't know.
I'm gonna get you
some help out there, okay?
This is pissing me off.
Where are the police?
My police unit is stuck
in the water
and unable to respond as well.
Oh, lord. This is crazy.
We're gonna have to
send the cavalry.
I'm getting fire to you, okay?
There's teamwork in all aspects.
You cannot do this job without
thinking of it as a team.
It's a big old family.
The rain stopped,
but the water just keeps...
It just keeps rising.
Where is the water coming from?
I mean, I'm gonna have water
pretty soon.
Okay.
People are going up
and down both sides
of the street the wrong way,
trying to get out.
- Alright, sir.
- Oh, my god.
Water's coming in
on my thighs now.
Are you able to get out?
Maybe on the other side.
Yeah, I could, um...
I could jump out the window
or something.
I don't know.
I got to roll my pants up.
Can you see if
anybody is trapped
in their vehicles or not?
Yes, somebody is stuck
in their vehicle.
They're trying to climb out
the... the window now.
Alright, sweetie.
I want to make sure
you guys are okay as well.
A truck is stupidly
driving down the street.
Don't come this way.
Come on! Stop!
Slow down. Come on!
Slow down! Slow down!
Slow down! Slow down! Hey!
Don't come this way. Stop!
Slow down! Come on!
Slow down! Slow down!
Slow down! Slow down! Hey!
Hello?
Are you there?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Swear to god,
people are disgusting.
It's okay. We're go...
But we're gonna get you
some help, though.
That's the most important thing.
I swear, I'mma get my belt
and whoop somebody's tail.
I understand.
New orleans is uniquely
vulnerable to flooding.
The city's like a bowl
resting an average
of six feet below sea level,
making every storm
a potential catastrophe.
See the fire truck coming?
No. I guess the fire truck
couldn't come this way.
He turned off.
We're gonna
make sure you're okay,
and we just have to go
check on your vehicle later.
It's unfortunate,
but it ain't worth your life.
Yeah, it's dangerous
to get out right here.
It's just water.
Alright, hold on for me
just a minute, sir.
I don't want to let you
off the phone yet.
I just want to make sure
I get you some help, okay?
I just checked with the bridge.
We are standing up
our high-water assets
to get them ready
for deployment.
I got some cars stranded.
There's a lady was stranded
on top of her car.
She did manage
to get out of the vehicle.
Okay.
I hear sirens.
Yeah,
that's the fire department.
Lord, the houses
are getting flooded over there.
Oh, that's just great.
Is that the kind of night
we gonna have?
Oh, man, I hope not.
The rain just started.
It's new orleans, unfortunately.
Of course we try and prepare,
but at times,
911 is our only lifeline
to save us from the power
of mother nature.
Sometimes, though,
our interactions with
the natural world
can be a little less
life-threatening.
Austin 911. Do you need
police, fire, or ems?
We have a peacock
in the middle of the street,
and people are dodging it.
I'm sorry. Y-you have a what
in the middle of the street?
A peacock. Okay.
Hold on one second for me.
Okay, has anybody
been injured at all?
Okay. Okay.
I'm sorry. One more time?
Okay. Okay, gotcha. Gotcha.
Headed down...
Which direction is he going?
Southbound?
Alright. I've got that call
entered for you.
If anything changes
before the officers get there,
just give us
a call back again, okay?
Alright. Thank you.
Peacock's on the run.
That's funny.
911. What's the address
of the emergency?
My name's frank.
My phone is about ready to die.
I'm at the talkeetna river.
I got stuck on my four-wheeler
out here.
I went to go through a little
channel and it was muck,
and my damn boot blew about
and I got a fractured leg.
Can't make it out of here.
Did you get into the water
or anything like that?
I'm in knee deep,
almost waist deep.
You were submerged down
to the waist or so?
Yes.
Okay.
Do you have any help with you?
No, I've got nobody. Okay.
I just need help
to get out of here.
I can't walk out of here
with a fractured leg.
There's just no way.
I ask for the battery
life for search and rescues.
If it's less than, say, 10%,
try to keep those
phone calls brief.
Just got to conserve
that battery life.
Where are you right now?
So you take the highway east.
It's about a mile back.
You go on the riverbed.
There's a four-wheeler track
straight ahead.
Because you're low on battery,
I'm gonna let you go.
You want me
to shoot my gun in the air?
Let's not worry about that
quite yet.
I want you to dial 911
if anything else does worsen
in the meanwhile.
We're getting the help paged
out right now, okay?
Oh, I'm disconnected.
Did it just happen?
Yes, just happened.
He thinks
he has a fractured ankle.
Can he not ride
his four-wheeler out of there?
Yeah, no, it was
because of the accident.
It sounds like
it's in the water.
Is he wet?
He was wet down to the...
Down to the waist.
- Is he currently in the water?
- No.
911. What is the address
of your emergency?
Hi, this is frank.
I'm calling back in.
Man, I feel like a total jerk.
We've got help headed your way.
Fire department's
bringing in some atvs.
And we got troopers notified
as well, okay?
Do you have any... any...
Okay, I'm sorry.
No, you don't need to be sorry.
Okay, don't... don't waste
your time with that.
Do you have gps coordinates
on your phone?
I got one of those fancy phones.
I don't know how to use it.
Can you go to your compass?
I don't know.
I've never used the compass.
Let's see.
Okay, my lat is
62.3235 degrees north.
My long is
150.1203 degrees west.
Okay.
I've got a fractured leg.
I do this all the time.
I'm even back here bear hunting.
This is my bear station.
What's the percentage
on your phone?
Darn.
I'm on...
You know that feeling
when your cellphone's
about to die?
That weird anxiety of being
cut off from the entire world?
Well, what are you
worried about?
Missing a text from a friend
or checking your social media?
Imagine it's night,
you're in the
remote alaskan wilderness
surrounded by grizzly bears,
your leg's broken,
the sun has set,
and the temperature is dropping.
And every time you make
a call for help,
that battery gets closer
and closer to dying.
Did we get good
coordinates for him, miles?
Yes, it's in there.
In the middle of
freakin' nowhere.
That's... I told...
I mean, like,
in the middle of nowhere.
See, that's the river.
Those are correct coordinates?
That's what he gave us,
but I'm thinking maybe
he didn't get them right.
Hey, kristen, did you give
these coordinates to them?
We haven't given them
the coordinates yet.
I don't think they're gonna be
able to drive there with an atv,
if that's really where he is.
That looks more like a helo.
Right.
We want to help you,
we might be able to find you,
but we can't get to you quickly.
The geographic square mileage
is huge.
Just at least let the guys
on atvs know
that those are their coordinates
before they go zooming out there
at night with the grizzlies.
City of new orleans 911.
What's the address
of your emergency?
Yeah, I don't have the address.
I left my daughter to sleep over
at my dad's house.
Mm-hmm.
Then she just called me
and told me that
my dad's not breathing
and he's purple in the face.
I'm... I'm on my way
back there now.
And she... she's only 9.
And she called me
crying herself.
And I was like,
"I'm calling for you, baby."
how old is your father?
H-he's 65.
Is he diagnosed with anything?
I don't... let me have you
talk to my husband.
He's got heart problems.
Alright.
So he does have heart problems.
Alright. I've sent this over
to my dispatcher
to get an ambulance,
and the fire department's
gonna go out there.
What's your daughter's name?
'cause I'm gonna call her
since she's on the scene
so I can find out
further information.
Her name's madison.
She's only 9 years old, ma'am.
The fire department
and the ambulance
is gonna go out there,
and I'm advising them
that she's on scene
with him by herself.
She's not gonna be able
to really...
How far away are you guys?
Probably 15 minutes.
I'm gonna give madison
a call, okay?
Alright.
With a child,
you have to talk slow.
You have to talk steady.
I have to be a little more
softer in my tone.
With an adult,
you can be a little more direct.
But with a child,
you don't want to scare them
from the beginning.
Hello?
Hi. Is this madison?
Yes, ma'am.
Hi, madison. My name's amanda.
I'm with the new orleans
police department.
How's your grandfather?
Where is he?
Um, he's in the room.
Okay. Can you get next to him so
you can tell me what he's doing?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, I do have an ambulance
coming out to you.
Okay.
Let me know when you're there,
okay?
I'm there.
Alright, what is he doing?
Is he's awake?
No, ma'am.
Is he breathing?
Um, like, his stomach's moving,
but not a lot.
Can I get you to do something
for me?
Yes, ma'am.
Alright, I want you to
tell me "now"
every time he takes a breath in,
okay?
So that I can calculate
his breathing.
Okay, say "now" for me, okay?
Okay.
Tell me "now" every time
he takes a breath in.
I need you to say "now"...
I don't hear him breathing.
Madison, can I get you to
attempt cpr on him?
I'll tell you how to do it,
and I'll stay
on the line with you, okay?
Okay. Can I put you on speaker?
Yes, please.
Okay.
Alright, so what is... this is
what I want you to do.
I want you to take both
of your hands...
Mm-hmm.
...And I want you
to place the heel of your hand
on the breastbone.
That's gonna be
in between his nipples.
Okay.
Alright, I want you to put
one hand on top of each other,
and let me know
when you have it like that.
I have it.
Alright, so I want you to...
I want you to press hard
as you can down, okay?
And I'm gonna count with you.
We're gonna do compressions
until help arrives.
Okay.
We're gonna pump
the chest hard and fast,
at least twice per second
and two inches deep.
So I need you to
go as hard as...
Down as hard as
you possibly can, okay?
Okay.
Let me know
when you're ready.
I'm ready. Alright.
We're going to start now.
One, two, three, four.
Count out loud with me
so that I can know
you're doing it correctly, okay?
One, two, three, four.
- One, two, three.
- One, two...
One, two, three, four.
Are you pumping, madison?
Madison. Yes.
Are you pressing down hard?
He... he's all, like,
purple in the face,
and I can't... like,
he's spitting out water.
So he's spitting out water?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, so you don't want
to continue,
or you want to keep trying
until the help arrives?
He's making some kind of noise.
Right, so that...
Yeah, that means
he's agonal breathing,
which means
he's not breathing correctly.
So we continue the compressions
we can...
That'll help him until the units
arrive and take over.
I'm scared.
But if you're scared,
I understand.
Do you want to continue?
Madison?
I'm here.
Alright,
we're gonna continue, okay?
One, two... count with me, okay?
One...
One, two, three, four.
Alright, we're gonna
continue, okay?
One, two... count with me, okay?
One...
One, two, three, four.
They're here.
And also,
I talked to your mom and...
They're here?
They're, like, in there
with him.
Okay.
So the fire department's there
with him?
Mm-hmm.
And your mom and dad
are en route to you now, okay?
I spoke with them. Okay.
Alright. You did good.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
If you're giving
cpr instructions,
you may have been on the phone
for two minutes, but to me,
it felt like I've been on there
my whole 12-hour shift.
I mean, I never want to have to
give a child
cpr instructions for someone.
I love kids.
I have 12 nieces and nephews,
so I've been around kids
my whole life.
A child shouldn't have
to go through that.
She was really scared. - Mm-hmm.
But on the call,
the father was like
he shouldn't
have left her there.
But he was like, he kind...
He's kind of glad
because she was able
to get him help.
But I feel like that's
a big responsibility
on someone that young.
Right.
And she was petrified
and having to do cpr
on an adult that...
On her grandfather. Yeah.
But it looks like he's okay.
He's at the hospital now.
But...
Well, at least I'm glad
she was there to help him.
Mm-hmm.
911. What's the address
of the emergency?
This is frank. I'm just east
of the talkeetna river again.
Doggone it, you guys got
better things to do.
No, no, this is exactly
what we're here for.
I-I'm sorry. No, you just relax.
You try to stay comfortable
until we get you that help.
I have been a call taker
for about
two and a half years now,
so not very long
compared to my peers.
When I look at the people
that I work with,
I see heroes.
The purpose that
I was looking for,
for serving the community,
for making a positive difference
in lives,
I'm finding it here.
How are you doing on warmth?
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah. I mean,
I'm a little bit chilled,
but I can't walk out of here.
Alright, you're doing
a very good job.
You just stay right with me,
okay?
I hear a wheeler now.
Is that your help?
I'm not sure.
Let me double check.
Does it sound like
that's gonna be, uh...
I can't get ahold of my guys
on the radio.
Okay. They're too far out.
I keep trying to reach them,
but...
Okay.
If you're able to do so, maybe
just try to holler for them.
Hey!
Do you have enough battery
for me to stay on the line
with you while they get to you?
I got 1% right now.
I've been keeping it warm
in my underwear.
Okay.
Wait. They're coming towards me.
I see light.
Lights are coming towards you?
They must be in the river.
Okay.
Hey!
Do you have any flashlights?
Anything that can make light?
Just my phone. Hey!
They're driving upriver from me.
Hey! Hey!
Yeah, they're heading
away from me now.
Help! Hey!
Help!
Hey!
City of new orleans 911.
What's the address
of your emergency?
Repeat for me, ma'am?
Is anyone in danger right now?
Man.
Boxers hanging on his ankle?
Okay, and what else
did you notice about him?
What? I'm sorry.
Alright, ma'am.
Stay on the line.
I'm getting this
information out.
He's naked. Who?
The man on louisa.
Oh, lord.
Well, the sun not out,
so it can't be a suntan.
Not trying to get no suntan.
Alright, I do apologize
for the silence, ma'am.
Just getting
the information out.
That's okay.
I am having someone sent over
to the location.
Okay. Alright. Thank you, ma'am.
Alright.
Mm. They do some weird stuff
in this city, child.
I sent them some help.
They out early.
Every 911 call
has a unique twist,
challenge, or puzzle
to decipher.
Technology helps our call takers
communicate.
Austin 911. Do you need
police, fire, or ems?
I need police.
It helps them
locate the person in need.
Okay, what's going on right now
at that location?
Tracking technology
can even reassure a caller
that help is just moments away.
They're coming to
you right now, okay?
Don't panic.
Okay. Thank you so much.
But there's no computer
on the planet
that can replace the empathy
or determination it takes
to truly get to the bottom
of every story.
Austin 911. This is austin 911.
Do you have an emergency?
Somebody just rang my doorbell
at this late hour,
and they're wearing a mask.
Okay.
So it's somebody
that has a mask on.
Okay.
And is it just
yourself in the home?
Yes.
Baker 704 is advising
on a suspicious person.
You're doing a great job, okay?
I already have help on the way,
okay?
Okay.
Can you see where they are now?
Are they still there?
I'm too afraid to look
through the window.
He keeps looking through
my window in the kitchen.
That's what scared me.
He's been to the front door
three times
and around to the side,
I think only once,
but I don't know for sure.
Were you able to see any weapons
on him at all?
Uh, they looked to be carrying
a lot of cloth.
Carrying cloth?
Yeah.
The officers are coming
as fast as they can, okay?
Okay.
Do you remember
if they had all tried
to get inside of your home?
No, not yet.
Okay.
They're now walking down
the driveway, but very slowly.
They're not leaving.
Okay, and can you see anything
about the suspect?
How tall they are?
Any kind of clothing
description?
If they're dark colors?
Okay.
He's sitting in my yard.
Oh, lord, god.
Did it appear that he was
intoxicated or on drugs
or having mental health issues
or any...
Any kind of injured at all?
Okay. Officers are coming
as fast as they can.
They're on allandale, okay?
Oh, man.
Hello?
Are you still there?
Yes.
Okay.
What are you seeing and hearing?
They may be gone.
We're gonna check the area
and make sure.
They're almost there.
Oh, my god!
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Oh, god. They're coming back.
You should be seeing officers
here in just a minute.
I don't blame you at all.
Can you see or hear
anything else?
What's going on?
Oh, my god!
He's back up in the driveway!
Okay.
Oh, god. They're coming back.
You should be seeing officers
here in just a minute.
Can you see or hear
anything else from where you are
without going outside or
making yourself uncomfortable?
What's going on?
I think it might be my...
My sister.
It's your sister?
Oh, my god.
Can you tell if it's your sister
right now?
Beverly?
My god.
You scared
the living crap out of me.
I'm glad it...
It all worked out.
Go ahead and speak
with the officer.
Call back if anything changes,
okay?
Thank you. I'm so sorry.
You're welcome, ma'am. Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Ah, priceless.
It's the complainant's sister.
Can't. I can't with people.
She said he had, like,
a bag of clothes
or something like that,
and I was just like...
She thought it was a murder bag?
Funny.
Hey!
It's been just over an hour
since a stranded bear hunter
called 911.
Help! Help!
Yeah!
Yeah? I think
someone responded to him.
Ooh, really? We have a response?
Somebody yelled back?
Yeah, somebody yelled.
No, I'm across the river!
Downstream!
They're talking to me now,
so they know I'm here.
Okay. Okay, that's good.
I'm gonna be right here
on the line with you.
I think the fire chief is here
with me now.
He's in contact with you?
- Sweet.
- Whoo-hoo!
Don't make that noise
in the background.
Alright, sir, I'm gonna
go ahead and let you go
since he does have eyes on you.
Okay. Okay.
Hey, what's your name?
My name is miles.
Miles. Thank you, miles.
Oh... thank you very much.
Oh, thank... thank you, sir.
I'm glad you're okay.
Stay safe out there. Bye-bye.
He says he actually
recognizes the guy.
- Of course.
- He used to be fire department.
It's like the chief
or something, so...
Sweet.
Yay!
Good job, miles.
No, good job, everybody.
Good job, everybody.
For a search and rescue call,
the fact that
someone is able to call
from out in the middle
of nowhere
and speak to me directly is
the biggest asset that we have.
So even in the worst situations,
people just know
"all I got to do is dial 911,"
and we stand a very good chance
of finding you.
Subtitles >>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org