-[man speaks indistinctly on radio]
-[woman speaks indistinctly on radio]
[cars honking]
[man on radio] If you're heading
into Manhattan, it's a real stinker today.
All major routes between Downtown
and Midtown are jammed.
If you're trying to get to Midtown
do yourself a favor, jump on the subway.
[siren wails]
[train rumbles]
[sneezes]
[woman on PA]
Fifty-ninth Street.
This is 59th Street, people.
Shop till you drop.
-Stand clear of the closing doors, please.
-[kid chuckles]
[woman on PA]
Okay. Fifty-first Street.
Fifty-first Street.
Watch your step.
Stand clear of the closing doors, please.
Forty-second Street.
Grand Central Station.
[sighs]
[woman on PA] Stand clear
of the closing doors, please.
[train rumbles]
[train screeches]
[woman on PA]
Twenty-eighth Street, people.
[door closing]
Hey, I gotta see back there.
-[gun clicks]
-Whoa, whoa, whoa. What do you want?
I'm taking your train.
[knocking on door]
-Yeah?
-Back up, lady.
Whoa! What the hell are you doing?
Now, open that cab door. Do it now.
Get back. Move. Back. [sniffs]
Get back.
Get your foot off the mike pedal
or I'll shoot it off.
-Just back off with that gun, all right?
-Just answer the question.
What do you see?
I see a man
leaning against the front car.
When he gets on, you shut the doors.
All right.
[bell ringing]
Happy?
-[sneezes]
-[knocking on door]
[exhales]
-All right, Mr. Green?
-Yeah, hundred percent.
Okay. Let's go for a ride.
[train rumbles]
-[sniffs]
-[train thuds]
-Oh.
-I thought you could drive this thing.
Yeah, it wasn't my fault.
This train bucks all the time,
especially in switching.
-She's a dog.
-Yeah, I know she's a dog. [sniffs]
Where's the electric box?
[train rumbling]
[brakes screeching]
[grunts]
I'm taking the brake handle,
reverse key. [sniffs]
And I want your cutting key too.
[Mr. Green sniffing]
Thank you.
Command Center
will call in about a minute.
You will not answer. Is that clear?
Yes, sir. They can call all they want.
I'm deaf. I'm out of it.
- [breathes nervously]
- Keep still.
-[exhales]
-Calm.
Very good.
[man coughs]
-[man] Yeah, yeah, go ahead.
-Why did the train stop?
[clears throat]
Hey, mister, what's going on?
-Thank you, Mr. Grey.
-Don't mention, Mr. Green.
[Mr. Green sniffs]
-Excuse me.
-Hey! Who the hell are you?
-Can I have your, uh, cab key, please?
-[woman] Give him the key.
-Please.
-Give him the key.
-No.
-Give it up!
Thank you.
Frank, what's going on with Pelham?
[phone ringing]
-What's going on here? Look at this.
-[laughs]
What the heck is going on?
-Look at it, Caz.
-What?
Stonehouse, what's the problem?
[Frank] I got a southbound local,
he's laying down between 23rd and 28th.
-[man] How long?
-A couple, three minutes.
I tried to raise him with the radio
but he won't answer the radio.
-Why won't he answer the radio?
-Don't worry. It could be a lot of things.
[Frank over radio]
Command Center calling Pelham 123.
Pelham 123, do you read me?
Come in, please. Where are you?
[clunks]
[Frank over radio]
Pelham 123, come in, please.
What are you, deaf?
[rumbling]
Well, he's moving now.
[beeps]
-That dumb idiot's moving backwards!
-[man] Oh, no!
[screeches]
-Stopped again.
-Stopped is better than backwards.
Yeah. Pelham 123, please, come in.
[coughs]
[Frank] Command Center to Pelham 123,
do you read me? Come in, please.
Command Center to Pelham 123,
come in, please.
What the hell?
-Any trouble, Mr. Green?
-[sniffs]
Smooth as silk, Mr. Blue.
Well, let's get it moving.
-We're behind two minutes.
-Okay.
Here we go.
[Frank] Command Center to Pelham 123,
come in, please.
[train rumbles]
-Whoa! There you go.
-She's moving again.
Forward this time.
[beeps]
Oh, my God! She's split! Look at this.
-Yeah, I can see that.
-I've never seen that done.
[exhales] Holy mackerel!
-[woman 1 gasping]
-[woman 2] Hey, hey.
-[man] Hey, hey!
-[people screaming in panic]
-[people screaming indistinctly]
-[gun clicks]
-[man] What's going on?
-[woman] Oh, my God!
Attention, please! Everybody, sit down.
Sit down.
Remain seated.
If you rise, you will be shot.
-[woman 1] What?
-[woman 2] Oh, my God!
-[people chattering]
-Silence!
[chattering stops]
-Who's with you?
-Uh, nobody.
I mean, my mom is meeting us.
She said to call 911 if we're not home
in exactly 38 hours.
Uh, minutes.
This is not gonna happen.
See that red dot on your chest?
If I squeeze this trigger,
I'll fill it with 850 rounds a minute.
Sit down.
Sit down!
Very good.
You want a pack of gum?
Take it.
Thank you.
[screeches]
[man]
He has stopped again.
[Frank] Hey, people,
I got cars piling up here.
What's he doing now?
Pelham 123, come in, please!
What are they doing now?
What a couple of mental cases.
I'm going down there.
Command Center to Pelham 123,
come in, please!
[Mr. Blue]
Train operator!
-Yes, sir?
-[Mr. Blue] Come to me.
Come!
All right, this is what I want you to do.
I want you to go back to those five cars
that we cut loose.
I want you to gather those people together
and walk them back
to the 28th Street Station. You got that?
People hate getting off
in a middle of a tunnel.
-Please shut up and just do it.
-Yes, sir.
Please let me off.
I have a doctor's appointment.
-No.
-Come on, lady. Sit down.
Please.
The same thing happened to me
on the Long Island Railroad. I swear.
I couldn't go through it all over again.
Nobody leaves.
Sit down, lady. [sniffs]
Okay. Except my brother.
-Nobody leaves.
-Come on. He's just a kid.
-Quiet up, little man.
-Sit down.
Oh, excuse me, mister.
Don't you think you should let us in
on what's going on?
-Maybe we could help.
-[door opens]
You're being held by four dangerous people
with automatic weapons.
That's what's going on.
Is that clear?
[footsteps approaching]
[grunts]
[box opens]
[people screaming indistinctly]
-[man] Hey, what's going on?
-Hey, hey, calm down.
-All right, calm down!
-[screaming stops]
Sit down.
-[device beeping]
-[Mr. Green sighing]
[Mr. Green sighs]
-[coughs]
-[Frank speaking over radio, indistinct]
Motion detector is in place.
Power is out between 14th and 33rd.
All four tracks.
Local express, northbound and south.
-I still see lights on the tunnel.
-Emergency lighting.
They're on AC, just like the signals.
Do you read me?
Pelham 123, come in, please.
She's still laying dead.
-What time you got, Mr. Green?
-I got 3:10.
Command Center to Pelham 123.
Did you cut the electricity down there?
Answer me.
-It's time to talk to them.
-[clears throat]
[coughs]
-[sniffs]
-Are you all right?
This thing's gonna kill me.
-That's entirely possible.
-[sighs]
This is Pelham 123 to Command Center,
do you read me?
Yeah. I read you, you maniac!
Where the hell have you been?
Do you know that Caz Holowitcz
is personally coming down there
to fry your ass?
We have taken your train.
I repeat, we have taken your train.
[people chattering]
Everybody just shut up, okay?
Just wait--
-Shut up in here now!
-[chattering stops]
Pelham 123...
what exactly do you mean
that the train has been taken?
-Are you the operator?
-Negative.
-Then who are you?
-We have hijacked your train.
What?
[Mr. Blue]
We are heavily armed.
We are holding hostages,
and we will not hesitate to kill any
and all of them
if you do not do precisely as we say.
Am I making myself clear?
Absolutely, yes. Sure.
[beeps]
Do not bother using your six wire.
I will communicate
only with the New York City Police
Hostage Negotiation Team,
nobody else.
That's all.
[sniffs]
[phone ringing]
-Yeah?
-Detective Specialist Inez Raye, please.
-Prescotti?
-Hey! I didn't recognized your voice.
-How's the transit authority?
-Hey, you must miss me, right?
Glad to be out of the real world?
I'm not out of it right now. We got
some psycho that just hijacked a train.
How fast can you get over
to the 42nd Street Command Center?
-I'll be right over.
-[Prescotti] All right, hurry up.
[Mr. Green sighing]
[sniffs]
-[Mr. Blue] Perimeter clear?
-Clear as day.
[sighs]
[machine hums]
[monitor beeping]
[Frank] Listen, are you gonna wait
for your partner or you wanna, uh--?
[Prescotti]
We hear you, Pelham 123. We hear you.
Hello. Can you hear us?
Can you hear us? Come in, please.
Identify yourself.
Yeah, I'm Detective Prescotti
of the Negotiation team.
Can you tell me your name?
What would you like me to call you?
Give me something so that we can talk
to each other. How about that, huh?
-Call me Blue.
-All right, Blue.
Call me Anthony, all right?
Why don't you tell me in your own words
what's going on down there?
I'd like to hear it from you.
Anthony, we have 14 hostages,
including two children.
And we will kill one
every time you do not follow our commands.
I hope that's clear.
Listen, there's no reason
for anybody to get hurt.
We're gonna work through this, okay?
[Blue]
We demand five million dollars in cash
for the release of the subway car
and all the hostages.
It is now 3:13.
The money must be in our hands by 4:13.
One hour from now.
I know your capabilities.
At precisely 4:13,
we will execute one hostage
for every minute you are late.
When you've contacted the mayor's office,
report back to me
for further instructions.
All right, let me see
if I got this straight, okay?
These demands are not negotiable.
We got 14 people. Two are kids.
They want five million.
Okay. But let's make sure we understand
that no one has to get hurt.
Blue, come in.
Pelham 123, this is Command Center.
I got to find out
that I have everything together on this.
Please, Blue, come back to me.
Come back, Blue.
Blue, come in, come in.
Pelham 123, come in.
[people chattering]
[woman]
This is ridiculous.
What's the hold up?
Something on the track?
Is it a jumper or a pusher?
I believe
it's a mechanical problem, ma'am.
-[man over radio] Central to Post 17.
-Excuse me. Post 17. Go ahead, Central.
[man]
Call by landline immediately.
-Uh-huh.
-[man] Do you copy?
Yeah.
[man 1]
Hey, officer, what's going on here?
[man 2]
Yeah, what's going on around here?
Hey, officer, I'm talking to you.
What are you, on a break?
-Calling your bookie?
-[phone rings]
Take the bus, ma'am.
Post 17, what do we got?
[man over phone]
A subway car has been hijacked.
There are hostages involved,
we're not putting it out on the radio.
We're trying to keep the media out of it
as long as possible.
I read you.
[man] There's a transit
authority supervisor down there
somewhere between 28th and 14th.
I saw him a couple of minutes ago.
He was headed down track on foot.
[man]
Find him and get him out!
Officer, are you listening?
[officer] Post 17 to Central,
I'm looking down the tunnel now.
I don't see him. I'm going in after him.
[people chattering]
[Caz] Where are you going?
Your job is to stay on that train.
-They said they'd kill me.
-You're like the captain of a ship.
-You're supposed to go down with it.
-That young woman conductor is going down,
-I'd do it for you?
-Excuse me, do you work for the subway?
You butt out! Tell Command Central
I'm on my way to investigate.
-I wouldn't do that if I were you.
-I know you wouldn't.
Excuse me, I'm sorry.
Which is the famous third rail?
That's it.
Six hundred and twenty-five volts.
-[chuckles] Fry you to a crisp.
-If the power is on, which it ain't.
Let's cut through the fat real quick.
He's not negotiating.
He's determined to complete the job.
He's a consummate pro.
He'll only talk to us on his terms
when he wants to.
-Yeah, I wouldn't wait for him to call.
-You should be sitting in this seat.
You got here first.
I'll coach and you can be the hero.
Thanks a lot.
-This is boring.
-Be happy it's so boring.
-Shut up.
-Yeah.
-You know, why don't you let the kids go?
-Nobody asked you, bitch.
-Yo, watch your mouth.
-Watch yours.
Yo, nobody means any disrespect.
I'm sorry. My bad. All right?
You got kids here. It's unpredictable.
I'm just saying
that you should let 'em go. That's all.
Nobody's supposed to talk.
Nobody's talking.
Do you mind not pointing that gun?
[whispers]
Shoot him.
[sighs]
Hey.
Do you like pornography?
Hmm?
I do.
Huh?
Do you like guns?
This is a really cool gun.
What's your name, huh?
Come on. Whisper it to me.
Shaky.
I'll call you "Shaky".
[chuckles]
Hey.
Shaky.
Mr. Grey.
-[sighs]
-Can I see you a moment, please?
Keep my seat warm.
Yeah?
Leave the woman alone.
Just stand here, Mr. Grey.
"Stand here, Mr. Grey", what?
What's the magic word... Mr. Blue?
Money.
[door lock clicking]
[chuckles]
What?
[Anthony]
Hello, Blue. Pelham 123, come in.
Come in, Pelham 123. Do you hear me?
Pelham 123, come in.
Do you have authorization
from the mayor's office
to pay the five million dollars?
No, not yet.
[Mr. Blue]
You have 49 minutes.
-[Anthony] Listen...
-And we will execute a hostage.
Listen, it's gonna take time
to get that kind of money.
You know that, Blue. And that's the truth.
Now, do you want me
to tell you the truth here
or do you want me to lie to you?
Truth would be less costly
for the people on this train.
[Anthony]
Good. Then we understand each other.
Now... You got two kids on the train.
Yes. Your point being?
Well, I can tell you I got one.
They get hungry, they get antsy.
They're a factor that you can't control.
Why don't we just release the children?
-The children stay.
-[sneezes]
Bless you.
Everything that you try to do to cooperate
is gonna work in your favor.
Every person that you release
is another argument
your attorney can make
before the judge.
-No, no, no. I will not be judged.
-[sniffs]
What does that mean?
You have 48 minutes. Thank you.
[Anthony]
Blue, come on. Just stay with me, Blue.
This guy won't budge.
I got to pee.
-You got to go to the bathroom.
-Quiet.
He's got to go to the bathroom.
You have to let him go.
-Yeah, he can hold it.
-Come on. It could get nasty.
[sighs]
Brown.
-What?
-Kid's got to pee.
[Brown]
So?
-So take him.
-Why me?
Just do it.
I'll take him. Come on, babe.
Not you. Sit down.
Where's the bathroom?
You're just gonna have to go
off the edge, all right, babe?
-Don't look.
-[woman] I promise.
So what's that supposed to be?
-It's a solid gold M16.
-Nice thing to wear around your neck.
Is that supposed to make you bad?
-We're not supposed to talk to you.
-Come on.
It's just us.
Bad guys are over there.
I was bad too.
I was so bad.
I was so bad, they took my baby away.
So?
So now I don't hangout
with my old friends
who ain't got no damn life.
I got me a job, and I got my son back.
He's four years old now.
He's got his whole life ahead of him.
You know that?
Just like this little kid right here.
Come on, Brown.
Just say he escaped. Say it was my fault.
They'd kill you.
Come on.
Detectives Raye, Prescotti, deputy mayor.
-Hello.
-[Anthony] Hi, how are you?
What about the ransom?
The mayor will not allow himself to be
boxed into a corner by a bunch of crazies.
With all due respect,
but these people are not crazy.
It's reasonable and prudent
to suppose you can hijack a train,
get five million dollars in cash,
and walk out through a subway tunnel
in the middle of Manhattan
at four in the afternoon
while the whole world watches it on TV?
Yes!
-They have a plan.
-What is it?
Respectfully, sir... we don't know.
Well, what do they want?
Could be a mercenary
who doesn't care about the cause.
Cause is money.
Yeah, but, uh, not a lot.
Come on down here, John.
We have a guy
that's got 14 hostages in there,
with two kids being part of that
14 hostages. He's a consummate pro.
And he's planned down to the second,
and he's given us a deadline of 4:13.
This guy could ask you for $30 million,
and you'd have to give it to him.
Timing and control
are everything to this man.
-So he's not gonna give it up?
-[Raye and Anthony] No.
Yes. Well, the City of New York
does not give in to terrorists.
How about just getting the money,
just as an option?
Do your job. We don't want options.
[sirens wailing]
I got a transit authority supervisor
headed down the tunnel.
One of the guys thinks it's his train.
-[Raye] Get him out.
-Yeah, I dispatched a patrol officer.
You mean to tell me
an officer has a radio down there?
-[officer] Yeah.
-That's good.
He can be our eyes.
-[beeps]
-[footsteps approaching]
[beeping]
[computer beeping]
Action.
-Move it, move it, move it. Move it.
-[woman] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Just back it up, cowboy.
-What the hell do you think you're doing?
-[gun cocks]
This is city property
you're fooling around with.
Yeah? So's the pigeon poop
on Grant's Tomb.
I'm a line superintendent.
I'm coming on board.
-I warned you, stupid.
-[Caz grunts]
[woman gasping]
Oh!
Hey, everybody forward!
Let's go, let's go!
[people screaming]
Everybody forward. Let's go.
What happened?
Hey, I warned the stupid bastard.
He just kept coming.
-Was he alone?
-I didn't see anything.
[Mr. Green]
There's another blip on the screen.
-[Mr. Blue] Just one?
-As far as I know, yeah.
Okay.
Not unexpected.
Stay calm.
-Watch the door.
-I got it.
I thought no one was supposed to get hurt.
That's what you said, right?
No one was supposed to get hurt, right?
[sighs]
I guess I got us on the scoreboard, huh?
[radio clicks]
I can't believe it.
They just shot the supervisor.
Is he alive? Can we help him?
No.
They just drew first blood.
-Uh, your line supervisor.
-Caz Holowitcz?
They shot Caz Holowitcz?
Uh, I don't have positive identification.
They shot Caz Holowitcz. They shot Caz.
Brown...
Listen, you know you can get out
of this anytime, right?
You just walk out that door anytime.
-You don't get it.
-I do get it, okay?
It's about fear.
You think this makes you bad, huh?
You know this is wrong.
Come on.
Mr. Brown...
I want you to walk over to the other end
and cover that door.
I want Mr. Grey over here with me
so I can keep an eye on him.
He loves his guns.
Maybe it was necessary.
I didn't see.
He got off on it.
[Anthony over radio]
Come in, Pelham 123.
You just shot our line supervisor.
I thought we had an agreement
going here, Blue.
Come in, Pelham 123.
Blue, come in...
We told you that's what you get,
didn't we?
[sneezes]
But you're too arrogant
and almighty to think...
[door opens]
...that anyone could ever crack
the system. Well, somebody did, all right?
-All right? Well, that's what you get.
-[Anthony] Who is this? Hello?
-Who is this?
-[door slams]
Hello, Pelham 123.
Who is this, Pelham 123?
Tell them.
We told you to stay away.
Who is this?
Who was that guy?
I told you that this wasn't a game.
[Anthony]
Hello, Blue. Come in, Blue. Come in--
I do the talking. Yes?
Yeah. [sniffs]
Yeah, sure. Sorry.
I just-- I knew the line super.
-Did you?
-Yeah.
Caz Holowitcz.
Flamboyant jerk.
Ran his own old kingdom.
That's what I'm talking about. That's what
I was always running up against.
You must... stay relaxed.
I'm relaxed.
I mean, I'm not--
You know, I'm... I'm relaxed.
[sighs]
You...
You are a curious man.
All right, hold it.
People, people, listen up.
There's an undercover cop on the train.
There were two, street crime unit.
One got off at 33rd Street.
Called in later when the news got out.
Partner is still on the train,
-one of the hostages.
-Male or female?
Don't know yet.
-[Raye] What time?
-3:31.
Somebody's got to fix
this digital on here now too.
-Hey.
-[man] Yes, sir.
[Anthony]
Fix the digital on this side over here.
[man]
Right away.
What are you people doing here, huh?
-I'm sorry, all right?
-I have got operators calling...
And there's a row of computers
that just went out.
I'm sorry, all right?
We all have problems right now.
Yeah, yeah. We all got problems, huh?
You wanna hear about problems?
How about half a million passengers
trying to get home?
-Stonehouse, I'm sorry.
-I'm gonna tell you something.
I never thought I'd see the day
that talking to a murderer
would take priority
over running a railroad!
Pelham 123 to Command Center.
[Anthony]
Blue, come in. Yeah, we're here.
You know what we're trying to do
out here, right?
You have 40 minutes left.
I don't like this guy.
Look, you either gonna deal with me
or you can deal with the tactical team.
My high command
is already getting antsy so...
Please,
I think we can talk this thing through.
It's just me and you.
You asked for us and here we are.
[talks with Italian accent]
Bravo, bravo, Antonio.
You play your part very well.
I'm not playing and neither are you.
Now, there's one man down already,
but I think we can work this out.
We?
-It will work out.
-[handset beeps]
Blue.
Blue?
Now, explain to me this.
These lights are the power boxes.
And these are the ladders to the exits.
It's the emergency ones.
-How many blocks are we looking at here?
-Ten blocks.
-Thirty?
-Oh, yeah.
-Thirty exits in a ten-block area.
Well, that makes sense.
-You better get your Plan B ready.
-Why the sudden change?
There's no sudden change.
I'm just playing the odds.
[Shaky breathing heavily]
[labored breathing]
-Hey. Do you have a medical condition?
-I can't breathe.
-Heart problems?
-I can't--
-Asthma?
-[gasping]
Listen, you're okay. Just breathe.
-Three deep breathes. Here you go.
-[Shaky inhales]
Are your people in place?
I can have three five-man teams
in the subway in two minutes
but it's a gamble.
The hijackers are protected.
We don't know how many
or where they are in the train.
-Go in. Take 'em out.
-[woman] Yes, sir.
[Shaky crying]
-Shut!
-[gasps]
Shut up, Shaky.
You, sit down now.
-Shut your face.
-[door opens]
Everything quiet out here, Mr. Grey?
-[Shaky sobs]
-[Mr. Grey] Everything's fine.
[men over radio talking indistinctly]
[man over radio]
Stay out of sight.
-Repeat, stay out of sight.
-[man] Take cover. Take cover.
[man]
Get in position.
Lay down.
Hey. Go, go, go. Go.
[beeping]
Look at this. Look at this.
-[Mr. Blue] It's just like clockwork.
-Like clockwork?
-You better be right.
-Of course I'm right.
[sighs] They sure are taking their time.
Don't worry.
They'll pay us. They have no choice.
They might not just go along with it,
you know. [sniffs]
You know, they might say, "Okay,"
and then try to...
Well, then a lot of people will die.
Including us. [sniffs]
-Well, either you live or you die.
-Think I care.
I don't care. Who wants to drive
a subway train the rest of his life?
-What'd they finally nail you for?
-They didn't nail me, I was framed.
I was. [sniffs]
They had a gang running dope
on the subways,
giving it to a train operator,
him giving it to a contact downtown.
They tried to pin it on me.
They didn't have any evidence.
-Hmm. You were innocent.
-Yeah.
[chuckles]
Yeah, I was innocent.
I wouldn't do something like that.
You think I'd do something like that?
Sniper reports
that there are two other suspects
down there with machine guns,
plus whoever else is in the cab with Blue.
Excuse me.
There's another voice on this tape.
-Can you cue it up?
-Yeah.
[tape playing in reverse]
-Go ahead, play.
-[man] Okay.
[Mr. Green] ...but you're
too arrogant and almighty to think
that anyone could ever crack the system.
Well, somebody did, all right?
[sneezing]
I told you it's going around.
This guy sounds like a train operator.
Astoria Boulevard.
-Myrtle Avenue.
-Flatbush.
Pelham 123 to Command Center.
-Anthony here. Go ahead.
-You have 33 minutes left, Anthony.
[Anthony]
I'm listening, Blue.
You are to have an armored car
waiting at the northwest corner
of the South Ferry subway entrance.
Got it.
You will have First Avenue cleared
to the Queensboro Bridge.
Where are you going?
Further instructions to follow. Blue out.
-How about the ransom?
-Under discussion at the mayor's office.
-What's taking so long?
-Well, it's not that simple.
Try getting a bank to do business
with the City of New York.
Get the money cleared as fast as you can.
We might get another shot at them.
You would pay,
and go along with this loony scheme
of driving an armored car
through the streets of Manhattan?
Yes, I would, sir.
Listen, I would pay,
I'd get more time with the hostages,
and, look it,
I'd get another shot at these guys,
and I might be able to bring
a couple of the bad guys down.
-You mean, you'd kill the bad guys?
-That would be the plan, sir.
-Good footage.
-Excellent footage, sir.
What about the hostages?
Any chance of them
being caught in-- in the middle?
-There's no guarantee.
-The snipers don't miss.
So maybe we lose one or two,
that's not bad out of eight.
As long as it's not a child.
No, no, there's 14 hostages, sir.
And, yeah, I mean, the mayor would
have won by a landslide but killing a kid,
-that would be hard to put a spin on it.
-We're talking about people's lives.
We're talking about the six o'clock news.
What time did you say
-this would be going down?
-Anytime you like, sir.
We can't move without the ransom money.
-Are we agreed on that?
-Yes.
You make me ashamed to say
that I work for the City of New York.
Just put it down
and do what you're supposed to do.
Excuse me.
But I need a list of all the MTA workers
who were fired or who quit under
bad circumstances in the last ten years.
Yeah, well, you do it yourself, okay?
'Cause I got few other things
to do over here.
Maybe you didn't notice.
Send all locals around the loop
at South Ferry, will you?
Reroute that thing over there, please.
[keyboard clicking]
Mr. Stonehouse, I'm sorry
that you lost your friend today.
But someone down there,
one of those suspects,
they know how the subways system works.
They know how to run a train,
it's one of yours.
It's one of mine?
-I'll get you a list of the employees.
-Thank you.
-[siren wailing]
-[people chattering]
Hey, guys, can we get inside?
-No, no. You can't go in there.
-No. No access.
[whispers]
Let's go to the other side.
[officer]
Yes, you, back behind the barricade.
Back it up.
[people chattering]
[woman singing in Spanish]
Nobody's supposed to talk.
-You, get over here.
-Hey, leave him alone!
-Stop it. Stop it.
-[grunts]
-[kid] What're you doing? Leave him alone.
-Sit.
-Stop it! Stop it!
-[kid] Leave him alone.
♪ I'm never gonna do without ♪
[woman]
Come on. Just calm down.
♪ I'm never gonna do without ♪
Please, stop. Please.
What are you doing?
What is your problem?
Huh?
Are you gonna shoot her?
Aren't we the hero?
You've got the money.
I'm going down there now.
-Meet me at the South Ferry entrance.
-Yes.
Command Center to Pelham 123.
They've agreed to pay the ransom.
I repeat, they have agreed
to pay the ransom.
Please take down
the next set of instructions.
All right, everybody take it down.
Suzanne, you're on.
The money is to be paid
in 50s and 100s.
All bills, random serial numbers.
It is to be bound in packs of 5,000,
crosswise with rubber bands.
Got it.
You will have a large private aircraft
waiting at the Marine Air Terminal.
Make sure there's food.
These people are hungry.
I don't understand. What food?
-The hostages. They're coming with me.
-Right.
He's taking the hostages with him?
The mayor's gonna flip.
Get someone.
Okay, Blue, you have your ransom.
Now, about the children?
Blue out.
[Anthony]
Come in, Blue. Come in.
[radio clunking]
Blue. Come in, Blue.
Blue, come in.
Please tell me what are you gonna do.
Come on, Blue. Come in.
[Mr. Blue]
What's happening here?
-What's happening?
-Yeah.
You brought the girl. Go ask her.
Attention, please.
The city has agreed
to pay for your release.
[people cheering]
[woman]
Yes.
As soon as you get the money,
will you let us go?
No. But shortly after.
Mister, would you mind telling us
how much you're getting?
-And why does that interest you?
-A person likes to know his worth.
Five million dollars.
Each?
All together.
That's not so terrific.
I need you to stay away from the women.
And I need you to stay out of my face.
I have shot people for not obeying me.
Well, I guess that's the difference
between me and you.
See, if I want somebody shot,
I'll do it myself.
With $5 million on the way,
it's a good time to shoot each other.
Women.
[people chattering]
[man]
Get the bag. Let's move it.
[man] Right over here.
Okay, very good. Pack it up.
-[people speaking indistinctly]
-[machines whirring]
They're telling me
they're sorting the money
but they're gonna need more time, Blue.
Come in. Come in.
-No more time.
-We're asking for 15 minutes more.
-Negative.
-Ten minutes, then.
Just give us ten more minutes.
Listen, you're in charge.
You can make this thing turn out right.
-It will.
-[handset beeps]
Fifteen minutes.
We do it by the numbers.
Just like the plan.
-Maybe an hour is not enough time.
-An hour is plenty.
You know how the system works.
You give 'em an hour, they take an hour,
you give 'em two, they take two.
An hour is plenty.
What if they can't make it?
Then we do what we said we'd do.
How long ago did I tell them
to get that money ready?
I asked them to do this
at least 25 minutes ago.
[machine whirring]
[people chattering]
-[man] Here you go.
-Get it. Got it all?
[sighs]
[people chattering]
-[man 1] Coming out.
-[man 2] Come on. Let's get over there.
-All right, here we go.
-The money is here.
The money is here.
Move it! Move it!
Here we go.
Move. Move!
[siren wails]
Proceeding west on Canal Street.
We're on our way to Lafayette.
Traffic heavy.
[woman over radio] We'll clear you
all the way to 28th Street.
-It's gonna be tight.
-[woman] Copy that.
-[sirens wailing]
-[car honking]
[cars screeching]
[woman over radio] There's a delay.
The patrol car has crashed.
Repeat, the patrol car has crashed.
There's been an accident.
Yeah. What?
I don't believe it.
There's been an accident.
The cruiser crashed,
they're out of commission.
Tell them to get the money
and keep going.
Get the money out. Keep on going. Move!
Yeah.
-Are you all right?
-Get the money.
All right, let's go. Go.
Command Center to Pelham 123.
Come in, Blue. We've got a problem.
Which is what?
The motorcade
that was bringing the money just crashed.
I told you no more concessions.
If you thought I wasn't serious,
then you're even more incompetent
than I give you credit for.
Mr. Green...
Yeah.
We are coming up on one minute.
Which one is it gonna be?
[gun clicks]
What difference does it make?
There it is. There it is.
-[man] Can you zoom in?
-[woman sighs] No.
No, we gotta move up.
Take it easy, okay?
I don't wanna get any closer
to those crazies than we have to.
-They're not gonna make it.
-He'll execute, no question.
Are you prepared to hit the train?
We'll do what we have to do
but it's not gonna be a walk in the park.
You give us the word and we'll go in.
-Fifty-five seconds.
-I don't believe this.
Well, if you don't have
the stomach for it, stay here.
What do they expect us to do?
If they know that we're wrecked,
how can they ask us--
They don't know anything.
That's it.
Command Center to Pelham 123.
The money has arrived.
I repeat, the money has arrived.
-Excuse me. What are you doing?
-They only know what we tell 'em.
Command Center to Pelham 123.
Come in, Blue. This is Anthony.
The money has arrived.
I repeat, the money has arrived.
You just made it, didn't you?
-Yeah.
-Listen closely.
You are to send two
unarmed police officers down the track.
Carrying five million dollars
in small bills, right?
They can manage.
Now, the children will open the bags
so no dye packs.
Got it.
[handset beeps]
[sirens wailing]
[people chattering]
All right, make some room.
-Come on.
-All right, let's go.
Go, go! Get it down there.
[beeping]
There they are.
It's too soon.
[man] Got a report
there's someone in the tunnel.
Hold your position.
See if you can get them out
without being seen.
Idiots.
Okay. How's the light?
Come on.
[mimicking gunshots]
Pow!
[blows]
-Hey, hey. Stop.
-[gasps]
-Stop. Police. Oh, Jesus!
-[man] Don't shoot!
-[gun fires]
-Who's shooting?
Look out! Don't shoot!
-[glass shatters]
-[people screaming]
[man over radio]
Someone's shooting down there.
[people screaming]
[man]
We have shots fired.
[grunts]
[people screaming]
Shut up and be quiet!
-What the hell are you doing?
-[Mr. Blue] Shut up.
[man over radio]
What's going on down there?
Hold your fire. Hold your fire.
I don't know who fired first,
but these two TV news guys
were right in the middle of it.
They're okay. They weren't hit.
[woman]
Excuse me.
I know first aid, I can help her.
-[Mr. Blue] Everybody shut up!
-[Mr. Green] Go on and go up there.
-Where are you shot, huh?
-Over here.
Let me see it.
You're gonna be all right, okay?
[Brown gasping]
Okay. This is what I want you to do,
just press on it.
-[gasps]
-I know it hurts. I know.
[Brown sighs]
-A lot of pressure, all right?
-Okay.
Where did you learn that?
[chuckles] On the job training, babe.
You're gonna be okay, all right?
Lucky for me.
You.
Me?
-Stand up, please.
-Hey, Mr. Blue.
This one is like my angel of mercy.
She's saving my life over here.
You'll be all right.
Come along.
-What for?
-I need your help. Come on.
Lucky bitch. You're getting out of here.
[door opens]
What I need you to do is I need you
to go down about a hundred feet.
Just wait for the men
delivering the money.
Be careful stepping off the train.
Hey.
When you see that baby,
you give him a hug for me, okay?
-Come on.
-Yeah.
Come on.
Should I tell them
that we need a medic?
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
[gasps]
[gunshots]
They just shot a hostage.
Get the kids.
Why? We're meeting their demands.
-They're getting their money.
-[man] Somebody threw a shot at them.
-[Raye] Who?
-Nobody knows.
Command Center to Pelham 123.
The money is in the tunnel,
and you shoot somebody?
-That wasn't the deal, Blue.
-You shot one of my people.
I told you what the penalty would be.
-[woman 1] What are you doing?
-[kid] Stop!
[woman 2]
Let him go!
[people screaming]
No!
-[man] Come on, bring them back.
-Shut up.
Why?
[people screaming]
Come on.
Now they've got two boys.
I can't tell what they're doing with them.
They're bringing out two kids.
What are you doing with the kids, Blue?
Two boys have been moved
to the back of the train.
-I'm going in with tear gas.
-Wait.
Why wait? They just killed a hostage.
-He's on it.
-What are you doing with the kids, Blue?
Whatever I do with the boys,
you can't stop me, can you?
No, Blue, you're in charge.
Well, I'm here. You're there.
And everything is going
according to your plan,
so there's no problem, right?
The money is in the tunnel.
I guarantee you that.
My men are down there,
and if you'll just give 'em a minute,
they'll walk it to you.
-[Mr. Green] Lights in the tunnel.
-Lights!
Just stay seated, people.
Okay, close enough.
Toss the bags up on the train.
Okay, gentlemen, turn around.
Go home.
Boys, look at me.
Drag the money right here.
Dump it out on the floor.
Oh!
Wow.
You boys ever see $5 million before?
Mr. Green...
[Mr. Grey chuckles]
Time to take care of business.
Give us a hand, Mr. Green.
[chuckles] Whoo!
[man over radio]
No one makes a move. Pull back.
Here's the complete list
of all the MTA employees
who were let go under bad circumstances
in the last ten years.
-How many?
-In total 63.
But half are either dead
or in the loony bin.
Uh, I can help narrow it down for you.
-Okay.
[Mr. Blue]
Pelham 123 to Command Center.
Quiet, everyone. Suzanne, get on this.
[Mr. Blue]
These will be my final instructions.
One,
immediately after this conversation,
you are to restore power
to the entire sector.
[Anthony]
Restore power.
Two, clear all local tracks.
And by clear,
I mean all signal set to green.
If I see a red light,
let alone get tripped by one,
I kill a hostage.
Got it.
Three, all south bound
and north bound trains
are to remain line dead.
If I see or pass a moving train,
-I kill a hostage.
-Got it.
Four, at the South Ferry Station,
I expect the armored car
and all roads clear
to the Marine Air Terminal.
-The plane should be fueled for--
-[Anthony] Tell me where you're going.
The plane should be fueled
for an international flight,
that's all you need to know.
Five, clear all police personnel
from the tunnel.
If you deviate in any way
from these instructions...
I kill a hostage.
-Blue out.
-[handset beeps]
We pull the ESU out of the tunnel
and secure the area around South Ferry.
Let's go, people. On the double.
[beeping]
-[man over radio] Pull back.
-Pull back.
Move it. Move it.
In a moment, the train will start moving.
-[train hums]
-[hostages sigh]
We expect to release you
in a short while.
[woman sighs]
But you will continue to do
exactly as we say.
[knocking on door]
-Very good.
-[Mr. Green sneezes]
[train brakes hissing]
[rumbles]
-[beeps]
-[woman] Wait, we got a problem here.
He's moving.
We're not prepared for this, man.
Pelham 123. Blue, what are you doing?
Blue. Blue, come in.
The track isn't clear.
Blue, we're not set up yet.
Why are you moving?
Slight change of plan.
Well, they're telling me you're gonna
start running into red lights.
Well, then you better make them green.
Continuing slow,
about five miles per hour.
They haven't figure anything out.
-Of course not.
-[lever thuds]
[screeching]
[train hisses]
She's stopped again.
[shatters]
-Coming.
-Tighten that up.
Sixty seconds, Mr. Green.
All right, Mr. Green?
Ready to roll, yeah.
[Anthony] Command Center
to Pelham 123. Come in.
Are all tracks clear
and signals set to green?
What's going on, Blue?
Are all tracks clear
and signals set to green?
-All clear.
-Yes.
You're a real gent.
Over and out.
Hello. Hello?
He's broke the connection. He's gone.
He broke the connection here.
[sniffs]
What are you lookin' at?
[laughs]
Ladies and gentlemen...
I am going out on the tracks
but I will have my eye on you.
You've been very helpful.
I want you to continue to be that way.
Thank you.
Ready?
[train rumbles]
He's moving.
Let's go. Move out.
Hey, hey. You better sit down.
Hey. Hold on. Hold on.
I'm a police officer.
-What?
-[woman] She's a cop?
[grunts]
Oh, my leg.
I think I heard someone.
-[Mr. Blue] Mr. Green. Mr. Green!
-I think I heard someone.
What if they're not on the train?
-That could never happen.
-What if they set the throttle
-and jumped off the train?
-Hey, move the Pelham line, please.
There's a little gizmo
called a dead man's feature.
It's build right
into the controller's handle,
in case the operator drops dead.
Somebody's hand
is always gotta be on that thing
or the train stops cold.
It's low tech but it works.
-Where are they taking us now?
-Don't worry, don't worry.
They'll gonna let us go pretty soon.
Can't anybody count?
All four of them got off!
-There's nobody's driving the train!
-[people screaming]
[Mr. Blue] We do it by the numbers
just as we planned.
-[Mr. Green coughs]
-[Mr. Blue] First...
Coats.
Check the load in your handguns.
[guns clicking]
We're not stopping. We're gonna be killed.
[train rumbling]
[Mr. Blue] Next, release the magazine
from your automatic weapon.
[Mr. Green coughing]
Switch coats.
Have you released the magazine
from your automatic weapon, Mr. Grey?
Are you serious, man?
Can you hurry up, please?
Mr. Grey, release the magazine
from your automatic weapon.
-Watch me.
-Do what he says so we can get
-the hell out of here, will you?
-Why don't you shut your face?
-Do it.
-[kissing]
So long, folks.
Bunch of losers.
-[gunshot]
-[grunts]
Let's go.
Let's go! Get his money, Mr. Green.
I've been going over his plan
and how it's tied into that sudden move.
-[sighs] The train moved, it stopped.
-Why?
-Because the police in the tunnel--
-That's what he said.
And you don't believe him?
Suppose he was trying to do something
that he didn't want anybody else to see.
-Like what?
-Like getting off the train.
-The train is moving. They can't do it!
-He beat it.
-The dead man's feature.
-He beat it. He beat it. He beat it!
-He beat the dead man's feature!
-The dead man's feature.
-We will stop.
-How do you know?
But I do know.
I've been riding on this subway cars
for over 60 years.
-I'm an expert.
-[woman crying]
They got these things called stoppers
or stickers, or something like that.
So whenever a train goes through
a red light, it automatically stops it.
-Cool, except for one thing.
-What's that?
They're all green.
[people screaming]
[man]
What's going on?
[men chattering]
[Mr. Green]
Come on. Let's get the hell out of here.
-[gun clicks]
-[Mr. Green] Let's just go.
-[Anthony] Keep the change, all right?
-[man] Hey, taxi.
[sniffs]
[Mr. Brown]
Come on. Hurry up.
-[gun fires]
-[Brown grunts]
[gunshot]
-Call for back up.
-Don't go down there.
Stop the train.
[gasps]
[train screeching]
[people screaming]
[people chattering indistinctly]
Leave her.
Leave her. Traffic's bad.
We'll meet where we said.
Go, Mr. Green. Go!
[officer grunting]
[grunts]
You were on the train.
Are you a cop?
Well done.
The mayor will come to your funeral.
-[gun clicks]
-[breathes heavily]
[gun fires]
Put it down!
No way.
Come on.
Do the honorable thing.
Put it down. This is over.
Honor amongst thieves.
Could you use half a million dollars?
My ex-wife would love it.
I just don't like the odds.
There's a whole platoon coming down here.
Just put it down, man.
[Mr. Blue grunts]
Tell me something, Anthony.
They still execute in this state?
No, Mr. Blue, they don't.
[electricity sizzles]
[sighs]
You did real good, ma'am.
[beeps]
Reset the signals.
Everything on the line goes red.
When it hits the loop at South Ferry
he'll be doing 70.
[Frank] We gonna stop him
before he hits the loop.
[woman]
Red, we need a red.
-[train rumbling]
-[people screaming]
We're going too fast to make it.
It's red.
-It's red!
-[people screaming]
-[train screeches]
[man grunts]
-[electricity crackles]
-[train screeches]
I told you it would stop. [laughs]
[people cheering]
How many guys left on the MTA list?
-Eight or nine.
-Let's go.
[man]
Who's there?
New York City Police.
Can we speak to you for just a second?
What can I do for you?
Sorry to have bothered you.
[Raye]
Good evening.
Aah!
[laughing]
-Langman.
-Four.
[laughs]
[knock on door]
Yeah?
New York City Police Department,
can we talk to you for a second?
Just a minute.
[sighs]
-How many more of this we got?
-Five.
I'm in the, uh... I'm in the toilet.
Just a minute.
Hold on. I'll be right there.
Coming.
[gasps]
Um...
-[knocking on door]
-Yeah.
-Hubert Langman?
Hi, I'm Detective Raye.
This is Detective Prescotti.
-Can we ask you a couple of questions?
-I'm sorry, what?
It will just take a couple of minutes.
-Can we come in?
-Yeah.
Thank you.
Where were you this afternoon?
Oh, um, here.
-Do you work?
-Yeah. Yeah, I work.
What do you do?
In New Jersey,
I, uh, work for a private bus company.
School buses?
Minivans. I take seniors to the mall.
-You take seniors to the mall?
-Yeah.
It's nice.
Is this a job that you got after
you were fired from the transit authority?
What does that have to do with anything?
Oh, there was a big hijacking today
at the subway.
[chuckles]
Are you kidding?
[chuckles] No.
You know anything about that?
No.
Well, the record shows
that you were really angry.
Angry enough to,
uh, get back at someone?
Oh, sure, you know. Yeah, I was angry.
[chuckles nervously]
Um, but I left that behind.
Got anybody that can vouch
for your being here all afternoon?
Yeah, my, uh, my cat.
-Cat?
-Yeah, I was... I was here sleeping.
[sniffs]
Smells good. What you cooking?
Excuse me. Don't you need, uh, a warrant
to go, uh, poking around in people's pots?
You just need to be incredibly hungry.
[snorts]
Yeah, I know I have a gripe
with the transit authority
but that's ancient history, you know.
I-- You don't have a right to be here.
Well, listen, I'll get in touch with you
when I need more information.
Make sure you stay in the city.
[Raye]
Thank you, Mr. Langman.
You know what, this is my home,
you know, and I think
I have a right to privacy here.
So... Yeah, go!
And get the hell out.
Sorry if we bothered you.
[sneezes]
[Anthony]
Bless you.
-[Raye] I told you it's going around.
-[door clicking and opening]