Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Zed: Welcome back
to Seabrook,
where belonging
is everything.
Addison:
We're a strong, united
and tight-knit community.
And that's a good thing 'cause
it wasn't always this way.
There was a time when
we had to protect ourselves.
Legend has it that when the
first settlers came to Seabrook,
they found wild beasts
with sharp claws
lurking in the forest.
(snarling)
Zed: Which sparked
an epic battle.
Seabrook settlers bravely
fought off the monstrous attack.
And discovered a powerful
energy source.
Realizing they discovered
a precious resource,
they safeguarded it
from the beasts.
Addison: They weren't going to
let anyone steal their treasure.
So they hid it.
And the town prospered
and grew rich
by harnessing the precious
energy source.
Seabrook benefited greatly
as it grew strong,
happy, and unified.
Zed: The beasts were
a distant memory.
Addison: Seabrook forgot
monsters could be real.
Zed: Until clearly,
they were.
A little lime soda mixed
with a dash
of industrial strength
Seabrook energy...
- And boom!
- (explosion)
Zombies were created.
(growling and snarling)
In a lot of ways,
Seabrook's moved on since then.
But it's hard to bury
your past.
(growling)
(terrified screaming)
Kids:
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
(playful growling)
Hey, I'm Zed.
And yup, still a zombie.
(grunts)
For zombies in Seabrook,
things are changing.
Every day is better
than the last.
Seabrook is getting rid of all
of its old anti-monster laws,
so now Zombietown is open
to everyone.
Come on!
Wait, wait, wait!
No, Zoey, wait for me!
Wait. Watch out!
And business is booming.
Hey, hey!
What's up, coach?
Oh, football off-season
has been good to me, Zed.
Invested in a Fro-Yo cart.
Little side hustle,
gonna go global,
gonna buy a car,
get some dress shirts,
go on vacation
without my great aunt Edna.
Though she loves
swimwear weather.
You know I might just
bring her along.
Cauliflower brains
mocha crunch, please.
You got it!
Seabrook has way more flavors
than just vanilla now.
I'll take a vanilla, coach.
What? I like vanilla.
In a couple days,
we're even tearing down
old Seabrook power
to build a new cheer pavilion.
And not to take too much credit
for all the positive changes,
but yeah, I did good.
It's hard to believe
there was a time
when people were afraid
of zombies.
Okay, let's triple check that.
Hey, Dad.
Hey, son.
First day as foreman
of the demo crew.
- Big day for zombie-kind.
- Yeah, you'll do great.
Just don't make any lame
zombie dad jokes.
But the workin' stiffs love 'em.
(laughs)
(cheering)
Boy: Go, Shrimpy! Go Shrimpy!
Cheer Camp!
Even more sparkly
than I dreamed.
(laughs)
Hi, I'm Addison, and this
is cheer camp,
a place where everyone belongs.
We're a unified squad and...
Bucky: Split up.
Usually unified.
(chuckles)
(whistle blows)
♪♪
- Woo!
- All: Yay, Bucky!
That's cheer captain Bucky,
my cousin.
(applause)
You've all heard the stories
of bloodthirsty monsters
- who roam these woods,
- (Shrimpy whimpering)
feasting on innocent
cheerleaders.
- Boo!
- (screams)
(Bucky laughs)
Well, those stories are just
silly make believe.
But you'd better believe
we're gonna break you down
and build you back up into peppy
little cheer machines like...
- Lacey!
- (applause)
- Stacey!
And our most recent Acey,
JC.
(applause)
I'm Kevin.
...Right.
We changed my name to JC,
which I love by the way.
Long live the Aceys!
(applause)
You three lead the veterans,
you're the A-team.
Addison, Bree, you take
the newbies.
You're the, uh, you're
the Z-team.
(yelling)
Hey, hey! Ho, ho!
This demolition
has got to go!
They can't tear it down, Zed.
Seabrook power hasn't worked
for years.
It's an important part of
zombie heritage.
This is progress, Eliza.
And now we can even
go to Prawn.
Prawn is like super-sized prom,
but Mighty Shrimp themed.
And, this is the first year
zombies can attend.
And it's gonna be epic.
I'm loud and proud to be
a zombie.
Sometimes too loud.
Soon, Z-band tech will get
so good
that zombies will blend
right in.
I dream of a day we ditch
our Z-bands
and let our
inner monsters roar.
(roars)
Zombies, this is obviously
your first cheer camp.
Now, I'm not anti-change,
I'm just pro keeping things
the way they are,
because you don't mess
with success.
(laughs)
This week, the veterans
and the newbies will compete
for the Cheer Camp Cup
to see who is more
cheertastic!
The veterans have always
won the Cheer Camp Cup,
right Aceys?
All: Right!
We'll see about that.
To the cheer course!
Watch and learn, snowball.
Ah yes, my hair.
Still white,
still well-conditioned,
and still drawing fire
from the Aceys.
Bucky: Addison,
get those pom-poms pumping.
Let's show 'em that we got this.
All: Yeah!
- Let's go!
- Come on, Z-team!
♪ We're back here on the scene
and everyone's together ♪
♪ With zombies on the team ♪
♪ It's better than ever ♪
♪ Better than ever ♪
♪ Those moves won't
get the gold ♪
♪ Green hair is so whatever ♪
♪ Well, you'll never break
the mold ♪
♪ 'Cause we're better
than ever ♪
♪ Better than ever ♪
♪ Tearing down
the power plant ♪
♪ You're welcome, Seabrook ♪
♪ I'm your man ♪
♪ To build the place
where everyone can cheer ♪
♪ I'm making Zombie-kind cool,
not feared ♪
♪ Making progress,
that sounds great ♪
♪ But what's the price
we have to pay? ♪
♪ Ready for a new day,
ready for a change ♪
♪ People, zombies,
everybody say ♪
♪ Hey, we got this ♪
♪ Teaming up to
make progress ♪
♪ Change the rules,
you can't stop this ♪
♪ Together we rise,
you know we got this ♪
♪ Hey, we got this ♪
- ♪ Teaming up to make progress ♪
- (screaming)
♪ Change the rules
you can't stop this ♪
♪ Together we rise,
you know we got this ♪
♪♪
(laughs)
♪ I wish that I could call
I hope you get my letters ♪
♪ Hope I get asked
to Prawn ♪
♪ And be better than ever ♪
♪ Better than ever ♪
♪ Oh Addison, my love's
gargargaza forever ♪
- ♪ We pull the strings ♪
- ♪ We run the show ♪
♪ 'Cause we're
better than ever ♪
♪ Better than ever ♪
♪ Finally allowed
to go to Prawn ♪
♪ Gonna get our
ziga-ziga-zombie on ♪
♪ Counting down the days,
I've been keeping track ♪
♪ Kinda wishing Addison
would write me back ♪
♪ Imagine me taking
her to the dance ♪
♪ A human and a zombie,
hand in hand ♪
♪ Ready for a new day,
ready for a change ♪
♪ People, zombies,
everybody say.. ♪
♪ Hey, we got this ♪
♪ Teaming up to make
progress ♪
♪ Change the rules,
you can't stop this ♪
♪ Together we rise,
you know we got this ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ We got this ♪
♪ Teaming up to make
progress ♪
♪ Change the rules,
you can't stop this ♪
♪ Together we rise,
you know we got this ♪
(slurps)
Hmmm...
♪♪
♪ Here in this hall,
up on these walls ♪
♪ Picturing Addison
beside me ♪
♪ Then they will say
we're all the same ♪
♪ And they can see
the life inside me ♪
♪ Oh what's it gonna take,
what's it gonna take ♪
♪ What's it gonna take,
♪ What's it gonna take? ♪
The last day of Cheer Camp,
and our final challenge!
Zombies, your unique squad
would have to crush
the course record to win.
- So not happening.
- (Shrimpy whines)
(whistle blows)
Yeah, we are different,
Bucky,
but that's what makes
us stronger.
Za! (grunts)
All: Way stronger!
(whistle blows)
♪♪
(murmuring)
(whistle blowing)
Woo! Come on, Z-team.
Here we go!
♪♪
(whistle blows)
- Addison: Okay, we got this!
- Z-Team: Let's go!
♪♪
Z-Team: We got this!
A-Team: We got this!
♪♪
Whoa, ugh!
Z-Team: We got this!
Climb, climb, climb!
Whoa! Ugh!
Help me!
- Ugh!
- Z-Team: Almost there!
- We got this! (screams)
- (A-Team groaning)
♪ Ready for a new day
Ready for a change ♪
♪ People, zombies,
everybody say! ♪
♪ Hey, we got this ♪
♪ Teaming up to
make progress ♪
♪ Change the rules,
you can't stop this ♪
♪ Together we rise,
you know we got this ♪
♪ Hey, we got this ♪
♪ Teaming up to make
progress ♪
♪ Change the rules,
you can't stop this ♪
♪ Together we rise,
you know we got this ♪
♪ Hey, we got this ♪
♪ Teaming up to make
progress ♪
♪ Change the rules,
you can't stop this ♪
♪ Together we rise,
you know we got this ♪
♪ Hey, we got this ♪
♪ Teaming up to make
progress ♪
♪ Change the rules,
you can't stop this ♪
♪ Together we rise,
you know we got this ♪
Girl:
Bye, Zed.
(bell ringing)
(laughing)
Bucky: (groans)
Z-team wins.
(cheering)
Aceys, disappointing.
You can't be scared to get those
jazz hands dirty.
- Uh... Wha...
- (sighs)
The Cheer Camp Cup is yours.
(cheering)
- Whoa.
- I'm glad you enjoyed it.
Now let's make this victory
about me.
I've decided to be school
president this year.
Now technically,
there's an election,
but come on.
Which means we'll need
a new cheer captain
while I rule the school.
Who's worthy to lead?
(all clamoring)
What do you mean?
It's me!
Kevin: Me, me, me,
me, me, me, me, me!
No! No, no, no, no.
We... we need a captain that's
going to build a united squad.
Someone like Addison.
Thanks, Bree.
Being cheer captain has always
been my dream.
(chanting):
Addison! Addison!
- Z-Team: Addison! Addison! Addison!
- (groaning)
(indistinct chattering)
Cheer Camp's over and we're
finally headed home.
I'm so excited to see,
well, you know.
(laughs)
Yes! I got invited to Prawn!
(applause)
Well, getting invited
to Prawn sounds great,
but Bonzo won't even
look at me.
No invitation to Prawn
for me, either.
Do you think Zed forgot
about me?
No.
When do I throw the confetti?
You'll know.
♪♪
(speaking Zombie)
(Bree gasps)
Bree:
Addison... will you...
(Bree gasps)
(electrical sparks)
All: Go to The Prawn!
With...
(ding!)
- Zed!
- Uh-oh!
(screaming)
(screams)
(horn honks)
(groans)
(screaming)
Zed!
Hi!
- (groans)
- (screaming continues)
(screaming continues)
- (groans)
- Now!
(screaming)
Bucky:
Is everybody okay?
(screaming)
Nothing can happen to me,
I'm way too important!
Everyone, stay calm.
Great leadership, Addie.
Very future cheer captain
of you.
Zed!
(groans)
(thud)
(birds squawking)
Ah!
(distant whispering
and hissing sounds)
Who's there?
Zed?
Hello?
Can anybody hear me?
Zed?
(gasps)
(growling)
(howling)
(wolves howling)
- (screams)
- (groans)
Zed! (laughs)
I missed you too.
Boy:
There they are!
Zoey.
We're not alone.
We're surrounded by...
werewolves.
Cool!
- What?
- Wolves?
- What wolves?
- Here wolves?
Aceys:
Were-wolves?
Nobody's gonna believe this.
Bucky:
Werewolves are real!
I always, always said
the stories of monsters
in the forest were real.
And no one believed me.
I thought werewolves
were just myths.
Yeah, like cavities.
Those are real too?
Werewolves, ew.
I really hope my allergies
don't act up.
Please can I have one?
I'm the only zombie
in my class.
A werewolf friend
would be great.
I'll feed him and walk him.
Yeah, werewolves
ain't class pets, Zoey.
And they certainly
ain't friendly.
I'm okay.
Aunt Missy, Uncle Dale.
The crash was horrible,
but I protected Addison.
Anyone as courageous as me
would've done the same.
Though not really,
I am super brave.
Mom, Dad,
everything is fine.
It's not fine. There are
werewolves circling us right now,
waiting to attack.
Yeah, and I'm way too tasty.
I'm always looking like
a snack.
Somebody has to do something.
And someone will.
Hold my purse.
(gavel slams)
By order of city council,
effective immediately,
all anti-monster laws
are reinstated.
(gavel slams)
(cheering and applause)
Mom, that is unfair!
- Zed, we need to talk.
- We do.
Even though you didn't write,
or answer any of my letters.
No, I wrote.
A lot.
(sighs) The Aceys shredded
all of our letters.
(chuckles)
Addison.
Will you make me
the luckiest zombie
and be my date to Prawn?
- No.
- Great! No?
Everyone's freaking out
about werewolves,
so the anti-monster laws are
in affect again, which means...
Zombies can't go to Prawn.
Ouch.
But we're going to fight this,
Zed.
Okay, so that's why
you said no?
Yeah.
Why are you smiling?
Because when you said no,
I thought you didn't
like me anymore.
But the only problem here
is a bunch of blood-thirsty
werewolves.
We can so fix that.
(laughs)
Announcer:
Attention all citizens.
Monster laws have
been reinstated.
All curfews will be
strictly enforced.
Attention all citizens.
Werewolves have been
sighted in the area.
Take cover immediately.
Keep children and pets inside.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're closed.
For good.
Dreams of Fro-Yo success
melted away.
With monsters everywhere.
Look, I like zombies.
They like Fro-Yo.
But werewolves like human flesh.
Maybe with sprinkles.
Everybody likes sprinkles.
Just run.
High knees, run!
(grunts)
Announcer:
Attention all citizens.
Werewolves have been
sighted in the area.
Take cover immediately.
Keep children and pets inside.
They see one werewolf,
and we can't go to Prawn?
Okay, we have to fight this.
Protest.
Boycott.
Hunger strike!
Fine. Finish your sandwich,
but this is so unfair.
Announcer: Warning,
werewolves have been sighted in the area.
- Take cover immediately.
- Zoey, come on home.
It's not safe out here with
these werewolves on the loose.
Just one sec.
Have you seen a werewolf?
I'm looking for a were-friend.
Silly kid, there's no
such thing as werewolves.
But we heard it howl.
Maybe it was a hiker saying,
"howl's it going?"
It was a werewolf.
My, what big eyes you have.
Zevon:
Zoey!
Come on.
♪♪
Willa: He's back.
Wolves!
Wyatt: Over here!
Man:
Come gather!
♪♪
(snarls)
Willa:
What did you find out?
They saw you howling,
Willa.
So?
We're exposed.
(laughs)
Looks nothing like us, Wyatt.
We have way better hair
than that.
Stop being such a worry-wolf,
brother.
I only said "awoo"!
It's like saying "ciao"
or "aloha."
Or "I'll rip your throat out."
Anyway, who cares
what they think?
It's a terrible town.
We have to find
the Great Alpha.
If there even is
a Great Alpha.
Willa, we saw her
in the forest.
- She had the white hair.
- It was probably just the light.
She's real,
and she's going to lead us
to the moonstone.
And you know we don't have
much time.
More and more of our pack
are getting sick.
Our necklaces are almost
out of power.
We need to find the moonstone.
And when we do, we can
recharge our necklaces
and stay wolf strong
for another 100 years.
Okay. Even if the girl
is the Great Alpha,
how do we find her?
I found this in the woods.
It's hers.
(gasps) We'll track her down
with our keen sense of smell.
Says Seabrook High on it,
so I thought we might
just look there.
Ugh!
Okay, fine.
We find the girl,
and if she's the Great Alpha,
she'll tell us where
the moonstone is hidden.
We go in the morning.
We go tonight!
Or tonight works.
(all howling)
♪♪
♪ No one's catching me
unless I want to be caught ♪
♪ I'm dancing
in the shadows ♪
♪ Ain't no leash
when I walk ♪
♪ It's great to feel
invincible ♪
♪ It's great to feel alive ♪
♪ My appetite's insatiable ♪
♪ There's nowhere
it can hide ♪
♪ Our freedom isn't
up to them ♪
- ♪ It's only up to us! ♪
- ♪ Us! ♪
♪ I'm the Alpha,
I'm the leader ♪
- ♪ I'm the one to trust ♪
- ♪ Trust! ♪
♪ Together we do
whatever it takes ♪
♪ We're in this pack
for life ♪
(howling)
♪ We're wolves ♪
♪ We own the night ♪
♪ Oh we own what we own ♪
♪ Oh we own the night ♪
♪ We own the night ♪
♪ The only thing that is worse
than our bark's our bite ♪
♪ Oh we own,
what we own ♪
♪ We own the night ♪
♪♪
♪ I'm picking up the scent ♪
- ♪ It seems we're on the right track ♪
- ♪ Track! ♪
♪ The moonlight's
on the rooftops ♪
- ♪ The wind is at our backs ♪
- ♪ Backs! ♪
♪ We're living
in the shadows ♪
- ♪ We're living for the chase ♪
- ♪ Chase! ♪
♪ Our legacy is
in our sights ♪
♪ So let's pick up the pace ♪
♪ We're on a quest to find
the power that's inside of us ♪
- ♪ Us! ♪
- ♪ She's the Alpha, she's the leader ♪
- ♪ She's the one to trust ♪
- ♪ Trust! ♪
♪ Together we do
whatever it takes ♪
♪ We're in this pack
for life ♪
(howling)
♪ We're wolves,
we own the night ♪
♪ Oh we own what we own ♪
♪ Oh we own the night ♪
♪ We own the night ♪
♪ The only thing that is worse
than our bark's our bite ♪
♪ Oh we own what we own ♪
♪♪
♪ We own the night ♪
♪ We own what we own ♪
♪ The night is our home ♪
♪ Wolves! ♪
(howling)
♪ We own the night ♪
♪ Oh we own what we own ♪
♪ Oh we own the night ♪
♪ We own the night ♪
♪ The only thing that is worse
than our bark's our bite ♪
♪ Oh we own what we own ♪
♪ We own the night ♪
We'll hide here,
find the girl,
get our moonstone and leave
this awful place.
I wouldn't call it awful.
They got something
called Fro-Yo.
Yeah, you're right.
This town's the worst.
Boy: Hey, I guess I
will see you after tryouts.
Girl:
Yeah, sure, awesome.
Boy:
Hey, man, how are you...
I really thought we'd all be
at the Prawn together.
- I thought Seabrook could change.
- It did.
Believe me, I will find a way
to get us to the Prawn.
Or we could miss it together.
I'm not letting you miss
the Prawn.
If you can't go,
I'm not going.
Well, I like you too much
not to let you go.
to leave you behind.
I am so not going.
Ugh, you guys even fight
like a perfect couple.
How's it going, Eliza?
You know, fighting injustice
is keeping me busy.
And looking good doing it,
Zom-bae.
(laughs)
I'm thinking the student
president
should get his own
corner office.
Let's see if we can move out
the math department.
- Write that down.
- Done.
Addison!
Time to officially nominate me
as president.
Let's keep it understated,
yet extravagant and flashy.
Ooh, yeah.
Bucky:
Make sure...
Cheer could be so much
more than
just pom-pomming for Bucky.
Lacey:
Uh, Addison?
Once we're cheer captain,
you are so off the team.
And when I'm cheer captain,
you'll be welcome to stay,
because I'll be making cheer
about bringing people together.
(laughs)
That was awful trash talk.
I know, right?
You will never be
cheer captain, freak.
Stacey:
See ya.
I gotta find a way to get us
to the Prawn.
We can crash it.
I mean, we can't make the rules,
but we can break 'em.
(snaps fingers)
Well, we can make the rules!
We just need the right leader.
- (cheering)
- Okay, are there any more nominees for president?
Just a reminder that being part
of student council
means that we get to hang.
Anybody, anybody want
to hang?
Just... anyone want
to hang out?
Anyone?
Oh, we could come up with our
very own complicated high five.
That'd be fun, huh?
Like...
Oooh...
(band plays fanfare)
Students: (chanting)
Go! Go! Go!
(cheering)
Hi!
(cheering and applause)
Good job!
Okay.
(cheering)
Great news, we have a brilliant
and cheer tested candidate
running for president
this year.
Me!
(cheering)
(chanting)
Bucky! Bucky! Bucky!
Students: Bucky!
I'm running against Bucky
for president,
but I need to one-up
his entrance.
The question is, how?
(chanting continues)
(grunts)
(grunting)
- Bucky! Bucky! Bucky!
- (chanting stops)
Woo!
Excuse me.
(laughs)
Zombie strong!
(cheering)
Zed:
Hello, everyone.
My name is Zed, and I am running
for president.
(cheering and laughing)
Zed can't steal my spotlight.
What about the whole
anti-monster thingy?
Shh...
Anyone can run
for president, Bucky.
She actually has a point,
Mr. Bucky.
- (furiously) What?!
- Yes.
A zombie president?
Aceys: Ew!
(cheering)
As the first ever
zombie president,
I will allow zombies to go
to the Prawn,
I will take Addison
as my date,
and we will get our photo
on the Prawn wall of fame.
Maybe they'll rename the school
after me one day.
Zed Necrodopolous High.
Preferably before I graduate.
Okay.
If you vote for me, I will bring
you prosperity and awesomeness!
(cheering wildly)
Crowd: (chanting) Zed! Zed!
Zed! Zed! Zed! Zed! Zed! Zed!
- The Great Alpha's near.
- Focus.
Remember, we're fierce,
we're savage.
We're werewolves!
That's right, Wynter.
We're scared of nothing.
Except silver.
Yeah, silver.
And ticks.
And rabies.
Come on, if we're quiet,
we can be in and out of here
before they even know
we're here.
(yelps)
Ah, silver! Oh, pain!
- I can take it.
- (sizzling)
No, I can't!
Nice grab.
Come on.
Zed:
As your president,
I will make Seabrook a place
that embraces zombies and...
(fearfully)
Werewolves?
Uh, no. Why would we want...
(screams)
Werewolves!
(screaming)
There she is!
Football team!
Defense, Z 24.
- Boy 1: Right!
- Boy 2: Let's go Mighty Shrimp!
Where's the moonstone,
white hair?
I think you've got
the wrong person.
Uh, Eliza?
What are you doing?
Let's smash our Z-bands
and zombie out.
We can use our strength
to fend them off.
We can't lose control.
We are not monsters.
Our razor sharp claws will gut
'em and splatter their blood.
(screaming)
Too much?
Wolves! On my command!
(snarling)
Willa.
We can't go to war
with the whole town.
We'll never find the moonstone
if they're on high alert.
I hate it when you're right.
Wolves, stand down.
Okay.
Sorry.
We werewolves so admire
your town,
and we just came here
to join your school.
(murmurs of confusion)
What? They can't join
our school.
Technically the
Forbidden Forest
is within the school district.
So, welcome to Seabrook!
(awkward laugh)
Zed:
Zed for prez!
Vote Zed for prez,
because I'm a zombie,
not a zom-can't-be.
Okay, here's our platform.
We fight for zombie toppings
on pizza in the cafeteria.
-Right.
- Get Zombie tongue taught
as a second language.
- Good.
- And how to overthrow your oppressors after school club.
- Eliza.
- Sorry, right. Don't over promise.
But more importantly,
we allow zombies at Prawn.
Good luck, Mr. Future President.
Hey Zed, did you hear?
Addie's being tested
for captain,
and she gets to run
cheer practice tomorrow.
It's not a big deal.
Okay, it's huge.
A huge chance to fail!
If Addie aces this practice,
oh my gosh,
she's so going to be cheer
captain once Bucky wins.
He's so gonna win,
because you know, elections,
they're just like these
big old popularity contests.
And Bucky is super popular.
- (clears throat)
- So... what?
Thanks, Bree.
I know it's weird
I'll only be cheer captain
if Bucky's president, but...
No, that just means
neither of us can lose,
because one of us is going
to get what we want.
And I can live with that.
Me too.
You'll do great, Zed.
Zed for prez!
Addison:
(speaking Zombie)
Thank you.
Bucky (on PA): Shish, boom.
Bucky Buchanan for president.
A vote for Bucky is a vote
for cheer-fection.
♪♪
(snarls)
These sheep just let us in?
Baaaad idea.
We agreed to play nice.
Oh, this is me being nice.
Now let's find that moonstone.
With cheer fans in Bucky's camp,
and zombies and the football
team in mine,
the school's split right down
the middle.
Werewolves are the swing vote.
Wolves are key to winning
this election.
But you know winning over
the wolves is going to be hard.
Zed:
Trust me, I got this.
We're going to win the wolves
votes, and more.
We just have to show them
how to fit in, like us.
- Easy.
- (school bell rings)
- (howling)
- (gasps)
(howling)
(indistinct chatter)
(clears throat)
(awkward laugh)
Okay, this is a little
bit weird.
Hey, that dog just ate
my homework!
Lies!
These history books
claim werewolves
attacked Seabrook settlers.
But they struck first
and stole our moonstone.
I'm sorry, I didn't know that.
There's a lot you don't know.
I know the alarm's going
to go off
if you don't check out
those books.
(electrical zapping)
Our necklaces have a way
with electronics.
♪♪
Willa: (groans)
Useless.
None of these history books say
where the moonstone is hidden.
Win the wolves' vote,
win the election. Easy.
Hello wolves, allow me
to introduce myself.
I'm Zed, zombie, football star,
presidential hopeful.
(laughs weakly)
...Okay.
When zombies first came
to Seabrook,
we were outsiders, too.
Which is why you need a great
president like Zed
to represent you.
We'd be honored if you guys
joined us.
Our pack is our pack.
We don't need anyone else,
so...
Zoey:
Who doesn't want more friends?
Underneath all that fluffy hair,
I bet you're a real softie.
I am a mean, mean werewolf,
kid.
I am tough and rough.
Aww, you said "ruff."
Like a sweet little puppy dog.
Ruff, ruff!
We are beasts of the forest,
we will never be tamed.
Oh boy.
Oh wow, that's great.
Oh wow.
(whispers)
Sorry.
We're nothing like you zombies.
You sort of are.
Your necklace is powered, right?
Kind of like an organic Z-band.
You're smarter than he looks.
Thanks.
That necklace keeps you
from fully wolfing out?
The opposite.
Our moonstones make us
our true werewolf selves.
So without it you'd be human?
No, we'd die.
We'd be nothing.
Imagine how alive you'd feel
if you didn't have to tamp
things down.
Hold back your true selves.
Actually, I've got this theory
that zombies might've evolved
- beyond their need for Z-bands.
- (laughs uncomfortably)
Z-bands are great.
They help you fit in.
And I think you guys would have
a much better time at Seabrook
if you just followed
in our footsteps.
Join a club,
play football.
I'll even teach you
how to tackle.
Just lighten up.
Be more like us.
♪♪
♪ Do it like
the zombies do ♪
♪ Brush your fangs
when you wake up ♪
♪ Comb your hair,
do your makeup ♪
♪ Sleep at night,
don't stay up ♪
♪ Do it like the zombies do ♪
♪ Don't stand out
when you're fitting in ♪
♪ When in doubt,
do the opposite ♪
♪ Don't listen to him ♪
♪ He's a hypocrite ♪
♪ Do it like the zombies do ♪
♪ All you've got to do
is give an inch ♪
♪ Then we gonna take it
to the top ♪
♪ Do it like the zombies do ♪
- ♪ When the moon is full, no howling ♪
- (howls)
♪ Don't run in the halls,
no growling ♪
♪ Let's go to the mall
start styling ♪
♪ Do it like the zombies do ♪
♪ Trim your claws,
get a manicure ♪
♪ Cut your fangs,
leave it on the floor ♪
♪ Now wag your tail
like a Labrador ♪
♪ Do it like the zombies do ♪
♪ All you've got to do
is give an inch ♪
♪ Then we gonna take it
to the top ♪
♪ Do it like the zombies do ♪
♪ Don't stop ♪
♪ Do it ♪
♪ Stand up, stand up ♪
♪ Stand up straight and do
your homework ♪
♪ Smile a lot when
you network ♪
♪ Did I mention
no one gets hurt? ♪
- (groans)
- ♪ Do it like the zombies do ♪
♪ I hope you're open
to my advice ♪
♪ Oh, it's invaluable
to us, right? ♪
♪ It sounds like this could
be a paradise ♪
♪ Do it like the zombies do ♪
♪ Why should we change ♪
♪ They should be like us ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ He may eat brains
but he's got no guts ♪
♪ He's gone insane,
yeah, he's acting nuts ♪
♪ Come on, we've got
moves to bust ♪
♪ Waaaah ♪
♪ All you've got to do
is give an inch ♪
♪ Then we gonna take it
to the top ♪
♪ Do it like the zombies do ♪
♪ Don't stop ♪
(grunts)
(wolves laugh)
(wolves howling)
Zed: Oh!
(Bonzo speaking Zombie)
Eliza: Yeah, that went badly.
No way Zed is getting
the wolf vote.
All right, what are
our poll numbers?
(speaks Zombie)
Ugh. That's awful.
We just gotta make sure
you deliver
a killer speech tomorrow, okay?
So the first step is...
More glossy publicity shots.
(laughs)
(speaks Zombie)
Yeah, I look a little human,
but that's only because
people are lumping
werewolves and zombies together.
I gotta show them that I'm
nothing like those furballs.
(blows whistle)
I am so fired up to be
running cheer practice.
Together, we can do anything.
Sorry, but this practice space
is for cheerleaders only.
Ha! Just try and get us
to leave.
Wynter.
Some respect.
No, I don't want you to leave.
I want you to stay.
Show us what you can do.
The cheer team is for everyone.
Addison: Five, six,
seven, eight!
♪♪
(howling)
(speaks Zombie)
♪♪
(cheering)
Yeah. That scruffy, super
handsome, fine-smelling Wyatt
is really into Addison.
You know what?
They're just cheering.
- (Wyatt laughing)
- And laughing.
That was so amazing.
You are all natural
cheerleaders.
But I'm sure she's just
convincing the wolves
to vote for me.
We wolves work well together.
But I'm not a wolf.
Hmm.
I'm not threatened.
- (Wynter coughing)
- Wynter?
(coughing)
(clapping)
Well done, Addison.
With werewolves on cheer,
this election is so in the bag.
Bucky, this is not
about politics.
I always just felt like cheer
could unite.
You are going to make
a great cheer captain.
I'm gonna be cheer captain!
(applause)
I was thinking the team
could move beyond trophies
and we could start
an outreach program.
Whoa. Cheer is what
I say cheer's about.
And it's about winning.
Hi, I'm Bucky.
Vote for Bucky.
Hey, Bucky Buchanan
for president.
You are a leader, Addison.
But of something
a lot greater than cheer.
Zed!
What's wrong?
Werewolves. They're not
interested in fitting in.
They're into cheer.
No, they're into you,
and you're into him... them.
What?
Why are you acting like this?
Do you know how hard it was
for zombies?
Now everything is just being
handed to the werewolves
- on a silver platter.
- Actually, they hate silver.
I'm trying to win an election
for my people, for you.
So we can go to Prawn,
so we can be accepted.
That's not being accepted.
That's being afraid to show
who you really are.
Says the girl who wore a wig
her whole life.
Yeah. I did.
Because I always felt
like an outsider.
And even though I might be
cheer captain, I still do.
You know I don't have
a place here!
Don't have a zombie crew.
I don't know what I am!
So excuse me for respecting
a pack of werewolves
who are proud of
who they are.
(exhales)
♪♪
♪ How do people
make it look easy ♪
♪ Are they happy or
just good at deceiving ♪
♪ I just want a bit of
that feeling for myself ♪
♪ I don't put the pressure
of soulmates ♪
♪ I just want somebody
who knows me ♪
♪ 'Cause every now and then
I admit ♪
Both: ♪ I need a little
bit of help ♪
♪♪
Addison: ♪ I don't
feel like I belong ♪
♪ Anywhere, where,
where, where ♪
♪ How did things keep
going wrong ♪
♪ How did we get here,
here, here ♪
♪ The more I cover up
my flaws ♪
♪ The more they appear ♪
♪ I gotta find where
I belong ♪
♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ I wish that I could feel
the way you do sometimes ♪
♪ Just stuck on the outside ♪
♪ While I'm in
here wondering ♪
♪ Why I had to make
it worse ♪
♪ You were already hurt ♪
♪ Don't want to be another
thing on your mind ♪
♪ I wish that I could make
a change ♪
♪ Instead of making
mistakes ♪
♪ Trying to hold you up ♪
♪ Instead I'm the one
pushing away ♪
♪ Just want to understand,
but every time I can't ♪
♪ And I don't know why ♪
♪ I don't feel like
I belong ♪
♪ Anywhere, where,
where, where ♪
♪ How did I get this
so wrong ♪
♪ To leave us right here,
here, here ♪
♪ The more I cover up
my flaws ♪
♪ The more they appear ♪
♪ I gotta find where
I belong ♪
♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ Everywhere I go ♪
♪ Don't feel like home ♪
♪ Even my parents
they act like they know ♪
♪ Guess I have to leave
to finally see ♪
♪ If there's someone
out there ♪
♪ And they're just like me ♪
♪ Then I'll go ♪
♪ Yeah, I'll go ♪
♪ I don't feel like
I belong ♪
♪ Anywhere, where,
where, where ♪
♪ How did I get this
so wrong ♪
♪ To lead us right here,
here, here ♪
♪ The more I cover up
my flaws ♪
♪ The more they appear ♪
♪ I gotta find
where I belong ♪
♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ I don't feel like,
I don't feel like ♪
♪ I don't feel like ♪
♪ I don't feel like
I don't feel like ♪
♪ Gotta find where
I belong ♪
(typing)
(message sends)
(sighs)
(scraping sounds)
Zed?
(gasps)
Come with us.
What's so important?
You are.
Where are we going?
It's a wolf secret.
If we told you,
we'd have to kill you.
Too much, too much,
I knew it.
Sorry.
Welcome!
But not too welcome!
(hisses)
(coughs)
Are you okay?
My necklace is losing
its charge.
Every day, more and more
of our pack becomes sick
because their moonstones
lose their power.
All of our elders are too sick
to travel, which leaves...
...which leaves taking care of
the pack to us.
To me.
You'll be fine, Wynter.
I promise.
You'd better be right
about this.
We need to find
the moonstone soon.
Follow us, Addison.
Please.
You guys!
I have to go apologize
to Addison right now.
- Gruzah!
- Yeah I know, I want to see it too.
You know, ever since
football ended,
I've so missed watching you
get pummeled.
Announcer:
Attention citizens.
All curfews will be
strictly enforced.
(speaks Zombie)
Yeah, with the curfew
in effect,
it's gonna be nearly impossible
to get past the Z-patrol.
Hey guys!
And yet somehow
Bree just did.
Have you, have you guys
seen Addison?
She texted me for help,
but she's not home,
and she's not answering
her phone.
...Oh.
Hey, Bonzo.
(speaks Zombie)
(laughs)
You guys, focus!
Oh.
Addison needs help.
Okay, if her phone is on,
I can track her.
(beeping)
She's in the Forbidden Forest.
The wolves.
They kidnapped her.
You guys, we have
to help Addison.
The wolf den!
Addison: Wow.
It's okay to be impressed.
Wyatt:
Our language.
(howls)
Addison!
- That means welcome.
- (howls)
(laughing)
Ostrich boots?
No, I think Addison meant
(howls)
- (laughing)
- Polka dot unicorn?
Cool, where?
Oh, no. Sorry, um.
Uh...
(howls briefly)
Whoa, whoa, language.
There are were-pups around.
She needs to put a pebble
in the swear-wolf jar.
(wolves howling)
I am so sorry.
Enough.
This is not why we brought
her here.
Why am I here?
(howling)
I believe you will lead us
to the moonstone.
I believe you're
the Great Alpha.
a werewolf.
What?!
♪♪
♪ Turn up,
explain our history ♪
♪ Pull back the veil
of mystery ♪
♪ What's written on the cave
is prophecy ♪
♪ The Great Alpha
is our destiny ♪
♪ Show us the power
of chemistry ♪
♪ Lead us to the source
of our energy ♪
♪ No one knows
her identity ♪
♪ But she looks like you,
identically ♪
♪ This is how we're
living our lives ♪
♪ Living our lives ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Can you feel the call
to the wild ♪
♪ Call to the wild ♪
♪ The call to the wild ♪
♪ We are the call ♪
♪ We are the call
to the wild ♪
♪ I see a real community ♪
♪ Unique, but you
have unity ♪
♪ You know who
you're supposed to be ♪
♪ Release to the rhythm
totally ♪
♪ I feel divine when
you're close to me ♪
♪ And you can feel it too,
or hopefully ♪
♪ Now look up and tell me
what you really see ♪
♪ A bunch of stray wolves
or a family? ♪
♪ This is how we're living
our lives ♪
♪ Living our lives ♪
♪ Living our lives,
yeah ♪
♪ Can you feel the call
to the wild ♪
♪ Call to the wild ♪
♪ The call to the wild ♪
♪ We are the call ♪
♪ We are the call
to the wild ♪
♪ We are the call ♪
♪ We are the call
to the wild ♪
♪ Hold up, before you do ♪
♪ Let me interrupt ♪
♪ She's a cheerleader,
not an Alpha ♪
♪ You're in the den ♪
♪ But you'll need to earn
my trust ♪
♪ Now show me what you got ♪
♪ If you're one of us ♪
♪♪
(howling)
(cheering loudly)
♪ This is how we're living
our lives ♪
♪ It's how you're living.. ♪
♪ Living our lives ♪
♪ Living our lives, yeah ♪
♪ Can you feel the call
to the wild ♪
♪ I can feel the.. ♪
♪ The call to the wild ♪
♪ We are the call ♪
♪ We are the call
to the wild ♪
♪ We are the call ♪
♪ We are the call
to the wild ♪
(howling)
Addison!
Zed!
Don't make me
take this off!
You don't want to see me
zombie out.
(snarling)
(growling)
Wolves!
(snarling)
(distortedly)
Stay back!
Addison:
No!
(hissing and snarling)
(growling)
Addison:
No, stop!
Zed! I want to be here!
What?
But... but you texted
"Help!"
I needed help on
the chemistry homework.
Didn't you see
the beaker emoji?
Oh... I do now.
(laughs awkwardly)
By the way, I love
this new look.
New hairstylist?
Werewolves, they know hair.
And manicures.
All: Mmm-hmm.
They think I may be
a werewolf too.
What? How?
Maybe a grandparent.
My hair means something.
This could be my pack.
For centuries, this has been
set aside for the Great Alpha.
A fully charged moonstone
is priceless to us, Addison.
If you're truly one of us,
when you put it on,
you'll be transformed
into a werewolf.
Part of our pack, forever.
What? No!
Wait.
Can I think about it?
For a day.
Once you've joined us, you can
lead us to the hidden moonstone.
But she doesn't know
where it is.
Zed:
What?
(rumbling)
(speaks Zombie)
Yeah. The explosion came
from Seabrook Power.
They must be testing charges
for the demolition tomorrow.
Seabrook Power is the birthplace
of zombies.
Zed:
A little lime soda mixed
with some mysterious energy,
and bang!
Zombies.
(snarls)
Nice story, but it doesn't
concern us.
But it does concern you,
Willa.
Seabrook Power was fueled
by a mysterious energy source.
That could be your moonstone,
right?
She found the moonstone.
She's amazing.
Wyatt:
If she's right...
Wow.
We'll see you at school
tomorrow, Addison.
Okay. Tomorrow.
Big day.
If they destroy that building,
it'll crush the moonstone
underneath.
We can't let that happen.
- Addison can help.
- Maybe once she's one of us.
But until then,
I lead this pack.
We need to stop them from
destroying the moonstone.
Whatever it takes.
(howls)
(howling)
♪♪
So.
New look?
I like it.
My new friends like it.
Did you join a, um,
rock band?
Announcer: It's
election day, Seabrook!
We have an assembly to hear from
our presidential candidates,
and it is going to be so good
to see you all.
- Girl: Addison?
- Boy: Check her out!
- Girl: She looks amazing!
- Boy: Look what she's wearing!
Boy 2:
That is a fresh look!
Whoa! Bad hair day?
Bad hair life?
I think it looks great.
- Yeah, not so much.
- (snaps fingers)
Addison, if you ever expect
to be cheer captain...
Well, maybe I don't.
Maybe cheer team
isn't for me after all.
(Aceys gasps)
Addison!
I was up all night thinking.
You're not a werewolf,
you can't be.
But I love moonlight strolls.
Yeah, you like sunsets too.
That doesn't mean you're
a vampire.
- Zed...
- Look.
It's really hard being
considered a monster.
Trust me.
All I've ever wanted
is to find my pack.
And now I finally have.
When I see the wolves,
I'm going to put this on.
And I'm really sorry I can't
make the debate,
but I need to find the wolves.
Good luck.
Whoops, almost forgot.
You'll do great, Zed.
Are you ready for the debate?
Come on, we're going
to be late.
You're going to prove
to everyone
that we're more than just...
...Monsters.
- Bucky made me look...
- ...Scary.
Announcer:
Attention, attention.
This is an active
demolition site.
All personnel please
evacuate immediately.
Demolition is scheduled
for 5:00 PM this evening.
All right, we don't have
much time.
This is how we sabotage
the demolition and stop them.
It's my responsibility to make
sure we're all safe.
We follow my lead.
It's a good plan, Willa.
Addison:
What plan?
We're going after
the moonstone.
Top secret.
You can't tell anyone.
Bad wolf, bad wolf!
You're going after
the moonstone now?
It won't survive
the detonation.
Then let me join you.
I'm ready to become
a wolf.
If you really are one.
(gasps)
It's gone.
You lost it?
Do you know how precious
a moonstone necklace is?
If she was serious
about being a wolf,
if she was the Great Alpha,
she wouldn't have been
so careless.
No, I... I don't know how!
I...
Stay out of our amazing hair.
You got your speech?
Addison's necklace?
I took it.
I can't let her become
a werewolf.
I have to protect her.
All of this,
running for president,
it's all for her.
No, Zed.
This is bigger than that,
okay?
This is for you, for me,
for all zombies everywhere.
This is more important
than anything else.
Look, we'll deal
with this later, okay?
Just become president.
That's what zombies need.
(exhales)
(cheering)
Your first nominee for...
Running for president,
wearing the sequined
Mighty Shrimp uniform...
Three time MVP,
lean, mean, cheering machine...
And captain of our hearts...
All: Bucky!
(loud cheering)
(dance music fanfare)
Your other candidate of...
Why not?
Introducing our soon-to-be
first green-haired president
and repping a proud people,
Zed!
(loud cheering)
Hear him roar!
(growls)
Um no, actually, we're not
going to roar.
No roaring.
Zed'll fight for you!
You know what, um,
I'm not going to fight.
'Cause, no, this isn't
a fight.
This is just a nice lil' cordial
debate we're having here today.
Good to hear, Zed.
(laughs)
Oh, did you see that?
That was a high-five.
No.
Are you ready to battle?
(loud cheering)
(rap music)
♪ Ha, ha ♪
(Bonzo speaks Zombie)
♪ It is my mission ♪
♪ We got a goal in mind ♪
♪ Save our tradition ♪
♪ That is the bottom line ♪
♪ We're always winnin' ♪
♪ Look how the trophies
shine ♪
♪ You're going down ♪
♪ Burying you back
underground ♪
♪ I'm the one who stands up
for the people ♪
♪ I embrace diversity ♪
♪ Treat everyone as equal ♪
- ♪ Zed is thoughtful ♪
- ♪ Thanks ♪
- ♪ He's a natural born leader ♪
- ♪ True ♪
♪ And if you think
about it ♪
♪ Bucky is neither ♪
♪ Yo, I will win this race ♪
♪ I'm a cheer rockstar ♪
♪ Mirrors love my face ♪
♪ Your ego made your
head so big ♪
♪ You can't see ♪
♪ You got no shot
to beat me ♪
All: Ooooh!
♪ I know ya hear me,
if ya with me stand up ♪
♪ No way you win if you go
against us ♪
♪ In pictures, we're
more glamorous ♪
♪ You wanna battle
with the best? ♪
♪ Good luck!
Let's go! ♪
♪ You need a leader who
looks out for the crowd ♪
♪ Then I'm winning ♪
♪ Someone that'll
make you proud ♪
♪ Then I'm winning ♪
♪ There through
the ups and downs ♪
♪ I'm winning ♪
♪ Let me hear
you scream it loud ♪
♪ I'm winning ♪
♪ I challenge an old
way of thinking ♪
♪ Yo, I know I'd be a much
better president ♪
♪ Tell 'em your reasons ♪
♪ I'm a real human ♪
♪ There's no danger in that ♪
- ♪ They're real monsters ♪
- ♪ Man! ♪
♪ What if they turn back? ♪
♪ We aren't monsters, man ♪
♪ We win the football games ♪
♪ We joined the cheer squad ♪
♪ Monsters wouldn't
do those things ♪
♪ We got a good attitude ♪
♪ Dude, you eat brains ♪
♪ If I did, you don't have one
so you'd be safe ♪
(rapping in Zombie)
♪ Ohhh Zigna Do dinga ♪
♪ Badda do ♪
♪ Bidda ba dida bow ♪
♪ Deda Zaga dada
doo ahh ♪
♪ You're all weird
and strange ♪
♪ We are here for change ♪
♪ We need a president
who'll do whatever it takes ♪
♪ Look, we can go back
and forth ♪
♪ But in the end
it's fact ♪
♪ You're a monster and
you can't debate that ♪
♪ I know ya hear me ♪
♪ If ya with me
stand up ♪
♪ No way you win if you go
against us ♪
♪ I know we'll be victorious ♪
- ♪ You wanna battle with the best, good luck ♪
- ♪ Let's go! ♪
- ♪ You need a leader who looks out for the crowd ♪
- ♪ Then I'm winning ♪
- ♪ Someone that'll make you proud ♪
- ♪ There through the ups and downs ♪
- ♪ I'm winning ♪
- ♪ Let me hear you scream it loud ♪
- ♪ You wanna change Seabrook ♪
- ♪ Yeah, for the better ♪
♪ Aha! I knew it! How's it better
to have zombies at Prawn? ♪
- ♪ Our dance game's strong ♪
- ♪ What? ♪
♪ Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go ♪
♪ Zombie tongue
at Seabrook's ♪
(in Zombie)
Graba gaba Zigna
♪ I think I'd make a fine
President too ♪
♪ Thanks for
the compliment ♪
♪ I think you'd like Zombie
as a second language ♪
♪ It's an easy A ♪
♪ What's next, more zombie
dates on calendar? ♪
- ♪ More holidays ♪
- All: Yay!
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ And as an added perk ♪
♪ If I'm president ♪
♪ No more homework! ♪
♪ You need a leader who
looks out for the crowd ♪
♪ Then I'm winning ♪
- ♪ Someone that'll make you proud ♪
- ♪ I'm winning ♪
- ♪ There through the ups and downs ♪
- ♪ Let me hear you scream it loud ♪
- ♪ I'm winning ♪
♪ You need a leader who looks
out for the crowd ♪
♪ Then I'm winning ♪
- ♪ Someone that'll make you proud ♪
- ♪ I'm winning! ♪
- ♪ There through the ups and downs ♪
- ♪ I'm winning ♪
♪ Let me hear you scream
it loud ♪
♪ I'm winning ♪
(loud cheering)
No!
Zed for prez!
Vote for me, because I swear
I'm no monster.
(electric zapping)
(loud growls)
Oh no!
Addison's necklace is shutting
down your Z-band.
(terrified screams)
(loud roars)
See! See! He's a monster!
(terrified screams)
Can't let them see me
as monster!
(terrified screaming)
Breathe. Focus, okay?
You can control this.
You don't have to hide,
Zed.
(loud roar)
I know you won't hurt me,
big guy.
But they don't!
(terrified screaming)
Go on, throw it!
(loud roar)
Zed, the necklace!
Remove it!
Zed, wait.
I lost the election.
Maybe.
Probably.
Yeah, you did.
Look, but the problem is
you lost yourself first.
(alarm blaring)
Willa: We triggered the alarm,
hurry!
Wolves, freeze where you are!
(growling and snarling)
Addie, are you okay?
I lost the necklace,
Bree.
I let the wolves down.
(alarm blaring)
The Z-alarm?
Announcer:
Attention! Attention!
Monster activity
at Seabrook Power.
It's the werewolves.
We need to help them.
Bree, would you?
I will.
I'm in. Always.
We can't do this alone.
We need to rally the Z-team.
Right.
No. Actually, we're gonna
need everyone.
Aye-aye, captain.
- Come on!
- Okay.
You're trespassing,
werewolves!
How can we be trespassing
on our own land?
This is werewolf territory!
I don't know anything
about that.
We can take them.
(growling and snarling)
♪♪
(snarling)
♪ Hear it getting louder ♪
♪ A call for revolution,
yeah ♪
♪ We came for what
was ours ♪
♪ It's time for restitution ♪
♪ We'll protect our own,
take back the stone ♪
♪ No human nature cannot
hold us down ♪
♪ Stranded at the bottom ♪
♪ But we're more than
a whisper ♪
♪ No, we'll never
be forgotten ♪
♪ Our blood's thicker
than silver, yeah ♪
♪ When worlds collide
it's do or die ♪
♪ So tell me, is it wrong
to stand your ground? ♪
♪ Hear us howl ♪
♪ All or nothing ♪
♪ Fangs are out
We ain't running ♪
♪ Hear us howl
It's all or nothing ♪
♪ Oooooooh ♪
♪ This is a declaration ♪
♪ Ooooooh ♪
♪ Of a new generation ♪
♪ It's now or never ♪
♪ We're in this together ♪
♪ We'll fight through
the highs and the lows ♪
♪ No we won't break ♪
♪ We're more than flesh
and bone ♪
♪♪
Arrest them!
(coughing)
Colloidal silver.
That'll tame these beasts.
Demo time.
Everybody clear out.
I failed you.
They'll destroy the moonstone.
They'll destroy us.
Addison: No!
Both: Addison?
♪ The world has gone crazy ♪
♪ And no one seems
to listen ♪
♪ Gotta step in
No more maybes ♪
♪ And stop the demolition ♪
♪ Is it hope or fear
look in the mirror ♪
♪ Everything we've built
is coming down ♪
♪ No more hesitation ♪
♪ It's time we start
to realize ♪
♪ With all this separation ♪
♪ Silence is
still taking sides ♪
♪ So use your voice
make a choice ♪
♪ And tell me are you standing
with the crowd? ♪
♪ Ooooooh ♪
♪ This is a declaration ♪
♪ Ooooooooh ♪
♪ Of a new generation ♪
♪ It's now or never ♪
♪ We're in this together ♪
♪ We'll fight through
the highs and the lows ♪
♪ No we won't break ♪
♪ We're more than flesh
and bone ♪
(grunts)
♪ We say no more bad blood ♪
♪ No more bad blood ♪
♪ Aaaaaaay ♪
♪ No way they can't
stop us ♪
♪ No they can't stop us ♪
♪ Aaaaaaay ♪
♪ We say no more bad blood ♪
♪ No more bad blood ♪
♪ Aaaaaaay ♪
♪ No way ♪
♪ They can't stop us ♪
♪ No they can't stop us ♪
♪ History changes ♪
♪ But we lost the pages
we wrote ♪
♪ When you lose direction
Can't see the reflection ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ We came from the bottom ♪
♪ Then became the problem ♪
♪ Now everything's
out of control ♪
♪ So hey, are you with me? ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Oooooooh ♪
♪ This is a declaration ♪
♪ Of a new generation ♪
♪ It's now or never ♪
♪ We're in this together ♪
♪ We'll fight through
the highs and the lows ♪
All: Yeah!
♪ No we won't break ♪
♪ We're more than flesh
and bone ♪
♪♪
You gotta stop the demolition,
Dad.
I know how hard you worked
to get this job.
But if it's gonna hurt
the werewolves,
you have to stop it.
You're right.
And Addison's right.
Shut it down.
Stop the detonation.
Tomorrow, when it's safe,
we'll find what
you're looking for.
But right now,
you can all go home.
(cheering)
Yes!
Zed: Hey.
We did it, we stopped
the demo!
(laughs)
What's wrong?
Addison.
I'm gonna lose the election,
which means I can't take
you to Prawn.
That's okay, Zed.
We cannot go to
the Prawn together.
He found it!
(laughs)
Thank you.
- What?
- I took it.
I stole it when
you weren't looking.
I thought I lost it.
- I questioned myself.
- Addison, I'm sorry.
I was afraid that if you turned
into a wolf, I'd lose you.
You don't get to make
that choice for me!
But a werewolf?
I finally find where
I belong,
and you try to steal that
from me?
Why would I ever go to the Prawn
with you after what you did?
Am I?
You're beautiful, Addie,
but the same beautiful
that you've always been.
She's not a werewolf.
Oh my gosh, boss, boss!
We got a problem!
- What?
- The remote shorted out,
and now the detonation
timer's running.
Zevon:
Well, shut it off!
I can't.
No, no!
(explosion booming)
What have they done?
(werewolves coughing)
Addison?
The center of Zombie and
Werewolf culture is in rubble,
and I still don't have a pack.
Bucky (on PA):
Attention, everyone.
This is your new president,
Bucky reminding you
that the Prawn
is tomorrow night.
Principal Lee (on PA):
As you know,
with the anti-monster laws
still in place,
this is a human only event.
(both speaking zombie)
(coughing)
They were wrong to destroy
Seabrook power,
and I was wrong about
werewolves.
You have every right to fight
for who you are.
Yeah, but what are we now,
zombie?
You're fierce,
proud werewolves.
Yeah, they think we're monsters.
We are monsters.
♪♪
Thank you, sir.
After you.
What's that?
♪♪
It's zombies!
And werewolves.
In formal wear?
♪♪
They look good.
You guys can't be here.
There are laws against this.
Bad laws are meant
to be broken.
And monsters don't follow
the rules.
Zombies are a part of
Seabrook, Bucky.
And we deserve
to be here.
We're a part of Seabrook, too.
The originals, in fact.
Someone's gotta stop you.
(snarls)
Welcome to Prawn.
(coughs)
(chattering)
Bonzo!
(speaking Zombie)
Yes. I'll go to Prawn
with you!
(giggles)
Addison.
I had no right to take
your necklace
to stop you from becoming
a werewolf.
I couldn't handle the fact
that you might be a monster,
'cause I couldn't accept
the fact that I am one.
I thought everything would make
sense if I was a werewolf,
but I'm not.
And I don't even know
if I'm a cheerleader.
You're a leader, Addison.
You make others belong.
At camp, at cheer practice.
You're the one protesting
for what's right.
You bring people together.
♪♪
♪ You're from the
perfect paradise ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ And I'm living on
the darker side ♪
♪ Ooh, I had a feeling
if you got to know me ♪
♪ Right from the start
you caught my eye ♪
♪ And something inside me
came to life ♪
♪ Ooh, I've got a feeling ♪
♪ Now you really know me ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ This could be,
this could be ordinary ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ Could we be something
extraordinary ♪
♪ You and me side by side ♪
♪ Out in the broad daylight ♪
♪ If they laugh,
we'll say ♪
♪ We're going to be someday ♪
♪ Someday, someday ♪
♪ We're gonna be someday ♪
(rumbling)
This way!
(screaming)
(glass rattling)
You're supposed to protect
your president!
(yelps)
(rumbling)
(screaming)
Zed: The energy from the moonstone
must've created the fault line.
Willa:
What?
Zed: If we follow this crack,
it may lead us to the moonstone.
So it's only buried
and not destroyed.
(rumbling)
We have to get to it.
Quickly, while we still can.
It's this way.
I see the light.
It's coming
from Seabrook Power.
Here it is!
(growling)
(screams)
We have to move it out of here.
Legend says that together,
our pack can move the stone.
All of us, lift!
(grunting)
It's too heavy.
There's not enough of us.
Then maybe you need to expand
your pack.
Addison?
(rumbling)
We came here to help.
Come on, everyone.
We got this!
Right.
Hurry, before it's too late!
Together lift!
(rumbling)
Chamber's collapsed.
We can't carry the moonstone
through.
Eliza: Your Z-band,
it's still broken.
Zed, take it off.
Lift the slab.
Okay, Zed, you can
do this.
I'm not ready. What if
I can't control it?
All: Oh!
Zed, you have to.
(roar)
Yes!
Addison:
Come on, you can do this.
(loud grunts)
(roar)
Oh, no!
Zed!
(rapid beeping)
(cheering)
Zed! Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm me.
We crushed it!
We nailed it!
We so rock! Yes!
Too much?
Perfect.
(laughs)
We did it.
Say "brains."
Both: Brains!
(camera shutter snaps)
We're getting our first zombie
on the Prawn wall of fame.
(all howling)
Hey, you said that perfectly.
Bonzo's got an ear
for languages.
- (laughs)
- (speaking zombie)
♪♪
♪ We are all different,
baby ♪
♪ But that's what I like ♪
♪ We're separate
but we're together ♪
♪ Like stars in the sky ♪
♪ We've got a good thing
going on ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Nobody has to feel alone,
oh yeah ♪
♪ One of us chased the day ♪
♪ And one of us faced
the night ♪
♪ And all of us paved
the way ♪
♪ To where we all
are tonight ♪
♪ Turned around ♪
♪ And now we've found ♪
♪ That we are now ♪
♪ All ♪
♪ One for all ♪
♪ Used to be divided ♪
♪ And now we're all united ♪
♪ One for all ♪
♪ This party ain't private ♪
♪ Everyone's invited ♪
♪ One for all ♪
♪ No wristband required ♪
♪ Get hype, get excited ♪
♪ One for all, one for all ♪
♪ One for all,
one for all ♪
♪ There's something here
that's magic ♪
♪ Let's dance until dawn ♪
♪ The feeling is automatic ♪
♪ It's where we belong ♪
♪ We're so unique,
we're not the same ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ And that's what gives us
all our strength ♪
♪ One of us chased the day ♪
♪ And one of us faced
the night ♪
♪ And all of us paved
the way ♪
♪ To where we all
are tonight ♪
♪ Turned around ♪
♪ And now we've found ♪
(loud roar)
♪ All ♪
♪ We have got to bring
it on, on ♪
♪ Watch me shake it like
a pom-pom ♪
♪ Yeah, shake it, shake it,
shake it, shake it ♪
♪ Shake it like a pom-pom ♪
♪ Yeah, get sick, get ill ♪
♪ Lean back with
the zombie tilt ♪
♪ Hey, with a zombie tilt ♪
♪ Yeah, with a zombie tilt ♪
♪ New kids on
the new block ♪
(howling)
♪ Werewolves do
the moon walk ♪
♪ Do the ooooh, do the oooh ♪
♪ One for all ♪
♪ Used to be divided ♪
♪ Now we're all united ♪
♪ One for all ♪
♪ This party ain't private ♪
♪ Everyone's invited ♪
- ♪ One for all ♪
- ♪ No wristband required ♪
♪ One for all ♪
♪ Get hype, get excited ♪
♪ One for all, one for all ♪
♪ One for all,
one for all ♪
Who wants pizza?
(cheering wildly)
♪ One for all ♪
♪♪
(howling)
♪ One for all ♪
(cheering)
(eerie music)
(static sounds)
Weird.
♪♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org