[eerie music playing]
ANNOUNCER [ON TV]:
For the past 10 years,
New Yorkers have
known who to turn to
for the most accurate weather.
He's a MAN 1: who has broughtthem events as they were
happening before they happened.
[children chattering]
In fact, it's almost unnaturalhow accurate this man
has been about the weather.
It's made us wonder.
Starting this winter,
he'll be giving
his heart and soul to
do it for the rest of us
all across the country.
[clicking]
This is your new
"Hello, USA" weatherman.
This man is Greg Harrison.
And he's willing to
do whatever it takes.
GREG: Well, let's cut to it.
I'm getting the sense youdidn't like the commercial.
Now what makes you think that?
Because you haven't
said a word about it,
which is not like you.
Well.
Come on, out with it.
I can take it.
I can take the truth.
Tell me what the younger
generation thinks.
[laughs] I thought itmade you look a little evil.
The message is
that I'm ruthless,
that I'll do whatever
it takes to bring
the people the weather.
They like that.
But you're not ruthless, Greg.
Jane, you have to be
pretty ruthless to get
to be national weatherman.
Or a good kiss ass.
Have you smelled this vanilla?
Smell it.
I--
See how ruthless I am?
My parent's brownstone
was just like this one.
Grove Street was just
around the corner.
I used to walk home from schooldown this street all the time.
[sighs]
[footsteps]
Hello?
[door slamming]
Not very friendly.
It's nice, isn't it?
Yeah, it's all
right, all right.
Sorry, it's not
exactly my style.
Oh, as if you
had a style, Greg.
That's why I hooked
up with you, dear.
So your aunt fell
down all those stairs?
That's a lot of stairs
for an old lady.
That is a lot of
stairs for anybody.
Somebody should have toldher to move somewhere else.
She wouldn't have listened.
My aunt depended on no one.
I would come here to visither when I was little.
I remember I used to
lie awake at night
and fantasize about havingmy own apartment just
like this one.
And now it's mine.
Yours?
She snuck my
name on the lease.
So I pay what she
payed, $400 a month.
$400?
The landlord can't be
too happy about that.
You might me able to subletthis place, $3,000-$4,000 easy.
I'm not going to
sublet it, Greg.
I'm keeping it.
Keeping it?
I don't understand.
We just got a place together.
I just want a little space.
Is that a crime?
My office is so small, andCheryl shares that with me.
I just-- this place is so cheap.
And you, this is yourgraceful way of telling me?
I was-- I was waiting for the--
that's why--
MAN 1: Hey, you're
Greg Harrison, "Rise
and Shine New York," right?
Let me shake your hand.
You're great.
Well, thanks a lot.
You know, I appreciate
that, really.
OK. [LAUGHING
NERVOUSLY] See you.
Thanks.
You have a good night.
[CHUCKLING] OK, heh-heh.
That's why you keptpushing back the moving day?
This is your graceful
way out of it?
You want me to live in theWestchester house by myself?
I'm in the middle of the
most important career
move of my life.
I need you now.
Why couldn't you tell me sooner?
I didn't know sooner.
Jane, you think
you can just throw
other people's lives intoturmoil and it doesn't matter?
It does.
It has serious repercussions.
Can we talk about this?
If you'd calm down, Greg.
What about dinner?
Look, you'll
have to forgive me.
I'm really not in the
mood to go out anymore.
I'm gonna go open up.
Oh, you've got keys.
How'd you get the keys?
I'm moving into theapartment on the fifth floor.
My name's Jane Emelin.
I've seen you here
before, haven't I?
Probably.
I used to visit my Aunt Cecile.
Did you know Cecile?
Oh, well, of course I did.
Hello, Jane.
My name's Martha Stewart--
not the famous one though.
Right.
Oh, you know, I'm
the one who found her.
It was just awful, herhead smashed to potatoes.
Poor dear.
Do you need any help
carrying your things in?
No, I'm fine.
I have movers coming.
I have a lot of stuff.
Oh, good, good, good.
That's what this building has--
can't be bought, can't be sold.
Have you met anyone else yet?
In the building, you mean?
No, not yet.
Oh, well, we're all avery friendly group here.
Mr. And Mrs. Bryant live
on the second floor.
Mr. Collins lives
on the third floor.
He's a dashing man.
You should probably
leave him alone though.
He likes his privacy.
What about the
person right beneath me
with all those trash bags?
The fourth floor?
Yeah.
Oh, dear Alice, poor thing.
She was hit really hard
by your aunt's death.
It was just about more
than she could stomach.
You won't have to
see much of her.
She's a hermit, an
eccentric, you know.
Yeah.
Oh, what's this?
So you like older men, do you?
No, not necessarily.
He looks a lot likethat weatherman, you know,
the "Rise and Shine" guy?
Yeah, that's him.
Where did you meet?
I helped him with his office.
Secretary?
Not quite.
I help him with acquisitions.
I'm an interior designer.
Well.
[pounding]
Yes?
What's going on here?
You just come here and noone says anything to me?
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
You will be.
You can't just move inhere without talking to me.
Give me your keys.
Now, Jerry.
Jerry, calm down.
Calm down, dear.
You know you're
not allowed keys.
It's all right.
What was that about?
He's the super.
Well, he's actually
the landlord's nephew.
He probably just thought he'dbe moving into the apartment.
He has to live in the basementwith all the storage, you see.
He's got a disability.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
[soft music playing]
Oof.
Ah.
[nail clattering]
Whoa.
Shit.
OK.
[distant scream]
[man yelling]
[tense music playing]
[intercom buzzing]
Hello?
[static]
[intercom buzzing]
Who is it?
[static]
[footsteps]
[door slamming]
[intercom buzzing]
Hello?
DELIVERYMAN [ON INTERCOM]:Delivery for Jane Emelin.
What?
He said it has to be
set up in your bedroom,
and we have to
program it for you.
He said you wouldn't
know how to.
Yeah, I don't know howbecause I hate television.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I'm just trying to do my job.
OK.
Well, I have to get ready.
Yeah, we'll just set this up.
Then we'll get out of your way.
Yeah, OK.
Altercation?
[sighs]
Jerry?
Did you have something--
I know you meant it as
a nice gesture, Greg.
But the thing takes
up half my bedroom.
I don't know.
Get somebody to come
and get rid of it.
Yeah, what surprise?
Cheryl, you want to
come bring those in?
OK.
I've got to go.
All right, I'll
talk to you later.
Goodbye.
Everything OK with him?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Why?
I don't know.
You seem a little tense.
That's because
the lady downstairs
left me this crabby note.
I want to move my furniturearound before it gets too late.
Jeez.
I have to bring in
those tear sheets.
I know.
You know, I have a goodidea of what you're going for.
I could start it for you.
And then you could unpack.
Yeah, that would be great.
Would you do that for me?
So call me at home if
you have any questions.
I've got it all under control.
I'm just trying
to figure it out,
what I could have
done differently.
It's not about you.
It's about me.
It's about this place.
[sighs]
When you asked me
to move in with you,
I really wanted
for it to be right.
I really did.
And I tried to convince myself.
Look, Greg, I've nevereven lived on my own yet.
I'd hate to have to us move allthe way out there and find out
that we didn't really know whatwe were getting ourselves into.
I just know that
this isn't going
to turn out the way you want.
Can't we just keep it
the way it is for now,
and then we'll see?
Well, I don't see
that I have much choice.
[thunder booming]
Ah.
Hey.
Hey, wait.
Oh, I thought you
were Mrs. Stewart.
Mrs. Stewart?
[BREATHLESSLY] Yes, thank god.
That woman pursues me everytime I walk into this place.
It's getting me in shape,I'll tell you that.
How do you do?
I'm Mr. Collins.
You must be Miss
Emelin, the new tenant.
We, none of us, knew that, um--
that Mrs. Lewis had anyone.
Such a tragedy, what happened.
Yeah.
I'm sorry I haven't comeup to introduce myself.
It's bad form.
No, not at all.
I should have introduced myself.
Actually, I'm kind of
off to a rocky start
with half the building already.
[laughs]
I've always been amazed
at your profession,
to go into other people'shouses and decide
how they should live.
It's true.
But I find that people don'tknow what they really want.
And most of the time, I havea better idea than they do.
The job is to try and get insidetheir heads and figure it out.
Sometimes that's tough.
Oh, the million
dollar question, what
goes on inside others' heads?
We only know what they show us.
It's true.
Quite a collection
you have here.
Oh, thank you, Mr. Collins.
It's kind of all over
the place right now.
That carving, is
that South American?
Actually, that's aCambodian protective spirit.
And you hang it above thedoorway, and it protects you.
I haven't figured out
just how to hang it yet.
I'm a collector
myself, you know--
Mid-East, mostly.
I'm terrible.
I keep on getting
more and more things.
And I don't have
the space for it.
Well, I could really
chat all night.
But you've obviously got
some work ahead of you.
Yeah.
It's good to get a bettersense of you, Miss Emelin.
[fly buzzing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[gasps]
OPERATOR [ON PHONE]: 911,what's your emergency?
Hi.
I'm not sure if this
is an emergency or not.
But--
OPERATOR [ON PHONE]:
Name and address?
Jane Emelin, 146 11th Street.
I just saw something
in the window right
across the way from mine.
And I'm not sure
what the address is.
I just know it's right--
[knocking on door]
Can you hold on for
one second, please?
Sorry to bother you so late.
I hope you don't
still have company.
On the phone with
your boyfriend?
No.
Just wondering if I couldborrow a little sugar, dear.
Sure.
Oh, thank you.
GREG [ON TV]: Good morning.
Rise and shine, and getout of bed, New York City.
Wipe that sleep out of you eyes.
Come on, everybody.
Don't be a plain-Jane.
Ugh.
[plays harmonica note]
GREG [ON TV]: And[SINGING] Rise and shine,
and give out your glory, glory.
Rise and shine, and give
out your glory, glory.
And I got a letter from
Todd Jacobs, age 5,
asking how to
become a weatherman.
Well, Ted, there's
a lot you can do
to learn more about the
environment around you.
This week is a
good week to start.
As you can see
from the satellite,
look, we've got some beautifullyunstable weather moving
towards the Big Shiny Apple thismorning, or by this evening,
or tomorrow Dust off andwhip out those umbrellas.
We should be getting a douser.
Clouds are already moving--
Oh, gross.
GREG [ON TV]:
--North and the West.
Thunderstorms are
already popping up
in South Central New Hampshireand Eastern Massachusetts.
[classical music playing]
[laughs]
Oh, boy.
[grunting]
[neighbor pounding]
Sorry.
"You've been warned.
Take it seriously."
Uh.
[ominous music playing]
You need any help
back there, young lady?
Oh, no.
I'm just looking for
the right size nails.
[knocking]
WOMAN: Let me in.
Come on.
For the last time,
I'm telling you.
Uh, open up.
Come on.
MARTHA: It's Mrs. Bryant.
Her husband accidentally
locked her out again.
They're both deaf,
blind as bats too.
Oh, and don't touch her.
They scare very easily.
So I gather you met
Mr. Collins last night.
Yeah, he's very nice.
Well, I'm glad you met.
But it's best not
to bother him again.
Well, I didn't think
I was bothering him.
Well, I understand, dear.
But it's really best
to leave him alone.
OK.
MRS. BRYANT: Open the door.
Just open this door.
[SIGHING] Oh, damn it.
[footsteps]
[heavy breathing]
Hello?
Apartment 5?
You just move in, Jane?
I saw your note on
the door downstairs.
Oh, yeah.
I haven't met her yet.
You stick something inhere trying to open the door?
No.
Well, there's something
jamming this up.
You're gonna need a new lock.
OK, I think this
should cover it.
We saw each other
last night, didn't we?
I'm sorry?
I live right over
there across the way.
You were looking
in my apartment.
No.
I-- well, I wasn't--
Don't you know aboutpeople and their privacy?
I'm just kidding.
Don't worry about it.
I hope you didn't call thecops on me or anything.
No.
No, of course not.
I just happened tonotice you and your wife.
She's not my wife.
She's just helping
me with something.
Here's your new set.
Thank you very much.
It's a great apartment.
It's one of my
favorite buildings--
It's impossible to get
into this building.
Is that key to my place also?
Yeah.
I keep a master to every lockI work on in this building.
The super isn't allowed
to keep keys here.
He's a little strange.
You know, you have a
really interesting face.
[SIGHING] Uh.
[neighbor pounding]
Aw, come on.
This is absurd.
I gotta move in, Granny.
[stomping on floor]
Unbelievable.
[pounding continues]
[laughing]
[footsteps approaching]
Oh, man.
OK, listen to this.
"You must lay large area rugsor buffers down to reduce
everyday oral disturbances.
You are forbidden to
wear shoes after dark.
You may keep them outside yourdoor as is customary in Japan."
Japan?
And there's more.
"After 10 PM, no
guests are allowed.
Any romantic liaisons may becarried out with common regard
for oral disturbance."
She keeps saying that.
Oral disturbance.
"If objects are
to be moved around,
you may do so between
1:00 and 1:15.
This includes any previsions."
I mean, is she
fucking kidding me?
How many?
Pages, pages upon
pages of this stuff.
And then the last sentencesays, "You have now been warned,
so there will be
no forgiveness."
You know, you should askaround about this lady.
She sounds a little kooky.
Yeah, she does, doesn't she?
I mean do you think a little oldwoman could have written that?
Yeah, why not?
[fly buzzing]
Hey, you gotta close yourwindows or something.
You got a fly problem in here.
[sighs]
Oh, I don't know.
I'm probably
overreacting, but it--
it just seems so
vicious and weird,
like I have to walk oneggshells in my own apartment.
I understand.
You're loving
this, aren't you?
[laughs]
Don't say I didn't warn you.
These people are
very predictable.
You had this romantic
idea of a friendly--
[knocking on door]
[gasps]
Are we a little nervous?
Hi.
MR. COLLINS: I saw this
at an auction today.
I thought you would like it.
Consider it a housewarming gift.
Wow, that's very nice.
Thank you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize that--
No, that's OK.
That's Greg Harrison,
the weatherman.
Well, you know, I watch youevery morning that you're on.
Oh, that's very kind.
Thank you.
We actually went to the
same high school, PS 4.
My name is Albert Collins.
Collins?
You used to live downin this area, didn't you?
Did we know each other?
No, no, no.
You wouldn't have known me.
But I thought that sinceyou're such a famous alumnus,
I had to mention it anyway.
I didn't mean to intrude.
I--
[phone ringing]
- Not at all.
Not at all.
JANE: Hello?
Excuse me.
I have to take this.
- Yeah.
OK?
Have a seat.
Oh.
JANE: Yes, I'm listening.
Thank you.
So you decided
to stay down here.
Oh, yeah.
[LAUGHING NERVOUSLY] Excuse me.
Don't worry about it.
Have a seat.
So they still talk
about me at PS 4?
Yes, I understand.
Of course, it's very hard.
I'm on your side
though, Mrs. Adamson.
I know.
I'll speak to you firstthing tomorrow morning, OK?
All right.
OK, buh-bye.
Sorry about that.
She keeps threatening
to get another--
Hello?
Hello, Greg?
GREG: Jane?
[gasps]
[sighs]
You scared me.
Are you sure this alonespace is good for your health?
Where did you go?
Just out in the hallway.
I was just saying
goodbye to Collins.
He's a nice guy.
Let's eat.
I'm famished.
What?
You have to wipe
those completely,
otherwise they spot.
I am.
No, look.
This one's starting
to streak already.
Well, this is the
way I wipe plates.
What's with you
all of a sudden?
Don't get offended because Iwant my plates a certain way.
Your plates.
You have to haveeverything a certain way.
What is that supposed to mean?
Forget it, nothing.
No.
What does that mean?
Please, I'm trying
to concentrate.
Stop it.
You know, nothing is
a compromise with you.
It's either your way or bust.
[laughs]
You're really going tothrow a fit because of the way
I want my plates.
Come on, Jane.You're smarter than that.
This isn't about
your goddamn dishes.
What is the difference?
What is the difference ifI move out there with you
or if I just stay
out there with you?
Come on, Greg.
I thought we had a
great night together.
We ate together.We're washing dishes together.
But it's your place.
It's not our place.
You know what your
problem is, Greg?
You are so hung up on terms.
I really-- I don't think itwould make a bit of difference.
I really don't.
- Jane, I love you.
I love spending time with you.
But Jane, what do you
think we're doing here?
We're playing house.
I'm tired of-- of playing.
[neighbor pounding]
I'm not taking shit
from you tonight.
[loud crack]
Ah!
I was just standing right there.
And then, all of a sudden, thetiles just started exploding.
I mean, look at my floor.
[CHUCKLING] Yeah.
[door closing]
Any answer?
No.
That's because she supposedlynever answers the door.
You know, the lady from thefirst floor said an 80-year-old
woman lives downstairs.
Yeah, that's her.
That's Alice.
Well, they blew up in a line.
I'd say it was
your heating pipes.
It happens in these
old buildings.
You weren't there.
It was explosive.
It was violent.
It's not heating pipes.
WOMAN 1 [ON POLICE RADIO]:Officer, please come in.
Excuse me.
Ah, of course, Elly.
WOMAN 1 [ON POLICE RADIO]:Jane Emelin, special case.
Yeah.
Jane Emelin?
- Yes.
You called a few nights agoand started to report something
else about this neighbor?
No, no.
That was another
person across the way
in the building next to mine.
All right.
Now listen.
You can fill out a
report if you want to.
OK.
But if you ask me, youshould call your landlord
and check your pipes.
[SARCASTICALLY]
My pipes, yeah, OK.
Thank you.
I thought it might be you.
What was all the hubbub
earlier with the police?
Don't worry about it, Martha.
I'm taking care of the problem.
We don't like the
police coming here.
You mess with me,
I mess with you.
[music - l7, "mantra down"]
[SINGING] Got my mantra down.
Got my mantra down.
Ultra violet light,
such a violent life,
such a violent life.
Got my mantra down.
[YELLING] You hear that?
You hear that?
Do you hear that?
Yeah!
[SINGING] Got my mantra down.
Got my mantra down.
Hey!
Ultra violet light,
such a violent life,
such a violent life.
[muffled rock music]
Woo!
[music drifting downstairs]
[neighbor pounding]
I overslept.
The power somehow justwent off in my apartment.
I'm leaving right now.
Fuck you already.
Oh!
[ominous music playing]
Is there anything
we can do legally?
Anything at all?
I'm just trying to
think impartially here.
I don't think anyone's goingto believe an old lady is
capable of doing all this.
Has anyone else complained?
No.
But I don't think it's
just a coincidence.
It's been happening
since I moved in.
Everything you have
is circumstantial.
Listen, Jane.
I'll do whatever you want me to.
But between you
and me, if you're
having this many
problems, maybe it would
be easier just to move out.
Moving out is not an
option for me, Ashley.
This apartment's just a fluke.
You and Greg were
gonna move in together.
Are you on Greg's payroll?
Jane?
Did you bring in the mock-upsfor the Baron meeting today?
Oh, no.
I forgot about that.
I think one of the moversmoved them into the basement.
I'll look for them.
- We need them.
- Yeah, I know.
I know.
I'll get them to you.
It'll just be a little later.
You know, Jane, you're alittle spun out these days.
Maybe you should justlet me go to the meeting,
just until you've calmed downand settled this stuff at home.
Cheryl, I'd
appreciate it if you'd
keep the personal
shit to yourself
and just focus on
the office right now.
I'll be fine.
OK?
OK.
[suspenseful music playing]
[gasps]
Jesus!
What are you doing downhere without the lights on?
Mr. Collins, the light
switch didn't work.
I just came down here toget something from a box.
You scared me to death.
You know, I almost knockedon your door earlier.
Are you all right, Miss Emelin?
I hear the police
were here last night.
What on earth could havewarranted calling the police?
Well, I called them
because I had to.
I'm being attacked by
the woman downstairs.
I'm afraid Alice didn't likeyour Aunt Cecile very much.
She must be taking
it out on you.
Martha told me that
they were friends.
Friends?
Not at all.
No.
No, the truth is Alice doesn'tget along with anyone, really.
I'm sorry this has been
so difficult for you.
But you know, sometimes it justtakes time to find your groove.
Of course, sometimes peoplejust never do find it.
It's like oil and water.
Buildings like this are
just about compromise.
So maybe this is a sign
that it was smart of you
to move to
Westchester after all.
Westchester?
You mean Greg's house?
Aw, you-- it sounds
like a lovely home.
And he-- he's such a nice man.
Yes.
He is.
No, I'm not moving there.
I'll fit in just fine here.
Thank you very much.
I didn't mean to
insult you, Miss Emelin.
I'm just trying
to look after you.
No, I appreciate your
concern, Mr. Collins.
But I'll be fine.
Not to worry.
[knocking on door]
MR BRYANT: Will you let
me in, Betty, please?
Betty!
Good evening.
MR BRYANT: Betty.
Oh, very well, thank you.
Just trying to find
the groove here.
Betty, come on.
Betty, will you
let me in, please?
Darn it, Betty!
[clanging]
[water running]
LOCKSMITH: You
just move in, Jane?
Ah!
[breathing heavily]
[gasps]
Oh, my god.
[gasping]
Oh!
Ah!
Oh, shit!
Oh!
Oh-ho, whoa.
Oh, you got an army in there.
How long's this been going on?
Just this morning.
I mean, don't you think
that's a little strange?
You clean up after
yourself and everything?
Yes.
I'm gonna be a while.
OK.
So what do you think?
I come back later
this afternoon?
Is that good?
Yeah, I may need
reinforcements.
Fine.
Do whatever you have to do.
Yeah, get back.
Hey!
Get back in.
I'll be right
over, Mrs. Adamson,
and then we'll work it out.
I've just been having someproblems-- and these--
at home lately.
Um, can I get you to
deliver this to my place
at around 5:00?
No problem.
What's your address?
JANE: 146 11st
Street, Apartment 5.
Of course.
Well, you'll be comfortablewith everything.
It's not a problem.
OK, I'll see you soon.
Say hello to
Miss Cooper for me.
Miss Cooper?
You know her?
We've been bringing her
groceries for 15 years.
Then two months ago therewas a note saying she doesn't
want deliveries anymore.
Will you tell her
we're asking about her?
Yeah, OK.
I'll tell her.
Thank you very much.
Come back soon.
We know your address
I wanted to talk to
you about Alice, Martha.
Alice?
I was down at
the Korean grocery.
And he told me that
she, all of a sudden,
just stopped ordering
groceries from them.
Wait a minute.
Why are you asking the
Koreans about Alice?
I didn't ask him.
He just told me that.
What is it with you?
First, the police--
then the Koreans?
Don't you have any respectfor people's privacy?
Who do you think you are?
A spy?
No, I'm not a spy.
And what about what Itold you about Mr. Collins?
I asked you to leave
the poor man alone.
He told me that you'vebeen knocking on his door,
asking about this and
that, and this and that.
There are rules here.
But you have to be
a rebel, don't you?
You are just like your aunt.
Why are you attacking meall of a sudden, Martha?
I'm not attacking you.
I'm warning you.
You are walking on very
thin ice down here.
You're putting thethermometer on the radiator.
Some of us are
trying to live here.
We gotta talk.
You been noticing a lotmore flies in your apartment
these days?
Yeah, a few, now
that you mention it.
They've been coming upthrough the drain in your tub.
Them white things in
your tub are maggots.
Something must have
died in those pipes.
They like to nest
in soft tissue.
Something died?
Ah, don't worry.
I sprayed pretty good.
But I'd keep a plug inthat drain for a few days.
OK.
Now about the mice.
I was cleaning up
when I found this.
Now take a close look.
You see that white mouse?
That's an albino mouse.
That ain't natural.
That's a laboratory mouse.
People use them to
feed their pet snakes.
I don't understand.
At first, I didn't either.
Come here.
I covered this up for you.
That's the mousehole there?
Take a look at that hole.
That ain't no mousehole.
Somebody drilled that.
You don't have a
mouse problem, lady.
You got a neighbor problem.
[ominous music playing]
[receding footsteps]
Greg, are you there?
Will you pick up, please?
OK, there's some verybad things happening now.
I think something really strangeis going on with the neighbor
down below me.
I really need you
to call me back.
OK, please?
Can you hear me?
Are you there?
All right, bye.
[gasps]
[clanging]
Oh, my god.
[WHISPERING] Oh, oh, my gosh.
Portcullis.
[intercom buzzing]
Hello?
MAN 2 [ON INTERCOM]:
Hi, I have a delivery
for your neighbor upstairs.
Can I leave it with you?
Yeah.
I'll be right down.
[eerie music playing]
OK.
[sobbing]
[gas hissing]
WOMAN 2 [ON PA]:
X-ray tech to ICU.
NURSE 2: Over here,
she needed an EKG.
Let me know.
Thank you.
JANE: I'm trying to tellyou that somebody hit me.
And look at my forehead.
You passed out
from the gas, Jane.
You hit your head on the floor.
You're my lawyer, OK?
Now help me out here.
I'm telling you that
somebody hit me.
Did you see him?
I don't remember.
They said her memory wasgoing to be a little shaky.
I remember everything.
I remember everything
that happened to me.
I remember-- he sent me apicture of Cecile's dead body,
Greg, like he was behind it.
[crying]
And I was taking these pictures.
I was going to show you.
I had all the proof.
He stole everything that I had.
What pictures?
This fucking
maniac, he diagrammed
my apartment on his ceiling.
I saw it.
He knew exactly
where everything was,
and he had it all mapped out.
I saw it.
ASHLEY: Who is he?
There is no old
woman downstairs.
An old woman couldn't
have done what I saw.
He did something to her.
Did any of the
neighbors see anything?
They don't think
anything is going on.
Well, we have to
go to the police.
ASHLEY: With what?
Can we show the police anything?
My floor, he drilled
a hole in my floor.
Um, there's no hole.
What?
POLICE OFFICER: You
sure it was here?
JANE: Yes.
I'm positive it was here.
Oh, I don't understand.
Are you all right?
[WEAKLY] Yeah, I'm fine, fine.
We have a reoccurring
10-90 with Jane Emelin.
MAN 3 [ON POLICE RADIO]: Yes.
I have 1785--
It just doesn't
make any sense.
MAN 3 [ON POLICE RADIO]: --asa recurring special case.
You've called a fewtimes before, haven't you,
Miss Emelin?
A few times?
Yes.
I tried to get help.
Copy that.
All right.
I'll go down and check
the hall downstairs
and see if I can see anything.
I don't understand.
GREG: So how come youdidn't tell me about calling
the police those other times?
Keep a list.
You know, they think
we're both crazy.
I saw the plans in the
fourth-floor apartment.
And whoever this
guy is, he wants
to take the building back.
How about all the peopleon the other three floors?
Why hasn't anything
happened to them?
Nobody knows what you're
talking about, Jane.
We could go back theretomorrow when I feel better.
And then I'll show you exactly
what I'm talking about.
I could find the exterminator.
No.
No, this has got to stop.
Nobody believes you, Jane.
Listen, you never even haveto go back in that building.
The phone gets
turned off tonight.
I'll get the movers to
pack you up tomorrow.
You are safe.
You've got a great
house up in the country.
Things got out of hand.
And it happened badly.
But it's a good thing thatwe're moving in together.
And I will give
you what you need.
I promise.
[dramatic music playing]
Knock, knock, knock!
You think you can get rid of me?
Come on, you son of a bitch!
Face me now.
Come on out and face
me, you motherfucker.
I'm not afraid of you.
Come out, you fucking coward.
You'd better come downstairs.
He wants to take
my place, take
it over, that fucking coward.
I know you think I'm crazy.
But I'm not.
I'm not crazy.
No, not at all.
Because I know what I know.
I know he did something
to that woman.
And I know he did
something to my aunt.
I know it now.
I believe you.
You do?
Yeah.
There is something
really evil going on.
Evil-- you think so?
I saw it.
I saw it upstairs.
It's not something that I'mjust going to walk away from.
I'm trying to own what's mine.
And I have rights.
And I won't have somebodyjust try to take that from me.
I understand.
I have a right to be herejust like anybody else.
And he wants to take thataway from me-- my right?
You were saying?
[WHISPERS] Portcullis.
[grunts]
MR. COLLINS: I tried tolook after you, to give you
the clues, to make
you see that this
was not where you belonged.
Unlike the others, I gaveyou the chance to leave.
But you wanted to
know the answer
to the million dollar question.
Do you know it now?
You're here.
Welcome to my design.
Welcome to the
inside of my mind.
[flies buzzing]
Oh, oh, oh.
[gasping and sobbing]
MR. COLLINS: Ever been caughtin a portcullis before?
A chamber to insulate thepharaohs in their tombs.
This is my version.
Help!
Silence is the mostbeautiful noise in the world.
But you don't understand that.
A building is an organic
creature, you know?
And the organism of this
building, what I need
is not a lot to ask for.
But you have to
have your own rules.
Cecile didn't understand.
Alice didn't understand.
You, all of you, are infections.
And infections have to
be cleared or cut out.
[dramatic music playing]
[grunts]
[screams]
Ah!
[panting]
[phone beeping]
[whimpering]
It's very sad, Miss Emelin.
We see the world in much
the same way, I think.
Territory is very
important to us.
Unfortunately, yourterritory infringes on mine.
[suspenseful music playing]
Yah!
I think is the only way out.
Ow, oh.
What are you doing?
[screaming]
[moaning]
[grunts]
[screams]
GREG: Collins.
Gregory.
Give it.
[howls]
Ah!
[screaming]
[sobbing]
Shh.
GREG [ON TV]: Rise and
shine, New York City.
Even though we've had
a very feisty fall,
we've unfortunately got an evenmore active winter on the way.
This is also,unfortunately, my last show
as your local forecaster.
[applause]
[audience booing]
Now, now, now.
I'll still be with you
though every morning--
MAN 4 [ON TV]: You suck, Greg.
GREG [ON TV]: --on "Hello, USA."
But first, let me give
you that one last look
at the weather in your area.
Showers--
Did you get everything
we wanted today?
Yeah, the Adamson's
are back on track.
Of course, I made
a few suggestions.
I think you'd approve.
Well, I'm sure I would.
I have total faith
in you, Cheryl.
Hey, I'm just
trying to do my job.
Oh, yeah, that locksmith guycalled and left his address.
Said he needs to see you.
He has something to show you.
Oh, good.
I never got a
chance to thank him.
ANNOUNCER [ON TV]:
For the past 10 years,
New Yorkers have
known who to turn to
for the most accurate weather.
He's the man who has broughtthem events as they were
happening before they happened.
In fact, it's almost unnaturalhow accurate this man
has been about the weather.
It's made us wonder.
Starting this winter,
he'll be giving
his heart and soul to
do it for the rest of us
all across the country.
This man is your new,
"Hello, USA" weatherman.
This man is Greg Harrison.
And he's willing to
do whatever it takes.
[music playing]