(Multicom Jingle)
(tinkling music)
(waves crashing)
(light jazz music)
- [Marilyn] When I was
born in the charity ward
of the Los Angeles County
Hospital, my mother wasn't there.
Where my mother was, no one knew.
- Mrs. Mortenson, are you in here?
(baby cries)
Shh.
Mrs. Mortenson?
Mrs. Mortenson, is that you back there?
We've been searching
all over the hospital.
Aren't you even gonna have a look
at your beautiful little girl?
Please, Mrs. Mortenson,
you can't stay in here.
(baby crying)
This is one sweet baby.
- Am I really the mother?
- Of course you're the mother.
I helped with the delivery.
Come on now.
- But what if I drop it?
(baby crying)
Oh, it's so hot,
and heavy.
- She's a normal, healthy baby.
A beauty.
Look at those eyes.
- Hell, kid wasn't half
bad-looking, I decided to keep her.
I named her Norma, after Norma Talmadge,
and Jeane after Jean Harlow.
Norma Jeane Baker.
Baker's not her father, but he's
the husband I hated the least.
(laughs)
- Oh!
Oh my goodness.
Oh!
Oh, honey, now listen.
Do you remember what I
told you, Norma Jeane,
when you're with your mother, watch out
for those changes of moods?
- I do, Grandma.
I always do what you say.
- Well if you think that
it's getting dangerous,
I want you to run to a
telephone and call me.
I will go and I will get a taxi cab
and I don't even care if it's $5,
I'm gonna come and get you.
Will you remember?
- I'll remember.
- Oh, look, look, look.
See that tough guy?
A regular Jimmy Cagney.
Now that is a movie star I really like.
A real man.
He knows when his number's up.
- What about that one?
- That one.
That one is Mary Pickford.
America's sweetheart.
- Oh Grandma, where do
they go when they fly away?
- I don't know.
China!
- Let's go to China, fly with me!
Come on!
- My crazy daughter was
unfit to be a mother.
I took Norma Jeane when
she was just a baby.
I wanted to adopt her, give
her my last name, Monroe.
But Gladys wouldn't let me.
Oh no.
- Norma Jeane, come.
- [Della] She preferred to board her out.
- Norma Jeane, my love,
come come come, come.
- [Della] Paid me $5 a week plus expenses.
- Your birthday.
I will not be deprived of
mother love on this special day.
Oh.
- Wait.
Wait.
Tell me something, what
have you been smoking?
Look at me, girl.
Are you hopped up?
- I've never even smelled
marijuana, let alone smoked it.
And that goes double for opium.
Never.
- [Della] Wait!
- Rain or shine, sickness or in health,
till death do us part, I vow.
There you go, baby.
- When will you be getting
my granddaughter back?
- Ignore your grandmother, dear,
she's silent film and we are talkies.
(upbeat jazz music)
(horn honks)
(children chattering)
My new neighborhood.
And only six minutes from the studio.
I have a surprise for you, birthday girl.
Let's go.
There's someone waiting and
he might be getting impatient.
Voila!
(panting)
(sighs)
Well let's see, where could
our special someone be?
Very cold, you're cold,
you're cold, you're cold.
Getting warmer.
Oh, come on, come on, in here.
Hmm?
Oh, Norma Jeane.
I swear, sometimes I think you're blind.
Open your eyes.
Don't you see?
No?
This man is your father.
- My father?
- Yes.
What'd you think, you didn't have one?
Oh, it's a beautiful
name, an important name,
but a name I can't utter, even
Grandma Della doesn't know.
- Where is he?
- Away.
At a great distance.
He's risked his life in
the name of democracy.
But someday, he will return
to Los Angeles to claim you.
Happy birthday, Norma Jeane.
Didn't I tell you this
would be your special day?
Oh yes, yes, I have a dress for you.
Beautiful, satin.
You'll look like a princess.
Too short?
Well, go on, try it on.
Hophead bastard of a baker.
Spelled birthday wrong.
And your name.
I told him.
(upbeat jazz music)
Norma Jeane.
You must make a wish.
A wish to make you know
who return to us soon.
Go on, go on.
(blowing)
(laughing)
There you are, good as a prayer.
Well, don't be scared.
Only gonna cut the cake.
(water running)
Shame on you.
Oh, shame, the cake!
Cake all over you.
Oh.
Do you do these things deliberately?
- No, I didn't.
- Well who did, Santa Claus?
Don't you know that I borrowed this dress
from the studio and now it's ruined?
Where do you think clothes come from?
You think they just grow on trees?
Sit, sit!
- It's kind of hot.
Mother!
- No, sit still.
Where is the soap?
Soap.
So much dirt, outside of us and in.
Hope is the thing with feathers
that perches in the soul
and sings the tune without the words,
and never stops at all.
Emily Dickinson, that's
so lovely, isn't it?
Hope is the thing with feathers
that perches in the soul.
I always wanted to be a
poet, like Emily Dickinson or
Edna St. Vincent Millay.
I have the soul of a poet.
Of course, I was an
actress once, you know.
I just trasnferred to another department.
Maybe you'll be my poet.
What's wrong with me?
I can't believe it, I almost forgot.
I have another present
for the birthday girl.
Come on.
Ta da.
Norma Jeane, do you remember who
used to sleep in this drawer?
In this very drawer, you
remember who slept here?
You.
You, Norma Jeane.
I was so poor I couldn't afford a crib.
This drawer was your crib.
(somber piano music)
Sweet dreams.
- Daddy.
Daddy.
It would be said of me that
I was unhappy as a child,
that my childhood was a desperate one,
but let me tell you, I was never unhappy.
So long as I had my mother,
I was never unhappy.
And my father, well,
I had a picture of him
forever etched in my mind.
(laughing)
- Norma Jeane?
Norma Jeane!
- Here she comes.
That old fat elephant.
Let's run.
She don't see us.
- Norma Jeane!
Norma Jeane.
(wind blowing)
(birds chirping)
- Grandma, I'm home!
Grandma?
(gasps) Grandma!
(coughing)
(Norma Jeane crying)
- I love you so much.
- It was my fault she died.
I wouldn't come when she called.
I was bad.
- Look, it was God's fault.
Now, go to bed.
I have to get up early in the morning.
(sighs)
- Mother.
Can she hear us?
Can Grandma hear us?
- I hope not.
- It was my fault.
Oh Mommy.
- Don't call me Mommy.
I just, I hate those pukey cute titles.
(crying)
Look.
Your grandma's number came up is all.
You don't go until your number's up.
That's why I'm a fatalist.
Can't argue with logic.
(coughing)
This cough.
My hands too.
The chemicals in the film
lab are stronger now.
My eyes, my lungs.
My job is killing me.
You know what you have to
do after school tomorrow?
- Walk to the movie?
- Sit at the back on the aisle.
Don't sit too close to men.
- But see, they keep sitting by me.
- You're not listening.
On the way home, walk on the
curb under the street light.
That way you'll be seen if
anybody tries to grab you.
(coughing)
Don't tell anybody about
these movie days, all right?
I have to work late.
There are tasks in developing
that only I can do.
I mustn't fail.
They would fire me, and
that would be the end.
I'm not a bad mother.
I coulda put you in an
orphanage and I didn't, did I?
- Mommy!
- Oh, damn.
(sighs)
What next?
(somber music)
- [Woman] Hello darling.
- [Man] Vera.
How did you happen to come?
- [Woman] Just passin' by.
I wanted to rub my nose against your door.
- And then the fairy princess died,
she had golden hair and it was spread out
all over her pillow.
- That was the end?
Huh.
The dark prince was long
gone by then, I suppose.
Careful, careful, careful.
- No, no, the dark prince loved her.
He was standing over her, crying.
I don't want her to die.
- That's because you understand
how important it is to stay alive.
- Easy.
(grunts)
- Be careful, boys.
Fredrick March gave me this piano
and I don't want it to get scratched.
(man chuckles)
Your father would be
so jealous if he knew.
I have plans for you.
For us.
(upbeat jazz music)
Ah, there, you see?
The home of Barbara Lamar,
the girl who's too beautiful.
That's just a joke, sweetie.
Can't be too beautiful, just
like you can't be too rich.
(chuckles)
Don't squint, darling.
You'll make yourself wear
glasses and that'll be the end.
- Look, there's a castle!
- That's where Jean Harlow used to live.
Jean, our Jean.
The one you were named after.
Look, look, look, over there.
Merna Loy.
(sighs)
Ah,
this is the most famous of all.
Falcon's Lair, home of the
late Rudolph Valentino.
The man had no talent for acting at all.
No talent for life.
But he was photogenic and
he died at the right time.
Remember, Norma Jeane,
die at the right time.
(simple piano music)
(humming)
- That tickles.
- Now don't be silly, you come
back here, finish the piece.
Now.
(humming)
(simple piano music)
(laughing)
- [Gladys] What's going on in there?
- No more lessons today.
(light jazz music)
(laughing)
- Tickle me.
- No.
No.
- Tickle me with your tongue.
- Norma Jeane, behave yourself.
(blows)
Stop that, that's disgusting.
Norma, Clive, what is this?
(blows)
- Not a thing.
What do you mean?
- Norma Jeane, you are all nerved up.
You go into your room right now.
(laughs)
Naughty, giggling little girl.
- My mother called Los
Angeles the city of sin.
She said mankind wasn't
meant to live here,
that we were being punished for
our stupidity and our pride.
- Norma Jeane, there's fire in the hills.
20 feet high.
Fields of fire.
Canyons of fire.
I heard it on the radio.
Hurry, come on.
We'll go to your father's,
we'll be safe there.
- Where?
- Earthquakes, fires,
the air smothering us.
Some of us were born here,
and some of us would die here.
It's a pact we made with the devil.
(sirens wailing)
(whistle blowing)
(men chattering)
- Where the hell do
you think you're going?
- I wanna see hell close up.
- Who's that with you?
- Well, that's Shirley Temple.
Look, I had been invited
to a private residence
at the top of Little Canyon.
The owner has a fireproof mansion,
I can't say the man's name,
but it's one that you all know.
He's in the film industry,
and this is his daughter.
- Well, I'm sorry ma'am,
you can't go up this road.
Why don't you go home, calm down,
and put your little girl to bed.
- Don't you condescend to me, Officer,
don't you tell me what to do.
- Lady, you're either drunk or doped up,
and nobody's got time for it tonight.
- Why don't you just shoot me.
(tires squealing)
- Was he here?
Father?
All this time?
Why didn't he come and see us?
- You shut up!
It isn't fair.
I'm 34 years old.
No man'll look at me anymore.
I've given my youth to the
studio for what, for you!
(knocking)
- Norma Jeane.
- Mother called the studio
to tell them she was sick.
They were mean, they told
her not to come back to work.
- Unlock the door.
- [Norma Jeane] I can't, Mr. Pierce.
She made me promise.
- How long have you been in there?
- Two days.
- I brought you some food.
I'll leave it right outside the door.
- Poison.
They're trying to poison me.
(plate clatters)
- No Mother, it was
your friend, Mr. Pierce.
- Your father gave me
$225 to get rid of you
before you were even born.
I should've listened to him.
He loved me before I got pregnant,
then after, don't call me,
don't follow me on the street.
I have to cleanse you.
- [Norma Jeane] No Mother, please!
- [Gladys] You're afflicted.
I have to make you clean.
- Mother!
- I have to.
I have to.
You're a freak.
A freak with deformity
disguised as a little girl.
(crying)
It's you.
You're the reason your father went away!
He didn't want you!
- Mr. Pierce!
(knocking)
Mr. Pierce!
(bell ringing)
(somber music)
(people chattering)
- [Man] Open up in there, come on!
(banging on door)
- Go away!
Leave me alone!
- You're coming with us now.
- Stop it!
(fire roaring)
(shouting)
There's three more.
(somber music)
(car door closes)
- Please, Norma Jeane.
- You said you were taking
me to see my mother.
- Please, Norma Jeane, be a good girl.
- This is an orphanage!
- Don't kick people, Norma Jeane.
There's nowhere else I can take you.
Your mother is sick.
The doctors say she's very sick.
She tried to hurt you, she can't be
a mother to you right now.
Forgive me, Norma Jeane.
Ow!
Norma Jeane!
Bad girl, very bad.
Don't you understand, I feel terrible,
but I can't be your mother.
God knows, I have to work,
I have no money saved.
- This is a mistake.
I have a mother.
I have a father.
He lives in a big
mansion in Beverly Hills.
- Child, save your
tears, you may need them.
- There was a fairy tale I
used to tell Norma Jeane.
I made it up myself.
Little girl who sees too much,
little girl who hears too much.
A crow comes to peck out her eyes,
a big fish comes to gobble up her ears,
a red fox bites off her nose.
See what happens, Miss?
(girls shouting)
(gasps)
- Smells like smoke.
What happened?
Where do you wear these?
Movie star clothes.
(girls laughing)
Look at me, Ginger Rogers.
Why you holding that freaky thing?
A little mouse.
Cat got your tongue?
Little orphan girl?
- I'm not an orphan.
My mother's in the hospital.
My father lives in a big
mansion in Beverly Hills.
- That's bull.
Liar.
(bell ringing)
Your mother and father are
dead, just like everybody else.
Everybody's dead.
(somber music)
(insects chirping)
- [Man] And Clara and her prince
sailed home in a magic sleigh.
- And they lived happily ever after.
The end.
(cheering and applauding)
Merry Christmas, dear children.
Now we have presents for everybody!
(girls shouting)
- [Man] This is yours.
Here you go.
- And this one's for you.
- A fairy princess and a dark prince.
- What?
- Don't you know?
Movie stars.
- Come on up stage.
Oh come on, you'll be all right.
- Hi.
- [Photographer] There you
go, that's a great one.
I gotta get one.
- Come on honey, a nice smile.
- [Photographer] Give us a big smile.
Come on sweetie, let's see it.
Oh, look at that, beautiful.
All right, hold that.
- Open your present, darling.
What is that?
- A baby tiger, mine.
Where are you, Daddy?
If I was prettier, would you come for me?
(somber music)
Someone come to take me away,
so I'll never be sad again.
You.
You could be my magic friend.
(girls chattering)
- You're a very hard worker, Norma Jeane.
You must know that cleanliness
is next to godliness.
- My mother doesn't believe in God.
- Perhaps your mother's
mind has been poisoned.
I believe that a person can surmount
any of life's challenges
through hard work and prayer.
Without drugs, without alcohol.
- I will never take drugs.
I will never, ever drink.
- I have some books you
might find interesting.
You have an inquisitive mind, Norma Jeane.
Put it to use.
(bell ringing)
- [Woman] She looks just
like our Cynthia Rose.
- Mr. And Mrs. Mount lost
their little daughter
when she was eight years old.
- Polio.
We have a picture.
- [Norma Jeane] Pretty.
- Norma Jeane, why don't you recite
one of your poems for these nice people?
Norma Jeane's become quite a poet
while she's been staying with us.
- Poet.
On top of everything else.
Oh yes, we'd love to hear.
- Where do you go when you disappear?
Wherever you are, are you alone?
You can endure any pain, if
you have a family and a home.
- Darling, we have a home for you.
A beautiful home in Pasadena.
There's a room just for you.
It's pale pink and there's
a canopy over the bed.
- Norma Jeane, would you
like to live with us?
- Yes, can I be Cynthia Rose?
(birds chirping)
- I'm sorry, Norma Jeane.
I know your mother loves you, dear,
and wants you to be happy.
But she refuses to sign
the adoption papers again.
- It isn't fair, Dr. Mittelstadt.
My mother, she's sick and she's crazy.
- Norma Jeane.
- This is the third time I had
a chance to be in a family.
I did everything you said.
I wrote to my mother, I begged her,
I prayed and prayed and prayed.
- Prayer cannot change
the science of being.
It only brings us in
better harmony with it.
- Then what good is it?
- My mother didn't know
how to be a mother to me.
But she didn't want anyone
else to be my mother,
so Dr. Mittelstadt promised
to find me a foster home.
We didn't need my mother's
permission for that.
A foster home, didn't make any difference.
Any home, any home at all.
Well, Norma Jeane, we will miss you.
- Yes, I will miss all of you.
- The Perigs are a good foster family.
You'll be going to school in Van Ives.
And if things work out
well, you'll be able
to live with them until you're 18.
Then you're on your own.
Now, there's $20.60 in your account.
As a going away gift,
I've doubled that sum.
- Thank you.
- Remember us with kindness, Norma Jeane.
(birds chirping)
(upbeat jazz music)
(door opens)
- Oh, Norma Jeane, let
me take that from you.
- Oh--
- No, honey, honey, you do
enough around here already.
Doesn't she Warren?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you always keep
your room so neat and tidy,
and look at you, you always look like
you just stepped out of the bathtub.
(Norma Jeane laughs)
Here, why don't you have a seat
and let me fix you a plate.
This is a big day for you.
- You don't have to
wait on me, Aunt Elsie.
- Did you memorize your play?
- Yeah, I worked on it
practically all night,
I'm so nervous, Aunt
Elsie, my head, my stomach.
- Do you need an aspirin?
- No, I'll be fine, I just
gotta set my mind to it.
- You always say that.
It doesn't work for me.
Maybe it's because I
only have half a mind.
(both laughing)
- What's in a name?
That which we call a
rose by any other name
would smell as sweet.
So Romeo would, were he not Romeo called,
retain that dear perfection which he owes
without that title.
Romeo, doth thy name and for thy name,
which is no part of thee, take all myself.
(sighs)
Thank you, magic friend.
Thank you.
- Next.
Who's next?
(whispering)
Norma Jeane.
- What's in a name?
A name by any other rose...
A rose by any other name
would smell as sweet,
so to...
I'm sorry, could I start again?
No, see, I think I could be
Juliet, I know, I am Juliet.
(students laughing)
- Thank you, Norma Jeane, but
I don't think the playwright
Mr. William Shakespeare
would've seen it that way.
(students laughing)
(crying)
- This all may seem important
to you now, Norma Jeane.
Someday you'll laugh about it.
- I couldn't even make
it as a cheerleader.
- That's because you're a
poet, not a cheerleader.
- Do you mean that, Mr. Herring?
- I've read your poems.
They're very good.
Good rhyming.
- I have lots of them, hundreds
of them, I love poetry.
- Well bring them in.
I'm happy to read them.
- I wanna write poetry like
Edna St. Vincent Millay,
or Robert Browning.
Oh, Mr. Herring, I wanna learn.
And my mother, she was a
film actress for the studio,
she was an understudy for Joan
Crawford and Gloria Swanson.
Well she died in an airplane
crash over the Atlantic
in 1934, and there was no
one to take me in, so--
- Life must be very
difficult for a young girl
like yourself, Norma Jeane.
- I love the way you say my name.
It makes me feel magical.
You can kiss me, but only
with your mouth closed.
Thank you, Mr. Herring, you're
the most wonderful teacher
in the whole wide world.
(light music)
(insects chirping)
This is me.
Well, just a little kiss.
Not the kind with your mouth open.
Bye.
- What is it, Warren?
- Nothing.
- Norma Jeane wasn't the
one to blame for this.
My husband was the one to blame.
And even that poor bastard
was halfway innocent.
Maybe even helpless.
Have to face it.
It's a man's world.
And to survive, a woman
must betray her own kind.
A woman has to protect herself
against a girl like Norma Jeane.
(birds chirping)
Norma Jeane, I been
thinking about something.
It's time that you got married.
- What?
- Well you know, you're
gonna be 16 in June.
And that's about the time I got married.
- But I don't have a steady boyfriend.
- You have too many boyfriends.
- But I'm not in love.
- At your age it's easy to get in love.
And say, Norma Jeane, I've been hearing
some things about you lately.
- Oh, you mean Mr. Herring, my teacher?
I'm not seeing him anymore, Aunt Elsie,
I didn't know he was married, I swear.
- With this terrible war starting
and all of our young
boys going off to fight,
you better grab yourself a husband
while there's still one
available and in one piece.
(lighter clicking)
- You're serious, you're not joking?
- Do I look like I'm joking?
Does Hitler?
- But I still have two
years of high school to go.
- Honey, you don't need
a diploma to get married.
- But I'm too young, Aunt Elsie.
I don't wanna get married.
I wanna be a nurse, with the war going on
I can help all the suffering--
- We don't have the room anymore,
my sister and her kids
are gonna come here--
- I don't need an actual room, I mean,
I could sleep on the sofa, or in the car.
Aunt Elsie, I'll do anything,
I'll work harder Aunt Elsie--
- Honey, you do work hard.
- Please don't send me back
to the home, Aunt Elsie,
I'll kill myself, I will.
- Stop it.
(Norma Jeane crying)
Crying never helps.
If it did, we'd all be a
lot better off, wouldn't we?
- Why do you want to get rid of her?
She helps you around
the house, doesn't she?
- Mm-hmm.
- She's a good kid.
- Well we certainly don't
her to end up like Lucille.
15, pregnant, that boy
just ran out on her.
- So what, you're just gonna
send her back to County?
Back to the orphanage?
- No.
I'm gonna get that little girl
married, outta here and safe.
Ba ba.
- I'm sorry, Aunt Elsie,
I'm just scared I guess.
- Oh, I understand, honey.
But you'll get over it.
Wait till you see this boy.
He's so cute.
And a hard worker.
He works at Lockheed now,
but I think after the war
he'll probably have his own business.
- I wish I could go to the
war, I wish I was a man.
- You?
You can't even watch me clean a chicken.
(laughs)
Oh, this war.
It is getting so bad in Europe.
All the young boys have enlisted now.
You wanna have babies, don't you?
- Babies?
- Time's running out.
- Well, if I had a baby, I
would never be alone, would I?
- That's right, Norma Jeane.
You'd never be alone.
This is for your own good, baby.
You have to grow up sometime.
I guess if your number's
up, Aunt Elsie, it's up.
- Yeah.
- She's a good Christian
girl and she doesn't
drink or smoke.
She reads the Bible, and
she's a born homemaker.
You have to go overseas, you're gonna need
someone to come home to.
- Mom.
Got you to come home to, right?
And write to me?
Why would I need anybody else?
- Now Bucky, you just promise me.
Just be nice.
- Okay.
- Hi Bess, how are you?
Good, good to see you.
Go ahead.
- Hi.
I'm Bucky.
- I'm Norma Jeane.
- Well, Norma Jeane,
you're the prettiest girl
I've seen outside the movies.
(laughs)
I'm beginning to believe
in love at first sight.
(Norma Jeane laughs)
(soft jazz music)
(people chattering)
(laughing)
- What did your family say when they saw
my birth certificate, father unknown?
- Don't give it another thought, honey.
No Glazer's gonna look down on somebody
for reasons that can't be helped.
I'll punch 'em in the nose if they do.
(laughs)
Thank you.
- Ooh, I think I've had enough,
I've never had champagne before.
- Oh, hey!
(Norma Jean squeals)
- [Man] Sorry.
(Bucky laughing)
Easy.
Look, I said I'm sorry.
- Oh dear.
And Bucky's sister was kind enough
to let you borrow her dress.
Just like the movies, huh?
- I just wish my mother
could've been here.
I sent her an invitation, but--
- Well, you never have
to fret about that again.
Now you have a mother-in-law.
(laughs)
- Oh, Aunt Elsie, I'm frightened.
I mean, I'm frightened about tonight.
- Oh honey, don't be frightened.
All you have to do really
is stay outta their way.
(laughs)
I wish I coulda kicked
Warren out and kept you.
- Are you happy?
Huh?
Are you happy?
- Yes, it's the happiest
day of my whole life.
Bucky, I love you, I love
you, now my life is perfect.
Daddy.
You'll never leave me, will you?
- Baby, why would I leave you?
I just married you.
- It kinda smells in
here like insect spray.
It's cruel.
The way they kill them that
way is cruel, don't you think?
- I'm only thinking of one thing.
- Wait, just let me get my nightgown.
- No, no nightgown.
I been dreaming of this.
Aww jeez, baby, I love you so much.
You're so good, and so
sweet, and so beautiful.
- You do love me, don't you Bucky?
And I'm married, and I'm never
gonna be alone again, right?
♪ Bye-O baby buns, your
daddy's gone a-hunting ♪
♪ To catch a little rabbit skin
to wrap my little baby in ♪
(humming)
- Beautiful baby, and beautiful mother.
(laughs)
What is your little girl's name?
- Arina.
Aren't you, honey?
Aren't you?
- [Woman] You must be very proud.
- Yes I am.
I mean, we both are.
- Is your husband?
- He's overseas, far away in New Guinea.
(laughs)
(light jazz music)
Hi Harriet.
We're back.
Arina and I had a lovely walk, didn't we?
Come on.
Oh, oh, aww.
We did, didn't we, we had a nice--
(baby crying)
Oh no.
Look at your mommy.
Don't cry.
You know, I'll tend to her anytime,
I mean I just love to, I do.
How's tomorrow morning?
Would that be all right?
You know what, I'll see you
tomorrow morning, Harriet.
- See, I don't know if
I'm gonna go for the Navy,
the Marines, or the Merchant Marines,
but God made the US
number one for a reason,
and we gotta uphold that responsibility.
- Well what if bombs ever
fall on this country?
I mean, what would happen to
us, what would be our fate?
- Our fate?
You use such weird words sometimes.
(laughs)
Don't worry about it.
If the Japs try to bomb the US,
we will blast them out of the sky
with the secrete missiles
that we're making at Lockheed.
You know, some of the women
whose husbands are overseas
have started working for the war effort,
and I was thinking that--
- Glazer women don't
work outside of the home.
- But it's war time, isn't that different?
- No wife of mine, ever.
- More macaroni and cheese?
We have potatoes and biscuits,
I got tapioca pudding with
bananas and whipped cream.
You liked it, didn't you Daddy?
I mean, I just wanna be the best wife
in the whole world, I do.
- No, it was delicious,
it was really good.
But you know how that
white food kinda bloats me.
- Oh, there was ketchup Daddy, that's red.
Oh, look what I made for Arina.
I made it out of a sock
and some black felt,
it's just like the one I got
for Christmas at the orphanage.
It's cute, huh? (laughs)
- You got nothing else to do around here
except for tending somebody else's kid?
- Well, I just feel sorry for them,
I mean Harriet's husband
is missing in action--
- Enough about Harriet.
- What?
- I got you, baby.
(Norma Jeane squeals)
(laughing)
- Oh, she loves it.
See, I used little black buttons for eyes.
Oh, Harriet, if I had a Arina, I would be
the happiest girl in the whole world!
I would!
(men chattering)
- Listen to this.
When you read this, Big Daddy,
think of Baby Doll and the red hot loving
she's gonna give you when
you come home tonight.
(laughing)
- Big Daddy.
- She's always leaving notes in my lunch.
She cooks and cleans and
scrubs everything all day.
She's so neat, and pretty.
She even writes me poetry.
- This is better than any poetry.
Take a look at this.
My girl.
- Not as sexy as my Norma Jeane.
I mean, if she had that kinda underwear.
(laughing)
(laughs)
- All this makeup.
- Oh, shh, come on, be a sport.
I want the guys to see
how beautiful my wife is.
Okay, smile for Daddy.
Put your arm behind your head like this.
See, that's what they call a glamour shot.
You like to look glamorous, huh?
(laughing)
(camera clicking)
- Daddy, come on, that's enough.
It's lonely here in this
big old bed by myself.
(camera clicking)
- [Bucky] That's good now.
- Daddy, I don't wanna,
it doesn't feel right,
I mean, I just, this
wig, and this makeup, I--
- No no, you likey, you likey, you like it
because it makes me hot.
Don't, it's fun, it's fun.
- No, Bucky, no, see, it's not fun.
- Come on, would you loosen up?
Guys do things like this with
their wives all the time.
There's no harm in it.
- I just, I don't like
looking like this, I mean,
it makes me not know who I am.
I thought you loved me.
- You know, sometimes I don't think
you feel much in your body.
- What?
- The way a woman is supposed to feel.
- No, Bucky, I didn't mean it, I'm just,
I'm sorry, I'm getting my period
and I have terrible cramps,
and I'll pose--
- Then take an aspirin.
- No, Bucky, wait.
- This is strictly confidential, okay?
Not to go beyond us.
- This is your wife?
Glazer, you're one lucky bastard.
- Man, if I had a wife
that looked like this,
I wouldn't be showing
her pictures to nobody.
I'd be putting her under lock and key.
- Ah, well, I don't have
to worry about that.
Norma Jeane's only got eyes for me.
(knocking)
- Harriet?
- Harriet left last night.
She packed up Arina and took off.
She said she wasn't cut out to be a widow.
(laughs)
- She wouldn't leave
without saying goodbye,
without having Arina say
goodbye, she wouldn't--
- Well she would and she did.
- She would not.
God wouldn't let her.
(insects chirping)
(somber music)
(baby crying)
(gasps)
- Norma Jeane?
Norma Jeane, you mopped
this floor yesterday.
Listen honey.
I enlisted this morning
in the Merchant Marines.
And we both knew that this was coming.
Probably be shipped out in six weeks.
I have to serve my country.
May sound corny, but that's how I feel.
- Oh Bucky.
- Dear God.
Help us mortals to understand your will.
- [Norma Jeane] Daddy.
- [Bucky] Norma Jeane, I told
you, I gotta get my sleep,
I have to report early in the morning.
- Gimme a baby.
I want a baby.
- I'll be damned, Norma
Jeane, we went through this.
World War II is no time to start a family.
- [Norma Jeane] Don't
leave me Daddy, please,
if you leave me I'll die.
- [Bucky] Calm down, you're not gonna die.
- [Norma Jeane] I want a baby.
- Norma Jeane.
Norma Jeane, stop it.
Just stop it, you're smothering me.
- Oh Daddy.
- Look, cooking and
cleaning and making out
like I'm God or something,
I don't wanna be God.
Just get off of me, you sad sick cow!
(crying)
Norma Jeane, what the hell?
- No.
Oh Daddy.
You love me, don't you?
Don't you Daddy?
- Sure I do.
Sure I love you, baby, come on.
I married you, didn't I?
- I love you.
I love you so much.
Don't leave me.
(crying)
(somber music)
- Goodbye Norma Jeane.
She was a sweet kid, but so emotional.
She was wanting love all the time.
She was immature and unreliable.
But I guess so was I.
We were too young.
If she would've been a better cook
and not so emotional, it might've worked.
- If he loved me, he
wouldn't have left me.
If he left me, he didn't love me.
I was 18, no longer a ward of LA County,
for the first time in my life, I was free.
Not an orphan or a foster child,
not a daughter or a
daughter-in-law, not a wife.
Because of the war, I was free.
My life would now begin.
I was nobody's daughter.
(upbeat jazz music)
- Norma Jeane.
This stuff'll penetrate your brain.
Maybe you better get some fresh air.
- I don't get tired.
I mean, I don't have time, I
wouldn't want to lose my job.
(laughing)
Sorry, I'm just a little dizzy.
Gosh. (laughs)
- I notice your wedding rings.
- Oh, yeah, my husband's
lost in action in New Guinea.
- I'm sorry.
Must be lonely.
You live alone?
- Oh, a furnished room in
Burbank, but I love it.
Not so much housework for just one person.
- Maybe some night we could have dinner.
- Oh, well, I wouldn't feel right
until I know where my husband is.
(laughs)
- Hold it.
(camera clicks)
Beautiful.
- Oh no, I can't, please, I can't.
- Come on, it's for the boys overseas,
the stars and stripes.
Don't want our boys to despair, do you?
That's tantamount to treason.
(laughs)
- Well, can't you use somebody else?
- Not since I found you.
Come over here.
Come on.
Yeah, stand there, baby.
Yeah, like that.
- Wait, I don't... (laughs)
- That's good.
That's what the boys want from me.
T and A.
Baby, you've got 'em.
(camera clicks)
This is just the beginning.
We're gonna make beautiful music together.
(upbeat jazz music)
(camera clicking)
(laughs)
She was my sweet little oaky cash cow.
Sweet, but goofy.
Interested in all my books about Marxism
and the meaning of life.
She was trying to read Schopenhauer, even.
I plucked her out of oblivion.
A Van Ives hick with ambition.
(men chattering)
- Son of a, that's my wife.
Hey, this is my wife.
- How do we really know this is your wife?
(men whooping and chattering)
- She wasn't wearing a brassiere.
Probably no underpants either.
Showing everything she had like a whore.
Sure I was damned angry, I still am.
Shamed my family's name.
No Glazer's ever been divorced.
No Glazers' wives ever ran off.
(goat bleats)
- Otto, you like me, don't you?
I mean like a girlfriend, or?
- I don't wanna hurt you, Norma Jeane.
Come on, don't play dumber than you are.
That look, what you just did.
Gotta learn about lighting.
You're not always gonna have me around.
(camera clicking)
(light jazz music)
- Don't make me into a joke, Otto.
- You're already a joke.
The female body is a joke.
All this fecundity, this beauty.
The aim is to drive men wild to copulate
and reproduce the species,
and what's the species?
99% of humankind doesn't deserve to live.
Take it off.
Nobody's here.
- Are you crazy?
Never.
- You holding out for a film career?
Sooner or later, baby,
you'll come back to me.
- Maybe so.
But not in my birthday suit.
(camera clicks)
- Hi!
How are ya?
(people chattering)
- There he is.
- He looks like Rumpelstiltskin.
- Isaac.
This is Norma Jeane Baker,
Mr. IE Shinn, your new agent.
- I appreciate this.
- Sit, sit.
Get rid of the curls, your
hair should be lighter,
and your eyebrows are too thin.
And you have to learn how to walk,
how to carry yourself, how to breathe.
(laughs)
- Well maybe I should go
back to spraying airplanes.
(laughing)
- No, you're gonna have
a career, I guarantee it.
Now, every decade, there has
to be a glamour girl, a star,
I think that would be the
role for you, my dear.
- Oh, Mr. Shinn, that isn't who I am.
- You just do what I say
and I'm gonna get you
the contract with the studio.
- Studio?
My mother worked for the studio,
she was responsible for
some wonderful films.
- Really?
Where's your mother now, dear?
- Oh, she died.
(laughs)
(crow cawing)
Mother?
Oh Mother.
Mother.
I didn't know what to do, I didn't know
if you wanted to see me, you
never answered my letters.
It's been so long.
I'm sorry I haven't...
I don't know where to
begin, I've been modeling.
I brought you some of
my pictures to show you.
This one is me as Miss
Aluminum Products 1945.
And this is me as Miss Paper
Products, I like this one.
And here's me as Miss
California Dairy. (laughs)
It's kinda, but this one
was in Good Housekeeping.
Oh Mother, this past year,
it's been so exciting,
I've been modeling, I'm under contract
at the studio where you used to work.
It's just been so exciting.
And wonderful.
- I don't know you, who are you?
(somber music)
- Hold it, I love it.
- No, Otto, not now.
- Come on, I was born for this,
breasts jiggling, tears running.
- Do you hear me, Otto?
I said stop, I said stop.
(camera clicking)
I'm leaving all this behind, Otto.
I'm going to invent myself.
A new self.
And I'm never gonna look back again.
(upbeat jazz music)
- [Man] All right, let's go.
Come on, bring it.
I got it.
(whistling)
(typewriter clacking)
(typewriter dings)
- Hello.
I'm Norma Jeane Baker,
I have an appointment
to see Mr. R.
- What was the name again?
- Norma Jeane Baker?
I have an appointment, to see
Mr. R, before my audition.
- [Mr. R] Come inside and close the door.
- Oh! (laughs)
- You think this is a Marx brothers movie?
- No, I...
- You like my aviary.
- Oh, they're all dead.
(birds chirping)
- Taxidermy is the most
restful of my hobbies.
Someday I might show you my
laboratory, in the desert.
(laughs)
- Well, I'm just glad there
aren't any hummingbirds,
I mean, they're so
helpless and tiny. (laughs)
- Come on.
Let's drop the goo goo routine.
You can't be as dumb as you look.
Get down, blondie.
Good girl.
- I take it your interview
with Mr. R is over?
- Yes.
You wouldn't happen to have an aspirin
or anything, would you?
- I have some codine.
One or two?
- Two.
Thank you.
I don't usually take painkillers,
but I just got my period
and I have to audition, so.
- You might need these for later.
- Thank you.
I wonder.
(laughs)
I wouldn't happen to
have a stain on my skirt
or anything, would I?
- No.
I don't see any stain.
- Hello.
I'm here to read for
Scudda Hoo, Scudda Hay.
June Haver's girlfriend.
It's just a few lines.
- You won't have to audition.
- Well, I know I'm late, but I mean,
it's only 20 minutes, and I had a meeting.
- You have the part.
- You mean I'm cast?
- If your name is Norma Jeane Baker?
(laughs)
- Yes, but I don't...
- You're in.
Here's a script, and you'll report here
at seven a.m. tomorrow.
- You mean I'm in the
movie, I'm cast, I'm in.
- Mr. R was impressed.
And your agent is waiting
for you in his office.
(laughs)
- Thank you, thank you.
- Norma Jeane is a hick name.
It's an oaky name.
It has no glamour or allure.
- Well, actually, I--
- My assistant put some
names together here.
Myra, Mona, Mina, Marilyn, Mavis.
I want the Mmm mmm sound.
Last name will be Miller.
- Well, I'd like to retain Norma at least,
I mean, that is my real name, so.
- Mira Miller, Mina
Miller, Marilyn Miller.
- Already a Marilyn Miller on Broadway.
(spits)
- Damn.
- Norma Miller?
My grandmother's last name was Monroe.
- Marilyn.
- Marilyn Monroe!
It's sexy!
(laughing)
- That's your new name.
- Well, now you're a true starlet.
(laughing)
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
(somber music)
- Marilyn Monroe.
My name.
My name is Marilyn Monroe.
I couldn't be sold any other way, I guess.
And I saw that I must be sold.
For then I would be desired.
Then I would be loved.
- So.
The studio dropped you.
- My scene.
They edited my scene down to second, so.
- I knew you'd be back.
Here you go.
Standard release form.
- How much?
- 50 bucks.
- Only 50?
- The only offer we've got is
from Ace Hollywood Calendars.
Take it or leave it.
(somber music)
Shinn's supposed to be working for you.
He's your agent.
What does he say?
- Well he's hoping to get
me cast in a serious role,
like Olivia De Havilland in Snake Pit,
but until then, my car got
repossessed this morning.
- I'm using the crushed
velvet for a candy box effect.
You're a piece of candy.
- Otto.
Can I use the bathroom?
- No, the toilet's broken.
- Well, I just want to wash my--
- No.
Now let's get started, Miss Golden Dreams.
(laughs)
- Wait, is that what I'm supposed to be?
- Shoes, you're wearing shoes?
- Oh.
Because the floor's dirty.
- Don't be stupid.
You ever see a nude in shoes?
Come on baby, everything off.
- Otto, can you promise
me not to photograph
the bottoms, I mean, the soles of my feet?
Promise me, okay, please.
- I'm trying to concentrate,
you're getting on my nerves.
- It's just, I've never
posed naked before.
- Not naked, sweetheart, nude.
Not smut, art.
There's a crucial distinction.
- Like photographer not
pornographer. (laughs)
Otto, don't make me into a joke, okay?
Please.
- I believe that she could see herself
through the camera eye.
It was more powerful, more totally sexual
than any human connection.
Her problem wasn't that
she was a dumb blonde,
it's that she wasn't a
blonde and she wasn't dumb.
- I'm still there.
- Norma Jeane, sweetheart.
I want you to meet a friend of mine.
Old comrade from the trenches,
Cass Chaplin, son of Charlie.
- Hello Norma.
- I know your eyes.
My mother had a City Lights poster
of Charlie Chaplin when
I was a little girl.
- We know each other, Norma.
We've always known each other.
You have to be a Gemini.
- June 1st, 1926.
- I know.
We're twins.
(laughs)
I saw in her not the tramp, the slut,
the joke who was Marilyn Monroe,
but the eager, hopeful young
girl who was Norma Jeane.
Why did we love each other?
Maybe because both our
fathers had disowned us.
The bastards.
I'd love her like a brother,
as a twin, with my soul.
(people chattering)
- Hi, hi.
This is Marilyn.
- Monroe, Marilyn Monroe.
- I've read Asphalt
Jungle, the entire script.
It's a strange and disturbing story,
like a novel by Dostoevsky,
where you feel sympathy
for the killers and you don't
want to see them punished.
- So you've read
Dostoevsky, have you honey?
Well, let's see what you can do.
After all, you're the
first one to have read
the whole script.
(man laughs)
- When you first see Angela, she's asleep,
so that's how I've been rehearsing.
Oh.
I must have been asleep.
What's the big idea standing
there staring at me, Uncle Lon?
- [Man] Don't call me Uncle Lon.
- [Marilyn] I thought you liked it.
- [Man] Maybe I did, but I don't anymore.
- I had the market send over
some smoked mackerel for you.
I know how you love it for breakfast.
- Some sweet kid.
It's late, why don't you go to bed.
- Thank you, Miss Monroe.
Very good.
- It was pretty bad, wasn't it?
Sexy blonde, nice looking girl.
Like Lana Turner.
But too intense.
Can't act.
- Sweet Mary.
Will you look at the
ass on that little girl.
- Do you hear it?
Cass, wake up, there are voices again.
- Oh, it's all in your head, Norma,
you're exhausted, you need sleep.
- I can't sleep!
The director hates me,
he said I got the part
by walking away.
I'm not an idiot, I know what that means.
- Norma, let the bastard
lead you through your scenes.
That's what films are.
Not real acting, not theater.
Why work so hard?
God, you're sweating like a horse.
Why does this mean so much?
- 'Cause I don't wanna die.
- What?
- If I fail, if they
fire me, I'd wanna die.
- You're not gonna die.
You work too hard to die.
(sighs)
- If only we could live in a
little stucco house in Venice.
(laughs)
- Remember, I like to keep
my clothes in a suitcase.
- I know, but this'd be different
because we'd have a baby,
and he'd have dark hair and
beautiful eyes, a prince baby.
Charlie Chaplin's grandson.
What would Grandma Della say?
She loved the Little Tramp.
- The Tramp despised
children, especially his own.
You're lucky, Norma, you
never met your father.
- I'd like to know who he is.
Shake his hand, say hello, goodbye.
(groans)
Can't sleep, Cass.
(sighs)
I'm gonna ruin everything,
they're gonna replace me.
(pills rattling)
- A little potion, darling.
To help you, to help us both sleep.
- What is it?
- A little magic.
Sleep is the sweetest state.
You're dead, yet alive, exquisite!
- I don't believe in barbiturates.
I believe the mind can control everything.
- Well try it, you'll see
what happens tomorrow.
- No.
- Open your mouth.
You'll sleep like a baby, I promise.
(gentle music)
- [Man] Roll camera.
- I had the market send some
smoked mackerel for you.
I know how you love it for breakfast.
- [Man] Some sweet kid.
- She was fascinating to watch.
Like a mental patient, almost.
Not acting, no technique.
It was all there from the beginning.
Her genius, you could say.
Her madness.
- White suits you, dear, it really does.
White suits you so well.
You'll wear that one to the screening.
And we have some suits
over here, and some shoes.
(laughs)
- Mr. Shinn, it's all too much.
- Well, it's an investment
in Marilyn Monroe.
You know, when The Asphalt
Jungle is released,
Miss Monroe is gonna
be a very hot property.
I have faith, even if you don't.
- Oh, I do, but, I do have faith,
enough to move mountains, it's just that,
well, Otto said I'm photogenic,
but it's just a trick.
- Stay away from Otto.
Pornographer.
I hope you've put him behind you.
- Oh yes I have.
- Otto, Cass Chaplin, you should stay away
from people like that.
- But I love Cass, I hope
he'll marry me someday soon.
- Do you know he's a drunk?
He's a loser, a jinx.
- Mr. Shinn.
- He owes money all over town.
He leeches onto women.
I don't want you to be
seen in public with him.
- Well then I won't be
needing the dress, Mr. Shinn,
because I won't be going to the premiere.
- Oh yes you will!
The studio expects Marilyn,
and Marilyn is gonna be there.
You signed a contract to
fulfill publicity requirements.
You see, I invented you,
and I understand you,
and I'm the one who has your
best interests at heart.
- You didn't invent me.
I invented myself.
- Oh, don't get metaphysical on me.
Marilyn is a knockout,
and Marilyn has talent.
She just has to be, she doesn't
need to understand or think.
Trust me on that.
Pick you up for the
screening, seven sharp.
You're gonna look dynamite in that dress.
- Thank you, Daddy.
(upbeat jazz music)
(people chattering)
- Marilyn, you look fantastic.
- Look, there's someone
I'd like you to meet.
- I need to find Cass.
- Clark Gable.
- Ms. Monroe, you were radiant.
- Oh my goodness.
I've dreamed of--
- Don't be shy, dear.
- My Gable, when I was a little girl,
my mother had a photo of a
man, he looked just like you.
I think maybe we're related?
- I don't--
- Gladys Mortenson, she
worked at the studio,
developing film, you must remember.
- I'm sorry, I don't
think I know your mother.
Excuse me.
- But...
- What was that?
- He looked like a photo of my father.
Where's Cass, I need to find Cass,
he promised me he'd be here, I wonder
if something's happened to him.
- Marilyn, this isn't the time
to be thinking about Cass.
This is your time.
This is a victory.
You've shown them all.
You heard what he said,
didn't you, Clark Gable?
He said you were radiant.
So, be radiant.
The studio's gonna take you back.
I'm gonna get you $500 a
week this time. (chuckles)
And this is just the beginning, dear.
Just the beginning.
Hey, Freddy.
Come over here.
I want you to meet Marilyn Monroe.
- Hi.
(tinkling music)
(upbeat jazz music)
- Could you wait for me a minute?
I'm not sure if anybody's home.
Thank you.
(knocking)
Cass?
(insects chirping)
Baby?
(laughing)
- Norma, darling.
Wait, don't run away.
I want you to meet Eddie
G, he's my twin too,
and Myra, say hello to Myra.
- Could you take me home, please?
Just take me home.
(crying)
(retching)
- Okay, okay, I think
I've got the solution.
You need a man to feel
safe, to feel loved,
to feel like a real person,
and I want to marry you.
- Oh, Mr. Shinn.
- First of all, call me
Isaac, and just hear me out.
I'm gonna draw up a prenuptial agreement
leaving you virtually my
entire estate when I die.
I'm gonna cut everybody else
out and I am worth millions.
Does that make you feel safe enough?
- Mr. Shinn, I mean, Isaac, I,
why,
I don't wanna be the one to, you know,
hurt your family, or take
money from your children.
- They don't give a damn about me.
- I'm not in love with you that way.
- Sweetheart, I know you
don't love me in that way,
but there are other ways.
So long as you respect me.
- Oh, Mr. Shinn, yes, I do.
- And you trust me.
- Yes, I do.
- And you know I have your
best interests at heart,
that's a good foundation for a marriage,
along with the prenuptial agreement.
- No, see, I could only marry
for love, not for money.
No.
I'm sorry, I just,
I love you, but I'm not in love with you.
Please forgive me.
- Max Leary wants to see you tomorrow.
He wants to discuss a role
for you in his new picture.
- Mr. Shinn.
Isaac.
(light jazz music)
(knocking)
- Marilyn.
Hello.
(snaps fingers)
Daydreaming, honey?
- No.
- So.
You think we can work together, hmm?
- Yes I do.
I do.
- I saw you in Asphalt Jungle.
I was impressed.
I'm not forcing you, am I baby?
- No. (laughs)
- You're free to leave at any time.
- It wasn't me, all those times.
It was my destiny.
Like a comet, veering toward Earth.
In the gravitational
pull, you can't resist,
you try, but you can't.
So you're afraid that if you
resist, you won't be loved,
or wanted, or given a chance.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
- Sweetheart?
We got the part.
You awake, kid?
I'm telling you, you got the female lead.
Max Leary asked for you, we got the part.
- Oh, that's good news.
- Good news, it's terrific news.
So is somebody there with you?
You don't sound very happy.
- Oh no, I am, I am happy.
- You don't sound happy, Norma Jeane.
I'd like to know why the hell not.
I bust my ass at the
studio talking you up,
and you're, oh yes, unhappy.
Look, I know the part
doesn't make much sense,
but it's your first starring role!
Marilyn is on her way!
(people chattering)
(bell ringing)
- You need to push yourself, baby.
- [Man] All right, here we go, folks.
Roll camera.
Mark it.
- Okay, let's go.
Action.
- You aren't going to run
out on me, are you Georgie?
- [George] Hey baby, what
are you talking about?
- You love me, I know you
love me, I can feel it,
in my skin and in my bones.
- That cunning little bitch Marilyn Monroe
stole every scene we were in together.
Every scene.
It was like my guts were
being sucked out of me.
- I'm sorry, could I just
talk to you for a moment?
- Cut.
- Either she can't act at all,
or she's acting all the time.
Her entire life's an act.
(bell ringing)
- I know what Fawn would say,
and these aren't Fawn's words.
Well, I'd like to rewrite the scene,
just a few lines, just a little.
- What if every actress
wants to alter lines?
- I'm not every actress.
- You're too intense, Marilyn.
You're going to wear yourself out.
- Look, in real life, Fawn
would be used and beaten
and shared by men, she'd be drinking
and taking drugs and then she'd be dead.
- She's a character in a movie.
What's wrong with you?
- No!
No, she's real.
She's inside me, I know her.
- Are you on pain killers?
- No, I'm just trying to tell you
that I don't want Fawn to die.
- You don't have to
think about this stuff.
You only have to be Marilyn.
Nobody wants to listen
to this tortured crap
out of your mouth.
Trust me on this, sweetheart.
- I'm gonna play Fawn my
way because I know her.
(somber music)
- Miss Monroe.
I think I saw your picture
in a magazine the other day.
- Oh, maybe.
- I loved you in All About Eve.
You played a good part.
- Thank you.
Is my mother--
- In there.
- I'll give this to you, some money
for some things she might need.
Mother.
Here you are.
- You smell.
- It's the chemical bleach
they use on my hair,
mixed with Chanel perfume.
I thought you might enjoy...
I've been working as an actress, Mother.
Serious, demanding work.
Of course, I don't own the dress,
the studio provided it
for the photo shoot.
But I know it doesn't look much like me,
they say Marilyn is very photogenic.
- Huh.
Does her father know?
- My father?
Know what?
- About this Marilyn.
- Well, he wouldn't know
my professional name,
I guess, how could he?
Mother, if you told me his name,
I could send him this magazine,
I could call him up sometime,
if he's still living in Hollywood?
Mother, it would mean so
much to me to know who he is.
To know him.
I wouldn't bother him, I promise.
- No.
- Mother please, please.
(somber music)
- [Man] Stop.
You don't wanna do that.
Give it to me.
- [Man] Cut.
Print it.
(phone ringing)
- Hello.
- You never told me you
did something like this,
Miss Golden Dreams.
- Isaac?
- Right here in front of me.
It's on the front page along
with US casualties in Korea.
You're right next to a
picture of the Rosenbergs
being sentenced to death!
It's in the Hollywood
Reporter and Variety!
I mean, when did you do this, 1949?
You were under contract!
Ooh, dope.
- I don't know what you're talking about,
Miss Golden Dreams?
What does that mean?
- It means soft-core porn
with that creep Otto!
Don't you see, the studio
can suspend you for this,
and it's at the worst possible time.
They're considering you for a new film
opposite Joseph Cotton, Niagara.
Marilyn was mine too, you dumb broad!
Marilyn was mine, Marilyn was beautiful,
and you had no right to despoil her.
- Isaac.
(phone clicks, dial tone beeping)
Hello?
It's like I'm a commie, I guess.
All the papers after me.
- This one here.
Miss Golden Dreams?
- I'm not a criminal.
I posed nude once in my entire
life because I was desperate.
$50.
It's just a silly picture.
- Didn't you sign an agreement
stipulating that behavior
contrary to morals of
the Hollywood community
would result in suspension
of your contract
or even termination?
(light jazz music)
- Did you ever see photos
of the Nazi death camps?
Or Hiroshima?
Piles of corpses like
lumber, babies, children.
That's something to be upset
about, that's pornography,
not some (laughs) sad, dumb
broad desperate for 50 bucks.
- I wanted to punish
her for being a tramp,
and for bleeding on my
beautiful white fur carpet.
But I couldn't get rid of
her because I was afraid
she'd be hired by a competitor.
We ended up forgiving her for the calendar
and raised her salary
to 1000 bucks a week.
We couldn't invent another blonde.
One that could make so
much money so cheap.
(phone ringing)
- Isaac?
- [Betty] No, this is Betty,
Mr. Shinn's secretary.
- Betty?
- [Betty] Norma Jeane.
Are you sitting down?
- What?
- [Betty] Mr. Shinn, he's dead.
His heart.
- What?
(somber music)
It was me.
It was my fault.
Oh Betty, he died over nothing. (crying)
Oh god.
(phone clatters)
(retching)
(crying)
(upbeat jazz music)
Mr. Shinn was my friend.
Maybe my only real friend.
- Well, that's the first thing
you have to learn about Hollywood.
Your agent is never your friend.
It's the business we're in.
Acting is the only profession I know.
- There's our girl.
Woohoo.
- What's this, no more fraternizing.
- With all the bucks I'm
investing in this movie,
do I get to boogie with the star?
(laughing)
- Joseph Cotton is
really the star, Mister.
- Well dang, I don't wanna dance with him.
I just wanna see if these things are real.
- Trust me, they're real.
- We're gonna have to (mumbling).
- You're not being very friendly.
- I'm sorry.
- Come on, let's party.
(gasps)
- You don't belong with people
who don't love you, Norma.
- Oh Cass, I've missed you.
- Come with us.
(upbeat jazz music)
Oh, this is great.
Here we are.
- [Norma Jeane] Let me out,
let me out, let me out!
Let me out!
- Oh, the sea air.
- Where did you guys get
this car, it's so great!
- We borrowed it?
- We borrow everything.
- Come, come, come, come, come, come.
- [Cass] Whoa, watch your step, baby.
(Norma Jeane screams)
(laughing)
- You saved me, I'm free, I'm free!
- Oh.
- Wait.
- It's okay.
(light music)
(light jazz music)
(bell ringing)
(people chattering)
- Oh, the lights, the set.
Ah.
Have you seen Miss Monroe?
- She's over there.
- It is time to celebrate,
Miss Golden Dreams.
- [Norma Jeane] Oh, oh, pretty.
- Look at us.
Aren't we beautiful?
- Yes.
The mirror, my magic friend.
- Mine too.
You know, I set up one to watch
my self even on the toilet.
(laughing)
- That's it, Miss Monroe.
I'll tell them you're ready.
- Could you put these in water?
And also don't forget to
take some of those cookies
for your mom, I don't
need cookies. (laughs)
So they want me to wear
flesh-colored underwear
in this next scene, but I'm gonna go nude.
They want me to be a slut, I'll be a slut.
- That's right.
The human body is meant to be seen,
not hidden away like some
ugly festering wound.
- Unless of course it is
an ugly festering wound.
Then it should be hidden.
(laughing)
- Well here's to us.
Ooh.
- Ooh.
- Action.
Cut.
Rose honey, I love it, but we'll never
get it past the censor.
- Oh, but the sheet covers everything.
- Not really, it's
obvious what you're doing.
- No, see, this is important.
Rose is mocking her husband, I mean,
he's impotent, he can't do anything.
God, this role, it's so
underwritten and unconvincing.
I wanna write some lines.
Came to me last night.
Rose had a baby and the baby died.
Rose is a woman with a secret.
See, that's why I'm playing her this way,
I can remember how it happened.
- What?
How what happened?
- This baby.
Rose shut it in a bureau
drawer and suffocated.
She was making love with a man and they
didn't hear the baby crying in the drawer.
And when they finished the baby was dead.
- How the hell do you know that?
- Hey.
I know.
I used to know Rose.
(upbeat jazz music)
(people chattering)
Do you remember the day you
invited me to see your aviary?
I was just a girl then, I was so scared.
- I don't have an aviary.
- What about the white fur rug?
I got blood on your white
fur rug and you yelled at me.
(laughing)
- Afraid I do not, Miss Monroe,
I have no white fur rug.
Excuse me.
- Marilyn, as your agent,
I have a word of advice.
Just smile, don't make trouble.
Don't sabotage yourself.
Another thing,
don't ever mention that your
mother is in a mental hospital.
Niagara's gonna make a bundle.
Everybody's gonna be talking
about Marilyn Monroe.
- The number one sex
symbol of the 20th century.
What a laugh.
She wasn't even good at making love.
Basically she never knew how.
Oh sure, her body was this gorgeous thing.
She'd stare at it in the mirror.
But she never knew how to operate it.
Neither did anybody else.
Norma darling, you are a star, and this
is where a star should live.
(Norma Jeane squeals)
(laughing)
- Oh my god, it's beautiful.
I mean, I don't know how
I'm gonna pay for it,
'cause I had to throw in
the money for the lease,
but it's beautiful!
- No no no, don't worry.
(laughing)
We'll help you.
- Absolutely, when we got a job.
But you know what we need
is some decent furniture.
Dining room table.
- We'll cook, we'll entertain.
The beautiful parties, black tie.
- [Marilyn] And it'll be like
a home, a real home, and--
- That's right, my love, a haven.
I'll even unpack my suitcase.
- I won't be alone?
Hmm.
- Norma, I wanna show you something.
It's better at night than in day.
- Oh.
(insects chirping)
You know, I read that the
universe is billions of years old,
and it began in a single
explosion from a tiny particle.
The fact of a star is it burns out.
Celestial stars or human.
(chuckles)
- I'll drink to that.
(laughs)
(glass shatters)
Oh, god.
(laughing)
Blood vow.
Come here.
We're the Gemini, the three of us.
Like the twins, only there's three.
- Mm-hmm.
- Always love one another.
- In sickness and in health.
(laughs)
- Till death do we part.
(laughing)
- Well, Mrs. Perig, you're
about five weeks pregnant.
The baby will arrive in mid-April.
- What?
- It'll be all right.
You're in excellent health.
- Oh no, I'm happy, I'm so happy.
I want this baby.
My husband and I, we've
been trying for years.
This is wonderful.
(light jazz music)
(sighs)
- Norma, dear, what is
it, you look fraught.
- Well,
I don't know which one,
so I guess you're both
about to become fathers.
- Oh.
Norma.
You think you are?
- Yes.
Well, I mean, it's what
I've always wanted,
you're happy for me, aren't you?
- Yes, of course.
- It's wonderful.
It's just that Cass and I
aren't working, and a baby.
- Well no, see, I got it all figured out,
I'm gonna postpone my next film,
and I can make money being
photographed for magazines,
and well, I won't show
for three or four months,
and I'm gonna let my hair grow
out, I'm gonna be natural.
(laughs)
- Waiter, I think we need a couple
of bottles of wine over here.
- We're celebrating.
(laughing)
- It's good, the wakeup call, you know?
I'm gonna join AA.
- You're right, this is the
time to go on the wagon.
We're not getting any
younger, or any healthier.
- We need a house.
We need a big house, with
land, and trees and a view.
- Where will you get
the money for a house?
- You're in our hands now, my darling.
Leave it to us.
- We should take out insurance,
in case one of us dies,
that way we know the
baby will taken care of.
- I don't wanna talk about dying.
Oh, look!
(sighs)
Little tiger.
I had one like him once at the orphanage.
(glass shatters)
(Norma Jeane squeals)
(Norma Jeane laughs)
- Baby's first play thing.
Cute.
That was Norma Jeane
Baker, when we knew her.
When we were the Gemini.
Before she betrayed us.
Or maybe we betrayed her.
A long time ago.
- You can't turn it down.
Will you listen to me, please?
- I'm sorry, yes, what?
- You've never done musical comedy before.
This is a fantastic opportunity.
And the deal is--
- Musical comedy?
I can't dance and I can't sing.
- Very funny.
You're the next Carol Lombard.
You've been taking lessons, everybody says
you're very promising, a natural talent.
- I can't, I'm sorry, not
now, my personal life,
you know, I'm not just
some thing in the movies.
- [Agent] Marilyn, what,
I didn't quite hear.
- How much would I get?
- Contract salary.
$1500 a week, the
estimate around 12 weeks.
- Mm-hmm.
How much would Jane Russell get?
- The deal is pending,
figures aren't finalized.
- [Marilyn] How much?
- Well they're asking $100,000.
(laughing)
- And I'm the blonde.
I'm going to hang up now, goodbye.
- [Agent] Marilyn, wait--
- Screw Marilyn, she isn't here.
(phone hangs up)
- I bought it for her, the
the role of Laura Liley.
I didn't want Carol Channing
from the Broadway production.
I wanted it as a showcase
for Marilyn Monroe.
Since Niagara she was our
highest grossing actress,
although in my estimation
she was still a tramp.
- When you had me, Mother,
you weren't married, I guess,
you didn't have a man supporting you.
Yet you had a baby.
Oh, you were so brave, Mother.
To have me.
I mean to not get rid of me.
- You're so old.
Your hair is white.
(laughs)
- Oh Mother.
It's preposterous, isn't it?
How can I do this?
A baby and no husband?
I shoulda married Mr. Shinn.
You wanna know something funny?
He didn't leave me anything, not a penny.
He just made me a slave to
the studio for seven years.
You know how much money I have?
$18.
$18 and I'm supposed to be a movie star.
I love Cass.
But I'm not sure I can trust him.
Eddie G either.
Maybe they want me to die in childbirth
and collect the insurance.
They're just little boys.
Children.
Expensive children.
- Your mother's been doing so well.
But there are lapses.
Paranoid schizophrenia
is a mystery illness.
It reminds me of multiple
sclerosis, a syndrome of symptoms.
- Is it inherited?
- Well, it has been
noticed, in some families,
a certain tendency.
- My father was normal, very normal.
He died in Spain in 1936.
Actually, he was killed in the war.
- Slugger.
What do you say?
What, you just fly in?
- Yeah.
- Hey, tell Gino who's here,
tell him to put some steaks on.
- [Waiter] Yes sir.
- Listen, this blonde, Marilyn Monroe?
- [Man] So?
What about her?
- I'd like to date her.
- Her?
This broad's a tramp.
She's been a tramp from the get-go.
She's a bottle blonde, a cow.
She don't wear underwear.
She pals around with Jews
and lives with two junkies.
She's serviced every guy in
town, and more outta town.
Little girl can't get enough.
- I just wanna date her.
Make the arrangements.
(cha cha music)
- I'm not merchandise.
My illustrious agent says
this guy wants to date me,
and you know what that means.
- He's famous, must be rich.
I think Rin-Tin-Tin's
right, you should meet him.
- Yeah, she could play hard to get.
- Or hard to get into.
Great role for Marilyn.
- I'm not gonna meet him, I
hate baseball and I'm pregnant.
Cass, I thought you said you
weren't gonna drink anymore.
- Well you're so healthy
and sane about all this
that one of the Gemini has to crack up.
I don't mind if the direction is me.
- You serious, Cass?
I can't support everybody.
- She's right, Cass, you know
we should draw up our wills
and our insurance promises.
- That's a terrific idea, Eddie.
Yeah, I worry about the kid sometimes.
You know, the San Andreas fault.
- You know, you guys, you
aren't listening to me.
We don't have any money.
All you do is sit around
here all day drinking,
and I don't know what
to do, Cass, I don't,
I don't know what to do.
- You're no fun anymore, Norma.
Why don't you just relax and join us?
I think little mama
needs a tequila, Eddie G.
(laughs)
(laughing)
- I don't know what else to do.
I can't count on them
for anything, I'm alone.
- All right, now,
Marilyn, what I'm gonna do
is turn you over to my assistant Yvette.
You know Yvette.
She'll help you, okay?
(crying)
- Don't worry, Marilyn,
it's all taken care of.
It's a clinic, nothing
backstreet or dangerous.
- I've changed my mind.
- You won't feel a thing.
- No, I've changed my mind.
- I have arranged everything.
You have a new apartment,
we'll take you there after.
You never have to see
those degenerates again.
- My mind is my own to change.
It is.
- [Nurse] It's all right.
- Wait.
Please, this is a mistake,
I don't want to do this,
please don't, I made a mistake.
- It's all right, dear, it's all right.
- Just please, I don't
wanna do this, I don't.
- [Doctor] Don't worry, my
dear, you're in good hands.
- I don't wanna do this, no,
this is a mistake, please.
- Don't worry about me.
I've got a golf date
with Bing Crosby later.
- Please don't look at me.
Don't take my picture,
don't take my picture.
- Don't struggle, please.
There will be minimal pain,
and then this injection will
produce a light twilight sleep.
You don't understand, this is a mistake.
This isn't me.
(gentle music)
- Wait!
- Come back here.
(baby crying)
(screaming)
(somber music)
- Miss Monroe, they're waiting for you.
- Okay.
- The codine will help with the pain,
and the benzodrine will
give you quick energy.
- Nembutol?
- Sound sleep.
Dreamless sleep.
Think of me as your
closest friend, Marilyn.
Anything you need, call Dr. Bob.
(upbeat jazz music)
♪ I've heard of affairs
that are strictly platonic ♪
♪ But diamonds are a girl's best friend ♪
♪ And I think affairs that
you must keep masonic ♪
♪ Are better bets if little
pets get big bagettes ♪
♪ Time rolls on ♪
♪ And youth is gone ♪
♪ And you can't straighten
up when you bend ♪
♪ But stiff back or stiff knees ♪
♪ You stand straight at Tiffany's ♪
♪ Diamonds ♪
♪ I don't mean rhinestones ♪
♪ But diamonds ♪
♪ Are a girl's best ♪
♪ Best friend ♪
- [Man] Cut, perfect.
(people chattering and applauding)
- For this I killed my baby.
(light jazz music)
- I think I'll have the
filet of sol, asparagus,
I'll have a steak, rare,
baked potato, no sour cream.
So, how'd you get your start?
- What start?
- The movie business, acting.
- Oh, right.
Yeah, I don't know.
I was discovered, I guess.
Well, I acted in high school.
I was Juliet in Romeo and Juliet.
I had a wonderful acting teacher
and he taught me to believe in myself,
and now I'm doing my first musical comedy,
big budget production of
Gentlemen Prefer Blondes.
I'm frightened, the eyes of
the world and all that, so.
What about you?
- Well, I've always loved baseball,
from the time I was a little boy.
It's almost a religion.
And I sure didn't want to be fisherman
like my father and my brothers.
I was just no good at it,
being in a boat, the ocean.
Dying fish.
(laughs)
- I don't blame you.
Poor fish.
I used to love softball.
- Really?
- Yes, yes.
Well, in high school, sometimes
I played with the boys,
when they let me. (laughs)
- What was your position?
- I guess batter? (laughs)
- When they let you.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- So yeah, baseball was my ticket out,
and I've always been grateful.
But you know, I've got to admit,
it's lonely now that I've retired.
- Well, you don't seem, I mean,
you're always in the papers,
it doesn't seem like you're retired.
- Hey, I'm not in the papers
as much as you, Marilyn.
- Oh, that's just studio
publicity, I hate it.
Well anyway, it's only for a little while,
until I get some money
saved and then I'm gonna do
some serious roles, on the stage.
Don't laugh at me, but
when I was Rose in Niagara,
you know what I was thinking?
I could play Lady MacBeth someday.
Anyway.
What I'm doing, it's
not gonna last, but you,
well you're a champion
athlete, everybody loves you.
You'll last forever.
- Okay.
Yeah, I guess.
- Mostly I wanna settle down,
like you, like any girl.
Have a family.
I love children, I'm
just crazy about babies.
- I know what you mean.
I have a son.
- A little boy?
You do?
- Yeah.
He's 10 years old.
He's with my ex-wife, so
I don't get to see him
as much as I'd like to.
- Oh, I always wanted a little boy.
Would you excuse me?
(crying)
- Miss, you all right?
(whispering)
- She left everything behind.
She broke the sacred trust.
The covenant.
When I heard about the
abortion, I called her.
She kept blaming Marilyn.
It wasn't Marilyn, it was her.
It was all Norma.
(car door closes)
- Oh, this dress is worse
than a straitjacket.
If I breathe the seams will pop.
I swear, Whitey, I'm a slave to this
Marilyn Monroe. (laughs)
- Now Miss Monroe, please don't flinch.
Have I ever stabbed you in the eye?
So, is your friend gonna
be at the premiere?
- No, he can't make it, he's being honored
at the Baseball Hall of Fame, or fishing
with Hemingway today, I don't know,
I can't keep track of it all.
Anyway, the PR staff are pissed. (laughs)
- Listen to this one.
Dear Miss Monroe, I'm 13 years old,
I think you are the most
beautiful movie star,
only my mother won't
let me go to your shows.
- I don't blame her.
Didi, make sure we answer all those,
I don't wanna miss anybody.
- Don't move, this is crucial.
I'm gonna move the beauty
mark down just a fraction.
- Ow!
- Dear Norma Jeane, this is possibly
the hardest letter I have ever penned.
I know your mother is a sick woman,
but she also has an evil heart.
She expelled me from your life.
I'm your father, Norma Jeane.
- What?
- Oh, it's probably some prank.
There's no return address, but
it was mailed in Los Angeles.
- I'll contact you again soon.
Look for me, my precious daughter upon
a special occasion in your life when...
Whitey, my father, I've
waited my whole life--
- Are you are, Miss Monroe?
- I can't.
Whitey, get me some
Bennies and some Nebutol.
(upbeat jazz music)
(people cheering)
- Tell our radio audience,
are you lonely tonight?
- Well, I--
- When are you and the
slugger gonna get married?
- As soon as I decide,
you'll be the first to know,
before he does.
- This must be very exciting for you.
- Oh yes, my mother used to
bring me here to this theater
when I was a little
girl, it's very exciting.
- Thank you very much.
- Jane.
(mumbling)
- Strip?
- No baby, the kiss.
(laughing)
- We've arranged for you to
stay in the imperial suite.
(mumbling)
Now be sure to go alone.
Someone special will be waiting.
- My father?
(laughs)
Champagne and Benzodrine.
The warm fizzing of my
blood, the happiness
pounding in my heart,
someone special will be
waiting for you.
It was like a happy ending
to a long, confusing movie.
I wanted to tell Cass.
If only I could tell Cass.
(light piano music)
- Daddy.
- Marilyn.
I'm sorry, I'd hoped I'd
make it to the premiere,
but I couldn't get a flight in time.
(laughs)
- Gosh, golly, I... (laughs)
Yeah, this is--
- Listen to me.
- Mm. (laughs)
- I wanna take care of you.
I wanna protect you from all the jackals.
We love each other, I think
it's time to get married.
- Married?
- Do you like it?
- Yes, darling, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, your hands, your strong, strong,
your beautiful hands, you see now,
now my life is perfect, it is.
(reporters shouting)
- I just wanna say this
is the happiest day
of my whole life.
(reporters shouting)
(light jazz music)
- I gotta be heard, scumbag.
- Hey, with the right kind of
attitude, I'm on your side.
I admire you, always have.
Hey, I'm a Yankees fan.
Admire your lady too.
Real high class lady.
It's just I feel strongly
that these old negatives
should be taken off the market.
So they can't be misappropriated.
Thanks, slugger.
You did the right thing.
(grunts)
(tires squealing)
(car door closes)
- [Norma Jeane] Hi.
- Don't you ever pick anything up?
- I don't know how it got this way,
I've been sick, I guess.
Oh!
God!
- Is that what you are?
Meat?
- No Daddy, I don't wanna be.
- Look at this mess.
Look at it.
The tissues all covered with makeup?
(Norma Jeane squeals)
You never put a lid on anything.
You even forget to flush the toilet!
(crying)
These people are exploiting
you, can't you see that?
They make millions, they pay
you peanuts on that contract.
You tell them no, this new movie, no deal.
- No Daddy, I have to
work, I have to work,
it's my life, I have to work.
- No.
You tell them you're quitting.
Your husband says you're quitting!
(crying)
Look at you.
I can't stand to see you cheapen yourself.
God, I'm sorry I hit you.
I never wanna hurt you.
- I know, Daddy, I know.
I know.
It's so scary, isn't it?
How scenes with actual people,
they just go on and on,
and what's to stop them?
Nobody yells "cut."
(crying)
- She meant more to me
than she meant to herself.
I can see that now.
She loved me.
I know that now too.
But we hurt each other
like wounded animals.
After she died, I had
roses sent to her crypt,
three times a week, for 20 years.
- Good of you to come to the
funeral, I appreciate it.
- Your father, he was
always so kind to me,
your whole family, taking me in.
- [Man] Taking you in?
You worked for every penny.
You ran our house, our family.
You were family.
Mother tells me you have
children of your own now.
- Four.
Three daughters, and
the oldest one, a son.
- A son.
I missed out, no children, yet.
I hope you're happy, Magda.
- [Norma Jeane] Happy?
- [Man] Your husband?
- My husband, is a good man.
- [Man] Oh Magda.
- Isaac, it's all right.
No more words.
Mr. Straussberg, excuse me,
can I do it again please,
'cause I know I can do it better.
Just...
- Sure.
- [Man] Uh-oh, oh.
(people murmuring)
- [Strassberg] Stay.
You'll see, she's not bad.
- You cast her without telling me.
- I told you on the phone.
- You didn't say her name,
you didn't say Hollywood.
- She's through with Hollywood.
They're suing her, the studio.
I called her agent.
She owes them four or five movies.
Suspended without pay and
hasn't anything saved.
Look.
She walked into my office a few weeks ago,
getting over a painful divorce.
She said she was ready
to learn real acting.
- Don't give me that crap, Lee.
It's very obvious what's going on.
You've fallen in love with a movie star.
You bastard.
(upbeat jazz music)
(people laughing and chattering)
- [Norma Jeane] I'm so
honored that I could read
for the part of Magda, I was terrified.
I thought you'd take one look at me
and speak to Mr. Straussberg
and I'd be out of the cast.
- Are you sure that's
all you're gonna drink?
- Oh, yes.
Water, I drink water. (laughs)
See, my only clear thought was
that if I fail, well, it's
winter here, freezing,
it wouldn't be hard to die, would it?
- Yes.
Well, about my play.
Magda is from a world
where people do freeze
during the winter.
She's a farm girl from Poland, a survivor.
I'm not sure that she
adds up for the audience.
- I have some ideas about Magda.
I mean, if you're interested.
- Of course I'm interested.
- This girl Magda, she's like the girl
in Chekhov's Three
Sisters, you know the girl
who marries the brother and
she has the sash on her dress
that isn't the right
color, only with Magda
it's the way she speaks English.
- Did Mr. Straussberg tell you this?
- No, no, I read the play
myself years ago. (laughs)
I always thought I could play Natasha.
I mean, someone like
me could play Natasha,
'cause well, she doesn't
belong in a good family,
and people laugh at her. (laughs)
See, but then Chekhov, well
he surprises you because
Natasha, who has her sympathy,
but she turns out to be so
selfish, so devious, really bad.
- You're saying I made Magda too good.
- No.
I guess, (laughs)
I guess I said the wrong thing.
- No, no.
Writers are strange characters.
There was a Magda in my
life, and I did love her,
when I was young.
Look, I wrote the play a long time ago,
it's too sentimental, but
there's something in it.
- Like Chekhov?
- I'm afraid I'm not much like Chekhov.
(laughs)
- What revered in Magda is, well,
she had her baby because she loved it.
I mean, before it was
even born she loved it.
Isaac didn't know, nobody knew,
but she finds a man to marry
her so her baby could be born.
I'm sorry, it's...
- We don't have to talk
about the play, Marilyn.
I should call you Marilyn, shouldn't I?
Or is that a stage name?
- Well, you could call me
Norma, that's my real name.
- Somehow Norma doesn't suit you.
- It doesn't?
Norma Jeane is what my
mother called me, actually.
My mother, and my
father, it doesn't matter
what you call me, you could whistle.
(laughing)
You could call me Hey You.
- Hey you.
(horn honks)
You are different.
Other men just see a body,
they're just attracted sexually.
- You're a lovely woman,
that's not a debit.
Maybe I'm not so different.
Do you know I wanna hold you?
I've always been faithful to my wife.
I do not take my marriage casually.
I have two children, a family.
- Oh gosh, I understand.
I guess, I'm sorry.
(light jazz music)
- I didn't want to love this woman.
A Hollywood actress.
I had heard all the rumors.
When I met her, I didn't
believe any of them.
- Hi, it's me.
Your Magda.
- Hey you.
- I had the power.
I would rewrite her story.
- I went to this tram bookshop today,
I bought those out of print plays of yours
that I hadn't read yet.
Your wonderful work, I admire you so much.
- I wanna see you.
I just don't want to involve
you in all my problems.
- [Woman] Anybody home?
- I'm on the phone, I'll be right there.
- I wanted to be a great actress for him,
to make him proud of me.
God I loved him.
I was so deeply in love,
I wanted to die sometimes.
No, no, I wanted to live.
Just to live, and know
that he was living too.
Before you I wasn't anyone.
I wasn't even born.
There were other men, but you'll never
write about me, will you?
About us?
When maybe you don't love me anymore?
- I'll always love you.
- But you're a writer.
First you see and then you write.
I mean, if we broke up.
- We won't break up.
- Other men, well that was
Marilyn Monroe, that wasn't me.
Most men I don't even feel
anything, but with you.
- I wish I didn't have to go to Tucson.
It just feels so far away.
- I know.
But we need money for your divorce.
I'm gonna convert.
I'm gonna un-baptize my
faith and become a Jew.
(both laugh)
In my soul I'm Jewish.
Let him kiss me with
the kisses of his mouth,
for thy love is better than wine.
(horns honking)
(reporters shouting)
(cameras flashing)
- Miss Monroe, this is your
first visit to England.
What are your impressions?
- Well you're my first
impressions, and you seem friendly.
- How does it feel to be married?
- Wonderful, now my life is perfect.
- Are you excited about
working with Laurence Olivier?
- Well actually, I'm a little scared.
- If you'll excuse us, please.
(reporters shouting)
- Do we have an estimate as to when
Miss Monroe will be ready?
(sighs)
Well, it's been five hours.
We only had one day with her last week.
Ah, here she is.
The lead actress.
- I'm sorry if I've kept you all waiting.
- Oh, you are worth waiting for, darling.
So, let's get on with it.
The lighting's all set, you
hurriedly take your place
at the end of the line here
to curtsy to the archduke, me.
- Can I speak with you for a moment?
See, the showgirl doesn't dance.
Why?
- Well, it isn't in the script.
- Why?
- It wasn't in the play.
Well it's too late now anyway,
it would cost too much.
It would take you forever to
perform those scenes, Marilyn.
Just learn your lines.
- But I don't like this.
I don't like that my strap
breaks when I curtsy.
See, I think it's cheap
and it's Vaudeville,
and it's the Marx brothers, and I don't--
- Darling, it's comedy.
- But--
- Marylin, my dear.
Just act sexy.
- Darling?
Darling?
(knocking)
Darling, what are you doing in there?
Huh?
- I'm sick.
- What?
- Olivier's making me sick.
He put a curse on me.
- Oh, no, darling, don't think that way.
He admires you.
- No.
No, no, no, when he touches
me, his skin crawls.
It's like his nostrils, do I smell?
Do I smell?
Because I don't understand,
it's like the hate me,
I mean they look at me, and
their eyes or something,
they hate me, they hate me.
I can't, I can't--
- Norma, Norma, that's not true.
That's not true.
Now listen to me, listen
to me, listen to me.
There is a car that's downstairs
and it's been waiting for
you for over an hour, okay?
- I'm sick.
- Now you gotta get up, yes, get up
and get in the shower, and we'll do this.
- I don't wanna go!
- Norma, god, you're frightening me,
I mean, this is serious.
Come on, people are you counting on you.
Please don't do this to yourself.
- You admire him, you admire him, you do.
You're on his side.
(crying)
- Okay.
I'll show you admire.
Look.
You smuggled these.
You smuggled these on the
plane and you promised me.
You promised me!
- Why don't you just let me
die, that's what you all want!
- Please, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, just please,
why do you think like this?
Why are you doing this?
- 'Cause you never once defended
me against that bastard.
You never once defended me.
- I was just trying to be fair.
I wasn't sure who was in the wrong.
- He despises Marilyn.
- No.
No, you despise Marilyn.
- Forgive me baby.
Oh, forgive me.
Forgive me.
I want you baby.
I'm so proud of you.
- It was a nightmare.
Why did I marry her?
Why did I think I was strong enough?
I had to save her.
Get her away from the
expectations of others,
away from England when
the movie was finished.
I had to take her to a safe place,
a place in Maine where I'd
been with my former wife.
I had to return Norma to life.
- Oh Daddy, thank you,
this is the happiest day
in my whole life, give me your hand.
Can you feel the heartbeat? (laughs)
- Yes.
- Oh god, he's in there
sleeping, dreaming,
two months and and six days in the world.
I want baby to be born
here where it's peaceful,
with a midwife.
- Midwife?
(Norma Jeane laughs)
- Oh, I don't wanna die
in a hospital, Daddy.
Oh, don't ever make me go back,
I don't wanna be her ever again.
I escaped with my life but just barely.
(screams)
Come on!
(laughing)
- I already told you, my
wife is not interested
in movies at this present time.
- [Man On Phone] Some Like It
Hot's a very special project.
They've written it especially for Marilyn.
They're offering a minimum of 100,000.
- We appreciate the offer, but my wife
is expecting our baby in December.
I can't talk now.
(phone hangs up)
(gulls cawing)
- Daddy, I'm sorry, honest,
but it was so exciting,
I got this letter when I
went to the post office
from my father, and I just
went to that little cafe,
you know, and I just sat there
and I read it over and over
and I watched the birds and the waves,
and the ice cream melted in my car
'cause I left all the groceries--
- Who's Cass?
- What?
- It was in one of your books.
The Actor's Handbook and the Actor's Life.
There was an inscription.
- Oh.
Cass, well, that was a long time ago.
- I'd just like to know, you know,
how long were you with
him, this Cass person?
- With him?
- Yeah.
- We palled around, Daddy, I don't know,
I'm not an adding machine,
please don't start.
- What do you expect?
I've been waiting for you all day.
Just been half crazy with worry.
Is that blood on your pants?
On your pants.
Are you miscarrying?
- Oh gosh. (laughs)
Daddy, it's raspberries,
I was eating raspberries,
I guess I made a pig of myself,
please don't be so suspicious.
- I just want you to understand.
I just, I've been worried.
I don't know where you are,
or what you've been doing.
- What would I be doing, hmm?
Okay, don't look so sad, just don't.
Here, taste.
Taste.
They're delicious.
Don't you wanna see my letter?
He says how much he loves me.
- It could be a cruel prank.
- No.
It's my father, I know it is.
And he's gonna make
contact with me in person.
(light jazz music)
Daddy.
Daddy, wake up.
- Oh, Norma.
- No Daddy, there's
something in the cellar,
I can hear a baby crying in the cellar.
I can hear it, I can, can't you hear it?
- You're having a nightmare.
- No, I wasn't asleep.
I can hear it, there's
something trapped down there,
please, can you just...
(water dripping)
- [Playwright] There's
nothing down here, Norma.
- Oh Daddy.
Guess you have to humor
a pregnant woman, huh?
You don't think I'm crazy, do you?
Oh Daddy, please don't write about me.
- Let's go to bed.
(cats mewing)
Maybe you should stop feeding these cats.
- I don't want 'em to die.
- Well more and more'll
just keep showing up.
Can't feed the entire state.
- I know Daddy, you're right.
- [Playwright] You gonna
be okay on your own here
for a few hours?
- Of course.
Yeah.
I'm gonna write my mother,
I thought I might ask her
to come visit us.
- That would be lovely.
I'd like to meet her.
See you.
(bell rings)
(typewriter clacking)
- Dear Mother. (typewriter dings)
I have heard from my father.
I've heard from my father.
Someday, someday when the baby's,
someday when baby is...
David can't bear that any
man might look upon her
without desire, she can't bear looking
the mirror and see the lines in her face.
He's writing about me.
Oh my god.
- Norma!
Norma!
Norma?
Oh my god, what happened?
(crying)
- The baby, the baby.
Daddy.
My baby.
(somber music)
You lied to me.
Said you'd never write about me.
- What are you talking about?
- Character in your new play.
- Darling, Ava is nothing like you.
She's a woman in her 50s.
I love you, darling.
I love you.
I would never, ever do
anything to hurt you.
Listen to me, Norma, listen to me.
Listen to me.
The baby, we won't give up.
We won't, we'll try again,
and again, and again.
- Oh Daddy.
Why not just tell the truth for once?
Please.
(crying)
- Marilyn.
How happy we are to have
you back on the team.
- It was the cats.
The cats that I was feeding.
They're the ones that wanted baby dead.
- Marilyn?
- They were in the cellar making noises.
Trying to get me to come down the stairs.
It's all clear now.
Everything's all clear.
- Just hold still, Miss Monroe.
This should get you through the dinner.
It might be good to have your husband here
while you're working.
- Miss Monroe?
There's someone here to see you.
He says it's important, an Eddie G?
I think he's been drinking.
- Hi.
- How did you know where to find me?
- There's no secrets in Hollywood.
Norma, something terrible
has happened today.
Cass died.
- Cass?
- An alchy death, not a junkie death.
He was up in the Tapinka Canyon.
He left a memento for you.
- No.
- No what?
- I don't want it.
I don't want it.
A tiger.
The one for the baby.
Why?
To MM, in her life, your tearful father.
Cass was the one who wrote the
letters from my father, Cass?
You know, you never wanted this baby,
Cass never wanted this
baby, don't pretend,
no, don't pretend, you stay away from me!
- Norma--
- Stay away from me.
(people chattering)
(carnival music)
(Norma Jeane laughs)
- Your little girl is so
pretty, she's so pretty.
Do you wanna ride the
Ferris wheel, can she?
- Can I?
- Come on.
Come on.
(both laughing)
Take us up.
Wanna go up?
(Norma laughing)
(girl squeals)
Isn't this fun?
- This is fun!
(light jazz music)
(laughing)
(screams)
We're flying across the
ocean to China, like birds.
(laughing)
Oh, so pretty up here.
Do you know that I'm
Marilyn Monroe? (laughing)
This is fun.
No no no, wait.
Do me a favor, darling.
Keep it forever, okay?
Okay?
Okay.
- [Girl] Look what she gave me!
(talking indistinctly)
(waves crashing)
(gulls cawing)
- I dreamt last night that I
was pregnant with his baby.
(laughs)
- You mean the president's?
- It's just a dream.
I'm never gonna be a mother.
'Cause when your number
is up, it's up. (laughs)
Now, he is a man who knows how to make
a woman feel like a true woman.
Even with his bad back. (laughs)
You know what I said to
him after we were finished?
I said, "if I was Castro,
I'd be real afraid of you."
(laughing)
- You wanna be careful, Miss Monroe.
- I know he can't leave her.
His wife.
Even though he loves me.
Catholics, everything. (scoffs and laughs)
- That isn't what I meant.
All of this, could be dangerous.
- Yeah.
All those little social security men
listening to our phone calls. (laughs)
- Don't you mean secret service men?
- Oh.
I better not make any wrong moves.
They might draw their guns
and shoot me. (laughs)
I'm nervous.
(somber piano music)
Takes longer and longer.
Maybe I should refuse to appear. (laughs)
Oh god, the studio's gonna
fire me, and I'm almost broke.
- No, no, Miss Monroe.
They would never do that.
This is for the president,
the honor of a lifetime.
- Honor.
They said they'd pay for all my expenses,
the dress and the plane and
everything, so here I am.
(laughs)
The president's wind-up sex toy.
Hang on a sec.
Okay.
(laughs)
(somber piano music)
(knocking on door)
- [Man] Miss Monroe, how much longer?
We can't keep the
audience waiting forever.
- Minutes, just a few minutes.
We're working, we're working.
- What if I forget the words?
- You can't forget the
words to Happy Birthday.
(laughs)
- He thinks I'm so funny.
I told him I write my own
lines, you know what he said?
He said, "Marilyn, you have
the nicest lines in show biz."
(laughing)
- She's coming, she's
coming, she's almost here.
Almost.
Marilyn.
(laughing)
(sighs)
- Oh gosh, I thought I was
dead, just for a second there.
Promise me something.
After I'm gone, (laughs)
you'll make Marilyn up one final time.
- Miss Monroe, I will.
Now go out there and knock his socks off.
- Okay.
- Don't let me hear anybody say
anything against Miss Monroe.
I'll shove their teeth down their throats.
She was the only one
of them that was human.
(audience cheering and applauding)
(whistling)
(laughs)
(somber piano music)
(Multicom Jingle)