Yes?
Someone is here, someone is in my room
Someone will be up immediatly.
Something is...
Come in!
Someone was in here.
Whoever it was left that bag.
Did you open it?
No.
Did you touch it?
Who knows what's inside of that bag?
I was afraid to even go near it.
Perhaps...
...there's another person...
...who left the bag...
...which is...
...very beautiful.
You know...
I just arrived yesterday.
I don't know anyone here in Shanghai.
You have met no one here?
No, I'm telling you. I met no one.
I went out today for a lunch meeting with
a woman I work with.
Several others in our company will arrive
tomorrow.
We needed...
...to go over arrangements.
Lunch...
yes,
but now, it's very late in the night.
Yes.
I went after lunch to see the tower
The Pearl Tower
I went to see it.
I had learned it was inspired by a poem
a poem about...
...different sized pearls falling in jade...
...a jade plate...
I thought I heard this sound...
...as I looked up at the Tower.
I felt...
Yes?
I...
It's...
...it's silly
What?
I felt I had been here before...
...in Shanghai
This feeling came over me as I heard...
...the pearls...
...falling and hitting the jade...
That most beautiful sound
I don't know...
...where or how I...
...went in.
It seemed as if suddenly I was in the old Shanghai
I saw...
...buildings...
...winding alleys...
...narrow stairs...
...I heard music...
I can't be here.
I wish I could...
...to be with you.
It's all very beautiful...
...so beautiful...
It's very beautiful...
Yes...
You know...
...I have to leave you...
Please...
...I love you!
And I love you!
I love you!