[Police radio]
[Siren]
We've got two white males
on the run, do you copy?
- Traffic?
- Something like that.
- All right, let's do this.
- All right,
let's get this over with.
- Hwaah!
- You better go home now
before my dad gets here.
- Go home now?
Baby girl,
I'm the daddy
of all daddies.
- You ain't got no business
around here.
- Come on,
you know you want it.
- Say, bitch.
- You gotta go home now
- before my daddy get here.
- I better go home now?
Baby girl,
I am the daddy of all daddies.
- You ain't got no business
around here.
- I got business around here.
I'm in the business of getting
my money.
- What money?
- The money that's in the bag.
- What bag, this bag?
- You better give me
that here bag.
- Man: Cut.
- Give me that bag, bitch.
- Man: Cut!
- Very nice, oh, darling,
you're looking wonderful.
Oh, yeah,
you can go, thanks.
Girl, you got the parts.
Uh, the part.
- Uh-uh. Nah.
- Give me the bag!
- Hey, wait up.
Long time no see,
how you been?
- Hey. Uh, it's gonna be
my year, you know?
- Yeah.
- Congratulations on the parts.
- I know eddy j,
don't mind him.
- Man: Give me the bag.
- I can't say I wasn't
looking to--
- hopefully we get to work
together again,
I had a really,
really good time.
- Man: Cut.
- How was that one for camera?
Was it cool?
I had a great time, one of my--
you look good though, love.
It's always good seeing you.
- Thank you, you too.
- No need for
the suit, brother,
the lawyer's
already been cast.
You'll be reading these.
Off you go.
Come on,
we don't have all day.
- Ahem.
Hwaah!
I deals drugs but ain't nothing
wrong with what I do.
I'm the ghetto rider.
The hoods the way it read.
Street punks
and the doctor is seen.
Shit, if I don't supply,
what my niggas
gon' get high at?
That's the problem.
That ain't a problem,
that's a motherfucking problem.
- Now you know
that is some bullshit, son.
- Not black enough.
I know black.
Shit, I am black.
Well, when you say black,
what exactly do you mean?
You know, thuggish, gangsta,
a brother that don't give
a fuck.
Bishop from juice.
A real nigga.
- Mmm,
kinda like my story.
What is your story?
Man, nigga like me ain't
never even knew my pops.
See, you could be him
for all I know,
and I wouldn't have no idea.
Momma Dukes od'd on crack
when I was six years old
so I had to get raised up
by my grandmother.
Tell me how the hell big momma's
supposed to raise a man?
Committed my first robbery
at, like, 11.
Some old-ass white lady
didn't want to spare a dollar,
and I asked that bitch nicely.
Son, I got two kids. My new
bitch, she pregnant right now.
And on top of all of that,
I'm looking at, like,
3 to 5 right now
with possession with
intent to sell up in rikers.
All this acting shit, man,
this right here is--
just my way of trying
to get some money, man.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- You feel me?
- I feel you, brother.
[Screams]
- Man: I want to get you
outside.
[Clattering]
[Typing]
- What are you doing
under there, man?
- Maintenance, uh--
smoothin' this baby out.
What's up, love?
Can I ask you a question?
- Sounds like you just did.
- Why didn't you come in when
you know you're on the schedule?
- I read it wrong, man.
- That's bullshit, man,
you couldn't lie in high school,
you can't lie now.
Call yourself an actor,
that's good.
What's up, Denzel?
- Hey listen, man, first of all,
acting is the truth.
- Oh, yeah? Huh.
- Yeah.
- Secondly, shut the fuck up.
- Is the real cool an act?
This whole thing right here,
is this is an act?
- It's my work space, man,
I'm chilling, all right?
- Guy with the fly swatter.
You got your little umbrella,
you got your--your--
your radio over here.
You're on spring break, right?
- I'm-a do my cool thing, man,
you do your grease monkey thing,
- all right?
- You work her well.
- It looks good.
- The ladies like me.
- Uh-huh.
- Speaking of--
that's me.
You do you, I do me.
- Hope she likes, uh,
fly swatters.
- Hey, hey, Renee.
What's up, baby? Give me a kiss.
- Now, now, now, don't hey me.
- What?
- I thought you owned this
place?
- [Stammers] Well, um,
I do, I do.
- I found out from keisha
that you just pump the gas.
Welcome to my station.
How can I help you today,
beautiful?
- I need directions to
Manhattan,
can you please give them to me?
I'm in a rush.
- Ah, New York City ain't
going nowhere.
- Ah, this is your station?
- Mm-hm.
- You're Phil?
- Yeah, I mean, don't worry
about the name tag.
- You are a gas attendant.
- Well, that is true.
- And the only thing you own
is that silly little bike over
there
and that silly little bike isn't
even the collector's item
- you say it is.
- Oh, now, that's a lie.
- It's a huffy!
- Well, yes, it is a huffy,
but it is a 1990 huffy,
discontinued model.
Therefore, by definition,
a collector's item.
- Don't lie.
Hey, you?
- Aaah!
- Can you come over here
for a second?
- Why people always gonna run
to the white guy?
- Can I aks you a question?
- Yeah, you just did.
- Does he own this place?
- He owns that huffy.
- Is his real name Phil?
- It says cool on his name tag.
- You're in the middle.
- Hey--
Yo, what was that?
- Yup.
- Look around you, man,
we work at a gas station.
- Mm-hm.
- You fix cars, I pump gas.
I can barely keep
my fingernails clean.
- There's some special soap
in the back if you--
- is this what you want
for yourself?
- Look, I happen
to like my life.
- Yeah, well,
whatever works for you.
- Yeah, whatever works for you,
too.
- When's the last time
you booked something?
- Whatever, man,
I've done commercials.
Today's ordinary burger
just can't satisfy
the modern-day black man.
We likes our food to have
that extra large flavor, baby.
That's why,
here at burger Jester,
we have a commitment to beef.
With the introduction of
the new big daddy burger, baby.
This right here ain't your
daddy's burger, baby.
- Hey big, daddy.
- Hey, sugar,
why don't you plant one on me?
- Woman: This is big, daddy.
- Man: Keep it real.
When you eat your meal.
Burger Jester, 77 burger Lane,
south orange, New Jersey,
www.bigdaddyburger.com.
Available now!
- I'm out! Cover me, homeboy.
- Homeboy?
- All right, dawg,
brother, playa.
- Now, you know you ain't
supposed to be doing that.
- You know, you were supposed
to be here at 10 am.
You know,
you don't own this place?
You know you sit over there
with your music
and your--
[Beatboxing]
- All right, all right,
you sound like my wife, man.
- Hey, get a girlfriend first.
You're in the middle.
- Learn how to drive.
Watch it, loser.
I'm working here.
[Laughter]
[Tires squeal]
Baby, baby, we are closed.
[Bell]
Damn, up to the last
tick on the clock.
[Stammers] Charli?
- Reggie?
- What--what are you doing--
- what are you doing here?
Do you work here?
- Say what?
- Do you work here?
- Here?
- Uh--
- yeah?
- Well, I mean technically,
not really,
I mean, I'm still acting, just--
just paying off some bills,
this, just doing this as
you know, a favor to my man.
Part time, that's all.
- Uniform and all?
- Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
He likes everything to be
official.
Image is everything, you know.
- Fill me up please, unleaded.
Enjoy this now, lady,
'cause it's not every day
that a woman gets her gas pumped
by such talented hands.
[Car horn toots]
- Here.
- No, no, no, let me get that.
Let me get that.
- Don't go breaking your piggy
bank for me, please.
Take it
and keep the change.
- Look, why don't--
why don't we start again?
You were empty, I was here.
Come on,
what are the chances of that?
- 100%.
The chances of pulling into
a gas station
when you need gas are 100%.
- Out of all the gas stations
in all the world,
you happen to pull into
this particular one,
where I help out
every now and again.
You're just gonna act like
you don't know me, huh?
- I'm acting like this
because I do know you.
Thank you.
[Car horn]
[Breaking glass]
[Tires squealing]
- Just--ok, just--just--breathe.
- He just, he hit me
and he just--
- yeah, yeah, yeah. Just--
[breaking glass]
Look at this.
[Tires squealing]
Oh, my god.
- You probably wanna
leave it here.
[Laughs]
- Little evel knievel action
going on.
Why are you back, Charli?
- What?
- What brings you back
into town?
- I'm getting married
on Saturday.
My fiance and I,
we moved back last weekend.
- Saturday? Today's--today's--
today's Thursday.
- Yeah.
- [Stammers] Wow, I mean--
- I have to get home.
- Hey, wait.
- What are you doing?
- You'll see.
- No, no, no, no, Reggie.
Reggie, that's not--
that's not necessary. It's fine.
I can just walk by myself.
It's fine.
- You could walk
but you will not walk.
I'm a gentleman,
I can't--i can't let you do it.
Your chariot awaits.
- You don't wanna do this.
- I do.
- I don't.
Oh!
- What, what, what,
what's going on?
- Keys are in the car.
- Oh, well, you know,
we can go back and get them or
I can just wait here with you,
whatever you wanna do.
- You go get 'em.
- Me go get 'em?
Come on,
and leave you here all alone?
I would never do that.
I'm too much of a gentleman.
It wouldn't be the first time.
It's a nice little setup
you got here.
Trees, bushes all manicured.
It's a good look for you.
Charli, I'm only working there
just to pay off my tuition bills
while I act, ok?
That's all,
just making some moves.
Give a brother some credit.
- It doesn't matter.
- Hey, baby,
will you come help me
with some of this stuff?
Uh--
- Charli: Hi.
[Man laughs]
- Man: Hey.
[Man whispers]
Mm-mm-mm!
What's up, man?
Who's this?
- Oh. Babe, I had a little
accident at the gas station.
- Accident?
Are you all right?
- Yeah, i'm--I'm all right.
He walked me home.
- All right, ed Marshall.
Charli's fiance.
Husband, come Saturday.
Listen, I'll handle any legal
recourse. I specialize in--
- it was a hit and run, baby.
- A hit and run?
- Yeah, they took off before
I could even get out of the car.
- Are you all right?
- You specialize in divorce?
- Yeah, that and other aspects
of the law.
I passed the bar
in seven states.
- Ah.
- Yeah.
- Uh, look , man, I don't want
your card.
- Oh, you're above the law?
- I'm just not a criminal, man.
- Ha, ha.
I didn't say
you were a criminal. Got you.
Listen, listen, sooner or later,
everyone gets caught
doing something, all right?
- That's when I come in.
- Oh? Wow.
That's--that's scary.
- Yeah,
it was a pleasure meeting you
and I wanna thank you,
for looking after
the love of my life.
Now, you keep doing
your good works.
Good samaritan, huh!
Samaritan negro. Come on.
- Are you ok, baby?
- I'm really ok.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- No.
- We need to go to the hospital?
- No. No, no.
- Hey, hey.
- Mm.
- What's up, momma?
- Ahem.
- Oh, yeah, the hat.
- Hello, mother.
- What's wrong, baby?
- [Sighs] Nothing.
- Auditions?
Hey, hey, brother.
- Did my agent call?
- No.
Check your fax machine, though.
- You lock everything up tight?
- Yep.
- Aaah!
Oh, yeah!
- Thank you.
- Move over, junior.
- Ma, what's--what's
all the food for?
- Saturday's event.
- What's the event?
- A wedding.
- A wedding?
You know, a bride,
a groom, a cake,
but most importantly, my food.
- Please do not tell me that you
are catering Charli's wedding.
- Now I think you will wanna
dip that in the sauce.
- Why are you avoiding
the question?
- What question?
- Is it Charli's wedding?
- Huh?
- Charli, tall pretty girl,
love of my life?
- It's her wedding.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Why should I tell you
what your ex-fiancee does?
You messed that one up
for yourself, bubba.
- Maybe I should get a little
bit more ice.
- Ahem!
- Well, you don't know
the whole story.
- Well, I don't need to know it.
You cannot treat real people
like they're characters
in a script
and then expect
a fairy-tale ending.
- There's one more thing.
- Oh yeah, what's that?
- I'm expanding my business.
Going regional next month.
- Well, hey, that's good news.
- Yeah, I'll have
a larger kitchen,
I'm gonna be working from home.
- Well, you already
work from home.
- Wh--what?
- We're moving.
- Two hours away.
- I don't know if you remember,
but I go back and forth
from the house to the city
to go to auditions,
have you even considered that?
- Did you even consider that
I have been cooking meals
for 200 people on a 4-eye stove
ever since
your father and I divorced?
- What am I supposed to do?
- [Sighs] Look, honey, baby,
this is our place.
Phil and I want a place
for ourselves.
So we can start building
some new memories.
- [Laughs] Yeah.
Yeah, o-ho! You almost got me,
man, you're a funny dude.
This is--
this is a joke, right?
This is a joke, you--you--you--
I was late to work today, mom,
that's why,
'cause I was late to work,
you're trying to teach me
a lesson,
well the lesson's learnt, man,
I'm a changed man.
I will be on time, Jack,
right on the dot.
Every day. I'm a changed man,
you know, you can--
guarantee that,
you've got my word,
scout's honor, pinky swear,
bet on black.
You know what they say, that
home black, I saw that on--
on soul train.
You guys--
you guys are serious.
- You ever think about, uh--
getting your own place?
- Ma?
- You need to be near the city
and we don't.
Maybe you ought to think about
getting a place closer.
- Yeah.
- This is not the night
to hear this.
- Baby, there's just no
perfect time for some things.
Sometimes you have just got
to do what you've got to do.
Sometimes--
- sometimes seems like every
time for me.
- Excuse me.
- Where are you going?
- Apartment hunting.
- He's just hard-headed,
you know, like I used to be.
- Mm-hm, I know you're
hard headed,
but I thought bones were
supposed to get softer
as you got older.
- [Laughs]
Now that's funny.
You know, baby,
my bones are good.
- Aaah!
- [Laughs] Come here.
- Hi.
- Oh.
- Mm.
Mm.
What did you think of the
rehearsal?
- If the wedding goes as smooth
as the rehearsal
I'll be more than happy.
I'm a little nervous about
the floral arrangements, though.
I might check that out tomorrow.
- What's up with that?
- I don't know,
I'm just unsure
and I didn't wanna settle.
- Settle?
My wife will never
have to settle about anything.
- Future wife.
- Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Future wife. Now didn't the
brochure guarantee
100% customer satisfaction?
- Yes.
- Yes, it did, so now, if
they didn't provide that, then--
- oh, god, Johnnie Cochran,
wait a second.
- What?
- Slow down.
What did I say?
- You said you'd handle it
tomorrow.
- And what am I gonna do?
- You're gonna handle it
tomorrow.
- Ok, good.
- The defense rests.
- Very good.
- What?
- You smell like garlic,
it's awful.
- Garlic?
- Yeah.
- Garlic is the flavor of love,
you ain't know?
- Says who?
- Says the man who loves you
dearly.
- Oh, god, no,
you smell like garlic.
That's awful.
- Come here, come here, come
here.
- Oh!
No, don't tickle, don't tickle.
- I'm tickling!
[Both laughing]
[Laughter]
- Charli: Aaah, the food!
- Oh! Ow!
- My masterpiece.
I got it, I got it.
It's ok.
- God!
- It's ok. Ok.
It's still ok, baby.
- Good.
- Whoo! Ok.
- Are you all right?
- You're not the first guy
that's tickled me, you know?
- You're talking about
after the accident?
- Oh?
Yeah, it was nothing,
it was nothing, honestly.
- Nothing?
Baby, you were involved
in a hit and run.
- I know,
he'll track them down.
[Doorbell]
[Whispers] What are you
doing here?
- How you gonna marry this dude
over me?
- Sh. We haven't spoken
in over three years.
You don't get to ask why.
- Why not?
- Because you don't.
- Why is that?
- You just don't, ok?
- In case you forgot, Charli,
you're the one that broke up
with me.
That's why we haven't spoken
in, like, over three years.
- If you would have been there
for me
we'd be having a different
conversation right now,
but you weren't.
I just wanna talk,
it's too late to even do that?
- Too late.
I question your sanity
sometimes, you know that?
- Yeah, well, my straitjacket's
on the back of the bike.
- Huh! Really funny.
- Ed? Hey, big guy,
what's going on, man?
- What's up?
- Um--
would you believe, I managed
to get the plates
on those kids after all?
I saw them on my way
home from work,
followed them
for, like, 2 miles.
- Wow, on that bike?
- [Charli scoffs]
- Yeah. It's got ten speeds.
- Oh.
- Well, your card came in handy
after all.
- Um, thanks, but you know,
this could have waited till the
morning, man, it's 11 o'clock,
you know?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, well, this is,
uh, it's kinda urgent.
- And well, we were just about
to have dinner
so if you don't mind--
- no, i--i don't mind,
actually i'm--
I am a little bit thirsty
after the whole bike ordeal.
Wouldn't mind a little
sip of something.
I could hold you for negligence,
if you don't, you know that.
- Hey.
- All right?
- All right, come on, man. Come
on. I'll get you something.
- Thank you.
- Come on. All right?
- Oh, yeah. Excuse me.
- So let me, uh--
put some pants on, right?
What?
Ed: Bam!
[Laughs]
- Is that um,
that's takeout?
- Oh, come on, all home-made,
strictly fresh,
ain't that right, Charli?
- Yes.
- That's right.
- I can tell this is probably
pretty good,
you know, I know a little thing
or two about fine cuisine.
First of all, because
I love to eat
and secondly, because my mother
is a caterer.
- [Laughs] Fine cuisine.
Like it.
- You know what, you should have
her cater your wedding.
- No, well, that's
her department, you know,
we already got somebody,
right, baby?
- Yeah, yeah, we do.
- Hmm, that's too bad.
Ah, let's eat.
- Your nails are horrendous.
- Thank you.
You must be one hell
of an attorney, ed.
To get her hand in marriage.
What'd you do, sue her for it?
[Both laugh]
Yeah. That's a tough hand to
keep, brother,
that's a tough hand to keep.
- Do you two know each other?
- Oh, yeah, no doubt.
No doubt, man.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- She--she didn't tell you?
- I was gonna tell you
but the door rang and--
- what were you gonna say?
- The truth.
- I doubt that.
- What is the truth?
- Charli: Nothing.
- Aah. Well, now, the truth--
- nothing special, trust me.
- Let me tell the brother
the truth, he wants
to know the truth.
The truth is, that, you know,
at one point in time
Charli was the most
important thing in my life, man.
When we were kids growing up.
Then you know,
as friends do,
we drifted apart
things happen, life changes,
blase, blah.
- I had this friend, Darlene,
beautiful girl, she was great,
she moved away, I was young.
- Cool: She was hot?
- She was fine.
[Laughs]
Now baby,
I just had a moment,
can't a brother have a moment?
You know what I'm saying.
- Cool: I understand what you
mean though, man, 'cause
Charli--
whoo-hoo!
- Come on, Charli is the best.
- Cool: Charli, Charli, Charli.
[Laughs]
Charli's something else, man.
- What?
What? What? What?
- Well, listen, if I had
one negative thing
to say about Charli, this has
just popped into my head now.
Is that, you know,
as much as she likes
to face problems head-on,
she tends to skirt the issue
when it comes to the big
problems.
- And you're the--
you're the most qualified person
to talk about that?
- Baby, ok, I will say
one thing.
That, sometimes--right?
Well, we know you're
a great psychologist, right,
that's in no dispute.
But sometimes you don't always
apply your own analysis
to yourself.
- And you're the most qualified
person to talk about that?
- It's true, it's true.
- Hey, you know what I mean?
- Hey!
- Come on, man, now.
- Hey, how about--how about that
one guy you were engaged to?
What was his name, uh, Reginald,
I believe?
- Charli: What about him?
- The bullshit actor dude.
- He's a loser.
- A--a loser?
[Stammers] Was he that bad?
- Well, from what I hear.
- You know what,
I don't even remember anymore.
- Mmm, I don't know, Charli,
you called it off with him about
a month before the wedding,
right?
He was taking you home from
school and by the time
he got to the end of the
driveway, everything was over.
The marriage, the wedding,
the relationship, everything.
What was supposed to be
the beginning became the end.
Cause that's what they had
told me at the gas station.
- Well, you know, it was the end
of the road.
- That's right.
And the start of another.
- Yes.
- Come here, you.
- Mmm. Mm!
- That's some bullshit, Charli.
I mean, I'm sorry, but it is.
It's some bullshit.
You don't do that to people.
Sorry, man, but I'm just
not in the business
of sugar-coating the truth.
- No, no, you're in the business
of--of what?
Ignoring the truth.
- Well I'm in the business
of trying to start the dinner.
You know can we, can we,
ask a blessing or something?
- Yes.
- You know, just whatever we
need to do, let's get to eat.
- How about blessing the fact
that is two black people in
love.
Black love, I love it,
it just warms my heart.
- All right, well, to love.
- To Charli.
- And to you.
- Hey, why not?
- My brother that smells
like gasoline
can still drawing board me.
[Laughs]
- Hey, check it out, I'm gonna
skedaddle, man, you know.
- What are you talking about?
Uh-uh.
- You haven't even eaten.
- Nah,
- I gotta peddle my way home.
- Ed: No.
- Baby, if he has to go,
he has things to do,
we have to go to bed, we have
so many things to do tomorrow.
- It's days before the wedding.
- It's fine, yeah, sure,
if you've gotta go, bro,
I understand.
- All right, thanks, man.
Hey, do me a favor, man.
- What's that?
- Take care of this
precious woman.
- Oh, I certainly will.
She is my best friend.
- Always a pleasure.
- I'll show you out.
- All right, man.
I hate you sometimes, man.
♪ Can't nobody love you
like I'm loving you, baby ♪
♪ 'cause they don't know how
to love you like I do ♪
♪ and--
- bubba, wake up, come on now.
- [Grunts]
- You've been waking up to
this song for three years now.
Where'd you go last night?
I'd tell you not to do it
but I know who I'm talking to.
- Hey?
- Mmm?
- Treat my client
with some respect?
Bubba!
- Hey, hey, I'm up.
I'm up. I'm going to work.
- I love you, son.
- I love you too.
Yeah. You love me so much,
you kick me up out the house.
I don't need that love.
You're the most beautiful woman
in the world, you know that?
I love your lips, your eyes,
your ears.
- Good morning.
- Is the car ready yet?
- Uh, yeah.
My boy over at Stan's
hooked the door up for me
from a junk yard.
- $500 job.
- $500?
- It's complicated stuff.
- When's it getting picked up?
- Uh, this attorney called me
about it this morning.
Made a point of telling me
he practiced law.
- Better make it 600.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna get breakfast,
you good?
- No, I'm straight, man, thanks.
- All right.
- I'll catch you later.
- Mm-hm.
- Don't touch the car, right?
- That's your job.
- Yeah, you know.
- Cool, what you doing?
Wh--what you doing?
Get out the car.
You know, you work,
you can have a car like that
you can sit in all day long.
- You're tired?
- No, I was just--
- get out the car.
- Cool: Fill her up?
- Customer: No, no.
$5, regular.
- What's up? How you doing?
- I'm all right, how you doing?
- I'm chilling.
- Uh, you did some great work
on the car, dude.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I got no money for gas though,
your work was expensive.
- I hooked you up, new shocks,
I gave you--
your brakes were kind of
sticking. I gave you some--
- yeah, good, how you doing?
- Yeah, I'm pretty good.
- Your girl good?
- Yeah.
- Tell her I said hey.
- I will.
- She's cute, man.
- Yeah.
- You guys look good together.
- All right.
- Customer: It's all there.
- Cool: 16.59?
- It's $5.
- You said fill her up.
It's 16.59.
- I didn't say fill her up.
- Yeah, that's what you said,
man.
- I didn't say fill it up.
- I wouldn't have filled
your tank if you didn't say
fill her up.
- Yeah, you take it back out,
then. I said $5.
- Why would I fill it up
if you didn't say that?
- Yeah, why you fill it up
if I didn't say that?
- 'Cause you said--
- I ain't say that.
- You said that, man.
- Yo, yo, yo.
- This guy crazy,
this guy crazy.
Don't worry about it,
I got you.
You just tell your friends
where to come
to get their car smoothed out,
all right?
- I'll tell 'em.
Take it easy, man,
good to see you.
- All right, man.
- Hey, man, I need you
to cover for me again.
- All I do is cover for you, no.
- Come on, man,
I cover for you too.
Look, what do you think Phil
will be more upset about,
me coming in late,
or you overcharging customers
for the cars you joyride in?
One's illegal, one's not.
- I got my reasons.
- You have reasons
for overcharging your customers?
- Yeah.
- What are these reasons, man?
What do you need money for?
- What? What the hell's
that supposed to mean?
- I'm working on something.
- What?
What are you working on?
- When will you be back?
- I'll be in and out all day.
- No, man,
you work until we close.
Listen,
I will cover you for an hour.
- No, no, no, no, no.
I need more time than that.
- Well, no.
- Please, listen.
You said you wanted to know
who the real cool is, right?
- That was yesterday, today,
I'm all right.
- You know whose car that is
in the garage?
- Which one?
- The only car in the garage,
stupid, the accord.
- I'll know when they bring it
back in for more work.
- It's Charli's.
- Charli Reynolds?
- Charli from high school?
- Yeah, college too.
- Charli, your ex-fiancee.
- Yes, yes.
That attorney that you spoke to
earlier today,
come the end of the day
on Saturday,
her new husband.
- Damn, that's tomorrow.
- I know this.
- Blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah. Wait.
So you want me to work for you
so you can go out
and live some love fantasy
you've got planned in your head?
Look around you, bro,
this ain't--
there ain't no Bridges here.
This ain't Madison county.
This is essex county, bro.
- Stop calling me bro, homeboy
and all that other stuff.
Man, I'm getting tired of it.
- You still love her?
Listen, man, regardless,
I ain't working for you all day.
I'm sorry, dawg,
that's outlandish,
- that's preposterous.
- What?
Come on, man, I got some
auditions I gotta go to too.
- There comes a time
in every man's life
when he has to put
his foot down.
This is that time,
I am that man.
Sorry.
- I'll tell Phil right now
that you grease the customers.
- Right now.
- I told you, man,
- I got my reasons.
- What are these reasons?
- Just--
give me the damn bank.
- My man, yes,
a little advance on my paycheck.
Phil said it was cool
and it can all go to you--
- all right, all right,
all right.
- If you just hold me down.
- All right, all right.
- Thanks a lot, man. God bless.
Come on,
let me see my balance.
80 bucks.
What? Man!
I know I put a check-- damn!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa! Hold up. Damn!
Aah!
[Heavy breathing]
[Musical tone]
- Reginald coolidge.
Reginald coolidge?
Ok, we now have
Reginald coolidge.
- Hey, how you doing?
- Hi.
- All right, thank you. Leave
that there, please.
- Ok, sit down.
- Um, we decided to call you in
after looking at your reel.
He wants an unknown
and you are that.
I mean, I don't remember
seeing you in anything.
- Uh, thank you.
- Thank me? For what?
- You know, for having me in
despite my unknownness.
- You're welcome.
Go ahead.
- Mr. Big daddy burger.
- Hey, it ain't
your daddy's burger.
You know,
because that's what they say.
I'm the spokesperson
for their campaign.
- That's what it is, I knew
I know you from somewhere.
- You know, "hey, big daddy."
- Yeah.
- Do you remember that?
I was actually, um, the female
lead in the commercial
with him, but, uh--he s good.
- You act?
- Well, I did,
it was a while ago.
- Excuse me.
- Anyway, I don't know how much
you know about what we're doing,
but we're not gonna burn
one frame of film
on any of that typical black
bullshit that they're doing.
- So uh, what is it about?
- It's a comedy, a black comedy.
About what would happen
if black people
got reparations
for slavery.
- Doesn't sound funny to me
at all.
- And that's the point.
Our goal here is to keep
drug dealer
off the top of a lot of resumes.
Have you ever played
a drug dealer?
- Uh, ye--a street pharmacist.
- Look, let me paint the
picture.
A fictitious town in Virginia,
new hope.
A black town, and nobody has
any real problems.
There aren't any class issues
and everything you need
is at the general store.
New hope was founded
during a reconstruction.
On land purchased by
several families of free men.
These families happen to be
direct lineage
to the original 23 slaves
brought to jamestown, Virginia
in the year 1619.
Today, these families get
reparations checks
of a very significant amount.
Problem is, they can't tell
anybody that they got 'em
or it all falls apart.
- So what happens?
- What about US.
It's the title.
So what about you?
- So you don't want me
to read the lines?
- Just wanna hear a little bit
about you.
- Uh, my story. Here we go.
Hwaah!
Here we go.
Well, I am 28 years old,
six foot one inches tall.
And I'm black.
Whatever the hell that means.
Um, I live at home with my mom
and her boyfriend
who I wish she never had.
I go on auditions
every day of the week.
If I'm lucky.
If I'm not auditioning
for a killer or a rapist
or something like that,
I'm even luckier.
Ah, da-da-da-da, da-da-da-da--
oh, until this morning,
I rode the same bike
that I had on my paper route
17 years ago,
I rode it every day.
Then it got stolen.
That's kind wack.
I don't even know why
I'm telling you that. Uh--
let's see what else, I mean,
even though there's the big
stereotype and everything,
I've gotta admit,
I love me some chicken,
fried chicken,
that's my favorite.
It tastes so good.
Don't you agree?
Uh, something else,
that, uh--
that pretty much, uh-- scene.
- That's it?
- [Laughs]
- Yeah.
Yeah, that's it, yeah.
- You told US how tall you are,
how old you are,
where you live,
you're black, you're 28,
you like fried chicken.
Who are you?
Uh--
Call in our next actor.
- You know, there's no one else
out there. It's lunch time.
So if there's something
you wanted to add maybe we can--
- he's done, he's done.
The audition is over.
- Well, I'm sorry,
what did I do?
- You didn't do anything at all.
- Woman: You know what I'd like?
One of those Cuban sandwiches
from downstairs.
- Man: I thought you gave up
the pork?
- Woman: Oh, no, no, no,
not at all.
- Man: Where's lunch?
- Young woman: I'll call it in.
The regular, big daddy burger?
- Man: Uh, yeah, thank you.
Big daddy burger please.
When actors like this,
they come in here,
no preparation--
- young woman: Yes, I'd like to
make an order.
- Don't know what they're doing,
don't know who they are.
- Young woman: One big daddy
burger.
- Woman: Yeah, I think we
should--
- man: The audition's over.
- Woman: Yeah.
Thank you.
Ok, first off,
you can't pull a gun
on a person, all right?
Fake or not.
- They said they wanted black.
You know what,
forget about that.
Why don't you get a chair
in this office?
- I have a chair in this place.
My clients are supposed to be
out booking jobs
and making money, you're the
only one who comes in here
and complains about standing.
- Yeah. I wonder why?
- You know what, mister,
you can check that attitude.
I am busting my neck for you.
- You have to read
some of these things
that these people have me doing.
- That's not my problem,
what they have you doing.
If you have a problem with
what they have you doing,
then get some brothers
to write a script
or you write a script.
That's not my job.
- Hey, something has to give.
- And you know what it is?
You. You wanna make it
all the way to the top,
I'll tell you what,
you gotta take a few shorts
along the way.
You gotta lose a couple battles
to win the war, all right?
So you play a few rapists.
So you--
you play a few drug dealers,
you play some basketball,
you play some football.
Come on, you be the best damn
stereotype you know how to be.
- There are certain things
I just can't do.
- Won't do. That's all right.
That's all right. You know why?
'Cause they're hiring
accountants at h&r block.
Tax season is coming up,
here, want an application?
- Why do you even have this,
man?
- Because as long as
you're standing there,
I need to supplement my income.
- How'd the audition go today?
- Fuck Pete chatmon.
- Uhhh.
That good, huh?
You wanna talk about it?
- No.
Thank you.
- For what?
- For standing by me.
- Go figure. You know,
despite the many asshole-ish
properties in your personality,
there's something about you
I find likeable.
Here,
some new auditions.
If you can do them.
- Hey, just two-way me if
anything happens with anything.
- Mm-hm.
Ciao, baby.
- Yeah, bye.
- Pete chatmon, please.
Petey, hi,
hey, Cole Carter here.
Yeah, how's it going?
No,
just got back from Sundance.
Working on my tan. Uh-huh.
[Laughs]
- Man: Put on your helmet.
Let's play.
- [Shouts]
- You're running down the field,
they're coming after you,
they're tackling left,
they're tackling right
but you're too fancy for them.
Sweet feet, that's it,
that's it,
getting jiggy, getting jiggy.
Now, basketball.
What have you got?
You call yourself a black man?
Dribble that damn ball.
Round and round,
do it like curly.
LeBron James, magnificent.
Haaah!
- Man: Go ahead now, rape her.
- Cool: Do what?
Hey, no, I will not calm down.
Hey, hooligan,
get your hands off me.
This is ridiculous.
- I'm the murderer, right?
- Pete: Who are you?
- Cole: You be the best
damn stereotype
you know how to be.
- Cool's mom: We're moving.
- Phil: Do you ever think about
getting your own place?
- Pete: The audition's over.
- [Charli laughing]
- Try to focus.
Look, just, do this,
do this. Hwaah!
- Ok, ok.
- Hwaah!
- Charli: Are you here for me?
I'm here for you.
You're gonna make it.
"We've been together
for quite some time now.
"Long enough to start thinking
about things--
"the big things."
Is this for a soap opera?
- Come on. I don't do soaps.
It's a pilot.
- Oh?
- Continue.
Ok.
"You've been there for me
since the beginning.
"I wanna be here for you
until the end."
- "I love you so much."
- You're gonna do great things.
[Cole laughing]
- Cool: Bullshit actor dude.
- You're gonna make it, cool.
I just don't know if
it's with me.
Or with yourself.
"I love how your eyebrows serve
as a perfect umbrella
"to your brown eyes.
"I love all five feet
seven inches of you
"and how your brown and
turquoise sweat pants
"paint the perfect silhouette
around a work of art.
"On down to the brown shoes,
"and don't let me forget
the--the green tank top."
Did you write this?
- What?
Let me see that.
- I just--oh, damn!
Look, I gave you my copy
and then you--
- baby, what--
- why are you doing that, no,
we'll read.
I promise I'll be--
I'll do it better.
What are you--
what are you doing?
- Will you marry me?
- Are you serious?
- I'm serious,
will you marry me?
Be my wife?
[- Charli laughs]
Oh, my god.
- Are you smiling because
you're gonna say yes
or you smiling because you don't
want to--
- yes! Yes!
- Thank you,
that's what I wanna hear,
let me get your finger.
- Oh, my god.
- Cool: It's only the beginning,
I promise you,
I'll get you a better ring.
- Oh, my god.
Hey?
- Again?
- I can't stay away
from my favorite lady.
- Don't come by my house
anymore, ok?
- My life is not your movie set.
- You're right, you're so right.
I apologize. Most likely,
it won't happen again.
- Oh!
- I see you had the chef
pick up the car?
- No, he had some cases
to take care of
so I went and picked it up
from Derrick.
For some reason,
ed liked you, so--
- oh, yeah? That would
probably be the charm.
'Cause I'm a real charming guy,
a lot of people say that.
Of course I'd prefer if
the charm worked on you.
- Did you really get
the license plates?
- Oh, hm-- the--the plates?
- The plates, cool?
- Oh. Oh!
- Some things never change.
- Yeah.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, what are--
what are you doing?
- Yeah, I need a ride to work.
- How did you get here?
- I walked.
- Well, then walk back.
- Come on, Charli, these--
these ain't my walking shoes.
They're my dancing shoes.
- Get in.
- Girl, let me ask you
a question.
- What?
- No, never mind, forget it.
- That's so typical of you.
I know your game.
Play the card,
put it on the table.
- No, no, no, no, talking about
what ed has over me
is not my idea of witty banter
or--or stimulating conversation.
I'll take the card back,
forget it.
- Really?
Yes, that's just so typical,
that's so you, you know?
You make the rules
and only you can break them.
Hypocrisy at its finest.
Go ahead, just say it.
- No, let's move on
to something else, man.
You know, you look beautiful
today, let's talk about that.
- Fuck off.
- [Laughs]
- Reggie, this may be your last
chance to say anything to me.
Just say it, Reggie.
- The only reason why I knew
it was you the other day
was 'cause of your eyes,
not 'cause of your smile.
- You're definitely
getting better.
- What?
I'm serious, this is not an act.
- I'm stressed, ok?
I mean, I'm planning a wedding.
I'll be the happiest woman
when tomorrow,
I walk down that aisle,
I meet ed down there
and I say, "I do," ok?
- Planning? You sure?
Show--show me some planning?
Let me see
your to do list, Charli.
Where's the Microsoft outlook?
Don't you got a BlackBerry
or something like that?
How about a post-it note,
for god's sake?
We are chilling on the side
of the road
in a car
that has just stopped.
What exactly
are you planning here?
- My mother's doing
all the planning so--
- oh, boy, everybody loves
big momma.
- What is that about?
- Come on, you know
she never liked me.
- You're right. She's good
with that kind of stuff.
- Ha ha ha.
- There's not much left to do
anyway.
Just double check on the flowers
and show up, that's it.
- Show up to marry
the wrong guy, if you ask me.
If you don't see that, I don't
know what the fuck is wrong with
you, Charli. Damn.
- You know what, Reggie,
you know,
there's no need for you
to be disrespecting me.
Just get out of the car.
Get out of the car.
- Come--
- it was a bad idea, get out.
- Come on, Charli.
- Reggie, get out.
- You know, fine, fine, fine,
I'm going, I'm going.
You know, you wanna go home to
your little fake-ass
thurgood Marshall,
you know, do that, he doesn't
know you like I do anyway.
Man, you're being stupid.
- Fine!
- Ow!
- Then that's what I am.
Get out of my car.
- Well, I am going.
- I can't fucking take
your shit anymore.
- I ain't stupid.
- Stupid!
- So how do you get out
of this motherfucker?
Get some power locks.
[Engine splutters]
- Charli: Oh, come on, come on.
[Musical tone]
[Engine splutters]
What the f--
I told you to leave.
- No, no I'm not going anywhere.
Just watch out.
- Why do you have to be pushing
me all the time?
- Just--woman.
See cause the re--
'cause this thing, when you--
no, but then sometimes on the
car, like this, you need to get
under--
I don't know what-- I don't know
what I'm doing.
- Of course.
- Come on, Charli,
let me just spend
this last afternoon
with you, huh?
- No.
- Come on, look, I know
I can't have anything more.
I can't possibly have
anything less
than how it stands now.
Come on, let me just go into
the city with you
and help you out with all
the wedding things
if you need it.
- You're gonna help me
with my wedding plans?
- Yeah.
I'm man enough to do that.
You can even call big momma
and tell her
who helped you with everything.
Look, I'm sorry about
the comment in the car.
It was rude.
- Yeah, I don't know, Reggie.
- You know me, don't you?
- That's why I say that
I don't-- I don't know, i--
- look, I would do a lot of
things
but what I won't do is
disrespect your relationship.
Unless, of course,
you ask me to.
What do you say?
Jersey transit?
[Musical tone]
- I can't make up my mind
about these flowers.
- Mmm. Some may
call that a sign.
- This is it, ok?
What do you think?
- You really wanna know?
I think it's really too late
to change anything, Charli.
You gotta marry the dude.
- I'm not asking you that.
- No, I was just joking.
No, seriously though,
I think simple is better.
Love is simple, right?
- Yeah.
- Get your favorite color
and nothing else.
- Get red.
- I love red.
All right. Hi?
- Hi?
- I'm driving you crazy here.
So, ok.
- Yeah.
- I have 75 of these setting
ordered for tomorrow, right?
- And how is that looking?
- It looks good, but you don't.
- Oh.
- Relax.
Girl, come on,
you getting married.
Jump on the broom.
You two look like
such a good couple.
Ye-- aww.
Hey, can I get a bouquet
of those for the missus?
- All right.
- Wow.
Congratulations on the wedding.
A whole lot of shopping for
three very, very, small bags.
Oh, I don't--i don't--
- no,
- you said you were man enough
to handle this.
- Yeah, I know-- woman,
I know what I said.
The roses smell good.
- You wanna go somewhere to eat?
- No--problem.
- Can you hold my bags?
- Uh--
- do you have a choice?
- Not really.
I'm looking real masculine
right now
with these purple bags,
thank you.
- And with the flowers too.
Anyway, come on.
I hope you didn't mind the
street meat.
- Street meat?
- Yeah. You know, hot dogs,
kebabs, gyros,
anything you get
on the street.
Meat from the street,
street meat.
A term of endearment, comes
before a little worry once you
get--
catch a bad batch.
- It's not half as bad.
- Mmm, what?
Street meat or me?
- The street meat.
- Ha ha ha. Thanks.
What is that--
- hey, cool?
How you doing?
- Hey? Hey!
- Farrah, how you doing?
- Good.
- Yeah, Farrah,
this is, uh, this is Charli,
Charli, this is Farrah.
- Hey.
You're here for the callback,
right?
- Ah, yes,
yes, I'm here for the callback.
- You too?
- Just booked what about US.
- Wow, hey, congratulations.
That's, that's good.
- Yeah. Thanks for the well
wishes.
- No, really, it's good news.
It's just been kind of
a crazy day, that's all.
Check it out,
you think they still up there?
- They were packing up
when I was leaving, so, well--
I think I'm gonna go.
- Hey, just--congratulations,
for real this time.
I'm proud of you.
Ok, uh, look.
I have this really big audition,
it just so happens to be boom!
Right here in this building
where we're sitting in front of.
I mean, I was supposed to be
here a couple of hours ago.
- Oh, wow.
Because of me,
you didn't get here on time?
What? You wasted two hours
on little old me?
- Come on, babe.
- Don't babe me.
- Now, listen, we, we were
walking down the street,
enjoying the street meat,
it was good, delicious,
it was delectable, right?
And then, pow!
Let's just walk into the lobby,
we can discuss it in there.
If anything, the audition
might be over.
- Ok.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I knew you'd understand,
that's why you're who you are.
I hope they're still there.
I really need this job, Charli.
- You blew it.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- Man, come on.
- You're kidding, right?
I know I'm running late, man,
I just, I ran into a couple of
things.
- Yeah, I see.
- No, he was--
my car broke down, all right?
And, and--he--he was just trying
to help me fix it.
That's why he was late.
- Ok.
Well, you've got the bags,
you've got the roses,
good luck with your career.
- This, this is my life, Charli,
this here is my story.
Why are you walking away?
Don't walk away from me.
- Why not, huh?
- Just let me talk to you
for a second.
- You don't wanna hear
what I have to say.
- What, are you gonna
tell me tomorrow?
- As much as I care about
what you're going through,
I'm not gonna offer you
a shoulder to lean on.
Ok?
Because for once,
I'm gonna be the selfish one.
Go find somebody else because
I'm gonna think about myself.
For once, Reggie,
that's all you had to do.
All you had to do
was think about me.
You can't do this anymore,
you have to stop,
you have to leave me alone.
- I can't, I can't, Charli.
Look, I've fallen in love
with you for the second time.
You know what? I never fell out
of love with you
the first time when I walked
you home from school
and you slipped
on that ice patch.
This is life, this right here is
the illest movie that there is,
except there's no credits
to walk out on.
No--no script, no--no rehearsal,
just raw emotion.
Which you never got from me
when we were together because--
I was too afraid to take
the armor off.
I love you, Charli,
you can't tell me
that you don't love me.
You can't tell me that.
- No, I can't tell you that.
And you can't expect US
to be good
only because, all of a sudden,
you've found the softness
that it takes to be
a fucking man, Reggie.
You just can't do that.
- Cool: We're not through,
Charli.
- Excuse me.
[Engine spluttering]
[Engine starts]
Charli: I'll drive you
to the station.
- Thank you.
- Where's Derrick?
- He had an emergency.
He left five hours ago.
What you acting all upset about?
I haven't even told you
the good news yet.
- What's that?
- You're fired.
Well, you act like your name's
not on the schedule.
I'm just trying to make it
a reality for you.
- Don't you want me
to pay you back?
- Oh, you will.
Every last cent.
But where you get the money
from, that's on you.
- So it's just like that?
- It is that.
Mm-hm. You're free to go.
See you around.
Do you wanna come in?
[Man on TV] From the face-off,
back to the corner,
makes a shot--
- You know, I don't--
I don't do too much of this.
- I know you don't,
it's just in case.
- You can't stay long anyway.
- Man on TV: Hope you come back
tomorrow.
- Where is he?
- Bachelor party.
Ah! What is this?
..Ordinary burgers
just can't satisfy
the modern-day black man.
We likes our food to have that
extra large flavor, baby.
That's why,
here at burger Jester,
we have a commitment to beef.
I don't wanna watch this.
What you got to listen to?
Word. You still have this?
Does ed know how you feel
when you listen to this song?
♪ Can't nobody love you
like I'm loving you, baby ♪
♪ 'cause they don't know how
one last dance?
♪ To love you like I do
♪ oh, mmmm
- only cause you look like
a sad puppy in the rain.
♪ Like I'm loving you, baby
♪ 'cause they don't know how
to love you like I do ♪
♪ I'm gonna love you
in the morning ♪
♪ love you late at night
♪ girl, I ain't gonna stop
loving you ♪
♪ till you tell me everything's
all right ♪
♪ everything's all right
♪ ooh
♪ can't nobody love you
like I'm loving you right now ♪
♪ 'cause they don't know how to
love you like I do ♪
♪ and, oh, oh, oh,
can't nobody kiss you ♪
♪ can't nobody kiss you
♪ like I'm kissing you,
little girl ♪
♪ 'cause they don't know
how to kiss you like I do ♪
♪ no, they don't know how
to love you ♪
♪ like I do
- Charli,
Why isn't this our wedding?
- We shouldn't have done that.
- If you tell me right now
that you love him
more than you love me,
I'll go, no questions.
- Reggie, it's not that simple.
- It is that simple.
- You think--you think
only--only with love,
two people can--can make it?
- What is it about this guy?
What does he have that I don't
have?
- He's just-- he's consistent.
He gives me a happiness.
He notices if I've--
if I've cut my hair.
He wants to have a family,
therefore he works hard for it
and we're moving to a home
and we're doing it right.
- You're doing it typical,
a house, a car,
all--these things
come with time.
Why does he get this
and I don't?
- He can be a good father.
- You don't know what kind of
father I could have been.
You left.
- Baby? Hey!
- Ed.
- Look,
I was just about to leave, man.
- Is there something
you wanna tell me?
I can jump to conclusions
real quick
but I'm trying to be an adult
about this right now.
I'm trying real hard.
- Just relax, she loves you,
you'll be a great father.
- Reggie?
This is Reggie?
You two sat up in my house,
at my table,
and lied to my face?
- Ed, ed, it's not--
it's not what you think.
Baby, no, it's-- it's--
it was my mistake.
- Oh, no, no, I'm just looking
at the evidence, all right?
- Oh, no, no,
you have to trust me on this.
I'm very sorry, ok?
- Charli, Charli, come on,
Charli. Come on.
It's my fault, man.
- Oh, no, no, this is between
me and her.
Not you or whoever
you're pretending to be today.
All right? So just get the hell
out of my house.
- Don't touch me, man.
- Hey, man.
I'm not gonna ask you again,
let's go.
Get out of my house, man!
- No! No!
- This is my house.
- Ed, stop it!
What are you doing?
Ed, stop it!
You have to go.
- This is how the story ends?
- Yes.
- The story?
I haven't hit anybody
since golden gloves.
- There aren't enough words
for me to apologize.
- Hey, you're right about that.
You are right about that.
- I'm very sorry,
I can't tell you enough.
- Yeah, and what am I supposed
to do?
What?
Believe you with the same, uh--
same trust now,
with the same ease now,
- with the same anything?
- Yes, of course.
- Oh, of course, of course.
Yeah.
- Ed, what are you doing?
- Uh, exactly, what am I doing?
You, on the couch,
not me, go.
- No.
- The couch.
- Do you still wanna do this?
- I'm gonna sleep on it.
- You're gonna sleep on it?
- Yes.
- We're getting married
in less than ten hours, ed.
- Then you should have thought
about that
for the last ten hours
you spent with that dude.
Huh?
What about those ten hours?
- If you don't want this, what
are we gonna tell everybody?
- I'm not telling anybody shit.
If we don't do this, you're
gonna tell them the truth.
You're gonna tell them
what you did.
- [Sobs]
- I love you.
- I love you too, Charli.
That hasn't changed.
But I'm gonna go to bed.
[Knock]
- Cool's mother:
Come and get it, bubba.
- Good morning.
- Have a seat.
- How was the wedding?
- I don't know,
I cooked the food
but I couldn't stay there
for that.
Hm.
- Uh--amen.
- [Both] Amen.
- Um, you can work
at the station for as long
as you need to or want to.
- All right, thanks.
- Uh--
uh--
sometimes, love takes
a long time to work itself out.
- What are you saying to me,
man?
- No, no, no, I'm not
talking about me and you,
I'm talking about US.
I've known your mother
for 30 years.
- Ma, you cheated on dad?
- No.
- What are you saying?
- No, no, no, no.
- Whoa, this is not going
as smoothly as I planned.
Let's just hop right to it.
What I'm saying this morning is,
people marry the wrong people
all the time.
- And it's no different
with Charli
that it was with me
and your father.
Baby, if it's true
and if it's right,
love will find its way home.
- Yeah.
- Now, I know the last few days
have been hard on you.
But I have something
to tell you.
- Oh, no, come on, y'all,
I'm in a real--
fragile place right now
I don't need to hear
any more bad news.
- I've asked your mother
to marry me.
- And I've accepted.
- Congratulations.
Yeah, yeah, congratulations.
- Yeah, you know, that thing
you do with the feathers.
Yeah.
Listen, uh, sweetie, I gotta go.
Gotta go. Right.
[Purrs] Bye.
How are you?
- I'm still standing.
- Ah.
- Do you have anything for me?
- I have some advice for you.
Come here, have a seat.
Come on.
I may not look like you
or talk like you,
fortunately I don't have
your attitude,
but I have been
in your shoes before.
It's all gonna work out.
It's all gonna work out
if you stay out of your own way.
- That's it?
- That's it.
That one's free,
I got something else for you.
- Please don't let it be
a bullshit audition.
I will quit the business before
I do another bullshit audition.
Matter of fact, I was thinking
about writing a screenplay
about my own life.
- Slow down, Waldo salt,
get out of my chair.
Out, out, come on,
come on, come on.
For your information,
I have to let you know
that chatmon has a part in
what about US.
That he wants to offer to you.
- The lead?
- A part.
He wrote a very small role
into the script.
It's take it or leave it,
they need to know today,
- what do you say?
- Yes.
- Yes?
- You're sure, 'cause remember,
a minute ago,
you were--you were embarking on
that writing career?
- Yes.
I want the part, yes.
- Hey, now, now.
- All right!
- Yeah!
Man, what you got for me?
Make my day.
- We've got your phone bill,
the visa,
playboy magazine.
- Men's entertainment.
- As they say.
- Yes!
- And, hold on, what's this?
You have a good day now.
- Yeah.
Man: And cut.
Ok, I think we've got
everything we need.
- Good work, baby.
- Oh, thank you.
- You look good.
- I'm trying to give it
a little character,
so I can be remembered.
- What's up?
Who are you?
- I'm darrel.
- Darrel?
- Yeah.
- Oh, well, darrel,
don't ever think
that this isn't a great job.
And no matter what, always show
up on time, you got me?
Yeah.
- How long you been working
here, man?
- A year. I came here
right after you left.
That's what big Phil told me.
- You know who I am?
- Of course I know who you are,
everyone around here knows who
you are.
You're cool, man.
I'm darrel,
Derrick's my cousin.
- [Laughs] Hey, cool.
- What's up, Phil?
How you doing, man?
- Oh, man, as you can see,
same old station.
Gas, cars, cars, gas.
- [Laughs]
- We've been through quite
a few mechanics though.
Hard to keep a quality guy.
But the kid on the pump,
he is good.
Never breaks the rules,
always on time.
- You hired Derrick's cousin?
- Derrick's a good kid.
I just couldn't have all that
mess brewing around the station.
- Oh, yeah, like fraud.
Yeah, I see that.
- Yeah, fraud.
- You should watch out,
it might run in the family.
- Yeah, well, I would have
helped the kid if he'd only
asked.
[Bell]
- Hello, ma'am?
- Ma'am? Wow. You do that.
I mean, you're trying
to be polite, but no.
Just fill it up, ok? Premium.
- Ok.
- Here is the final
tuition repayment.
Just get a big-screen TV
in your new house.
On me.
- Wow.
- Well, you've been taking good
care of my mom too. I mean that.
- Look, you, uh--do you have
furniture for your place?
- Yeah. Yeah, you know, a little
something something.
I'm just happy to be in
a new place with no mice.
- Oh!
- For a change, you know?
It's just that I work so much
it's like I'm rarely ever there.
- Yeah.
- That's ok, though.
- Yeah, it's, uh-- yeah.
- Yeah.
Which reminds me,
yeah, I got a--
I got an appointment in an hour.
I gotta get out of here.
- Oh, that's cool.
You take care, son.
- Fill her up?
Yeah.
- Hey.
- I saw your film.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
- Yeah, well I mean, I wouldn't
really call it my film,
being as I was only on screen
for, like, 48 seconds.
- Come on,
it was good, it was good.
- Thank you.
No, no, no, come on.
- [Sighs]
Ok.
- We learnt a lot that day.
Is matrimony as holy
as they say it is?
- We didn't get married.
I've thought about you.
I feel like I should be able
to say that I didn't, but--
- I've thought about you too,
I'm not afraid to admit it.
What are you--
what are you up to right now?
- Come on, cool.
- No, it's just, you know,
I miss you sometimes,
that's all.
Well--
you look good up on that screen.
- Yeah? Thank you.
- Look, um--
I don't know, you know,
just in case, you know?
You never know.
Maybe we'll run into
each other sometime.
And my mother always said
you were the one.
- Bye.
- Is everything ok?
- Light's green, baby.
♪ Oh, what's your story?
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, life is
a stage, so play your part ♪
♪ step on stage
right from the start ♪
♪ everybody out there
got a role to play ♪
♪ take my advice,
hear what I say ♪
♪ some might have it,
some might not ♪
♪ you gotta be clever
about what you got ♪
♪ you got a little,
you got a lot ♪
♪ some get stabbed
and some get shot ♪
♪ as time goes on,
some things will change ♪
♪ your age, your weight,
your face, your name ♪
♪ as life goes on,
you'll change your mind ♪
♪ you'll seek some light
where you were blind ♪
♪ it's all just a part
of the game we play ♪
♪ so don't play a hit
like the players say ♪
♪ some win, some lose,
hey, that's ok ♪
♪ the game is the same
when the players play ♪
♪ ooh,
do you know what you are? ♪
♪ Oh, what's your story?
♪ Ooh,
do you know what you are? ♪
♪ Oh, what's your story?
♪ Ooh,
do you know what you are? ♪
♪ Oh, what's your story?
♪ Ooh,
do you know what you are? ♪
♪ Look about it,
your bet last night was right ♪
♪ you only caught US out 'cause
your pants were tight ♪
♪ how many times
have you played the game? ♪
♪ Same old line,
"baby, what's your name?" ♪
♪ heinous play
on the court before ♪
♪ and he'll do a fortune
in a court of law ♪
♪ the very same guy
that's with your friend ♪
♪ but you just wanna ride
in his benz ♪
♪ think you're playing him
but you're not ♪
♪ 'cause he's trying
to get what you got ♪
♪ you get some jewellery
and some cash ♪
♪ and you foolishly
giving up the act ♪
♪ take what he got,
he got the bug ♪
♪ think what you did,
you get the nuts ♪
♪ it's all just a part
of the game we play ♪
♪ when you see those players
just walk away ♪
♪ ooh,
do you know what you are? ♪
♪ Oh, what's your story?
♪ Ooh,
do you know what you are? ♪
♪ Oh, what's your story?
♪ Ooh,
do you know what you are? ♪
♪ Oh, what's your story?
♪ Ooh,
do you know what you are? ♪
♪ this is what I'm saying
♪ everybody plays
the pool sometime ♪
♪ but sometimes
that's not cool ♪
♪ everybody wanna be cool
♪ everybody can't be cool
♪ play the game,
don't break the rules ♪
♪ learn a little something like
you learned at school ♪
♪ listen to what
I'm saying to you ♪
♪ 'cause I do the things
real cool people do ♪
♪ hey, my tools, they say
be part of the crowd ♪
♪ I try to run
this for real ♪
♪ they say I'm being too proud
♪ and when I roll
with the punches ♪
♪ I get knocked on the ground
♪ by all this bullshit
going down ♪
♪ do you know? Do you know?
♪ Do you know what you are?
♪ oh, what's your story?
♪ Who you are?
♪ Who are you?
♪ do you know?
♪ oh, what's your story?
♪ Do you know who you are?
Who you are? ♪
♪ Do you know?
♪ oh, what's your story?