Subtitles by explosiveskull
- [girl] Beth, is it on?
- [Beth] We're rolling.
[girl] Places, guys.
This one's for real.
"For centuries, the dark hand of Narash has
been spreading across the borderlands,
ruling with blood
and necromancy.
Are you the chosen one to challenge
him, to crush his bones into dust,
and pry out his innards
with the tip of your sword?"
- [Meg] Beth, film me.
- [hisses]
[Beth] Meg, you look like a boy.
[giggles]
- Yes! I am the...
- That's my part.
I just wanted to make
sure you did it right.
This is the pivotal point
for your character.
- Just let me do it my way.
- But I'm the director.
- [Beth] Hi, Amy.
- [giggles]
- [Meg] Okay, fine.
- [Beth] Try it again.
"I am the rightful paladin. Tell me my path,
Lord Gillian, I shall fulfill my prophecy."
"You must travel beyond
the catacombs of Eryx,
through the valley of Guell,
and climb the denizen steps
where no human has dared
to venture."
"Ever dared to venture, yet."
Uh, it's more like:
"Ever dared to venture, yet!"
In order to continue,
you must offer
sacrifice to Rian,
a dark fairy
of the Killian order.
"You must bring me
the dragon scale relic
of the forgotten droids."
- [giggles]
- Druids!
Whatever.
- "Do you accept?"
- "I am not afraid."
She turned and said farewell,
floating bravely forth,
on her long, unknown journey,
far away.
- End book one.
- [girls clapping]
[Beth] Hey, Jo,
do the epilogue!
But we've heard it
a million times!
It's my favorite part.
The people have spoken.
[sighs]
[Jo] It is not enough for the brave
heroine to desire greatness.
No, even the lowliest serf in the
kingdom may desire greatness.
For our heroine to succeed,
she must demand greatness.
To snatch it
from the powers that be
and wave it over the parapet
for all to see.
To prove
that she is their queen,
and the magnificent rightful
heir to her birthright.
[sighs]
Uh, well,
thank you, Josephine.
Oh, it's just Jo.
You certainly gave us
an entertaining read.
- [chuckles]
- [scoffs]
Uh, listen,
it's not my taste per se,
but I could see how it
could appeal to others.
- What are you going for? Young adult fantasy?
- Uh, no.
It can't be Y.A.
There's no love story.
- It's not a love story.
- Then it's definitely a pass for me.
- [Clarkson] Yeah, it's a pass for me as well.
- [Henry] Me too, sweetie.
You have a very creative mind.
But, there's something
missing in the authenticity.
I can't hear your voice.
It's not about me!
All the same,
it's still gonna be a pass.
Professor?
Yeah, it's a pass
from me as well.
Thanks.
No, thank you.
Really I...
I appreciate you judging
my artistic aptitude
on three pages
of my 400-page novel.
Thank you.
[rhythmic tapping]
[man singing gospel]
♪ Mmm ♪
- ♪ Lord can you give me ♪
- ♪ Mmm ♪
- ♪ A little bit of grace ♪
- [sighs]
- ♪ Mmm ♪
- ♪ Oh, can you hear me? ♪
♪ It's been one of those days ♪
- ♪ Mmm ♪
- ♪ So I'll be waiting Down by the riverbanks ♪
- ♪ You know I'll be praying So please don't delay ♪
- ♪ Mmm ♪
- ♪ Oh, please don't delay ♪
[sighs]
Hurry up!
The lava's rising.
[woman] Is there any way you could
give me a one-time extension?
- I promise, it won't happen again.
- My earring!
Leave it! No! She just
spontaneously combusted!
- We have to move on.
- Oh, come on.
Jo!
She chose her fate.
We are not
going without her.
[woman] Is there any way
you could reverse the fee?
- Apollyon!
- [woman] Yes?
[girls calling]
Apollyon!
[woman] I'm sorry.
Can you just hold?
- [phone beeps]
- I am here!
From whence come you,
and whither are you bound?
We have traveled
from the city of desolation
- through the fires of purgatory, fighting beasts of the night.
- [gasps]
- We seek access to the city of Zion.
- Ooh. Hmm.
You may release
your burdens.
But you must each sacrifice
one valuable to the altar.
But choose carefully.
Be not selfish!
Whatever you select
must be of great value.
Good. Yes.
- Hair?
- It's valuable to me.
Hmm.
Your castles await you.
- Go!
- [Jo] Except for Amy.
- [phone beeps]
- Oh.
- Hey!
- Oh. Ah.
Hello? Thanks for holding.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, let me in!
- [knocking]
- No! You cheated!
You don't deserve
to be in the castle!
- Just let her in.
- [Jo] She has to play by the rules!
- [Amy knocking]
- It's just a game.
- Let me in!
- [Jo] It's not a game to me!
- Let her in.
- [sighs]
- All my sisters are allowed in my castle.
[Meg] Mine too.
- Oh, my goodness.
- This is so cool.
Mine's pink!
"Welcome to your castles
in the air.
Fill them wisely.
Love Marmee."
[gasps]
- Jo, what's in your castle?
- [Jo] Well, I want a lot of things.
- I, Jo March...
- [older Jo] I, Jo March...
I, Jo March... I'll get out of this
town and move to the big city.
I, Jo March, will be a
very successful writer
and will buy a big house in the
city so we can all live together.
[Meg] I don't want to
live with you forever!
I want to get married
and have kids and...
And have a nanny,
and a maid, and... a butler!
- [Jo] Amy, that's stupid.
- [Meg] Hey, you can't judge other people's castles.
[Jo] Fine.
Then I change the rules of mine.
Only Beth and I are
allowed in my castle.
[Amy] Hey!
I, Jo March, will be
a very successful writer,
and will visit
every single country
and eat out
every single meal.
Oh, and I will see every play and
musical and opera ever written.
Or will be written
ever.
[Beth]
I think that's too long.
I, Jo March, will be a very
successful writer and will...
do
all the things.
[Amy] My turn.
I, Amy March, will be...
a rich and famous painter
so I can...
buy whatever I want
and go wherever I want.
[Beth giggles]
Amy.
I, Margaret March, will have
a family of my own,
and, um, just be...
well, happy.
[Jo] And?
[Meg] And nothing.
- Beth?
- [young Beth] I, Elizabeth March...
I, Elizabeth March...
[laughs]
I don't know what to say.
[Jo] Just... think about what you
want to be when you grow up.
[Beth]
Well, I think this is my castle.
- The attic?
- Just being here with all of you.
[Jo] Okay, Beth.
Yeah, that's really sweet.
We'll take it.
- [giggling]
- Let's make an oath.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
[Jo] All right.
[sighs]
To always help each other
reach our castles.
No matter
where they may be.
[sighs]
[kisses]
- [men murmuring]
- [Freddy] "Everybody gets a prize" mentality.
- [Henry] My principles could be...
- [Freddy] No. Not everybody wins.
Hey, excuse me!
Excuse me.
- Professor Bhaer.
- Oh, dear.
Hey!
- It's dragon lady.
- Professor Bhaer!
- Good luck with that.
- I need to talk to you.
Just Jo, with the
fantasy novel, right?
It's a high-fantasy
mythopoeic fable.
Sorry I'm not more
familiar with that genre.
Yeah, neither was your panel
of patriarchs in there.
Which, you know, I might expect
from some of those hacks,
but not from you.
Not from someone
with your résumé.
It doesn't matter.
I will find my audience,
no thanks to Columbia or Hooton
Muffin or however you say it.
- I'm sure you will.
- You probably didn't even understand that the protagonist
- is actually a girl who dresses up as a boy.
- I didn't.
And when I was growing up,
I dressed up as a boy.
I was inspired by my
"authentic self," you see?
I really think you would have understood
that and possibly even enjoyed it a little,
had you heard more than
a measly three-minute reading
in a synthetic,
almost hostile environment,
where the critiques were really more
about subjective capitalistic conjecture
than a chance for writers
to be discovered.
I'd be happy to read
more of your novel.
You would?
Oh, yes! Thank you!
I've been wanting anyone...
everyone... to read it.
Besides my sister.
Freddy, by the way.
Freddy Bhaer.
Here. Contact info,
title page.
E-mail would have been fine.
No.
You have to hold the words,
let them seep into your skin.
All right.
I'll be expecting your call.
[sighs]
[horns honking]
- [machine beeps]
- Hey, it's Freddy. I'm just, uh, checking in.
I haven't heard from you. I know
that notes can be overwhelming.
Keep your chin up.
- Let me know when you have another draft.
- [beeps]
[vibrating]
Josephine? Good heavens, child. It
smells like a Turkish bath in here.
[sighs]
If you're going to quarantine yourself
in this room for weeks on end,
the least you could do
is crack a window.
The least you could do
is knock.
Oh, I'm your employer,
and I'm supposed to knock?
How very millennial of you.
Dinner's at 6:00.
- I don't want her to starve
- [growls]
while you escape into
your Neverwood Forest
or whatever
you're scribbling about.
I will do my best.
Well, I sure hope
that's enough.
Love you too,
Aunt March.
[sighs]
Honey, it's Mom, just wanting
to know how your meetings went.
So exciting. I bet they were busy fighting over
who gets to publish Concord's own Jo March.
[chuckles] Anyway, I
know you're busy,
but just check in and let us know when
you're coming home for Christm... [beeps]
[Amy] This is going to be
the worst Christmas ever.
All my friends at school
get a whole pile of presents,
and we get nothing.
Well, we each get one gift, and
that's more than most people get.
You want to know
what I asked for?
Do not say a bra.
New paintbrushes!
[Jo] There he is again!
[wind howling]
[Meg] I heard he just
moved here from Europe.
Maybe he was forced
to move here,
after stowing away on
the Trans-Siberian railroad.
Marmee said his parents
just died in a car accident.
He doesn't
have any siblings,
- so now he has to live with his grandfather.
- How sad.
He's kind of cute, though.
I mean,
I guess, for an old guy.
[laughing]
I don't think I could
ever live in that creepy house.
Mr. Laurence is so scary.
Oh, maybe Mr. Laurence
isn't his grandfather.
He's the new kid's
vampire mentor,
and he's trying to tame
his ravishing appetite.
- Wait, that is really good.
- [chuckles]
We should do something
nice for them.
- Maybe we could bake them something.
- [Amy] Yes!
[gasps]
[on radio]
♪ Angels we have heard on high ♪
Ooh.
Amy, let's wait till
everyone gets here, okay?
But I'm starving!
You continue to use
that word incorrectly.
- You know what I mean.
- Actually, I don't.
- Shut up, Jo.
- [Marmee] Good morning!
Oh, it smells like Christmas
in here.
- You're back!
- How was the shelter?
- [Marmee] Well...
- There were so many people there,
we didn't have enough
food for everyone.
See Amy? Those
people are starving.
But not if
they like cupcakes.
- Oh!
- I'll grab my costumes.
We can do
the nativity musical!
Oh! No, no, no, no, no.
Not the cupcakes!
Can we just be
a normal family
and eat breakfast
and open presents at home?
- [knocks]
- I'll get that.
- Oh, hi.
- [Meg] Hi.
- Hey, hi.
- Hi.
- Oh!
- I think this one's yours.
Yeah.
- Thank you so much.
- There you go.
Fat ol' Goob
is always running away.
- Yeah.
- Dove? Where are you?
Dove? I thought
you called him Goob.
Oh, I'm Dove.
I mean, I'm Meg.
But my family...
That's what they call me.
I'm John Brooke. I live next
door with the Laurences.
- Oh.
- You don't look like a Laurence.
- This is my sister, Jo.
- Yeah, I'm just a family friend of the Laurences.
Mr. Laurence hired me to tutor his
grandson. Math, music and whatever else.
- That's nice.
- So the new kid has a manny.
Nope. Just a tutor.
Right. Okay, yeah.
Well, uh, we have to go
help some poor people.
- Oh.
- So we'll catch you later.
Merry Christmas.
- Mm, bye!
- Merry Christmas.
- [man] Goob, buddy. Get off the computer.
- [Meg] Oops, sorry, Dad.
- Rascal.
- [meows]
- Come here, Goob.
- What do you got for me, Amy?
Okay. This one
is Marmee's favorite.
- Wow.
- She says it's very "ethetically" pleasing.
- Aesthetically.
- Aesthetically. [chuckles]
Well done. Amy, that's beautiful.
You're getting so good!
[chuckles]
Thank you.
- Did I show you this one?
- No. No, no, no. Your time is up!
- Jo.
- No.
Come on!
Time is up!
- Move.
- Hey, you guys.
Thank you.
Hi, Dad.
Okay, really quick question.
Uh, when you first cut into a
liver, is the blood that seeps out,
is it more crimson or maroon?
Writing a murder mystery,
are we?
- No, it's a post-apocalyptic zombie thriller.
- Whoa.
Uh, crimson, I would say.
But I only operate on humans.
- So I don't really know about zombie blood.
- Okay. Thank you.
All right, listen up, girls.
I only have a minute left.
Jo, I'm going to put you
in charge of the club this year.
So here's your marching orders.
[clears throat]
Your first assignment of the year will
be to write your grievances every week
and come up with a plan
as to how to fix them.
That way, you can be strong,
kind, independent little women
like your mother.
- Is that clear?
- Sir, yes, sir!
Good. At ease, soldiers.
I love you guys so much.
- Hey, where's my beautiful Marmee?
- Marmee!
- I need to see her one more time.
- Hi.
Ah, there she is.
Hi, Marmee.
- I love you so much.
- [girls] Love you, Dad!
Merry Christmas, you guys.
I miss you so much.
I'll think about you every day.
I promise.
[all]
Merry Christmas, Dad!
- Take care of your mom. I love you.
- [Meg] Always.
Bye.
[all sigh]
Fifteen! Sixteen! Seventeen!
Say it with me, ladies!
[all]
Eighteen! Nineteen! Twenty!
All right. [blows whistle]
Fall in, soldiers!
As Staff Sergeant
of the Pickwick Club,
I request a read of the earthly
grievances of each of our members
as requested
by our commander-in-chief.
- Staff Sergeant Snodgrass.
- [clears throat]
Your clothes and notebooks are everywhere
and when asked to clean it up,
you launched an airborne Cabbage
Patch at Private Winkle's head!
You're lucky
that you missed.
With all due respect,
who's the lucky one?
- Soldier...
- Apologies, Private. Duly noted.
- [clears throat]
- Corporal Tupman.
Though we love
your feline companion,
we request that you fulfill
your kitty litter duties
and pick up the litter box since the stench
is considered to be highly offensive.
Can do, sir.
Private Winkle. It has been reported
that on multiple occasions,
you have stolen toilet paper
out of the latrine,
with the express purpose
of stuffing your shirt.
- [giggles]
- You are so mean!
On the contrary.
We wish only to help you enjoy
your youthful freedom,
for you will soon come to know the cumbersome
and unwieldy nature of a full chest.
- Like you would know.
- Private Winkle!
[sighs, clears throat]
General Pickwick!
It has been noted that you have
not visited the shelter all week
because of frequent flirtations
with the manny.
So you must go twice
next week.
Sir, yes, sir.
- [Aunt March] Josephine, what on earth is going on here?
- [dog whining]
Wha... Sorry. I'm... I'm just, uh... trying
to lay everything out, see everything.
I'm not talking about
your little story.
I'm talking about the fact that
Katinka's water bowl is bone dry,
and she pooped
in the entryway.
- Serious? I just took her out.
- When? Last Christmas?
- What am I paying you for?
- I'm sorry my life doesn't revolve around your dog.
Well, what does it revolve
around, exactly? Hmm?
Trolls? Dragons?
Cross-dressing pirates?
I don't mean
to hurt your feelings.
I'm just worried
about you is all.
Is this really the life you want?
The life of... insecurity?
Yes.
What if the professor
doesn't like this version
or the next?
- He will.
- I hate to see you working so hard
when it could all
come to nothing.
There's no shame
in changing your mind.
You're still...
youngish.
It's not too late to pursue something
with a little more promise in it.
I know it doesn't look
like much right now,
but you are going to be sorry
you ever doubted me.
I certainly hope so.
Just think about a
plan "B." [kisses]
- I knew it. You hate the new beginning.
- No.
I liked it.
A lot, actually.
But then I've always been a
fan of A Wrinkle in Time.
I am trying to get
inspired by the greats.
Isn't that what artists do?
Yes.
And then they tell
their own stories.
- Was it at least better than the last time you read it?
- It was.
But...
Am I a hopeless case?
Please just tell me now.
Save me the heartache.
You know, there are
other things I could do.
I do have
marketable skills.
I could be a nanny
till the day I croak.
I love books. I-I should be
an old spinster librarian
who reads saucy romance
novels under her desk.
I'm sure you'll
find time for both.
You are not helping!
I'm not your therapist.
I'm your editor.
I'm not going to pity an artist
for taking their stripes.
You signed up for this struggle the
moment you called yourself a writer.
I have a feeling you'd
be bored with anything less.
[sighs] You're good, Jo.
You're a good writer.
But now that I've gotten
to know you, as a person,
you are far more interesting
than what you write.
I want to be reading...
more of this.
More of you.
Me?
I am not
interesting!
Hell,
I'm 29 years old.
And I live alone in Queens while
I work for my great aunt.
I still haven't been to Europe.
I haven't been marooned
on a desert island.
I haven't been falsely
accused of murder.
I haven't even been
a victim of identify theft!
If... If my younger self
could see me now,
she'd straight up join a nunnery because
at least then her life would have purpose.
Actually,
that is not a bad idea.
Do nuns take old people
like me?
See? More of this.
Where are you going?
Thanks to you, I have a
whole new draft to start.
We could talk about something else. It
doesn't always have to be about your work.
I don't have time
to sit and chat.
If my muse
isn't going to visit me,
- I am going to find her and knock her dumb door down.
- [ladder rattles]
Maybe I can help.
- ['50s rock]
- [Amy] You guys...
My nose won't stop growing!
- I need a nose job.
- Take that ridiculous thing off.
You don't know what it's like to have
everyone else make fun of your nose.
What is it gonna be like when you cut off
your circulation and your nose falls off?
- You'd look like Voldemort.
- [Jo] Oh! That would be awesome.
- [chuckles]
- Why can't I go to the New Year's Eve party?
You can go to all the parties
you want when you're older.
For now, you can stay home and watch
the ball drop with Marmee and Beth.
- Does that sound like any fun to you?
- Yes.
It's not.
I'm the worst.
I always fall asleep
before midnight.
Yeah! You see what I mean?
Beth is so boring!
And I could care less
about watching a ball drop.
- [Beth] Couldn't care less.
- What's the difference?
Well, if you could care less, that means you
care a little bit about the ball dropping.
- I don't.
- Okay, look. I think you're lucky.
I would rather pass a kidney stone
than go to this freakin' party.
- You have to come with me. You promised.
- I'll go!
[all]
You're too young!
Can I at least
pick out your outfit?
No, I'm wearing this.
[Amy scoffs]
You'll never get a boyfriend.
- That's the plan.
- [hissing]
- I don't want a boyfriend. Boys are gross. I...
- What's that smell?
[gasps]
Jo!
- Are you kidding me?
- I'm sorry! You should have never let me do this!
- Meg, Meg, Meg.
- [Beth] Say "sorry"!
[Amy] You can just cover
it up with a headband.
You still look
so pretty.
It's not that bad,
is it?
- [all] No.
- [Amy] Not at all.
I don't like looking at
myself in the mirror.
Me neither.
You get used to it.
Jo, why don't you wear one too?
You can match Meg.
I'm not wearing
a stupid headband.
You don't even like Sally Moffat, and
her, like, giggly little brat pack.
- They're not that bad.
- They talk about the stupidest things.
And her brother always
gives me the weirdest looks.
Let's go get pizza instead
and say that we didn't.
Jo, listen.
I'm sick of being the weird
home-schooled sisters.
I want to make friends and go to
parties and talk to guys our own age.
Why?
Because I just do!
[sighs]
And I really need
you to be my wing woman.
[sighs] Wing woman
reporting for duty.
[squeals]
[hip-hop] ♪ It's Saturday night
And I'm feeling real good ♪
I am so glad you're here.
I have somebody that I have been
meaning to introduce you to.
You. Who are you?
And who do you know here?
Hi.
- Sorry!
- Excuse me.
[screams]
- Meg. This has to go.
- Hi.
And you
are coming with me.
Bye.
So much for
wing womaning.
♪ We tip 'em so big
So they serve what we wish ♪
♪ A good night
This is what it is ♪
♪ We just don't go out clubbing
First we cruising ♪
♪ And my boys I call 'em up ♪
♪ Tell 'em where we at
And what is up ♪
♪ It's Saturday night
And I'm feeling real good ♪
♪ Usually I be chilling
But tonight I feel like ♪
♪ I hit the club and get loose ♪
♪ Yeah, I feel good
And it's Saturday night ♪
♪ Everything going smooth ♪
♪ Gotta call my crew
'Cause tonight be the night ♪
♪ We hit the club
And get loose ♪
[muffled music]
- Sorry!
- Sorry.
Avoiding people?
- What?
- Me too.
I'm only here because my grandpa
thinks I need to make friends.
I guess when your grandpa thinks
you're a loner, you probably are.
So you're the infamous
Laurence grandson.
Infamous?
Well, my theory... was that you
were an international spy,
seeking refuge
in an inconspicuous town.
Well, you're right.
- And now you die.
- [grunts]
[chuckles]
I'm Jo.
Laurie.
Goody-goody, Meggy March.
Who let you
out of the henhouse?
[chanting] Drink! Drink!
Drink! Drink!
Whoo!
- Come on. It's not gonna kill you!
- I'll do it.
You speak French?
I had to.
I lived there for three years.
No way. You have to
tell me all about it!
I'm going to Paris
after college.
I'm gonna do
all the things.
It's pretty much just like anywhere else.
It's just... more French.
Well, it's definitely
not as boring as here.
Here's not so bad.
So far at least.
I cannot wait
to leave this place.
I have two years
till I go to Oxford.
I'm a novelist
and a playwright.
I'm going to be very
successful and very rich.
Not like filthy rich
like you and your grandpa,
but just rich enough that I buy a
house in Europe and bring my sisters
and pay for everything.
Wow, sounds like
you've got it all figured out.
♪ Stay in the zone
Where I'm just me, girl ♪
♪ Super faded Sometimes
I feel Like I made it ♪
♪ Nine clouds high
Wave good-bye ♪
♪ Goin' to a world where
You're my girl and ♪
[hip-hop continues]
Ferdinand doesn't want to go into the
jungle until she has both of her legs,
- so she has to wait until the curse is lifted.
- Naturally.
But the thing
that she doesn't know
is that she actually has to get
to the edge of the jungle
for the curse to be lifted!
- See, so it's this whole Catch-22 thing.
- [song changes]
Wait, wait, wait.
I love this song!
- Come on!
- Wait! What?
♪ Baby, don't fight ♪
♪ I want to see you
Move tonight ♪
♪ Turn out the lights ♪
♪ Dancing is a human right ♪
♪ Baby, don't fight ♪
♪ I want to see you
Move tonight ♪
♪ Turn out the lights ♪
♪ Dancing is a human right ♪
[clapping]
[grunts]
Meg March.
I haven't seen you
since, like, kindergarten.
You're, like,
really hot now.
- Are you on Myspace?
- Mm, no.
[gasps]
[crowd laughing]
Uh, are you okay?
♪ Baby, don't fight ♪
♪ I want to see you
Move tonight ♪
♪ Turn out the lights ♪
♪ Dancing is a human right ♪
♪ Baby, don't fight ♪
♪ I want to see you
Move tonight ♪
♪ Turn out the lights ♪
♪ Dancing is a human right ♪
[Jo] Meg, seriously, no one is even
going to remember like, next week.
Wasn't it kind of
a little fun?
I don't know if I see any dancing
going on back there. Come on now.
How could you not
dance to this?
- [hip-hop]
- [shouting, indistinct]
- [music continues]
- Hat time, Megan.
- [laughs]
- [Laurie] Right on point!
- I know. I know.
- [Laurie] I'm feelin' it.
[Marmee] Thank you so much
for taking care of my girls.
My pleasure. It's nice
to finally meet you.
Yeah. You can
call me Marmee.
- And this here is Amy.
- Hello, Amy.
Amy, Laurie.
Uh, um.
[chuckles]
I'm sorry. My hair's
a mess right now.
- I was braiding it.
- I'm actually kind of digging the one-sided thing.
You could start a trend
with that.
- [Marmee] That's Beth.
- Hey, Beth.
[Jo] Don't worry, Beth.
He's a good egg.
Promise.
Is that a guitar
I see over there?
- You mind if I, uh...
- No, of course not.
I mean, it might be
way out of tune.
I'm tryin' to impress my new neighbors.
You mind helpin' me out?
- All right.
- So, we're gonna have a concert?
Let's see.
[strums, in tune]
Hey, we're in luck.
♪ Can't see the sign ♪
♪ It's seven below ♪
♪ Can't go to class
Stuck in the snow ♪
♪ I've got my coat
I've got my pride ♪
♪ Nothin's gonna stop me
From goin' outside ♪
♪ It don't take much
To melt the snow ♪
♪ Just let the sunshine glow ♪
♪ I wanna sing
With the band in my head ♪
♪ And I'll scream Till
you've heard What I said ♪
♪ Try to win
All the games that I play ♪
♪ I got everyone
And everything I need ♪
♪ It's a beautiful day ♪
♪ A beautiful day ♪
- [no audible dialogue]
- [acoustic guitar]
[woman] ♪ Should auld
acquaintance Be forgot ♪
♪ And never brought to mind? ♪
♪ Should auld acquaintance
Be forgot ♪
♪ And days of auld lang syne ♪
♪ For auld lang syne, my dear ♪
♪ For auld lang syne ♪
♪ We'll take
A cup of kindness yet ♪
- Oh, guys! It's almost time!
- [Marmee] Oh, no, no, no!
Come on, come on!
- Wait, wait, wait. Hurry up. Hurry up.
- [meows]
[Laurie]
Okay, ten, nine, eight...
- [all] Seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
- Amy!
- Happy New Year! Whoo!
- ♪ For auld lang syne, my dear ♪
- Happy New Year, honey.
- ♪ For auld lang syne ♪
- Kiss.
- I love you.
- Happy new year!
The March sister who's going to get
the New Year's Eve kiss from me...
is...
Goob!
[girls laughing]
At this time, I wish to propose
a new member to the club.
- What?
- This nominee...
deserves a chance and would be
deeply grateful to join our ranks.
- Goob.
- No. No.
Further, I believe this soldier will
add a unique voice to the platoon.
[all]
Who?
I nominate
Mr. Laurie Laurence.
- Mm-hmm.
- No! No, no, no. That would be so embarrassing!
I agree with Amy.
I mean, Private Winkle.
He would just make fun of us.
I give my word, as a soldier,
and as Staff Sergeant
that he will not make fun of
our grievances or our oaths.
He wants nothing more than
to be a full part of the PC!
He's like our brother!
Guys, we have to do it!
- What if he tells Brooke?
- I promise I won't tell a soul!
- Traitor!
- [Meg] You've been in there the whole time?
- I hardly heard anything.
- You heard everything!
My fellow comrades. I come to you
as a lowly Private First Class!
A faithful friend
and a keeper of secrets.
As a token of my appreciation for your
consideration, I have brought you this.
Whoa.
[Meg] What is it? A birdhouse?
- What's it for?
- Every club needs a secret mailbox.
To keep our correspondence safely in
the hedge between our two nations.
This one is for secrets,
never to be told.
An alliance then?
Well, then, Private.
As General, I say...
welcome
to the Pickwick Club.
- [exhales]
- Yes!
[girl]
Your sister's really not coming?
She said she's not interested
in "primitive rituals."
Tonight is going to be
anything but primitive.
Oh!
Your step-mom is the best!
I know, right?
That's a cute little dress.
- It was my grandma's.
- How couture.
Just throwing this
out there.
I think I might have something
a little bit more flattering.
Totally goes with our color
scheme, don't you think?
- Um...
- Here.
You definitely have
the body for it.
Yes, I would kill
for that stomach.
- Really?
- Face it, Meg. You're hot.
- Everyone knows you're hot.
- Especially Brian.
I heard he was dating
Miss Cape Cod.
Well, here's to
the best prom ever!
♪ Pack it up ♪
♪ Let me let go ♪
♪ Sink inside your bottle Livin'
like There's no tomorrow ♪
♪ Pack it up
Hey ♪
♪ All we need
Is drinks and music ♪
♪ Used to dream and now
We have the chance to do it ♪
[music continues, indistinct]
[crowd chatters, indistinct]
[chuckles]
[music continues]
[coughs]
I'm gonna go dance
with my friends.
[laughing]
[gasps]
Let's go.
♪ Same old struggle
Same old game ♪
♪ The same old hustle
Same old lane ♪
♪ The same old routine
Make you think ♪
♪ I been trippin'
I been stuck ♪
♪ In my position every day ♪
♪ Wishin' I was young ♪
[music continues, indistinct]
- Where are we going?
- It's a surprise.
Sorry. It's...
stuffy up there.
We're in a basement.
- Oh! [giggles]
- [laughs]
[music pounding]
[music muffled]
[clears throat]
That's gross.
That's Jäger.
It's an acquired taste.
Maybe this will help.
[Laurie] Meg?
What are you doing here?
Jo said you might need a
"wing woman" or wingman.
I don't.
Okay.
[scoffs]
What's with Willy Wonka?
[sighs]
Nothing.
[sucking]
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
[sighs]
What's the problem?
I don't want to do this.
[sighs]
Fine. There's plenty
other girls that do.
[sighs]
[people chattering]
[John Brooke]
Meg!
Laurie send you?
I thought you might
need a ride.
Well, I don't.
Hungry?
[sighs]
There you go.
- [chuckles]
- Come on.
Burgers and fries.
So did you at least
get a slow dance in?
- Nobody does that anymore.
- What? That's stupid.
You look
really pretty.
[cackles]
Yeah, I doubt that.
I'm so stupid.
I just...
I wanted to be like
everyone else for once.
I don't know.
Fitting in is overrated.
Why are you
so sweet to me?
You're a dove.
- You can't be mean to a dove.
- [chuckles]
It's impossible.
Can't do it.
- [vomits]
- Oh.
[door closes]
Hey oh!
Oh!
I didn't know that you were coming.
I'm such mess right now.
It's okay. I'm just
here to pick up Jo.
[sighs]
Jo! Laurie's here!
- So, what you got goin' on here?
- I finished my Paris skyline.
- Nobody cares.
- Laurie does.
It's very nice.
[giggles]
Come on. I don't want
to miss the previews.
Sorry, I'm in the zone.
Hold on one second.
- [clears throat]
- I'm onto something really good. Hold on!
Hold on!
Okay!
- Can I come?
- No.
- Why not?
- Because we don't want you to come.
- [Laurie] That's not true.
- No.
She's not coming.
I'm not a kid. You don't get
to tell me what to do anymore!
Actually, you are. By definition, in fact.
Look it up.
Okay, Jo, easy.
Come on.
You don't have to deal with her
all day like I do.
I just want to see a
movie with my sister.
You just want to
see a movie with Laurie.
She's so obsessed
with you.
It's sickening.
- [door slams]
- I hate you!
[sighs]
[Laurie] Hey, it's not too late.
You wanna go to Scoops maybe?
[Jo] Laurie, no. I don't have time
to go get ice cream right now.
- I am so inspired by that movie!
- [Laurie laughs]
Inspired? I thought you
said you hated it.
I did. But it just inspired
me to write something better.
'Cause if that crap is
getting made into movies,
my scripts are
going to crush it.
Oh, I thought you were
a novelist, not a screenwriter.
I am. I just... I'm gonna do both.
How hard can it be?
Have you seen my notebook?
You know, I don't know why you
don't just use my old laptop.
What would happen if it randomly
deleted all of my work?
But a hard copy,
you never lose.
- Well, except for right now.
- It is not lost. It is misplaced.
Okay, uh, guess I'll...
see you later then?
Okay, bye.
[door closes]
Still moping?
Still looking for something?
Give me that!
Amy! Amy! Amy!
Give me that.
Amy, give me that.
Amy! Amy!
- Open the door, you little brat!
- You should have let me come!
- No one wanted you there!
- Laurie said he did!
He also said he liked your paintings,
but he lied so you don't cry about it.
[grunts] Why do you have
to be so difficult?
- He's my friend too!
- No, he's not.
He thinks you're stupid and immature,
just like the rest of us do.
No!
[screams]
- I'm going to kill you!
- [screams]
- What's going on?
- She burned it!
Burned what?
Put that down!
My notebook!
What is wrong with you?
You! Go to your room.
Honey.
I'm sorry. Hey...
I will never write
like that again!
I know you're angry
right now and I get it.
It's going to
take some time to heal.
But I promise you,
the longer it takes for you to forgive
her, the longer your pain will last.
All right, Rene, you ready for
a wild ride into the sunset?
Come on.
Crap. Buckle
on the cinch is busted.
We'll have to double up.
Serious?
What? Do you think
I want to ride with you?
- It's either this or we can't go.
- Fine.
We only have an hour of daylight.
[clicks tongue]
- Come on.
[Amy] Jo! Laurie!
Guys!
I wanna come with!
- [horse whinnies]
- Jo! Jo! Wait up!
Hold up, guys!
Guys, wait!
Jo!
Whoa, whoa.
- What should we do?
- What do you think?
[sighs]
♪ Every smile
Every laugh ♪
♪ All the memories
That we have ♪
♪ That's what
I'm takin' with me ♪
♪ Strong of faith
No more fear ♪
♪ Yeah
We started somethin' here ♪
♪ Love will grow ♪
♪ It's what I'm takin' with me
When I go ♪
Come on!
Hey, look.
Is that Saint?
[Jo]
Sure looks like it.
Hey. Hey.
- [Laurie] Saint.
- Saint!
Easy, boy. Hey.
[Jo] Saint.
Yeah, come here.
No, no. Saint.
- [Laurie] Jo, you don't think...
- No.
- [Laurie] There's no way.
- She's back at the barn.
- Amy!
- [Laurie] Hey, Amy!
Amy!
Amy, yell if you can hear me.
- [whinnies]
- Saddle.
Amy?
- Amy?
- Amy!
Amy!
Amy. No. No, no, no.
Help me.
Please.
[Laurie]
Easy, easy. Amy.
- Amy!
- Easy. Easy, easy.
Oh, my God.
Amy.
Amy!
Jo, it's okay.
Hold this. Hold this on her.
Hold it right there. I'm
gonna go get some help.
- No. Amy. [sobbing]
- It's okay.
- Amy.
- Come on.
Amy.
You're gonna be okay.
Please.
Help.
[crying]
Amy.
[Amy] I just wanted
to come with you.
I know.
I should have let you.
I'm sorry
I destroyed your journal.
I don't care
about the journal.
Okay, I so cared
It was my entire life's work.
How can I not?
But, I'd rather lose every word
I ever wrote than lose you.
[chuckles]
That's a lot of words.
I'll write a heck
of a lot more.
Maybe this will help.
Amy.
[scoffs]
I know that sometimes you might
not like me much, but...
No.
Do not say that.
We are just...
different.
And know what 'tis to pity.
Let gentleness
my strong enforcement be,
in the which hope
I blush and hide my sword.
True it is that
we have seen better days
and have with holy bell
been knolled to church.
I like watching
the rehearsals.
Well, the Duke
needs to step it up.
He's still
not off book.
Just let the creative
process inspire you.
Or just try to enjoy it.
I will have you know I love plays,
I just hate this monologue.
What? How? Why?
It's beautiful.
Beautiful?
It's depressing.
All the world's a stage
and all the men and women
merely players.
[Jo with actor] They have
their exits and entrances,
and one man in his time
plays many parts.
It is one of Bill's
most depressing soliloquies.
I like to think a life is a bit more
meaningful than playing a part on a stage.
Shining morning face creeping like
a snail unwillingly to school.
- I don't see it that way at all.
- No?
Please enlighten me,
Professor Bhaer.
I think it's about growth
and accepting change.
We come into this world perfect.
Then we go through all these stages of
learning, shifting, changing, breaking even.
And we become
something new,
something... far from perfect
but perfectly unique.
I find that inspiring.
I guess that is one way
to think about it.
"Last scene of all, that
ends this strange history,
is second childishness
and mere oblivion,
sans teeth, sans taste,
sans every... thing."
[Laurie] I'm scared.
You have a hundred letters in your hand.
Open 'em. One will be a yes.
I still can't believe
you only applied to one school.
When you're meant for the best,
you don't settle for less.
I'd settle for UMass
Lowell at this point.
Just open them.
[sighs] I can't. You do it.
- Okay.
- Uh, start with this one.
[grunts]
Okay.
Right.
"Mr. Laurie Laurence,
thank you for your application
to Stanford University.
We are pleased to announce your
acceptance for the fall semester."
- I got in?
- Yes! I knew you would.
I can't believe it!
- Yes.
- [laughs]
Let's open the rest.
Oh! Throw 'em away! Burn 'em! I don't care.
I'm going to Stanford!
[screams]
Okay, okay.
Your turn.
[sighs]
You do the honors.
[in posh accent]
With pleasure.
"Miss Josephine March, We thank you for
your interest in the University of Oxford.
It is with regret that..."
Jo, I'm sorry.
[sighs]
[yells]
You've got to get goin'. You're
going to miss orientation.
Stanford waits for no man.
[clears throat]
It's not fair.
- You're so much smarter than me.
- It's fine.
I'm gonna hang out here, write a
few novels and hang out with Beth.
You're gonna be back
before we know it.
- I'll text you when I get there.
- Yeah.
Do all the things
for me.
I will.
♪ Come join me ♪
♪ Within the belly
Of the big blue sea ♪
♪ Set a sail
Catch a breeze ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Don't forget
To fill your suitcase ♪
♪ Now watch it sink 'Cause where
we're going We don't need a thing ♪
See you soon.
♪ Not a map or receipt ♪
♪ 'Cause where we've been
Is who we used to be ♪
♪ We started wrapping
Our regrets in cloth ♪
♪ Are you defined
By all the things you want? ♪
♪ Or did you get caught ♪
♪ Up in the things
That we are not? ♪
It's so good. You have
to go to New York.
Really? You think so?
Yes.
Okay. Was it too much
to kill off Theonia?
No.
All the best stories
have some tragedy.
What if Marek
was actually a girl,
who dresses up as a boy
to make her journey safer,
but then by the third act
she can no longer hide?
Beth.
That is genius!
I think that Clarissa should still
fall in love with the Prince.
It's not a love story!
Isn't everything?
Overall, though,
I loved it.
I don't think I'll ever be as good
at anything as you are at writing.
You're way better
at being a good human.
I can help you
with that.
Oh, and piano.
Mmm.
Can't help you there.
You're pretty much
hopeless.
- [scoffs]
- [giggles]
I just...
I want to write something that
won't be forgotten after I die.
You will.
I know it.
- It's the one.
- What do you mean?
You know. The draft to
send out to publishers?
[grunts]
Jo. I-I don't...
- It's not quite ready.
- How do you know?
You haven't finished it yet.
[scoffs]
I just know.
It's a grueling process.
Listen.
Madeleine L'Engle
racked up 26 rejections
before Wrinkle
was published.
Is that supposed to
make me feel better?
It's supposed to
give you perspective.
Even Freddy Bhaer wrote
an impressive 14 novels
before he was published.
Oh, "Freddy Bhaer."
Wow.
You love throwing your name
in there, right?
[sighs]
Is it any good?
Some say yes.
The New Yorker said "lacks
linguistic vision," so...
You should
read it sometime.
I will.
Right after
you send off my draft.
Maybe... Maybe it's time to
take a break from this one.
Work on something new.
Something new?
I've been working on this
for ten years.
That's exactly
why it might be helpful
to try working on something
else for a change.
So you're not going to help me?
What do you think
I've been doing?
I don't know, actually.
Why do you spend so much time with
me if you don't think I can do it?
I didn't say that, and I thought
we liked spending time together.
That's beside the point!
Is it?
- [phone vibrates]
- Josephine.
- I have to go.
- We need to talk about this.
I don't want to talk about it.
[door slams]
[sighs]
Marmee, I just want to say
before you say anything...
Listen to me.
It's back.
[Jo]
You have to eat it!
[Amy] I don't wanna eat it.
It's so gross!
[Jo]
You asked for a dare!
Don't eat it
if you don't want to.
What the heck,
you guys?
- Come back.
- Oh, my God!
Let it go.
Whatever! I heard
you the first time!
Okay, okay.
We're going on.
It's my turn.
It's my turn. Okay.
Laurie, truth or dare.
- Truth.
- Coward.
Who do you think
is the prettiest girl here?
Oh, you are lame.
Easy. Meg.
No question.
Now, Brooke, um, what's your
thoughts on the matter? Hmm?
You know, I only see inner beauty.
So...
Oh! Okay. All right.
That's enough.
- [retches]
- Look, she's pretty.
Inside and out.
We all get it.
- This is stupid. Let's play Extreme Sardine.
- Yeah!
I say the last person to find me has
to lick every one of our big toes.
Oh!
One, two,
[all]
three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine,
[both] ten.
Oh.
I see you!
Jo?
[taps piano keys]
[begins playing piano]
- What do you think you're doing?
- I'm so sorry. The...
You come in here,
you play my favorite piece,
and you don't have
the decency to finish it?
Hmm?
Go.
I-I'm sorry.
As well you should be.
And I think that you should come
over here three days a week
and play whatever you like.
Do we have a deal?
Well, then I...
I think this calls for a
little Beethoven, don't you?
[continues playing]
[doctor]
Chronic myelogenous leukemia.
Leukemia?
She's young, so there's
a lot we can do.
- [whispers] Cancer?
- It's a type of cancer.
[Marmee] So, okay.
What can we do?
We want to start with radiation
and chemotherapy immediately.
It will be very hard on her.
She's already quite frail.
- But she seems like a fighter.
- Do not call her frail!
You don't even know her!
Josephine.
Meg, honey, will you
go get her please? Go.
- I'm really sorry.
- It's a lot.
Uhh!
[yells]
I'm sorry.
[monitor beeping]
[sighs]
It's gonna be okay.
What if I get sick too?
What if I die before
I get to do anything?
I've never been in love.
I've never had a boyfriend.
Never even been kissed.
Hey. You're gonna be okay.
I promise. You're not gonna
die without being kissed.
How do you know?
I just know.
Even if I have to
do it myself,
I'm gonna make it happen.
[chuckling]
Fine.
Excuse me, sir, you can't go
past here without signing in.
I'm not a sir, sir.
Check your clipboard. Name's Jo March.
I'm already signed in.
[sighs] You're tired, honey.
I'm sorry.
- You're looking better though.
- Thanks.
- Where have you been?
- I was so worried about you.
Beth, do not worry about me. I'm fine.
I-I'm sorry. I freaked out.
I know. I-I felt so helpless,
and so I had to do something.
So I started on the Internet,
didn't know what to do.
Horrible idea. WebMD
scared the crap out of me.
And then I started Googling
all these cures and treatments
and three hours in, I realized
that's not what you need.
Beth, I know
you're gonna fight this.
And I know
you're gonna beat it.
You have to.
So, one thing
that I promise...
that I'm going to be by your
side for every bit of it.
So if you have to go on a special
diet of spinach juice and tree bark,
- I will eat it with you.
- [giggling]
If you have to bathe
in essential oils twice a day,
I will join that pyramid scheme,
and I will get you those oils.
If you're gonna lose
that gorgeous hair...
well, soldier...
[gasps]
I'm losing it with you.
Wow!
That's really bald.
[trembling]
God, it feels like
the head of an alien.
[Marmee] What did you do with your hair?
Did you donate it?
No, Mom. I sold it to pay
for that stupid candy machine.
Yeah, they've got a good
selection down there.
- [screams]
- Gosh!
Jo!
How did you... Why?
Your one beauty.
Honey, cheer up. She's
gonna be all right.
[Jo] I shouldn't be this upset.
[Marmee] We all are, honey.
Come on, Jo.
It's natural.
It's okay to be upset. I know
she means the world to you.
No, it's... I never
realized how ugly I am.
Oh, honey,
your hair will grow back.
Not for forever.
Trust me, when you
look back at this time,
you're not gonna care
how you looked.
Besides. What's the most important
is the workings of your mind.
Your humor, your kindness.
Your courage.
Don't tell Bethy, okay?
Of course not.
She's lucky to have you.
- Are you all ready?
- Yeah.
Oh, they're coming.
♪ Deck the halls
With bows of holly ♪
♪ Fa-la la-la-la
La-la la-la ♪
♪ 'Tis the season
To be jolly ♪
♪ Fa-la la-la-la
La-la la-la ♪
- ♪ Don we now... ♪
- Uh, we've gotta open...
I think we could use
some accompaniment.
Would you do the honors?
[Mr. Laurence]
Merry Christmas.
Thank you, Mr. Laurence.
Of course. Here.
Play something.
- Can we do "Angels"?
- Yeah, of course.
[begins playing]
♪ Angels we have heard
On high ♪
♪ Singing sweetly ♪
[no audible dialogue]
♪ In Excelsis Deo ♪
[all clamoring]
Dad!
- Oh! Honey!
- Oh.
Bethy. Hey, my girl.
Look at us,
a couple wounded soldiers.
- I miss you, Dad.
- I've missed you so much.
I love you.
Oh, I've missed you guys
so much.
Oh, how I've missed
my little women.
[Jo's voice]
Hey, Bethy, it's me.
I am on the train back home.
Don't worry. You beat this once,
and you are going to
beat it again. Okay?
I love you.
I'll be there soon.
[Meg's voice] It'll be summer, Beth
is in remission. It's perfect timing.
[Jo's voice] We weren't supposed to
get married until we're 30, Meg!
- You broke the oath!
- It was a stupid oath that we made when we were kids.
Why do you even want
to get married?
We don't live in the 1700s. We
don't have to rely on men anymore.
- Because I love him.
- Oh, how do you even know?
Look, I just know. And I
really need you to support me.
Well, I can't.
I know you don't understand
why I wanna be a mom and
get married and have kids,
but it's what I want.
I don't believe you.
It's not your castle.
It's mine.
Meg, just remember this.
One day when you're 40 years
old, you're gonna wake up
and you're gonna look at
your wrinkly face in the mirror,
and you're gonna ask yourself,
"What did I do with my life,
except give up everything
for a man?"
How dare you belittle
my life and my dreams?
I have always been there for you with
your work and all of your ambitions,
no matter how insane
they seemed to me.
I'm not asking you to change,
all I'm asking... Jo!
[sighs]
All I'm asking is that you
be by my side for one day
to support me in the life I have
chosen to live, without judgment.
You seriously can't
give me that?
How selfish are you?
Dove's right.
We're growing up.
You have to deal with that.
So, I'm just supposed to sit
around, let her ruin her life?
Well, that's the point.
It's her life, it's not yours.
She's going to regret this.
If you don't go to this wedding,
you will regret it.
[no audible dialogue]
[Jo] A toast to the college grad!
You're a real Stanford man now.
[Laurie]
Cheers to a piece of paper.
- So, what's next?
- I don't know.
Part of me wants to just chill
out and work on my music,
but there's so much pressure
to go out and get a real job.
Grandpa wants me to move
to London
and learn the exciting world
of bond trading.
No, that is awesome.
You have to do it.
But what about my music?
Do both. It's London.
Come on.
You can't pass it up.
- Come with me.
- [scoffs] Okay.
You know I want to, but I can't.
Not yet anyway.
Why not? You've always said you
wanted to get out of here, so do it.
I have classes at Lowell.
I-I cannot be
that far from Beth.
What if we both go
to New York instead?
- You hate New York.
- So what?
It's closer to the family.
Then we could be together.
No.
No. You need to go
to Europe.
- Do not change your plans for me.
- But I want to be with you.
I will come visit you
whenever I can.
Jo, listen to me.
I want to be with you.
What?
I love you, Jo March.
Whoa! Wha...
Okay, okay. Don't be stubborn
because I know you love me too.
- I do, but...
- But what?
- You're like my brother.
- But I'm not.
- But I don't love you like that.
- Yes, you do.
Jo, I'm your favorite person
in this whole world.
Yeah, you-you are,
but it's... it's...
No, what we have is... It
is not that kind of love.
- It's...
- Because you won't...
It's not you, Laurie. It's just I don't
know if that's what I want, Laurie.
- Yes, you do.
- With anyone ever!
- No, I don't!
- Yes, you will! One day you will!
You're gonna find someone...
that's gonna make it impossible
for you to say no.
It's just not gonna be me.
Laurie, it's... Laurie!
Laurie!
Hey, Freddy, it's Jo.
I had some family stuff come up, so
I'm gonna be going home for a while.
Hopefully, I'll see you
after the holidays.
[Meg] It seems like
we're missing something.
[Brooke] That's not it.
- No, the other one.
- Which one?
Yeah.
Wow. It looks so great.
- I think we're good, right?
- No. No, not yet, honey.
Could you find a home
for this?
[clears throat]
[both] Jo!
Hi!
Are you kidding me?
- [laughing]
- And it's twins. So...
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I wanted to surprise you.
Oh, please! You wanted
to see my reaction.
Oh.
It was entertaining.
- Oh, Marmee.
- Welcome home, Jo! Welcome home, baby.
- Merry Christmas.
Where is she?
- What you been up to?
- You know me.
Out every night,
hittin' the club.
[beatboxing]
[both laugh]
I've missed you.
I mean, I don't miss waking up at 3:00 a.m.
every morning to:
"Beth. Beth, do you think
Lithgo is a good pirate name?"
It's not.
I'm sorry I haven't
visited in a while.
That's okay.
You're out making your mark
in New York City.
So proud of you.
Waking up every morning
in a city full of...
I hate it.
- I thought you loved it.
- No.
Well, it's New York.
Everybody says they love it.
You have to,
but nobody really does.
I thought I would feel inspired, but
instead of bringing out my creativity,
- it brings out my anger issues.
- Uh-oh.
Sometimes when I'm
walking up the subway steps,
and people are shoving
and on their phones,
I just want to grab them
by the shoulders and scream,
"Do you know there is a big,
spacious green world out there?"
You don't though, right?
One time, to a really nice
Chinese man named Han.
And, apparently, everybody's
dream is to be a writer.
Except Han. He's a fishmonger,
and he's doing great.
I just...
don't think I can compete.
You're the best writer
I know.
Well, no offense,
but you don't get out much.
[both laugh]
[Jo] Still think there's some
pretty juicy secrets in here.
Don't even think
about it.
I'm pretty sure we've
outgrown the club rules.
- Maybe you old hags have.
- [gasps] Amy! You made it!
Ooh.
You seriously look like this
after an international flight?
It was the longest flight
of my life.
[laughs]
- [Beth] Amy.
- Beth!
- I missed you.
- I missed you more.
Mm! Whoa! We do not fit
on this like we used to.
Amy, I want to hear
all about Oxford.
One semester left, and already
two different galleries
wanna buy my Haslemere
landscape series.
What about the
"Watching Deer Triptych"?
- Oh, that's my favorite!
- The what?
So, last week, I met
with the Lisson Gallery,
- and they seem interested.
- That's so exciting!
Wait, what? The what gallery? Why do I
not know what you're talking about?
If you answered your phone,
you would know.
Wait. Who dug this out?
Oh...
I always want to read through
it when I'm here alone.
Oh, my gosh.
What?
Okay.
I think it's time
to share this one.
♪ I'm not afraid
Of the storm ♪
So, I guess now I know why you
joined the home-schooled crew.
Yep. And now you know why I
used to clip little pug nose.
I miss your
little pug nose.
- ♪ As they made ♪
- [no audible dialogue]
- ♪ In your heart ♪
- I had such a crush on him.
You had a crush
on everybody.
Hey!
[Meg] Prom.
The year you didn't come.
[Jo] Chasing wine coolers with
Jägermeister? Rookie mistake
[all laugh]
[Jo] It was the best
of Christmases.
It was the worst
[Beth] It seems like
it was yesterday.
- When did we get so old?
- [Amy] Speak for yourself!
♪ All of our stories ♪
Oh, he still hates
when you call him that.
Then I will continue
to do so.
I'm just glad
you speak to him at all.
I think it should be illegal for
anybody under 30 to get married.
Well, you're almost there,
so... any prospects?
No. Not you too?
I'm just curious. And
vicariously living through you.
Hey, Jo. Do you mind
helping me with dinner?
Oh, sorry. We're working
on our "Heart and Soul" duet.
Really gonna wow
everyone this year.
- Just come help me, please.
- Put me on trash duty.
Jo, please.
[Jo] I thought you
needed my help.
[Amy] I just said that because I
wanted to be alone for a minute.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. I just wanted to catch up.
There's so much
going on in both our lives
that I don't even know what we
don't know about each other.
- You know what I mean?
- Not really.
[forced laugh]
Okay, um...
I wanted to tell you
about me and...
[Meg] Laurie, you made it!
Laurie?
- It's so good to see you.
- You too.
Laurie.
Jo.
[screams]
[both laughing]
Laurie, I thought you
couldn't come till later.
I caught an earlier flight.
I wanted to surprise you guys.
Well, we are
definitely surprised.
I am so glad you're here.
Now it feels like Christmas.
- Hey, Laurie.
- Oh, my Bethy.
- Mmm.
- How are you?
You know me. Just happy
that everyone's home.
I missed my platoon.
Okay. What's new? I have not
talked to you in, like, forever!
You mean the last four e-mails that I
sent you that you didn't write back?
You know I'm better in person.
Come on. Tell me everything.
Spare me no details. None.
You first.
[no audible dialogue]
You know you're gonna
be a grandpa soon.
- If it's a girl...
- Grandpa? No.
[Marmee] We're gonna be
grandparents, guys!
- I'm not ready for that. I'm not ready for Grandpa.
- Twice as good.
I wanna hear about the business.
How's the...
You know, business is good.
[Jo]
He's lying!
He's a working man now. It's
respectable to be a working man.
I... I, uh, I can't complain.
[Meg] Are you
still doing your music?
You know, I can't complain.
- [everyone laughs]
- Gotcha. Gotcha.
You okay?
Oops. Merry Christmas,
my pretties.
- [all yelling]
- Aunt March!
- Hey!
- [Jo] What are you doing here?
What a surprise.
What happened to
your seniors cruise?
Well, I don't know.
I suppose the Danube has lost
its luster in my old age.
Aunt March, I think
that you're the only person
in the history of time that's
ever gotten bored with Europe.
- Besides Marco Polo.
- And Christopher Columbus.
- Countless immigrants also.
- Mm-hmm.
- The Vikings.
- The Beatles.
- One Direction.
- Tons of people, really.
Yeah, I get it.
Okay, got it. Ha ha!
Josephine,
this is for you.
You shouldn't have.
What?
I didn't. I found it
on your doorstep.
- Oh.
- Nearly tripped over it
when I went to pick up
your mail.
Can't say "Grandpa."
Somethin' else.
Pappy, pappy.
Poppy, Pop-pop.
Look at that.
[Marmee]
Who's it from?
Ooh. Who's Freddy?
Are you 12?
[Meg]
What does the note say?
It said,
"When life is rough..."
That's all I got to
before she slammed it shut.
[Papa March] All right, take it easy.
She's not gonna tell you.
You little cheat!
She'll tell me. Right?
- Yeah.
- Don't even try it.
- I'm not telling you.
- Come on.
- No.
- Jo, you always...
- I'm not telling anyone!
- You always tell your dad.
It's literally nothing.
There's nothing to tell!
- It's seriously nothing.
- Leave her alone.
It's probably from that
professor she's been seeing.
- Oh.
- [together] What?
- Professor?
- [Papa March] How old is this professor?
No, no, no, no.
We are not seeing each other.
He is a professor at Columbia
who is interested in my writing.
That's is all.
Jo, that's so exciting.
Is he also interested
in you?
No. It's strictly professional.
- Then why would he send you a package on Christmas Eve?
- That's a good point.
Because it's Christmas,
and you give people presents
on Christmas.
He sent me a Christmas present!
Why is that so hard to understand?
Is that okay with everybody?
That's very okay.
That is totally fine.
Come on.
No, I don't think so.
You're children.
All of you.
Especially Dad.
All of you!
No. That's great that he likes your
writing. He's a very smart man.
I wouldn't say that he likes it.
Every time I send him a draft, he sends
me pages and pages and pages of notes.
But I guess no matter how many drafts
I send, he still reads them, so...
Well, then he definitely
has a crush on you.
All right.
All right, I'm done. Out!
Hey, Jo.
You get back in that seat.
- Move, move!
- Sit down. We're just teasing you.
We're just interested
in your life.
Then stop trying
to freak me out.
[Papa March] All right, Joe.
Maybe you're just
overthinking this a bit.
Not every guy
has alterior motives.
"Ulterior."
"Ul" with a "U." It...
- You know what I meant.
- If you're gonna make a point, use the right word.
Laurie always read your stuff.
He was always just a friend.
Yeah. Maybe he's just a normal guy who just
so happens to be into mythopoeic fables.
- Yeah.
- [Laurie] You know?
Yes.
A toast. To Jo's novel,
and its inevitable success.
- Cheers.
- Cheers to Jo.
[all] Cheers.
And to Freddy. May his intentions be
pure and his heart not be broken.
I am not cheersing to that.
No! I am not... I am
not cheersing to that!
I am not cheersing!
Stop! I'm not!
[Jo] No!
Cheers.
[Laurie] That was a
good one, Marmee.
[text sends]
[sighs]
[glass shatters]
[gasps]
Amy, are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm such a klutz.
- Oh, my... You're bleeding.
- I know.
[Amy] Jo! Come back!
Please just talk to me!
Let me explain.
He's been in London. So, of course
we've been seeing a lot of each other.
At first,
it was just as friends,
but then at some point,
it changed.
So, what?
You're dating now?
I know this must be
so weird for you.
At first it was weird
for me too...
but please
don't be mad at me.
Do you love him?
I think I always have.
And how does he feel?
The same.
At least that's what
he tells me.
Then, I'm happy for you.
You are?
Of course.
That stinkin' Laurie.
He has been trying to weasel his way
into this family since day one.
[singing, faint]
♪ In Excelsis Deo ♪
♪ Gloria ♪
Did you know?
No.
I think
everybody else did.
[scoffs]
Wow.
I think they were nervous
about how you would react.
Why did she
have to choose him?
I know he's amazing.
Why my Laurie?
You didn't want him.
Yeah, but I didn't want anyone
else to have him either.
Especially not Amy.
My baby sister
who has everything,
whose life
I'm completely jealous of.
We each have our own
paths to our castles.
Remember?
There's no competition here.
You're my person.
Meg has Brooke.
Marmee has Dad.
Apparently, Laurie has Amy.
I have you.
- Jo?
- Yeah?
I wanna see the ocean.
[waves crashing]
[seagull crying]
[Jo] The beach is so wonderfully
creepy in the winter.
It's the perfect setting
for a murder mystery.
[laughing]
Never stop doing
what you love.
Ever.
You were meant
to tell stories.
Am I though?
Listen to me.
I'm not always gonna
be here to tell you.
Don't talk like that.
- Jo.
- Beth.
- I've known for a while now.
- Stop it.
- And I've come to terms with it.
- Don't...
I see you all so...
healthy and strong...
fighting for your dreams.
And I know I'm different.
No. You have to get better.
I...
You have to.
I try. Really I do.
Every day I just feel
myself slipping away.
I...
I don't think that I was ever
meant to be here for long.
And there's a reason why
I never wanted to move away.
Or to meet a boy or to
have a career or a family.
I just know that
I'm gonna miss you.
Even on the other side.
I don't want to live
in a world without you.
Don't say that.
I'm counting on you.
You have to do
all the things for me.
♪ World is crying ♪
♪ So I pretend ♪
♪ Good things never ♪
♪ Have to end ♪
♪ Can't feel a thing
But my heartbeat ♪
But this pounding ♪
♪ Can't feel a thing
But my heartbeat ♪
Ah! Stop! Wait!
[panting]
Don't mind me. Just managing
my anger over here.
Does it ever go away?
The anger? The pain?
The guilt?
Or the sadness?
When do I stop
feeling like this?
Bethy's life was harder than all
of ours, and she was the happiest.
You know how you always said that you
two were gonna do all the things?
You have to do this for her.
You have to feel...
all the feelings.
The only thing I feel
is emptiness.
Like nothing I do matters.
What is the point in even trying if
everything can be taken away from you?
Just stop. I am not gonna let you
turn into somebody that you are not.
The Jo that I raised is fearless,
is relentless, is passionate.
I used to be.
Then everything turned out
different than I expected.
You're a writer.
Don't you want your
story to be unexpected?
[Amy's voice] Apollyon!
Apollyon!
[Jo's voice] I, Jo March, will
be a very successful writer.
And will do all the things.
[Amy] You don't know what it's
like to have everyone else
make fun of your nose.
What if I die before
I get to do anything?
Jo, how could you?
Your one beauty?
[Jo] Wing woman,
reporting for duty.
[Meg's voice] It's not
your castle, it's mine.
[Jo] At this time, I wish to
propose a new member to the club.
I wanna write something that
won't be forgotten after I die.
[Beth] You will.
I know it.
I don't think I'll ever be as good
at anything as you are at writing.
[Jo] You're way better
at being a good human.
- [Beth] I think this is my castle.
- [Amy] The attic?
[Beth] Just being
here with all of you.
[older Beth] We're growing up.
You have to deal with that.
To always help each other
reach our castles.
No matter where they may be.
[Jo's voice] There are
many Beths in the world.
Shy and quiet.
Sitting in corners till needed.
And living for others
so cheerfully,
that no one sees the sacrifices
till the little cricket
on the hearth stops chirping.
And the sweet,
sunshiny presence vanishes...
leaving silence
and shadow behind.
[sighs]
[giggling]
You happy? Yeah.
- [crying]
- Oh.
- I have no idea what to do with them yet.
- [chuckling]
But I think once they
become actual humans,
I'm gonna be
their favorite aunt.
- I'm sure you will be.
- [knocking]
Could you get it?
It might be their playdate.
Playdate? They...
They hardly move.
Just get the door.
Come here.
There we go.
Oh, hi.
Hi, there. Oh, my.
Who could be at the door?
Freddy.
What are you doing here?
I read your book.
A few times... actually.
Did you take a six-hour train
ride just to tell me that?
I needed to see something.
The famous March attic.
I can see why this was
a young tomboy's playground.
You really did read it.
Mm-hmm.
Jo, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for
how we left things.
Me too.
I was not ready
to hear the truth.
But you were right.
You ready for
some more truth?
Let me guess.
It was childish,
cliché...
and my family is...
weird and boring.
The beginning was slow.
Your structure needs work,
and you have a tendency
for run-on sentences.
But it's beautiful
and authentic.
And I loved it.
You did?
I might have
even cried.
Twice.
I think this is the one.
Come back
to New York with me.
I can help you
get this book out.
Beth wouldn't want you to stay here
and let your talents go to waste.
Come back with me.
That was supposed to be
my part.
Get used to it.
[no audible dialogue]
Hey, munchkins. What have you got?
Show me.
Oh, it's so pretty.
Is this for Aunt Jo?
Thank you so much.
I cannot believe
I'm breaking my own oath.
[all laugh]
You didn't break
the important ones.
I hate doing this
without her.
She's here.
I propose an oath.
An oath to surpass
all other oaths.
To always...
always...
try and be as good...
and sweet and strong...
as our Beth.
Always and forever.
[all laughing]
[sighs]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
♪ Painted a street scene
In Paris ♪
♪ Just before the dawn ♪
♪ Dance in the showers ♪
♪ Of a late night
Summer storm ♪
♪ Write your stories in glory ♪
♪ Fly on sister'd wings ♪
♪ Your tickled neck
Is her whisper ♪
♪ Do all the things ♪
♪ Drink the painful rain ♪
♪ That drips on the memory ♪
♪ Draft another stack
Bound with self-reverie ♪
♪ Scream from the tallest ♪
♪ So the mountains hear
Your dreams ♪
♪ She's always here
Reminding you ♪
♪ Do all the things ♪
♪ All the things
In your heart ♪
In your dreams ♪
♪ It doesn't matter ♪
♪ Big or small ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Do it all ♪
[chorus]
♪ All the things ♪
[scatting]
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Do all the things ♪
[song ends]
♪ Da-da da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Da-da-da ♪
♪ The heart has
It's ups and downs ♪
♪ And turnarounds ♪
♪ Dead ends
And new beginnings ♪
♪ The heart has it's miracles ♪
♪ Valleys and pinnacles ♪
♪ But every page ♪
♪ Is solid proof I'm living ♪
♪ If I could go back
And rewrite it ♪
♪ From the start ♪
♪ I wouldn't erase
Any chapter of my heart ♪
♪ Love every chapter
Of my heart ♪
♪ I'm still in the middle ♪
♪ It can feel like a riddle ♪
♪ All these pages to go
So much I still don't know ♪
♪ Even though every line Doesn't
make perfect sense To me ♪
♪ It's my story ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ If I could go back
And rewrite it ♪
♪ From the start ♪
♪ From the torn pages
To my favorite parts ♪
♪ I wouldn't erase any chapter
Of my heart ♪
♪ Love every chapter