You're tuned to Bludso on the radio.
Stage one of my dramatic transformation
is almost complete.
Oh, my God. You're such a child.
Well, I'm an actual child, so...
How is that an insult?
It just means it's working.
Girls, we're home!
Listeners, the music
will be right back after a quick break.
Fine, but don't get mad when
you're just as nappy as you ever were.
- Come on, Linda!
- I'm right here!
Ow! Linda!
Oh! Aah!
Calm down.
I'm putting the neutralizer in now.
Hurry up. It really hurts!
Hold on.
Anna, you've been with
our family for a year.
This is way past due.
You might could pass
as my sister, after all.
Should it still burn?
Linda!
Hey, what... What's going on up there?
That hurts.
Linda?
I did what the box told me.
Girls!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to!
- Hey, what's going on up there?
- It was the box!
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to do it!
Ow.
The call was for
a Downtown Julie Brown type.
Someone worldly, articulate,
knowledgeable, charismatic?
Black?
Assistant at Culture for four years.
- Uh-huh.
- They never gave you a shot?
Only so many spots in Culture.
Um, we just need a little bit more
rock than urban here.
Perfect.
I appeal to a global audience,
you know?
"It's Anna Bludso, coming at you
with the hottest of the hot."
Thank you so much.
RMV. Rock Music Video.
The only place that will rock you.
You know you want it.
- Oh!
- Hey. All right.
She doesn't work here,
does she?
From the people
that brought you RMV,
we are Culture.
Featuring Brook-Lynne, Sista Soul,
and Julius.
Culture. We're coming on for you.
Damn it.
All right, big board meeting.
You're all called here.
You know something's up.
And I'm not gonna bullshit you.
Do you know what Culture is
to the suits downstairs?
It's a liability.
It's in place only so that
Yetnikoff at CBS and Clive Davis at Arista
don't sue RMV's asses
for not playing "that black disco shit."
Their words.
I'd love to tell you the board put me here
because they think I'm
some kind of wunderkind,
but the truth is, anytime they see
an executive with a hairline
and a working dick, they think
he's not qualified to do shit,
except babysit a loss leader.
But let me tell you something.
This is exactly where I want to be.
I spent my entire summer at the Apollo,
kicking it with Teddy Riley,
Jimmy Jam and Terry Lewis.
Hip hop? This New Jack shit?
It's the future.
And not just black music.
It's the future of the
entire music industry.
And we have a chance to own it.
Look at Julius' whack-ass fade.
- He's cute.
- Is not.
- Nigga think he Eddie Murphy.
- Shut up!
- She ain't wrong.
- Which is why Edna
has decided to step down
as EVP of programming.
- Wait, what?
- Edna!
- Hell, no.
- Culture needs to grow in a direction I simply cannot take it.
- It's okay. It's totally admirable.
- She said she was gonna give me a raise.
- Well, that's out.
- I begged her to stay.
But I'm confident
we're in excellent hands.
Allow me to introduce your new EVP:
The legendary Zora Choice.
- Thank you, Grant.
Now, I know what you're all thinking.
They say I'm the world's first
black supermodel.
Of course it's a light-skinned bitch.
And what does a...
An aging supermodel
know about running a channel?
Well, I've been quietly inching my way
toward this goal for quite some time now.
And rest assured, I will be consulting
the brilliant Edna Knight
- as long as she'll have me.
- Absolutely.
Programming will be suspended
for a few weeks while we are retooling.
I, I know it seems sudden,
but we simply must.
If Cult, and that's what we're calling it,
by the way,
if Cult is going to be the authority
on pop culture in the '90s,
well, we simply must be sure
of its direction.
My assistant Rosalyn will be
setting up meetings with all of you,
just to get to know you,
and find out what skills
you will bring to Cult.
"The Block" continues to do
well enough in the ratings.
Especially with our very exciting and
contractually obligated Sandra premiere.
That program will continue
as scheduled.
If this succeeds,
we change popular culture.
Y'all, we are doomed.
Come on, there's gotta be
something we can do.
Edna, this is your channel.
- Look, I just bought a condo, okay?
I'm not going back to radio.
Edna, she brought her own assistant!
Okay, look, I'm gonna start
my own production company
that's programming for us, by us.
Now, it's gonna take
a few months to get started,
but I will be calling you all, okay?
And then maybe we can work for
somebody other than them.
Uh, I'll be waiting by the phone.
It's your man Julius,
and welcome to The Block,
where we got a bangin' exclusive
from the princess of pop soul.
It's already on the Billboard top 10,
- and has its sights on number one.
- Excuse me, excuse me. Thank you.
Thank you so... I'm so sorry I'm late,
guys. Beauty takes time.
Anna better not be
still hooking up with him.
You know Anna
don't live in the real world.
- Oh, hey, Anna.
- Thanks for proofing, girl.
- No problem.
- ...four, three, two,
Hey, it's your man, Julius,
and welcome to The Block,
where we got a bangin' exclusive
from the princess of pop soul...
"I Get It!"
I said...
Is that a new nose?
Contouring.
And contacts, maybe?
Oh, that thing must be glued down.
Or a really good relaxer, maybe.
Mm-mm, my shit don't move like that,
and I'm part Cherokee.
It's a weave, I think.
Yeah, my girl Tanitra
just started doing those.
Take whatever hair you want
and sew it into your real hair.
- Ugh, that sounds painful.
And expensive.
It actually sounds like a good idea.
Guess it's better than
a creamy crack, right?
Of course,
I know what's better than either.
- Okay, Sojourner Truth.
Ain't nobody got time for all that upkeep.
- Really, dookie braids?
- It didn't take that long.
Hell, I think I need me a cigarette.
I think I need a weave.
How anyone can sew someone else's
dead energy into their head is beyond me.
You see shorty's hair?
I get it, okay?
Aah.
Ahem.
- Crazy day.
- Humph.
So, what are you doing tonight?
You know,
I've been seeing someone.
You heard me. Hmm?
Like, a therapist, or...
I know I've crossed some lines.
Turned us into something
we should have never been.
We've been crossing a line for years.
Fresh!
You know, I'll take
full responsibility for it.
We crossed the line this afternoon
in your dressing room!
But you pushed for that, though.
I am sorry.
It's, it's been killing me, though.
All right?
Has it?
Anna! We need you now!
Coming!
Jesus.
Anna, you all right, girl?
Yeah, just...
these cramps, and this,
this damned machine.
Oh, just ask.
You know we are all synced up in here.
Hey.
You'll be all right.
Why would they get rid of you?
You barely cost the network anything.
You ever have a dream...
Something...
you would do anything for?
Especially when someone says...
you can't do it.
You don't deserve it.
You were that dream for me.
No. Your career was your dream.
Just know that I will always love you.
My lovin'.
You're never gotta get it.
That was amazing.
Sandra, oh, my gosh.
She's so sexy. So beautiful.
Listen, I'm your man, Julius.
And I'm gonna be here,
you know, I got some stuff
to really put you in the mood.
Get your candy box going, ladies.
Put a little bit of sugar in there.
I got everything that you need.
That's right. Everything right here.
Right here. You know.
I love using
this time to talk to the ladies,
because you all buy tickets to things,
so y'all know where I'm gonna be at.
I'm gonna be DJing downtown...
You're ten days late!
Don't think I won't
kick your ass out of here!
God damn it.
All right, I'll be back tomorrow.
I thought she was just
getting to know us.
Hey girl, how you holdin' up?
Anna? Zora will see you now.
Girl to girl, this isn't a chat.
It's an interview. Understand?
I'm getting the picture.
So, you were Edna's assistant, no?
I mean, I'm sure
you're much more than that.
You've been here forever.
But that was your title.
Yes.
Edna was very concerned
about her dear Anna.
She never got you promoted?
It almost happened.
After I came up with The Block,
Edna said...
You came up with The Block?
I wanted to produce, and host, but...
But that went to Julius.
Hmm.
Julius was a receptionist
when I started.
Mr. Madison must have
seen something in him.
So, what do you think of the network,
as a whole?
Um...
Uh, empowering.
Once more with feeling, darling.
The Block is a good start.
But I think Grant's right.
This new Teddy Riley sound...
Everyone's stealing our styles,
and making it palatable for RMV.
Our music is way beyond the black charts
and we're the only one in town
who will play them.
It's not a niche. It's the future.
Why aren't we playing the real deal,
like, what the kids who buy music
actually listen to?
Culture viewership skews fairly older.
Um, right.
So, our VJs could...
host different blocks
of specialized videos
throughout the day.
And we could...
more than host.
They could rep different styles of music.
And they have their viewers call in,
and vote for their favorites.
Something for everyone, you know?
So no one feels left out.
All while we cultivate
a more engaged audience.
Consumer research disguised
as entertainment.
Sounds pricey.
- RMV has plenty of empty stages.
We just need a phone line.
Uh, and it all culminates into
a daily live countdown show.
Do me a write-up.
A treatment, some sample scripts,
budget, list of guests that could come on.
How did you know I'd ask for this?
I didn't.
Obviously, I don't need an assistant.
Perhaps an associate producer.
Uh, Anna, who... who does your hair?
No one.
Me.
Aren't you tired of it?
All the stares you get
walking through the RMV lobby?
Everyone wondering why you're here.
If you went to any other floor
in this tower for a job interview,
you wouldn't get past reception.
And you know that.
Sistas get fired for less than that
every day.
Now, music people have
certain expectations,
and my girls need to flow freely.
I wonder, do you want to be
one of my girls?
Yes.
Anna's living in a fantasy.
I mean, how long...
- Uh, so this is the book Mama gave me...
- Hey, baby.
Uh, took me years to track it down.
Look who decided to grace us
with her presence.
Unc.
Mama used to know all these by heart.
Almost wondered if there was even
an actual book.
Something new for his
wall of oppression.
Child, please.
Does
it have the, um... what was it?
- "Skinny, Skinny" story.
- "Skinny, skinny, don't you know me."
It's a folk tale the slaves
used to tell about witches
who would leave their own skin
at night to go haunting.
- Oh.
- Aah.
"Moss Hair Girl."
That was the one Mom used to tell.
Uh, can I take a look?
- Uh, yeah.
- Thank you.
So, Anna, how's work?
- Intense.
- Um, I can relate to that.
I hardly see this one anymore.
Well, they have me teaching history now,
in addition to English lit,
and I just started an after school
college prep program.
- Remarkable.
- Uh...
I'm sorry. Anna, I cut you off.
You were talking about work?
Now, are you still interning
for that lady?
Executive assistant, and no.
Actually, she left the company.
Oh. Your job's not
in jeopardy now, is it?
No! Not at all.
Look, they're doing some retooling,
and actually, they're looking at giving me
my own show, so...
When does it air, Anna?
I mean, there's still a lot to do,
so it might be a while,
but it's all moving along.
Hope it works out.
It already is, so...
- Oh, the flying African story.
I did my thesis on these.
- Yes!
- No, that's in there?
It's ridiculous.
I'm sorry?
I'm just, um,
surprised to see a room
full of people
with doctorates, like,
trippin' over superstitions
and fairy tales.
Fairy tales.
Humph.
How does one group of people
subjugate another?
Uh, Amos... No,
no, no. I'm just educating the girl.
You subjugate a people
by telling them their science
is superstition,
their faith is heresy,
and their wisdom is make-believe.
They called the American Indians savages.
And they called us...
Well, what didn't they call us?
- I got it, okay?
- No, you don't get it.
From the moment you are born,
you are so thoroughly indoctrinated
by the insanity of
Western European world views,
you can't bear to see yourself
the way nature would have.
And you scoff at us and our superstitions.
Well...
those superstitions are in fact
tributaries leading to rivers
and oceans of truth
about what you really are.
And who you might have been.
Someone pass the salt.
Uh, why you never bring Julius?
His show is doing really well, so...
it keeps him busy.
- Hmm.
- Our show, really.
But you're making your rent, right?
Anna, no. Your credit.
You can't mess with that. Baby...
They wanna raise the rent 500-
- What? What? 500?
Five hundred bucks. I'll figure it out.
No, that is outrageous.
White folks started moving in, so...
Well, they have a habit
of doing that, don't they?
- Auntie, no.
- Mm-mm.
Please. Your uncle doesn't know anything
about my little account.
Humph. Besides, you can pay me back
when your show comes through.
Okay?
Okay.
Mm. So...
We finally gonna do something...
Auntie!
Oh, okay. All right. I'm just sayin'...
Wigs have gone a long way since,
you know...
last time you tried 'em.
What'd you want me to do with that?
It's a book. People read 'em.
I'm good.
I forget to leave Professor Bludso
at work sometimes.
I'm sorry.
Don't you think Kieren might be
more into that folklore stuff?
You're into it, too.
As long as it involves a fly girl
making it big in the city.
Starring Sandra.
- A fly girl, huh?
- Hey.
Their stories run the world.
Sure as the sun, these are ours.
Hi.
Um, are your prices listed?
Oh, for a sew in?
- Yeah.
- Oh, hair and service is 450.
- Four hundred and fifty?
- Mm.
And Virgie's earliest appointment
is the 15th...
of February.
Look, sista to sista,
I work in TV.
I'm actually a VJ at Culture,
and girl to girl, I really need this.
Well, I can see that.
Look, I don't know how it works
in your hood, or wherever.
But we are a world-class salon, okay?
Look, I'm sure you can find
someone else to hook you up.
Excuse me!
- Hi.
- Uh, Denise?
Please. I just need a moment.
You ever had a dream?
One you'd be willing
to do anything for?
Very few things are worth
doing anything for, baby.
Right. Especially when
everyone says you can't do it.
You don't deserve this,
says you don't belong
where you know
your destiny tells you to be.
Sista, have you ever been there?
Okay.
It'll be my good deed for the day.
You can wait over
there until she can slip you in.
Sweetheart.
All right, baby.
Let's find her.
Go on and look around, honey.
You won't see my supply
at any other salon.
My sources are exclusive.
I thought so.
I really do feel something.
Clients wear this stuff as magic.
You know, in some parts of India,
a woman's hair is her
most prized possession.
It's the greatest sacrifice
she can make to her gods.
This came all the way from India?
Forget about where it's from.
Let's focus on where it's going.
You're not tender-headed, are you?
I'm sorry!
I'll be fine.
Aah.
Ow.
My mama used a hot comb on me.
And she burned the shit
out of my scalp.
Ow. Ow.
You almost finished?
Ow.
Sweetheart.
I'm sorry, I... I've never had
my hair done before.
You're not the first to faint.
Ow.
- It's...
- Stunning.
My line of essential oils for the scalp.
Proprietary blend.
You want to get it between your braids
and work it into the hair,
at least twice a day.
Trust me. And never get it wet.
It'll hurt for the first week or so.
A lot, but that's normal
for the first time.
But once you get through it,
I'll never be this bad again, okay?
I thought you said
there wouldn't be anybody else here.
She's leaving.
When she tells you not to get it wet,
believe her.
What the hell, Sandra?
Rain at the venue.
Manager wanted a Diana Ross moment.
Oh, such a fan.
I work for Culture, and it's all because
growing up, I saw you.
Someone who looks like me on TV.
Love, love the new video.
So does the label.
Hey! It's Anna. Leave a message.
Hey, it's Edna.
It's happening a lot faster
than I thought,
and I want you by my side.
Call me, sis.
This is it! Open it!
Fuck.
- What?
- Fuckin' rent! That's what.
I paid you.
That increase happened after...
The increase happened
when I say it did.
It's 500 bucks. Now.
What are you gonna do? Just
drag me into the middle of the street?
Mr. Tannen!
Cops will do that for me.
My toilet's overflowing!
"First there was only
the wild beasts and the red man.
Then the white man came
and brought our people."
"The Moss Haired Girl."
"The house negress was a plain woman"
"who took up walking in them woods
when her work was done."
"She'd see tress covered
in black moss so fine
"it looked like massa hair.
She stole the moss from the tree,
and made herself a wig."
Welcome back to RMV.
Can you believe it?
We are gonna do something so crazy
and so different for us right now.
Okay, the princess of soul, Sandra...
- Ow! Ow.
- Is now the queen of pop!
Her newest single "I Get It"
is rising the pop charts,
so let's give it up for her RMV debut.
Here's Sandra!
Yeah, man.
Oh, who dat?
Oh, oh, my, my, my.
Anna, uh, so I got these
Janet Jackson tickets, if you...
Feel like...
- Hey, girl.
- Hi.
Hmm. Humph!
Aah.
- Mm.
- Wow.
You look good, girl.
Hey.
Thanks to you.
I overheard Zora's hair speech.
So, I thought she might like this.
How does it feel?
It's fine.
I know. When I first got mine in,
I wasn't used to all that length.
I was always swiping at my neck,
- like, "What is this?
- Yeah."
Oh, there's a planning meeting
in the conference room at 11:00,
and Zora wants you there.
She... She does?
She does.
Ew!
I told you.
So sad.
Mm. Lookin' fly, Anna.
Fuck you.
So, uh, here's where I'm at.
No more cooking shows.
No more hair shows.
No more endless blocks
of Anita Baker.
She gave us good love,
and we've had enough of it.
Ooh, uh, what's wrong with
Anita Baker?
Look, Hair Beat got mad ratings.
A point 6 in 5 share
would make me mad, as well.
That ain't bad for cable.
Brook, you are better than Hair Beat.
You've got personality.
With clothes that fit,
you could be a star.
Sista Soul, you could be...
something.
The quiet storm is a little
too loud for our channel.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I love the whole organic,
earthy dashiki vibe,
but we need to find you a new lane.
A new lane?
Sista, I represent black women, okay?
Real working women.
Who evidently don't have cable.
Don't come up in here trying to
make us something we ain't.
Yo, yo, yo. I don't want to change you.
- Mostly just Sista.
- Brook.
I want you more... whatever this is.
This is what we can sell
advertising around.
Uh, let us not be precious here.
Back me up on this, Anna.
Oh, so you've been
talking to her about us.
- Got it.
- I didn't say anything like that.
Humph.
- Wow.
- This is what I want to do.
I want to create a
programming centerpiece.
Live. Something fresh.
- A live call-in countdown show.
- Live countdown show.
- Viewers rank their favorite videos.
- ...vote for their favorites.
Then we create programming blocks to
showcase these videos, - ...who rep different styles.
...in new and exciting ways.
You want us to reprogram
an entire network...
...in six weeks?
If you plan to still be working here
in six weeks, Sheryl, yes.
What kind of advertising?
You wanted to see me?
What the hell was that in there?
I'm just confused.
You haven't commented on the proposal,
and suddenly...
You being invited in a meeting
with producers and hosts
was my comment.
Virgie's?
Yes.
It has her signature.
What?
Are you giving me the show?
To host?
Awful big bet to make on someone
who's never hosted a show before.
Like the one Grant made on Julius?
Or is Julius somehow special?
What are you getting at?
It just seems like Julius is the
only one not under a microscope.
Like he's getting special treatment
or something.
And why would he get that?
Because we're fucking?
What?
We're fucking.
You have a problem with that?
Why would I?
Your private life is your business.
A live show is all hands on deck.
I need everyone working on this.
I will decide who the lead is
when I can see what you all can do.
Cool?
Oh, and, uh, Anna?
Get your girls in check.
Zora's who you've been seeing?
Nigga, you get out the hood
off my idea. You wanna what, trade up?
Just chill with that.
Who else knows?
- Your girl told me.
And I use the term "girl" very loosely.
- 'Cause she old enough to be your mama.
- Enough with that.
Okay?
- But it makes sense.
'Cause you act like a fuckin' child!
So, what, you're gonna sleep your way
to the top, like a little bitch?
- What?
- This is the first time I actually heard you raise your voice.
- I kind of like it.
- Fuck you!
Listen, I don't want this
to get out okay?
Tell Zora that, then.
Oh, I will.
You know, I'm not the only one
with secrets around this place.
Unless you found somebody
to do that thing that you like.
What's that got to do with anything?
This is a gossipy office, and, uh...
your discretion is appreciated, okay?
We had fun.
Let's not make it more than that, okay?
Ow.
Hey, it's me!
Just wanted to make sure
you're not dead.
- Hey.
- Whoa.
So this is why you haven't been
at dinner in a while. Okay.
Oh, my God. Dad is going to flip.
And Mom?
- Actually, Mom's gonna love it, but...
- So nice to see you, too, Linda.
You hungry?
You can't get that wet, can you?
Like, at all.
Oh, honey. I think you're allergic.
No, it's human.
I think my neck's just...
not used to having all this
brushing up against it.
Oh, so you're the one
that's been hogging this.
Unc gave that to me to read.
Yeah, like a month ago.
Okay. Keep it. I don't care.
Hey. I wasn't done!
It's fine.
Kieren says I've put on a few.
What?
Hey, what...
What does Julius think?
He loves it.
You must have all those
famous people on speed-dial.
I mean, not all of 'em.
So cool.
You knew what you were gonna do
your whole life.
Dad knew what I was gonna do
before I was even born.
Must be nice.
I should... I should go.
Oh, but first...
These are for you.
Aah! Thank you.
- Love you.
- Love you, too.
- Have a good night.
- Okay. Drive safe.
I always do!
You're
tuned to Bludso on the radio.
Stage one of my dramatic transformation
is almost complete.
Oh, my God. You're such a child.
Well, I'm an actual child, so...
how is that an insult?
It just means it's working.
Listeners, the music will be right back
after a quick break.
Fine, but don't
get mad when you're just as nappy as you ever were.
Mr. Tannen.
- May I help you with...?
- Do we still gotta do this?
Come on, Linda!
- I'm right here!
- Do what?
I actually have your money.
W-Why don't you hold onto it?
You been drinking, Mr. Tannen?
- Don't do that.
You're not the only one, you know.
I know the game.
You know, my cousin's actually waiting...
No, she's not.
Relax, baby.
Black pussy is a passion of mine.
How about some music? Thin walls, right?
Okay.
YOUNG ANNA : Linda!
Fuck!
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
We're just gettin' started. Yeah!
Mr. Tannen?
Mr. Tannen.
Oh.
What the fuck is this?
Good morning, Los Angeles.
You were listening to "One Night,"
the latest from Sandra.
We got traffic and weather coming up
for you right after the break,
but first, some good news.
Stay close to that dial
for your chance to win tickets
to see the The Fellas,
live and in concert at the Forum.
- We're ready to transport.
- All right.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Mm-hmm. Mr. Tannen.
They found that bastard
dead in the dumpster.
The door to the roof was open.
There was empty bottles of gin everywhere.
You know what? I bet he slipped.
Ooh, that drunk-ass.
Liv.
Yeah.
How horrible.
You know what he did to me?
He tried to raise my rent by $500.
I had to threaten to sue his ass.
He ever try that shit with you?
- No. Thank God.
- Mm-hmm. Yeah, praise Heaven.
Fucking rapist.
Damn, that took a turn.
Ooh, Mr. Tannen, you dead.
Bye, girl.
I'm not changing who I am
just to appeal to some whiter...
...wider demographic.
No one's asking you
to change who you are. Just...
the way you look.
The name of your show.
It's not that big of a deal.
You know how long
it took me to get here?
How many interviews I've had to walk into,
not knowing if they wanted Angela Davis,
or Diahann Carroll, or Queen Latifah,
or fucking Claire Huxtable.
I'm sick of this shit!
- Come on, Sista.
It ain't gotta be all that.
I mean, look. Black women are magic.
You know that.
We could put our hair
all the way up to the sky,
drape it down to our shoulders,
or somewhere in between.
Shit, Patti LaBelle changed her hairstyle
20 times in one performance.
What you need is a new attitude.
Yeah, but that was her choice.
A career in TV was your choice.
I chose a career at Culture.
A place where I ain't gotta
look like a different bitch every week
just to do what I love.
Culture is dead.
For real?
- Sista.
- Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
Sista...
Hey.
- Yes, Sheryl?
- Um, is this a programming meeting?
It was.
I wasn't informed.
I'm the VP of programming.
What have you done for me lately?
Anna, you have a month.
It's not fair. It's not,
playing by these rules, but...
Do you really want to quit the game?
And it's fun. I'm telling you.
It's like...
Like Halloween or something.
People look at you
and they see somebody else,
and somehow, you become...
more of yourself.
Or at least, a bigger version, or...
I don't know.
Look,
let's just get through this season,
and then take that shit out.
Wear what you want to wear.
And we'll all go to Jamaica, or something.
Jamaica, bitch?
You, me, and Brook.
Look...
Please, please don't quit.
Y'all the only ones here I understand.
I'll think about it.
Got the news.
Never again.
Baxter was a...
a bad man. But I'm not...
Aah!
Come on! Come on, come on!
So, Sista.
Divas with soul.
A block of all women,
MCs, soul singers,
and of course, occasionally,
the men we love.
Nice.
Um, so, with Sista,
we now have enough VJs for every segment
of the audience.
Mm, that just leaves a host.
I think you'd agree that
no one Grant's team suggested had that.
Anna, I know how hard
you're angling for this, and...
I've seen the work you're putting in,
and...
I'm impressed.
You still using the pink stuff?
Yeah.
It's not enough, is it?
What? Do you mean...?
Guess who...?
Ooh. My bad, Anna.
You, uh, ready for that lunch meeting?
I'm starving.
Can't wait for tonight.
You okay, Sis?
Up all night.
Lord, they put this thing in tight.
I'll be all right.
- What changed your mind, girl?
I love it.
Me, too, girl.
You did good today.
Thanks, girl.
Ow.
Are you serious?
This never happened.
What's up, everybody?
We are here to celebrate
the hottest 24-hour music network, Cult,
and here are The Fellas!
Hey.
Wow. Oh, my God.
You look great.
- Hey!
- Sista!
Look at you.
Wow!
Anna.
You never called me back.
Babe, I've been so busy.
Rubbish. I want you and me
at the Madonna party, okay?
- Call me back.
- I'll see. I'll see.
Okay.
...every time!
Well, as I live and breathe.
You made it!
Isn't it exquisite?
Yes, well,
it's certainly very different.
Uh, what'd you say?
Congratulations.
We... so need to catch up.
Let's go find somewhere to talk.
Come on.
Now, your first reaction may be
that the office seems cold.
But we like to think of Cult
as a little more posh.
Wouldn't you say?
That's some hair.
Yeah.
Can you believe it?
I'd have to see it to believe it.
It's...
been hard without you, Edna.
You seem to have adjusted pretty well.
I had no choice.
You always have a choice.
Not always.
Okay.
Edna, what is it?
Grant offered me the world
to turn what was for the people,
by the people, into...
this.
I chose to walk away.
I almost got evicted.
I had something for you, Anna.
You never returned my phone calls.
I have something here.
Finally, after four years.
You want me to start over?
I can't afford that.
You couldn't afford that hair,
but that didn't stop you.
Mm.
Not with what you paid me.
She's giving me my own show.
More than that.
She's making me the centerpiece
of the entire channel.
Well, I hope it's worth it.
There's a code.
Uh, 1-8-6-6,
9-8.
It's still locked.
Did you press pound?
Like I said, I hope it's worth it.
It is.
Yeah, you know I could help you
with whatever you need.
Yeah.
Julius!
Mm, mm, mm.
Hey.
Oh, my God. Hey.
Um, you're...
Germane.
I met you at Sandra's spot, right?
Yeah, Anna. Anna Bludso, um, with Cult.
- Hey, let me ask you a question.
Have you been back...
there? Virgie's.
Oh. No.
Why?
It's just that ever since
she started going there,
Sandra's been acting a little...
Anna.
Anna Bludso.
Mr. Madison?
Zora?
- You know what?
It's not a big deal.
No, you should stay and say hi.
Uh, I don't do suits. I, uh...
I, I'll see you around.
So, word on the street is
you're our secret weapon.
Where did Zora find you?
I've worked here for four years.
So, Zora shared with me
your plans for Cult Live. Brilliant.
Now, be prepared. You're gonna get
a little bit of push back
on the host thing. I'm all in.
Yeah? You are?
There's no one better to have
as the face of Cult Live.
Wow.
- You really mean that?
- Abso-fucking-lutely.
Zora back on screen? Slam dunk.
Very proud of what the two of you
put together. All right?
Excuse me. Rosalyn?
- Anna...
- Zora.
Sorry, excuse me, Anna. This is, um...
Z, I mean, come on. It's your party.
And you've ruined it.
Where the hell were you?
Hey. Come on.
Hey, don't leave...
Eh, Anna... I mean, Zora!
Shit.
Everything okay?
You smoking again?
So, um, you good?
Listen, she's a monster, Anna.
She's manipulative, she's possessive,
she's insecure...
It must be awful, Julius.
I really fucked things up, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know I did.
Can I tell you something?
Fuck!
What?
I miss you. Okay? So, so much. And I...
I know it's not fair to you,
and I shouldn't say that, but it's true.
You ever...
...miss me?
I know, I shouldn't ask that.
Right?
You drive?
Which one? Red or white, Anna?
Anna?
I used to fantasize about
waking up in your bed.
And I would go to start
packing my things,
and you would grab me.
And you would say,
"Where are you going, Anna?
This is your home, Anna."
That's so stupid, huh?
I'm gonna go.
Hey, hey, hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Where you going?
Pick your weapon.
Oh!
That's it?
I've got an early morning.
Mm.
I'll be looking like Zorro.
Or I'll be the Phantom of Your
Ass. Come on.
- Did you miss that?
- Yeah. You miss this?
Fuck.
- Last time you were inside of me...
- Uh-huh...
Were you thinking about her?
- Who?
- Zora. Were you thinking of her?
Huh? Wha...
Oh, Anna.
Your eyes.
You never looked so beautiful.
And what about the blonde from RMV?
Huh? What?
I don't know what you're talking...
From the party. The blonde.
Oh. Where are you going with this?
I want to know...
- I'm the best...
- The best...
Yeah, you never
could resist a little bit of rope, huh?
- Guess not.
- Fucking ride that dick.
Ride that shit hard...
I'm the best?
- Fuckin' best, baby.
- Best you ever had?
Best I fucking had!
Then why did you leave?
- Could... Could you chill out, baby?
It's a little sensitive down there.
I can relate.
Aah! Aah!
I did what the box told me.
- Hello?
- Hey, Linda?
Hey, it's Anna.
Uh, you know that book? Unc's book?
I never finished the moss girl story.
Could you read it to me?
Right now?
Just from the part
where she gets the wig.
You know,
it helps me fall asleep.
That's... not weird at all.
So, slave girl... Moss...
Blah, blah, blah. All right...
"She made herself a wig.
"She sees herself in the mirror
and she thinks she looks good.
"Almost like someone else
was staring back at her. Someone was.
"She came across a slave crying
on account of massa's whip,
"and looked down and see her wig
start drinking the blood from his wound.
"'What kind of moss is this?' she say.
"But with his dying breath,
he tell her, 'That ain't moss.
"'That's the hair of witches
from the before time.
"'They need blood to grow strong enough
to take over a person's body.
"'Then, they can come back to the world.'
"She ain't want to believe him,
"but then she feel her hair
wrap around her neck,
"and strangle her.
"Even now, if you still see her
walking around them woods,
"remember, it's only her body.
The witches take turns in her head."
Welcome, honey.
Thank you for taking me last minute.
All good.
I had an opening, like I said.
This gon' take a while
to get all this out.
...first of all, okay,
'cause I know who my daddy is.
Couple hours.
- Okay.
All right, Coral.
Miss Thing better be ready,
'cause I don't have all night.
Well...
I didn't know you went here, Edna.
Crowned is Black Hollywood's
secret weapon.
'Course, you'd know that if
you didn't have a thing
about people being in your hair.
If that were ever true.
- She's fucking killing me.
- Aisha will be out in a minute.
- No, I do. I have to go.
I told you that.
It's kind of funny seeing you here.
Damn, this is in here tight.
- Ow!
- Okay, hey, hey.
Don't go there with that.
I'm sorry. It hurts so bad.
- I fucked up.
- Jesus, Anna.
It's just hair.
Edna, I'm so sorry.
You were my friend and my mentor.
I just got caught up. I got...
really caught up.
I'm still caught up.
Ow.
You know I talk a lot of shit.
But the truth is,
I can't fault you for doing
whatever it takes
to get where they keep trying
to keep us from getting.
And fuck you. The hair looks good.
That's probably why I'm so mad.
You know, in a perfect world,
a woman would be able to wear her hair
the fuck the way she wants to.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, if she wants another weave,
I ain't the one.
Can you put it up in a bun, please?
What's that, darlin'?
Uh, just put it up as tight as you can.
Uh, I don't want to yank it.
I'm tender headed.
Girl, I'm so sorry.
Y'all, this surfer nigga from Venice
got me so twisted. Mm.
I don't know. You got a surfer
colonizing your lands?
Oh, Lord.
- Be right back.
- Jesus.
Anna...
Oh, shit!
Aah!
Oh! Aah!
No!
It's Zora.
Can't come to the phone right now,
so please leave a message.
Truth be told,
I'm probably still at the office.
Oh, Sheryl!
Zora?
Anna.
Something bad has happened.
Oh, I'm aware.
It's happening to you, too.
What do you mean?
How many lives has it taken?
It's so strange.
One moment you think
you recognize yourself,
and then the next
there's this rush of hunger.
Sheryl came in. All kind of job demands.
Spelling out all of her strengths.
If only timing was one of them.
This is happening to other people?
Let me check with my killer weave
support group
and find out their sentiments.
I don't fucking know
what's happening with everyone else!
Now, who else have you told about this?
- No one!
- Of course not!
No one would fuckin' believe it!
That rush of hunger.
How often do you get it?
- At first, it was like, once in a while.
Then it started to be constant.
And some days it doesn't stop.
Do you get the dreams, too?
Oh, my God.
It's... It's trying to get in here.
It wants to take over us.
Fuck it. It's just hair.
Just... It's just hair.
- It won't let you! It won't let you!
- It's fucking just hair!
Aah! Aah!
Unc?
Anna.
- What are you doing?
- I couldn't sleep. What's your excuse?
And how often do you come by in the...
...dead of night?
Are you looking for anything
in particular?
Uh, the, um...
uh, moss haired girl.
Anything hair-related, really.
Yeah, so, this one has a few
hair stories in it.
It's mostly from American Indian tribes.
There are some tribes who believe that
a person's hair holds all their thoughts,
even after death.
The idea being that
one must have pure intentions,
so that enemies can't use
the hair they leave behind
for evil spells.
"First, there was only the
wild beasts and the red man."
Do you think the moss tree story
could somehow be related?
Like, uh, maybe the hair in the tree
was enchanted, or...
I don't know.
It's fun to think about.
But didn't you say that
the native tribes of this land
and the ones brought here were wise
about things we've forgotten?
Things we consider... magic?
Sure. But the minute you start
supposing and what if-ing,
and now you've, you've, you've
stereotyped a whole group of people.
If there's something that
they were trying to warn us about,
or even, if there's something real, then...
We'd never know.
Conquerors don't write much
about the people they conquer.
What is this about?
I'm doing a segment. Um...
...inspired by you.
A little hair history thing.
That's very sweet.
Um, time to put this old man to bed.
Past my bedtime, so...
Always good to see you, honey.
- You, too.
- Mm.
You look...
...beautiful.
Hey, it's Anna.
Leave a message.
Anna, it's Rosalyn.
It's almost noon. Where are you?
Ooh. Not today, Satan. Not today.
Anna! Oh, thank God.
No one's been able to reach Zora.
Have you heard from her?
No.
Anna.
- Honey, are you okay?
- Yeah.
No, I know. It's been so crazy.
Anna...
We need a host.
You sure about the belt?
It's pristine. Nice heels.
- Thank you.
- It's time.
What's up, America?
I'm Anna Bludso, your host for today.
Now, if you've been watching
the promos,
I know you were expecting
someone a little taller,
a little more model-esque, but...
Psych! You got me!
Okay, all right, all right.
Welcome to Cult Live!
All the fans out here are going crazy.
You know why? 'Cause they want to know
who's got the number one spot.
Okay. Well, we're down to our top two.
- Who got it?
- What haven't we seen yet?
Well, you know, we ain't seen
"Break U" by The Fellas yet.
And you know I mess with The Fellas.
Sometimes.
Okay. Our number two video is...
Which means our number one video...
Wait, wait, wait!
Now, everyone at Cult knows
Anna is Sandra's biggest fan
in the whole world.
So, we thought we'd do something
special...
All right, sis. Do you mind?
And the number one video is...
Sorry Fellas...
"I Get It," by me!
And... commercial.
Goodnight. See you all tomorrow.
Zora.
Anna.
- Hey.
- Hey, girl.
Wow. You were...
- great.
- Ros, did you see Zora?
No, Anna. She's totally M. I. A.
I saw her looking out of that window.
I've been organizing her office
for hours. She's not here.
Ros, I saw her.
Anna...
there's something...
Ros?
Ro...
What's the code?
Help me!
Somebody help me! No!
Fuck!
Oh, shit! What the fuck!
Come on, man. I ain't one of them!
- You're not?
- No!
What were you doing upstairs?
I thought motherfuckers
was going up there to celebrate,
so shit, I went, too.
Shit, I was trying to blend in with these
zombie bitches to keep 'em at bay.
Brook, you gotta take this out.
I don't know the last time
you went to Virgie's...
- Virgie's?
Bitch, I ain't got $500 to give her!
Especially when La'Neka
hook a sister up for $250!
Look, I cannot die today, okay?
I haven't been to church
in like, 15 years.
Aah!
Anna!
Shit.
Aah!
This bitch is trying to kill me!
Anna, cut this bitch!
Bitch, what is you doin'?
I done seen all the Jason movies.
You ain't gotta check to see
if she's dead!
Come on!
I should have died back there.
But I'll tell you what.
That crazy hoe had them blue eyes
directed on you. Okay?
Come on, come on, come on, come on...
Uh, h... Hey. Hey, hey, girl.
Hey.
Did you forget your coat?
Shit.
Please, please, please.
Please, God. Please, somebody.
What the fuck?
Okay, okay, okay.
"Porcine albumin."
Pig's blood?
This is a fucking appetizer.
Oh, love your hair! Super cute.
Thanks. It's a little tight,
but hopefully my boyfriend
fucks it loose tonight.
I'm just kidding. I need it to last.
Okay, here's the last of it.
At least for me, it is.
Girl, I can't carry no more of your stuff.
What'd you pack in there? Bricks?
Oh, and before I forget to tell you,
I'm gonna be late for dinner tonight.
I'm doing something super top secret.
Can't tell you. Okay, fine.
Don't pull my leg...
"Even now, if you see the moss haired girl
"walking around in them woods,
"remember, it's only her body.
The witches take turns in her head."
"As for massa,
"he was survived by two boys
"who would take over the land
and all that grew upon it,"
"including the hair that seemed like
moss on the trees."
"The way they saw it,
"as long as their name
was on the land,"
"they could do as they pleased
with anything that grew from it..."
"Whether it was plants..."
"Or people."
"If it grew on the land,
their daddy claimed..."
"They owned it."
"And it owned them."
Anna.
Um, what'd you say?
I said I may be late for dinner.
I finally got in at Virgie's!
Girl, I am so over this
Creamy Crack relaxer!
Just put someone else's hair
on my head and call it a day!
Linda!