I'm very, very tired.
I would like one very, very quiet room.
Is that for a very, very quiet room?
All right. If you say so.
A witch's brew for me and you
With goblin poo and pig slop goo
A hotel guest?
To serve and uphold
the comfort of each guest.
To strive for perfection in guest hospitality.
These are the bylaws of
the Hotel Transylvania
as written by its manager and founder,
Count Dracula.
Pardon me, your guest—ship.
But will you be needing anything?
The poor dear,
all tuckered out like a wee baby.
What a horrible draft.
He'll surely catch death of a cold.
Hey, broom. Broom.
Hey, broom. Hey!
That spider will wake him for sure.
You're dead, pesky noisemaker.