- ♪ La la la
♪ La la la
♪ And if that dog
named Rover won't bark ♪
♪ Auntie's gonna buy
you a horse and cart ♪
♪ And if that horse
and cart fall down ♪
♪ You're still the sweetest
little girl in-- ♪
[ Creaking ]
It's all right.
Don't worry about a thing.
- Good night, love bug.
- Good night, Mommy.
Happy New Year.
What's wrong with Mommy?
- Sometimes people's
minds wear out.
They get a little tired.
Your mom just needs to
take a break, that's all.
- Good night, Auntie Judith.
- Good night, love bug.
You get under the covers.
Hmm...
[ Chuckling ]
Sleep tight.
I'm going to destroy you,
you maniac!
Leave, before I call the police!
[ Screaming ]
[ Thump ]
[ Knock and scream ]
- I'm sorry.
[ Sobbing ]
I'm sorry.
[ Woman mumbling ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Woman sobbing ]
- Mommy?
Mommy?
What's going on?
- Alex!
- Mommy!
[ Screaming ]
- Alex!
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Exhaling ]
- Sam, you're killing me.
It's been years since
I dreamt about it.
- Hey, you're the one who
opened it up for discussion.
By the way, I am
charging you for this.
- Oh, that's real nice.
I'm not that scared little
6-year-old anymore, you know?
You know what? You owe me some
freebies, so I'm collecting.
- All right. So what all
happened while I was away?
- Well, be proud of me.
I'm taking control of my life.
- Whoa, whoa.
Now I'm afraid.
What's up?
- I'm divorcing Dan and I'm
moving back into the brownstone.
- Whoa, whoa. Stop.
Come on. Let's hear it.
What's up?
- Look, this is what you get
for being a world-reknowned
psychiatrist
and being on a lecture
tour for 2 months.
Just be happy for me, Sam.
- I'm elated you're leaving Dan.
You shouldn't have married him.
But as a psychiatrist--
- I know what you think:
That's why I had this dream,
and I shouldn't move
into the brownstone.
But trust me on this.
I know what I'm doing.
- That's not
what I'm afraid of.
- Come on, old man!
- Old man?
I'll show you some old man!
I'm so charging you for this!
- Hi, J.J.
- Hey, Mrs. Lambeth! How was
the jog this morning?
- The park was beautiful.
I got you this.
- This is why you're
my favorite tenant.
Always thinking of my stomach.
Good morning, Mr. Lambeth.
- Take care of my
lovely wife, J.J.
- Please, Dan.
What the hell's
going on in here?
- Mrs. Lambeth,
Jacob Anderson.
Mr. Lambeth hired us
to take inventory
of the assets
for the divorce.
We'll be out of
here in a few hours.
- Mr. Hickson, please.
Alexandra Lambeth.
He no longer represents me?
A conflict of interest?
Thank you.
- No, I'm sorry.
You can't take that.
- It was my aunt's.
I came into the marriage
with it, I'm leaving with it.
OK?
- Fine.
- So what else did my husband
take out of the apartment?
- Some personal effects.
- Oh, I see.
- I've been
asked to inform you
that this apartment is
part of Tregold's holdings.
Therefore it doesn't belong
to you or your husband.
The company will be assuming
occupancy as of the 14th
and you'll be asked to
surrender your keys by then.
- Oh, really? I'd
like to do that now.
- Mrs. Lambeth--
- It's Kent. Miss Kent.
- Mrs. Kent--
- I don't want any
of it, all right?
I'll just be upstairs
collecting some of
my personal effects.
- Well, there's one last thing.
I've been asked to inform
you that your invitation
to the children's charity
reception still stands.
- Because you're no
longer sitting on my couch
paying me for my advice,
as I friend, I get to say this.
I don't think you
should live here.
- You know, you're starting
to sound like a parrot.
I love you for it.
I really thank you for clearing
your schedule to do this.
- I wouldn't let you
exorcise this beast alone.
- It's just a house.
With the changes I've
made, it's now my house.
Come on.
- Hey...
You all right?
- Yes, I'm fine.
It looks great, huh?
- Um-hmm.
- Miss Kent?
Still have a few things to fix,
but we're pretty much
done in the living room.
- You did a great job, Ed.
- Thanks.
No real structural problems
except the 2nd floor.
We moved the rest of the
furniture up to the attic
like you requested.
And everything's been rewired
to bring you up to code.
Let me show you the pool.
We've totally upgraded it.
I really think you're
going to like it.
[ Running water ]
She's a beauty, huh?
Sealed two streamline cracks,
but they weren't a problem.
A little tempermental
to clean...
Come, I'll show you upstairs.
- Bye, Sammy.
- Everything looks real good.
- All right, I'll
call you later.
- All right, honey. Bye-bye.
[ Men working and talking ]
- Uh, Ed?
Uh...
Glad you're here.
I believe I owe you this.
- Oh, thanks.
- Wow...
- Miss Kent, can I
ask about the key?
- Oh, I'm gonna need a set...
- No, I meant the
rose around your neck.
- Um sorry, but
this isn't a key.
- May I?
- Sure.
[ Chuckles ]
- Oh yeah. This looks
like a pendant.
Watch.
- I never knew!
- I saw my first one
about 20 years ago.
It was a butterfly,
and I've seen 3 others.
- How did you--
- It's become a
fascination with me.
It was made back in '29,
after the Market crashed.
This very famous locksmith,
Stanley Gruman,
he was hired by some
of society's elite
to hide the keys to
vault rooms in pendants.
- To a vault room?
- A hidden room in the house
where they would
store valuables.
Behind a false wall
in a cellar or attic.
Sort of pride myself
on finding them.
I'd be very happy to
look for it if you'd like.
- No, that won't be necessary.
Thank you.
- I've taken care of the new
artists and the Bowen exhibits.
The gallery will be fine
without you for a few days.
Even the boss
deserves time off.
[ Sighs ]
- Oh, I'd better be careful.
You just might replace me.
- Yeah well, I am getting
a little addicted
to the power, you know?
- Miss Kent?
Can I have a word?
- Sure.
- Your check was returned.
- That's not possible.
I'll take care of it, OK?
- I'm going to cut my
crew down until you do.
Sorry.
All right guys,
let's wrap it up.
- Yeah.
Really...
I understand.
- So?
What's the Prince
Charming update?
- Well, he froze
all of our accounts.
I have zero money.
- You're taking
this very well.
You are going to fight him?
- No, I'm not
going to fight him.
That's exactly what he wants.
I'll just draw a
paycheck from the gallery.
- Welcome to the fabulous land
of high credit card debt
and week-to-week living.
You'll love it. Forget Dan.
- Yeah, forget Dan.
- Besides, you have
a mysterious key!
- I do have a mysterious key!
You're right.
To a mysterious room.
Come on, let's get some
champagne and start looking.
Let's start by
tapping on the walls.
- Tap all you want,
I'm going for refills.
- Looking, looking...
- Looking...
- We'd probably do better
if we weren't drinking.
- Like I'd even be doing
this if we weren't.
Found some antique dust bunnies!
- Where's this damn room?
[ Both sigh ]
- It's like not being able to
finish The Timescrossword.
I mean, where does someone
hide a whole room?
- I have no idea.
We looked everywhere.
- Yeah.
- Don't you have
a meeting to go to?
- You're really
OK living here?
- Mmm...
Yeah. I'm OK living here.
- Oh, when you see Dan, will
you smack him for me once?
- How about twice?
[ Laughing ]
[ Chatter ]
Hey, sweetie.
Your shoe is undone here.
Don't want you to fall
down and hurt yourself.
There you go.
That's a pretty dress.
- Thank you.
- [Dan]: Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your
attention, please?
Thank you.
I just want to take
a moment to say welcome
and thank you for joining us
for our annual children's
fundraising event.
As you are aware,
there are thousands of kids
all across this world
who lack even the basic
necessities of life.
And our organization
comes together...
- You were great with her.
Have any kids of your own?
- Not so much as
a pet or a plant.
[ Chuckling ]
- I'm Mike Stanheight.
- Um, Alexandra Kent.
- You close with
yours? Your mom?
- Listen Mr. Stanheight...
You don't know me
and I don't know you.
- You're right, I'm sorry.
It's none of my business.
- No harm done.
- Occupational hazard.
I should wear
a neon sign warning,
"Head of Psychiatry,
Metro General. Run!"
- How's that make you feel?
[ Both laughing ]
- Touché.
Well it all started when my
father wouldn't allow me
to dress up my goldfish Eli--
- Dr. Stanheight, I really
should be going back downstairs.
But it was nice meeting you.
- You too, Miss Kent.
- Our office will call
you next week. All right?
Thank you.
- Yeah. All right.
- Alex...
You look stunning.
- Dan, please.
You know, you
already made your move
by taking my lawyer and
freezing our bank accounts.
Well, here's mine.
I remove myself of everything.
The money's yours.
- Well, don't be ridiculous!
We both know that you
cannot support yourself.
- Wrong about that.
I still have the money
from my aunt's estate
and there's the gallery.
It's time we say goodbye.
Thank you.
- Yeah, it's an awkward
time to get a cab.
- Oh...
- Here, let me try.
[ Honking ]
[ She laughs ]
- Uh, I think you're
scaring them away.
- I think you're
probably right.
- See? It's all in the wrist.
Thank you, though.
- You're welcome.
Hey, um...
If you ever want to not talk...
- Thanks.
- And it's Mike.
- It was nice to meet you, Mike.
- You too.
- And it's Alexandra.
- Bye.
- It's the perfect time.
She took her meds and
she's out for the night.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
[ Door opens in hallway ]
[ Screaming ]
- Who are you?
Who are you?
- Alex, I'm sorry. I should
have gone over there with you.
- No.
I needed to go on my own.
- Don't...
Don't put any faith
into this, all right?
We've been down this road.
Your mother suffers from
severe psychotic delusions
and paranoia.
This is her way of
denying what happened.
It enables her to live in
her world without guilt.
- I know.
I know. I'm just...
[ Sighs ]
I'm just mad at myself.
I thought enough
time had passed by.
He asked me if
I missed her and...
How do you miss something
you never had, you know?
I don't have a mother.
I never had a mother.
- Hey.
I'm proud of you.
You faced down your fears,
you went and saw her.
I mean, that had to be
really, really difficult.
- Yeah.
You're a dear friend.
Thank you.
[ Sighing ]
- I'm sorry.
Did I startle you?
- What are you
doing in my house?
- This house.
See, I've always
loved this house.
For years I suggested
we move here.
Funny how now you
decide to do so.
- How did you get in?
- Don't get upset.
I had the contractor make me
a set of keys when I paid him.
- I want you to leave.
- Come on, Ali.
I miss you, I need you.
- Please, Dan.
- Let's stop this.
I want you to come home.
- I'm taking control
of my life now.
- You love me.
- I did.
- You will again.
- I won't!
- Listen to me, Alexandra!
I am not screwing around here!
Now, I can make it
very difficult for you
and make sure you
get absolutely nothing!
- Fine.
'Cause you don't
own me anymore.
Give me my keys.
[ Door closing ]
- Are you OK?
Alex, you scared me!
Look at me!
Are you all right?
- Fine! Fine!
- Here, this will take
the edge off anything.
You're keeping the bottle.
- What is it?
- It's the 8th wonder
of the world: Valium.
Don't give me
any lip. Swallow.
- One?
- One.
So, what were you
trying to do exactly?
Break an underwater
record or something?
- I don't know. I don't
know what I was thinking.
- Well, after what
Dan did tonight,
of course your mind would race.
I'm staying with you a few days.
- Thank you.
So, what's going
on at the gallery?
What's wrong?
- Dan took it from you.
He had some schlumpy
lawyer camped out.
He was yanking the poor
guy's electronic leash
every 10 minutes for an
update on your reaction.
I didn't have the heart to tell
him you'd hadn't been in lately.
- Who is he handing
the reins to?
- Alex, I say go
after the gallery.
Fight him for it.
- It's you?
Of course. You're
the perfect choice.
[ Sighing ]
I'm thinking of opening
a gallery of my own.
- A gallery costs money.
A lot of money. And last I
heard, you don't have any.
Unless you found
that hidden room.
- I'll throw a reception here,
attract a few investors...
some artists...
- You know the kind of
business we could do here?
- We?
- Dan!
- Sam! To what do I
owe this displeasure?
- Leave her alone.
She's finally got
a chance to be happy.
Don't take that
away from her.
- Hmm. Always her protector.
You know, you really
must be loving this.
After all, this is what
you've always wanted.
Having Alexandra
all to yourself.
- Oh, come on, Dan!
You're tearing her
apart, all right?
Just grow up and let it go.
- I'll tell you what.
I'll make you a deal.
I'll let her go when you do.
Now if you excuse me,
I'm late for a meeting.
- I couldn't find your coffee.
I'll go get some later on.
Here you go.
[ Doorbell ]
Oh, I'll get that.
Oh, good morning!
She's right here.
Alex?
- Miss Kent, thank you
for understanding.
Mr. Lambeth said the two
of you were reconciling.
I really should have
checked with you first.
- Yeah, Dan can be
very persuasive.
Here's the new set of keys.
- I guess the
silver lining is that
we were both paid in
full and then some.
I can start up again
anytime you'd like.
- Actually, there's going
to be some design changes
so if you could give
us a couple of days...
- Sure.
- Oh Ed, do us a favour.
Take a picture of us.
It'll be a great publicity
still for our investors.
- A picture of us...
Of course! A picture of us.
- Is everything
all right, Miss Kent?
- That's it.
There had to be somebody
else in this room.
- Is something wrong, Alex?
- I gotta go.
I gotta go.
Sorry, Gina.
- Thanks.
I think you're a really
great artist too.
Do you want to borrow
some of my curlers?
- Mother?
Mother?
- I really like orange.
- It's Alexandra.
I have to ask you something.
Who is this man here?
Who is this?
You see this picture?
It's New Year's Eve.
There's you, Aunt Judith,
and me.
At the Christmas tree.
Someone was in this
room that night, right?
Someone was in this room.
So, can you tell me
who was in the room?
Who took the picture?
[ Inhaling ]
Somebody had to take
the picture, right?
Can you tell me who
took the picture?
Mother, please tell me
who took the picture.
I need to know who
took the picture.
Just stop colouring!
I don't need you to colour, I
want you to answer my question!
Who took the picture?
Please tell me who
took this picture!
I need to know! Damn it!
What is wrong with you?
You got to tell me!
No! Please tell me!
- You must leave.
You're upsetting her.
I know you know who took this!
- She can't understand you!
Please, leave now
before I call security!
- No! She knows who...
- Gentlemen came everyday
and little Blue Betty
hopped away.
[ Laughing ]
She hopped upstairs
to make her bed
and tumbled down
and broke her head.
I broke her head!
- Calm down!
- I broke her head!
I broke her head!
- Don't let me stop you crying.
No analyzing or consoling
while I'm on lunch break.
Look...
I owe you an apology.
I should have told you
I was Evelyn's doctor.
I've been working with
your mom about 6 months.
I...
I like her.
I want to help her.
I went to that party
looking for you.
I saw it as a way to unlock
some of her mysteries.
Maybe plant the seeds for a
reconciliation. I don't know.
I do know you weren't
what I was expecting.
Not at all.
- I should be going.
- If there's anything
I can ever do...
or not do.
- Thanks.
Excuse me.
- We sedated her.
I've never seen her
this out of control.
Drawing all over everything,
fighting with us...
She even smashed the
mirror in the bathroom.
I'll be next door
if you need me.
- That's it, isn't it?
- Don't you understand?
Somebody else had to be in
that room to take that picture.
- You know, I don't want
you investing yourself
in these pictures.
It isn't healthy.
They probably used
a timer or something.
Alex, the past is
the past, all right?
Just let it go.
- It's not that easy, Sam.
[ Sighing ]
You should have seen
her. It was awful.
I've been so angry with
her for so many years.
I just wanted her
to tell me the truth.
Tell me what happened.
Her mind is gone. She's...
...wasting away.
- So you're hoping these
pictures, these drawings
will give you the
answers that you do like
to make her a
saint or a martyr.
Well, let me tell
you something, Alex:
You can't change what she did
or who she is, period.
You can't. You cannot.
Now, I thought you knew that.
- I do.
I just opened myself up
to her all over again and...
Add on the living in
the brownstone and Dan...
Why am I second
guessing myself?
- Well, make it simple.
Cut her out of your life.
You can't allow yourself
to feel sorry for her.
You made the break
that you needed to.
So now, sell the brownstone.
Let me take care of Dan.
- No, I'll handle him.
- You need another attorney.
One that's not going
to sell you out.
I'm going to give
Brian Segray a call.
- I can call him.
- Better yet, I'll
get you his number.
- What?
- Oh, where do the years go?
You know that you were
my first child patient.
You were unresponsive,
catatonic,
but you had a mean right hook.
And very sharp teeth.
So, you kind of glossed
over selling the brownstone.
How is it living there anyway?
Anything you want to discuss?
- Discuss.
Nice segue back
into doctor-patient.
No, I'm not going to sell it.
Because then it wins.
Besides, I'm getting
very comfortable there.
A few twinges in the night...
It's nothing, though.
- Twinges?
- I'm invoking my
non-patient rights here.
- All right.
One more comment and
I'll let you off the hook.
If you live where such a
traumatic event occurred
it could trigger things in you.
Twinges.
I want you to promise me
that you will come to me
if it gets to be too much.
- It's getting used to bumps
in the night. It's fine.
Besides, Gina's staying
with me for a while.
- Nevertheless, I'd like to
prescribe something for you.
- Oh, I got that covered.
- How so?
- Gina gave me
some Valium she had.
- Not a bad choice. Pretty much
what I would have suggested.
So, Valium it is.
- Good evening, sir.
- I'm looking for
an Alexandra Kent.
Oh, sorry. Lambeth.
This is listed as
her contact address.
I'm her mother's physician.
- Hmm.
She moved into her family's
house on the east side.
You tell her J.J. says hi.
- You're looking
for my wife?
I don't believe we've
been introduced.
Dan Lambeth.
- Mike Stanheight.
- Yeah, I know who you are.
You're mommy dearest's doctor.
So tell me, Mike,
how is dear old
Evelyn these days?
- I'm not at liberty to
discuss her condition with you.
- Hmm.
Are you always in the habit
of bringing flowers
to your patients?
Come on, Mike. Using Evelyn
to get closer to Ali...
It's a novel approach,
but it won't work.
A word of advice, our
separation is merely temporary.
- Fortunately, you don't
get to make that decision.
She does.
- Actually, it was first and
my last camping experience.
More of an electricity and
running water kind of girl.
- Certainly explains the
lack of fire right now.
- I wouldn't know
how to save my life.
- Come on, let me show you.
- These are beautiful.
- It's the only thing
I remember from Scouts.
- You were a Scout?
- Yeah! Come on.
- There you go.
Ow!
- Ooh!
- Ow!
- Oh, Jesus Christ!
Geez, I don't think
you're going to make it.
- Ahh... that burns.
- Just in case.
- Did you learn
that in Scouts too?
[ Both chuckle ]
- Well, I'd hate to say you
have to have it amputated.
- Yeah, that would be bad.
I'm really glad
you came here.
[ Voices ]
Ah!
- Hi, love bug.
You're just like me.
[ Screaming ]
- It's OK. You're just
having a bad dream.
- You know, you should go.
- Just tell me what it was.
- I'm gonna go
to the bathroom.
I really want you
to just not be here.
[ Door closing ]
- Gentlemen came every day...
Ah!
Little Blue Betty hopped away!
- Gina?
Gina, are you here?
[ Clanging ]
Ah!
- Oh. You OK?
- Yeah, I...
I just... Oh, God.
I... I didn't know
anybody was here.
- Just me and Gina.
She's up here, I think.
- Thanks.
- OK.
[ Sighing ]
- Listen, Ed. Let me talk
to you for a second.
- Yeah?
- Well, now really
isn't a good time.
I was wondering if you could
finish the work up here later.
- No, that's not good.
I've got another job later.
- I'm asking if you could
like, leave, basically.
[ Scoffs ]
- Whatever you'd like.
- Where's he going?
Ed, where are you going?
- I asked him to leave.
- Hold on, Ed!
You can't do that, Alex!
You know, I quit
my job for this!
We need the work
done for the gallery!
[ Ed and Gina talking quietly ]
- [Ed]: I don't care!
[ Door opening and closing ]
- He'll be back tomorrow.
- What were you doing up there?
- I was looking for
the hidden room.
I was mapping layout for gallery
storage. You want to see?
- No, no. I trust you.
Um look, I'm fine
staying here by myself.
I think Dan's done the
worst that he can do.
So consider yourself sprung.
- Alex...
- Mike, I can't talk right now.
- Alex, there's
been an accident.
[ Sighing ]
Your mom's dead.
Alex, it was an accident.
- You're lying.
- She got into the common room.
She broke a mirror...
- You're lying.
- She knicked an artery.
Alex!
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Sobbing ]
- Why?
What if they were more
than just drawings?
And I didn't believe her?
I'm the one that agitated her.
- You can't feel responsible
for her death, Alex.
- But what I'm seeing
and what I'm hearing
are memories I'm never going
to be able to forgive myself.
What is it, Sam? I mean,
I'm becoming paranoid!
I don't want to be like her!
- If you really want to
get to the bottom of this
we can work it through.
Break down every detail
that you remember
with everything that
you're experiencing now.
Or if you'd like
to give it a try,
we could regress you.
Alex, I want you to just
focus on the pendant.
Try to look right through it.
And breathe...
And focus on the pendant.
Let the pendant bring you back.
The pendant is
taking you back.
Back...
The pendant is taking you back.
- Mommy!
No!
Oh God!
Oh my God!
- It's OK. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Alex, I'm so sorry.
I should have known.
Alex, you witnessed your
mother murder your aunt
and then she tried to kill you.
Listen.
You and I know
that you're afraid of
becoming like Evelyn.
But I think that
subconsciously, Alex,
you think that you are Evelyn
and that you might
have even killed.
- I would never do that, Sam!
- No, no. I know.
I agree.
- Oh!
- But with all the stress
that you're under right now
with Dan, and your mother,
and that brownstone
your mind is just having
a little trouble adjusting.
Now listen, listen.
I need you to tell me.
Have you had any of these
episodes outside of the house?
- Sam, you're scaring me! I'm
not having a breakdown, Sam!
- You're not having a breakdown.
Now, the Valium's fine, Alex.
But I'd like you to try
something more targeted
to your own anxiety, all right?
I want you to take
these for a few days
to see how they work for you.
If it's a fit, I'll
get you a prescription.
- OK.
- Good.
- Thank you.
- Listen...
I'm going to make the
arrangements for your mother.
I'll take care of that.
And I will get you through
this. I promise you.
I promise you.
- Thank you.
- What were you trying to say?
[ Knocking ]
- Alex! Alex!
Alex! What the
hell are you doing?
The building inspector's waiting
for you downstairs, remember?
- Oh my God. Um, just
stall him or something.
- OK, but hurry up!
- Ah...
Two...
- I've got your current
building permits
as well as the voided one
that was filed in '85.
These are standard forms.
- Wait. Did you say '85?
What was it for?
- Well, don't know.
But it's the same contractor
you're using now.
- Oh my God.
It was you!
It was you, you murderer!
You murderer!
- What's wrong with you?
- Thought you could void
the permits to hide yourself?
You were wrong!
- What's she talking about?
- Alex, calm down.
He has nothing--
- Was it for the money?
The hidden room?
Is that why you took advantage
of my mentally-ill mother
and you murdered my aunt?
I should murder you myself!
- Go ahead, murder me!
Somebody call the cops.
This woman's nuts!
She needs to be locked up.
- Yeah, call the cops!
- You see this? I had
emergency heart surgery.
I was in the hospital the
week your aunt was murdered.
Don't believe me?
Check the hospital records.
- Why not tell me
you were here before?
- Because I didn't
want to dredge up
any bad memories for you.
You know what? You're psychotic.
I quit.
- Ed, come on! Come on!
- Oh, that's good! Go after him!
I saw you guys conspiring!
I heard the whispering!
- OK, you need to get a grip!
Ed was helping us off the books!
Dan cancelled part
of his payment.
I figured you already had
too much to worry about
so I didn't tell you!
- I didn't know! I didn't...
- Alex,
you need to pull
yourself together.
- You saw her drawings,
my aunt's murder.
In some of them she drew a man.
I want to know if
you think he's real.
- You're asking me if I believe
Evelyn murdered your aunt?
- Do you think
someone else was there?
- I don't think there was.
I think she drew him
to forgive herself.
- Are you saying
she made it up?
- No, no. Her reality split.
She truly believed
there was someone else
when her mind allowed her to.
When it didn't, she saw
herself as the killer.
A mental break is like two
realities overlapping,
constantly weaving,
so they both seem real.
- Two realities? What causes it?
- Genetics, severe trauma,
any number of things.
I can tell you this:
I don't believe her true break
occurred until after the murder.
Give me a second.
I want to show you something.
- I'm not like her.
I'm not like her.
Shouldn't there be another
index card up there?
Or did sleeping with me
not give you enough
insight into my mother?
- Alexandra, it's
not what you think.
Alex, please wait!
- Look, just
stay away from me!
- Alex, let me
explain what you saw.
It's a map of your mother's
mind. How she processed things.
Her two realities.
Your last visit with her
triggered something.
The key to that night, the one
thing she'd never drawn.
This is the "why".
You must want to know.
- No, I don't want to know!
She was insane, all right?
- OK, look, I'm sorry.
Look, I won't
pursue it either.
You're a beautiful, intelligent
woman who I want to get to know,
not analyze.
You have to believe I didn't
become intimate with you
for any other reason.
- I don't know. I just don't
want to see you anymore.
Hey, Sam.
- Oh, hi. I was just
coming to see you.
- Yeah? What's up?
These are her things, huh?
- The sanitarium handed
them over to me and...
I'm sorry. I didn't know how
to prepare you for this.
OK...
What's happening here?
- Nothing. It's fine, it's fine.
- Stop, stop.
Why don't I take these?
I don't think this is a
good idea for you right now.
- No, I got it.
It's fine, it's fine.
I'm tired.
I got it.
- OK.
Alex...
Get some rest, OK?
I'll see you tomorrow.
- OK, so just make sure
these are taken care of
and I guess we
can fudge the rest.
There you go.
- Sure.
- All right, here's
what I got to say.
I was way out of line,
and I'm truly sorry for that.
- Yeah, you were an ass.
But I forgive you.
- No harm done.
I guess I should have told
you about the other job, huh?
- Thanks.
Well, in honour of...
[ Both laughing ]
- Oh, you'll score a few
dates with that one.
- You think?
I don't know about that.
- Oh yeah.
- Some champagne?
- Thank you.
- Have I told you
how proud I am of you?
You're really doing it. You are
taking control of your life.
Well, here's to
your new gallery.
- To the gallery, and
to you being in my life.
Thanks for coming.
- All right.
- Can you take this?
- OK.
- Thanks.
- I had them add just
a bit of cranberry.
I remember how
much you enjoyed it.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
I didn't invite you
here to become friends.
It's not like that we're--
- Ali, I know.
We're getting a
divorce. I know this.
I just thought maybe
one drink, one toast?
- Oh. Well, one's all you get.
- One is all I need.
To getting you back.
- No.
You'll never change.
How about...
To saying goodbye.
- Goodbye, Ali.
- Get away from me!
Get away from me!
Get away from my life!
Oh my God!
I just don't know
what's wrong with me.
I feel like
I'm losing my mind.
I mean, I was fine all day
today. Absolutely fine.
- Ali, shh...
Listen to me. It's
going to be all right.
Here, just lie back
on the couch. Come on.
Atta girl.
- Thank you.
- I'll get you some water.
- [Dan]: A little
bit of cranberry...
I had them add just a
little bit of cranberry.
I remember how much
you enjoyed that.
I just thought maybe
one drink, one toast?
One is all I need.
One drink is all I need.
Ali...
- Oh...
- Is everything
all right?
- I'm just really,
really tired.
I think sleep is good.
I'm just going to go to bed.
I'll call you tomorrow.
- No, no, no. I'm going
to sleep here tonight.
And make sure
you're all right.
- No, I'm fine.
I'm completely fine.
- I insist, and I will not
take no for an answer.
Now, come on.
- OK. All right.
- Here we go.
Don't worry about that
mess, OK? I'll clean it up.
And I'll be right
here if you need me, OK?
I'll need a pillow.
- Right.
- You're trembling!
- Yeah.
- Let's get you
tucked into bed.
- No, I'm fine.
- Good night, Alexandra.
- Good night.
[ Door slams and thumping ]
- Alex?
Alex?
My God, what have you done?
- Sam?
- I'm her doctor.
OK, let's get up now.
Slowly, slowly...
Hey, hey...
It's me.
Alex...
I've hired the best criminal
lawyer in the city.
And we are going to get you
out of this. I promise.
I just wish you'd listened
to me about Dan.
Everything's going
to be all right.
Just rest now.
Now you just rest.
- [P.A.]: Dr. Keane,
call your service...
- What happened to your hand?
- Playing tennis.
I'd like to handle
Alexandra's treatment
before she's transferred.
- I understand. I'll get
it OK'd with the ward.
Give me a couple of days.
- It's been cleared.
I'll bring her file
with me tomorrow.
I've noted the Haldol
dosage on her chart.
- She'll be out
a couple of hours.
I'll take a run
at her later today.
- That won't be necessary.
I'll be the only
one working with her.
Just keep her sedated
'till the morning.
The rest will do her good.
- [P.A.]: Dr. Howley, please
report to Radiology.
Dr. Peter Howley.
- Mind if I show you something?
Evelyn started drawing this
after Alexandra's first visit.
Does it mean anything to you?
I can't seem to figure it out.
- Mike, you're a doctor
with a bright future.
Don't make the same mistake I
did by dwelling on a patient
that you can no longer help.
- How are you feeling?
- Like garbage.
- At least you're awake.
Listen, I have to ask:
If you'd prefer
another doctor...
- No.
- Dr. Bradburn's bringing
your files down tomorrow.
I've got his notation on your
chart that you're on Haldol.
He forgot to write
down the dosage.
Do you know what it was?
Was it a blue or a green pill?
- Uh...
It was a anti-anxiety
medication.
- When did you stop the Haldol?
- I was never prescribed it.
- Can you describe
the anti-anxiety pill?
- Uh...
I don't know. It was...
[ Dripping ]
...square and round.
Uh, yellow and round.
I don't know...
- You OK?
You want a glass of water?
I'm your doctor now.
I want to be your friend.
- I don't remember killing Dan.
- Look, I'm a little confused
about the medication
you were taking.
Do you recognize the pill?
That can't be it.
[ Screaming ]
Alex, what's happening?
Alex, talk to me.
- He gave me the pills.
- Who?
- He killed her.
- Who, Alex?
- The tapes, the tapes.
I know where the tapes are.
- Who?
- Oh my God!
- Who, Alex?
- I remember her
yelling, screaming
'cause she was
going to destroy him.
- Who, Alex?
- He killed her!
He killed my aunt!
- I want to help you.
I'm going to leave
this for you, OK?
I want you to write
everything down.
Make it clear.
I got to check some things out.
I'll be back in
a couple of hours
and we'll discuss this, OK?
Kelly.
Have her blood drawn.
I want to know what residual
drugs are in her system.
Add a request
for Haldol levels.
See if you can work
some of your magic
and have the lab
put a rush on it.
- No problem. I'll
do that for you.
- Thanks.
- Wait! Hold on!
- Dr. Stanheight?
Here are the labs you wanted.
- You're the best.
Hi, this is
Dr. Mike Stanheight
over at Metro General.
I just admitted a patient
who is on staff over there.
I need to know what medications
he's currently taking.
Samuel Bradburn.
How you doing?
- I'm ready to talk.
- Tell me what you
believe has happened.
- I believe Sam murdered my
aunt and blamed my mother.
He's played with my memories,
changed my thinking, and...
I believe he switched the
Valium that I was taking
with some other medication
to make me think
that I was going crazy.
So that if I ever
did remember anything,
everybody would just
not believe me.
He murdered Dan to frame me.
- Tell me what you know.
- I know I'm not insane.
- The lab found no traces
of Haldol in your system.
But did find large
amounts of Penatral,
a blood pressure medication.
Given in high doses, it's known
to create hallucinations,
even psychotic episodes
in people without
high blood pressure.
You'd never be prescribed
that medication.
I know for a fact, Sam was.
But there's no way to prove
that he gave it to you.
You're not insane.
I did a little digging.
I discovered that Sam isolated
and overmedicated Evelyn
for years after the murder.
His course of
treatment made it sure
that no one would be able to
unlock what was in her head.
Again, it doesn't prove anything
except possible patient neglect.
Bradburn's a very
highly-regarded figure
in the psychiatric community.
Proving anything's
going to be difficult.
- The tape's in the brownstone.
I don't know where the room is,
but I've got the key.
- Bye.
- I'm taking her down for an MRI
while there's no traffic.
- Hold on. I'll call
someone to go down with you.
- Down worry about it.
I sedated her.
Won't be conscious till morning.
I'll have her back in 30.
- No, I think I
should call somebody.
- The amount of
drugs I shot in her,
just knit me a hat
while we're gone.
- Sure, if I could figure out
how to keep the
wool on the needles.
- The rabbit goes in
the whole, around the tree
and back out again.
What can I say? I visit my
grandmother during the summers.
- At 30, right?
Around the...
the tree and...
- There's cameras,
so don't move.
OK, let's go.
Let's go!
[ Dog barking in distance ]
- [P.A.]: Please report
to patient room 7329e.
[ Tap dripping ]
- Let me see your wrist.
Let's get rid of this bracelet.
I don't get it.
Evelyn broke the mirror
and drew the videotape
on the plywood backing.
[ Gasping ]
It's a two-way mirror.
Alexandra, stand back.
- The VCR and tape have
to be in the vault room.
Come on.
The hidden room has
to be in here somewhere.
Try to find a
door or something.
Look for a keyhole.
- Did you find something?
- I don't know.
Give me your flashlight.
It's not working.
- Try it again.
- That's it. The vault.
Oh my God.
I was here with my aunt.
There's already a tape in here.
- So, you're sure?
You know what this might be?
- Yes, yes.
There I am.
There's my mother.
What...?
Sam...
What?
Wait! It stopped!
- The tape's run out!
- I need to know what
happened that night!
- Alex, we can figure it out.
- I need to know now.
- Come on. Come on.
I still think this is too
aggressive an environment.
Especially after the tapes.
- No. No, it's not.
[ Sighing ]
- Focus on the flame.
Feel the glow surround you.
And walk yourself
through the flame.
Breathe...
Deeper...
Let yourself go.
- ♪♪ And if that horse
and cart fall down ♪
♪ You'll still be the sweetest
little girl in town ♪♪
You're her doctor!
You took advantage of her!
I want you to leave
before I call the police!
- No! I love her!
- You're sick!
I'm going to destroy you, Sam.
- Give me the damn tape!
- Go to hell!
- I'm sorry.
- You maniac!
Get out!
- Arrgh!
- Mommy?
Mommy?
What's going on?
- [Sam]: Evelyn! Where's
the damn tape?
- Mommy!
[ Screaming ]
[ Doorbell ]
- Happy New Year!
- Help! Help!
In here!
- Mike?
Mike?
- Now you know.
I...
I loved your mother.
And I killed your aunt
so she couldn't destroy me.
No more secrets
between us, Alex.
I manipulated you.
And I drugged you.
And I killed Dan.
And it is all...
your fault!
None of this had to happen.
But you...
Just...
You couldn't leave
the past alone.
Safe with the memories
that I gave you.
That I...
created for you.
Why couldn't you, Alex?
Why couldn't you?
- Don't...
- Why couldn't you?
- Ah!
- It's nothing
personal, sweetheart
No, no, no.
I just want my life back.
Arrgh!
This ends now.
Argh!
[ Screaming ]
- Come on, old man!
- Ah!
[ Breathing heavily ]
Look out, Mike!
- Hold on! Wait up!
Come on! I'm still
recovering here!
- Yeah? You keep telling
yourself that
when I beat you
again tomorrow.
- Uh-huh?
- Come on. I'll make
you some lunch.
Grilled cheese?
- Grilled cheese. Fantastic!
Closed captions:Global Vision