- STAT COM confirms radio
transmission from Raven team.
Gentlemen, insertion
was successful.
Our men are in position.
All that's left now
is the fireworks.
- You're sure cocky
about all this.
- It's all been thought
out, rethought out,
and re-rethought out.
We planned for
every contingency.
666 decoder is ours.
- Well, not ours really.
At least, not for long.
Certainly not for the
price Adeeb is paying us
to hand over that little puppy.
- You guys are sure quick
to crack open the champagne.
All we've done is get
men into enemy territory.
They haven't even
retrieved the decoder,
let alone gotten out.
- They'll get out,
with the decoder.
These cats will.
- You're putting a lotta
stock in him, Bill.
- I didn't make him
Raven team leader
because he's got a nice smile.
- We can't all choose
our subordinates based
on whether or not we
want to sleep with them.
- Ah, hell.
You gonna keep
giving me a hard time
about that girl in accounting?
Did you see the body on her?
- Alright, alright,
enough of that.
We're making decisions
here that will
affect the rest of our lives.
- In less than one hour the
extraction will be complete,
the decoder will
be on its way here,
and you gentlemen will be
on a road paved with gold.
As soon as we turn the device
over to our Iranian friend.
- Let's kick some ass.
- Hey, sergeant.
Raven, right flank!
Raven, cover!
Deuce, the ammo truck!
- Spike!
Move.
- Moving.
- Cover.
Move!
- Moving.
- Move!
- Moving!
- Move.
- Moving.
Move.
- Move.
- Moving.
- Go!
- Martin, get down!
Steve!
- Oh, god.
- Hang in there,
buddy, hang in there!
Come on.
Steve.
- Where's the rest of 'em?
- They're dead.
- Alright, we got four minutes
to get in there and get that--
- Didn't you hear what I
said, you son of a bitch?
- I feel worse about it than
you do, now stack 'em up!
You know what we
want, where is it?
Where is it?
- Bullseye!
I got it.
- You got a lotta chutzpah.
A lotta chutzpah!
Didn't help.
- Soviet 666 codebreaker.
Oh, yeah.
- These two pieces
are codependent.
- Ah.
You have one without the other,
it ain't worth a
shit, but together.
Together, shit.
This little booger can
infiltrate and seize control
of any computer defense
network known to Man,
including Uncle Sam's,
you know what I'm sayin'?
- I know what you're saying.
The mother of all decoders.
50 million bucks.
Time to boogie.
We won't need her
anymore, waste her.
- We got what we came for.
- I said waste her!
- How'd you know?
I didn't.
Move!
- Moving!
- Connor!
You son of a bitch!
You'll make it.
You're with a hell
of a soldier, Mike.
Where the hell is that chopper?
- Raven, this is my last job.
I'm out.
- What?
- I quit, as of now.
Glad you didn't
decide that 15 minutes ago.
- I'm telling you, this is it.
I'm out of Raven team.
- What are you talking about?
I recruited you.
You're the best I ever saw.
- I used to be the best, I
can't do this any longer.
You saw me hesitate.
I can't kill anymore.
- You know what you need?
You need a little vacation.
So do I!
We gotta go somewhere, you know?
Together.
Where they wear nothing
but thong bikinis.
You'd look good
in a thong bikini.
- What the fuck
is wrong with you?
I don't see the glory
in killing kids anymore.
We're just mercenaries.
We're paid killers.
- We're not mercenaries.
Mercenaries get a hell of a
lot more money than we do!
We are paid government
operatives and we're
not paid enough.
You know why they took us?
Because we are the best.
We were sent to get this gizmo
because we are indestructible!
Where the hell you been?
Stealing this chopper.
Where are the others?
- Taking harp lessons.
I'm gonna make
some sand castles!
Whoa!
- It's over, Raven!
- What?
- I said I'm out, I'm out!
- Okay.
You're out, I'll go with ya!
- You're coming with me?
- Yeah, and we're gonna
take this gizmo, too.
- We can't do that!
That has to go back
to the company!
- Are you crazy?
This is worth 50 million bucks!
You know what the
company's gonna do?
They're gonna give
it to the Iranians!
- You're full of shit, Raven!
- No, you're full of shit!
You just come down in
a little white balloon?
What's the matter with you?
You know how much this thing
is worth on the black market?
- I said, I'm gettin'
out, not sellin' out!
- Alright, you're out!
- I'm out!
- Don't make me do this
the hard way, Deuce!
Gah!
Ah!
- Hey.
- I didn't mean to wake you.
- What's the matter?
- Dreams.
- Bad dreams?
Wanna talk about it?
- No.
- Make friends with
your nightmares, Martin.
- I know.
- You and your secrets.
I never met anyone
with so many secrets.
- I just don't like
talking about my past.
- Well, we've been
together almost a year
and sometimes I feel like I
don't know anything about you.
How about I tell you about
the dream I've been having?
It's the one where.
- I kind of like that dream.
Yeah.
- Martin, why don't you ever
tell me about your dreams?
You know, dreams tell
a lot about a person.
I always hear you saying things.
- I talk in my sleep?
- Sometimes.
You say Raven.
So I guess you're
not gonna tell me?
- It's not for you, babe.
- Someday I want a
family like that, Martin.
What are you afraid of?
- Afraid of the bubble bursting.
Losing the best thing
that's ever happened to me.
I don't wanna lose you.
- Hey.
You're not gonna lose me.
I gotta go.
- Okay.
- Hey.
What are ya doin'?
- I'm buffalo hunting,
what does it look like?
- Looks like you're watching me.
- Sorry, man, I don't know
what you're talking about.
- You gotta bait that hook
if you wanna catch something.
- I don't remember asking
for a fishing lesson.
And what are you, Tarzan,
the neighborhood watch?
- Oh, we just don't
get too many strangers
fishing this stretch
of the beach.
You catch much with a Nikon
Reflex and a telephoto lens?
- You know, I don't
have to talk to you.
I don't have to tell you squat.
I didn't know I had
to get permission
to do something
on a public beach!
- It's a private beach.
I'd like to keep it that way.
- Can I have my ball?
Hey, mister, can I have my ball?
- Don't let me catch
you hear again.
- Thanks.
- Martin, I'll see you later!
- I don't believe it.
Yes, sir.
- I want this call traced.
I knew you weren't dead.
- I'm gonna make this
fast, so don't try
to trace it, Billy Gilley.
I want the other half of that
decoder and I want it now.
- Other half?
We didn't get either piece.
I even sent a SEAL team
out to search that lake
and all we found was a wrecked
chopper and a dead pilot.
- Okay, that's the
way you want it.
I'm gonna take out the Four
Star group and I'm gonna
take 'em out one at
a time, you included.
- Raven, listen to
me for a minute.
- You won't know
when I'm gonna start.
When I finish, there
won't be enough left
for the ants to have a picnic.
Sweet dreams, asshole.
- Katz.
- You've been a real
trooper, Marsha.
Hanging in here all
these crazy hours.
I'm gonna be sorry
to see you go.
- No problem, Senator.
The agency explained what was
involved when they called.
Although, I don't think I
could do this full time.
- I wish you could.
You're the best
temp I've ever had.
Hell, you're the best
secretary, period.
- Well, Senator, thank you,
but I'm sure your regular
assistant is terrific.
- You know what I'm thinking?
The least I can do is
buy you a nice dinner.
What's your favorite restaurant?
- Oh, no, Senator, really--
- Now, come on.
You've gotta be just
as hungry as I am.
Let's wrap this up and
go get something to eat.
- Senator Berg's office.
- Bill Gilley for the senator.
- Well, I'll see if
the senator's still in.
I believe he may
have left already.
- How about the Carriage House?
Now, that's the best
restaurant on the hill.
- I love the Carriage House.
Shall I say you'll call
back in the morning?
- Late in the morning.
- I'm sorry, Mr.
Gilley, but I believe
that he's already left.
- Bill, what's going on?
- We've got a situation here.
There's a plane leaving Dallas
at 11:45 tomorrow morning.
Be on it.
- What the hell are
you talking about?
- Now, hold on, slow down.
I can't just drop everything.
I've got a full plate here.
- I don't care about
your full plate.
Be on that plane.
And leave your little
black book at home.
You take the time
to unzip your fly
on this trip and you
may find yourself dead!
- You're right, I am starving.
- I will call you on the
Selby contracts tomorrow.
Okey-doke?
Hello.
- Adeeb, Bill Gilley.
- I told you never to
call me on this phone.
- I've got good news,
terrific news actually.
- Are you a fool?
I will not discuss this
matter on a cellphone.
- Alright, we can
discuss it in person.
I'm free tomorrow afternoon.
- You are anything
but free, Mr. Gilley.
And we will meet
when I am available.
Tomorrow night.
- Alright, I can make it
tomorrow night, no problem.
See you then.
- Idiot.
- I've been waiting
for you, senator.
You're late.
You know, you're not
supposed to keep me waiting.
- I'm sorry.
- Well, I'm sorry, but
sorry doesn't cut it.
Now get over here,
and undress me.
- Darling, you are special, mm.
- What?
- It's locked.
- It's locked, so what?
- Oh my god, he's alive!
- Are they busy?
- Very busy.
- Come on, baby, you're
starting to scare me here.
- He's gonna kill us!
- What a way to go!
- Scared the shit outta me.
You know, I oughta
get more for this.
He was a little bull,
ripped the film right
outta my camera.
Luckily, I took
more than one roll.
They were living
together in La Jolla.
He's a nine-to-fiver,
a boat mechanic.
Goes by the name
of Martin Grant.
- She's a hot little pincushion,
works in the Federal
Building Downtown.
- The Federal Building?
- Yeah, works on the
staff of a Senator Mixton.
Her name is Cali,
it's Cali Goodwin.
- Why'd you take so many
pictures of the broad?
- Pretty girl.
- The senator and I
go back a long way.
- Yeah, like I give a shit.
Look, why don't you
give me my money,
let me get outta here.
You got everything you
want in the envelope.
I'll tell you something,
Katz, you give me the creeps.
- I give you the creeps?
That's too bad.
It's too bad I don't
give you the runs.
- What the hell is this?
- A new diet.
- Hey, man, what are you doing?
Come on, Katz, I mean I've
known you since I was thin.
- That's right.
I'd shoot you in the belly.
Take about five years
to reach your heart.
I left you a nice headstone.
- I can't believe that crazy
bastard just killed Tom,
just like that.
- He just played
golf two weeks ago.
Tom joined this
new country club.
He and Jenny were so excited.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah,
he was a great guy.
And he knew every dirty joke,
and he got laid three
or four times a day
and now he's dead, which
is what we're going to be
if we don't figure out
what we're going to do.
- Can you spare one of those?
- So, what are we gonna do?
- I haven't the faintest idea.
- When he first surfaced I
thought it was good news.
I thought we'd finally
get off the hot seat
with the deed by being able
to offer him something.
That Raven would be looking to
go back to business as usual.
- Business as usual?
For that maniac, it's murder.
He's gotten back to
business as usual.
Why did he turn on us?
This I don't understand?
- Why?
Because he figured
out that we sent him
on a one-way mission that's why.
- Well, we intended
for him to come back.
After all, we
needed the decoder.
- Yes, we needed
him to come back.
I think he knew that.
I think he also
knew it was the last
thing we needed him to do.
- Alright, we should
feed him to Adeeb.
We'll get 'em both
off our backs.
- Now, I spoke with Adeeb.
- You did, when?
- Yesterday, before Tom
got himself blown up
and I realized how
flipped out Raven was.
- How did it go?
- Oh, it went great
since I thought I
was gonna be able
to deliver the decoder to him.
- You told him we
had the decoder?
- I thought we would.
I thought Raven was just
setting us up for the big bucks.
Then he hung up on me,
but I thought he'd call
back and try to
jack up the price.
So, yeah, yeah, I told him we
would be able to deliver it.
In fact, I set up a
meeting for tonight.
I think I'm ready
for one of those now.
- Shit, in a hand cart.
You'll have to keep
that appointment.
- Me, what am I
gonna say to him?
Does he think I
have the decoder?
- Just do what you
always do, bullshit.
You're a senator
for Christ's sake.
- Sheez.
- Alright, forget it.
I'll handle it myself.
- Alright, alright.
What do we do about Raven?
- Well, that's what
we're here for.
Between the three of us we must
have an IQ that
totals at least 100.
I think we should be
able to out think Raven.
We've done it before.
We should be able to do it now.
Thank you for seeing me, Adeeb.
If I'm early, I could
always wait out in--
- Say what you have to say.
I have already waited too long
for you to tell me
where the decoder is.
- Perhaps this should
wait until you're through.
- Do not concern
yourself with Miko.
She speaks only Japanese.
Now, where is it?
- I guarantee you'll have
it by the end of the week.
That is what you
told me two years ago
when I paid for it in full.
- And we had a
setback as I told you.
We lost our whole
team on that mission.
The device has been recovered.
There are just a
few small matters
to be concluded and
the decoder is yours.
A little late, but just as
valuable, perhaps even more so.
- You have used up
all my goodwill.
The entire Four Star team
is running on borrowed time.
I only waited to see
if the device surfaced
somewhere else on the market,
perhaps to a higher bidder.
You and the others would
have heard from me again.
- Let's not start
with the threats.
First of all, no one was
screwing anyone here.
You paid for the device, it
was always coming to you.
- Two years late.
- But here, nonetheless.
And by the end of the
week, like I said.
- You've had enough time.
In 72 hours, I will have
the decoder which I paid for
or you, Mr. Gilley,
will have much trouble,
which you have paid for.
- What the hell is 24
hours, more or less?
- Exactly.
One of my assistants will
call you with the particulars.
- Keep it coming.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
You finished already?
- Yeah, it was just
the bleeder valve.
- Guess your outta here then.
- That I am, got me
a hot date tonight.
- Don't let your
girlfriend find out.
- A year as of today.
- How did a bum like you end
up with a sweetheart like that?
Martin.
- What?
- How did a bum like you end
up with a sweetheart like that?
- Uh, we kept bumping
into each other
and she finally asked
me out to dinner.
I've been hooked ever since.
- So you got a
surprise for tonight?
- Surprise.
Yeah, I'd say I have a
little surprise for her.
- I bet you do.
- Martin, it's beautiful.
I don't know what to say.
- Yes, might be a good answer.
- Yes, I'll marry you.
- Have I told you
how much I love you?
- I think you just did.
- You mean the world to me.
What do you say
the two of us start
our lives fresh, somewhere else?
- What do you mean?
- Let's move.
Anywhere you wanna go.
- Oh, sweetheart,
I don't wanna move.
This is our home.
If this is about the
nightmares you've been having,
I have something
special for you, too.
'Kay?
- Yeah.
- Come here.
Open it.
It's a dreamcatcher.
We can hang it over
our bed and it'll
catch all your bad dreams.
- It's wonderful.
Tonight, Mrs. Grant,
I've got a feeling my nightmares
are gonna be a
million miles away.
- I hope so.
Martin?
Promise me something.
- What is it?
- Promise me someday there'll
be no secrets between us.
- I knew you were still alive.
- Let me ask you something.
Do you get paid by the
barnacle or by the hour?
- You sent the fat guy with
the elephant lens, didn't you?
- I don't know what
you're talking about.
- Oh, sure you do.
I thought the CIA
had finally caught up
to me until, uh, the paper read
that a private eye
was found dead.
Then I knew it was you.
- Long time no see.
- Not long enough, Raven.
- Well.
You went from crack commando
to Popeye the sailor.
It was a great career move.
- Puppets, that's all we were.
- Great, you finally got it.
You know, when they
found the helicopter
they thought I was dead.
Funny thing happened
to you on your way
to this stylish job you got.
You forgot to give your half of
the decoder back to the company.
- Well, I wish I could help you,
but it kinda got
lost in the water.
- Is that what you told 'em?
That's good.
You see, 'cause I
have the other half.
And that makes us partners.
We're millionaires.
- We've had this conversation,
Raven, and you shot me.
- You grabbed the gun.
- You're doing exactly
what they want you to do.
Sell it.
- How many barnacles
do you have to scrape,
kid, to get millions of dollars?
- It's not gonna happen, Raven.
- I don't think you
know about this.
A few days ago, a senator,
Burke, he was wasted.
It's gonna happen again.
Gonna go from Four
Star to Three Star
to Two Star and then No Stars.
- Just getting rid of
your competition, huh?
- I don't have any competition.
- I don't have the device.
- Of course, you do.
- Get out of here, Raven,
I've got work to do.
- Great to see you, kid.
Just a word of advice.
You know that beautiful
gal that you're dating.
I'd be careful if I were you.
She's a bitch.
- Listen up, now.
I mean, it's going
on as we speak, bro.
I'm talking about UN
tanks on US soil, man.
Training, practicing maneuvers.
- You know, you talk too much.
- Well, baby, maybe
you don't talk enough.
- I let this do my talking.
- You know something, Eva?
We got a cause
going on here, baby.
We stand for something, just
in case you fucking forgot!
- What is it, Gary,
you worried about me?
Huh?
- What about you, Hub?
- I got no beef with you.
- Here's some beef
for you, baby.
- Alright, children,
put your toys down.
Put 'em down!
Go load the van.
Hey.
You alright?
- We need to talk.
- Later.
- No, now!
- I love it when you
talk rough to me.
- Do you?
I can barely remember.
- Why don't we talk when
the men are not around?
- What men, they're scum.
- Why don't we talk when
the scum is not around?
- Whatever they are,
they're fanatics!
You know, they're fighting
for this cause and that.
Things they don't
even understand
but they will kill for that.
- Takes all kinds.
- No, it only takes one kind.
Our kind.
We kill for money, none
of which I've seen yet.
You did say more than
I could ever spend.
- I said more than
we can ever spend.
If you're gonna quote
me, quote me correctly.
- There are many things I
can quote you saying to me.
- You know the difference
between us and the scum?
- Hm?
- We know when.
- We know when, what?
- We know when to shoot,
we know when to lay low.
We know when to pull out.
We know when to let go.
Now.
This could mean millions,
millions for us.
We got one shot.
I've been planning
escaping for so long
I can't remember, and I'm
not gonna let you blow it
'cause you can't control
yourself for one week
or one month, or however long
it takes for this to go down.
Now, you are a great
lady, but not that great.
And if you believe that,
I got some swamp property
in Florida I'll sell you.
Now, I got a call
on next senator.
- Mixton.
- Mixton, right.
- Senator, here are the
demographics from the committee.
Night.
- Good night.
- Coffee Young Center,
may I help you?
Hi, Al, it's Cali.
- Hi, how are you?
- Very well, thank you.
Did he tell you the news?
Yes, he did.
- Isn't it wonderful?
- It's great.
When are you getting married?
- Well, we haven't
set a date yet.
Could I talk to Martin?
- Yes, hold on.
Hey, Martin!
Guess who?
- Hello?
- Hey, you.
- Hey, baby,
what are you doing?
- Ooh, not much.
Financial meetings, board
meetings, committee meetings.
How 'bout you?
- Chris craft, Hatteras,
and Bay liners.
- I love you.
- Did you call just
to tell me that?
And what if it was?
- I'd say you made my day.
Good.
Then I'll see you later?
You can bet on it.
- Okay, buh-bye.
- Step over here please.
- I got a plate in my knee
and a plate in my shoulder.
- Hey, you got a plate
in your knee and a
plate in your shoulder.
- Is there an echo in here?
I think I just said that.
Hello.
Thank you.
- Have this delivered
to the senator
after his meeting and
hold all of my calls.
- Where's Katz?
- He's supposed to be with you.
- I didn't see him.
- Yeah?
- I'm out.
Blow it.
- Katz is out, blow it.
- To freedom.
- It's too late now.
I'll get that first
thing in the morning.
Thanks.
This is WGYN Radio
with a newsflash.
Minutes ago, the
Federal Building located
in Downtown San Diego
suffered a massive explosion.
No word on survivors but
the casualties are mounting.
- Oh my God!
Martin!
Once again, a major explosion
has rocked Downtown San Diego.
So far there are four deaths.
Most of the damage was localized
to California senator
Wilbur Mixton's wing.
It is believed his entire
staff has been killed.
- Sir.
- Hi.
Nice pad.
- You son of a bitch, you killed
all those innocent people.
- We rang the fire alarm.
Most of the people got out.
- Cali was in that building.
- As for Cali, I told you it was
gonna happen at the boat yard.
You shoulda warned her.
- You're crazy.
Uh huh.
I am crazy.
You'd do well to member that.
Now where is the other
half of the decoder?
- I told you, I don't have it.
- You have it alright.
And you better start
remembering where it is
'cause if you don't, I'm gonna
start blowing up buildings
and this time I'm not
gonna ring any fire alarms.
You hear me?
Get it together!
You know, you're full of shit!
I said, waste her!
- Cali was in that building.
- Most of the people got out.
Where is the other
half of the decoder?
- Alright, Katz, you want it,
you got it.
- Adeeb, my friend.
Good to see you again.
- How long is it since you've
been in my neck of the woods?
- Enough of your pleasantries,
I have already been through it.
It has been one year
since we last met.
It has been two
years since I paid
your group for the codebreaker.
And don't think
that doesn't bother
me just as much as it does you.
- Two years and I
still do not have it.
- I have agents working
on it right now, Adeeb.
We're close, we're
very, very close.
We're very close.
Believe me, I want this thing.
As promised.
- Well, you had
better work faster
as you do not have
that much time.
- Wait a minute, are
you threatening me.
Look.
Calm down.
This is supposed to
be a friendly business meeting.
Right?
Adeeb, friends don't
threaten one another.
- All I meant was I want
the decoder or my money
before the rest of
you are executed.
- Executed.
- You are in a bit of
trouble, my friend.
Two of your associates
have already been killed.
- Well.
Look, I have people looking
into that, believe me.
Nothing is gonna happen to me.
- I got Sklar in my sights.
- Everybody, set in.
- Check.
- We just have to
be a little patient.
Just both of us, a
little more patient.
Just give me a little more time.
- Alright, it's your kill shot.
On your call.
- Always with you, it's--
- Son of a bitch!
- What is happening?
- Deuce?
- What the hell is going on?
- Don't fall apart.
Everybody stick to
business, alright?
I got the senator.
- Hello, senator.
- Katz.
I knew it, I knew it.
I told the others you didn't
die in a chopper crash.
I've been hearing
that a lot lately.
I'm indestructible.
Sorry, you're not.
- Wait a minute,
hold it, hold it.
Don't get crazy.
- Well, there's crazy
good and crazy bad.
I'm crazy good.
It keeps me sharp.
- Listen, I can
still help you, Katz.
I got connections,
contacts, important people.
- Pop quiz.
Who can take this country
down faster than anybody?
- Bzzz, times up.
Corrupt officials like you
that don't care anything
about this country, just
care about themselves.
Well, I'm taking
you off the ballot.
- Please, man.
Christ, have some compassion.
- Compassion?
Oh, I took that in night school.
I failed it.
Say good night.
Raven.
- Hello, Deuce?
I thought that was you.
Where are you?
- Close by.
This Raven team isn't
as good as we were.
You're right,
you did me a favor.
Now I don't have
so many partners.
Just you and me
kid, right, 50-50?
- Sure.
Come on out, we'll
talk about it.
I don't think so.
We'll talk later.
Gotta run.
- Who are you?
Who are you?
The FBI?
You work for the
government, you scumbag?
Why don't you kill me?
Go ahead, do it.
- My fiance was
in that building.
- Don't take it personally,
it was business.
- It was murder.
- It was part of a job.
- You must be proud of yourself.
Killing innocent
people for money.
And what did you get for it?
Nothing.
Where is Katz headed?
- You got all the king's men,
but you didn't get
the king himself.
- You should think about
who you're dying for.
Katz doesn't give
a shit about you.
How does it feel to be used?
You heard him, you're
all expendable.
- Go to hell.
Hey!
Don't let them take me alive.
- Where is he?
- At base in Carlsbad.
A closed down
warehouse, 1500 Cherry.
- Okay, thanks.
- It's a warzone.
- It was a war, Russ,
with heavy casualties.
We've got one dead
senator, Robert Sklar.
Shot at close range,
execution style.
A multi-billionaire
oil sheik, Adeeb Husay.
Four dead John Does
and one dead Jane Doe.
- That's a mess.
- Yeah, a bloody one.
- Let's get outta here.
- Okay.
- Okay, the commanders
are connected
to a group of
anti-government militants.
Agents in San Diego are trying
to link these terrorists
to the bombing last week.
- Okay.
- Now one member, Gary Alban,
has a warehouse in Carlsbad.
- Call Jim Jacobson
in Washington.
Tell him I need a
federal warrant to
search those premises.
And a SWAT team to meet
us there in two hours.
- Two hours?
- Did I stutter?
- Two hours.
- Cali!
- Ah!
Untie me.
- Very touching.
Drop it, Deuce.
Drop the knife or
I'll put a hole
right between her
pretty little eyes.
Thank you.
I was keeping her
for my trump card.
Got a great little broad there.
Had a wonderful talk with her.
Now she knows
everything about you.
I had my way with
her a couple times.
You're not gonna buy that, huh?
I didn't think you would.
- I just wanted out.
- Uh huh.
Well, I just wanted
the other half
of this goddamn decoder!
- Move in!
- Cali, this way.
Go!
- Freeze, freeze!
Up against the car, come on.
- You have the right
to remain silent.
- Mr. Katz.
- Yo.
- Russ Cormack here.
Listen, tied up a couple of
my boys in knots back there.
Said you wouldn't talk.
Cigarette?
- Yeah.
- Virginia boy, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
- In and out of detention halls.
At 16, you lied about your age.
Turned to professional boxing.
Invited by the judge to
enlist in the military.
- Oh yeah.
- 18, you're in Vietnam,
explosives expert.
Three tours of duty.
Worked for the Phoenix
Program as an assassin.
Cited for over 108 kills.
Jesus, how can one man
kill that many people?
- I was just doing what
the Man told me to do.
And I was good at it.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I bet you were.
Two Brown Stars,
two Silver Stars,
four Purple Hearts.
Made a Lieutenant Colonel,
then in 1976 the file ends.
Nothing.
Zip.
So what did you do, fall
off the face of the Earth?
- Come on, babe, we're here.
- What are we doing
at my brother's place?
- It's the safest
place I could think of.
Doesn't look like
anybody's home.
- Hey.
- I'd like to tell you,
Russ, I really would
cause you're a
very likable fella,
but, uh, that's
top secret and if
I told you I'd have to kill ya.
- You're a very funny guy.
- Yeah, I'm funny.
- Matter of fact, I'm opening
in Tahoe on the ninth,
that is if I, you know,
get out of all this mess.
You will come see me, won't ya?
- Nah.
What is this?
- Oh, that.
Well, that's classified, Russ.
I can't tell you about that.
- Russ, these guys
are with the CIA.
- Wait, wait, wait,
hold it, hold it.
- Agent Cormack,
I'm William Gilley.
I have papers from
Washington giving me custody
of the suspect.
- Hey, Gilley, how they hanging?
Watch him, Russ,
he's an asshole.
- You know this guy?
- I'll take that, too.
- No, no, my case.
- Not anymore.
- We'll talk outside.
- I bought some time.
I need to think about
what we're gonna do next.
- Can I ask you a question?
Yeah.
- Is your name even Martin?
Is anything you
ever told me true?
You lied to me!
- Listen to me.
I never lied to you when
I said that I loved you.
- Don't touch me.
- I needed to start over, Cali.
I thought I could leave
it behind and move on.
I thought maybe if you
didn't know about my past,
but knew what was in my heart
everything would be okay.
I was wrong.
- You did well, Agent Cormack.
You helped us a great deal.
- So long, Russ.
- I'll see that your
efforts are duly noted.
- That is the
biggest crock a shit
you heard in your entire career!
Thanks, Miller.
Not one thing that
man said since he
parachuted into this
case makes sense.
- Of course not, he's CIA.
They've got black
belts in bullshit.
You wanna get some sushi?
- You know, we busted our
humps in this case and
that Agent Gilley up
here like the prince
of darkness and snapped it
off our bladders and you want
to get something to eat
like it never happened.
- It didn't happen, not if
that's the way they want it.
- How much you wanna bet by
the time we clock in tomorrow
this case won't even be
in the computers anymore?
- I know.
- How about that sushi?
I'll pay.
- You'll pay?
- Did I stutter?
- Yeah, I got it.
We're on our way.
Alright, let's get
this show on the road.
- We're gonna talk, Billy Boy.
- Get in the car, Katz.
- Who's gonna put me in
the car, Heckle and Jekyll?
- Get in the car, boys.
You wanna talk,
come on, let's talk.
- You got some set of
balls, you know that?
- I heard that before,
but never from a man.
- Did you really think you
were gonna go into business
for yourself and I was
just gonna let you do it?
- Let me do it, let me?
- Every mission I ever
had I set up myself.
I call all the shots.
- You egomaniacal
prick, you work for me!
I backed up that mission
to snatch that decoder!
I provided the intel
and the recon and you
were supposed to
deliver it to me!
- It was a one-way mission,
you son of a bitch!
Nobody was gonna come
out of that alive
and if they did come out
alive you wouldn't have
let them stay alive, would ya?
I lost four good men over
there, four good soldiers!
And I lost whatever
was left of my goddamn
conscience 'cause you killed it!
- Jesus.
Well, no matter what you
thought was happening,
looks like we're going to
be working together again,
unless you'd rather go back in
there and face
that federal beef.
- Going where?
- Big Bear.
We got a job to finish.
It'll be just like old times.
- You can bet on it.
- Hey.
You're right.
I shoulda told you
everything and I'm sorry.
I promise no more secrets.
- Is the person I fell
in love with even real?
- Yeah.
Come here.
When did you
lose your conscience?
The moment I met you.
Billy Gilley.
You are an asshole.
- Good morning.
- How about some coffee?
- That'd be great.
- Water's on the stove.
- They got something
to eat in there?
- Not a whole lot.
Come here.
- What was that?
- Stay here.
- No way.
- Don't look so
surprised, Martin.
Deep inside, you knew
something was wrong, didn't ya?
You just didn't face it.
Turn around!
- Hey, Deuce.
You coming back like a song.
- More like the clap.
- I tell you the difference
between me and the clap?
- What's that?
- You get rid of the clap.
- That's very amusing, boys.
You two didn't really
think the company was
just gonna forget about
Raven team, did you?
You made history
with your kill ratio.
Now, come on,
mercenaries can't quit.
It just doesn't happen that way.
You were easy to
keep tabs on, Grant.
- Fuck you, Bill.
I wouldn't exactly call a
year of deep cover work easy,
especially living with this guy.
He's a fucking nut!
- I told you, she's a bitch.
- You know, I don't
get guys like you.
They sent me in to
gain your trust.
They thought you'd be
tough to get close to.
What a no-brainer.
- What took you so long, Cali?
Why didn't you just kill
me when you found me?
- Oh, you know the
answer to that one, Greg.
You two have something we want.
Your last mission was to
obtain a Soviet 666 codebreaker
for Washington, but somehow
Washington never got it.
- Washington was
never gonna get it,
were they, Billy Gilley?
I wanna introduce you to the
man behind the Raven team.
As a planner of
covert operations,
no one can touch you.
As a human being,
nobody wants to.
- And thanks to
you, Katz, the last
surviving member of Four Star.
- What does that make you?
The Lone Star?
- We want the device, Grant.
- I don't know what
you're talking about.
- I remember somewhere
somebody told me
that if you don't have both
devices, it's not worth a shit.
- Well, that's too bad
because I destroyed it.
- No, you didn't.
- I smashed that piece
of shit in 1000 pieces.
- That was a $50 million device.
- It's worth a
lot more than that
on the international market,
isn't it, Billy Gilley?
- Shut up!
Now, tell me the truth,
Grant, and I'll let you live.
I told you to shut up.
Now, where is it, Grant?
Would you like me
to shoot him again.
- Okay, you can have it.
It's in my duffle bag
in the back of my truck.
- Smart decision, Grant.
See, Cali, he isn't as
dumb as you said he was.
Watch them closely.
Kill them.
- Separate the two, guys.
Johnny, takes the
cuffs off of him.
Make it look like
they shot each other.
- Come on.
Ah shit, Raven, it's
just a flesh wound.
- Well, you did good, Deuce,
but we both got screwed.
- No, we didn't.
They did.
- Yeah.
Was that meant for me?
Makes you
wonder, don't it?
- No, whatever.