[Latin music plays]
[thunderclap]
Hi, I'm
Congressman Jose Maria Vega.
And with your help,
I am going to put Puerto Rico
back on the map again.
[Latin music plays]
If I am re-elected,
I will make sure
that our schools, our hospitals,
and our church organizations
that have been doing
such amazing work
for the community,
receive all the support
they deserve.
You can trust me on that.
We are going to rebuild
somehow, some way.
I think we did
a fantastic job in Puerto Rico.
Thanks
to the business incentives
I have already implemented,
I think we can all agree
the powerhouse
that is the Puerto Rican economy
is booming once again.
Is the crisis getting you down?
Are you feeling confused?
Worried?
Relax,
what you need is a new car.
No credit? No problem.
Bad credit? No problem.
Bankruptcy? No problem.
We have
certified bank officials on site
who will arrange a car loan
that's right for you instantly.
And this weekend,
it's my "Name Your Price"
extravaganza.
We have live music,
we have pinchos,
Brinca-brinca for the kids,
because as we say
in Morales Alto,
we can't solve the crisis,
but we can sell you a new car.
And that's my promise to you.
Hello.
My name is Rafa.
Rafa Rodriguez.
And I'm offering you
the best used autos
in all of Puerto Rico.
If you can find a better price
on any of these models,
I will pay the difference,
and that is my offer to you.
Rafa Quality Cars!
[Tape rewinds]
Hello, I'm--
[doorbell chimes]
Hello, my name is Rafa.
Rafa Rodriguez.
And I'm offering you
the best used cars
in all of Puerto Rico.
If you can f--
Hey! What's going on?
[Rafa bumps car]
Psst.
Let's go. Get out of the car.
Now.
Open the door
and get out of the car.
Get out of the--
Not through the window.
How did you get in there?
It was locked.
With a slim Jim.
[Truck horn honks]
Get out of here.
Give me back my Slim Jim.
I'm gonna give you back
your Slim Jim.
Go!
I'm gonna call the cops.
Ridiculous.
Hello, my name is Rafa.
Rafa Rodriguez,
and I'm bringing you
the best used autos
in all of Puerto Rico.
If you can find a better price--
[beeping]
[Rafa] I thought I told you
to get out of here.
Why aren't you at school?
Shut, because of the crisis.
Still no power.
Anyway, what are you doing?
I am making a commercial.
Shouldn't you be a bit more...
Oh!
Like the guys on TV?
Show some hustle.
I was getting to the hustle.
You wanna do me a favor?
Go home.
Can't.
My mom got arrested.
That was her?
- You only just moved in, right?
- Mm-hmm.
You have any relatives
to stay with?
Neighbor?
Trying to run a business,
you can't stay here.
Oh, yeah, I have an aunt.
But I need a ride.
"Hello, my name is Rafa.
Rafa Rodriguez.
And that is my promise to you."
Yes, very funny.
Do you have a wife?
Got any kids?
Geez, just making polite talk.
[Charm tinkling]
I have two boys, all grown up.
How much further is this?
[Girl] Um, here.
This is it?
Yeah.
[Rap music playing]
[Rafa] Not so fast,
I have angina.
[Panting]
[reggaeton music playing]
[girl coughs]
Forgot which one.
Home sweet home.
Where's your aunt?
Probably moved to Florida,
you know?
Most people do if they can.
Okay, well, thanks for the ride.
Oh, no, no. You can't stay here.
Titi won't mind.
What's Titi's last name?
Rodriguez.
Rodriguez?
[Girl] Yeah, Rodriguez.
[Rafa] What a coincidence,
that's my name.
[Girl] So? Lots of people
in Puerto Rico called Rodriguez.
- [Rafa] Hello?
- [Woman] Directory assistance.
I'd like the number
for Social Services.
- No!
- Yes. San Juan, yes, I'll hold.
You can't do that!
They'll put me
with foster parents.
And?
They take in kids
just to get the money.
And some of them
even interfere with them.
You know what that means?
The word "interfere"?
No, but if that happened to me,
that one would be on you.
[Rafa] Come on, let's go.
Gotta get back to work.
[Salsa music
playing over stereo]
Did you have
a fight with your sons?
Is that why you don't see them?
They stay with their mom.
And we don't talk much.
I guess we're both on our own.
[Salsa music plays]
What's that island?
It's not an island.
It's Florida.
It's where I'm from.
You came from Florida
to Puerto Rico?
That's right.
- Why?
- Good question.
They were supposed to give me
one more month to pay.
[Screams]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait!
[Screams]
You're supposed to give me
one more month!
The bank said installments!
Hey! Wait, wait, wait. Hey!
No!
Shit!
Oh, shit!
[Girl] Did he just
steal all your cars?
[Rafa] Just go, will you?
We're done here.
Yeah, is tonight
a good night to see Jupiter?
[Reggaeton music
playing over stereo]
[reggaeton playing]
[rooster crowing]
[rap music in Spanish playing]
[cheering]
Ah!
Hmm.
[Man] God bless you, princesa.
[Cheering]
[cheering]
Whoa!
Hey, Diego.
What the hell were you thinking?
Because even winners
lose sometimes.
Five thousand dollars.
It was a big bet, Rafa.
Never understand
why people bet so big
when they need money.
I don't need money.
Things are good.
So shall we say... two days?
Perfect.
I'll give you five.
It can be hard to get
a hold of cash right now.
Sounds good. I'm easy.
Just one thing.
Don't push it, Rafa.
We out of luck.
[Salsa music plays]
Oh.
Are you insane?
Ah!
Shit.
You bet $5,000!
Stop breaking into my car.
You seriously thought a rooster
would solve
all of your problems?
I need $10,000 to get
my cars back from the bank.
Without my cars,
I have no business.
Without my business,
I have no income.
Without income, I have no home.
Look. You've got four days,
23 hours, and 36 minutes
to pay that guy.
And we need a real plan,
you know?
Like, show some hustle.
What is it with this "we" thing?
There is no "we" here.
[Girl] I can help you.
Come on, let's go, Joe.
[Engine starts]
[girl] I saw what they do
to people who don't pay on time.
[Cheering]
What's your name?
Ana.
My name is Rafa.
I know.
It says it on your car lot.
[Dog whimpers in the distance]
[Ana] Night, Rafa.
[Rafa] Good night.
[Ana] Do you WhatsApp him?
Ana, leave that. Come on.
Sit down. Have some breakfast.
"Rafael Rodriguez.
Auto Trader Magazine Car Dealer.
Year 2002. Runner up."
You won.
Runner up. Come on.
Sit down. Have your breakfast.
You should have it here
so that people can see it.
Okay, sure. Thanks.
Listen, don't-- Don't hold--
go like this-- don't hold it.
You're not gonna
kill somebody with it.
Hold it like this.
Like that. Like that.
No, that's not good. Come on.
Stop. Stop that.
Don't do that. You know better.
[Salsa music playing]
[Latin music playing]
[Ana] Where are we going?
To see if your mom's home.
See? Gate's open. She's back.
[Ana bumps car]
[Ana] Mom's douchebag boyfriend.
Okay, so he can take care
of you.
- Go.
- Uh-uh.
Come on. Let's go.
I got things to do.
[Rap music plays]
[Ana] Get up, crackhead!
[Man] You shut up, bitch!
Let me in! Open the gate!
[Man] Keep shaking
the gate like that
and you see what happens.
[Music stops]
[door opens]
What you doing with this kid?
Bringing her home.
Ana, get back here!
How you dare behave like this
after I talked to you before?
Show some respect, okay?
[Dishes clinking]
[Ana] You mean you [inaudible].
Why should I respect you?
[Ana] Get away from me.
You can't tell me what to do.
- [Crash]
- [slap]
[Ana screams]
[man] I'm the one
putting food on the table.
Come back here!
[Car horn honks]
[buzz]
[kid laughs]
So, you are the guy
who's taking care of my kid?
Aren't you the guy
from the car lot?
Yes.
So, where is she?
She didn't wanna come in.
I'm sorry.
I can't look after your child.
Man, just chill out.
I'm gonna be out in a week.
Maybe even less, okay?
She needs to go
to Social Services.
You take her there, I'm never
gonna see her again, okay?
I'm not asking for much.
Just take care of her
for a couple days, man.
I'd do the same for you.
If you were in trouble,
I'd take care of your kid.
- Where is the father?
- [Woman] I don't know, man.
Somewhere in Palmas del Mar,
I think.
He's never around.
What am I supposed to do?
If I take her to him,
is he gonna understand?
Understand what?
That I'm a screw-up?
Listen, this is not about you.
This kid needs a parent.
You gotta call him.
I don't have his number.
Give me his name.
I'll keep you posted.
Thank you.
I'm taking you
to your father's house.
Sure, like he'd even know
who I am.
[Rafa] Well, he better,
because I'm driving
halfway across the island.
[Latin music
playing over cell phone]
You like that?
Do you?
I found it in my phone.
[Latin music playing]
I'm putting in
your telephone number
in case we get separated.
Do you want my number?
No.
Here.
Put this address in your GPS.
The one on top.
Is that where my dad live?
No. It's on the way.
Somebody owes me money.
It'll only be a minute.
Stay in the car.
[Doorbell rings]
[dog barking in the distance]
[door opens]
- Rafa.
- Hi.
Sorry, I hope you don't mind.
I was in the neighborhood.
No, no. Of course.
Come in, please.
Oh.
Who's this?
My name's Ana.
I'm Rafa's neighbor.
He's giving me
a ride to my papi 's house.
May I use your bathroom?
[Chuckling] Of course.
[Door closes]
[glass chinks]
Hey, don't touch that.
- [Woman] You look amazing.
- Thank you. Likewise.
Rafael and I go way back.
We met when he opened
his first car lot.
Good times, right?
Good times.
[Woman] And let me tell you,
this guy used to love to party.
We used to go dancing.
Yes.
He was always very kind to me.
Oh, bathroom.
Top of the stairs.
Do you want some iced tea?
Thank you.
[Toilet flushes]
[reporter]
Puerto Rico investigates.
We asked him
about his campaign donations,
where he gets them from,
and what exactly
is his connection
to the Church
of the Well of God.
All that and more,
coming up next.
[Vega] Let me make this
quite clear, okay?
I have heard all the stories
about my campaign funds
being used
for money laundering, all right?
And how I supposedly help
certain church organizations,
you know, embezzle funds
to buy condos in Florida.
And I also heard that--
that even they say that--
that I feed my enemies to--
to crocodiles.
I mean,
this is ridiculous, guys.
Please, come on.
I mean, this is--
this is fake news.
It's even worse than fake news.
So, how's business?
Well, uh...
Actually, not what I would like.
Thank you.
[Romantic Latin music playing]
Well...
Camila, come on.
He was always very kind to me.
[Both moan]
[Ana clears her throat]
[Camila exhales]
Would you like some iced tea,
sweetheart?
Huh?
- How much does she owe you?
- What?
How much does she owe you?
Like a thousand dollars.
She's good for it.
You don't know that.
She's got that screwed up there,
and a shit ton of perfume,
the expensive kind, not spray.
[Camila sighs]
He needs the money you owe him.
I mean, only if-- only--
only if you-- if you--
if, if it's, you know,
if it's convenient at this time.
It's not exactly--
[sighs]
Rafa, I feel dreadful.
[Slurps]
The crisis is affecting us all
in so many ways right now. I--
[Ana slurps]
You got the car out front.
I mean,
I can't even afford to run it.
- What, with gas prices...
- [Ana] Then you won't miss it.
We have our own tow truck.
It's a small one.
A thousand plus the hundred
I made us at the bar.
We make a good team, right?
I'm taking you
to your father's house.
I don't need your help.
Sure, you don't.
You'll be fine
when those guys come after you.
[Latin music playing]
[charm tinkling]
You need gas.
[Charm tinkling]
Wait in the car.
[Car door closes]
Want me to go pay?
[Doorbell chimes]
Hi, can you put 20 on pump four?
[Announcer]
Have you had enough politicians
who lie and cheat
and make promises
they can't keep?
Well, now's your chance
to make a real change.
Vote for Congressman
José Maria Vega and...
Do you have a restroom?
Out back.
Is it clean? Or kind of icky?
This is a gas station, honey.
Sometimes if it's really bad,
I prefer to wait. One time I--
Are you going
to give me the 20 bucks?
- Shoot! I forgot to take it.
- [Woman] Then you get it.
I'll go get it,
then I need your restroom.
[Announcer] Vote Vega, the only
politician you can really trust.
- Oh, do you sell gummy bears?
- [Woman] No.
[Doorbell chimes]
Let's go, Joe.
Go! Go!
[Car engine starts]
I just made us 20 bucks.
You didn't pay?
[Tires squeal]
What are you doing?
[Ana] Wait.
No, no, no, no, no!
Now you're gonna go
back in there,
you're gonna say you're sorry
and give her back the $20.
[Ana] Like hell I am.
You can't make me.
You're not my mother.
By the way,
your mother's in jail,
and that's exactly
where you're gonna end up
if you don't start
doing the right thing.
Now go in there,
tell her you're sorry.
What if I tuck it in the pump?
Go in there
and say you're sorry.
Tell her you made
an error in judgment.
Okay!
[Grunts]
[screams]
[doorbell chimes]
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
[Thief] Put your hands up. Now!
The floor.
[Screams]
[thief] You saw nothing!
[Announcer]
...the fifth of August
for the Church of the Well
of God Summer Spectacular
at the San Juan Arena.
Join us for an afternoon
of song, prayer,
and the celebration of God
with your prophet, Pastor Helen.
You okay?
[Announcer]
...the more you give,
the more you shall receive.
They're gone.
[Exhales]
[charm tinkling]
[Latin music starts playing]
[music stops]
I forgot to give her
the 20 bucks.
[Sad song plays]
What are you doing?
I wanna show you something.
Why are we staring
at some dumb pond?
[Ana screams]
[Rafa laughs]
Thanks a bunch.
Now I'm all wet!
[Rafa chuckles]
It's a blowhole.
You just have to wait
for the right wave.
The wave comes in
underneath the rocks
and it blows out the blowhole.
Be careful, or you're gonna
end up like Saint Tino.
You ever heard
the story of Saint Tino?
[Ana] No.
Saint Tino was a local farmer
who was crippled,
couldn't walk well.
Be careful.
And he was walking his cow,
stopped by the water,
and the cow fell into the lagoon
and dragged Tino
into the lagoon.
The rope that Tino was holding
got tangled in his leg
and, ooh,
pulled him into the lagoon,
and this lagoon is really deep.
And he was going down
and he knew he was gonna drown,
and that was it.
As he was going down,
God took pity on him
because Tino--
Listen to this.
He was a good man,
he was humble,
and he was honest.
Suddenly, a wave came
and blew Tino
out of the blowhole,
up into the sky
and landed him on the grass.
God saved his life.
[Ana] And was he cured?
- [Rafa] What?
- Was he cured?
Like, he was
no longer a cripple.
No, I think
he was still crippled.
That's not such a great story.
- What happened to the cow?
- [Rafa] The cow?
Cow drowned.
[Voicemail]
You have one new message.
[Beep]
[Diego] Rafa,
in case you were thinking,
I don't need any used cars,
okay?
Just so we're clear,
I need to be paid in cash.
How are you gonna get
the rest of the money?
You sure we going the right way?
Yup. Next right.
[Adventurous music plays]
[Rafa] You definitely put
in your father's address?
Check that map again.
You sure?
[Ana] Hey!
This doesn't have a signal.
It doesn't?
I guess it just dropped out,
but this was
definitely the right way.
[Both moan]
I don't remember
seeing any water on the map.
You did this on purpose!
[Ana grunts]
Don't shout at me.
I'm only eleven.
I don't have time for this, Ana.
Oh, you think I don't know that?
Just see
if you can get a signal.
Will you not jump on my car?
Give me the phone.
You've got a flat.
[Clatter]
Oh!
[Rafa exhales]
Rafa?
[Rafa] Hi.
See that?
I-- I lost my jack.
I wouldn't suppose you have
a spare jack you can lend me?
[Somber music plays]
[tense music plays]
Zuleika.
[Ana] Rafa!
[Pants]
[Rafa grunts]
[Rafa exhales]
[pants]
There you are.
I got us a jack.
Cool.
Okay, here we go.
Thank you very much.
We appreciate it.
We need to buy cañita
and sell it.
Are you out of your mind?
It's illegal.
If you get busted,
you're gonna end up
like your mother, in jail.
I don't get you.
You put a lot of money
on a dumb gallo,
but you won't do
something like this?
It is against the law.
I'm not a criminal.
I'm a car salesman.
Without any cars.
When are you
gonna show some hustle?
[Latin music plays]
It says there's a bar.
It's open 24 hours.
Exactly the right kind
of place to make a sale.
- Go on.
- [Rafa] Stay in the car.
- [Man] Good?
- Hey.
[Beep]
[Rafa] If you might
be interested in buying some...
[whispering] ...cañita?
- What?
- [Whispering] Cañita.
- Why are you whispering?
- I'm not sure.
- [Man] Is it good?
- It's very good.
You're gonna show me?
Bring it in?
[Man] Yeah.
Okay.
What the hell you doing?
People will
totally love this color.
They'll think it's flavored.
Flavored is a big seller.
You know, fruits.
I mean, that's what they say.
It's cool, right?
Cañita.
Yeah, that's not gonna fly.
Is it the color?
That's Smurf blue.
It's what the kids like.
[Man] That's not a kids' drink.
[Panting]
Great idea!
What?
[Trunk closes]
[charm tinkling]
You should call your sons
sometime.
They might like
to hear from you.
[Adventurous music plays]
[Rafa] We're here.
We're done for the night.
Unless you wanna drive.
[Salesman]
Certified bank officials on site
who will arrange a car loan
that's right for you instantly.
And this weekend,
in my "Name Your Price"
extravaganza,
we have live music,
we have pinchos,
Brinca-brinca for the kids,
because as we say--
[Helen]
The money raised in our church
goes to helping our community.
We're in the middle
of a crisis right now.
These are the times
that as a community,
we come together
and help others.
[Reporter] We saw Congressman
Vega here a few minutes ago--
I'm good, thanks.
[Reporter]
What's your connection to him?
Congressman Vega is helping
in any way possible
to get us out of this crisis.
[Cell phone rings]
[Helen] He's a huge supporter
of our church.
We love him dearly.
[Cell phone rings]
- Hello?
- [Diego] What's going on, Rafa?
Hey. How you doing, Diego?
[Clears his throat]
I'm at your car lot,
and it's empty.
[Rafa]
It's because I sold all my cars.
I told you business was good.
I'm down south buying stock.
Just relax.
You're gonna get your money.
I hope so, Rafa.
I really do.
[Inhales]
[exhales]
[moans]
Thanks.
[Knocking on the door]
Housekeeping.
I gotta take you, Ana.
[Knocking on the door]
[woman] Housekeeping!
[Lawn mower revvs]
[lawn mower revvs]
Ah!
[Rafa] This looks great.
You're gonna enjoy it here.
[Doorbell rings]
[footsteps approaching]
Is Javier home?
He's in the garden
playing with the kids.
Who should I say
wants to see him?
Rafael.
- One moment.
- [Rafa] Thank you.
[Kids laughing]
[water splashing]
[laughs]
[kids laughing]
Yes?
It's your daughter, Ana.
Her mother is incapacitated.
I don't have
a daughter called Ana.
[Rafa] With all due respect,
this is your daughter
and she needs a place to stay.
[Woman] Javier? What is it?
They got the wrong family.
Are we clear?
[Sad song plays]
[car door opens]
May we go now, please?
[Engine starts]
[sad music plays]
[bell tolls]
You know what we need?
Some ice cream.
Wait here.
- [Bells tinkling]
- [people singing]
[man] Hi! I got some presents.
Vote please.
Tell your mom and your dad
to vote for Vega, okay?
When they come back
from shopping,
make sure to tell them.
Señor Vega will make
Puerto Rico great again.
Go Vega!
- [Bells tinkling]
- [people singing]
[tense music plays]
[Rafa] Ana!
Ana! Ana!
Ana, come on, I have angina!
Ana!
[People talking indistinctively]
Ana.
[Panting]
[groans]
Hey! What you doing here?
I'm looking for someone.
I'm someone.
What do you want? I got...
Oh, no. A girl.
We got girls.
A young girl.
All our girls are young, chico.
Really young.
Like, ten years old.
No, no, no!
She's from my neighborhood.
She's a neighbor.
I'm looking after her.
Just looking after her.
Hey, hey!
[Panting]
[bells tinkling]
[panting]
Hey!
Hey! Where's my car?
[Rock music plays]
[cell phone rings]
Hello?
[Ana]
I'm sorry I ran away, okay?
But I got back and this guy
broke in and drove it off--
Where?
[Ana] The GPS says
it's Jackie's Repair Shop
on Calle Sicilia.
I can't see anything.
[Rafa] Listen, just stay calm.
Wait for me, stay in the car,
I'll be right there.
[Ana]
I'm hiding under my jacket.
Okay. I'm here. I'm here.
[Rafa panting]
I see-- Okay, I'm here.
I see it. I see it.
I see it.
[Rock music playing]
See me?
Come on, come on.
[Welder sizzling]
You okay?
Yeah.
[Welder sizzling]
Excuse me?
Hello?
This car was stolen.
It's my car.
Somebody stole my car
and brought it over here.
I want my car back.
Hey!
[Claps]
I'm talking to you. Hey!
[Moans]
[welder sizzling]
Sir...
...you have my papi 's car.
I know the crisis
is affecting us all
in so many ways right now,
but since my older brothers
left the island,
and my mother passed,
my papi has had to raise me
all by himself.
And all the time,
he has had to carry on
cleaning gas station toilets.
I've spent my life in that car.
That car is my home.
Please, señor,
don't destroy it.
[Man tapping]
Okay, I'll give you 400 cash,
right now.
Maybe you should start
buying and selling used cars.
Are you at least gonna thank me?
[Rafa] Come on,
get out of the car.
- Get out of the car.
- [Ana] Now what?
Come on, come here.
What do you want me
to thank you for, huh?
Breaking into my car
and then causing me
to lose my stock?
Oh, sure,
like that one's on me now.
Or maybe I should thank you
for almost getting beaten up
or maybe killed
because I went into the barrio
looking for you,
and some thugs
thought I was a pervert.
- A what?
- [Rafa] A pervert!
A pervert! Forget it!
Listen, I'm done going
throughout this island
acting like a babysitter.
I know you don't take
responsibility for any--
Okay, watch me
take responsibility.
- Let's go.
- Wait!
- Stop it!
- Come on, let's go. Come on!
- Stop!
- Come on.
- Let go!
- Let's go.
Come on, I'll show you
a little responsibility.
[Ana] Let go!
- [Rafa] Come on.
[Ana] Get off,
you're squishing my arm!
[Bells tinkling]
This church
is gonna look after you.
'Cause, frankly, right now,
I can't help you anymore.
And if you're lucky, you're
gonna find some help in there.
Now, go.
Fine, you don't think
you need help?
Well, I do.
[Helen] Say, hallelujah!
[Crowd] Hallelujah!
Say, hallelujah!
¶ Sing hallelujah ¶
[crowd] ¶ Hallelujah ¶
[Helen] ¶ Hallelujah ¶
The gospel tells us
that Jesus addresses
each individual
he encounters,
whether rich or poor,
in terms
of their common humanity,
not in terms
of their bank accounts.
Reminds me of one
my favorites, John 12.
We heard how Mary
took an expensive ointment
to anoint the feet of Jesus.
"But why was this ointment
not sold for 300 denarii
and given to the poor?"
Asked his disciples accusingly.
Despite their protest,
Jesus received the gift
well worth a year's wages
for most people.
This is the same Jesus
who was born in a stall,
the same Jesus
who died on a trash heap.
What does this
tell us about our Lord?
It tells us
that Jesus
in His infinite wisdom,
His infinite wisdom,
a wisdom that is
sometimes perplexing,
yet always greater than ours,
allowed us
to enjoy the fruits of our labor
while still on earth.
[Crowd] Amen.
[Helen] I'm only here with you
a limited time,
but let me be an example
of what one can achieve
through God's blessing.
- Can I hear "amen"?
- Amen!
[Helen] The crisis
that He has sent this island,
we all share together,
is His will.
[Crowd] Amen!
[Helen] He knows.
He knows we struggle.
While across the water
we imagine the wealth of others.
[Crowd] Amen.
[Helen] This is God's challenge
to the people of Puerto Rico,
a challenge we shall overcome.
[Crowd] Amen.
[Helen] Amen.
[Helen] And remember, remember.
The more we all give,
the more we receive.
- [Crowd] Hallelujah!
- Amen.
[Crowd] Amen.
- Amen!
- [Crowd] Amen.
In a church?
Are you out of your mind?
Oh, in case you forgot.
You don't think I could've taken
care of all that by now
if I hadn't been stuck with you?
- Stuck with me?
[Rafa] Yes.
You're showing
some hustle around here.
[Man] Excuse me, sir?
[Man] Four hundred and ten,
four hundred and forty,
four hundred and fifty,
four hundred and fifty five,
four hundred and sixty,
four hundred and seventy...
[Helen]
Either I just saw somebody
pretending they couldn't walk
taking money
from good church-going people
or I'm witnessing a miracle.
Which is it?
Miracle?
As a pastor, it is my duty
to try to help you
and your daughter.
Oh, he's not my dad.
What is your relationship
to this child?
- Uncle.
- Neighbor.
A neighbor
who tries to sell cars.
I'm more like a family friend.
No, just neighbor.
Ana would like to apologize.
Yes, I'm sure she would.
I'm sorry.
The church teaches forgiveness.
And penance.
Fraud is a serious matter.
[Chuckling]
Obviously, she's gonna--
She's gonna give back the money.
And perhaps a small atonement
could be made,
if, say, she did a little work
at the church.
Well, we'd be happy to come back
another time,
but right now
I'm kind of in a crisis.
Or we could call the police.
[Door opens]
[door closes]
Thank you.
[Ana] Welcome.
It's good being on the road.
Isn't it?
Why don't we stay here
and never go back to San Juan?
You should bring your sons here.
It'd be really nice.
They have a busy life.
They have family,
they have kids.
What are their names?
Nicolás
and Andrés.
Why don't you see them?
You can just get
a flight to Miami
or get them to get a flight.
Cheers.
Authorities in San Juan
suspected foul play
after finding the body of a man
washed up on Luquillo Beach.
Police believe this is
yet another homicide
linked to increasing
gambling debts
as people search
for ways out of this crisis.
And now it's time
to check our local weather...
[turns off TV]
[sighs]
...who wishes
to share her life experiences
and how her faith helped her
accept God's choices for her.
All right, Ana.
I want you to tell the story
exactly as we discussed
about how the church and prayer
has helped you live
with your disability, okay?
Thank you, Pastor Helen.
My name is Zuleika,
and this is my story.
When I was five,
my father became a drunk
and pushed me down some stairs.
I broke my legs.
They told me
I would never walk again.
A few days ago,
I met a kind man.
That's him right there.
[Whispering]
[Ana] He'd lost everything
through his misguided behavior.
He was a heavy gambler,
and he took tablets
for his vagina.
[Laughter]
But he told me
the story of Saint Tino.
One day, Tino was leading
his cow beside a small lagoon
and the cow slipped on a rock
and fell in,
pulling Tino with him.
Tino thought he would drown.
So he put his hands together
and said a prayer.
Tino stood up and was amazed
to see that he could walk again.
A few days ago,
I went there myself
and I gently dipped my legs in,
and I said a prayer.
[Gasping]
Oh, my God.
[Applause]
[Helen] What an amazing story.
Gentlemen.
Open your hearts, everybody.
Tell your friends and family
about what you have seen
and heard today.
Bring them to our church to hear
this miracle for themselves.
[Ana] If we get ten percent
for every atonement,
we can pay Diego on time,
and I bet I can get her
to raise our cut.
We're just trying to make it
through the crisis, Rafa.
[Sad song plays]
Come on, let's go. Bedtime.
Good night.
[Rafa] Ana!
[Ana] My name is Zuleika,
and this is my story.
When I was five,
my father became a drunk
and, in one
of his drunken rages,
he pushed me down the stairs.
I broke my backbone.
They told me
I would never walk again.
Until a few days ago, when I
heard the story of Saint Tino,
a crippled farmer who thought
God had forsaken him
because he was poor
and he couldn't walk well.
One day, Tino was walking
his favorite cow
beside a small lagoon
when the cow slipped on a rock
and fell in,
pulling Tino with him
into the dark depths.
Tino thought he would drown
because the cow was sinking,
so he tried to swim,
but he didn't have enough air.
So then he put his hands
together, he said a prayer.
And suddenly, the waters
of the well rose up.
Whoosh...
And placed him gently
on the grass,
as if God's hands
are made out of water.
[Rafa] Camila!
Wait, let me explain.
After hearing that story,
I was inspired.
My friend took me there.
Using a child to make money?
No. Listen.
Embezzling? From a church?
I'm not embezzling from them.
It's more complicated than that!
I used to have
feelings for you, Rafael.
I said a prayer and...
[gasping]
[applause]
Now I understand
why your business went bad.
Because you're a crook.
Because you are a crook!
Listen. Hey! Hey!
Camila.
[People cheering in the church]
[applause]
[sad song plays]
[man] Sir?
Sir?
Sir.
Hey!
We're done here.
That's it. We're done.
Ana. Leave that.
Hey. Hey. Leave that.
Let's go. We're out of here.
You wanna call the police?
Go ahead. Call the police.
'Cause what you're doing here
is not only fraud,
you're taking advantage of
people who don't have anything
which is exactly what's wrong
with this island right now.
People like you coming in
and taking advantage.
And where are you from?
I'm from San Juan.
- But you're not Puerto Rican.
- I'm from Miami.
- [Helen] Oh, yeah? Miami-Cuban?
- Yes!
So you probably came here
to sell cars
because of
the Puerto Rican tax breaks?
I came here
for many reasons. Ana.
But you came here with the hope
of making more money
and paying less taxes.
So isn't that taking advantage?
[Ana] Look, Rafa.
Helen's given me a great job.
You never know how much money
there is inside this.
Ana has decided she wants
to stay with the church
for our summer camp.
Oh, Ana's decided?
Yes, she has.
Ana? Ana?
[Sad song plays]
[Latin music playing]
[cell phone alarm ringing]
[alarm stops]
Got Diego's cash, Rafa?
I got it in the car.
How you doing?
[Rafa panting]
Wrong move, Rafa.
[Car horn honks]
[scoffs]
[pants]
[man] Now you're really
pissing me off, Rafa.
[Pants]
[panting]
[exhales]
[man moans]
[man moaning]
[car engine starts]
[tense music plays]
[exhales]
[tires squeal]
[car alarm sounds
in the distance]
[gasps]
[car engine drowns]
[car engine starts]
[sad music plays]
[reporter] ...that you are
receiving campaign donations
from a well-known
church organization.
Here we go again
with the below-the-belt
corruption accusations.
[Reporter] Hardly surprising
that people would be suspicious
if you are not prepared
to reveal the sources
of your campaign donations.
[Sad music plays]
[kids screaming]
Just a minute.
Hi. I'm here to pick up Ana.
Oh, we have no record
of anyone coming to collect her.
And, in any case, she's giving
a big testimony this week, so--
Giving a testimony?
- [Woman] Yeah.
- I'd like to speak with her.
I'm sorry, sir,
we just don't allow
unaccompanied adults
on the grounds.
Ana?
You okay?
Worried about you.
You mustn't worry.
God takes care of us all,
especially the goodly.
[Woman] You see?
Ana is safe and well.
[Ana] I will say
a prayer for you,
that you are able to see someday
the wrong roads
you have taken in life.
[Woman] Why don't you go
and give your friend a hug
and then we go back
to your game? Okay, Ana?
[Kid] Excuse me.
Ana wanted you to have this.
Thank you.
[Sad song plays]
[dial tone]
[man] Sorry, we're not here
at the moment.
Please leave a message.
[Beep]
Nicolás, this papi.
Listen, uh...
I wanna talk
to you and your brother.
I love you, guys,
and I miss you.
Please call.
[Exhales]
[Latin Christian music plays]
[man] All right. Let's go.
[Presenter]
Remember, the more you give,
the more you shall receive.
So please do whatever
you can to help us,
help the people of this island.
[Rock music playing]
[presenter] And now,
ladies and gentlemen, it's time
for the Church of the Well
of God Summer Spectacular.
Put your hands together
for your host,
our very own prophet,
an angel sent from God,
the amazing,
the awe-inspiring...
And now...
Pastor Helen.
[Ovation]
[chorus]
¶ Hallelujah, Hallelujah ¶
¶ Hallelujah ¶
Hallelujah!
[Crowd] Hallelujah!
Say hallelujah!
[Chorus] ¶ Hallelujah ¶
Right now,
I give you
Zuleika.
[Crowd cheering]
[chorus]
¶ Hallelujah, Hallelujah ¶
Hallelujah!
[Crowd] Hallelujah!
[Ana] When I was five,
my father broke my spine
with a metal bar.
I was made to sleep
outside our yard
in a pen with the roosters.
Sometimes,
they would peck at me.
[Cell phone rings]
Diego.
You know
what has to happen next.
[Rafa]
I don't know what to say.
I don't have your money.
[Diego] What the hell, Rafa?
Do what you gotta do.
Drop me in the ocean somewhere.
Whoosh!
The waters of the lagoon
rose up.
Tino was at the top floating,
saved by the clear blue waters
of the pool.
Finally, he was gently
placed down on the grass.
It was as if God
had placed his soul
in a giant car wash.
After hearing this story,
I wheeled myself up
to the lagoon.
I dipped my legs in
and I said a prayer
and well...
[crowd cheering]
Oof.
[Crowd cheering]
[chorus] ¶ Hallelujah ¶
¶ Hallelujah, Hallelujah ¶
[crowd cheering]
Beautiful.
Hallelujah.
[Crowd] Hallelujah!
Hallelujah!
- Smile.
- [Ana] God bless you all.
[Woman] Thank you.
Let's go, darling.
- What time are we playing later?
- I don't know.
[Ana] Helen.
I need my cut.
Well, that money
belongs to the church.
It's been donated.
We're giving it
to the Vega Campaign...
What?
...to make Puerto Rico
great again.
The church got
that money because of me,
because they believed my story!
No, dearie,
they liked your story
because it gave them hope,
and that made them feel good.
And that's your reward,
giving these people back
some hope.
We had a deal.
And that deal is done.
[Somber music plays]
[officer]
Sir, is this your vehicle?
Yeah.
- It's in a handicap spot.
- [Rafa] Shit.
- Sorry, I'll move it.
- [Officer] What's that?
What?
[Officer] That.
Soda.
It belonged to a friend of mine.
I gave her a ride,
left it in the car.
Can you open the trunk, please?
Hands behind your back, sir.
Please.
[Ana] Wait! Stop!
Stop it!
You can't do that.
Are you two together?
- No.
- Yes.
He's taking care of me.
My mother's in prison.
I have a moonshiner
hawking
outside the San Juan Arena.
And I'm also going to need
someone from Social Services
to deal with the matter.
- No.
- [Radio] Backup is on the way.
Copy that.
[Whistling]
[whistling]
[sad song plays]
[door squeaks]
...weekend, it's your "Name
Your Price" extravaganza.
[Whistle]
Got any cash?
[Girl] Where's your mommy, then?
She's not here, is she?
You're all on your own.
What the hell is this?
She has nothing.
[Girl 2]
She has just dirty laundry.
They'll probably take her out
with the dirty laundry.
Don't worry. We'll be around.
[Adventurous music plays]
[car horn honks]
[Latin music plays]
[ominous music plays]
[wind blows]
[gasps]
[screams]
[uplifting music]
[dial tone]
[panting]
Don't speak. Just listen.
I've got a plan.
[Car horn honks]
I'm not seeing Rafa.
Yeah. About that, he's in jail.
Is this a joke?
Look, you want
your money back, right?
The man's a loser.
Even losers win sometimes.
You just gotta trust me, Diego,
and you'll get
your money back and some.
We just gotta show some hustle.
[Latin music plays]
[Ana] Let's go, Joe.
I got blown out of the blowhole!
[Helen] I know
all our inner circle members
are grateful to Congressman Vega
for helping us
exceed our fundraising target.
Señor Vega, we wanna show you
our gratitude and our love.
We know God is smiling upon you
for the upcoming election.
Today, you are blessed.
Our crisis will soon be over.
- Amen.
- [Crowd] Amen.
[Applause]
[Helen] Are there
any other local businesspeople
who wish to have
a blessing today?
Anyone?
[Whispering]
Ah, welcome.
Can you-- Can you help them up?
And you are?
My name is Rafael Rodriguez.
And what is it you do, Rafael?
I run a business
in Barrio Obrero.
And God willing,
that business is prospering.
We all do what we have to do
in order to survive.
[Applause]
Let me say a few words
for you then.
- Lord--
- Let me say a few words for you.
[Whispering]
There is a man in the front row
seat in the aisle
and he's got a suit on.
He's from the Department
of the Treasury
and he wants to have
a serious talk with you
regarding your illegal donations
to the Vega campaign.
As you said,
fraud is a serious business.
You can't prove anything.
[Ana clears her throat]
[Helen] Well, that money
belongs to the church.
It's been donated.
We're giving it
to the Vega campaign
to make Puerto Rico great again.
[Woman]
I can't hear anything at all.
What is that little girl
showing Helen?
[Helen]
Because it gave them hope
and that made them feel good.
And that's your reward,
giving these people
back some hope.
[Man] Twenty-six thousand,
twenty-seven thousand,
- [man] twenty-eight...
- [Ana] Twenty-eight.
- [Man] ...twenty-nine.
- [Ana] Twenty-nine.
- [Man] ...thirty.
- [Ana] Thirty thousand.
Gentlemen.
[Latin music plays]
- Come on, baby.
- I'm so done.
- Come on.
- So many times.
Yeah, there you go, tough guy.
Yeah.
Looks like your mom's
cleaning house.
[Ana] Yeah.
[Rafa] You're not done
with this car yet?
What's the matter with you?
Come on, let's go.
Let's go, slowpoke.
Get a move on.
Show me some hustle.
I'll show you some hustle!
[Rafa laughs]
This enough hustle?
- Come on!
- I'll hustle you up.
I'll give you
something to hustle!
[Latin music plays]
You know what you need?
You need a car.
A cool car,
a second-hand car
from Rafa's Quality Cars.
Name it, we have it!
We got white cars, one owner.
We got blue cars
filled with half a tank of gas,
four-nine-nine-five.
We got SUVs, like new,
nine-nine-three-nine.
So many cars, we don't know
what to do with them.
They're cheap,
they're old, they're classic.
I can wash it for you,
but I can't drive it.
I'm only eleven!
Rafa's Quality Cars.
He doesn't just have
the coolest cars in Puerto Rico,
but he is the nicest guy,
and you can trust him.
That's my promise to you.
[Rafa] And cut.
[Latin music plays]