♪♪ [harp]
We're late.
Let's go.
I really need to get
those new shoes.
I'm not spending $120
for a pair of sneakers.
What?
Sorry. If you really
have to have them,
I'll split them with you, okay?
Can we go in the toy store?
Not today.
I have raised up my servant,
Emmanuel David Isaiah,
ever my righteous right hand,
to be the light and covenant
to my people,
to all those who repent
and come unto me.
For in my servant, Emmanuel,
is the fullness of the Gospel.
People will trust you more
without your beard.
And people are fools.
Hephzibah Eladah Isaiah,
thou were chosen
to be helpmate to Emmanuel,
to be submissive and obedient
to thy husband.
You will now
take into your heart
seven sisters
to share your home.
Seven jewels... gifts given
only to the most righteous
of men.
It is good. It is good.
Peace be with you.
We'll be a little late.
Can you spare some change?
Uh, sorry.
We don't have any money.
Say, can you
spare some change?
Uh, yeah.
You live around here?
Uh, actually, my sister and I
are walking the earth,
spreading the word of God.
I'm a good handyman,
if you have need.
Well, my husband
often hires men
to do various jobs
around the house...
construction, yard work,
that sort of thing.
Uh-huh.
We're doing some remodeling.
I'm sure he could find
some work for you.
Wonderful.
There you go.
What's your name?
Emmanuel.
It means "God with us."
And thank you so much
for this.
Okay, guys. Let's go.
Why did you give him money?
The church teaches us
to help those in need.
I've been called by the Lord
to preach to men
who have lost faith
and seek guidance.
That's admirable.
Oh, how's it going?
"I am but
humble messenger of God,
traveling the earth,
spreading His word."
A little odd.
"Little"?
But a good carpenter.
He knows roofing.
He knows the Bible, too,
or rather
his interpretation of it.
What?
I'm just surprised.
It's not like you
to help me find workers.
Oh, I felt sorry for him.
He seemed like a nice man
down on his luck.
Thought he needed a break.
[hammering]
Here you go.
Mmm. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
♪♪ [harp]
Emmanuel?
Mom, I'm going for a run.
No, Elizabeth. We have to be
at your school by 7:00.
Coach said if I'm gonna be
on the track team next year,
I have to run every day.
45 minutes, and that's it.
You still need time to shower,
dress, eat.
I'll be fine, Mom.
All right. Run up at the track,
and take someone with you.
I've got a final tomorrow.
I'll go.
Okay.
Let me get my shoes.
Oh. I need
to get back to Katie
about going up to the lake
with her family
after school's out.
Elizabeth, those two weeks
at the cabin are the only time
we can be together this summer.
It's only six days, Mom.
Please?
I really wanna go.
I'll discuss it with Daddy,
and we'll talk about it later.
But I have to get back
to her, and...
I said we'll talk
about it later.
Oh, Mrs. Traughber
wants me to come in early
and play my harp for everyone
as they come in.
Oh, great, honey.
Great.
[sizzling]
Oh!
Oh, boy.
Whoo!
[coughing]
[grunts]
Hi.
Ooh!
Wha...
Yeah. I burned the potatoes.
Ohh.
Yeah.
It's ten to 7:00.
She's not gonna have time
to play the harp.
We'll be lucky if we
even get there on time
for the assembly.
All right, all right.
[garage door clanking]
You know,
it's been doing that all day.
I'll check it out
when we get back.
What if someone comes in
and steals all my stuff
while we're gone?
Trust me,
no one wants your stuff.
[Ed]
Our Dear Father in Heaven,
we come before Thee
at the close of this day,
thankful for our family
and for all that we enjoy.
We're thankful for Grandpa,
his example, love,
and for all that
his life taught us.
We pray that Thou wilt
watch over and bless Grandma
that she might know
of our love for her.
Please bless us this night
and watch over us,
in the name of Jesus Christ.
Amen.
[together]
Sleep well, everyone.
Let's go, boys.
You gonna sleep
in your own bed like a big boy?
Hmm?
Elizabeth.
I spoke with Daddy.
You can go with Katie.
Thanks, Mom.
Okay.
[mutters]
[lock clicks]
[keyboard clacking]
Hey. Turn the lights out
when you come upstairs.
Yep.
Nice talking to you.
"But the younger sister,
who was not quite as rude
as the others,
"called her Cinderella.
"In her ragged clothing,
with her dirty face,
Cinderella's was yet
a hundred times more beautiful
than her stepsisters."
Hey, not too late, girls.
Okay, Dad.
Good night.
You sleep well.
I love you both.
I love you, too.
Love you.
[door closes]
"With her dirty face,
Cinderella was yet
a hundred times more beautiful
than her stepsisters."
[grunts]
[sighs]
[dog barking, distant]
Thy will be done.
[quietly]
Get up. Get up.
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Don't speak.
Get up and come with me.
What?
Don't make a sound
or I'll kill you,
and then I'll kill
the rest of your family.
Put your shoes on
and follow me.
Now.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
Now silence.
Okay? Absolute silence.
Do as I say.
Keep your mouth shut.
Go.
Shh.
Open it.
Hurry.
Go.
[Mary Katherine]
Mommy.
[whimpers]
What?
Someone took Elizabeth.
Wh-What?
What, Mary Katherine?
A man took Elizabeth.
Oh, honey,
I'm sure you were just
having a dream.
[sighs]
Oh, she's probably downstairs
asleep on the couch.
Oh, sweetie, sweetie.
Come here.
It's okay.
Elizabeth?
[Lois]
[descending footsteps]
Ed...
Ed! Call 911!
[panting]
Tell me, what happened?
A man took Elizabeth.
What...
What man? Who was it?
[phone buttons beeping]
I don't know.
Mary Katherine!
Yes. My daughter's been taken!
Tell Mommy what happened!
Yeah, yeah, she's gone!
Why did he take her?
I don't know.
Jim, he took her!
Mary Katherine saw him!
He... He... He...
She saw him take her!
Lois!
Why would he...
Why would anyone do that?
She saw him?
Who was it?
I don't know.
But find her.
[siren blaring]
We've... We've gotta find her.
We'll find her.
We've gotta find her!
Please! Please!
My... My daughter
was taken by a man.
Behold the sword of vengeance
hangeth over you,
and the time soon cometh
he avengeth the blood
of the saints and our people.
For he will not suffer
their cries any longer.
Where is she?
They're gonna find her.
The boys are looking for her.
Who would do this?
[door opens]
Who would...
Who would want to...
Mrs. Smart?
Hi, I'm Detective Coleman.
I need to ask you
a few questions.
You mind if I sit down? No.
Has your daughter ever
snuck out of the house
at night before?
No.
No. Elizabeth would never
leave the house without...
Did you have a fight?
Was she angry about something?
No.
[camera shutter clicking]
We... We had words
about a vacation
she wanted to take
with a friend, but...
but I told her
she could go.
Well, girls can be
really sensitive at this age.
Can I get the name
and number of her friend?
Elizabeth's not with Katie.
Does she have a boyfriend?
Maybe one who lives nearby?
Has a car?
Elizabeth doesn't
have a boyfriend.
She's 14.
How much time does she spend
on the Internet?
Do you know if she
was communicating
[door opens]
with anyone in particular?
Mom!
Oh, sweetie!
Someone took her.
[chattering]
Elizabeth Smart, age 14.
Apparent kidnapping.
The little sister saw the guy,
but she could be covering
for the big sister
if she snuck out.
The alarm was faulty.
The backdoor was unlocked.
They probably left that way.
The kitchen window was open,
and the screen's been cut.
Now, it looks to me like
it was cut from the inside.
Who are all these people?
Friends and family.
Some were here when we got here,
and more keep arriving.
Well, let's get them
all out of here.
This whole scene's
been contaminated.
All right.
I want you to listen to me.
Elizabeth is strong.
She's smart.
She's got good judgment.
So wherever she is,
she's being strong,
and she's gonna need you
to be strong for her.
Someone took her.
I don't know where she is.
Lois, look at me.
Look in my eyes.
Our Heavenly Father
knows where Elizabeth is.
Believe that in your heart.
She's got guardian angels
all around her.
Lois? Where...
Where is, uh, Lois?
Mr. Smart?
Mr. Smart,
I'm Detective Richard Kassen.
I'd like to ask you
a few questions.
Please, can you get
some more men out there looking?
Everything that can be done
right now is being done, sir.
If I could just take
a few minutes with you...
Where is everyone going?
This house is
a crime scene, Mr. Smart.
We have to take every precaution
to make sure that
whatever evidence is here
is not compromised in any way.
Yes, I understand.
All right. Good.
Let me just clear
a few things up.
Your daughter's name
was Elizabeth?
Yes. Is Elizabeth.
Right. Has she ever
run away before?
No. No, she didn't run away.
She was taken.
I know how girls
this age can be.
They think
they know everything...
Excuse me. What's being done?
We're gonna take you
and your family
down to the station.
[Officer]
Sir, you can't go in there.
Station?
It's okay, Officer.
Excuse me.
Wait a minute. What is it?
Who is this guy?
My brother Jim.
What are you doing?
I gotta get her picture
on the news.
Pete, set up
a house-to-house search
in the neighborhood.
Make sure you clear the homes
on the streets above
the Smart place.
Oh, and, uh, see if you can get
the chopper to do a flyover.
All right.
Mr. Smart, you may wanna
get some clothes on.
[crying]
[helicopter blades whirring]
[door buzzes]
What's going on?
Have a seat, Mr. Smart.
Where's my family?
What... What's...
What's being done?
Everybody's fine.
Your family's just fine.
Have a seat, please.
All right.
Look, here's the problem.
We don't have a whole lot
to go on.
We got a nine-year-old girl
woken up in the middle
of the night
who thinks maybe
she saw someone.
Mary Katherine got
a good look at the man.
She said he was wearing
a dark-colored cap...
I'm gonna level with you,
Mr. Smart.
I came in here to talk
to you alone,
just you and me.
Please, where are my children?
They're fine, Mrs. Smart.
Your mother
has the little ones,
and Mary Katherine
and the older boy
are right next door.
Now, we need to clear up
a few things.
How would you describe
your marriage?
You got a mortgage.
You got a job and a wife.
You got six kids.
That's a lot on your plate.
Sometimes you can react
in a moment.
You make a mistake,
you explode, things...
What does any of this have to do
with finding my daughter?
Mr. Smart, I have to ask you
these questions, all right?
It's procedure.
So, do you have something
to tell me?
I'm right here.
Your husband ever
get angry with you
or your children?
What? No. No.
I... I wanna go home.
I wanna be there
when Elizabeth gets home.
I need...
No, what we need to do
is get a good picture
of the family.
Now, what kind of father
is your husband?
My husband
did not take Elizabeth.
Now bring me my children now.
I just have
a few more questions.
Please bring me my children now!
You think it's me.
You think I took
my daughter and...
And what?
Hid her somewhere?
Is that what happened?
I did not take my daughter.
I understand
you've got to clear me.
I... I... I get that now.
But, please,
you're wasting time.
We've got to find Elizabeth
before they get too far.
Mr. Smart,
in our experience,
when a young girl is taken
from her home like this,
it is usually by someone
that she knows well, all right?
And she is usually found
within two miles
of her own home.
Did you know that?
No.
Your son Charles was home,
is that right?
Yes.
And does he get along
with your daughter?
They fight?
They close?
We're wasting time.
Charles had nothing
to do with this.
You think it might
be someone you know?
I'm not sure.
You said his voice
sounded familiar.
Yes, but not someone I know.
He was as tall as Charles.
Charles.
Is that your big brother?
How old is Charles?
He's 15.
So you and your sister
are pretty close in age.
You guys fight a lot?
Not a lot.
Sometimes, I guess.
You know, I had a sister.
I know how that can be.
Sometimes she makes you
so angry,
you just don't know
what to do.
Not really.
She's pretty,
that's for sure.
Maybe one of your friends
likes her.
Everyone likes her.
No, I mean
in a special way, like...
like a boyfriend.
No.
[chattering]
[siren blares]
[Officer]
Keep those people back,
you hear me?
[Woman]
Make sure you get
a shot of both!
[Reporters shouting questions]
Jim,
wha...
I need you to talk
to the media.
Oh, no, Jim.
I don't wanna say...
We need the press.
We've got to get
this story out now,
this minute.
We can't afford
to lose any more time.
The first few hours
are critical.
We need you to talk
to the public.
to whoever has her.
Could you talk to us?
Tell us something?
Look this way, please.
Please,
whoever took Elizabeth,
I can't imagine why
you would take her.
She's our daughter.
Please let her go
or... or bring her home.
Please bring her back.
I would pray that you realize
she's just a child.
This guy seems real.
She's our daughter.
I'm gonna call the FBI.
She needs to be home with us.
[Man]
Elizabeth!
[Woman]
[Jim] There's this guy
that's offered to fly over
the area in his Cessna.
Good.
And I spoke
to Dawn Anderson
from the Laura
Recovery Foundation.
She flew in from Texas
last night when she heard.
She's helping us set up
a search center
at the Shriners Hospital.
What did she have to say?
She said we gotta keep
Elizabeth's name
front and center.
Daily press briefings,
color posters
with all of her information
along the bottom...
age, height,
her hair and eye color,
what she was wearing
the night she was taken.
How many posters?
[dog barking]
Oh, I figure
50 to start with.
50 colored posters?
That'll take a long time.
Ed, 50,000 colored posters,
and we need them now.
We gotta cover the airports,
freeways, borders,
bus stations, you name it.
[Man]
Elizabeth!
[Emmanuel]
Thank thee God
for delivering
this jewel of innocence
that we may,
[crying]
as members of this society,
be faithful.
And through this great
trust of light,
priceless diamonds forming.
A brilliant
shining diamond truth.
Let us be obedient in all things
and willing to sacrifice
all things,
even our very lives
if necessary.
Cold?
That we be of mortal...
[Emmanuel continues rambling]
I wanna go home.
You are home.
[crying continues]
You're lucky.
He chose you.
...gleam in his eyes,
in his heart.
He who suffered and died...
[Man]
Elizabeth!
They're looking for me.
Don't worry.
They'll stop.
[Emmanuel]
They shall not find her.
She belongs to me.
Elizabeth!
[Emmanuel resumes rambling]
[ringing]
[beeping]
[beeps]
Hello?
Who is this?
No, absolutely not!
[beeps]
Who was that?
He said he was a reporter
with the
Salt Lake City Gazette.
He wanted to interview
Mary Katherine.
[ringing]
I'm sorry.
You can't touch that.
It's still part
of the crime scene.
[sniffles]
Can I get you something
to eat or drink?
How do I know if she's eating?
How do I know
if she's warm?
You're going to
find her, right?
We're doing
everything we can.
[Emmanuel]
Forget about your past life.
It had no meaning.
I'm all you have.
I'm the one who knows
the real you.
[fabric tears]
And that bright light
that shines within you
is something
only I can see.
I want my mom and dad.
They no longer exist.
Uh, this... this is a...
this is a list of everyone
I could remember who...
who worked on the house
in the last year.
This is a list
of all the people
that attended
Elizabeth's last concert.
And, um, these are...
these are the names
of... of all of her friends
that might've seen her
with someone.
Great.
This is all gonna help.
Uh, I need
to get back home.
I can have one of my men
take you back.
I need...
I need to... to...
Mr. Smart, are you all right?
Mr. Smart?
[beeps]
I need an ambulance
right away.
Ed Smart was taken
to the hospital today
after he collapsed.
Doctors there said
he was suffering
from exhaustion and stress
and is expected
to recover quickly.
The Smart family
has organized a search
through the mountains
behind their home
with the help
of thousands of volunteers.
Mayor Rocky Anderson
has just announced
that the reward
for Elizabeth's safe return
is up to $250,000.
The money appears to be coming
from major corporations
in the area
and concerned local citizens.
I have never seen anything
quite like the scope
of this search.
It seems as if the whole world
feels like they've
lost Elizabeth.
We're here to sign up.
Sorry, kids.
You've gotta be 18 to search.
We are 18.
Just be careful, okay?
[People shouting]
Elizabeth!
[plane overhead]
[Man yelling]
[dog barking]
[Woman]
Elizabeth!
[Man]
Elizabeth, can you hear us?
Elizabeth!
[Woman]
[Man]
Elizabeth!
Lay out the bedrolls,
then come join us
for God's bounty.
They're still
looking for me.
Did I not tell you
I am your salvation?
You eat
if I say you eat.
You sleep if I say you sleep.
I walked into your house
and took you.
God had me do that.
Don't you see?
You live if I let you live.
Your family lives
if I say they live.
Now do as I say.
[Man, distant]
Elizabeth!
[Woman, distant]
[Emmanuel's voice]
Don't say a word
or I will kill you
and your family.
[Man, distant]
Elizabeth!
[Woman]
[Man] Elizabeth!
Elizabeth! Elizabeth!
Elizabeth!
[yelling]
It's me, Daddy.
[chattering]
[Lois]
Did we say everything?
Did we remember to mention
the reward again?
[Man]
You did fine.
I don't know how
they expect you to become
public speakers overnight.
[Ed]
We just wanna say
the right thing,
reach whoever we can.
I'm Marc Klaas.
I'm here to help.
I followed your story.
I'm sorry about your daughter.
Thank you for coming.
The first thing
we need to do
is to get a forensic
specialist up here
to talk to
the younger sister.
She's an eyewitness,
and the image of that man
is burned into her retina.
Now, there's a woman
named Jeanne Boylan.
She's the leading forensic
sketch artist in the country,
and I can have her here
in half an hour.
The police and FBI told us
not to push her...
that we might
taint her memory.
Ed, your daughter's
been missing
for six days.
Jim...
You need to try
everything that you can.
Uh, this is Marc Klaas.
This is my brother Jim.
I know who you are.
Thanks for coming down.
We can use all the help
we can get.
Ed, why don't you let me
talk to your daughter?
What's her name? Mary Elizabeth?
Maybe I could get her
to remember...
You know what?
We really appreciate
the help, Marc,
but that's not gonna happen.
There's no way
this kid's still alive.
We're looking for a corpse.
I'm sorry.
From the bottom
of my heart,
thank you for helping.
Jim, if I could just
sit down with Ed and Lois
and talk to them.
I've been in their shoes,
and I can empathize
with what they're going through.
I'll try and arrange something.
How long are you in town?
As long as you need.
Good. Thank you.
I will talk to Ed tonight.
Uh, I'm gonna wanna film
our conversation.
Is that okay?
You wanna film
your "father to grieving father"
conversation?
Why?
Who are you representing?
Myself...
and Fox News.
They're very interested
in the whole story
surrounding the kidnapping,
and I thought it'd be
very good for this case...
Go home, Mr. Klaas.
I'm just here to help.
[Reporters shouting questions]
Hey, everyone.
This is Chris Thomas.
He and his partner
own Intrepid Group,
a public relations firm.
He's put his business on hold
to handle the media for us.
Thank you so much.
Thanks.
I've got some news.
Tomorrow morning,
the
Salt Lake City Tribune
is gonna run a story
that says the investigation
is now pointing
toward a family member.
[People gasping]
[Jim]
You've gotta be kidding.
Why? What happened
to that guy that the milkman saw
in the neighborhood?
The guy in the green Saturn?
Bret Michael Edmunds.
The police are looking for him.
They say they just
wanna talk to him,
but he has not
been identified as a suspect.
They can't find him
so it has to be one of us?
The article is gonna say
that it's been determined
that the window screen
was cut from the inside...
that the entrance was staged.
Two of the reporters
at the
Tribune...
a Kevin Cantera
and Michael Vigh...
claim they have four sources
within the police department
who will confirm
what they're printing.
What sources?
[Man]
Yeah.
You can't say that.
You can't just lie.
In any big story,
there's going to be
false accusations
and people who wanna
get their names in the paper.
People will read that.
They might believe it.
Well, the police
have to make a statement
saying it's not true.
I tried. They won't.
Not in time.
It'll be on
the news tonight.
It'll be in
the newspapers tomorrow.
Every news source in the country
will pick this up.
People will stop searching
if they read this article.
Why should they bother
searching for Elizabeth
when they think
we took her ourselves?
[murmuring]
[Chris]
We have to release
a family statement
saying that we're cooperating
with the police
and that we will continue
to do whatever it is
they ask of us, okay?
[machine crackling]
[Man]
How old are you?
[Ed]
I'm 46.
In those 46 years,
did you ever hurt anyone?
I... I... I don't understand.
You mean physically
or emotionally?
Just answer the question.
Yes, I guess
in 46 years,
I've hurt someone.
Is your name Ed?
Yes.
Did you take
your daughter, Elizabeth?
No.
Did you kill
your daughter, Elizabeth?
No.
You have no idea
how to serve me.
You mock me when you
pretend to love me.
That's not true.
I've given my whole life to you.
Perfect obedience
leads to perfect love,
leads to perfect faith.
You're not worthy.
Your soul is lost
in vanity and false pride.
Your role in this life
is to serve me!
I've done that!
You know to disobey me
is to go against God
and to damn yourself
to an eternity in hell?
You know that?
I've given up
my whole family!
I have followed you
wherever you've led me.
All I said was that
I miss my daughter.
She is your sister
in his eyes,
and you better get used
to the idea.
It's the plan...
[continues]
[screams]
Where are you going?
Nowhere. I was just...
You know I have your house
surrounded, don't you?
You know they will all die
if you are discovered?
You'll never know
who is part of me.
who you can trust.
Now let's go home.
You're a child
who ran away from her parents.
I'm the one
who saved you, right?
That's who I am...
your savior.
I will kill you.
I will kill your family.
They will all die.
[echoing]
It basically
says that, uh...
[clears throat]
It says that Jim
and David and Ed
are part of a gay sex ring...
that their wives
know about it,
and that somehow
the sex ring
is responsible for Elizabeth
being taken.
[laughter]
What's so funny?
It's just so ridiculous.
No one's gonna
believe that nonsense.
They've gone too far.
Unfortunately, the mainstream
media will pick this up,
so many people
will think it's true.
Oh!
You're going to
have to defend yourselves
if you wanna maintain
the support of the people.
[scoffs]
What do we do?
We reject this malicious attack
on our family.
We will not respond
to vicious lies.
We, as a family,
stand united in our faith
and in our desire
to find Elizabeth.
[Reporter]
One more question, please.
Mr. Smart! Mr. Smart!
[Reporters shouting questions]
How come we get
to live at home again?
Well, we have to be here
when Elizabeth gets back.
Later, we're gonna go
to the animal shelter
and get a dog.
I always wanted a dog.
Yeah.
You said
we couldn't have one.
Now we can.
I wish I had my BB gun.
I could've shot him.
Honey, this wasn't something
you could've stopped.
Mary Katherine
could've stopped him.
She could've screamed
or bit him.
That's not true.
Okay, your sister
may have saved your life.
She may have saved
all of our lives.
We don't know
what that man would've done.
And she kept watch
over all of us,
and she woke up Daddy
when she thought it was safe.
Mary Katherine is a hero.
You know that,
don't you, sweetie?
I could've stopped him.
I was too scared.
You did the right thing.
Do you think Elizabeth
knows that?
Yeah, I do.
[Ed]
Why wouldn't they be scared?
Someone can come in here
in the middle of the night,
take one of them,
and their father
wouldn't even hear.
[dog barking, distant]
Tear it up.
[paper ripping]
[crying]
[ripping continues]
[crying continues]
To the holders
of Elizabeth Ann Smart
and our friends
throughout the world,
it has been several weeks
since our daughter, Elizabeth,
was awakened and taken
by force from our home.
Every minute of every day,
we search for her
and pray for her
and yearn for her
to come home.
So many of you
have helped us in that search
and in our prayers,
and we wanna thank you
from the bottom of our hearts.
She's still out there,
waiting for us
to come and find her.
Someone out there
knows where she is.
Elizabeth, be strong.
We won't break our promise.
[gasps]
[laughing]
We are going to find you.
Bret Michael Edmunds,
who was seen
in the Smarts' neighborhood
the week of
Elizabeth's disappearance,
was questioned by police
in a West Virginia hospital.
It was determined
that Mr. Edmunds knows nothing
about the disappearance,
and we believe that this is
a dead end.
Thank you very much.
[Reporters shouting questions]
Guess what?
[Kassen]
What's that?
Remember Richard Ricci?
Worked at the Smart house.
Ricci. Ricci.
Oh, yeah. Tall guy.
Didn't we bring him in
for questioning,
and his wife gave him an alibi?
Yeah, they just brought him in
on a parole violation.
I think we should
question him again.
All right. Make it so.
Thanks.
Give up.
You're not gonna find anything.
You can ask me
for 24 more hours,
and the answer
will still be no.
I did not have anything
to do with taking that girl.
Okay, fine.
Let's start again
at the beginning.
Your dime.
I got nowhere to go.
Sure you do,
you heartless bastard.
How about I throw you in
with the general population
and let them ask you
where you put the little girl?
You know I lost
my own son when he was just 9?
Don't tell me about heartless.
You played that card, Richard.
Where'd you go
in the jeep?
You took their jewelry.
When did you decide
to take their daughter?
[sighs]
Go to hell.
We've arrested a guy
on a parole violation.
[Coleman]
He was on one of your lists.
He worked at your house
for a long time.
Who?
His name is Richard Ricci.
Richard...
He knew all our children
by name.
We gave him a jeep
so he could come and go.
He knew the layout
of our house.
I fired him because
Lois's jewelry was missing.
Ricci's a heroin addict.
He's got a record that
goes back three decades.
[Coleman]
We found it when
we searched his home.
That's my bracelet.
He's probably pawned
some of the stones.
Now, he's got
a dubious alibi
for the night that
Elizabeth was taken,
and, uh...
Yeah?
Two days before the night
Elizabeth disappeared,
Ricci took his jeep
out of a garage
where it was being serviced.
When he returned it
several days later,
it was covered in mud,
two of the seat covers
were missing,
and there were
a thousand extra miles
on the vehicle that he can't,
or won't, account for.
[Coleman]
Now, we're analyzing
the mud that was on the jeep,
see if we can't figure out
where he's been, but...
So where is she?
Where is Elizabeth?
I'm afraid we don't know.
He's not talking.
[Coleman]
He's claiming he's innocent.
His wife, Angela,
says he was with her
the night...
well, that night.
Ed, Lois,
I'm 99.9% sure
that we have our guy.
[sniffling]
[no audible dialogue]
[crying]
[screaming]
[dog barking]
Mom!
[screaming]
How can you call it a prank?
It happened exactly
the same way as our house.
The screen was cut
the exact same way.
She's my niece.
How can that be a coincidence?
Detective,
[sighs]
I... I... I don't mean
to do that...
tell you how to do your job,
but it seems to me...
I... I know, but...
Fine.
[beeps]
It's like the police
simply want to be done with it.
Ed, maybe it is
just a copycat.
You know
how crazy people are.
And Richard Ricci
is in custody.
Come on, Lois.
The screen, the knife.
I know it's the same man.
[gavel bangs]
[Judge]
The State of Utah
vs. Richard Ricci.
Mr. Ricci, you've been
convicted of burglary
and will be held
pending sentencing.
The sentencing will be set
for August 30.
Your trail for bank robbery
has been set for November...
Forget the robbery.
Why isn't he asking him
where Elizabeth is?
They haven't even charged him
with that yet.
Excuse me.
Mrs. Ricci?
Please, I beg you.
Please ask Richard
to tell us where he was,
what he knows.
Does he know where
Elizabeth is?
Look, I know
that you're hurting,
but Richard was in bed
with me that night.
Where did he go
in the jeep?
Why won't he tell us
where he was?
Why does he keep
changing his story?
Honestly, I don't know.
But I know that Richie
would never hurt a child.
Never.
Please.
I'll talk to him again.
It's been two weeks.
Angela doesn't seem
to know anything.
That's because Ricci
hasn't told her anything.
Well, maybe
I could talk to him.
I could plead with him
as a mother.
I'll see what I can do.
Please.
We could go to the mayor.
He'd understand.
He'd help us.
Mrs. Smart,
we have to go through
so many official channels...
At any time,
our daughter could be killed!
Do you realize that?
Even now while we're standing
here talking about it!
I'll see what I can do.
[paper ripping]
[phone ringing]
Mmm.
[beeps]
Hello?
Oh.
Well, thank you
for telling me.
[beeps]
That was Detective Kassen.
Richard Ricci suffered
a brain aneurysm last night.
What?
Well, what does that mean?
Essentially, he's brain dead.
No.
Then it's... it...
it's... it's over.
Come. Come here.
[crying]
I'm sorry you're so sad.
I'm just tired,
Mary Katherine.
She's gonna come home.
I know she is.
It's too bad
we have to wait so long.
That's not the man
that took Elizabeth.
A-Are you sure, honey?
I'm positive.
But Mary Katherine
just saw the picture,
and she says
it's not Ricci.
Maybe he's not
the right man after all.
It was him, Ed.
He was probably
working with someone,
but it was him.
The police are sure.
Maybe we should be following
other leads.
There are no other leads.
Well, of course there are.
I can't let this
consume my life anymore.
I have five other children
who need me.
They have to start school.
They have to start living
a normal life,
and I'm never here,
because I'm in press conferences
from 4:00 a.m. to midnight.
Do you wanna have
a memorial for her?
Is that what
you're saying?
No.
I'll always have hope.
But I'm so afraid,
every time the phone rings,
it's the police telling me
they found her body.
She's gone.
She's just gone.
I don't believe that.
Well, I have to.
For the other children,
I have to.
..."and reserve a swift judgment
against every worker"...
[continues rambling]
You are so young,
and you know so little.
But as you grow up,
you will understand
how lucky you are
to be here, away from
the sins of the world.
My family's
still looking for me.
[chuckles]
No.
No, they stopped long ago.
[firewood thudding]
[Emmanuel]
Stop crying.
Don't be lifted up in pride.
You should pray for forgiveness
for holding on
to worldy connections.
Your only connection is to me
and to God everlasting.
Now come. Come, come.
[chattering]
I have to go
to the bathroom.
[scraping]
I think there might be something
to the call we got from Texas
about the guy in the car.
Ed, it's over, all right?
Now, we have searched
all across America.
We've had dozens
of FBI investigators
work this case.
We've brought in
cold case experts,
criminal profilers.
We've done it all.
You're just gonna have to
find a way to let go.
My daughter is alive, Richard.
I know she's out there,
and she's depending on me
to find her.
Well, it's possible
that somebody that knows Ricci
will come forward and tell us...
Mary Katherine saw
a picture of Ricci.
She says it's not him.
He was not the one
in her room that night.
I know Mary Katherine
didn't recognize his picture,
but it was late
and it was dark.
Look, Ed, I understand
how you feel.
I really do.
There is no evidence
my daughter is dead.
None.
She's alive,
and I will not give up.
With or without your help,
I will never give up.
[Ed]
And we're offering
a $10,000 reward
for any information
clearing Richard Ricci.
We know that Ricci
had someone meet him
when he dropped off the jeep
at the garage.
We still stand firm
in our belief
that Elizabeth is alive.
Mary Katherine,
you hungry?
No, thanks.
How's the scrapbook coming?
Really good.
I've got something
from almost every week
she's been gone.
I don't want her to feel
like she missed anything.
[chuckles]
Oh, you're
a wonderful sister.
You know that,
don't you?
You know, honey,
there's a chance
that Elizabeth is in heaven
with Grandpa.
I know, but she's not.
She's trying to get home.
"Cry the Lord, and with you,
I will stand by you."
Daddy, I think
I know who it is.
Hmm?
I think I know
who took Elizabeth.
It was Emmanuel.
Remember that guy we met
when we were shopping?
That was, uh...
The guy that came
to the house to work
on the roof with you.
That was over a year ago?
Yes.
This is a new lead.
This is who
she remembers.
You said, "Don't taint
her memory," and we didn't.
And her mind finally cleared.
She remembered.
She always said he was
about as tall as Charles,
which is 5'8".
Ricci was over six feet.
Over six feet.
I get it, Ed.
Look, you're just gonna
have to trust on this.
We are doing everything
that we can.
I don't know why
you didn't have me
make a sketch.
I was on the roof with him.
I remember what he looks like.
Ed, I'm sorry. I just...
I don't think
this is going anywhere.
Now, I'm gonna send a couple
guys around the shelters
to look for this, uh...
Emmanuel.
...this Emmanuel.
There could be a hundred
homeless guys
that do odd jobs.
Mary Katherine doesn't
remember a hundred men,
she remembers just one.
I know, Ed.
We talked to her.
Now, let me see
what I can do.
Okay.
Ed, it's Peter Coleman.
Listen, I've just met
this artist, Darlene Neilson.
Would you mind trying her out?
Maybe you guys can come up
with a sketch of the man
that Mary Katherine remembers.
[Officer]
Attempted shoplifting.
Calls himself Emmanuel.
Doesn't have any ID,
but gives his date of birth
as sometime after
the birth of Christ.
[Officer on radio]
Is he cooperating with you?
Yeah, seems harmless.
Then we got nothing here.
No warrants.
Roger. Let him go.
Okay.
On your way.
May I help you?
I'm looking for maps
of San Diego
and the surrounding areas.
Yes. Maps.
That will be in
our reference section.
Emmanuel will kill
the rest of your family.
He has followers
surrounding your house.
Are you two okay?
Yes, we're fine,
thank you.
My daughter and I...
we're planning on traveling
south with my husband.
He's... He's just
looking at maps now.
[Emmanuel]
Thank you so much.
Are you okay?
Are you Elizabeth Smart?
Her name is Augustine.
She's very shy.
Well, you folks
have a nice day.
Thank you so much, Officer.
[Man]
This is the final boarding call
for Coach 63 to San Diego.
Final boarding call
[Ed]
Our Father in heaven,
we are thankful for our family
gathered together here
on Elizabeth's birthday.
We thank Thee for Elizabeth,
for her spirit
of love and kindness.
We ask that Thou
wilt watch over her
and keep her safe,
that she might one day
return to us.
We pray that the abductor
might feel Thy spirit,
and his heart be softened
and changed
that he might let her go.
We do this in the name
of Jesus Christ.
Amen.
[together]
I thought we could go
around the table
and each say something
that we remember
and miss about Elizabeth.
I know that I miss
her helping me
make blueberry pancakes
on Sunday mornings.
[chuckling]
I miss her
reading to me.
I'm old enough
to read by myself,
but it's better
when she reads to me,
so I can close my eyes
and picture the story.
[Man coughing]
[chattering]
[train horn blaring]
[Emmanuel]
On this day 15 years ago,
Jesus chose you
to come into this world.
And it was then
that He whispered to me
that you would be mine.
[Man coughing]
[train horn blaring]
Happy birthday.
[chattering]
[Man]
Merry Christmas to you.
[Woman]
Yeah.
[chattering continues]
Get back in line.
I want more food.
Don't speak to anyone.
I never do.
Good girl.
So your dad and I made
each of you a memory box.
We wrote each of you
a letter
telling you how much
you mean to us.
Thank you.
And we put it
inside of a box
with some pictures
and things we collected
over the years.
What about a miracle?
What?
It's Christmas.
Maybe we'll get a miracle.
I hope so, honey.
[Emmanuel]
On this day many years ago,
a child was born.
A special child
that would die
for our sins.
Now I am here,
as God willed it,
to spread His word.
Shall we pray?
Having heard Your words,
Father,
and having understood
your plan for me,
I will be Your vessel
in this world
and in heaven beyond.
Let us hold hands.
I will call
this shining soul Augustine.
She will forever be mine
and forever serve the Lord
through me.
Do you do so freely,
Augustine?
♪ Jesus chose you
to come into this world ♪
♪ And it was then
that He whispered to me... ♪
We sent people around
to all the surrounding shelters,
looking for this Emmanuel.
We don't have anything
in our database.
There's not a whole lot more
we can do.
Ricci took her, all right?
He may have had an accomplice,
and we are still looking
for the guy.
You've been looking for him
since October.
Nothing's happening.
What can it hurt
to put out the sketch?
It can generate
hundreds of false leads.
All our manpower looking
for Ricci's accomplice
goes on a wild-goose chase,
we lose time and focus.
It's frustrating
not having answers, Ed.
I know that.
Let us do this our way.
[scoffs]
W... W... What...
Richard...
Hey, Ed?
Do what you feel
in your heart.
Anyone with information
about Richard Ricci
is asked to come forward.
The Smarts want
to clear Mr. Ricci
of kidnapping Elizabeth.
Ed.
Elizabeth,
we are looking for you.
We have not given up.
We know you're trying
to come home to us.
We will never give up.
Thanks, Ed.
You can wrap that up now
if you want.
I think it's gonna
generate some new calls.
John, can I speak to you
in confidence?
You know you can.
You know how grateful
I am to you for calling us
and putting us
on your program.
I know. I'll continue
to do anything I can.
Mary Katherine
came to me in October,
told me she thinks
she remembers
who was in
her room that night.
She said it was
this fellow, Emmanuel,
who worked for us
more than a year ago.
He was only at the house
for a few hours,
but she seems to remember.
I had a sketch made,
but Lois doesn't want me
to go out with it
because she wants
to protect Mary Katherine.
Have you told the police?
Yes.
But they say
don't release it.
It might generate hundreds
of false leads.
And if we put out
a picture of him,
it might scare him off,
and he'll go underground.
It's your daughter
who's missing.
She doesn't belong
to the detectives
working your case.
You do what you think
is best for your family.
Thanks, John.
I'll call you if I decide
to go out with it.
Okay.
You say you have
new information
on the Elizabeth Smart
kidnapping?
I spoke with Ed recently.
He told me his young daughter,
Mary Katherine,
remembers who was in
her room that night.
[Man]
After all this time?
She's the only eyewitness
to the crime.
I met her.
She's a bright young girl.
America's Most Wanted
is going to take a look
a look at this new information.
Wh... What did you do?
I told him that
in confidence.
Do you know
what this means?
This will take
the spotlight off of Ricci.
And what if
Mary Katherine is wrong?
W... We can't put her
through that again.
She's suffered enough.
Don't do this to her.
But...th... there's a chance.
What were you thinking?
[sighs]
[beeps]
Hey.
It's late.
You should go to bed.
I didn't realize
he was dangerous.
he could be someone
who could hurt us.
He seemed nice.
It's not your fault.
Of course it's my fault.
I'm the mother. I'm supposed
to keep my children safe.
You kept them safe.
You did everything
in your power
to give them a secure home.
Evil will find a place
through a crack in the wall.
There was nothing
we could've done to prevent it.
We go out
with that sketch tomorrow.
Really?
I don't know if Emmanuel's
involved or not,
but we have to eliminate him
as a suspect.
Okay.
There are good reasons
why Richard Ricci
is the top potential suspect
in Elizabeth's kidnapping.
He stole from our home.
He lied to us.
He never came forward
with satisfactory answers
to our questions.
The Smarts are on
a wild-goose chase.
This guy... this Emmanuel...
is just one of a dozen guys
we're looking at.
I don't blame Ed.
He's just trying
to keep the case alive.
He's trying to keep
Elizabeth's name in the press.
There are, however,
reasons to believe Ricci
was not the person
in the house that night.
Mary Katherine
described a man
about her brother's height,
which is 5'8".
Ricci was over six feet.
She said
the man was familiar
but not someone
she knew well.
Richard Ricci
was in our home for months.
She would've known him.
Mary Katherine
has come forward
with this man.
He calls himself Emmanuel.
Our number-one suspect
is still Richard Ricci,
and we continue to believe
that he is the one
who took Elizabeth.
We are not saying
he's a suspect.
He's just someone
we'd like to speak to.
Richard Ricci
may have been involved
in Elizabeth's kidnapping,
but I don't believe
he's the one who took her.
[Woman]
So where are you guys from?
[Emmanuel] We're from heaven.
We were sent here by God
to do His work.
There you go.
Thanks.
Do you have a bag?
Yeah.
[glass shatters]
Hey.
Hmm?
What are you doing here?
What's your name?
Michael Jensen.
Come on.
Get up, please.
Come on. Let's go.
[camera shutter clicks]
Relax your hand, please.
Turn to the right.
[camera shutter clicks]
It's been days.
Where is he?
He would never abandon us.
We will die without him.
He's watching us.
He wants to make sure
of our devotion to him.
It's a test.
Oh, we are worthy of his love.
We are worthy of his love.
We haven't eaten in days.
I'm starving.
Stop being so selfish.
We are worthy of his love.
We are worthy of...
Say it!
We are worthy of his love.
We are worthy
of your love!
That evening in the church,
Your Honor,
was the worst night
of my life.
I got drunk for the first time
in, what, 22 years?
This last week,
however, in jail
has been for me like Jonah
getting swallowed
by the whale.
It's turned me right around.
I know what I need to do,
what the Lord wants me to do
with my life.
And I'm...
[sighs]
I am terribly sorry.
Nothing like this
is ever going
to happen again.
Last week, we showed you
a sketch of a man
that might have taken
Elizabeth Smart.
Thanks to one of
our viewers calling in,
we've been able
to identify him.
His name
is Brian David Mitchell.
He calls himself Emmanuel
for religious reasons.
He is believed
to be traveling with his wife,
Wanda Barzee.
Cops stress
he is not a suspect.
They just wanna question him
in Elizabeth's disappearance.
[doorbell rings]
Yes?
Mr. Smart?
Yes.
My name is Stacey McGinty.
I'm a relative
of Brian Mitchell's.
Ah. Uh, please,
uh, come in.
No, thank you.
I can't stay.
I just wanted to come by
and tell you...
I don't know if Brian
is the one who took her or not.
If it his him,
she's still alive.
He doesn't kill them.
He murders their spirit
and takes their soul.
Excuse me.
Could you spare some change?
Ma'am, some change?
God bless you, sir.
Excuse me, sir.
Could you spare some change?
Can you spare some change?
[Man on phone]
911 operator.
What's your emergency?
[Woman]
Yes. Is this where I call if I
think I see that Emmanuel guy?
The guy they're looking for
in connection with the
Elizabeth Smart kidnapping case?
Is he wearing robes?
No, but he's got
a big bushy beard and long hair.
Is he alone?
No, he was with two ladies,
and they're carrying bedrolls.
How long ago did you see them?
I just saw them.
You, can you spare some change?
Sir, could you
spare some change?
Burn in hell.
Excuse me. Would you happen
to have some money for us?
Ma'am, would you happen
to have...
No!
[police radio chatter]
Can you spare some change,
ma'am?
Can you spare some change?
Burn in hell
the lot of you.
Good morning,
Officer.
Good morning.
Mmm. What's your name, sir?
Peter Marshall.
Can I see some ID, sir?
Oh, we're messengers of God.
We're free
of all worldly things.
Simply traveling the earth
spreading God's word.
My wife Juliette,
our daughter Augustine.
[siren wailing]
[car door opens]
[bells tolling]
Transients.
He says his name's
Peter Marshall,
but he doesn't have
any ID.
Augustine, you can't say a word.
You know that.
Let's just relax.
Hmm?
Mr. Marshall.
Can I talk to you
over here for a moment?
Absolutely.
Ma'am, you, too,
if you don't mind.
She'll be fine.
Can I ask your name?
My name is
Augustine Ann Marshall.
I'm traveling with
my mother and father.
We're from Miami,
Florida.
Where in Miami
do you live?
Just Miami.
Do you live
near the water?
Yes.
Why are you wearing a wig?
That's personal.
Can you tell me
your name?
My name is
Augustine Ann Marshall.
I'm traveling with
my mother and father.
Do you have
a place to stay?
We're from Miami,
Florida.
I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you.
Can you tell me
your name now?
My name is
Augustine Ann Marshall,
and we're from Miami,
Florida.
So you don't know
where in Miami you're from?
All I know is I said is that
we're ministers of God,
and we're traveling
to spread His word.
You know, Elizabeth,
there are a lot of people
looking for you
and missing you.
[chattering]
You're safe now.
All you have to do
is tell me you're Elizabeth.
Thou sayeth.
I sayeth.
What's gonna happen
to them?
Will they be okay?
The police just called.
They want me to come down
to the station right away.
Why?
They wouldn't say.
I think they may have found
Brian Mitchell.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[phone ringing]
[beeps]
Hello?
[engine starts]
Yes, it is.
This is Lois.
[car departs]
Uh, no.
You just missed him. He...
Told me what?
No. I... I don't know.
Charles!
Elizabeth?
[gasps]
Is it...
Is it really you?
Yes, Daddy.
Don't get your hopes up, Mom.
We've gone through this before,
and it wasn't her.
I know. I know.
Come on.
Oh...
Oh, my baby.
[crying]
I can't believe
it's really you.
[mutters]
I knew it.
[crying]
[applause, cheering]