Hello, I'm Danielle Steel.
I'm glad you've joined us tonight
for Palamino.
When I wrote Palomino,
I loved the idea of writing
a book about cowboys.
Samantha Taylor is a successful
photographer in New York,
who leaves her sophisticated world
for life on a ranch
and the challenges she meets there.
Her life will take some intriguing turns.
I hope you enjoy our story tonight.
Thank you for being with us.
That's it, okay...
keep looking, that's good...
Good!
Fabulous!
A little more, a little more, that's it.
Go down a little bit.
Good, good.
Good. I like it, I like it.
You'll drive the girls nuts. Uh-huh.
Great.
Great, right there, uh-huh.
Just like if you can't get any better,
you go on something like this.
If you ever change anything,
you're dead.
- You know it's 6 o'clock, right?
- Already?
Mm, do you mind?
Of course not.
- This is Warren Taylor. - And
Liz Corey and this is the evening news.
Among tonight's top stories,
are the Geneva Peace Summit.
On the domestic scene: New evidence
presented at a senate investigation,
indicates that the cost
to S&L bailout,
will be even higher
than previously thought.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
You're home early.
The dinner with the network brass
got cancelled.
I'm beat. You mind if we eat out tonight?
I could just call Marty and Jim...
Sam, don't. I don't want to
have dinner with friends...
I want us to talk.
Okay.
What is it? You look so serious.
I don't know how to say this...
I don't even know where to begin.
Say what?
I want out of this marriage.
I didn't mean for it
to happen this way.
I don't even know
how it started, it just...
Is there someone else?
Who is she? Do I know her?
It's Liz.
Oh... god.
How could you... do that?
Look, I tried to break it off,
several times, but
I can't.
Do you love her?
Answer me!
Yes.
How long has this been going on?
Almost a year now.
Look, I'm sorry, I know I should've
told you about this a long time ago...
Don't touch me!
I don't want to hurt you, Sam.
That's what makes it so hard.
It's because I can't have a baby,
isn't it?
That has nothing to do with this.
Wh... what are you doing?
You don't have to leave tonight...
I have to decide what I'm gonna do.
I can't do that here.
Well, no-one ever
works out anything apart.
Oh, you're leaving because
you're going to her.
You've already made the decision,
haven't you?
You know things have not been right
between us for some time!
Don't tell me what I know!
Because I'll tell you what I thought.
I thought you were faithful to me. I
thought that our marriage mattered to you.
I thought if I had a problem
because I couldn't have kids,
we would overcome it.
I thought...
you loved me.
SEVERAL MONTHS LATER
Romance of the century.
Please join us tomorrow for part 2
on our continuing series
on mothers in the workplace.
And before we close, we would like
to make a formal announcement
of what may have been apparent
to most of you for some time now:
Liz and I are expecting
our first child in a few months.
Hopefully not with
on-the-air coverage.
Liz will be working with our news team
until the very end of her pregnancy.
Only if I can fit behind this desk.
- From all of us
- Goodnight.
- Yeah, who is it?
- It's me. You okay?
- Did you see the news?
- Hm.
Sorry.
I- I didn't know what to bring you.
You know what, a punching bag?
A case of Tequila? Or a big cheesecake?
- Oh, watch out for this glass. - What
happened here, huh? Or shouldn't I ask?
Does he think I'm a fool,
Charlie?
Didn't he think I'd be able to figure out
she was pregnant when he left me?
Why couldn't he have been honest,
why couldn't he have told me himself?
Because he's a coward, right?
Among other things.
I can't stop thinking about him. I can't
even stop watching that damn news show.
Well, don't do that to yourself,
that's just dumb.
You know Sam, you've got to get out
of here. You've got to get on with it.
How am I supposed
to do that, huh?
I'm supposed to pretend the last
7 years of my life didn't matter?
Of course they matter.
What you got to do is you got to focus,
on your work, on your and friends,
on the things
that make you happy.
This announcement that they made, it's
gonna generate a lot of interest, okay?
So I was thinking that, uh...
maybe it's not such a bad idea
to get out of town for a few weeks...
Ohh, what? And do what? Go lie on
a beach in Florida somewhere?
Oh, no, no, that's not my style.
Sam, Life Magazine...
Right?
Life Magazine is doing a photo
layout on the American cowboy.
Now they're talking about
using a freelancer.
Are you interested?
Mm...
- When do they want it?
- Immediately.
Hm.
- Have they chosen a location?
- No.
They're leaving that
up to the photographer.
Mm.
You remember my telling you about
my friend, Barbara Lord, from college?
Yeah. The one that
died in a plane crash.
Her mother, Caroline Lord,
still owns one of the most
successful ranches in California.
You think she'd
let you shoot there?
I bet she would.
Wow, hard to believe
we're only 4 hours from L.A.
Feels more like half a century,
don't it?
Yeah, it's true.
You know, Miss Caroline,
she just can't wait to see you.
You know,
of all her daughter's friends,
you were the favourite.
Well, I've missed her.
- Does she still have her Arabians?
- Oh, sure...
Morgans, quarter horses,
we just got 4 new thoroughbreds.
You know, most of the ranchers around
here are content with just their cattle,
not miss Caroline.
She's about the best horse woman
I ever saw.
No, wait, I do recall, you
weren't so chatty yourself, then.
Oh, I've always admired the way
Caroline was able to change.
Turn her life around.
How many people can do that?
I never knew her
when she lived in L.A. but
it's not hard to imagine her married
to a film director and giving parties
and going to screenings...
you know,
it's a world away
from running a ranch.
- I'll cool him down for you, ma'am.
- Give him a good rub down, Josh.
Oh, I've had some wonderful times here.
Samantha!
Oh... Samantha!
I'm so glad to see you again.
Welcome home.
You look wonderful.
Why is it I'm the only one
who ever seems to get any older?
Oh, you look the same to me
as you did when you were...
18 years old, riding quarter horses.
Well, he's a beautiful animal.
His name is "My Solitaire".
I like the look of an Arabian but
I love to ride a thoroughbred.
Of course, uh, it's a little crazy
at my age to buy something like that
oh, a final extravagance
but what the hell, I had to do it!
Come on, let's get you
out of those city clothes.
Well, you all set, Sam?
- Will you be needing anything else?
- No, thanks Bill, we'll be fine.
Then I'll see you two ladies
in the morning.
Bill's been your foreman now
for what, uh... 20 years?
24.
Oh.
Not much has changed since you left.
Well, good. I'd be
terribly disappointed if it had.
There's not much more to say
than what I said the other night.
The divorce was so awful.
So... public.
- Have you been out with anyone
since the break-up?  - No.
Why not?
I'm... not ready.
I don't think I ever will be.
I felt the same way
after my husband died.
But Sam, your life isn't over.
In some ways it's just begun.
We'd better get some sleep.
You have a big day tomorrow and
Bill has made all the arrangements,
the men are expecting you and they
ride out of here at the crack of dawn.
Thanks for everything,
Caroline, really.
I'm so glad you're here.
...the horse comes over
and he grabs his halter...
You must be Miss Lord's friend
from New York.
Yeah.
That's right. Samantha Taylor.
But everybody calls me Sam.
Tate Jordan, Assistant Foreman.
I appreciate you
letting me ride with you today.
Whatever Miss Lord's wants
is fine with me.
But I guess she didn't tell you how soon
we get started in the morning around here.
Only gonna have time
for about half that cup of coffee.
Half a cup's all I need.
What exactly is it
you're looking for out here?
I just want to watch you work,
take a few pictures, that's it.
Well, today we're gonna be around
enough cows for the winter feed.
Sounds fine.
I don't know what's so interesting about
watching a bunch of cowboys get dirty.
Well, maybe not to someone
who works on a ranch, but, uh...
to the rest of the country
who's still in love
with the idea of the cowboy
riding the range, you know?
How long's it been
since you've ridden?
A while.
But don't worry.
I can ride.
Yeah.
Josh, why don't you saddle up
the Lady for Miss Taylor?
- How are you holding up?
- Oh, I'm just fine.
but you know, you might consider
renaming this horse
"Grandma" might be more appropriate.
I could've handled an animal
with a little more spirit.
Let's go.
Well now, if it ain't your
great American cowboy.
That's enough out of you, Josh.
It's a shame to break in a brand new pair
of boots in a field full of cow paddies.
Why don't you all take a break.
We're gonna give, uh, Miss Taylor
a minute here to clean up her new boots.
Hey.
I don't care whether
you like me or not.
If you have a problem with my being here,
then we really need to talk about it.
The only problem I have is with that
steer and he's back in the corral.
Look, I really need your
cooperation here, OK?
Lady, I intend to cooperate.
Here you go, Sam.
What's his problem anyway?
Oh,  he just ain't used to
working around women.
Mm.
Come on. Come on!
Hi, Mrs Taylor.
How did it go today?
- Mm. Honestly?
- Hm-mm.
I can barely move.
How did the men treat you?
Oh, about as well
as could be expected.
Mm.
The magazine sent me
in search of images of the, uh,
old cowboy in the new west.
I think they thought
he would be hard to find.
You didn't have to look very far,
did you?
Oh, no. The spirit of John Wayne
is alive and well.
The men of this ranch they're hard working,
hard riding, down-to-the-core cowboys.
But they keep to themselves,
they're hard to predict.
Even Bill. I never know quite
what he'll do next.
But over the years I've learned
that it's much simpler just to
accept things the way they are.
You are gonna be
in agony tomorrow.
Oh, no I'm not. I'm gonna be
back on that damn horse.
Hopefully a better horse.
Oh, listen, why don't you take a break
from your work and ride My Solitaire
in the morning?
- Yeah, you mean it?
- I think you've earned it.
Tate, do you mind if I start one more
roll of film before I call it a day?
Yes ma'am, we would.
It's one thing for you to ride with us,
but this is private.
Even the other men's wives
don't come in here in the evenings.
Sorry.
Sam, I think you'll find My Solitaire
a far cry from Lady.
Thanks, Josh.
You have a good ride.
Oh, good morning.
Do you always ride like that?
Sometimes.
Just to show off,
or you like taking chances?
Well, I don't think that's
really any of your business.
Well, you made it my business.
Now you like it or not,
I'm responsible for you.
You don't know that horse well enough to
pull that kinda stunt you did over there.
You could've hurt yourself,
crippled this horse.
Yeah, well, I appreciate your concern
but Caroline would never hold you
responsible for what I do on horse,
she knows me too well.
Maybe she's never seen you
ride like that.
OK.
Look, I'm not saying
what I did was right,
making that jump
made me feel alive again.
I don't care what you
were doin' out there,
nothing's worth risking your life,
or this horse's.
Now, if you don't mind, I would like
to escort you back to the ranch.
Mm, thanks very much,
but I prefer to ride alone.
And I would prefer that you
get back to the house in one piece.
What is it with you anyway?
Don't you think I ride well enough
to handle this horse?
It takes more than being good
to handle a thoroughbred.
Takes caution and strength.
Right now I'm not sure
you're long on either of them.
Shall we?
Come on, kids.
Ah, now we're talkin'.
Excuse me, my lady.
It's been wonderful to have my dear friend
Samantha here for the past few weeks.
And as I look across to see,
I am indeed very, very thankful
to each and every one of you
here at my table.
- Happy Thanksgiving.
- Hear, hear.
Wait, wait a second...
Here's to all them fat cattle,
and all them long-stepping horses -
and a day off from both of them.
Yeah!
- You know, Sam...
- Mm-hm.
that long blonde mane of yours
you kind of remind me of a palomino.
Oh, Bill,you keep that up and I'll have to
add my name to your dance card tonight.
Wait a minute now,
if that's how you get a dance around here,
I got a real nice compliment for you Sam.
Tate here says that you ride better
than half of the hands on this ranch.
Coming from him, that's high praise.
Oh, you said that, hm?
Not exactly in those words.
♪  ♪
You look at her...
looking up up at that old old cowboy
like he was Tom Selleck.
Yeah, Bill's very popular. I'll
have to wait all night for my dance.
Where's your family tonight?
Well, my boy is 18...
he's working on a ranch in Arizona.
What about your wife?
Ex-wife.
She's in Washington state somewhere.
What about your family?
My mother passed away a few years ago,
my father when I was very young.
I don't really have any family left.
Uh, excuse me...
I need to get some more film.
I don't want to miss... the sunset.
What's he doing out there?
Watching the herd.
The coyotes have been coming down
out of the hills since the drought.
You guys spend a lot of time
alone out there, don't you?
Do you ever get lonely?
There's a difference between
being "alone" and being "lonely".
Anybody who does this kind of work's
gotta be comfortable with his own company.
Want to look?
Huh!
When we first met, you, uh...
really hated me, didn't you?
I did.
What made you change your mind?
The way I acted had
more to do with me than to you.
How so?
Let's just say I'm superstitious
about cameras.
What do you mean?
Some people don't like
having their picture taken.
Well, I hate having mine taken.
But I don't think that's it.
Maybe I was, uh...
afraid of what you'd see.
Ooh, well, you make it sound
very mystical.
You afraid I'd capture your soul?
My soul wasn't what I was worried about.
I should, um...
check on the horses.
And I guess I should...
get back to the party.
See you later.
Sam...
whatcha doing on Sunday?
I thought I might take the horse
out to the North Pasture.
It's a nice ride.
If you follow the ridge.
I'll keep it in mind.
Come in.
Happy Thanksgiving, honey.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Mornin'.
Hi.
Are you gonna be staying on
much longer?
Uh, I don't know.
I'm not that anxious to get back.
Why is that?
It's a long story.
I got all day.
I just got divorced.
My husband...
left me for another woman.
I know how that feels.
My ex-wife left me
almost 18 years ago.
Took my little boy
and ran off with some fella
that worked on the oil rig in the gulf.
Still think about her
every now and then.
Nobody bothers to
look at the sky in New York.
Even if they could find it.
You don't miss the city?
Well, see the thing about New York
is that it's addictive.
Once you break the habit
you're alright. But...
when you're hooked, look out.
It sounds like a couple of
women I've known.
Hm.
Like your ex-wife?
Yeah.
That's in the past.
I don't want to talk about her.
Remember the other day when
Bill said you look like a palomino?
He was right.
You have got the prettiest hair
I've ever seen.
It's, uh...
gettin' late.
Do you want some coffee?
You say that like you know a place
right around the corner.
Well, I do.
Whose is this?
Take a look.
"William B. King.
1949 Rodeo."
Is it Bill's cabin?
Should we be here?
Ever since I found the place,
I can't stay away from it.
Yes, I can see why.
I'm making some coffee.
Look at these these photos!
- It's theirs, isn't it?
- I think so.
- Does anyone else know?
- About them?
I'm not sure. They've
been awful careful.
Yet, Barbara and I used to
talk about it for hours.
convincing ourselves there was something
going on between the 2 of them
and then talking ourselves out of it
again. But we were never certain.
I wonder...
why they kept it a secret for so long?
Why they haven't gotten married?
Well, this isn't New York.
So?
I mean, lady ranchers don't take up
housekeeping with their foreman.
Why not?
It'd be beneath her
to marry Bill.
Oh, come on,
how can you say that?
Bill has got an 8th grade education
and about $1.22 to his name.
I don't think that matters
to Caroline.
Well, it matters to Bill.
Will you take a look at this.
Real records.
Don't see many of these anymore.
It looks Italian.
Opera. It must be hers.
Bob Wills and The Texas Playboys.
Oh, definitely Bills.
I kinda like this one myself.
♪  ♪
You know, I wanted to ask you
to dance the other night.
But I was afraid that you'd say no.
You were wrong.
Do you know how much I want you?
That isn't enough.
Well, I...
I understand, but...
I...
don't offer anything
more than that anymore.
Why is that?
I don't have... any more to give.
When was the last time you tried?
What do you want?
A perfect romance?
A wedding ring on your finger
before you go to bed?
What do you want, cowboy?
A quick roll in the hay?
I'm sorry...
I like you a lot.
I just don't want to get hurt again.
I can't promise you that.
Nobody can.
What I want is something real.
I want what they have.
Do you think they were so sure
of themselves in the beginning?
Hell, no. She was a rancher and he
was a ranch hand, that's all they knew.
No. But they also knew
they were in love.
Well, I wish I could give you the
kind of guarantees you're looking for.
I've talked it over with Caroline, Charlie,
I've decided to stay a little while longer.
Mm, tell him I've got a conflict.
Oh, uh, Charlie, I gotta go.
Listen, have some fun,
relax a little bit.
Oh, and don't forget
to water my plants.
I'll talk to you later in the week.
Josh told me that Caroline drove
down to L.A. for the night and
I just want to make sure you're alright.
Would you like to come down
and have dinner at the hall?
Oh, well, I thought women
weren't allowed in the hall.
Yeah well, sometimes-sometimes
you got to make an exception.
Well, I wouldn't want to compromise you,
get you in trouble with the other hands.
How about you stay and
have dinner here with me, instead?
Caroline has left more
than enough food for 2 people.
Are you sure that's alright?
Oh, um, yeah,
I'm sure she wouldn't mind.
Come on in.
[INAUDIBLE]
Well, you've seen one duck,
you've seen them all.
There's something I wanted
to ask you all night long.
Go ahead.
Who's Charlie?
Is he your boyfriend?
He's my agent.
Um...
I haven't been out with anyone
since my husband.
You know, if it wasn't so dark out
we could ride out to the cabin.
I better start cleaning the kitchen up.
Sam.
I never thought I'd say this
to anyone again.
I love you.
Well, uh...
are you're just saying that
because I told you that
making love wasn't enough for me?
I said it because I mean it.
I've been thinking about you a lot
the last couple of days.
And what you want hasn't been
any different than what I feel.
Just that you... well, you want me
to put words to my feelings and
I'm not used to doing that.
It's easier for me to say that I...
I want to make love to you
than it is to say I love you.
But Sam,
I've never met a woman that I've
wanted as much as I want you.
Morning.
Oh. Was that Charlie on the phone?
Yes. He's calmed down considerably since
he spoke with the senior editor at Life.
We got the cover.
Congratulations.
This is the shot they're using.
Whoo.
There is just something...
about a man wearing a Stetson.
Of course, some men
wear hats better than others.
How's about joining me
for some coffee?
Oh, no thanks. I've got a horse
waiting for me at the stables.
Where are you off to this morning?
Another long, lonely ride?
Oh, I'm never lonely
when I'm out there.
Especially not when I'm riding.
I've decided to stay...
a little while longer.
Maybe for Christmas.
Well, that's pretty wonderful news.
You did that for me?
For us.
I don't want to think about leaving
just yet.
Well then, don't.
What we got right now
is what matters.
Well, I was wondering...
do we, um...
have to keep it a secret until then?
Hm?
Well, we better keep
this a secret forever.
Look, no one knows
about us right now.
It's better for you that way
and that's the way I want to keep it.
Oh, well,
I want to be proud
of what we have, not...
be afraid of someone finding out.
Mm.
Well, we don't have to
cross that bridge just yet.
Mm-hm...
But, uh, sooner or later they're
going to have to deal with it.
So are we.
I'm not...
Caroline.
I won't sneak around forever.
No. Eventually, you'll...
be going back to New York.
We better start thinking about
getting out of this tub,
- and getting back to the ranch.
- Oh, no no, no, no.
No.
Not yet.
Mm-mm.
Not right now.
Looks good, huh?
I think she's in love.
Mm.
Who with?
Tate Jordan.
Tate!
You don't have to worry about Tate.
Why is that?
Well, he's not gonna make a move
on Sam. He knows better.
Well, 6 weeks ago I would've said Sam
was too sophisticated for him. But
when is being too... anything...
to stop people from falling in love?
Oh, I don't know, I just know
you worry too much.
Come on over here.
You just come and sit with me.
Mm...
I guess I missed you today.
I thought about you today, too.
- Did you?
- Mm-hm.
Do you realise in the last 5 years
we've only had Sunday breakfast
together about 18 times.
Ain't you got better things to do
than count our Sundays?
I'm tired of you leaving
in the middle of the night.
I want you here every morning.
I want to sit down at the
breakfast table with you and
see you across the table,
looking at me.
Watching me eat post toasties,
ain't all that glamorous, honey.
I'm serious.
Tell you,
you want to ride out to the cabin
next weekend? It's been a long time.
- You want to do that?
- What I want...
is to have breakfast with you
every single morning
for the rest of our lives.
Will you marry me?
I am honoured
to have been asked one more time.
Does that mean you're finally
going to say yes?
It means I just  love you too much
to do that to you.
Well, what should've done
is said just "to the hell with it all "
and gotten married 20 years ago!
Yeah.
Then folks would've been able to say
"well, she married beneath her".
The flamin' guy showed some promise.
What would they say now?
Well, they'd say "she finally
married the love of her life."
They'd say she up and went crazy
and married the ranch foreman.
Oh, for god's sake, Bill!
Nobody cares who you are
or who I am.
They have their own problems.
This ranch
works the way it does because
of who you are and who I am.
And it won't work if we change that.
Hey.
Now I'm gonna take a shower
and then we go to bed.
'Cause I'm tired.
I'm tired too.
I'm tired of hiding.
You know how much I love you.
Now come on.
Let's talk about it some other time.
Hmph.
Come on. Maybe next year.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
So, um, what would really happen,
if Bill and everybody
found out about us?
Doesn't matter.
Hm?
Why?
Because they're not gonna find out.
I won't let that happen to you, Sam.
This is Warren Taylor with the
special edition of late night news.
Do you like that guy?
No, I don't.
Are you sure?
You're watching him pretty close.
I thought he was the kind of guy
that women went crazy about.
I don't know why.
You're much better lookin'.
And a lot more decent,
and caring.
And a lot more understanding,
than he could ever be.
- You make it sound like you know him.
- I do.
He's my ex-husband.
That guy?
You're Warren Taylor's wife?
Ex-wife.
Why didn't you tell me that before?
It didn't seem very important.
Are you sure that's it?
What's the big deal?
I don't even know
your ex-wife's first name.
I tell you this much, she's sure as hell
isn't some damn television celebrity.
Who I was married to
has nothing to do with us.
I'm not so sure about that.
Do you know what felt just now
seeing him?
Nothing.
For the first time in almost a year,
I didn't feel a damn thing.
Not sick or nervousness
or angry or left out. Nothing!
I don't care anymore....
because I'm with you.
And you make me happy.
How can you say that, Sam?
Here you are with a
broken down cowboy,
who couldn't buy you
a cold beer on a hot night.
You're worth a million of him.
Hey...
what if I don't go back to New York?
I could... I could freelance from here.
I can work from anywhere.
Other people do it, I can do it too.
It won't work, Sam.
Well, why not?
Warren Taylor has
nothing to do with us.
Or are you just afraid
of a commitment?
Maybe I should be.
You're a hell of a woman, Sam,
and I love you.
But what have I got to offer you?
Who says you have to
offer me anything?
What are you gonna do? Leave your job,
your friends, your apartment
- and come shovel out a barn with me?
- Don't say it like that.
I love you.
You gonna love me in 5 years, Sam?
See, this has been a little vacation
for you, but
this is my life.
Year after year, it doesn't change.
It's all I got.
Why don't you get dressed
and I'll take you home.
What, back to New York?
Never mind the smart talk.
Just get dressed.
I can't believe you.
I'm through listening to this
old-fashioned garbage!
- I'll walk you home.
- No.
You're wrong about me.
About us.
I love you.
And that should be enough.
Hey baby.
Hey, sweetie.
Uh...
someone gave us a note.
- Did you find out anything?
- No, not really.
After he left me early this morning,
he went into town,
and cashed out all his accounts
and bought a truck.
I checked around
all the other ranches,
and nobody knows anything
about where he has gone.
Hey, Sam.
Sam, I truly am sorry.
I'm just sorry it had to happen.
But you got to understand with a man like
this he decides to up and go he just goes.
Mm, I see... yeah, well...
Thanks for trying, Bill.
Now, Caroline, don't you
look at me like that.
Some things just
ain't meant to be.
Damn you, Bill!
And damn all cowboys along with you!
How could he leave like that?
He loved working on this ranch.
Well, maybe he loved you more.
Maybe that's why he left.
I mean, what kind of life
would you have had with him here?
How can you say that?
What about you and Bill?
Somehow you've made it work.
That is a miracle.
Plain and simple.
But it is far from perfect.
I had finished leading one kind of life,
before I came to the ranch.
I was honestly ready for another.
And I'm old enough to compromise.
Now you don't have to
do that at your age.
Maybe it's time you
thought about going home, Sam.
You've got a whole life
waiting for you back east.
I know.
What about Tate?
What if he changes his mind,
what if he comes back?
Take it from me,
I have been waiting 20 years.
Cowboys do not change their minds.
Thanks for everything.
You really helped me
through a very hard time.
You take care of yourself.
You too.
Let's you and me ride out to the cabin.
When, this weekend?
Right now.
In the middle of the afternoon?
Are you losing your mind?
I'll meet you in an hour.
You're shooting the account
on Thursday, right?
Yeah. The magazine wants something
terribly European-looking and sophisticated.
He, of course, wants to wear
a black leather jacket
and quote unquote "American jeans".
Charlie, I expected things to be
different when I got back. I...
maybe 'cause I felt differently.
Are you alright?
No.
Oh, here they are.
That's Caroline.
This is Bill.
Oh, that's great. Yeah.
Is that him?
Yes.
Hi.
What's the matter, Bill?
Are you alright?
Shall I...
I'll get somebody to help.
No, no, I don't need no help.
I'm alright.
- No, no, I'll get somebody.
- I don't need help.
I ain't gonna die.
Gettin' down off this horse.
Damn!
There, yeah... ooh.
I've called Dr. Cooper,
and he's on his way.
Ahh... Dr. Cooper.
You know...
I'm so sorry, honey.
For what?
Everything I didn't do.
I don't have any regrets.
I've got enough for both of us.
- Don't say that.
- No, honey...
just like you said...
all those Sunday mornings
we missed together.
I wish I could give 'em back to you.
All wrapped up in a fancy package.
All that time we shoulda had together.
You have given me more,
than most people get in a whole
lifetime of Sunday mornings.
I love you, Bill.
Oh God, I love you, too.
Life wants to expand
my cowboy piece into a book.
They want to do
a coffee table edition
of a day in the life of the new American
cowboy. It's gonna be a big shoot.
They're gonna bring in an entire crew
and 3 of the photographers beside myself.
And even Charlie wants to come.
So...
can we shoot at your ranch?
Well, any other time I'd say yes...
- you know I'd love to see you.
- You sound worried.
What's the matter?
Bill... had a mild heart attack.
Oh, no.
Is he OK? Can I do anything?
He had a bypass several years ago
I don't know if they're gonna
do another one or not, and uh,
Well, I'm just afraid
if you shot the book here,
he would want to be all over the place,
trying to make things perfect.
You know how he is.
- Are you alright?
- Yes.
Don't worry about us.
If you like the general look
of this place,
I could call my friend Mike Holly
at the, uh, Courtney Stables.
It's just in the next county.
He'd love to have you.
Oh, well, that would be great.
Thank you.
Listen, if you need anything,
you call me, OK?
I love you.
I love you, too.
Bye-bye.
I can't thank you enough, Mike.
It's been an incredible 3 days.
Just disappointed I didn't  get a chance
to ride one of your horses.
How would you like to ride
my prize stallion?
Oh, I'd love it.
Tate?
Oh, he looked like someone I used to know.
Tate Jordan. He worked on the Lord ranch.
Yeah, I knew Tate.
I heard he went up to Wyoming.
Really?
Do you know where in Wyoming?
No. But I also heard
he went to Arizona. So...
you know how folks are.
They talk about who's around,
make up stories about who's going.
Come on,
let's get you on that horse.
Mike, you seen Sam?
No. Not since she
took my horse for a ride.
My god, that's her horse.
Something's happened, Mike.
Something must be wrong.
Wait. I see something.
Sam!
Sam...
She's alive.
You stay with her, I'm going
back to the ranch for help.
Just get somebody here
as fast as you can, alright?
Send in a helicopter if you have to.
Whatever it takes.
Sam.
Sam. You'll be OK.
Sammy?
I'm gonna help you.
Sam. Come on, Sam.
Open that up there.
Hurry up!
Hold that up.
I'm sorry...
Caroline?
- Charlie?
- Yeah.
Thanks for coming.
She's, uh... she's still in surgery.
She's in recovery...
it's a very complicated procedure...
Caroline, this is, uh, Dr. Field.
How is she?
Well, she made it through the surgery.
I was able to stop the internal bleeding
and, uh, remove the bone fragments and
now we just have to wait and see.
Well... how long
until we know something?
If she makes it through 'til tomorrow,
we'll have much better options.
And if she does then...
she'll be OK.
Right now,
she's very lucky to be alive.
She has a contusion of the spinal cord
which left her partially paralysed.
It's unlikely she'll ever regain
full use of her legs.
Oh...
There's a lot
we have to talk about, but
first let's just get her
through the night.
That night turned into several more.
I'm not sure how many.
But you remember, Charlie.
You were there
for everyone of them.
Now my days are measured
in small increments.
How many times I can lift.
Going to the bathroom by myself.
Re-learning...
re-thinking my whole life.
Oh, they never leave me alone,
you know?
Sometimes I think they're afraid
of what'll happen...
if they give me time to think.
Caroline, who's as wonderful as always,
tries to keep my spirits up.
She says that I have to
reclaim my independence.
But I don't know how to do that,
Charlie.
Because what I want is to be
the way I was before the accident.
My body doesn't feel like
it belongs to me anymore.
The only time I feel like myself, is
when I dream.
Because when I'm dreaming,
I'm not being poked and prodded, and...
and I'm not surrounded
by well-meaning strangers.
And I'm not in a wheelchair.
Watch your hip.
Use your weight to
bring your legs forward. Come on.
That's it.
Try to lift forward.
Good. Come on.
Let's try it again.
I don't want to.
I know just how you feel.
It's, uh, pretty impressive hardware
you got there, though.
It makes me look like Shredder.
You know he is? The Ninja Turtle bad guy?
He wore stuff on his legs, too.
Oh, I see.
Well, uh, what's your name?
I can't call you Shredder.
Timmy.
Let's try it again, Timmy.
OK?
OK.
Come on.
Tuck your hip.
Good.
Now move your weight. There you go.
And again.
Good.
Thank you, Sam. No one's ever
bought me colouring books before.
Oh, you're welcome.
Does anyone ever
come see you here?
Yes. My friend Caroline,
she comes once a week.
And my best friend he would come
but he lives in New York.
My mother would see me too,
but she can't...
she's in jail.
Oh.
She got 30 days.
OK, ready?
Here we go. Up.
Good, hold it.
Lock this in.
Alright, go.
Good.
OK.
Place your hips.
Not like that.
That's it!
That's it.
Alright, bring the chair.
- Good, good. Got it? Got it?
- Yeah.
- Right?
Down we go.
Got it?
Good.
Good work.
OK, just tell me it's gonna to get easier.
But it's not, is it?
Sam?
Caroline?
What am I gonna do?
My god, Sam, it's over.
Bill died last night.
I'm so sorry.
Is there anything I can do?
There's nothing anyone can do.
All my family gone
and now Bill. I...
I just feel like there's no one left,
and there's nothing to care about.
No, that's not true,
you still have the ranch.
And me.
And lots of people
who care about you.
Try to remember that.
You're too young, Sam. It's...
too hard for you to understand.
But thank you.
Goodbye, Sam.
Please don't cry.
Sometimes my mum just
cries and cries and cries.
Then I hold her.
Sam.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
The day I took this, was one of
the last times I was on a horse.
I don't know if I'll ever ride again.
You also said you'd
never fall in love again.
Bill was so straight in the saddle.
I could pick him out
of 20 men at 2 miles.
Well, I think I'll just put this aside,
I can't concentrate.
Why don't we just go outside.
It'll do us both some good.
Oh, you go on...
What about Josh?
I know he needs talk to you.
Maybe tomorrow.
The ranch just doesn't
mean anything without Bill here.
I'm sorry, Sam, it's how I feel.
A lot of people have relationships,
get married.
I don't know many who could honestly say
they had a love affair for over 20 years.
We did have that.
You're so sweet to come, Sam, but...
what I need now is time alone.
- Thanks, Josh. I'll be OK from here.
- You sure?
Yeah, it's fine. Thanks again.
- You're welcome. Call if you
need anything.  - I will.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye
Hi, Timmy.
Where are you goin'?
I'm leaving.
Timmy's mother
was released yesterday.
Well, I stopped back on the
way from the ranch and, uh,
bought you something.
Wow, Ninja Turtles!
There's a little spending money inside.
Listen, I, um...
I'm gonna give you my friend Charlie's
phone number. OK?
I'm gonna be going home
in a few weeks too, and...
Charlie always knows
where to find me.
So...
if you need me... for anything...
anything...
- you just call, OK?
- OK.
I have something for you too.
I made it all by myself.
Is this me?
This is you?
This is the way I, uh...
see myself when I'm dreaming.
It is?
Yeah.
How did you know that?
Sam...
Yeah.
will you dream about me?
Every night.
I'm gonna miss you,
so much.
We have to leave now, Timmy.
Goodbye, Sam.
Take care of yourself, OK?
I love you, Sam.
I love you too.
A FEW MONTHS LATER
Samantha Taylor.
Sam, it's Josh.
I hope you don't mind me calling
but I thought you'd want to know.
What is it, Josh, what?
What's the matter?
Miss Caroline's real sick.
Oh, no.
Bill loved to sit out here
in the late afternoon.
Are you sure you're strong enough?
Maybe it was a stupid idea
to have Josh carry you out.
No, I want to see all this again.
I can't see so that much
from my bedroom window.
We don't have to
tell each other goodbye.
Or how much
we meant to each other.
I love you, Caroline.
You've been like a daughter to me.
And I want you to have the ranch,
after I die.
But I don't want you to think of it...
as an obligation, it's a gift.
You don't have to keep it.
This ranch has given me
great pleasure.
But I don't want it preserved
as some sort of
homage to the past.
Promise me, Sam.
I promise.
I can't believe she's gone.
I'm real sorry.
Losing Miss Caroline must be like...
like losing your own mother.
No, it's different.
Caroline and I never fought.
Have you decided what you're gonna do
with the place? Are you gonna sell it?
I don't know.
It doesn't really
seem important anymore.
'Cause what I really want,
I can't have.
Come on, there's something
I think you should see.
Keep 'em shut.
OK.
Caroline had me make it up for you.
She believed you'd want to ride again.
Well...
let's give it a try.
Saddle him up.
Now hold on. Are you sure you
want to start with that horse?
He ain't been ridden for a while.
I don't want another horse.
I know this horse.
Isn't that right buddy?
We're old friends, aren't we?
Yeah.
OK.
Are you OK?
I hate to admit it...
even to you.
I'm a little afraid.
Let me take the reins.
Here we go. Nice and easy, boy.
Come on.
Nice and easy.
How are you doin'?
I feel like a baby.
Oh, you gotta learn to walk
before you can trot.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Alright, let me have 'em.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Don't worry,
I'll be right over here.
OK, buddy.
That's it.
Easy does it.
Nice boy.
Faster?
Faster, huh?
Yeah, let it loose a little bit.
You're doing good. You look great.
Good. Good.
Good! Good!
Come on boy, come on.
That's it.
Hey, look at me Josh, I'm runnin'.
You know, until now...
I didn't know what I wanted
to do with this ranch but...
I think I just figured it out.
I may be out of my mind but
can't you see this place
full of children?
Children?
Yeah. What I want to do...
is turn this ranch into a camp.
For kids.
Kids with special needs, like me.
Josh, you can teach anybody
how to ride.
Would you stay on? Be my foreman?
Yes, ma'am, I'd like that.
I've come home, Josh.
Now I know.
This is where I belong.
Dear Charlie,
although the Caroline Lord Ranch
For Children has only been open
for a few months,
I have twice as many applicants
as I have places available.
So I've sold off another 5,000 ares to
pay for renovations and 2 more buildings.
By next summer I hope we
won't have to turn anyone away.
I feel confident on horseback now.
I still use the leg straps
but the first saddle Josh made for me is now
one of a dozen we use to teach the kids.
I can remember a time when
only perfection seemed normal.
A time when I wouldn't have known
how to handle any of the problems
that are now part of an ordinary day:
Children who won't cooperate.
Artificial limbs that don't fit.
Wheelchairs that get stuck
and braces that break.
The mechanics of it all
strike me as extraordinary. But...
most extraordinary of all of it
is that it's become
a way of life.
As long as I can remember, Charlie,
I've longed for children.
And now I never have less than 20.
Come see me soon.
Love, Sam.
We have to find a place for you
to stay for a while.
Do you have a grandmother?
Or an aunt?
No.
How about your dad?
Is there somebody
we could call?
OK.
Look, maybe I can find a foster home
for you to stay in tonight.
We'll see what we can do.
And there's not just the cou...
Wait!
I got this.
OK.
Now that phase one is totally complete,
that we move back to the...
thank you -
north pasture,
- making them access...
- Sam!
Hey...
Hey, Timmy...
Oh...
look at you...
come here.
You come here.
I missed you.
There you go.
OK, Timmy, you hang on now.
- OK.
- Hang on tight right there.
Just hold on tight.
OK. How you doin'? You feel OK?
- You want to go faster?
- Yeah.
- Oh, will you look at him, Josh.
- Sure ain't afraid, is he?
Oh, no. He's a natural
on a horse, huh?
In a month he's
gonna be ridin' home.
♪ On top of old smokey ♪
♪ all covered with snow ♪
♪ I lost my true lover ♪
- He's sound asleep.
♪ ...by courtin' too slow... ♪
He had a big day.
How long is he gonna be with us?
As long as he wants to.
His mother died of a
drug overdose, and, uh,
none of the relatives were willing
or able to take him in.
Sounds like a hard life
for a little kid.
But I say now that
he's got you in his corner,
his life's gonna be changing.
- Let's hope so.
♪ On top of old smokey ♪
♪ all covered with snow... ♪
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You two guys, uh,
go on up ahead,
I've got to go back to the ranch,
I have some work to do.
OK. Come on, kid.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's goin' on? I thought you two
were gonna meet me at the stable.
- We took a little extra ride.
- Josh.
Well, I'll be doggoned.
Good to see you, Tate.
What brings you this way?
I was up in Santa Barbara
for the Vacaro show
when I heard about Bill and Caroline.
They're gonna be missed.
Yep.
Are you two ready to call it a day?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Let me give you a hand.
You have to unstrap my legs first.
What's going on here, Josh?
Why, things have changed
since you went away, Tate.
What's he doing here?
He came by to pay his respects.
He wants to see you.
- Did you tell him what happened to me?
- No.
We just talked about
the ranch, that's all.
Go outside and-and
tell him I'm gone
and-and you don't know
when I'll be back.
Go on, Josh, just do it.
You know, this isn't like you.
Don't you think at the very least you
owe him a couple of minutes of your time?
I don't owe him anything!
He left me!
Well then,
maybe you owe it to yourself.
Go outside and give him a horse,
so he can ride over to the graves
to pay his respects.
And tell him I'm...
I'll be gone until tomorrow.
OK.
But if you should change your mind...
Just do it, Josh!
Please?
Hey, Timmy.
You were kinda quiet at dinner tonight.
Anything bothering you?
Heather's leaving on Wednesday.
- She told me so.
- Oh...
Yeah, it's always sad when
somebody has to leave us.
I know you'll miss her.
When will I have to leave?
Timmy...
you never have to leave.
This is your home.
But... what if that social worker
comes and takes me away?
Uh...
What if we made it so that
no one could ever do that?
How?
Well...
if I adopted you...
then we'd belong
with each other.
Does that mean I can
stay here at the ranch forever?
Yeah.
Sam.
What?
I want to belong with you.
Oh... I want to belong with you, too.
Mm.
Oh, a big hug.
- Good morning, Josh.
- Good morning, Sam.
- Beautiful morning, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Would you mind keeping an eye on Timmy
for me for a couple of hours? - No problem.
I'm gonna take ride
out to the cabin.
Sooner or later I'll have to go out there and
go through it and pack things away but...
kind of want to see it one last time,
the way it was.
Thanks.
Come on.
Hello, Tate.
Josh told me you come out here.
I had to see you
before I took off for Montana.
Yeah, well, I uh...
I have to get back to the ranch
because I've been gone
too long already. Come on.
Sam, wait.
It's quite a place
you put together here.
What made you do it?
I never figured that
you'd leave New York.
I came back after Caroline died.
I still miss her.
Look, do you wanna get down
and talk a minute?
No.
I don't mean go into the cabin.
I wouldn't do that.
There's a lot I never said, Sam.
You don't have to say anything.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Maybe not to you.
But it does to me.
I want you to know one thing, Sam.
I was wrong.
What do you mean?
It was the biggest mistake of my life,
when I walked out on you.
I even had a falling out
with my son about it.
He said I always run away
from the important things,
the things that mattered.
I helped him buy
a little place in Montana
and stayed on to help him
get it goin' but...
to prove to him
he was wrong about me.
What I learned is that it doesn't
mean a damn if you are a rancher,
or a ranch hand
or a man or a woman.
If you live right,
and you love well and do good,
that's all that matters.
It's about the longest speech
I've ever made.
You know, you never were one
to bore me with conversation.
Do you remember the first time
we came out here?
Yeah. It was a long time ago.
- Come on, let's go for a walk.
- No, I have to get back...
If I don't do this now, I may
never get another chance...
- I told you I have to go now.
- Why?
- Because I have to.
- Look, why don't you just...
- Because it's too late.
- Sam, wait!
You're like the little girl
in the wheelchair, aren't you?
The one you taught to ride.
Sam, why didn't you tell me?
I don't want your pity.
I was wrong
to think that my being a ranch hand
would make a difference to you.
And you were wrong
if you think that
not being able to walk is
gonna make a difference to me.
No.
There are some things
that do make a difference.
Not to me.
Tell me how it happened.
It happened.
OK?
I can live with it.
But I can't force it on someone else.
Is there someone else?
- I mean if there is, I'll go away.
- No, there's no one else!
I don't want
or expect anything more
than what I have right now.
I belong...
on this ranch.
I feel...
like a part of this land...
and the kids, and...
and I have one little boy
that I'm going to adopt. I...
What about love?
What about it?
I remember once when you
wouldn't let me give up on it.
Things were different then.
They don't have to be.
Sam, you talk about...
bein' a part of this land.
I'll tell you something,
my whole life I've knocked around
from one ranch to another.
The only time I ever felt like
I really belonged somewhere
was when I was with you.
I'll always love you, Sam.
I love you, too.
Welcome home.
Thank you for being with us tonight,
for Palomino.
I hope to see you again soon
for our next movie.
Good night.