ZOMBIE APOCALYPSE
Translated by: VincentL
Paris, France
June 3
First infection of VM2 Virus appears
June 9
83% of the European Population is infected
June 14
VM2 spreads to Japan
Government collapses within 3 days
June 23
VM2 appears in Guthrie Center, Iowa
June 25
VM2 spreads unchecked across the U.S.
SURVIVORS
QUARANTINE AREA
RESTRICTED ACCESS
June 26
The army destroys transportation arteries to contain the infected
June 27
EMPS detonated
All electronics disabled
in final effort to isolate plague carriers
SIX MONTHS LATER
- Guys, I think we should've stayed at the cabin
- What, stuck? Besides, we need to find out what's happening.
- I mean, don't you think they would've found a cure by now?
- Well, they are all dead
Hello!!
It was gone man.
Kevin, don't go in there...
- Any food?
- Nothing.
Vending machine!
You're making so much noise.
Dude, just break it !
Guys...
Guys... Guys!!!
Kevin!
Come on! Come on, man!
Kevin, come on!
Stay back! Let's go this way, Kevin!
Come on, get outta here!
Help me! No! Oh God, help me!!!
Ramona, run! Get outta here!
Stay here!
You okay?
Okay. Just hang in there...
He's still alive!
- We gotta go, come on.
- Stay away! - No!!
- He's gonna change, come on!
- He's gonna be alright! Okay, just hang in there...
- Ramona, come here...
- Look, I... I'm sorry about your friend, but here, you can't look at this
- What are you guys going to do? He's still alive.
No!
Don't look! Look away!
- Hey, I'm Henry.
- Are you two hurt?
- Nah.
- Are you bitten? When the zombies got close to you?
- I don't know.
- Do me a favor. Stand up, spread your arms and legs.
- Why?
- Just a standard procedure. Just... do it, please.
Come on, come on!
Spread your arms, spread your arms.
Just doing a bite check, okay?
- You see any bites?
- Not yet...
Lift up your pant legs.
Okay. You're clear.
Nice to meet you.
Haven't met anybody breathing in quite awhile.
- You already meet Henry. This is Julian, Cassie.
- Come on. We gotta get outta here.
- Yeah, we do.
- Our Golden rules: "Forever wandering, lonely as clouds."
Wordsworth.
- So, where you're coming from?
- Kevin's dad had a cabin. We were just waiting there.
Thought we would wait until it's over.
So we came out.
I mean, it's over. Sort of...
Just not...not...not in a good way.
- You should come with us. Come on.
- No! Billy... We gotta do something.
- It's too dangerous.
- No! I've known him since college.
Sorry for your loss.
- Okay? But we need to get out...
- I'm not gonna leave my best friend lying, over there.
- or maybe he'd still be alive if you hadn't been wandering around like idiots.
- LIKE IDIOTS??? YOU KILLED MY BEST FRIEND!!!
He's a zombie. He... He's not your boy, he's not Kevin anymore...
I'm sorry, alright?
I didn't... I didn't mean that.
- So, what's your friend's name?
- Kevin. Kevin Anderson.
- And where's he from?
- Evansville.
Come on... We're not safe here.
We stick around, we're gonna turn into zombies too. Come on.
You want to end up like Kevin?
We gotta go, come on.
- How far to the docks?
- About a day or two.
Look.
What's the deal with the arrow?
- Archers.
- Must be the group ahead of us.
- So theory goes
- Start to see them back in Kansas, we've been seeing them ever since.
- Kansas, is that where you're from?
- No, we just passed through. We're from back east.
- On our way to Catalina.
- The island?
Yeah, the army cleared it.
It's a survivor refuge now.
- Yeah, well, we think.
- We know.
Okay, well look. We don't really know what's going on.
We had this radio, and it died.
And we couldn't get Kevin's truck started.
Must be the EMPs.
It took out all electronics, cars, plane, trains, everything.
- It was supposed to contain the plague here.
- Yeah, well that didn't work out so well.
Oh man...
Cities keep on burning.
And there's nothing to stop it.
You'll get used to it.
Oh wow, look. It's a dog.
Haven't seen a dog in months.
Come here doggie!
Doggie!
- Leave it. We can't take a dog with us.
- Sure we can.
- We can train it... not to bark at the zombies.
- Julian. You know we can't. Let's go.
Damn dog.
Gotta make a stop.
Come on, you're coming with me. You're my buddy.
- Buddy?
- Pee-buddy.
Look, I'm... I'm sorry about before.
It's just that...
if we'd got there sooner, I might've been able to save him.
- You know, it wasn't your fault.
- Well it... happened really quickly.
Yeah, I've always says,
That's why we've never go anywhere alone. Ever.
- Not even to pee, right?
- Tryin' to tell me that, those guys have always been...?
Yep.
- That's awkward.
- Better than a zombie catching you with your pants down.
- Erm... I'm a little shy...
- Ouw... Sorry, my bad. No rush.
Listen up guys. We normally go into town. Who used to be people there are now zombies.
Okay, we need to get you two some equipments. And the rest will be looking for some socks.
So, here's the drill:
We go into town, we do it quickly and quietly.
Follow my lead, okay?
Stop if I stop, go if I go.
Be quiet, most importantly, be very aware.
Look who it is. Check it out.
The truth I do not stretch or shove,
when I state that the dog is full of love.
- Wordsworth?
- No, actually, it's Ogden Nash.
- Wait, are you encouraging this?
No. Look, I drop the granola bar back awhile ago.
He looked... he looked hungry.
Stop it, Julian. It's gonna bark at the first zombie it see and get us all killed. Just get these equipments, move out.
Stay alert, stay quiet and stay on your feet.
You go down, you're not going back up. Not as a human anyway.
- Yeah, well those other ones were easy.
- Yeah, well they were old and slow.
- the fresh one are a lot faster.
- See a runner, scream out.
- What's a runner?
- Top of the zombie food chain. Very fast.
Very dangerous.
- It's a shambler. Looks like a onesy.
- Why don't you just kill it?
Best avoid the slow ones.
Kill them will make a noise and noise attract more undead.
Come on, come on!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa... Wait a minute.
Right there. Perfect.
- I don't know, looks like a lot of hiding places.
- We'll be quick, quiet.
It's us. Silent and deadly.
- Looks clear.
- Alright. Let's go.
- What are they doing?
- Smelling for zombies.
Any humans here?
- Hello?
- Quiet!
Okay, usual teams.
New guys come with us.
- Shouldn't we look for food?
- Why? We got all food in the world, literally.
We need some sturdy boots for you, something to cover your arms and legs.
- Look for something made out of hard plastic.
- And nothing softer. Zombies can chew right through that.
Make sure it's kinda light. Heavier means more sweat.
- Sorry, that was me.
- Got it!
Hey, why don't we take bikes?
It's easier than walking, right?
- Nah, that will make you a target for the runners.
- Yeah, makes it difficult to grab your weapons...
can't really hear them coming. Been there before, not doing that again.
Look at this. Just because it's the end of the world, doesn't mean people can't clean up.
Maybe whoever it was, started, I don't know. Everyone else was dead?
- What are you doing? Isn't that a waste of time?
- Depends on how you spend your time.
- Hey, do you see a woman size 7?
- Definitely not organizing shoes.
- Alright, I'm gonna look at the back to get some...
- Hold on, hold on. We'll go with you.
yeah, yeah, yeah. You, you gotta be careful.
You don't know what kind of putrid and damn mess you will find back there.
The zombies can't even figure out doors.
- Hey, remember that one guy? What was his name?
- Kirkman?
- Kirkman, yeah, yeah. This guy who was with us in this coffee shop once.
so, he was looking for this Star Grow or whatever, right?
And he opens the back door, like 50 zombies waiting.
- Ready?
- So what happened to this Kirkman guy?
- Just what you expect?
- So, what are we looking for again?
- Size 7, like a combat boot.
- Combat boot?
- Or something like that.
- You might be a natural in this.
- Those are 7
- Perfect!
We got company!!
We're going from the back!
Let's go!
- We should use blare.
- Okay, do it.
- Hurry up Julian!
- What's the hold up?
Hurry up now, it's getting ugly!
- That was the last one.
- Why are they leaving?
They are attracted to the sound.
Let's get going, that won't distract them for long.
This is crazy. We lost Kevin, now he's trying to kill us!
- It's okay.
- No, it's not okay. We can go back to Kevin. We can take food, I promise you...
- Ramona, we would never make it there.
- How do we know it's all like this in Catalina?
My husband told me, alright?
Guys, let's talk about it later.
Just find a place that's safe.
- Let's go
- Come on.
- More record-keeping?
- Yep.
- Who do you think is gonna read that?
- Well, on a good day, I think it will be my kids...
which I currently have none by the way.
- and on a bad day?
- figure it would be the guy who finds my body.
- it's awful.
- well, at least, you know, there's somebody left to find my body, right?
We're about 60 miles away from high school. We get up early, should be able to be there by nightfall.
- Highschool?
- Yeah, it's a survivor stronghold right outside of L.A. That's our next stop.
- How do you know it's still there?
- Man, you like to ask a lot of questions, don't you?
- Excuse me if I don't know everything, but I do want to...
- We ran into a group, was headed east.
- Said they stayed there, that there was quite the operation.
- East?
They heard it's a safe zone in South Dakota.
They didn't think Catalina existed.
- Found it.
- What? A civilization.
What is it?
Family dinner
Michigan in the summer. I mean, can you imagine?
I don't wanna go into detail, but the smell?
- And that's the end of that story.
- Yeah, I just ate.
So, weren't you saying you have a husband?
Yeah, Stew. Stewie.
Officially, acting sergeant general Stewart Anderson.
At least, that is two weeks into the crisis.
They were, uh, running low on doctors and he volunteered.
He ran with the government and I stayed to get my brother, Jake.
We were going to get the next flight out to Catalina.
- What happened?
- Let's talk about this another time.
There was no other flight. So I found Jake,
and headed West.
Then I met with Julian a day later.
Yeah, I was stuck behind a soda machine in S-Mart...
- can you imagine that?
- Yeah, I can imagine.
- Mack, I got him all outside of Pittsburgh.
- I don't know how much saving I did.
- I do
- met the big guy in Ohio.
- surrounded by, I kid you not, over a hundred zombies.
- and he's even looking for more.
- You killed my horse.
- I was pissed off. Now you can mess with me, but not my horse.
- We'll buy you some new horse someday.
Alright, enough melancholy. It's time for dessert.
I saved the best for the last.
- Smores!
- Oh, yeah!
- Hi
- That was actually kind of fun.
- It helps.
So, how come nobody would say what happened to Cassie's brother?
It actually happened before I met him.
They were out looking for supplies and they ran into a pack.
- Well, what do you mean? What's a pack?
- Well, it doesn't happen very often,
but sometimes the zombies will get together and they form a pack.
It's kinda like a... herd of cattle.
Kinda following each others lead.
For whatever reason...
- they keyed in on Jake.
- Did they kill him right in front of her?
I hope so, but being honest...
Cass thinks that, she saw it moving as it pulled him away.
She thinks he turned.
I mean, I mean it has to be so terrible just to think that he's out there and he's one of them.
Yeah, that's what it takes.
What about you? Have you left anyone?
Not after the plague, no.
But, uh, couple years before, I lost my wife.
- Cancer
- I'm so sorry.
It's her.
Wow, she's very pretty.
She looks like a wonderful person.
She was.
She made me a promise when she died, that,
I would go on living for both of us.
So... That's what I do.
Don't worry.
We'll get to Catalina.
What is that?
It's not a zombie. It's Julian's dog.
Get outta here. Get outta here!
Guys! Guys!
Get outta here, now!
- What did you do that for?
- Stay back, Julian! The dog's turned.
I didn't know dogs could get the plague.
Neither do we.
What about using flamethrowers?
Okay. So you find a zombie and you hit it with flamethrower.
Now what?
- Now it's dead.
- Now you're being attacked by flaming zombie.
- Burner is what we called it.
- Oh yeah, but eventually...
Severe head trauma remove the needs for eventually.
- What do we make of that?
- Sniper was there.
- Let's check it out.
- Right behind you.
There any humans in here?
- 30 hot shells.
- More zombies like our friend over here.
Let's get outta here.
HUMAN SAFE ZONE
There's a onesy looking passage by date.
Leave it alone, stay under the radar.
Ready? Let's go.
That zombie shots...
- So, where's everyone?
- If we're lucky, barricaded inside.
What if we're unlucky?
- Smells really bad in here...
- Yeah... It was zombies.
Any humans in here?
- Dunno guys, doesn't feel so good here.
- If anyone was here, we would've seen them by now.
- Let's just go this way.
- I want to go back to Kevin's cabin, come on...
- Hello!!
- Just calm down!
- I think we should get outta here.
- They're here.
- You sure?
- Yeah, they're here.
Ssttt...
The last safe house, before Catalina.
They're here.
I dunno, doesn't look so good down there either.
- There's the back door.
- We should go man.
They've been in here?
I know, who would've want to give up ball this luxury?
Look around for any papers, notes, signs. Anything.
Ambush!
They're coming!
To the doors!
Billy!
Guys, help Billy!
Billy! Get back!
Ramona!
Henry! Help me!
Back, back!
- Billy! - Billy!
- Henry! Help me!
Help me!
Help... Help me!!!
- Shut the door!
- Come on!
There was a zombie, so I called it.
Ramona, I'm sorry.
What? Wha... Where's Billy?
I'm sorry, we... we got separated.
What do you mean you got separated?
There is four of you!
- We should've gone back.
- OF course you should've gone back! You just left him?
We've tried Mack, we did. Okay? We did, we tried.
Listen, it could've been much worse, alright?
They are waiting for us inside.
- There's no way... There's no way they're waiting
- Yes, I'm telling you, alright? They're hiding. It was an ambush.
- Waiting for any of us to get out.
- Zombies don't hide, Julian!
Who cares if they were hiding?
Yes, she's right.
We just gotta get outta here.
Let's catch our breath.
I mean, how can a man of your stature not be wheezing?
I don't talk as much as you do.
- You alright?
- I'm kinda numb.
- Dammit!
- What?
- God, I lost my brush!
- We'll get you another brush.
No, Mack, I don't want another brush.
I want my things!
- When we get to Catalina...
- What if we don't??
What if they... What if they're all dead?
What if there's no one there?
Okay? This is... This is crazy man.
We're all going to die getting to Catalina.
- I don't plan on dyin'
- No one ever does, Julian!
- You're just tired...
- Yeah, you're right.
I'm tired of all this.
- What's the matter?
- I'm just tired, Henry...
It's going to be okay.
Do you wanna know why I want to go to Catalina?
One: no zombies.
Two: no zombies.
Three, I wanna, I want to take a shower.
I want a toilet that flushes. I want water...
hot water that comes out of a tap, that you don't put on a pot, boil over a fire. I want the hot water,
the... take a bath. That's right, I wanna take a shower.
together with... the girl.
I don't want too much, just a small house...
a garden.
grow tomatoes.
- I would like to do that again
- Me? I miss my horse.
- Damn, that's gotta be a big horse.
- Yeah...
Let's go to any place but here.
I don't want to die like Billy and Kevin...
Julian, get the map. We're moving out.
- Looks like we're staying west of there.
- We can cut pass these houses.
- Pick it up on the other side?
- Yeah... It's gonna get dark in a few hours.
We should move out. Get as far away from here as we can.
Look at that...
Things could get a lot worse for us.
How far do we have to go?
I dunno, maybe we're going the wrong way.
- you're kidding. We're going the right way.
- hey, do you guys see that smoke up ahead?
- Look.
- Looks like that house might be on fire.
- I see something moving up ahead
- Me too.
- What you make of it?
- I dunno, it looks like human.
Maybe it's the archers.
What do you say, should we help him?
Let's go! Hello!
- Hello!
- Julian, not so fast!
- Let's go.
- We lost a few of ours!
- You'll lose more if you don't come now.
- They're flanking us!
- Cassie! Henry!
- Shut up! You're drawing them to us!
Last chance. We're leaving.
- Where are the others?
- Don't know.
- How many more do you think?
Thanks for coming back for me.
- He's coming! - Keep him busy!
- What? - Distract him.
Over here! Over here!
Henry, watch out!
I wish I would've find this earlier.
Damn you ugly.
Let's go.
- Where are we going?
- We have a safe house set up.
- There's no creepers following us
- We left Banks behind to distract them
You left one man behind to distract a hundred zombies?
One girl. Don't worry, she knows what she's doing.
- How many of you are there?
- Just the three of us.
Okay. We're not too far away now.
Now watch for trip wires.
- They are marked by ribbon.
- Don't you think the ribbon will give it away?
No. Zombies don't know what ribbons are.
Look, we appreciate the help, but we have to find our friends.
- You honestly think they made it?
- We've fought our way across 2,000 miles, so yeah.
- Pretty sure they made it.
- You've made it that far?
- Hi. I'm Myrah.
- Julian.
- Hi Julian
- They wanna go back. They have two other people.
- You won't make it.
There's more of them than we thought.
We have to go.
- Alright, we're close.
- Listen, if you want to go after them, I got your back.
It honestly says a lot.
Okay. Damn it Cas, where are you?
We were headed through the city with ferry when we had a massive pack of the dead.
- Hey, we just comb zombies.
- What ferry?
Catalina sends a ferry every few weeks to pick up survivors
- At least that's what we heard.
- We heard about it back east.
- Took us a while to get here though.
- Thats the same with us, what was it? Six months?
We've been looking for a way around the undead for two days, but the city is full of them.
- Yeah, as a rule, we don't go to cities.
- Good rule. We came out of Chicago,
started with 20 survivors. Cops and firefighters, well armed.
We're the only ones that made it.
- Must've been difficult.
- Oh, they would still be alive if they listen to us.
Now look. The east route, it's filled with the dead, I'm ruling that out.
We all know what the suburbs look like.
Now we could come around down here to avoid the section and come out through the South.
- That'll take us two or three days at least.
- Correct. Now we don't know what we're going to find there.
- What about this north-west road here?
- Ah, I'm getting to that. Now we scouted this when we first got here.
And there's a lot of dead but compared to other options, it's probably our best.
We need to move quickly, no guns. Kill only the deads that are a threat.
Now look, I don't know if your teams are up to it.
But it might've been better, if you stay here,
- and let us bring back help.
- I don't have a team. I have friends. And they're up to it.
We just have to go back for Henry and Cass.
That kind of thinkings are gonna get you killed.
We saw how you handles yourself back there, and we all think you're up to it.
I have to think about my team, we're not dying for anyone else.
Alright, I'll make the decision for you.
If Henry and Cass are alive,
we're gonna take this route to get there. We'll go with you that far.
- After that? You're on your own.
- Thanks for the favor.
Alright, fine.
That area is my biggest concern, okay?
- There's a lot of dead.
- Can't... can't you just call them zombies?
- Yeah, really...
- The streets are narrow and they're gonna be hard to avoid.
So you do what we tell you, or do not come along, you understand?
- We'll help you through.
- Alright. This is gonna be a big day.
Let's turn in and get some rest.
My team will keep watch.
- I.. I just have a question
- Yeah?
- So we've been finding your arrows for weeks now.
- And?
- Why bows?
- Bows are a great weapon. They are silent.
Everybody that raids a sport or good store goes for the bullets, nobody even touches the arrows.
Because most people don't know how to shoot bows.
- We're part of the Quincy archery team. That's coach Sinclair.
- Ah... Alright.
Sweet dreams.
- You uh, you want me to take over while you get some sleep?
- We have a system going,
doesn't work well when we tried to include outsiders.
Yeah, you won't need it after tomorrow. We will be in Catalina.
That's... the plan anyway.
As they say, the best laid plans of mice and men often go astray.
It's actually gang aft a-gley.
From... I mean from the original.
Burn's... Burn's poem.
You tryin' to charm me with poetry, during zombie apocalypse?
Is it working?
Coz I wanna know.
I hope that's a satellite, not the space station.
Get some sleep, Julian.
You'll need it.
Hey look. What is that?
Satellite maybe, I don't know.
- Sometimes the end of the world is beautiful.
- Look, we gotta find a place to sleep.
It's going to be a busy day tomorrow.
- Alright, Banks will be in the lead, I'm 15 feets back, then Sarah and your team.
- Copy.
- Remember the hand signs?
- Uh, maybe
- Look, listen, wait, move up and rally.
- Which is the bad one?
- Rally, means I need help.
- If you're confused, ask Sarah.
We're only eliminating the dead, if they're a threat or they'll see us.
- We ran out of ammo last night.
- Good, or you will be tempted to shoot.
- Your version of good and mine are not the same.
- We're full with arrows.
- If anybody can save and retrieve an arrow, do it.
- We're gonna need 'em.
- You think the others make it out okay?
- Yeah, Mack will keep them save.
- We should go back man...
- Nah, we're gonna go towards the island. That's where they'll be headed.
You know, if we make it to Catalina, there will be other people there.
Well, I hope so.
I mean, my husband.
Yeah...
it's just that, you know, you and I have become... friends.
- and I don't wanna... don't wanna...
- yeah.
You'll be happy to see him, won't you?
Yeah, but I don't wanna change any...
Then I'll be happy too.
Ready, Banks? Go!
There are seven of them, all spread out.
Some looking our way.
- We probably do stop and drop?
- What's a stop and drop?
Pick off the furthest one.
When it drops, it will attract the rest.
- They go one way, we go the other.
- I bet you I can make it on the first try.
and I win.
Let's go.
Toilets!
Yes! Toilet time...
Julian, what are you doing?
Am I bit?
Got zombies!!
Move, move, move!
Down there! Get to the van!
Everybody in! Everybody in!
Oh, shit...
Gun looks intact. It's good.
Maybe we could find some ammo.
Not much here.
Bingo. I want to take it with us.
- Too heavy.
- Please?
Mack!
- I want you to keep this going.
- What?
- Keep it going for me, promise me.
- Why?
Look...
Write it down.
Julian. Seattle, Washington. Write it down.
- No... No, no.
- Mack! Mack, Mack! What's done, is done.
I'll make a path. Alright?
Let me get outta here.
- Keep quiet!
- Yes, I can distract them.
- It's not a bad idea.
- No, no, no...
Mack... Don't make this harder.
Find Cassie and Henry, get to Catalina and...
and live!
It's alright... It's alright.
Julian. Julian!
He's turned... He's turned.
- He's turning - Julian
- Hold him down!
- I can't fight it!
- Move!
Look away.
- Sorry... Sorry...
- Do it! - I'm sorry.
Ramona... Give me his machete.
Henry, behind you!
They're getting smarter.
Come on!
- They're leaving.
- Okay, let's move out.
Mack, come on!
Up there!
Man, this is getting worse and worse.
Think we're trapped, Henry.
- What's that?
- I think it's Mack
- Well, maybe we can work our way over to that roof
- I don't think so big guy.
Got a plan. Come on.
Cassie! This way!
To the boat! It's up ahead!
The gate! Get in!
Come on, come on! They are coming!
- Come on, get in!
- Go go go!
Okay, okay!
It's locked!
- I don't see any gaps.
- Unless the zombies are learning to climb,
think we're going to be okay.
- So you guys are the archer huh?
- Yeah. That's Banks, that's Sarah, I'm Brockton
Hey, I'm cassie, this is Henry.
We've admired your work.
Where's... Where's Julian?
He didn't make it Cass...
I thought Julian would've make it with us...
I'm sorry Cass...
Hey guys!
The ferry arrives noon, on Wednesday.
- What day is it?
- Julian would've known...
I found something.
Lot of instructions.
There's a quarantine procedure.
- All survivors will be segregated on the island for a week
- Make sense.
There's food.
Oh my God...
Brockton! Here!
My God...
Oh my God...
- Weapons! Banks, guard the rail.
- Zombie must've gotten here somehow.
- Most of them are torn...
- It doesn't make sense...
I never seen the dead drag a human away before.
Neither did we.
- Hey, what was that?
- What?
I don't know...
- Something is dragging the bodies through the top of the containers.
- What the hell?
- Watch out!
- Sara!!!
Henry! Help!!!
- You alright?
- Yeah...
Brockton, watch out!
- I'm coming! We'll deal with Brockton!
- Cassie!
- Henry! Need some help here!!!
Here kitty, kitty, kitty...
Here kitty...
- Meow, bitch.
- Henry, watch out!
I'm not through with you, bitch.
- We got that bitch...
- Yeah, we did...
Don't let me turn...
No...
Good bye, buddy...
Anyone see a ferry?
We're sure it's coming right?
- I hope so...
- It will come.
So Cas, what's gonna be the first thing you do when you get to Catalina?
Kiss my husband.
Find a new sword.
Translated by: VincentL