♪
(s
(sea
(seagu
(seagull s
(seagull squ
(seagull squaw
(seagull squawki
(seagull squawking)
>>
>> M
>> Mama?
>>
>> W
>> Wak
>> Wake up
>> Wake up,
>> Wake up, li
>> Wake up, litt
>> Wake up, little g
>> Wake up, little gir
>> Wake up, little girl.
I'
I'm
I'm afra
I'm afraid
I'm afraid w
I'm afraid we
I'm afraid we have
I'm afraid we have t
I'm afraid we have to
I'm afraid we have to go
I'm afraid we have to go now
I'm afraid we have to go now.
Wi
Will
Will y
Will you h
Will you hel
Will you help
Will you help yo
Will you help your m
Will you help your mam
Will you help your mama?
Ja
Jame
James,
James, hon
James, honey
James, honey,
James, honey, wa
James, honey, wake u
James, honey, wake up.
James, honey, wake up.I
James, honey, wake up.I ne
James, honey, wake up.I need
James, honey, wake up.I need you
James, honey, wake up.I need you t
James, honey, wake up.I need you to
James, honey, wake up.I need you to ge
James, honey, wake up.I need you to get up
James, honey, wake up.I need you to get upri
James, honey, wake up.I need you to get uprigh
James, honey, wake up.I need you to get upright no
James, honey, wake up.I need you to get upright now
James, honey, wake up.I need you to get upright now an
James, honey, wake up.I need you to get upright now and
James, honey, wake up.I need you to get upright now and come
James, honey, wake up.I need you to get upright now and come t
James, honey, wake up.I need you to get upright now and come to
I need you to get upright now and come to
I need you to get upright now and come tothe
I need you to get upright now and come tothe ki
I need you to get upright now and come tothe kitc
I need you to get upright now and come tothe kitche
I need you to get upright now and come tothe kitchen, o
I need you to get upright now and come tothe kitchen, oka
I need you to get upright now and come tothe kitchen, okay?
>>
>> W
>> Wha
>> What ti
>> What time
>> What time i
>> What time is
>> What time is it?
>> What time is it?>> S
>> What time is it?>> Sam
>> What time is it?>> Sammy
>> What time is it?>> Sammy,
>> What time is it?>> Sammy, hone
>> What time is it?>> Sammy, honey,
>> What time is it?>> Sammy, honey, w
>> What time is it?>> Sammy, honey, wak
>> What time is it?>> Sammy, honey, wake up
>> What time is it?>> Sammy, honey, wake up.
Come
Come o
Come on,
Come on, M
Come on, Mr. S
Come on, Mr. Sam
Come on, Mr. Sam-M
Come on, Mr. Sam-Man
Come on, Mr. Sam-Man,
Come on, Mr. Sam-Man,time
Come on, Mr. Sam-Man,time t
Come on, Mr. Sam-Man,time to
Come on, Mr. Sam-Man,time to ge
Come on, Mr. Sam-Man,time to get up
Come on, Mr. Sam-Man,time to get up n
Come on, Mr. Sam-Man,time to get up now
Come on, Mr. Sam-Man,time to get up now.
(c
(cri
(crick
(cricket
(crickets ch
(crickets chir
(crickets chirpi
(crickets chirping
(crickets chirping)
Ci
Cill
Cilla
Cilla Lo
Cilla Logan.
Cilla Logan.>>
Cilla Logan.>> O
Cilla Logan.>> Oka
Cilla Logan.>> Okay.
Cilla Logan.>> Okay.>>
Cilla Logan.>> Okay.>> A
Cilla Logan.>> Okay.>> And
Cilla Logan.>> Okay.>> And the
Cilla Logan.>> Okay.>> And then
Cilla Logan.>> Okay.>> And then it
Cilla Logan.>> Okay.>> And then it's
Cilla Logan.>> Okay.>> And then it's 172
Cilla Logan.>> Okay.>> And then it's 1724.
>> Okay.>> And then it's 1724.
>> Okay.>> And then it's 1724.1-
>> Okay.>> And then it's 1724.1-7.
>> And then it's 1724.1-7.
>> And then it's 1724.1-7.Th
>> And then it's 1724.1-7.That
>> And then it's 1724.1-7.That's
>> And then it's 1724.1-7.That's 7
>> And then it's 1724.1-7.That's 724.
Oc
Ocea
Ocean
Ocean Dr
Ocean Drive.
>>
>> W
>> We
>> We live
>> We lived
>> We lived wi
>> We lived with
>> We lived with our
>> We lived with our m
>> We lived with our mom
>> We lived with our momin
>> We lived with our momin a
>> We lived with our momin a l
>> We lived with our momin a littl
>> We lived with our momin a little
>> We lived with our momin a little ho
>> We lived with our momin a little hous
>> We lived with our momin a little house
>> We lived with our momin a little houseal
>> We lived with our momin a little houseall
>> We lived with our momin a little houseall by
>> We lived with our momin a little houseall by its
>> We lived with our momin a little houseall by itsel
>> We lived with our momin a little houseall by itself
in a little houseall by itself
in a little houseall by itselfou
in a little houseall by itselfout
in a little houseall by itselfout in
in a little houseall by itselfout in the
in a little houseall by itselfout in the d
in a little houseall by itselfout in the dun
in a little houseall by itselfout in the dunes
in a little houseall by itselfout in the dunes.
all by itselfout in the dunes.
all by itselfout in the dunes.I
all by itselfout in the dunes.I gu
all by itselfout in the dunes.I gues
all by itselfout in the dunes.I guess
all by itselfout in the dunes.I guess we w
all by itselfout in the dunes.I guess we wer
all by itselfout in the dunes.I guess we were
all by itselfout in the dunes.I guess we were po
all by itselfout in the dunes.I guess we were poor,
out in the dunes.I guess we were poor,
out in the dunes.I guess we were poor,bu
out in the dunes.I guess we were poor,but
out in the dunes.I guess we were poor,but we
out in the dunes.I guess we were poor,but we had
out in the dunes.I guess we were poor,but we had t
out in the dunes.I guess we were poor,but we had the
out in the dunes.I guess we were poor,but we had the o
out in the dunes.I guess we were poor,but we had the ocean
I guess we were poor,but we had the ocean
I guess we were poor,but we had the oceanan
I guess we were poor,but we had the oceanand
I guess we were poor,but we had the oceanand th
I guess we were poor,but we had the oceanand that w
I guess we were poor,but we had the oceanand that was
I guess we were poor,but we had the oceanand that was b
I guess we were poor,but we had the oceanand that was bet
I guess we were poor,but we had the oceanand that was better
I guess we were poor,but we had the oceanand that was better th
I guess we were poor,but we had the oceanand that was better than
but we had the oceanand that was better than
but we had the oceanand that was better thanan
but we had the oceanand that was better thanany
but we had the oceanand that was better thanany fa
but we had the oceanand that was better thanany fancy
but we had the oceanand that was better thanany fancy ho
but we had the oceanand that was better thanany fancy hous
but we had the oceanand that was better thanany fancy house.
Ma
Mama
Mama sai
Mama said
Mama said we
Mama said we w
Mama said we were
Mama said we were go
Mama said we were goin
Mama said we were going
Mama said we were going to
Mama said we were going toAu
Mama said we were going toAunt
Mama said we were going toAunt C
Mama said we were going toAunt Cil
Mama said we were going toAunt Cilla's
Mama said we were going toAunt Cilla's.
Bu
But
But dr
But drivin
But driving
But driving of
But driving off
But driving off in
But driving off inth
But driving off inthe
But driving off inthe midd
But driving off inthe middle
But driving off inthe middle o
But driving off inthe middle of
But driving off inthe middle of the
But driving off inthe middle of the ni
But driving off inthe middle of the nigh
But driving off inthe middle of the night
But driving off inthe middle of the nightju
But driving off inthe middle of the nightjust
But driving off inthe middle of the nightjust did
But driving off inthe middle of the nightjust didn'
But driving off inthe middle of the nightjust didn't
But driving off inthe middle of the nightjust didn't ma
But driving off inthe middle of the nightjust didn't make a
But driving off inthe middle of the nightjust didn't make any
But driving off inthe middle of the nightjust didn't make any s
But driving off inthe middle of the nightjust didn't make any sen
But driving off inthe middle of the nightjust didn't make any sense.
Fo
For
For on
For one th
For one thin
For one thing,
For one thing, w
For one thing, we ne
For one thing, we neve
For one thing, we never
For one thing, we neverto
For one thing, we nevertook
For one thing, we nevertook t
For one thing, we nevertook trips
For one thing, we nevertook trips.
For one thing, we nevertook trips.An
For one thing, we nevertook trips.And
For one thing, we nevertook trips.And he
For one thing, we nevertook trips.And here w
For one thing, we nevertook trips.And here we
For one thing, we nevertook trips.And here we we
For one thing, we nevertook trips.And here we were
For one thing, we nevertook trips.And here we were,
took trips.And here we were,
took trips.And here we were,he
took trips.And here we were,head
took trips.And here we were,headin
took trips.And here we were,heading al
took trips.And here we were,heading all
took trips.And here we were,heading all th
took trips.And here we were,heading all the
took trips.And here we were,heading all the way
took trips.And here we were,heading all the way do
took trips.And here we were,heading all the way down
And here we were,heading all the way down
And here we were,heading all the way downto
And here we were,heading all the way downto B
And here we were,heading all the way downto Bridg
And here we were,heading all the way downto Bridgep
And here we were,heading all the way downto Bridgepor
And here we were,heading all the way downto Bridgeport.
>> Y
>> You
>> You b
>> You be
>> You be good
>> You be good n
>> You be good now
>> You be good now,
>> You be good now,yo
>> You be good now,you
>> You be good now,you he
>> You be good now,you hear
>> You be good now,you hear?
Yo
You
You li
You litt
You little o
You little one
You little ones
You little ones mi
You little ones mind
You little ones mindwh
You little ones mindwhat
You little ones mindwhat D
You little ones mindwhat Dicey
You little ones mindwhat Dicey t
You little ones mindwhat Dicey tel
You little ones mindwhat Dicey tells
You little ones mindwhat Dicey tells you
You little ones mindwhat Dicey tells you.
You little ones mindwhat Dicey tells you.Yo
You little ones mindwhat Dicey tells you.You
You little ones mindwhat Dicey tells you.You he
You little ones mindwhat Dicey tells you.You hear m
You little ones mindwhat Dicey tells you.You hear me?
what Dicey tells you.You hear me?
what Dicey tells you.You hear me?>>
what Dicey tells you.You hear me?>> Y
what Dicey tells you.You hear me?>> Yes
what Dicey tells you.You hear me?>> Yes,
what Dicey tells you.You hear me?>> Yes, Momm
what Dicey tells you.You hear me?>> Yes, Mommy.
You hear me?>> Yes, Mommy.
You hear me?>> Yes, Mommy.>>
You hear me?>> Yes, Mommy.>> Y
You hear me?>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes,
You hear me?>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes, Ma
You hear me?>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes, Mama
You hear me?>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes, Mama.
>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes, Mama.
>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes, Mama.>>
>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes, Mama.>> I
>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes, Mama.>> It'
>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes, Mama.>> It's al
>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes, Mama.>> It's all
>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes, Mama.>> It's all ri
>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes, Mama.>> It's all righ
>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes, Mama.>> It's all right th
>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes, Mama.>> It's all right then
>> Yes, Mommy.>> Yes, Mama.>> It's all right then.
>>
>> S
>> She
>> She w
>> She was a
>> She was alw
>> She was alway
>> She was always
>> She was always doin
>> She was always doing
>> She was always doing th
>> She was always doing that
>> She was always doing that.
>> She was always doing that.Le
>> She was always doing that.Leav
>> She was always doing that.Leavin
>> She was always doing that.Leaving ev
>> She was always doing that.Leaving ever
>> She was always doing that.Leaving everyt
>> She was always doing that.Leaving everythi
>> She was always doing that.Leaving everything u
>> She was always doing that.Leaving everything up
>> She was always doing that.Leaving everything up to
>> She was always doing that.Leaving everything up to m
>> She was always doing that.Leaving everything up to me.
>> W
>> Whe
>> Where
>> Where a
>> Where are w
>> Where are we?
Wh
Why
Why di
Why did we
Why did we s
Why did we sto
Why did we stop?
Why did we stop?>>
Why did we stop?>> I
Why did we stop?>> I d
Why did we stop?>> I don't
Why did we stop?>> I don't k
Why did we stop?>> I don't kno
Why did we stop?>> I don't know.
Why did we stop?>> I don't know.Yo
Why did we stop?>> I don't know.You
Why did we stop?>> I don't know.You hear
Why did we stop?>> I don't know.You heard
Why did we stop?>> I don't know.You heard ev
Why did we stop?>> I don't know.You heard ever
Why did we stop?>> I don't know.You heard everythi
Why did we stop?>> I don't know.You heard everything
Why did we stop?>> I don't know.You heard everything s
Why did we stop?>> I don't know.You heard everything she
Why did we stop?>> I don't know.You heard everything she sai
Why did we stop?>> I don't know.You heard everything she said.
>> I don't know.You heard everything she said.
>> I don't know.You heard everything she said.Sa
>> I don't know.You heard everything she said.Same
>> I don't know.You heard everything she said.Same a
>> I don't know.You heard everything she said.Same as I
>> I don't know.You heard everything she said.Same as I di
>> I don't know.You heard everything she said.Same as I did.
You heard everything she said.Same as I did.
You heard everything she said.Same as I did.You
You heard everything she said.Same as I did.You te
You heard everything she said.Same as I did.You tell
You heard everything she said.Same as I did.You tell m
You heard everything she said.Same as I did.You tell me.
Same as I did.You tell me.
Same as I did.You tell me.>>
Same as I did.You tell me.>> A
Same as I did.You tell me.>> All
Same as I did.You tell me.>> All she
Same as I did.You tell me.>> All she s
Same as I did.You tell me.>> All she sai
Same as I did.You tell me.>> All she said
Same as I did.You tell me.>> All she said is w
Same as I did.You tell me.>> All she said is we
Same as I did.You tell me.>> All she said is we go
Same as I did.You tell me.>> All she said is we gott
Same as I did.You tell me.>> All she said is we gotta
You tell me.>> All she said is we gotta
You tell me.>> All she said is we gottast
You tell me.>> All she said is we gottastop
You tell me.>> All she said is we gottastop her
You tell me.>> All she said is we gottastop here,
You tell me.>> All she said is we gottastop here, s
You tell me.>> All she said is we gottastop here, she
You tell me.>> All she said is we gottastop here, she did
You tell me.>> All she said is we gottastop here, she didn'
You tell me.>> All she said is we gottastop here, she didn't
You tell me.>> All she said is we gottastop here, she didn't sa
You tell me.>> All she said is we gottastop here, she didn't say wh
You tell me.>> All she said is we gottastop here, she didn't say why.
Sh
She
She ne
She never
She never sa
She never says
She never says w
She never says why.
She never says why.(g
She never says why.(gir
She never says why.(girl
She never says why.(girl humm
She never says why.(girl hummin
She never says why.(girl humming)
>>
>> ♪ R
>> ♪ Roc
>> ♪ Rock-
>> ♪ Rock-a-
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye ba
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ O
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the tr
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the tree
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the treeto
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the treetop ♪
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the treetop ♪♪
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the treetop ♪♪ W
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When th
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wi
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind b
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blo
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blows
>> ♪ Rock-a-bye baby ♪♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blows ♪
♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blows ♪
♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blows ♪♪
♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ T
♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The
♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cra
♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradl
♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle
♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle wi
♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with r
♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with roc
♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with rock
♪ On the treetop ♪♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with rock ♪
♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with rock ♪
♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪
♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ W
♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ Whe
♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When th
♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the
♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bo
♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow
♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow brea
♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow breaks
♪ When the wind blows ♪♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow breaks ♪
♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow breaks ♪
♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪
♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ T
♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The
♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cra
♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradl
♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle
♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle wi
♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will f
♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fal
♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fall
♪ The cradle with rock ♪♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fall ♪
♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fall ♪
♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ A
♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And
♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And d
♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And dow
♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down wi
♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will
♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will c
♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will com
♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will come ba
♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will come baby
♪ When the bow breaks ♪♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will come baby ♪
♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will come baby ♪
♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will come baby ♪♪
♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will come baby ♪♪ C
♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will come baby ♪♪ Cra
♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will come baby ♪♪ Cradle
♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will come baby ♪♪ Cradle an
♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will come baby ♪♪ Cradle and
♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will come baby ♪♪ Cradle and al
♪ The cradle will fall ♪♪ And down will come baby ♪♪ Cradle and all ♪
>>
>> W
>> Wha
>> What ti
>> What time
>> What time i
>> What time is
>> What time is it?
>> What time is it?>>
>> What time is it?>> I
>> What time is it?>> I don
>> What time is it?>> I don't
>> What time is it?>> I don't k
>> What time is it?>> I don't kno
>> What time is it?>> I don't know.
>> What time is it?>> I don't know.Yo
>> What time is it?>> I don't know.You'
>> What time is it?>> I don't know.You've
>> What time is it?>> I don't know.You've bee
>> What time is it?>> I don't know.You've been
>> What time is it?>> I don't know.You've been as
>> What time is it?>> I don't know.You've been asle
>> What time is it?>> I don't know.You've been asleep a
>> What time is it?>> I don't know.You've been asleep a l
>> What time is it?>> I don't know.You've been asleep a lon
>> What time is it?>> I don't know.You've been asleep a long
>> What time is it?>> I don't know.You've been asleep a long time
>> What time is it?>> I don't know.You've been asleep a long time.
I'
I'm
I'm hu
I'm hung
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry.>> W
I'm hungry.>> Whe
I'm hungry.>> Where
I'm hungry.>> Where's
I'm hungry.>> Where's Mam
I'm hungry.>> Where's Mama?
I'm hungry.>> Where's Mama?>>
I'm hungry.>> Where's Mama?>> I
I'm hungry.>> Where's Mama?>> I d
I'm hungry.>> Where's Mama?>> I don
I'm hungry.>> Where's Mama?>> I don't k
I'm hungry.>> Where's Mama?>> I don't kno
I'm hungry.>> Where's Mama?>> I don't know.
>> Where's Mama?>> I don't know.
>> Where's Mama?>> I don't know.I'
>> Where's Mama?>> I don't know.I'm
>> Where's Mama?>> I don't know.I'm hung
>> Where's Mama?>> I don't know.I'm hungry
>> Where's Mama?>> I don't know.I'm hungry!
>> I don't know.I'm hungry!
>> I don't know.I'm hungry!>> Y
>> I don't know.I'm hungry!>> You
>> I don't know.I'm hungry!>> You'r
>> I don't know.I'm hungry!>> You're
>> I don't know.I'm hungry!>> You're alwa
>> I don't know.I'm hungry!>> You're always
>> I don't know.I'm hungry!>> You're always h
>> I don't know.I'm hungry!>> You're always hun
>> I don't know.I'm hungry!>> You're always hungry.
I'm hungry!>> You're always hungry.
I'm hungry!>> You're always hungry.>>
I'm hungry!>> You're always hungry.>> M
I'm hungry!>> You're always hungry.>> Me to
I'm hungry!>> You're always hungry.>> Me too.
>> You're always hungry.>> Me too.
>> You're always hungry.>> Me too.An
>> You're always hungry.>> Me too.And
>> You're always hungry.>> Me too.And I'm
>> You're always hungry.>> Me too.And I'm go
>> You're always hungry.>> Me too.And I'm goin
>> You're always hungry.>> Me too.And I'm going
>> You're always hungry.>> Me too.And I'm going to e
>> You're always hungry.>> Me too.And I'm going to eat
>> You're always hungry.>> Me too.And I'm going to eat.
>>
>> S
>> So wh
>> So what
>> So what d
>> So what do
>> So what do you
>> So what do youwant
>> So what do youwant m
>> So what do youwant me
>> So what do youwant me to
>> So what do youwant me to do?
>> So what do youwant me to do?Go
>> So what do youwant me to do?Go l
>> So what do youwant me to do?Go loo
>> So what do youwant me to do?Go look
>> So what do youwant me to do?Go look for
>> So what do youwant me to do?Go look for he
>> So what do youwant me to do?Go look for her?
want me to do?Go look for her?
want me to do?Go look for her?>> N
want me to do?Go look for her?>> No.
Go look for her?>> No.
Go look for her?>> No.Sa
Go look for her?>> No.Samm
Go look for her?>> No.Sammy,
Go look for her?>> No.Sammy, giv
Go look for her?>> No.Sammy, give
Go look for her?>> No.Sammy, give Ma
Go look for her?>> No.Sammy, give Mayb
Go look for her?>> No.Sammy, give Maybeth
>> No.Sammy, give Maybeth
>> No.Sammy, give Maybetha sa
>> No.Sammy, give Maybetha sand
>> No.Sammy, give Maybetha sandwi
>> No.Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich
>> No.Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich, to
>> No.Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich, too.
Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich, too.
Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich, too.Let
Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich, too.Let he
Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich, too.Let her
Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich, too.Let her ch
Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich, too.Let her choose
Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich, too.Let her choose f
Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich, too.Let her choose for
Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich, too.Let her choose for h
Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich, too.Let her choose for herse
Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich, too.Let her choose for herself
Sammy, give Maybetha sandwich, too.Let her choose for herself.
I'
I'm
I'm gonn
I'm gonna
I'm gonna go
I'm gonna go s
I'm gonna go see
I'm gonna go seewh
I'm gonna go seewhat
I'm gonna go seewhat tim
I'm gonna go seewhat time
I'm gonna go seewhat time it
I'm gonna go seewhat time it i
I'm gonna go seewhat time it is.
>>
>> D
>> Dic
>> Dicey?
Don'
Don't
Don't yo
Don't you
Don't you go a
Don't you go awa
Don't you go away,
Don't you go away, t
Don't you go away, too.
Don't you go away, too.♪
>>
>> D
>> Did y
>> Did you
>> Did you f
>> Did you fin
>> Did you find he
>> Did you find her?
>>
>> O
>> Over
>> Over he
>> Over here
>> Over here.
>>
>> Y
>> You
>> You kno
>> You know
>> You know wh
>> You know what
>> You know what--
>>
>> M
>> My
>> My st
>> My stomac
>> My stomach
>> My stomach fe
>> My stomach feel
>> My stomach feels we
>> My stomach feels weir
>> My stomach feels weird.
Wh
Why'
Why'd
Why'd sh
Why'd she do
Why'd she do t
Why'd she do thi
Why'd she do this?
Why'd she do this?Wh
Why'd she do this?What
Why'd she do this?What's
Why'd she do this?What's wro
Why'd she do this?What's wrong
Why'd she do this?What's wrong w
Why'd she do this?What's wrong wit
Why'd she do this?What's wrong with he
Why'd she do this?What's wrong with her?
Why'd she do this?What's wrong with her?!
Why'd she do this?What's wrong with her?!>>
Why'd she do this?What's wrong with her?!>> J
Why'd she do this?What's wrong with her?!>> Jam
Why'd she do this?What's wrong with her?!>> James
Why'd she do this?What's wrong with her?!>> James...
If s
If she
If she i
If she isn
If she isn't b
If she isn't bac
If she isn't back
If she isn't back by
If she isn't back by mor
If she isn't back by morni
If she isn't back by morning
If she isn't back by morning..
If she isn't back by morning...
..
...
... I
... I th
... I think
... I think we
... I think we s
... I think we sho
... I think we should
... I think we shouldgo
... I think we shouldgo o
... I think we shouldgo ont
... I think we shouldgo onto Br
... I think we shouldgo onto Brid
... I think we shouldgo onto Bridge
... I think we shouldgo onto Bridgepo
... I think we shouldgo onto Bridgeport.
>>
>> H
>> How
>> How a
>> How are w
>> How are we
>> How are we go
>> How are we gonn
>> How are we gonna ge
>> How are we gonna get
>> How are we gonna get th
>> How are we gonna get ther
>> How are we gonna get there?
>> How are we gonna get there?Can'
>> How are we gonna get there?Can't
>> How are we gonna get there?Can't dr
>> How are we gonna get there?Can't driv
>> How are we gonna get there?Can't drive, M
>> How are we gonna get there?Can't drive, Mam
>> How are we gonna get there?Can't drive, Mama
>> How are we gonna get there?Can't drive, Mama to
>> How are we gonna get there?Can't drive, Mama took t
>> How are we gonna get there?Can't drive, Mama took the
>> How are we gonna get there?Can't drive, Mama took the k
>> How are we gonna get there?Can't drive, Mama took the key
>> How are we gonna get there?Can't drive, Mama took the keys.
I th
I thin
I think
I think we
I think we sho
I think we shoul
I think we should
I think we should go
I think we should go to
I think we should go toth
I think we should go tothe
I think we should go tothe po
I think we should go tothe poli
I think we should go tothe police a
I think we should go tothe police and
I think we should go tothe police and a
I think we should go tothe police and ask
I think we should go tothe police and ask for
I think we should go tothe police and ask for h
I think we should go tothe police and ask for hel
I think we should go tothe police and ask for help.
I think we should go tothe police and ask for help.>>
I think we should go tothe police and ask for help.>> W
I think we should go tothe police and ask for help.>> We
I think we should go tothe police and ask for help.>> We can'
I think we should go tothe police and ask for help.>> We can't.
the police and ask for help.>> We can't.
the police and ask for help.>> We can't.If
the police and ask for help.>> We can't.If w
the police and ask for help.>> We can't.If we
the police and ask for help.>> We can't.If we go
the police and ask for help.>> We can't.If we go to
the police and ask for help.>> We can't.If we go to th
the police and ask for help.>> We can't.If we go to the
the police and ask for help.>> We can't.If we go to the po
the police and ask for help.>> We can't.If we go to the police
the police and ask for help.>> We can't.If we go to the police,
>> We can't.If we go to the police,
>> We can't.If we go to the police,th
>> We can't.If we go to the police,they
>> We can't.If we go to the police,they'r
>> We can't.If we go to the police,they're ju
>> We can't.If we go to the police,they're just
>> We can't.If we go to the police,they're just g
>> We can't.If we go to the police,they're just gon
>> We can't.If we go to the police,they're just gonna s
>> We can't.If we go to the police,they're just gonna spl
>> We can't.If we go to the police,they're just gonna split
>> We can't.If we go to the police,they're just gonna split u
>> We can't.If we go to the police,they're just gonna split us up
If we go to the police,they're just gonna split us up
If we go to the police,they're just gonna split us upan
If we go to the police,they're just gonna split us upand
If we go to the police,they're just gonna split us upand pu
If we go to the police,they're just gonna split us upand put
If we go to the police,they're just gonna split us upand put us i
If we go to the police,they're just gonna split us upand put us in
If we go to the police,they're just gonna split us upand put us in fo
If we go to the police,they're just gonna split us upand put us in fost
If we go to the police,they're just gonna split us upand put us in foster h
If we go to the police,they're just gonna split us upand put us in foster hom
If we go to the police,they're just gonna split us upand put us in foster homes
If we go to the police,they're just gonna split us upand put us in foster homes.
You
You re
You reme
You rememb
You remember t
You remember the
You remember the l
You remember the lad
You remember the lady
You remember the ladywh
You remember the ladywho
You remember the ladywho ca
You remember the ladywho came t
You remember the ladywho came to
You remember the ladywho came to ou
You remember the ladywho came to our
You remember the ladywho came to our hous
You remember the ladywho came to our house.
You remember the ladywho came to our house.The
You remember the ladywho came to our house.The so
You remember the ladywho came to our house.The soci
You remember the ladywho came to our house.The social
You remember the ladywho came to our house.The social wor
You remember the ladywho came to our house.The social worke
You remember the ladywho came to our house.The social worker.
Ok
Okay
Okay, th
Okay, then
Okay, then y
Okay, then you
Okay, then you kno
Okay, then you know
Okay, then you know it
Okay, then you know it's
Okay, then you know it's tru
Okay, then you know it's true.
>> D
>> Dic
>> Dicey
>> Dicey,
>> Dicey, do y
>> Dicey, do you
>> Dicey, do you t
>> Dicey, do you thi
>> Dicey, do you think M
>> Dicey, do you think Mam
>> Dicey, do you think Mama
>> Dicey, do you think Mamamean
>> Dicey, do you think Mamameant
>> Dicey, do you think Mamameant to
>> Dicey, do you think Mamameant to l
>> Dicey, do you think Mamameant to leave
>> Dicey, do you think Mamameant to leave u
>> Dicey, do you think Mamameant to leave us
>> Dicey, do you think Mamameant to leave us he
>> Dicey, do you think Mamameant to leave us here?
>>
>> I
>> I t
>> I think
>> I think s
>> I think she
>> I think she m
>> I think she meant
>> I think she meant t
>> I think she meant to
>> I think she meant tota
>> I think she meant totake
>> I think she meant totake u
>> I think she meant totake us to
>> I think she meant totake us to B
>> I think she meant totake us to Bri
>> I think she meant totake us to Bridg
>> I think she meant totake us to Bridgepor
>> I think she meant totake us to Bridgeport.
Mama
Mama l
Mama lov
Mama loves
Mama loves us.
Th
That
That's a
That's all
That's all I
That's all I k
That's all I know.
>>
>>Th
>>The ma
>>The mall
>>The mall i
>>The mall is
>>The mall is now
>>The mall is now cl
>>The mall is now clos
>>The mall is now closed
>>The mall is now closed.
>>The mall is now closed.>>
>>The mall is now closed.>>Wh
>>The mall is now closed.>>What w
>>The mall is now closed.>>What was
>>The mall is now closed.>>What was t
>>The mall is now closed.>>What was tha
>>The mall is now closed.>>What was that na
>>The mall is now closed.>>What was that name
>>The mall is now closed.>>What was that nameag
>>The mall is now closed.>>What was that nameagai
>>The mall is now closed.>>What was that nameagain, p
>>The mall is now closed.>>What was that nameagain, ple
>>The mall is now closed.>>What was that nameagain, pleas
>>The mall is now closed.>>What was that nameagain, please?
>>What was that nameagain, please?
>>What was that nameagain, please?>>
>>What was that nameagain, please?>> I
>>What was that nameagain, please?>> In
>>What was that nameagain, please?>> In Brid
>>What was that nameagain, please?>> In Bridge
>>What was that nameagain, please?>> In Bridgepo
>>What was that nameagain, please?>> In Bridgeport
>>What was that nameagain, please?>> In Bridgeport,
again, please?>> In Bridgeport,
again, please?>> In Bridgeport,Ci
again, please?>> In Bridgeport,Cill
again, please?>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Lo
again, please?>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Loga
again, please?>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan,
again, please?>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, o
again, please?>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Oc
again, please?>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocea
again, please?>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean
again, please?>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean Dr
again, please?>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.
>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.
>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>
>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>Th
>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That
>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That n
>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That num
>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number'
>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's
>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's un
>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unli
>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted
>> In Bridgeport,Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted.
Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted.
Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted.>>
Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted.>> W
Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted.>> Wel
Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, i
Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it'
Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's
Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an
Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an eme
Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emerg
Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emergen
Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emergency
Cilla Logan, on Ocean Drive.>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emergency.
>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emergency.
>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emergency.>>
>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well
>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well,
>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'
>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm
>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorr
>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry,
>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry, d
>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry, dea
>>That number's unlisted.>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,
>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,
>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,bu
>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but
>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we'r
>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're
>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're no
>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not
>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not allo
>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not allowe
>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not allowed
>> Well, it's an emergency.>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not allowed to
>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not allowed to
>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not allowed togi
>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not allowed togive t
>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not allowed togive tha
>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not allowed togive that
>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not allowed togive that in
>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not allowed togive that inform
>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not allowed togive that informat
>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not allowed togive that informatio
>>Well, I'm sorry, dear,but we're not allowed togive that information.
but we're not allowed togive that information.
but we're not allowed togive that information.Ca
but we're not allowed togive that information.Can
but we're not allowed togive that information.Can I he
but we're not allowed togive that information.Can I help
but we're not allowed togive that information.Can I help y
but we're not allowed togive that information.Can I help you
but we're not allowed togive that information.Can I help you wit
but we're not allowed togive that information.Can I help you with
give that information.Can I help you with
give that information.Can I help you withan
give that information.Can I help you withanot
give that information.Can I help you withanother
give that information.Can I help you withanother ca
give that information.Can I help you withanother call
give that information.Can I help you withanother call?
>>
>> C
>> Clo
>> Closing
>> Closing u
>> Closing up,
>> Closing up, k
>> Closing up, kid.
>> Closing up, kid.>>
>> Closing up, kid.>>He
>> Closing up, kid.>>Hell
>> Closing up, kid.>>Hello?
>> Y
>> You
>> You k
>> You kno
>> You know an
>> You know anyt
>> You know anythi
>> You know anything
>> You know anything abo
>> You know anything about
>> You know anything aboutth
>> You know anything aboutthat
>> You know anything aboutthat b
>> You know anything aboutthat bro
>> You know anything aboutthat broken
>> You know anything aboutthat broken wi
>> You know anything aboutthat broken wind
>> You know anything aboutthat broken window
>> You know anything aboutthat broken window ove
>> You know anything aboutthat broken window over
>> You know anything aboutthat broken window over th
>> You know anything aboutthat broken window over ther
>> You know anything aboutthat broken window over there
>> You know anything aboutthat broken window over thereat R
>> You know anything aboutthat broken window over thereat Rec
>> You know anything aboutthat broken window over thereat Recor
>> You know anything aboutthat broken window over thereat Record
>> You know anything aboutthat broken window over thereat Record City
>> You know anything aboutthat broken window over thereat Record City?
You
You lo
You look
You look f
You look famil
You look familia
You look familiar,
You look familiar,wh
You look familiar,what
You look familiar,what's
You look familiar,what's you
You look familiar,what's your
You look familiar,what's your na
You look familiar,what's your name
You look familiar,what's your name?
You look familiar,what's your name?>>
You look familiar,what's your name?>> K
You look familiar,what's your name?>> Kat
You look familiar,what's your name?>> Kathy.
what's your name?>> Kathy.
what's your name?>> Kathy.>> K
what's your name?>> Kathy.>> Kat
what's your name?>> Kathy.>> Kathy
what's your name?>> Kathy.>> Kathy,
what's your name?>> Kathy.>> Kathy, huh?
>> Kathy.>> Kathy, huh?
>> Kathy.>> Kathy, huh?Wh
>> Kathy.>> Kathy, huh?Wher
>> Kathy.>> Kathy, huh?Where
>> Kathy.>> Kathy, huh?Where do
>> Kathy.>> Kathy, huh?Where do you
>> Kathy.>> Kathy, huh?Where do you l
>> Kathy.>> Kathy, huh?Where do you liv
>> Kathy.>> Kathy, huh?Where do you live,
>> Kathy.>> Kathy, huh?Where do you live, Kat
>> Kathy.>> Kathy, huh?Where do you live, Kathy
>> Kathy.>> Kathy, huh?Where do you live, Kathy?
>> O
>> Ove
>> Over
>> Over th
>> Over there.
>> Over there.>>
>> Over there.>> W
>> Over there.>> Why
>> Over there.>> Why don
>> Over there.>> Why don't
>> Over there.>> Why don't w
>> Over there.>> Why don't we
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a l
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a lit
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a little
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a littletr
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a littletrip
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a littletrip tog
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a littletrip toget
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a littletrip togethe
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a littletrip together,
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sou
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sound
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sound g
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sound goo
>> Over there.>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sound good?
>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sound good?
>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sound good?>>
>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sound good?>> L
>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sound good?>> Loo
>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sound good?>> Look
>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sound good?>> Look it,
>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sound good?>> Look it, mi
>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sound good?>> Look it, mist
>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sound good?>> Look it, mister
>> Why don't we take a littletrip together, sound good?>> Look it, mister...
>>
>> W
>> Wai
>> Wait, y
>> Wait, you
>> Wait, you k
>> Wait, you kid
>> Wait, you kid!
>> Wait, you kid!He
>> Wait, you kid!Hey,
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, y
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you s
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you sto
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop ri
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right th
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right ther
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right there,
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right there, kid
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right there, kid!
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right there, kid!Yo
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right there, kid!You
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right there, kid!You st
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right there, kid!You stop r
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right there, kid!You stop rig
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right there, kid!You stop right
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right there, kid!You stop right t
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right there, kid!You stop right there
>> Wait, you kid!Hey, you stop right there, kid!You stop right there!
>>
>> C
>> Com
>> Come on
>> Come on,
>> Come on, Ja
>> Come on, Jame
>> Come on, James,
>> Come on, James,we
>> Come on, James,we g
>> Come on, James,we got t
>> Come on, James,we got to
>> Come on, James,we got to go
>> Come on, James,we got to go!
>> Come on, James,we got to go!Samm
>> Come on, James,we got to go!Sammy,
>> Come on, James,we got to go!Sammy, M
>> Come on, James,we got to go!Sammy, May
>> Come on, James,we got to go!Sammy, Maybeth
>> Come on, James,we got to go!Sammy, Maybeth,
>> Come on, James,we got to go!Sammy, Maybeth, wa
>> Come on, James,we got to go!Sammy, Maybeth, wake
>> Come on, James,we got to go!Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!
we got to go!Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!
we got to go!Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> W
we got to go!Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> Wha
we got to go!Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What
we got to go!Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What ha
we got to go!Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What happen
we got to go!Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What happened
we got to go!Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What happened?
Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What happened?
Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What happened?>>
Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What happened?>> I
Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What happened?>> I'l
Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What happened?>> I'll
Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What happened?>> I'll tell
Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What happened?>> I'll tell y
Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What happened?>> I'll tell you
Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What happened?>> I'll tell you l
Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What happened?>> I'll tell you later
Sammy, Maybeth, wake up!>> What happened?>> I'll tell you later.
>> What happened?>> I'll tell you later.
>> What happened?>> I'll tell you later.Ge
>> What happened?>> I'll tell you later.Get
>> What happened?>> I'll tell you later.Get ev
>> What happened?>> I'll tell you later.Get everyb
>> What happened?>> I'll tell you later.Get everybod
>> What happened?>> I'll tell you later.Get everybody'
>> What happened?>> I'll tell you later.Get everybody's
>> What happened?>> I'll tell you later.Get everybody's stuf
>> What happened?>> I'll tell you later.Get everybody's stuff.
>> I'll tell you later.Get everybody's stuff.
>> I'll tell you later.Get everybody's stuff.>>
>> I'll tell you later.Get everybody's stuff.>> W
>> I'll tell you later.Get everybody's stuff.>> Whe
>> I'll tell you later.Get everybody's stuff.>> Where a
>> I'll tell you later.Get everybody's stuff.>> Where are
>> I'll tell you later.Get everybody's stuff.>> Where are w
>> I'll tell you later.Get everybody's stuff.>> Where are we
>> I'll tell you later.Get everybody's stuff.>> Where are we goin
>> I'll tell you later.Get everybody's stuff.>> Where are we going?
Get everybody's stuff.>> Where are we going?
Get everybody's stuff.>> Where are we going?>>
Get everybody's stuff.>> Where are we going?>> N
Get everybody's stuff.>> Where are we going?>> Now
Get everybody's stuff.>> Where are we going?>> Now, Ja
Get everybody's stuff.>> Where are we going?>> Now, Jame
Get everybody's stuff.>> Where are we going?>> Now, James!
(c
(car
(car d
(car doo
(car door cl
(car door clos
(car door closin
(car door closing)
(b
(bir
(birds
(birds c
(birds chirp
(birds chirpin
(birds chirping)
Ja
Jame
James?
Yo
You
You aw
You awake?
>>
>> I
>> It'
>> It's st
>> It's stil
>> It's still
>> It's still tr
>> It's still true.
>>
>> A
>> All
>> All rig
>> All right
>> All right.
>> All right.Se
>> All right.See,
>> All right.See, thi
>> All right.See, this
>> All right.See, this is
>> All right.See, this is w
>> All right.See, this is where
>> All right.See, this is where w
>> All right.See, this is where we
>> All right.See, this is where we ar
>> All right.See, this is where we are
>> All right.See, this is where we arein P
>> All right.See, this is where we arein Pee
>> All right.See, this is where we arein Peewa
>> All right.See, this is where we arein Peewauk
>> All right.See, this is where we arein Peewauket.
See, this is where we arein Peewauket.
See, this is where we arein Peewauket.We
See, this is where we arein Peewauket.We'r
See, this is where we arein Peewauket.We're
See, this is where we arein Peewauket.We're go
See, this is where we arein Peewauket.We're gonna
See, this is where we arein Peewauket.We're gonna wa
See, this is where we arein Peewauket.We're gonna walk
See, this is where we arein Peewauket.We're gonna walk a
See, this is where we arein Peewauket.We're gonna walk along
See, this is where we arein Peewauket.We're gonna walk along h
See, this is where we arein Peewauket.We're gonna walk along her
See, this is where we arein Peewauket.We're gonna walk along here,
in Peewauket.We're gonna walk along here,
in Peewauket.We're gonna walk along here,Hi
in Peewauket.We're gonna walk along here,High
in Peewauket.We're gonna walk along here,Highwa
in Peewauket.We're gonna walk along here,Highway On
in Peewauket.We're gonna walk along here,Highway One,
in Peewauket.We're gonna walk along here,Highway One, u
in Peewauket.We're gonna walk along here,Highway One, unt
in Peewauket.We're gonna walk along here,Highway One, until w
in Peewauket.We're gonna walk along here,Highway One, until we
in Peewauket.We're gonna walk along here,Highway One, until we ge
in Peewauket.We're gonna walk along here,Highway One, until we get
We're gonna walk along here,Highway One, until we get
We're gonna walk along here,Highway One, until we getto
We're gonna walk along here,Highway One, until we getto B
We're gonna walk along here,Highway One, until we getto Bri
We're gonna walk along here,Highway One, until we getto Bridgep
We're gonna walk along here,Highway One, until we getto Bridgepor
We're gonna walk along here,Highway One, until we getto Bridgeport.
Highway One, until we getto Bridgeport.
Highway One, until we getto Bridgeport.>>
Highway One, until we getto Bridgeport.>> W
Highway One, until we getto Bridgeport.>> What
Highway One, until we getto Bridgeport.>> What ab
Highway One, until we getto Bridgeport.>> What abou
Highway One, until we getto Bridgeport.>> What about
Highway One, until we getto Bridgeport.>> What about Mama
Highway One, until we getto Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?
to Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?
to Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?>>
to Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?>> M
to Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?>> Mam
to Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?>> Mama
to Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?>> Mama will
to Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?>> Mama will k
to Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?>> Mama will kno
to Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know
to Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we w
to Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we wen
to Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went
to Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on
to Bridgeport.>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on to
>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on to
>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on toAu
>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on toAunt
>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cil
>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla
>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's
>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's,
>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and
>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and th
>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that
>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that's
>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that's whe
>> What about Mama?>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that's where
>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that's where
>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that's wheresh
>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'
>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll c
>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll com
>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come
>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to
>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to fin
>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to find
>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to find us
>> Mama will know we went on toAunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to find us.
Aunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to find us.
Aunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to find us.>>
Aunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to find us.>> O
Aunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to find us.>> Okay,
Aunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to find us.>> Okay, b
Aunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to find us.>> Okay, but
Aunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to find us.>> Okay, but w
Aunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to find us.>> Okay, but why a
Aunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to find us.>> Okay, but why are
Aunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to find us.>> Okay, but why aren'
Aunt Cilla's, and that's whereshe'll come to find us.>> Okay, but why aren't
she'll come to find us.>> Okay, but why aren't
she'll come to find us.>> Okay, but why aren'twe t
she'll come to find us.>> Okay, but why aren'twe tak
she'll come to find us.>> Okay, but why aren'twe takin
she'll come to find us.>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking
she'll come to find us.>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the
she'll come to find us.>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the bu
she'll come to find us.>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the bus?
>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the bus?
>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the bus?>>
>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the bus?>> B
>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the bus?>> Becau
>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the bus?>> Because
>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the bus?>> Because w
>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the bus?>> Because we'
>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the bus?>> Because we've o
>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the bus?>> Because we've onl
>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the bus?>> Because we've only
>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the bus?>> Because we've only go
>> Okay, but why aren'twe taking the bus?>> Because we've only got
we taking the bus?>> Because we've only got
we taking the bus?>> Because we've only got$9 a
we taking the bus?>> Because we've only got$9 all
we taking the bus?>> Because we've only got$9 all t
we taking the bus?>> Because we've only got$9 all tog
we taking the bus?>> Because we've only got$9 all togethe
we taking the bus?>> Because we've only got$9 all together.
>> Because we've only got$9 all together.
>> Because we've only got$9 all together.>>
>> Because we've only got$9 all together.>> $
>> Because we've only got$9 all together.>> $9?!
We s
We sho
We shoul
We shouldn
We shouldn't h
We shouldn't hav
We shouldn't have
We shouldn't have ha
We shouldn't have had
We shouldn't have hadsu
We shouldn't have hadsupp
We shouldn't have hadsupper
We shouldn't have hadsupper l
We shouldn't have hadsupper last
We shouldn't have hadsupper last ni
We shouldn't have hadsupper last nigh
We shouldn't have hadsupper last night.
We shouldn't have hadsupper last night.>>
We shouldn't have hadsupper last night.>> B
We shouldn't have hadsupper last night.>> But
We shouldn't have hadsupper last night.>> But w
We shouldn't have hadsupper last night.>> But we di
We shouldn't have hadsupper last night.>> But we did.
supper last night.>> But we did.
supper last night.>> But we did.So i
supper last night.>> But we did.So it'
supper last night.>> But we did.So it's
supper last night.>> But we did.So it's no
supper last night.>> But we did.So it's no goo
supper last night.>> But we did.So it's no good
supper last night.>> But we did.So it's no good th
supper last night.>> But we did.So it's no good thin
supper last night.>> But we did.So it's no good thinking
>> But we did.So it's no good thinking
>> But we did.So it's no good thinkingif w
>> But we did.So it's no good thinkingif we
>> But we did.So it's no good thinkingif we di
>> But we did.So it's no good thinkingif we didn
>> But we did.So it's no good thinkingif we didn't.
We
We c
We can't
We can't g
We can't go
We can't go ba
We can't go back
We can't go backand
We can't go backand we
We can't go backand we g
We can't go backand we got
We can't go backand we got to
We can't go backand we got to go
We can't go backand we got to go s
We can't go backand we got to go som
We can't go backand we got to go somewhe
We can't go backand we got to go somewhere
We can't go backand we got to go somewhere.
We can't go backand we got to go somewhere.We
We can't go backand we got to go somewhere.We'r
We can't go backand we got to go somewhere.We're
We can't go backand we got to go somewhere.We're go
We can't go backand we got to go somewhere.We're gonna
We can't go backand we got to go somewhere.We're gonna ha
We can't go backand we got to go somewhere.We're gonna have
We can't go backand we got to go somewhere.We're gonna have t
We can't go backand we got to go somewhere.We're gonna have to wa
We can't go backand we got to go somewhere.We're gonna have to walk
We can't go backand we got to go somewhere.We're gonna have to walk.
Ma
Mayb
Maybet
Maybeth?
Maybeth?>>
Maybeth?>> T
Maybeth?>> Tha
Maybeth?>> That's
Maybeth?>> That's fi
Maybeth?>> That's fine
Maybeth?>> That's fine,
Maybeth?>> That's fine, Dice
Maybeth?>> That's fine, Dicey.
>>
>> H
>> How
>> How far
>> How far i
>> How far is
>> How far is it
>> How far is it?
>> How far is it?I do
>> How far is it?I don'
>> How far is it?I don't
>> How far is it?I don't kn
>> How far is it?I don't know f
>> How far is it?I don't know for
>> How far is it?I don't know for s
>> How far is it?I don't know for sur
>> How far is it?I don't know for sure.
>> How far is it?I don't know for sure.It'l
>> How far is it?I don't know for sure.It'll
>> How far is it?I don't know for sure.It'll be
>> How far is it?I don't know for sure.It'll be h
>> How far is it?I don't know for sure.It'll be hard.
I don't know for sure.It'll be hard.
I don't know for sure.It'll be hard.We
I don't know for sure.It'll be hard.We h
I don't know for sure.It'll be hard.We have
I don't know for sure.It'll be hard.We have to
I don't know for sure.It'll be hard.We have to c
I don't know for sure.It'll be hard.We have to car
I don't know for sure.It'll be hard.We have to carry a
I don't know for sure.It'll be hard.We have to carry as
I don't know for sure.It'll be hard.We have to carry as li
I don't know for sure.It'll be hard.We have to carry as litt
I don't know for sure.It'll be hard.We have to carry as little
It'll be hard.We have to carry as little
It'll be hard.We have to carry as littleas
It'll be hard.We have to carry as littleas p
It'll be hard.We have to carry as littleas possi
It'll be hard.We have to carry as littleas possibl
It'll be hard.We have to carry as littleas possible.
We have to carry as littleas possible.
We have to carry as littleas possible.Just
We have to carry as littleas possible.Just o
We have to carry as littleas possible.Just one
We have to carry as littleas possible.Just one b
We have to carry as littleas possible.Just one bag f
We have to carry as littleas possible.Just one bag for
We have to carry as littleas possible.Just one bag for a
We have to carry as littleas possible.Just one bag for all
We have to carry as littleas possible.Just one bag for all of
We have to carry as littleas possible.Just one bag for all of us
We have to carry as littleas possible.Just one bag for all of us.
as possible.Just one bag for all of us.
as possible.Just one bag for all of us.>>
as possible.Just one bag for all of us.>> C
as possible.Just one bag for all of us.>> Can I
as possible.Just one bag for all of us.>> Can I b
as possible.Just one bag for all of us.>> Can I bri
as possible.Just one bag for all of us.>> Can I bring
as possible.Just one bag for all of us.>> Can I bring my
as possible.Just one bag for all of us.>> Can I bring my bo
as possible.Just one bag for all of us.>> Can I bring my book
as possible.Just one bag for all of us.>> Can I bring my book?
Just one bag for all of us.>> Can I bring my book?
Just one bag for all of us.>> Can I bring my book?>>
Just one bag for all of us.>> Can I bring my book?>> N
Just one bag for all of us.>> Can I bring my book?>> No.
>> Can I bring my book?>> No.
>> Can I bring my book?>> No.>>
>> Can I bring my book?>> No.>> E
>> Can I bring my book?>> No.>> Eve
>> Can I bring my book?>> No.>> Everybo
>> Can I bring my book?>> No.>> Everybody
>> Can I bring my book?>> No.>> Everybody p
>> Can I bring my book?>> No.>> Everybody put
>> Can I bring my book?>> No.>> Everybody put on
>> No.>> Everybody put on
>> No.>> Everybody put oncl
>> No.>> Everybody put onclea
>> No.>> Everybody put onclean
>> No.>> Everybody put onclean sock
>> No.>> Everybody put onclean socks.
>> Everybody put onclean socks.
>> Everybody put onclean socks.>>
>> Everybody put onclean socks.>> W
>> Everybody put onclean socks.>> Why
>> Everybody put onclean socks.>> Why?
clean socks.>> Why?
clean socks.>> Why?It
clean socks.>> Why?It's
clean socks.>> Why?It's hot
clean socks.>> Why?It's hotte
clean socks.>> Why?It's hotter
clean socks.>> Why?It's hotter wi
clean socks.>> Why?It's hotter with s
clean socks.>> Why?It's hotter with soc
clean socks.>> Why?It's hotter with socks
clean socks.>> Why?It's hotter with socks o
clean socks.>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.
>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.
>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.>> B
>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.>> Bec
>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.>> Becau
>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.>> Because
>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you
>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'l
>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll
>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll ge
>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll get bl
>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll get blis
>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll get bliste
>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll get blisters
>> Why?It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll get blisters.
It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll get blisters.
It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll get blisters.>>
It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I
It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm n
It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not
It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not g
It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not goi
It's hotter with socks on.>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not going!
>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not going!
>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not going!>>
>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not going!>> W
>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not going!>> What
>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not going!>> What ar
>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not going!>> What are
>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not going!>> What are yo
>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not going!>> What are you go
>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not going!>> What are you gonn
>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not going!>> What are you gonna
>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not going!>> What are you gonna do
>> Because you'll get blisters.>> I'm not going!>> What are you gonna do?
>> I'm not going!>> What are you gonna do?
>> I'm not going!>> What are you gonna do?>>
>> I'm not going!>> What are you gonna do?>> W
>> I'm not going!>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait
>> I'm not going!>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait he
>> I'm not going!>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here
>> I'm not going!>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here f
>> I'm not going!>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for M
>> I'm not going!>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mam
>> I'm not going!>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mama.
>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mama.
>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mama.Not
>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mama.Not he
>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mama.Not here
>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mama.Not here e
>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mama.Not here exact
>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mama.Not here exactly
>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mama.Not here exactly,
>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mama.Not here exactly, in
>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mama.Not here exactly, in the
>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mama.Not here exactly, in the c
>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mama.Not here exactly, in the car
>> What are you gonna do?>> Wait here for Mama.Not here exactly, in the car.
>>
>> S
>> Sam
>> Sammy..
>> Sammy...
..
...
... Mama
... Mama's
... Mama's n
... Mama's not
... Mama's not com
... Mama's not comin
... Mama's not coming
... Mama's not coming ba
... Mama's not coming back h
... Mama's not coming back her
... Mama's not coming back here.
... Mama's not coming back here.That
... Mama's not coming back here.That's
... Mama's not coming back here.That's w
... Mama's not coming back here.That's wha
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I th
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I thin
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I think.
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I think.I
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I think.I th
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I think.I thin
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I think.I think ma
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I think.I think mayb
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I think.I think maybe
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I think.I think maybe sh
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I think.I think maybe she's
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I think.I think maybe she's fo
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I think.I think maybe she's forg
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I think.I think maybe she's forgot
... Mama's not coming back here.That's what I think.I think maybe she's forgotten.
That's what I think.I think maybe she's forgotten.
That's what I think.I think maybe she's forgotten.>>
That's what I think.I think maybe she's forgotten.>> M
That's what I think.I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama
That's what I think.I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wo
That's what I think.I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama woul
That's what I think.I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn
That's what I think.I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn't f
That's what I think.I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn't for
That's what I think.I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn't forge
That's what I think.I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn't forget
That's what I think.I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn't forget me.
I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn't forget me.
I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>>
I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> N
I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No,
I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she
I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she w
I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she wou
I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she would
I think maybe she's forgotten.>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she wouldn't.
>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she wouldn't.
>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she wouldn't.She'
>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she wouldn't.She's
>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she wouldn't.She's fo
>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she wouldn't.She's forg
>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she wouldn't.She's forgotte
>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she wouldn't.She's forgotten
>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she wouldn't.She's forgotten wh
>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she wouldn't.She's forgotten wher
>> Mama wouldn't forget me.>> No, she wouldn't.She's forgotten where
>> No, she wouldn't.She's forgotten where
>> No, she wouldn't.She's forgotten wherewe a
>> No, she wouldn't.She's forgotten wherewe are
>> No, she wouldn't.She's forgotten wherewe are,
>> No, she wouldn't.She's forgotten wherewe are, I
>> No, she wouldn't.She's forgotten wherewe are, I thin
>> No, she wouldn't.She's forgotten wherewe are, I think.
So i
So if
So if we
So if we g
So if we go on
So if we go on t
So if we go on to
So if we go on to Au
So if we go on to Aunt C
So if we go on to Aunt Cil
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's,
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's,that
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's,that's
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's,that's w
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's,that's whe
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's,that's where s
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's,that's where she
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's,that's where she'l
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's,that's where she'll
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's,that's where she'llprob
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's,that's where she'llprobab
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's,that's where she'llprobably
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's,that's where she'llprobably b
So if we go on to Aunt Cilla's,that's where she'llprobably be.
that's where she'llprobably be.
that's where she'llprobably be.We
that's where she'llprobably be.We h
that's where she'llprobably be.We hav
that's where she'llprobably be.We have to
that's where she'llprobably be.We have to g
that's where she'llprobably be.We have to go
that's where she'llprobably be.We have to go fi
that's where she'llprobably be.We have to go find h
that's where she'llprobably be.We have to go find her
that's where she'llprobably be.We have to go find her.
probably be.We have to go find her.
probably be.We have to go find her.>>
probably be.We have to go find her.>> I
probably be.We have to go find her.>> I d
probably be.We have to go find her.>> I don't
probably be.We have to go find her.>> I don't w
probably be.We have to go find her.>> I don't wan
probably be.We have to go find her.>> I don't want
probably be.We have to go find her.>> I don't want to.
We have to go find her.>> I don't want to.
We have to go find her.>> I don't want to.>> I
We have to go find her.>> I don't want to.>> I d
We have to go find her.>> I don't want to.>> I do
We have to go find her.>> I don't want to.>> I do no
We have to go find her.>> I don't want to.>> I do not wa
We have to go find her.>> I don't want to.>> I do not want
We have to go find her.>> I don't want to.>> I do not want t
We have to go find her.>> I don't want to.>> I do not want to
We have to go find her.>> I don't want to.>> I do not want to eith
We have to go find her.>> I don't want to.>> I do not want to either
We have to go find her.>> I don't want to.>> I do not want to either,
>> I don't want to.>> I do not want to either,
>> I don't want to.>> I do not want to either,bu
>> I don't want to.>> I do not want to either,but
>> I don't want to.>> I do not want to either,but we
>> I don't want to.>> I do not want to either,but we h
>> I don't want to.>> I do not want to either,but we have
>> I don't want to.>> I do not want to either,but we have to
>> I don't want to.>> I do not want to either,but we have to.
>> I do not want to either,but we have to.
>> I do not want to either,but we have to.>>
>> I do not want to either,but we have to.>> N
>> I do not want to either,but we have to.>> No,
>> I do not want to either,but we have to.>> No, we
>> I do not want to either,but we have to.>> No, we do
>> I do not want to either,but we have to.>> No, we don'
>> I do not want to either,but we have to.>> No, we don't!
but we have to.>> No, we don't!
but we have to.>> No, we don't!>>
but we have to.>> No, we don't!>> T
but we have to.>> No, we don't!>> Then
but we have to.>> No, we don't!>> Then I'
but we have to.>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll
but we have to.>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll c
but we have to.>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll carry
but we have to.>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll carry y
but we have to.>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll carry you
but we have to.>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll carry you!
>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll carry you!
>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll carry you!>>
>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll carry you!>> I
>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'l
>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll
>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick
>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick y
>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick you
>> No, we don't!>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick you!
>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick you!
>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick you!>>
>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick you!>> D
>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick you!>> Don
>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick you!>> Don't y
>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you
>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you u
>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you und
>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you underst
>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you understan
>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you understand?
>> Then I'll carry you!>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you understand?!
>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you understand?!
>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you understand?!Sh
>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you understand?!She'
>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you understand?!She's no
>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you understand?!She's not
>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you understand?!She's not co
>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you understand?!She's not comi
>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you understand?!She's not coming b
>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you understand?!She's not coming bac
>> I'll kick you!>> Don't you understand?!She's not coming back!
>> Don't you understand?!She's not coming back!
>> Don't you understand?!She's not coming back!No
>> Don't you understand?!She's not coming back!Not
>> Don't you understand?!She's not coming back!Not he
>> Don't you understand?!She's not coming back!Not here!
>>
>> H
>> Hey
>> Hey, lo
>> Hey, look
>> Hey, look!
>> Hey, look!♪
>>
>> O
>> Oh no
>> Oh no.
>> Oh no.>>
>> Oh no.>> D
>> Oh no.>> Do
>> Oh no.>> Do you
>> Oh no.>> Do you th
>> Oh no.>> Do you thin
>> Oh no.>> Do you think
>> Oh no.>> Do you think they
>> Oh no.>> Do you think they'r
>> Oh no.>> Do you think they're
>> Oh no.>> Do you think they'relo
>> Oh no.>> Do you think they'relook
>> Oh no.>> Do you think they'relooking
>> Oh no.>> Do you think they'relooking fo
>> Oh no.>> Do you think they'relooking for
>> Oh no.>> Do you think they'relooking for us
>> Oh no.>> Do you think they'relooking for us?
>> Do you think they'relooking for us?
>> Do you think they'relooking for us?>> W
>> Do you think they'relooking for us?>> Wha
>> Do you think they'relooking for us?>> What
>> Do you think they'relooking for us?>> What ar
>> Do you think they'relooking for us?>> What are th
>> Do you think they'relooking for us?>> What are they
>> Do you think they'relooking for us?>> What are they d
>> Do you think they'relooking for us?>> What are they doi
>> Do you think they'relooking for us?>> What are they doing,
>> Do you think they'relooking for us?>> What are they doing, Di
>> Do you think they'relooking for us?>> What are they doing, Dice
>> Do you think they'relooking for us?>> What are they doing, Dicey?
looking for us?>> What are they doing, Dicey?
looking for us?>> What are they doing, Dicey?>> W
looking for us?>> What are they doing, Dicey?>> We
looking for us?>> What are they doing, Dicey?>> We go
looking for us?>> What are they doing, Dicey?>> We got
looking for us?>> What are they doing, Dicey?>> We got to g
looking for us?>> What are they doing, Dicey?>> We got to go.
>> What are they doing, Dicey?>> We got to go.
>> What are they doing, Dicey?>> We got to go.Samm
>> What are they doing, Dicey?>> We got to go.Sammy,
>> What are they doing, Dicey?>> We got to go.Sammy, r
>> What are they doing, Dicey?>> We got to go.Sammy, rig
>> What are they doing, Dicey?>> We got to go.Sammy, right n
>> What are they doing, Dicey?>> We got to go.Sammy, right now
>> What are they doing, Dicey?>> We got to go.Sammy, right now.
>>
>> N
>> No,
>> No, Dic
>> No, Dicey
>> No, Dicey!
>> No, Dicey!>> C
>> No, Dicey!>> Com
>> No, Dicey!>> Come
>> No, Dicey!>> Come on
>> No, Dicey!>> Come on, wa
>> No, Dicey!>> Come on, walk
>> No, Dicey!>> Come on, walk.
(e
(eng
(engine
(engine ru
(engine rumb
(engine rumbli
(engine rumbling)
(h
(hor
(horn ho
(horn honk
(horn honkin
(horn honking)
♪
(b
(bel
(bell
(bell di
(bell dingin
(bell dinging)
(s
(scr
(screa
(screaming
(screaming)
(screaming)>>
(screaming)>> S
(screaming)>> Sto
(screaming)>> Stop it
(screaming)>> Stop it o
(screaming)>> Stop it or
(screaming)>> Stop it or yo
(screaming)>> Stop it or you're
(screaming)>> Stop it or you're g
(screaming)>> Stop it or you're gon
(screaming)>> Stop it or you're gonna
(screaming)>> Stop it or you're gonna die
(screaming)>> Stop it or you're gonna die!
(screaming)>> Stop it or you're gonna die!>> A
(screaming)>> Stop it or you're gonna die!>> Ahh
(screaming)>> Stop it or you're gonna die!>> Ahh!
>>
>> D
>> Dic
>> Dicey
>> Dicey!
>>
>> ♪
>> ♪ The
>> ♪ The a
>> ♪ The ant
>> ♪ The ants
>> ♪ The ants go m
>> ♪ The ants go mar
>> ♪ The ants go march
>> ♪ The ants go marchin
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪♪
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ O
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by on
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hu
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah ♪
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ H
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hur
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah
>> ♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ T
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The a
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go m
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go mar
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marchin
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching ♪
♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching ♪
♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ O
♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One
♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One b
♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by
♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one
♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hu
♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurr
♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah
♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah ♪
♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah ♪
♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ H
♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hur
♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurra
♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah
♪ The ants go marching ♪♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ T
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ant
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go m
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go march
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marchin
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching.
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching...
♪ One by one hurrah ♪♪ Hurrah ♪♪ The ants go marching... ♪
(d
(dog
(dog b
(dog bar
(dog barking
(dog barking i
(dog barking in
(dog barking in th
(dog barking in the di
(dog barking in the dist
(dog barking in the distan
(dog barking in the distance
(dog barking in the distance)
>>
>> M
>> Maybe
>> Maybe w
>> Maybe we
>> Maybe we co
>> Maybe we could
>> Maybe we could li
>> Maybe we could live
>> Maybe we could live h
>> Maybe we could live here.
(a
(all
(all g
(all groan
(all groanin
(all groaning)
>>
>> I
>> It'
>> It's
>> It's a be
>> It's a bed.
>> It's a bed.It
>> It's a bed.It's
>> It's a bed.It's b
>> It's a bed.It's bet
>> It's a bed.It's better
>> It's a bed.It's better th
>> It's a bed.It's better than
>> It's a bed.It's better than a
>> It's a bed.It's better than a bed
>> It's a bed.It's better than a bed.
>> It's a bed.It's better than a bed.It
>> It's a bed.It's better than a bed.It's
>> It's a bed.It's better than a bed.It's a
>> It's a bed.It's better than a bed.It's a clo
>> It's a bed.It's better than a bed.It's a cloud
>> It's a bed.It's better than a bed.It's a cloud.
(b
(bir
(birds
(birds chi
(birds chirp
(birds chirpin
(birds chirping)
(c
(cri
(crick
(crickets
(crickets ch
(crickets chir
(crickets chirpi
(crickets chirping)
(crickets chirping)>>
(crickets chirping)>> S
(crickets chirping)>> Sam
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, do
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, don'
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, don't
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, don't bu
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, don't burn i
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, don't burn it.
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, don't burn it.>> I
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, don't burn it.>> I l
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, don't burn it.>> I lik
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, don't burn it.>> I like
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, don't burn it.>> I like it t
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, don't burn it.>> I like it tha
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, don't burn it.>> I like it that
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, don't burn it.>> I like it that wa
(crickets chirping)>> Sammy, don't burn it.>> I like it that way.
>>
>> W
>> Wha
>> What's
>> What's th
>> What's this
>> What's this A
>> What's this Aunt
>> What's this Aunt Ci
>> What's this Aunt Cill
>> What's this Aunt Cilla
>> What's this Aunt Cillagonn
>> What's this Aunt Cillagonna
>> What's this Aunt Cillagonna be
>> What's this Aunt Cillagonna be l
>> What's this Aunt Cillagonna be like?
>> I
>> I d
>> I don
>> I don't
>> I don't kno
>> I don't know,
>> I don't know,bu
>> I don't know,but
>> I don't know,but sh
>> I don't know,but she
>> I don't know,but she live
>> I don't know,but she lives
>> I don't know,but she lives in
>> I don't know,but she lives in a
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big m
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big man
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big mansi
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big mansion
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big mansionri
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big mansionrigh
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big mansionright ne
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big mansionright next
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big mansionright next t
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big mansionright next to
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big mansionright next to the
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big mansionright next to the oc
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big mansionright next to the ocea
>> I don't know,but she lives in a big mansionright next to the ocean.
but she lives in a big mansionright next to the ocean.
but she lives in a big mansionright next to the ocean.>> H
but she lives in a big mansionright next to the ocean.>> How
but she lives in a big mansionright next to the ocean.>> How d
but she lives in a big mansionright next to the ocean.>> How do
but she lives in a big mansionright next to the ocean.>> How do you
but she lives in a big mansionright next to the ocean.>> How do you kn
but she lives in a big mansionright next to the ocean.>> How do you know
but she lives in a big mansionright next to the ocean.>> How do you know?
right next to the ocean.>> How do you know?
right next to the ocean.>> How do you know?>> M
right next to the ocean.>> How do you know?>> Mam
right next to the ocean.>> How do you know?>> Mama
right next to the ocean.>> How do you know?>> Mama sa
right next to the ocean.>> How do you know?>> Mama said.
>> How do you know?>> Mama said.
>> How do you know?>> Mama said.>>
>> How do you know?>> Mama said.>> B
>> How do you know?>> Mama said.>> But
>> How do you know?>> Mama said.>> But she
>> How do you know?>> Mama said.>> But she's
>> How do you know?>> Mama said.>> But she's n
>> How do you know?>> Mama said.>> But she's nev
>> How do you know?>> Mama said.>> But she's never e
>> How do you know?>> Mama said.>> But she's never eve
>> How do you know?>> Mama said.>> But she's never even
>> Mama said.>> But she's never even
>> Mama said.>> But she's never evenbe
>> Mama said.>> But she's never evenbeen
>> Mama said.>> But she's never evenbeen the
>> Mama said.>> But she's never evenbeen there
>> Mama said.>> But she's never evenbeen there.
>> But she's never evenbeen there.
>> But she's never evenbeen there.Ju
>> But she's never evenbeen there.Just
>> But she's never evenbeen there.Just t
>> But she's never evenbeen there.Just that
>> But she's never evenbeen there.Just that du
>> But she's never evenbeen there.Just that dumb
>> But she's never evenbeen there.Just that dumb C
>> But she's never evenbeen there.Just that dumb Chris
>> But she's never evenbeen there.Just that dumb Christm
>> But she's never evenbeen there.Just that dumb Christmas
>> But she's never evenbeen there.Just that dumb Christmas c
>> But she's never evenbeen there.Just that dumb Christmas card
been there.Just that dumb Christmas card
been there.Just that dumb Christmas cardev
been there.Just that dumb Christmas cardever
been there.Just that dumb Christmas cardevery
been there.Just that dumb Christmas cardevery year
been there.Just that dumb Christmas cardevery year.
(d
(dog
(dog b
(dog barki
(dog barking
(dog barking i
(dog barking in
(dog barking in the
(dog barking in the di
(dog barking in the dist
(dog barking in the distan
(dog barking in the distance)
>>
>> T
>> They'
>> They're
>> They're d
>> They're don
>> They're done.
>> I
>> I w
>> I wis
>> I wish
>> I wish we h
>> I wish we had
>> I wish we hadke
>> I wish we hadketc
>> I wish we hadketchu
>> I wish we hadketchup
>> I wish we hadketchup and
>> I wish we hadketchup and mu
>> I wish we hadketchup and must
>> I wish we hadketchup and mustar
>> I wish we hadketchup and mustard.
>> I wish we hadketchup and mustard.>>
>> I wish we hadketchup and mustard.>> A
>> I wish we hadketchup and mustard.>> And w
>> I wish we hadketchup and mustard.>> And wat
>> I wish we hadketchup and mustard.>> And water
>> I wish we hadketchup and mustard.>> And waterme
>> I wish we hadketchup and mustard.>> And watermelon
>> I wish we hadketchup and mustard.>> And watermelon fo
>> I wish we hadketchup and mustard.>> And watermelon for
>> I wish we hadketchup and mustard.>> And watermelon for de
>> I wish we hadketchup and mustard.>> And watermelon for desser
>> I wish we hadketchup and mustard.>> And watermelon for dessert.
ketchup and mustard.>> And watermelon for dessert.
ketchup and mustard.>> And watermelon for dessert.>>
ketchup and mustard.>> And watermelon for dessert.>> Y
ketchup and mustard.>> And watermelon for dessert.>> Yea
ketchup and mustard.>> And watermelon for dessert.>> Yeah,
>> And watermelon for dessert.>> Yeah,
>> And watermelon for dessert.>> Yeah,an
>> And watermelon for dessert.>> Yeah,and
>> And watermelon for dessert.>> Yeah,and a
>> And watermelon for dessert.>> Yeah,and a choc
>> And watermelon for dessert.>> Yeah,and a chocol
>> And watermelon for dessert.>> Yeah,and a chocolat
>> And watermelon for dessert.>> Yeah,and a chocolate
>> And watermelon for dessert.>> Yeah,and a chocolate sund
>> And watermelon for dessert.>> Yeah,and a chocolate sundae
>> Yeah,and a chocolate sundae
>> Yeah,and a chocolate sundaewith
>> Yeah,and a chocolate sundaewith w
>> Yeah,and a chocolate sundaewith whi
>> Yeah,and a chocolate sundaewith whipp
>> Yeah,and a chocolate sundaewith whipped c
>> Yeah,and a chocolate sundaewith whipped cre
>> Yeah,and a chocolate sundaewith whipped cream
and a chocolate sundaewith whipped cream
and a chocolate sundaewith whipped creaman
and a chocolate sundaewith whipped creamand
and a chocolate sundaewith whipped creamand a ch
and a chocolate sundaewith whipped creamand a cher
and a chocolate sundaewith whipped creamand a cherry
and a chocolate sundaewith whipped creamand a cherry o
and a chocolate sundaewith whipped creamand a cherry on to
and a chocolate sundaewith whipped creamand a cherry on top.
with whipped creamand a cherry on top.
with whipped creamand a cherry on top.>>
with whipped creamand a cherry on top.>> Y
with whipped creamand a cherry on top.>> Yea
with whipped creamand a cherry on top.>> Yeah, m
with whipped creamand a cherry on top.>> Yeah, me
with whipped creamand a cherry on top.>> Yeah, me to
with whipped creamand a cherry on top.>> Yeah, me too,
and a cherry on top.>> Yeah, me too,
and a cherry on top.>> Yeah, me too,I
and a cherry on top.>> Yeah, me too,I wi
and a cherry on top.>> Yeah, me too,I wish
and a cherry on top.>> Yeah, me too,I wish I h
and a cherry on top.>> Yeah, me too,I wish I had
and a cherry on top.>> Yeah, me too,I wish I had t
and a cherry on top.>> Yeah, me too,I wish I had tha
and a cherry on top.>> Yeah, me too,I wish I had that.
>> Yeah, me too,I wish I had that.
>> Yeah, me too,I wish I had that.>>
>> Yeah, me too,I wish I had that.>> I
>> Yeah, me too,I wish I had that.>> I w
>> Yeah, me too,I wish I had that.>> I wis
>> Yeah, me too,I wish I had that.>> I wish we
>> Yeah, me too,I wish I had that.>> I wish we h
>> Yeah, me too,I wish I had that.>> I wish we had
>> Yeah, me too,I wish I had that.>> I wish we had M
>> Yeah, me too,I wish I had that.>> I wish we had Mama.
♪
♪ T
♪ The
♪ The wat
♪ The water
♪ The water i
♪ The water is
♪ The water is wide
♪ The water is wide ♪
♪
♪ I
♪ I c
♪ I can
♪ I can't c
♪ I can't cro
♪ I can't cross
♪ I can't cross o
♪ I can't cross over
♪ I can't cross over ♪
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ A
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And n
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And neith
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And neither
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And neither h
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And neither hav
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And neither have ♪
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And neither have ♪♪
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And neither have ♪♪ I
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And neither have ♪♪ I w
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And neither have ♪♪ I wings
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And neither have ♪♪ I wings t
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And neither have ♪♪ I wings to
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And neither have ♪♪ I wings to fl
♪ I can't cross over ♪♪ And neither have ♪♪ I wings to fly ♪
(b
(bir
(birds
(birds chi
(birds chirp
(birds chirpin
(birds chirping)
(h
(hor
(horn ho
(horn honk
(horn honkin
(horn honking
(horn honking in t
(horn honking in the
(horn honking in the d
(horn honking in the dis
(horn honking in the distanc
(horn honking in the distance)
>>
>> I
>> It's
>> It's st
>> It's stil
>> It's still
>> It's still true
>> It's still true.
♪
>>
>> N
>> No, h
>> No, hon
>> No, honey
>> No, honey,
>> No, honey,we d
>> No, honey,we don
>> No, honey,we don't
>> No, honey,we don't h
>> No, honey,we don't have
>> No, honey,we don't have ti
>> No, honey,we don't have time
>> No, honey,we don't have time.
>>
>> U
>> Ugh
>> Ugh..
>> Ugh... he
>> Ugh... here
>> Ugh... here c
>> Ugh... here com
>> Ugh... here comes D
>> Ugh... here comes Dad
>> Ugh... here comes Daddy
>> Ugh... here comes Daddy.
>> Ugh... here comes Daddy.>>
>> Ugh... here comes Daddy.>> H
>> Ugh... here comes Daddy.>> Hon
>> Ugh... here comes Daddy.>> Honey,
>> Ugh... here comes Daddy.>> Honey, le
>> Ugh... here comes Daddy.>> Honey, let'
>> Ugh... here comes Daddy.>> Honey, let's
>> Ugh... here comes Daddy.>> Honey, let's go.
>>
>> W
>> We
>> We ca
>> We can't
>> We can't wa
>> We can't walk
>> We can't walk t
>> We can't walk the b
>> We can't walk the bri
>> We can't walk the bridg
>> We can't walk the bridge.
>> We can't walk the bridge.Th
>> We can't walk the bridge.The
>> We can't walk the bridge.The po
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police c
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police cou
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pic
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pick
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pick us
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pick us u
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pick us up.
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pick us up.>>
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pick us up.>> C
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pick us up.>> Cou
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pick us up.>> Could w
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pick us up.>> Could we
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pick us up.>> Could we ta
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pick us up.>> Could we take
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pick us up.>> Could we take a b
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pick us up.>> Could we take a boa
>> We can't walk the bridge.The police could pick us up.>> Could we take a boat?
>>
>> W
>> We ne
>> We neve
>> We never
>> We never st
>> We never stole
>> We never stole th
>> We never stole thin
>> We never stole things
>> We never stole things.
>> We never stole things.We
>> We never stole things.We d
>> We never stole things.We don't
>> We never stole things.We don't h
>> We never stole things.We don't hav
>> We never stole things.We don't have
>> We never stole things.We don't have to s
>> We never stole things.We don't have to ste
>> We never stole things.We don't have to steal
>> We never stole things.We don't have to steal.
>> We never stole things.We don't have to steal.>>
>> We never stole things.We don't have to steal.>> N
>> We never stole things.We don't have to steal.>> Not s
>> We never stole things.We don't have to steal.>> Not ste
>> We never stole things.We don't have to steal.>> Not steal
>> We never stole things.We don't have to steal.>> Not steal i
>> We never stole things.We don't have to steal.>> Not steal it.
Ju
Just
Just b
Just borro
Just borrow
Just borrow it
Just borrow it.
(d
(dog
(dog b
(dog bar
(dog barking
(dog barking)
>>
>> H
>> Hur
>> Hurry,
>> Hurry, hu
>> Hurry, hurr
>> Hurry, hurry.
>> Hurry, hurry.Ge
>> Hurry, hurry.Get
>> Hurry, hurry.Get to t
>> Hurry, hurry.Get to the
>> Hurry, hurry.Get to the b
>> Hurry, hurry.Get to the bac
>> Hurry, hurry.Get to the back.
>> Hurry, hurry.Get to the back.Co
>> Hurry, hurry.Get to the back.Come
>> Hurry, hurry.Get to the back.Come o
>> Hurry, hurry.Get to the back.Come on, l
>> Hurry, hurry.Get to the back.Come on, let
>> Hurry, hurry.Get to the back.Come on, let's
>> Hurry, hurry.Get to the back.Come on, let's g
>> Hurry, hurry.Get to the back.Come on, let's go.
Get to the back.Come on, let's go.
Get to the back.Come on, let's go.>>
Get to the back.Come on, let's go.>> I
Get to the back.Come on, let's go.>> I'm
Get to the back.Come on, let's go.>> I'm g
Get to the back.Come on, let's go.>> I'm going
Get to the back.Come on, let's go.>> I'm going,
Get to the back.Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'
Get to the back.Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'm
Get to the back.Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'm goin
Get to the back.Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'm going.
Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'm going.
Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'm going.(d
Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'm going.(dog
Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'm going.(dog b
Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'm going.(dog barki
Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'm going.(dog barking
Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'm going.(dog barking c
Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'm going.(dog barking con
Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'm going.(dog barking continu
Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'm going.(dog barking continues
Come on, let's go.>> I'm going, I'm going.(dog barking continues)
(c
(cri
(crick
(cricket
(crickets ch
(crickets chir
(crickets chirpi
(crickets chirping
(crickets chirping)
(owl
(owl h
(owl hoo
(owl hooti
(owl hooting)
>> Y
>> You
>> You k
>> You kno
>> You know wh
>> You know what
>> You know what?
>> You know what?Wh
>> You know what?What
>> You know what?What k
>> You know what?What kin
>> You know what?What kind of
>> You know what?What kind of p
>> You know what?What kind of peo
>> You know what?What kind of peopl
>> You know what?What kind of people
>> You know what?What kind of peoplego
>> You know what?What kind of peoplego o
>> You know what?What kind of peoplego off
>> You know what?What kind of peoplego off, th
>> You know what?What kind of peoplego off, thou
>> You know what?What kind of peoplego off, though
>> You know what?What kind of peoplego off, though?
Fi
Firs
First
First ou
First our fa
First our fath
First our father
First our father a
First our father and n
First our father and now
First our father and now M
First our father and now Mam
First our father and now Mama.
Wh
What
What do
What do yo
What do you
What do you th
What do you think,
What do you think, t
What do you think, the
What do you think, there
What do you think, there's
What do you think, there'sjust
What do you think, there'sjust s
What do you think, there'sjust som
What do you think, there'sjust somet
What do you think, there'sjust something
What do you think, there'sjust something w
What do you think, there'sjust something wro
What do you think, there'sjust something wrong
What do you think, there'sjust something wrong wit
What do you think, there'sjust something wrong with
What do you think, there'sjust something wrong with us
What do you think, there'sjust something wrong with us?
What do you think, there'sjust something wrong with us?>>
What do you think, there'sjust something wrong with us?>> I
What do you think, there'sjust something wrong with us?>> I d
What do you think, there'sjust something wrong with us?>> I don
What do you think, there'sjust something wrong with us?>> I don't k
What do you think, there'sjust something wrong with us?>> I don't kno
What do you think, there'sjust something wrong with us?>> I don't know.
just something wrong with us?>> I don't know.
just something wrong with us?>> I don't know.I
just something wrong with us?>> I don't know.I do
just something wrong with us?>> I don't know.I don'
just something wrong with us?>> I don't know.I don't
just something wrong with us?>> I don't know.I don't care
just something wrong with us?>> I don't know.I don't care.
>>
>> D
>> Dic
>> Dicey?
>> Dicey?Do
>> Dicey?Do y
>> Dicey?Do you t
>> Dicey?Do you thi
>> Dicey?Do you think
>> Dicey?Do you think M
>> Dicey?Do you think Mama'
>> Dicey?Do you think Mama's
>> Dicey?Do you think Mama's de
>> Dicey?Do you think Mama's dead
>> Dicey?Do you think Mama's dead?
>>
>> I
>> I don
>> I don't
>> I don't k
>> I don't kno
>> I don't know.
Ho
How
How co
How could
How could I
How could I kn
How could I know
How could I know tha
How could I know that?
>> M
>> May
>> Maybe
>> Maybe s
>> Maybe she j
>> Maybe she jus
>> Maybe she just
>> Maybe she just go
>> Maybe she just got
>> Maybe she just gotki
>> Maybe she just gotkidn
>> Maybe she just gotkidnap
>> Maybe she just gotkidnappe
>> Maybe she just gotkidnapped.
>>
>> T
>> Tha
>> That ha
>> That happ
>> That happen
>> That happens
>> That happens to r
>> That happens to ric
>> That happens to rich
>> That happens to rich pe
>> That happens to rich people
>> That happens to rich people.
(s
(sig
(sighi
(sighing)
>>
>> S
>> Som
>> Some ki
>> Some kids
>> Some kids a
>> Some kids at
>> Some kids at scho
>> Some kids at school
>> Some kids at schoolsa
>> Some kids at schoolsaid
>> Some kids at schoolsaid t
>> Some kids at schoolsaid thing
>> Some kids at schoolsaid things
>> Some kids at schoolsaid things ab
>> Some kids at schoolsaid things abou
>> Some kids at schoolsaid things about Ma
>> Some kids at schoolsaid things about Mama
>> Some kids at schoolsaid things about Mama.
Ba
Bad
Bad th
Bad thin
Bad things,
Bad things,ab
Bad things,abou
Bad things,about no
Bad things,about not
Bad things,about not be
Bad things,about not bein
Bad things,about not being ma
Bad things,about not being marr
Bad things,about not being marrie
Bad things,about not being married.
>>
>> D
>> Did
>> Did the
>> Did they
>> Did they sa
>> Did they say
>> Did they say thin
>> Did they say things
>> Did they say things t
>> Did they say things to
>> Did they say things to Samm
>> Did they say things to Sammy?
>> Did they say things to Sammy?>>
>> Did they say things to Sammy?>> Y
>> Did they say things to Sammy?>> Yea
>> Did they say things to Sammy?>> Yeah.
>> Did they say things to Sammy?>> Yeah.I th
>> Did they say things to Sammy?>> Yeah.I thin
>> Did they say things to Sammy?>> Yeah.I think
>> Did they say things to Sammy?>> Yeah.I think he
>> Did they say things to Sammy?>> Yeah.I think he rea
>> Did they say things to Sammy?>> Yeah.I think he reall
>> Did they say things to Sammy?>> Yeah.I think he really
>> Did they say things to Sammy?>> Yeah.I think he really go
>> Did they say things to Sammy?>> Yeah.I think he really got it
>> Yeah.I think he really got it
>> Yeah.I think he really got itat
>> Yeah.I think he really got itat s
>> Yeah.I think he really got itat sch
>> Yeah.I think he really got itat schoo
>> Yeah.I think he really got itat school.
Some
Some k
Some kid
Some kids
Some kids said
Some kids said M
Some kids said Mam
Some kids said Mama
Some kids said Mama was
Some kids said Mama was cr
Some kids said Mama was craz
Some kids said Mama was crazy.
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>>
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> N
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not t
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me t
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me the
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't.
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't.>>
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't.>> T
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't.>> That'
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't.>> That's
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't.>> That's be
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't.>> That's beca
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't.>> That's because
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't.>> That's because yo
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't.>> That's because you
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't.>> That's because you ca
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't.>> That's because you can fi
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't.>> That's because you can figh
Some kids said Mama was crazy.>> Not to me they didn't.>> That's because you can fight.
Craz
Crazin
Crazines
Craziness
Craziness can
Craziness can ru
Craziness can run
Craziness can run in
Craziness can run inthe
Craziness can run inthe fa
Craziness can run inthe fami
Craziness can run inthe famili
Craziness can run inthe families,
Craziness can run inthe families, yo
Craziness can run inthe families, you
Craziness can run inthe families, you kn
Craziness can run inthe families, you know.
Craziness can run inthe families, you know.It
Craziness can run inthe families, you know.It's
Craziness can run inthe families, you know.It's h
Craziness can run inthe families, you know.It's her
Craziness can run inthe families, you know.It's heredit
Craziness can run inthe families, you know.It's hereditar
Craziness can run inthe families, you know.It's hereditary.
No
No m
No mat
No matter
No matter wh
No matter what
No matter what,
No matter what,we
No matter what,we'r
No matter what,we're al
No matter what,we're all
No matter what,we're all go
No matter what,we're all gonn
No matter what,we're all gonna di
No matter what,we're all gonna die.
No matter what,we're all gonna die.It
No matter what,we're all gonna die.It d
No matter what,we're all gonna die.It doe
No matter what,we're all gonna die.It doesn't
No matter what,we're all gonna die.It doesn't m
No matter what,we're all gonna die.It doesn't mat
No matter what,we're all gonna die.It doesn't matte
No matter what,we're all gonna die.It doesn't matter wh
No matter what,we're all gonna die.It doesn't matter what
No matter what,we're all gonna die.It doesn't matter what w
No matter what,we're all gonna die.It doesn't matter what we
No matter what,we're all gonna die.It doesn't matter what we do,
we're all gonna die.It doesn't matter what we do,
we're all gonna die.It doesn't matter what we do,do
we're all gonna die.It doesn't matter what we do,does
we're all gonna die.It doesn't matter what we do,does i
we're all gonna die.It doesn't matter what we do,does it?
♪
(thu
(thund
(thunder
(thunderin
(thundering)
(l
(lau
(laugh
(laughing)
(h
(hor
(horn
(horn ho
(horn honkin
(horn honking)
How
How mu
How much
How much m
How much money
How much money d
How much money do
How much money do we
How much money do we hav
How much money do we have?
How much money do we have?>>
How much money do we have?>> N
How much money do we have?>> Not
How much money do we have?>> Not muc
How much money do we have?>> Not much.
26 c
26 cen
26 cents.
26 cents.>>
26 cents.>> W
26 cents.>> Wel
26 cents.>> Well,
26 cents.>> Well, wha
26 cents.>> Well, what
26 cents.>> Well, what ar
26 cents.>> Well, what are
26 cents.>> Well, what are we g
26 cents.>> Well, what are we gon
26 cents.>> Well, what are we gonna
26 cents.>> Well, what are we gonna e
26 cents.>> Well, what are we gonna eat?
26 cents.>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>>
26 cents.>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I
26 cents.>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I d
26 cents.>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I don't
26 cents.>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I don't k
26 cents.>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I don't kno
26 cents.>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I don't know!
>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I don't know!
>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I don't know!We
>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I don't know!We'l
>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I don't know!We'll fi
>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I don't know!We'll find
>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I don't know!We'll find s
>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I don't know!We'll find som
>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I don't know!We'll find somethi
>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I don't know!We'll find something
>> Well, what are we gonna eat?>> I don't know!We'll find something.
>> I don't know!We'll find something.
>> I don't know!We'll find something.>>
>> I don't know!We'll find something.>> D
>> I don't know!We'll find something.>> Dic
>> I don't know!We'll find something.>> Dicey
>> I don't know!We'll find something.>> Dicey, we
>> I don't know!We'll find something.>> Dicey, we c
>> I don't know!We'll find something.>> Dicey, we can
>> I don't know!We'll find something.>> Dicey, we can't
We'll find something.>> Dicey, we can't
We'll find something.>> Dicey, we can'tdo
We'll find something.>> Dicey, we can'tdo t
We'll find something.>> Dicey, we can'tdo thi
We'll find something.>> Dicey, we can'tdo this an
We'll find something.>> Dicey, we can'tdo this anym
We'll find something.>> Dicey, we can'tdo this anymor
We'll find something.>> Dicey, we can'tdo this anymore.
>> Dicey, we can'tdo this anymore.
>> Dicey, we can'tdo this anymore.It
>> Dicey, we can'tdo this anymore.It's
>> Dicey, we can'tdo this anymore.It's n
>> Dicey, we can'tdo this anymore.It's not f
>> Dicey, we can'tdo this anymore.It's not fai
>> Dicey, we can'tdo this anymore.It's not fair
>> Dicey, we can'tdo this anymore.It's not fair to
do this anymore.It's not fair to
do this anymore.It's not fair toth
do this anymore.It's not fair tothe
do this anymore.It's not fair tothe litt
do this anymore.It's not fair tothe little
do this anymore.It's not fair tothe little k
do this anymore.It's not fair tothe little kid
do this anymore.It's not fair tothe little kids.
It's not fair tothe little kids.
It's not fair tothe little kids.>>
It's not fair tothe little kids.>> I
It's not fair tothe little kids.>> It'
It's not fair tothe little kids.>> It'll g
It's not fair tothe little kids.>> It'll get
It's not fair tothe little kids.>> It'll get b
It's not fair tothe little kids.>> It'll get bet
It's not fair tothe little kids.>> It'll get better.
the little kids.>> It'll get better.
the little kids.>> It'll get better.>>
the little kids.>> It'll get better.>> N
the little kids.>> It'll get better.>> No,
the little kids.>> It'll get better.>> No, it
the little kids.>> It'll get better.>> No, it wo
the little kids.>> It'll get better.>> No, it won'
the little kids.>> It'll get better.>> No, it won't.
>> It'll get better.>> No, it won't.
>> It'll get better.>> No, it won't.We
>> It'll get better.>> No, it won't.We g
>> It'll get better.>> No, it won't.We got
>> It'll get better.>> No, it won't.We got to
>> It'll get better.>> No, it won't.We got to ge
>> It'll get better.>> No, it won't.We got to get
>> It'll get better.>> No, it won't.We got to get he
>> It'll get better.>> No, it won't.We got to get help.
>> No, it won't.We got to get help.
>> No, it won't.We got to get help.>>
>> No, it won't.We got to get help.>> I
>> No, it won't.We got to get help.>> It'
>> No, it won't.We got to get help.>> It's ha
>> No, it won't.We got to get help.>> It's hard
>> No, it won't.We got to get help.>> It's hard t
>> No, it won't.We got to get help.>> It's hard to
>> No, it won't.We got to get help.>> It's hard to know
We got to get help.>> It's hard to know
We got to get help.>> It's hard to knowwh
We got to get help.>> It's hard to knowwho
We got to get help.>> It's hard to knowwho to t
We got to get help.>> It's hard to knowwho to tru
We got to get help.>> It's hard to knowwho to trust
We got to get help.>> It's hard to knowwho to trust,
We got to get help.>> It's hard to knowwho to trust, and
We got to get help.>> It's hard to knowwho to trust, and I
We got to get help.>> It's hard to knowwho to trust, and I ca
We got to get help.>> It's hard to knowwho to trust, and I can'
We got to get help.>> It's hard to knowwho to trust, and I can't
>> It's hard to knowwho to trust, and I can't
>> It's hard to knowwho to trust, and I can'tta
>> It's hard to knowwho to trust, and I can'ttake
>> It's hard to knowwho to trust, and I can'ttake a
>> It's hard to knowwho to trust, and I can'ttake any c
>> It's hard to knowwho to trust, and I can'ttake any cha
>> It's hard to knowwho to trust, and I can'ttake any chanc
>> It's hard to knowwho to trust, and I can'ttake any chances
>> It's hard to knowwho to trust, and I can'ttake any chances.
who to trust, and I can'ttake any chances.
who to trust, and I can'ttake any chances.Do
who to trust, and I can'ttake any chances.Do y
who to trust, and I can'ttake any chances.Do you u
who to trust, and I can'ttake any chances.Do you und
who to trust, and I can'ttake any chances.Do you under
who to trust, and I can'ttake any chances.Do you underst
who to trust, and I can'ttake any chances.Do you understand?
take any chances.Do you understand?
take any chances.Do you understand?>>
take any chances.Do you understand?>> W
take any chances.Do you understand?>> We'
take any chances.Do you understand?>> We're j
take any chances.Do you understand?>> We're jus
take any chances.Do you understand?>> We're just
take any chances.Do you understand?>> We're just ki
take any chances.Do you understand?>> We're just kids.
Do you understand?>> We're just kids.
Do you understand?>> We're just kids.We
Do you understand?>> We're just kids.We s
Do you understand?>> We're just kids.We shoul
Do you understand?>> We're just kids.We should
Do you understand?>> We're just kids.We should ha
Do you understand?>> We're just kids.We should have
Do you understand?>> We're just kids.We should have got
Do you understand?>> We're just kids.We should have got h
Do you understand?>> We're just kids.We should have got hel
Do you understand?>> We're just kids.We should have got help
>> We're just kids.We should have got help
>> We're just kids.We should have got helpfr
>> We're just kids.We should have got helpfrom
>> We're just kids.We should have got helpfrom the
>> We're just kids.We should have got helpfrom the v
>> We're just kids.We should have got helpfrom the ver
>> We're just kids.We should have got helpfrom the very
>> We're just kids.We should have got helpfrom the very begi
>> We're just kids.We should have got helpfrom the very beginn
>> We're just kids.We should have got helpfrom the very beginnin
>> We're just kids.We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.
We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.
We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.>>
We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.>> T
We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.>> Tha
We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.>> That's
We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.>> That's re
We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.>> That's real
We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.>> That's really
We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.>> That's really stu
We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.>> That's really stupi
We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.>> That's really stupid,
We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.>> That's really stupid, J
We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.>> That's really stupid, James
We should have got helpfrom the very beginning.>> That's really stupid, James!
from the very beginning.>> That's really stupid, James!
from the very beginning.>> That's really stupid, James!Yo
from the very beginning.>> That's really stupid, James!You
from the very beginning.>> That's really stupid, James!You know
from the very beginning.>> That's really stupid, James!You know w
from the very beginning.>> That's really stupid, James!You know we
from the very beginning.>> That's really stupid, James!You know we ca
from the very beginning.>> That's really stupid, James!You know we can't!
>> N
>> No,
>> No, I
>> No, I d
>> No, I don't
>> No, I don't k
>> No, I don't kno
>> No, I don't know.
>> No, I don't know.Anyt
>> No, I don't know.Anythi
>> No, I don't know.Anything
>> No, I don't know.Anything w
>> No, I don't know.Anything would
>> No, I don't know.Anything would b
>> No, I don't know.Anything would be
>> No, I don't know.Anything would be be
>> No, I don't know.Anything would be better
>> No, I don't know.Anything would be betterth
>> No, I don't know.Anything would be betterthan
>> No, I don't know.Anything would be betterthan t
>> No, I don't know.Anything would be betterthan thi
>> No, I don't know.Anything would be betterthan this.
Ev
Even
Even a
Even a fos
Even a foste
Even a foster
Even a foster ho
Even a foster home.
>>
>> W
>> We'
>> We'll
>> We'll mak
>> We'll make
>> We'll make it
>> We'll make it.
>> We'll make it.I'
>> We'll make it.I'll
>> We'll make it.I'll t
>> We'll make it.I'll think
>> We'll make it.I'll think o
>> We'll make it.I'll think of
>> We'll make it.I'll think of so
>> We'll make it.I'll think of someth
>> We'll make it.I'll think of somethin
>> We'll make it.I'll think of something.
>>
>> M
>> My
>> My stom
>> My stomac
>> My stomach
>> My stomach hu
>> My stomach hurts!
>> My stomach hurts!>>
>> My stomach hurts!>> M
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine,
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, t
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, too
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, too!
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, too!An
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, too!And
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, too!And I'
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, too!And I'll d
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, too!And I'll die
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, too!And I'll die i
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, too!And I'll die if
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, too!And I'll die if I do
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, too!And I'll die if I don'
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, too!And I'll die if I don't
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, too!And I'll die if I don't ea
>> My stomach hurts!>> Mine, too!And I'll die if I don't eat.
>> Mine, too!And I'll die if I don't eat.
>> Mine, too!And I'll die if I don't eat.>> Y
>> Mine, too!And I'll die if I don't eat.>> You
>> Mine, too!And I'll die if I don't eat.>> You w
>> Mine, too!And I'll die if I don't eat.>> You won
>> Mine, too!And I'll die if I don't eat.>> You won't d
>> Mine, too!And I'll die if I don't eat.>> You won't die
>> Mine, too!And I'll die if I don't eat.>> You won't die.
And I'll die if I don't eat.>> You won't die.
And I'll die if I don't eat.>> You won't die.No
And I'll die if I don't eat.>> You won't die.Not
And I'll die if I don't eat.>> You won't die.Not in
And I'll die if I don't eat.>> You won't die.Not in o
And I'll die if I don't eat.>> You won't die.Not in one d
And I'll die if I don't eat.>> You won't die.Not in one day
And I'll die if I don't eat.>> You won't die.Not in one day.
>> You won't die.Not in one day.
>> You won't die.Not in one day.St
>> You won't die.Not in one day.Star
>> You won't die.Not in one day.Starva
>> You won't die.Not in one day.Starvation
>> You won't die.Not in one day.Starvation t
>> You won't die.Not in one day.Starvation tak
>> You won't die.Not in one day.Starvation takes
>> You won't die.Not in one day.Starvation takes day
>> You won't die.Not in one day.Starvation takes days
>> You won't die.Not in one day.Starvation takes days an
>> You won't die.Not in one day.Starvation takes days and
>> You won't die.Not in one day.Starvation takes days and days
>> You won't die.Not in one day.Starvation takes days and days.
Not in one day.Starvation takes days and days.
Not in one day.Starvation takes days and days.Come
Not in one day.Starvation takes days and days.Come o
Not in one day.Starvation takes days and days.Come on.
Come
Come o
Come on!
♪
(s
(squ
(squeaki
(squeaking
(squeaking)
(bel
(bell
(bell ri
(bell ring
(bell ringing)
(d
(dri
(drill
(drill whi
(drill whirr
(drill whirrin
(drill whirring)
>> T
>> Tha
>> That'
>> That's
>> That's a go
>> That's a good
>> That's a good j
>> That's a good job
>> That's a good job, ki
>> That's a good job, kid.
>> That's a good job, kid.Co
>> That's a good job, kid.Come
>> That's a good job, kid.Come b
>> That's a good job, kid.Come back
>> That's a good job, kid.Come back an
>> That's a good job, kid.Come back anyt
>> That's a good job, kid.Come back anytim
>> That's a good job, kid.Come back anytime, h
>> That's a good job, kid.Come back anytime, huh
>> That's a good job, kid.Come back anytime, huh.
♪
(dog
(dog b
(dog bar
(dog barki
(dog barking i
(dog barking in
(dog barking in th
(dog barking in the
(dog barking in the dist
(dog barking in the distan
(dog barking in the distance
(dog barking in the distance)
(h
(hor
(horn
(horn honk
(horn honkin
(horn honking)
(eng
(engin
(engine
(engine ru
(engine rumbli
(engine rumbling
(engine rumbling)
(car
(car a
(car ala
(car alarm
(car alarm bla
(car alarm blari
(car alarm blaring
(car alarm blaring)
(car alarm blaring)(s
(car alarm blaring)(sir
(car alarm blaring)(siren b
(car alarm blaring)(siren bla
(car alarm blaring)(siren blari
(car alarm blaring)(siren blaring
(car alarm blaring)(siren blaring in
(car alarm blaring)(siren blaring in th
(car alarm blaring)(siren blaring in the
(car alarm blaring)(siren blaring in the di
(car alarm blaring)(siren blaring in the distan
(car alarm blaring)(siren blaring in the distance
(car alarm blaring)(siren blaring in the distance)
(b
(bel
(bell
(bell toll
(bell tollin
(bell tolling)
(t
(thu
(thunder
(thunderin
(thundering)
>>
>> Y
>> You
>> You, uh
>> You, uh,
>> You, uh, lo
>> You, uh, look
>> You, uh, looked l
>> You, uh, looked lik
>> You, uh, looked like
>> You, uh, looked likeyo
>> You, uh, looked likeyou
>> You, uh, looked likeyou were
>> You, uh, looked likeyou were c
>> You, uh, looked likeyou were cry
>> You, uh, looked likeyou were cryin
>> You, uh, looked likeyou were crying.
>> You, uh, looked likeyou were crying.Can
>> You, uh, looked likeyou were crying.Can I
>> You, uh, looked likeyou were crying.Can I he
>> You, uh, looked likeyou were crying.Can I help
>> You, uh, looked likeyou were crying.Can I help?
Yo
You
You lo
You lost?
Ca
Can
Can yo
Can you wa
Can you walk
Can you walk h
Can you walk hom
Can you walk home fr
Can you walk home from
Can you walk home from h
Can you walk home from her
Can you walk home from here?
Pa
Parl
Parlez-v
Parlez-vou
Parlez-vouz
Parlez-vouz fr
Parlez-vouz frança
Parlez-vouz français
Parlez-vouz français?
(t
(thu
(thund
(thunderin
(thundering)
(s
(sni
(sniff
(sniffli
(sniffling)
(sniffling)Can
(sniffling)Can I
(sniffling)Can I te
(sniffling)Can I tell
(sniffling)Can I tell you
(sniffling)Can I tell you w
(sniffling)Can I tell you wha
(sniffling)Can I tell you what
(sniffling)Can I tell you what I th
(sniffling)Can I tell you what I thin
(sniffling)Can I tell you what I think?
I
I th
I thin
I think yo
I think you
I think you do
I think you don'
I think you don't ha
I think you don't have
I think you don't havea
I think you don't havea pl
I think you don't havea plac
I think you don't havea place to
I think you don't havea place to s
I think you don't havea place to sle
I think you don't havea place to sleep
I think you don't havea place to sleepan
I think you don't havea place to sleepand
I think you don't havea place to sleepand you'
I think you don't havea place to sleepand you're
I think you don't havea place to sleepand you're p
I think you don't havea place to sleepand you're pro
I think you don't havea place to sleepand you're probabl
I think you don't havea place to sleepand you're probably
I think you don't havea place to sleepand you're probably hu
I think you don't havea place to sleepand you're probably hung
I think you don't havea place to sleepand you're probably hungry
a place to sleepand you're probably hungry
a place to sleepand you're probably hungryan
a place to sleepand you're probably hungryand
a place to sleepand you're probably hungryand fr
a place to sleepand you're probably hungryand fright
a place to sleepand you're probably hungryand frighten
a place to sleepand you're probably hungryand frightened
a place to sleepand you're probably hungryand frightened..
a place to sleepand you're probably hungryand frightened...
and you're probably hungryand frightened...
and you're probably hungryand frightened...an
and you're probably hungryand frightened...and
and you're probably hungryand frightened...and yo
and you're probably hungryand frightened...and you do
and you're probably hungryand frightened...and you don'
and you're probably hungryand frightened...and you don't
and you're probably hungryand frightened...and you don't wa
and you're probably hungryand frightened...and you don't wanna
and you're probably hungryand frightened...and you don't wanna te
and you're probably hungryand frightened...and you don't wanna tell
and you're probably hungryand frightened...and you don't wanna tell m
and you're probably hungryand frightened...and you don't wanna tell me
and frightened...and you don't wanna tell me
and frightened...and you don't wanna tell mean
and frightened...and you don't wanna tell meanyt
and frightened...and you don't wanna tell meanythi
and frightened...and you don't wanna tell meanything.
So
So f
So far
So far am
So far am I
So far am I ri
So far am I righ
So far am I right?
(s
(sni
(sniff
(sniffling
(sniffling)
(sniffling)I'
(sniffling)I've
(sniffling)I've bee
(sniffling)I've been
(sniffling)I've been in
(sniffling)I've been in y
(sniffling)I've been in your
(sniffling)I've been in your ki
(sniffling)I've been in your kind
(sniffling)I've been in your kind o
(sniffling)I've been in your kind of ja
(sniffling)I've been in your kind of jam
(sniffling)I've been in your kind of jammyse
(sniffling)I've been in your kind of jammyself
(sniffling)I've been in your kind of jammyself..
(sniffling)I've been in your kind of jammyself...
(sniffling)I've been in your kind of jammyself... more
(sniffling)I've been in your kind of jammyself... more t
(sniffling)I've been in your kind of jammyself... more tha
(sniffling)I've been in your kind of jammyself... more than
(sniffling)I've been in your kind of jammyself... more than once
(sniffling)I've been in your kind of jammyself... more than once.
(t
(thu
(thund
(thunderin
(thundering)
(thundering)Wh
(thundering)Why
(thundering)Why do
(thundering)Why don't
(thundering)Why don't yo
(thundering)Why don't you
(thundering)Why don't you co
(thundering)Why don't you come w
(thundering)Why don't you come wit
(thundering)Why don't you come with
(thundering)Why don't you come with me
(thundering)Why don't you come with mean
(thundering)Why don't you come with meand-
(thundering)Why don't you come with meand--
(thundering)Why don't you come with meand-- and
(thundering)Why don't you come with meand-- and we
(thundering)Why don't you come with meand-- and we'l
(thundering)Why don't you come with meand-- and we'll
(thundering)Why don't you come with meand-- and we'll get
(thundering)Why don't you come with meand-- and we'll get yo
(thundering)Why don't you come with meand-- and we'll get you
Why don't you come with meand-- and we'll get you
Why don't you come with meand-- and we'll get youso
Why don't you come with meand-- and we'll get yousome
Why don't you come with meand-- and we'll get yousometh
Why don't you come with meand-- and we'll get yousomething
Why don't you come with meand-- and we'll get yousomething to
Why don't you come with meand-- and we'll get yousomething to e
Why don't you come with meand-- and we'll get yousomething to eat
Why don't you come with meand-- and we'll get yousomething to eat.
and-- and we'll get yousomething to eat.
and-- and we'll get yousomething to eat.>> I
and-- and we'll get yousomething to eat.>> I d
and-- and we'll get yousomething to eat.>> I don
and-- and we'll get yousomething to eat.>> I don't
and-- and we'll get yousomething to eat.>> I don't hav
and-- and we'll get yousomething to eat.>> I don't have
and-- and we'll get yousomething to eat.>> I don't have an
and-- and we'll get yousomething to eat.>> I don't have any
and-- and we'll get yousomething to eat.>> I don't have any mone
and-- and we'll get yousomething to eat.>> I don't have any money.
something to eat.>> I don't have any money.
something to eat.>> I don't have any money.>> I
something to eat.>> I don't have any money.>> I d
something to eat.>> I don't have any money.>> I do.
>> I don't have any money.>> I do.
>> I don't have any money.>> I do.It
>> I don't have any money.>> I do.It's
>> I don't have any money.>> I do.It's a
>> I don't have any money.>> I do.It's a g
>> I don't have any money.>> I do.It's a great
>> I don't have any money.>> I do.It's a great s
>> I don't have any money.>> I do.It's a great spo
>> I don't have any money.>> I do.It's a great spot,
>> I do.It's a great spot,
>> I do.It's a great spot,ri
>> I do.It's a great spot,righ
>> I do.It's a great spot,right
>> I do.It's a great spot,right clos
>> I do.It's a great spot,right close
>> I do.It's a great spot,right close by
>> I do.It's a great spot,right close by.
Ha
Have
Have y
Have you
Have you mad
Have you made
Have you made up
Have you made up y
Have you made up your
Have you made up your mi
Have you made up your mind
Have you made up your mindto
Have you made up your mindto t
Have you made up your mindto tru
Have you made up your mindto trust m
Have you made up your mindto trust me
Have you made up your mindto trust me ye
Have you made up your mindto trust me yet?
>>
>> I
>> I'm
>> I'm afr
>> I'm afrai
>> I'm afraid
>> I'm afraid so
>> I'm afraid so.
Bu
But
But I'
But I'm no
But I'm not
But I'm not al
But I'm not alon
But I'm not alone.
Is
Is t
Is that
Is that ok
Is that okay
Is that okay?
>>
>> Y
>> Yea
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah.Yeah
>> Yeah.Yeah,
>> Yeah.Yeah, wh
>> Yeah.Yeah, what
>> Yeah.Yeah, whatever
>> Yeah.Yeah, whatever.
>> W
>> Wai
>> Wait
>> Wait he
>> Wait here p
>> Wait here ple
>> Wait here pleas
>> Wait here please.
(thu
(thund
(thunder
(thunderin
(thundering)
Sa
Samm
Sammy,
Sammy, M
Sammy, Maybe
Sammy, Maybeth
Sammy, Maybeth,
Sammy, Maybeth, co
Sammy, Maybeth, come o
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.We
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.We'r
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.We're
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.We're go
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.We're gonna
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.We're gonna ge
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.We're gonna get
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.We're gonna getso
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.We're gonna getsome
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.We're gonna getsomethin
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.We're gonna getsomething
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.We're gonna getsomething to
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.We're gonna getsomething to e
Sammy, Maybeth, come on.We're gonna getsomething to eat.
We're gonna getsomething to eat.
We're gonna getsomething to eat.♪
>>
>> ♪
>> ♪ G
>> ♪ Going
>> ♪ Going s
>> ♪ Going sha
>> ♪ Going shall
>> ♪ Going shallow w
>> ♪ Going shallow wal
>> ♪ Going shallow walki
>> ♪ Going shallow walking
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ A
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you g
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you goi
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ S
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Sha
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shall
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow w
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow wal
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walki
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking wit
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me?
>> ♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪
♪
♪ I
♪ I'm d
♪ I'm dri
♪ I'm drivi
♪ I'm driving
♪ I'm driving to
♪ I'm driving to Au
♪ I'm driving to Aunt
♪ I'm driving to Aunt C
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ D
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Drivi
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving t
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt C
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cil
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ D
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Dri
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Drivi
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving t
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Au
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cil
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's
♪ I'm driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ G
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna t
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna tak
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my p
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet g
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet gor
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ A
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you d
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you dri
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you drivi
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving t
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving to
♪ Driving to Aunt Cilla's ♪♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving to ♪
♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving to ♪
♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving to ♪♪
♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ A
♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt
♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Ci
♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cill
♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla'
♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's wi
♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with
♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with m
♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with me?
♪ Gonna take my pet gorilla ♪♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪
♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪
♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪
♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ '
♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Caus
♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause
♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause we
♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause we'r
♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause we're go
♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause we're goin
♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause we're going
♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause we're going to
♪ Are you driving to ♪♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪
♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪
♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ T
♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The
♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The o
♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The oce
♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The ocean
♪ Aunt Cilla's with me? ♪♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪
♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪
♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪
♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ G
♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Goi
♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going
♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to
♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to th
♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the
♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the be
♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach
♪ 'Cause we're going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ G
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gon
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna w
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna wal
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on th
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sa
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ I
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my b
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bar
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ G
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going s
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going sha
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shall
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow w
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow wal
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walki
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walking
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ G
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going s
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going sha
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shall
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow w
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow wal
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walki
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ A
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are y
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you g
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you goi
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ S
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shall
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow w
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow wal
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking w
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking wit
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me?
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪
♪
♪ G
♪ Goi
♪ Going t
♪ Going to
♪ Going to Br
♪ Going to Brid
♪ Going to Bridgepo
♪ Going to Bridgeport
♪ Going to Bridgeport ♪
♪ Going to Bridgeport ♪♪
♪ Going to Bridgeport ♪♪ G
♪ Going to Bridgeport ♪♪ Going
♪ Going to Bridgeport ♪♪ Going t
♪ Going to Bridgeport ♪♪ Going to
♪ Going to Bridgeport ♪♪ Going to Br
♪ Going to Bridgeport ♪♪ Going to Bridge
♪ Going to Bridgeport ♪♪ Going to Bridgepo
♪ Going to Bridgeport ♪♪ Going to Bridgeport
♪ Going to Bridgeport ♪♪ Going to Bridgeport ♪
>>
>> 6
>> 60-88
>> 60-88..
>> 60-88...
60-9
60-90.
60-90...
60-9
60-92.
60-92...
60-9
60-94...
>> I
>> Is
>> Is Ma
>> Is Mama
>> Is Mama gon
>> Is Mama gonna
>> Is Mama gonna b
>> Is Mama gonna be
>> Is Mama gonna be ther
>> Is Mama gonna be there?
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>>
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> L
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's h
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hop
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hope,
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hope, S
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hope, Sammy
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hope, Sammy.
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hope, Sammy.Le
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let'
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope r
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope rea
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope reall
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope really ha
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope really hard
>> Is Mama gonna be there?>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope really hard.
>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope really hard.
>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope really hard.>> I
>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope really hard.>> I h
>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope really hard.>> I hop
>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope really hard.>> I hope,
>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope really hard.>> I hope, I h
>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope really hard.>> I hope, I hop
>> Let's hope, Sammy.Let's hope really hard.>> I hope, I hope,
Let's hope really hard.>> I hope, I hope,
Let's hope really hard.>> I hope, I hope,I
Let's hope really hard.>> I hope, I hope,I ho
Let's hope really hard.>> I hope, I hope,I hope
Let's hope really hard.>> I hope, I hope,I hope,
Let's hope really hard.>> I hope, I hope,I hope, I ho
Let's hope really hard.>> I hope, I hope,I hope, I hope
Let's hope really hard.>> I hope, I hope,I hope, I hope..
Let's hope really hard.>> I hope, I hope,I hope, I hope...
>> I hope, I hope,I hope, I hope...
>> I hope, I hope,I hope, I hope...>> 1
>> I hope, I hope,I hope, I hope...>> 17-
>> I hope, I hope,I hope, I hope...>> 17-20
>> I hope, I hope,I hope, I hope...>> 17-20..
>> I hope, I hope,I hope, I hope...>> 17-20...
>>
>> 1
>> 17-24
>> 17-24.
(d
(dog
(dog b
(dog barki
(dog barking
(dog barking)
(doo
(doorb
(doorbel
(doorbell
(doorbell ring
(doorbell ringin
(doorbell ringing)
Samm
Sammy.
>>
>> Y
>> You g
>> You guy
>> You guys
>> You guys go
>> You guys got my
>> You guys got mynumb
>> You guys got mynumber
>> You guys got mynumbers,
>> You guys got mynumbers, r
>> You guys got mynumbers, right
>> You guys got mynumbers, right?
>> You guys got mynumbers, right?Zi
>> You guys got mynumbers, right?Zip
>> You guys got mynumbers, right?Zip co
>> You guys got mynumbers, right?Zip code,
>> You guys got mynumbers, right?Zip code, bi
>> You guys got mynumbers, right?Zip code, birt
>> You guys got mynumbers, right?Zip code, birthd
>> You guys got mynumbers, right?Zip code, birthday?
numbers, right?Zip code, birthday?
numbers, right?Zip code, birthday?Fo
numbers, right?Zip code, birthday?Foot
numbers, right?Zip code, birthday?Footba
numbers, right?Zip code, birthday?Football j
numbers, right?Zip code, birthday?Football jer
numbers, right?Zip code, birthday?Football jerse
numbers, right?Zip code, birthday?Football jersey?
Zip code, birthday?Football jersey?
Zip code, birthday?Football jersey?An
Zip code, birthday?Football jersey?And
Zip code, birthday?Football jersey?And yo
Zip code, birthday?Football jersey?And you'
Zip code, birthday?Football jersey?And you're g
Zip code, birthday?Football jersey?And you're gon
Zip code, birthday?Football jersey?And you're gonna
Zip code, birthday?Football jersey?And you're gonna c
Zip code, birthday?Football jersey?And you're gonna call
Zip code, birthday?Football jersey?And you're gonna call me
Zip code, birthday?Football jersey?And you're gonna call me i
Zip code, birthday?Football jersey?And you're gonna call me if
Football jersey?And you're gonna call me if
Football jersey?And you're gonna call me ifAu
Football jersey?And you're gonna call me ifAunt
Football jersey?And you're gonna call me ifAunt C
Football jersey?And you're gonna call me ifAunt Cilla
Football jersey?And you're gonna call me ifAunt Cilla d
Football jersey?And you're gonna call me ifAunt Cilla doe
Football jersey?And you're gonna call me ifAunt Cilla doesn
Football jersey?And you're gonna call me ifAunt Cilla doesn't s
Football jersey?And you're gonna call me ifAunt Cilla doesn't sho
Football jersey?And you're gonna call me ifAunt Cilla doesn't show,
Football jersey?And you're gonna call me ifAunt Cilla doesn't show, r
Football jersey?And you're gonna call me ifAunt Cilla doesn't show, right
Football jersey?And you're gonna call me ifAunt Cilla doesn't show, right?
And you're gonna call me ifAunt Cilla doesn't show, right?
And you're gonna call me ifAunt Cilla doesn't show, right?Ok
And you're gonna call me ifAunt Cilla doesn't show, right?Okay
And you're gonna call me ifAunt Cilla doesn't show, right?Okay.
Aunt Cilla doesn't show, right?Okay.
Aunt Cilla doesn't show, right?Okay.I'
Aunt Cilla doesn't show, right?Okay.I'm
Aunt Cilla doesn't show, right?Okay.I'm out
Aunt Cilla doesn't show, right?Okay.I'm out of
Aunt Cilla doesn't show, right?Okay.I'm out of h
Aunt Cilla doesn't show, right?Okay.I'm out of her
Aunt Cilla doesn't show, right?Okay.I'm out of here.
Okay.I'm out of here.
Okay.I'm out of here.Or
Okay.I'm out of here.Orga
Okay.I'm out of here.Organic
Okay.I'm out of here.Organic Ch
Okay.I'm out of here.Organic Chem
Okay.I'm out of here.Organic Chem i
Okay.I'm out of here.Organic Chem in a
Okay.I'm out of here.Organic Chem in a ha
Okay.I'm out of here.Organic Chem in a half
Okay.I'm out of here.Organic Chem in a half-h
Okay.I'm out of here.Organic Chem in a half-hour.
Go
Good
Good m
Good man
Good man, Ja
Good man, Jame
Good man, James.
>>
>> T
>> Tha
>> Thank y
>> Thank you
>> Thank you,
>> Thank you, Wi
>> Thank you, Windy.
>> Thank you, Windy.Than
>> Thank you, Windy.Thanks
>> Thank you, Windy.Thanks f
>> Thank you, Windy.Thanks for
>> Thank you, Windy.Thanks for eve
>> Thank you, Windy.Thanks for every
>> Thank you, Windy.Thanks for everyth
>> Thank you, Windy.Thanks for everythin
>> Thank you, Windy.Thanks for everything.
>>
>> B
>> Bye.
>> Bye.>> B
>> Bye.>> Bye
>> Bye.>> Bye,
>> Bye.>> Bye, Wi
>> Bye.>> Bye, Windy.
>> Bye.>> Bye, Windy.>>
>> Bye.>> Bye, Windy.>> B
>> Bye.>> Bye, Windy.>> Bye
>> Bye.>> Bye, Windy.>> Bye, Wi
>> Bye.>> Bye, Windy.>> Bye, Wind
>> Bye.>> Bye, Windy.>> Bye, Windy.
>> Bye, Windy.>> Bye, Windy.
>> Bye, Windy.>> Bye, Windy.(h
>> Bye, Windy.>> Bye, Windy.(hor
>> Bye, Windy.>> Bye, Windy.(horn
>> Bye, Windy.>> Bye, Windy.(horn honk
>> Bye, Windy.>> Bye, Windy.(horn honkin
>> Bye, Windy.>> Bye, Windy.(horn honking)
♪
♪(d
♪(dog
♪(dog b
♪(dog barki
♪(dog barking
♪(dog barking i
♪(dog barking in
♪(dog barking in the
♪(dog barking in the di
♪(dog barking in the dist
♪(dog barking in the distan
♪(dog barking in the distance)
(v
(van
(van d
(van door
(van door cl
(van door clos
(van door closin
(van door closing)
>>
>> S
>> See y
>> See you
>> See you t
>> See you tom
>> See you tomorro
>> See you tomorrow.
(b
(bir
(birds
(birds c
(birds chirp
(birds chirpin
(birds chirping)
>>
>> W
>> Wha
>> What ar
>> What are
>> What are yo
>> What are you
>> What are you doin
>> What are you doing
>> What are you doing he
>> What are you doing here
>> What are you doing here?
>> What are you doing here?Wh
>> What are you doing here?What
>> What are you doing here?What d
>> What are you doing here?What do
>> What are you doing here?What do you
>> What are you doing here?What do you wa
>> What are you doing here?What do you want
>> What are you doing here?What do you want?
>> What are you doing here?What do you want?>>
>> What are you doing here?What do you want?>> W
>> What are you doing here?What do you want?>> We'
>> What are you doing here?What do you want?>> We're t
>> What are you doing here?What do you want?>> We're the
>> What are you doing here?What do you want?>> We're the T
>> What are you doing here?What do you want?>> We're the Til
>> What are you doing here?What do you want?>> We're the Tillerm
>> What are you doing here?What do you want?>> We're the Tillerman
>> What are you doing here?What do you want?>> We're the Tillermans.
We
We'r
We're
We're he
We're helpin
We're helping
We're helping ou
We're helping our
We're helping our aunt
We're helping our aunt.
We're helping our aunt.Ou
We're helping our aunt.Our
We're helping our aunt.Our gr
We're helping our aunt.Our great
We're helping our aunt.Our great au
We're helping our aunt.Our great aunt
We're helping our aunt.Our great aunt,
We're helping our aunt.Our great aunt,Mr
We're helping our aunt.Our great aunt,Mrs.
We're helping our aunt.Our great aunt,Mrs. C
We're helping our aunt.Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla
We're helping our aunt.Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla L
We're helping our aunt.Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla Log
We're helping our aunt.Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla Logan
We're helping our aunt.Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla Logan.
Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla Logan.
Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla Logan.>> O
Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla Logan.>> Oh,
Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla Logan.>> Oh, t
Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla Logan.>> Oh, tha
Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla Logan.>> Oh, that is
Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla Logan.>> Oh, that is M
Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla Logan.>> Oh, that is Mot
Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla Logan.>> Oh, that is Mothe
Our great aunt,Mrs. Cilla Logan.>> Oh, that is Mother.
Mrs. Cilla Logan.>> Oh, that is Mother.
Mrs. Cilla Logan.>> Oh, that is Mother.No
Mrs. Cilla Logan.>> Oh, that is Mother.Not
Mrs. Cilla Logan.>> Oh, that is Mother.Not me.
>> Oh, that is Mother.Not me.
>> Oh, that is Mother.Not me.I'm
>> Oh, that is Mother.Not me.I'm he
>> Oh, that is Mother.Not me.I'm her
>> Oh, that is Mother.Not me.I'm her da
>> Oh, that is Mother.Not me.I'm her daught
>> Oh, that is Mother.Not me.I'm her daughter
>> Oh, that is Mother.Not me.I'm her daughter.
Th
That
That is,
That is, I
That is, I w
That is, I was
That is, I was her
That is, I was her d
That is, I was her dau
That is, I was her daugh
That is, I was her daughter.
That is, I was her daughter.Mo
That is, I was her daughter.Moth
That is, I was her daughter.Mother p
That is, I was her daughter.Mother pas
That is, I was her daughter.Mother passe
That is, I was her daughter.Mother passed
That is, I was her daughter.Mother passed on
That is, I was her daughter.Mother passed onth
That is, I was her daughter.Mother passed onthis
That is, I was her daughter.Mother passed onthis l
That is, I was her daughter.Mother passed onthis las
That is, I was her daughter.Mother passed onthis last Ma
That is, I was her daughter.Mother passed onthis last Marc
That is, I was her daughter.Mother passed onthis last March.
Bu
But
But do
But do c
But do come
But do come in
But do come in!
No
No n
No nee
No need to
No need to l
No need to loi
No need to loite
No need to loiter
No need to loiteron
No need to loiteron t
No need to loiteron the f
No need to loiteron the fro
No need to loiteron the front
No need to loiteron the front s
No need to loiteron the front stoop
No need to loiteron the front stoop.
This
This w
This way
This way.
I
I fo
I foun
I found
I found Moth
I found Mother
I found Mother s
I found Mother sit
I found Mother sitting
I found Mother sittingri
I found Mother sittingrigh
I found Mother sittingright th
I found Mother sittingright ther
I found Mother sittingright there.
I found Mother sittingright there.A
I found Mother sittingright there.A We
I found Mother sittingright there.A Wedn
I found Mother sittingright there.A Wednesda
I found Mother sittingright there.A Wednesday.
right there.A Wednesday.
right there.A Wednesday.Her
right there.A Wednesday.Her he
right there.A Wednesday.Her hear
right there.A Wednesday.Her heart
right there.A Wednesday.Her heart was
right there.A Wednesday.Her heart was we
right there.A Wednesday.Her heart was weak
right there.A Wednesday.Her heart was weak.
Bu
But
But sh
But she
But she neve
But she never.
But she never...
But she never...ne
But she never...neve
But she never...never
But she never...never comp
But she never...never compla
But she never...never complain
But she never...never complained
But she never...never complained.
>>
>> W
>> We're
>> We're s
>> We're sor
>> We're sorry
>> We're sorry.
>>
>> Y
>> Yes
>> Yes,
>> Yes, well
>> Yes, well..
>> Yes, well...
>> Yes, well...it w
>> Yes, well...it was
>> Yes, well...it was a
>> Yes, well...it was a g
>> Yes, well...it was a great
>> Yes, well...it was a great s
>> Yes, well...it was a great sho
>> Yes, well...it was a great shock
>> Yes, well...it was a great shock.
In f
In fac
In fact,
In fact, I
In fact, I've
In fact, I've no
In fact, I've not
In fact, I've not be
In fact, I've not been
In fact, I've not beenquit
In fact, I've not beenquite
In fact, I've not beenquite th
In fact, I've not beenquite the
In fact, I've not beenquite the same
In fact, I've not beenquite the same s
In fact, I've not beenquite the same sin
In fact, I've not beenquite the same since
In fact, I've not beenquite the same since Mot
In fact, I've not beenquite the same since Mothe
In fact, I've not beenquite the same since Mother
In fact, I've not beenquite the same since Motherwe
In fact, I've not beenquite the same since Motherwent
In fact, I've not beenquite the same since Motherwent awa
In fact, I've not beenquite the same since Motherwent away.
Pe
Peop
People
People hav
People have
People have sa
People have said
People have said tha
People have said that
People have said that to
People have said that to m
People have said that to me.
We
Well
Well,
Well, no
Well, now, t
Well, now, tel
Well, now, tell
Well, now, tell me
Well, now, tell me aga
Well, now, tell me again
Well, now, tell me againpr
Well, now, tell me againprec
Well, now, tell me againprecis
Well, now, tell me againprecisel
Well, now, tell me againprecisely wh
Well, now, tell me againprecisely who
Well, now, tell me againprecisely who yo
Well, now, tell me againprecisely who you
Well, now, tell me againprecisely who you are?
>>
>> O
>> Our
>> Our m
>> Our mothe
>> Our mother
>> Our mother is
>> Our mother is y
>> Our mother is your
>> Our mother is yourmo
>> Our mother is yourmoth
>> Our mother is yourmother's
>> Our mother is yourmother's n
>> Our mother is yourmother's nie
>> Our mother is yourmother's niece
>> Our mother is yourmother's niece.
>> Our mother is yourmother's niece.Sh
>> Our mother is yourmother's niece.She
>> Our mother is yourmother's niece.She se
>> Our mother is yourmother's niece.She sent u
>> Our mother is yourmother's niece.She sent us
>> Our mother is yourmother's niece.She sent us a
>> Our mother is yourmother's niece.She sent us a Ch
>> Our mother is yourmother's niece.She sent us a Christ
>> Our mother is yourmother's niece.She sent us a Christma
>> Our mother is yourmother's niece.She sent us a Christmas
>> Our mother is yourmother's niece.She sent us a Christmas ca
>> Our mother is yourmother's niece.She sent us a Christmas card
mother's niece.She sent us a Christmas card
mother's niece.She sent us a Christmas cardev
mother's niece.She sent us a Christmas cardever
mother's niece.She sent us a Christmas cardevery
mother's niece.She sent us a Christmas cardevery ye
mother's niece.She sent us a Christmas cardevery year.
She sent us a Christmas cardevery year.
She sent us a Christmas cardevery year.Th
She sent us a Christmas cardevery year.That
She sent us a Christmas cardevery year.That's
She sent us a Christmas cardevery year.That's how
She sent us a Christmas cardevery year.That's how w
She sent us a Christmas cardevery year.That's how we
She sent us a Christmas cardevery year.That's how we kn
She sent us a Christmas cardevery year.That's how we knew a
She sent us a Christmas cardevery year.That's how we knew abo
She sent us a Christmas cardevery year.That's how we knew about
every year.That's how we knew about
every year.That's how we knew aboutAu
every year.That's how we knew aboutAunt
every year.That's how we knew aboutAunt Cil
every year.That's how we knew aboutAunt Cilla
every year.That's how we knew aboutAunt Cilla a
every year.That's how we knew aboutAunt Cilla and
every year.That's how we knew aboutAunt Cilla and her
every year.That's how we knew aboutAunt Cilla and her a
every year.That's how we knew aboutAunt Cilla and her add
every year.That's how we knew aboutAunt Cilla and her addre
every year.That's how we knew aboutAunt Cilla and her address.
Bu
But
But I
But I do
But I don't
But I don't ev
But I don't even
But I don't even k
But I don't even know
But I don't even know yo
But I don't even know your
But I don't even know your n
But I don't even know your name.
But I don't even know your name.>>
But I don't even know your name.>> E
But I don't even know your name.>> Eun
But I don't even know your name.>> Eunice.
But I don't even know your name.>> Eunice.Eu
But I don't even know your name.>> Eunice.Euni
But I don't even know your name.>> Eunice.Eunice
But I don't even know your name.>> Eunice.Eunice L
But I don't even know your name.>> Eunice.Eunice Logan
But I don't even know your name.>> Eunice.Eunice Logan.
Uh
Uh,
Uh, do
Uh, does t
Uh, does tha
Uh, does that
Uh, does that ma
Uh, does that make u
Uh, does that make us
Uh, does that make usse
Uh, does that make usseco
Uh, does that make ussecond
Uh, does that make ussecond cou
Uh, does that make ussecond cousi
Uh, does that make ussecond cousins
Uh, does that make ussecond cousins?
Uh, does that make ussecond cousins?>>
Uh, does that make ussecond cousins?>> I
Uh, does that make ussecond cousins?>> I d
Uh, does that make ussecond cousins?>> I don
Uh, does that make ussecond cousins?>> I don't k
Uh, does that make ussecond cousins?>> I don't kno
Uh, does that make ussecond cousins?>> I don't know.
second cousins?>> I don't know.
second cousins?>> I don't know.>>
second cousins?>> I don't know.>> S
second cousins?>> I don't know.>> So wh
second cousins?>> I don't know.>> So what
second cousins?>> I don't know.>> So what--
second cousins?>> I don't know.>> So what-- w
second cousins?>> I don't know.>> So what-- where
second cousins?>> I don't know.>> So what-- where a
second cousins?>> I don't know.>> So what-- where are
>> I don't know.>> So what-- where are
>> I don't know.>> So what-- where areyo
>> I don't know.>> So what-- where areyour
>> I don't know.>> So what-- where areyour par
>> I don't know.>> So what-- where areyour paren
>> I don't know.>> So what-- where areyour parents
>> I don't know.>> So what-- where areyour parents?
>> So what-- where areyour parents?
>> So what-- where areyour parents?Ho
>> So what-- where areyour parents?How
>> So what-- where areyour parents?How lo
>> So what-- where areyour parents?How long a
>> So what-- where areyour parents?How long are
>> So what-- where areyour parents?How long are y
>> So what-- where areyour parents?How long are you
>> So what-- where areyour parents?How long are you vis
>> So what-- where areyour parents?How long are you visit
>> So what-- where areyour parents?How long are you visitin
>> So what-- where areyour parents?How long are you visiting
your parents?How long are you visiting
your parents?How long are you visitingin
your parents?How long are you visitingin B
your parents?How long are you visitingin Bridg
your parents?How long are you visitingin Bridgep
your parents?How long are you visitingin Bridgepor
your parents?How long are you visitingin Bridgeport?
>>
>> S
>> Sam
>> Sammy,
>> Sammy, Ma
>> Sammy, Mama
>> Sammy, Mama's
>> Sammy, Mama's not
>> Sammy, Mama's not h
>> Sammy, Mama's not her
>> Sammy, Mama's not here.
(c
(cry
(cryin
(crying)
(crying)>>
(crying)>> Y
(crying)>> You
(crying)>> You don
(crying)>> You don't
(crying)>> You don't k
(crying)>> You don't kno
(crying)>> You don't know wh
(crying)>> You don't know wher
(crying)>> You don't know where
(crying)>> You don't know whereyo
(crying)>> You don't know whereyou
(crying)>> You don't know whereyou mo
(crying)>> You don't know whereyou mother
(crying)>> You don't know whereyou mother i
(crying)>> You don't know whereyou mother is?
>> You don't know whereyou mother is?
>> You don't know whereyou mother is?An
>> You don't know whereyou mother is?And
>> You don't know whereyou mother is?And yo
>> You don't know whereyou mother is?And your f
>> You don't know whereyou mother is?And your fat
>> You don't know whereyou mother is?And your fathe
>> You don't know whereyou mother is?And your father?
Oh
Oh..
Oh... de
Oh... dear
Oh... dear,
Oh... dear,yo
Oh... dear,you
Oh... dear,you po
Oh... dear,you poor s
Oh... dear,you poor swe
Oh... dear,you poor sweet
Oh... dear,you poor sweet t
Oh... dear,you poor sweet thing
Oh... dear,you poor sweet things.
Wi
Will
Will y
Will you e
Will you exc
Will you excus
Will you excuse
Will you excuse me
Will you excuse mewh
Will you excuse mewhil
Will you excuse mewhile
Will you excuse mewhile I ma
Will you excuse mewhile I make
Will you excuse mewhile I make a
Will you excuse mewhile I make a p
Will you excuse mewhile I make a phone
Will you excuse mewhile I make a phone c
Will you excuse mewhile I make a phone cal
Will you excuse mewhile I make a phone call?
>>
>> L
>> Les
>> Lest I
>> Lest I fo
>> Lest I forg
>> Lest I forget
>> Lest I forget.
>> Lest I forget.I,
>> Lest I forget.I, u
>> Lest I forget.I, uh,
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I wen
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went ah
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went ahea
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went ahead
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went aheadan
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went aheadand
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went aheadand ca
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went aheadand called
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went aheadand called u
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went aheadand called up
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went aheadand called up th
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Pe
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peew
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peewau
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peewauke
>> Lest I forget.I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peewauket
I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peewauket
I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peewauketan
I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peewauketand
I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peewauketand th
I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peewauketand the
I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peewauketand the poli
I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peewauketand the police
I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peewauketand the police t
I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peewauketand the police the
I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peewauketand the police there d
I, uh, I went aheadand called up the Peewauketand the police there did
and called up the Peewauketand the police there did
and called up the Peewauketand the police there didim
and called up the Peewauketand the police there didimpo
and called up the Peewauketand the police there didimpoun
and called up the Peewauketand the police there didimpound th
and called up the Peewauketand the police there didimpound the
and called up the Peewauketand the police there didimpound the Pl
and called up the Peewauketand the police there didimpound the Plym
and called up the Peewauketand the police there didimpound the Plymouth
and called up the Peewauketand the police there didimpound the Plymouth V
and called up the Peewauketand the police there didimpound the Plymouth Vol
and called up the Peewauketand the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volar
and called up the Peewauketand the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volaré
and the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volaré
and the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volarére
and the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volaréregi
and the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volaréregist
and the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volaréregister
and the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volaréregistered t
and the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to
and the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Li
and the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza
and the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Til
and the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tille
and the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerm
and the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerman
and the police there didimpound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerman.
impound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerman.
impound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerman.I
impound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerman.I ex
impound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerman.I expl
impound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerman.I explaine
impound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerman.I explained
impound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerman.I explained yo
impound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your
impound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your sit
impound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situa
impound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situati
impound the Plymouth Volaréregistered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situation
registered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situation
registered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situationan
registered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situationand
registered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situationand they
registered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situationand they w
registered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situationand they wer
registered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situationand they were
registered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situationand they were good
registered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situationand they were good e
registered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situationand they were good eno
registered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situationand they were good enoug
registered to Liza Tillerman.I explained your situationand they were good enough
I explained your situationand they were good enough
I explained your situationand they were good enoughto
I explained your situationand they were good enoughto w
I explained your situationand they were good enoughto wir
I explained your situationand they were good enoughto wire
I explained your situationand they were good enoughto wire me $
I explained your situationand they were good enoughto wire me $15
I explained your situationand they were good enoughto wire me $150
and they were good enoughto wire me $150
and they were good enoughto wire me $150ag
and they were good enoughto wire me $150agai
and they were good enoughto wire me $150agains
and they were good enoughto wire me $150against th
and they were good enoughto wire me $150against the
and they were good enoughto wire me $150against the fu
and they were good enoughto wire me $150against the futu
and they were good enoughto wire me $150against the future s
and they were good enoughto wire me $150against the future sal
and they were good enoughto wire me $150against the future sale
to wire me $150against the future sale
to wire me $150against the future saleof
to wire me $150against the future saleof t
to wire me $150against the future saleof the
to wire me $150against the future saleof the v
to wire me $150against the future saleof the vehic
to wire me $150against the future saleof the vehicle
to wire me $150against the future saleof the vehicle a
to wire me $150against the future saleof the vehicle at
against the future saleof the vehicle at
against the future saleof the vehicle atth
against the future saleof the vehicle atthe
against the future saleof the vehicle atthe po
against the future saleof the vehicle atthe police
against the future saleof the vehicle atthe police a
against the future saleof the vehicle atthe police auc
against the future saleof the vehicle atthe police aucti
against the future saleof the vehicle atthe police auction.
of the vehicle atthe police auction.
of the vehicle atthe police auction.>>
of the vehicle atthe police auction.>> A
of the vehicle atthe police auction.>> Ah, E
of the vehicle atthe police auction.>> Ah, Eun
of the vehicle atthe police auction.>> Ah, Eunic
of the vehicle atthe police auction.>> Ah, Eunice,
of the vehicle atthe police auction.>> Ah, Eunice, why
of the vehicle atthe police auction.>> Ah, Eunice, why d
of the vehicle atthe police auction.>> Ah, Eunice, why don
of the vehicle atthe police auction.>> Ah, Eunice, why don't
of the vehicle atthe police auction.>> Ah, Eunice, why don't you
the police auction.>> Ah, Eunice, why don't you
the police auction.>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook
the police auction.>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook a
the police auction.>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook aft
the police auction.>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook after
the police auction.>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook after thi
the police auction.>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook after this
>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook after this
>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook after thisju
>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook after thisjust
>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook after thisjust f
>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook after thisjust for
>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook after thisjust for the
>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook after thisjust for the m
>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook after thisjust for the mea
>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook after thisjust for the meant
>> Ah, Eunice, why don't youlook after thisjust for the meantime?
look after thisjust for the meantime?
look after thisjust for the meantime?Ok
look after thisjust for the meantime?Okay
look after thisjust for the meantime?Okay,
look after thisjust for the meantime?Okay, with
look after thisjust for the meantime?Okay, with y
look after thisjust for the meantime?Okay, with you
look after thisjust for the meantime?Okay, with you,
look after thisjust for the meantime?Okay, with you, Dice
look after thisjust for the meantime?Okay, with you, Dicey?
>>
>> O
>> Oka
>> Okay, l
>> Okay, let
>> Okay, let's
>> Okay, let's g
>> Okay, let's get b
>> Okay, let's get bac
>> Okay, let's get back
>> Okay, let's get backto
>> Okay, let's get backto t
>> Okay, let's get backto the
>> Okay, let's get backto the des
>> Okay, let's get backto the descr
>> Okay, let's get backto the descrip
>> Okay, let's get backto the descripti
>> Okay, let's get backto the description.
>> Okay, let's get backto the description.Do
>> Okay, let's get backto the description.Do y
>> Okay, let's get backto the description.Do you
>> Okay, let's get backto the description.Do you rem
>> Okay, let's get backto the description.Do you remem
>> Okay, let's get backto the description.Do you remembe
>> Okay, let's get backto the description.Do you remember
>> Okay, let's get backto the description.Do you remember what
to the description.Do you remember what
to the description.Do you remember whatyo
to the description.Do you remember whatyour
to the description.Do you remember whatyour m
to the description.Do you remember whatyour mothe
to the description.Do you remember whatyour mother
to the description.Do you remember whatyour mother wa
to the description.Do you remember whatyour mother was
to the description.Do you remember whatyour mother was wear
to the description.Do you remember whatyour mother was wearin
to the description.Do you remember whatyour mother was wearing?
>>
>> B
>> Blu
>> Blue je
>> Blue jean
>> Blue jeans.
A
A sw
A sweate
A sweater.
A
A bi
A big
A big re
A big red sw
A big red swea
A big red sweate
A big red sweater
A big red sweater with
A big red sweater withho
A big red sweater withhole
A big red sweater withholes
A big red sweater withholes in t
A big red sweater withholes in the
A big red sweater withholes in the e
A big red sweater withholes in the elb
A big red sweater withholes in the elbows.
Sand
Sandal
Sandals
Sandals an
Sandals and a
Sandals and a pu
Sandals and a purs
Sandals and a purse.
>>
>> A
>> Any j
>> Any jew
>> Any jewel
>> Any jewelry
>> Any jewelry?
>> Any jewelry?Ri
>> Any jewelry?Ring
>> Any jewelry?Rings, a
>> Any jewelry?Rings, a w
>> Any jewelry?Rings, a wat
>> Any jewelry?Rings, a watch
>> Any jewelry?Rings, a watch?
No
No w
No wed
No weddi
No wedding r
No wedding rin
No wedding ring?
No wedding ring?>> N
No wedding ring?>> No.
No wedding ring?>> No.>>
No wedding ring?>> No.>> H
No wedding ring?>> No.>> Had
No wedding ring?>> No.>> Had you
No wedding ring?>> No.>> Had you t
No wedding ring?>> No.>> Had you the
No wedding ring?>> No.>> Had you the s
No wedding ring?>> No.>> Had you the same
No wedding ring?>> No.>> Had you the same fa
No wedding ring?>> No.>> Had you the same fath
No wedding ring?>> No.>> Had you the same father
No wedding ring?>> No.>> Had you the same father?
>> No.>> Had you the same father?
>> No.>> Had you the same father?Wo
>> No.>> Had you the same father?Woul
>> No.>> Had you the same father?Would
>> No.>> Had you the same father?Would you
>> No.>> Had you the same father?Would you kn
>> No.>> Had you the same father?Would you know
>> No.>> Had you the same father?Would you know t
>> No.>> Had you the same father?Would you know that?
>> Had you the same father?Would you know that?
>> Had you the same father?Would you know that?>>
>> Had you the same father?Would you know that?>> W
>> Had you the same father?Would you know that?>> We're
>> Had you the same father?Would you know that?>> We're n
>> Had you the same father?Would you know that?>> We're not
>> Had you the same father?Would you know that?>> We're not b
>> Had you the same father?Would you know that?>> We're not basta
>> Had you the same father?Would you know that?>> We're not bastard
>> Had you the same father?Would you know that?>> We're not bastards!
Would you know that?>> We're not bastards!
Would you know that?>> We're not bastards!>>
Would you know that?>> We're not bastards!>> S
Would you know that?>> We're not bastards!>> Sammy
Would you know that?>> We're not bastards!>> Sammy.
>> We're not bastards!>> Sammy.
>> We're not bastards!>> Sammy.(gas
>> We're not bastards!>> Sammy.(gaspi
>> We're not bastards!>> Sammy.(gasping
>> We're not bastards!>> Sammy.(gasping)
>> Sammy.(gasping)
>> Sammy.(gasping)>> I
>> Sammy.(gasping)>> It'
>> Sammy.(gasping)>> It's
>> Sammy.(gasping)>> It's al
>> Sammy.(gasping)>> It's all ri
>> Sammy.(gasping)>> It's all righ
>> Sammy.(gasping)>> It's all right.
(gasping)>> It's all right.
(gasping)>> It's all right.Th
(gasping)>> It's all right.They
(gasping)>> It's all right.They w
(gasping)>> It's all right.They wou
(gasping)>> It's all right.They would k
(gasping)>> It's all right.They would kno
(gasping)>> It's all right.They would know
(gasping)>> It's all right.They would know an
(gasping)>> It's all right.They would know and we
(gasping)>> It's all right.They would know and we w
(gasping)>> It's all right.They would know and we wou
(gasping)>> It's all right.They would know and we would
(gasping)>> It's all right.They would know and we wouldn't.
Ok
Okay
Okay, um
Okay, um..
Okay, um...
Okay, um...Di
Okay, um...Dice
Okay, um...Dicey,
Okay, um...Dicey, c
Okay, um...Dicey, can y
Okay, um...Dicey, can you
Okay, um...Dicey, can you t
Okay, um...Dicey, can you thi
Okay, um...Dicey, can you think o
Okay, um...Dicey, can you think of
Okay, um...Dicey, can you think ofan
Okay, um...Dicey, can you think ofanyp
Okay, um...Dicey, can you think ofanyplace
Okay, um...Dicey, can you think ofanyplace e
Okay, um...Dicey, can you think ofanyplace els
Okay, um...Dicey, can you think ofanyplace else
Okay, um...Dicey, can you think ofanyplace else your
Okay, um...Dicey, can you think ofanyplace else your m
Okay, um...Dicey, can you think ofanyplace else your mot
Okay, um...Dicey, can you think ofanyplace else your mothe
Okay, um...Dicey, can you think ofanyplace else your mother
Dicey, can you think ofanyplace else your mother
Dicey, can you think ofanyplace else your mothermi
Dicey, can you think ofanyplace else your mothermigh
Dicey, can you think ofanyplace else your mothermight
Dicey, can you think ofanyplace else your mothermight have
Dicey, can you think ofanyplace else your mothermight have g
Dicey, can you think ofanyplace else your mothermight have gon
Dicey, can you think ofanyplace else your mothermight have gone?
anyplace else your mothermight have gone?
anyplace else your mothermight have gone?Frie
anyplace else your mothermight have gone?Friend
anyplace else your mothermight have gone?Friends,
anyplace else your mothermight have gone?Friends, r
anyplace else your mothermight have gone?Friends, relat
anyplace else your mothermight have gone?Friends, relativ
anyplace else your mothermight have gone?Friends, relatives
anyplace else your mothermight have gone?Friends, relatives?
might have gone?Friends, relatives?
might have gone?Friends, relatives?>>
might have gone?Friends, relatives?>> O
might have gone?Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I
might have gone?Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I s
might have gone?Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I sho
might have gone?Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I shoul
might have gone?Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should te
might have gone?Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell
might have gone?Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell y
might have gone?Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell you
might have gone?Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell you,
Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell you,
Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell you,my
Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell you,my m
Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell you,my mot
Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell you,my mothe
Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell you,my mother ha
Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell you,my mother had
Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell you,my mother had on
Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell you,my mother had one
Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell you,my mother had one sist
Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell you,my mother had one sister
Friends, relatives?>> Oh, I should tell you,my mother had one sister,
>> Oh, I should tell you,my mother had one sister,
>> Oh, I should tell you,my mother had one sister,Ab
>> Oh, I should tell you,my mother had one sister,Abig
>> Oh, I should tell you,my mother had one sister,Abigai
>> Oh, I should tell you,my mother had one sister,Abigail...
my mother had one sister,Abigail...
my mother had one sister,Abigail...wh
my mother had one sister,Abigail...who
my mother had one sister,Abigail...who woul
my mother had one sister,Abigail...who would
my mother had one sister,Abigail...who would be
Abigail...who would be
Abigail...who would beth
Abigail...who would bethe
Abigail...who would bethe chil
Abigail...who would bethe childr
Abigail...who would bethe children
Abigail...who would bethe children's
Abigail...who would bethe children's gra
Abigail...who would bethe children's grand
Abigail...who would bethe children's grandmo
Abigail...who would bethe children's grandmoth
Abigail...who would bethe children's grandmother.
Ab
Abig
Abigai
Abigail wa
Abigail was
Abigail was mu
Abigail was much
Abigail was much you
Abigail was much young
Abigail was much younger
Abigail was much youngerthan
Abigail was much youngerthan m
Abigail was much youngerthan my
Abigail was much youngerthan my mo
Abigail was much youngerthan my mother
Abigail was much youngerthan my mother,
Abigail was much youngerthan my mother, an
Abigail was much youngerthan my mother, and
Abigail was much youngerthan my mother, and they
Abigail was much youngerthan my mother, and theyne
Abigail was much youngerthan my mother, and theyneve
Abigail was much youngerthan my mother, and theynever
Abigail was much youngerthan my mother, and theynever go
Abigail was much youngerthan my mother, and theynever got al
Abigail was much youngerthan my mother, and theynever got alon
Abigail was much youngerthan my mother, and theynever got along.
than my mother, and theynever got along.
than my mother, and theynever got along.La
than my mother, and theynever got along.Late
than my mother, and theynever got along.Later
than my mother, and theynever got along.Later we h
than my mother, and theynever got along.Later we hea
than my mother, and theynever got along.Later we heard
than my mother, and theynever got along.Later we heard s
than my mother, and theynever got along.Later we heard she m
than my mother, and theynever got along.Later we heard she mar
than my mother, and theynever got along.Later we heard she marri
than my mother, and theynever got along.Later we heard she married
never got along.Later we heard she married
never got along.Later we heard she marrieda
never got along.Later we heard she marrieda di
never got along.Later we heard she marrieda dirt
never got along.Later we heard she marrieda dirt f
never got along.Later we heard she marrieda dirt farme
never got along.Later we heard she marrieda dirt farmer
never got along.Later we heard she marrieda dirt farmer by
never got along.Later we heard she marrieda dirt farmer by t
never got along.Later we heard she marrieda dirt farmer by the n
never got along.Later we heard she marrieda dirt farmer by the nam
never got along.Later we heard she marrieda dirt farmer by the name
Later we heard she marrieda dirt farmer by the name
Later we heard she marrieda dirt farmer by the nameof
Later we heard she marrieda dirt farmer by the nameof T
Later we heard she marrieda dirt farmer by the nameof Tille
Later we heard she marrieda dirt farmer by the nameof Tillerm
Later we heard she marrieda dirt farmer by the nameof Tillerman
Later we heard she marrieda dirt farmer by the nameof Tillerman.
>>
>> W
>> Whi
>> Which o
>> Which one
>> Which one's
>> Which one's o
>> Which one's our g
>> Which one's our gra
>> Which one's our grand
>> Which one's our grandmo
>> Which one's our grandmother
>> Which one's our grandmother?
>> Which one's our grandmother?>>
>> Which one's our grandmother?>> T
>> Which one's our grandmother?>> The l
>> Which one's our grandmother?>> The lit
>> Which one's our grandmother?>> The littl
>> Which one's our grandmother?>> The little
>> Which one's our grandmother?>> The little girl
>> Which one's our grandmother?>> The little girlwith
>> Which one's our grandmother?>> The little girlwith t
>> Which one's our grandmother?>> The little girlwith the
>> Which one's our grandmother?>> The little girlwith the w
>> Which one's our grandmother?>> The little girlwith the wild
>> Which one's our grandmother?>> The little girlwith the wild ha
>> Which one's our grandmother?>> The little girlwith the wild hair
>> Which one's our grandmother?>> The little girlwith the wild hair.
I wr
I wrot
I wrote
I wrote he
I wrote her of
I wrote her of M
I wrote her of Mot
I wrote her of Mothe
I wrote her of Mother's
I wrote her of Mother's pa
I wrote her of Mother's pass
I wrote her of Mother's passin
I wrote her of Mother's passing
I wrote her of Mother's passingbut
I wrote her of Mother's passingbut re
I wrote her of Mother's passingbut rece
I wrote her of Mother's passingbut receiv
I wrote her of Mother's passingbut received n
I wrote her of Mother's passingbut received no
I wrote her of Mother's passingbut received no re
I wrote her of Mother's passingbut received no repl
I wrote her of Mother's passingbut received no reply.
>>
>> W
>> We ph
>> We phon
>> We phoned
>> We phoned o
>> We phoned our c
>> We phoned our chu
>> We phoned our churc
>> We phoned our church
>> We phoned our churchdo
>> We phoned our churchdown
>> We phoned our churchdown the
>> We phoned our churchdown there
>> We phoned our churchdown there a
>> We phoned our churchdown there and
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I a
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I ask
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I asked
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I askedthe
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I askedthe pa
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I askedthe past
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I askedthe pastor
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I askedthe pastor to
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I askedthe pastor to ma
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I askedthe pastor to make
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I askedthe pastor to make a
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I askedthe pastor to make a vis
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I askedthe pastor to make a visit
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitat
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitatio
>> We phoned our churchdown there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitation.
down there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitation.
down there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitation.Ap
down there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitation.Appa
down there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitation.Appare
down there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitation.Apparently
down there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitation.Apparently,
down there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, sh
down there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, she
down there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, she has
down there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, she has so
down there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, she has some
down there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, she has someth
down there and I askedthe pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, she has something
the pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, she has something
the pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, she has somethingof
the pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, she has somethingof a
the pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, she has somethingof a rep
the pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, she has somethingof a reput
the pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, she has somethingof a reputat
the pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, she has somethingof a reputatio
the pastor to make a visitation.Apparently, she has somethingof a reputation.
>> O
>> Oka
>> Okay.
>> Okay.We
>> Okay.We'l
>> Okay.We'll
>> Okay.We'll chec
>> Okay.We'll check
>> Okay.We'll check on
>> Okay.We'll check on i
>> Okay.We'll check on it.
>> Okay.We'll check on it.Uh
>> Okay.We'll check on it.Uh,
>> Okay.We'll check on it.Uh, wh
>> Okay.We'll check on it.Uh, what w
>> Okay.We'll check on it.Uh, what was
>> Okay.We'll check on it.Uh, what was t
>> Okay.We'll check on it.Uh, what was tha
>> Okay.We'll check on it.Uh, what was that lo
>> Okay.We'll check on it.Uh, what was that loca
>> Okay.We'll check on it.Uh, what was that locati
>> Okay.We'll check on it.Uh, what was that location
>> Okay.We'll check on it.Uh, what was that location,
We'll check on it.Uh, what was that location,
We'll check on it.Uh, what was that location,Fa
We'll check on it.Uh, what was that location,Fath
We'll check on it.Uh, what was that location,Father
We'll check on it.Uh, what was that location,Father?
Uh, what was that location,Father?
Uh, what was that location,Father?>> O
Uh, what was that location,Father?>> Oh,
Uh, what was that location,Father?>> Oh, M
Uh, what was that location,Father?>> Oh, Mar
Uh, what was that location,Father?>> Oh, Marylan
Uh, what was that location,Father?>> Oh, Maryland.
Father?>> Oh, Maryland.
Father?>> Oh, Maryland.Th
Father?>> Oh, Maryland.The
Father?>> Oh, Maryland.The to
Father?>> Oh, Maryland.The town o
Father?>> Oh, Maryland.The town of
Father?>> Oh, Maryland.The town of Cr
Father?>> Oh, Maryland.The town of Cris
Father?>> Oh, Maryland.The town of Crisfiel
Father?>> Oh, Maryland.The town of Crisfield.
>>
>> D
>> Dic
>> Dicey,
>> Dicey, do
>> Dicey, do y
>> Dicey, do you
>> Dicey, do you thi
>> Dicey, do you think
>> Dicey, do you think i
>> Dicey, do you think it'
>> Dicey, do you think it's
>> Dicey, do you think it'spo
>> Dicey, do you think it'sposs
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossib
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossible y
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossible you
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossible your
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossible your mo
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossible your mother
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossible your mother m
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossible your mother may
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossible your mother may h
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossible your mother may have
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossible your mother may havego
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossible your mother may havegone
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossible your mother may havegone t
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossible your mother may havegone there
>> Dicey, do you think it'spossible your mother may havegone there?
possible your mother may havegone there?
possible your mother may havegone there?>>
possible your mother may havegone there?>> I
possible your mother may havegone there?>> I don
possible your mother may havegone there?>> I don't
possible your mother may havegone there?>> I don't t
possible your mother may havegone there?>> I don't thi
possible your mother may havegone there?>> I don't think s
possible your mother may havegone there?>> I don't think so.
gone there?>> I don't think so.
gone there?>> I don't think so.Sh
gone there?>> I don't think so.She
gone there?>> I don't think so.She ne
gone there?>> I don't think so.She never
gone there?>> I don't think so.She never ta
gone there?>> I don't think so.She never talk
gone there?>> I don't think so.She never talked
gone there?>> I don't think so.She never talked abo
gone there?>> I don't think so.She never talked about
gone there?>> I don't think so.She never talked about h
gone there?>> I don't think so.She never talked about her
gone there?>> I don't think so.She never talked about her.
>> I don't think so.She never talked about her.
>> I don't think so.She never talked about her.>>
>> I don't think so.She never talked about her.>> O
>> I don't think so.She never talked about her.>> Okay.
We
Well
Well,
Well, we
Well, we'll
Well, we'll do
Well, we'll do t
Well, we'll do the
Well, we'll do the bes
Well, we'll do the best
Well, we'll do the bestwe
Well, we'll do the bestwe c
Well, we'll do the bestwe can
Well, we'll do the bestwe can, ki
Well, we'll do the bestwe can, kids
Well, we'll do the bestwe can, kids.
Well, we'll do the bestwe can, kids.Ha
Well, we'll do the bestwe can, kids.Hang
Well, we'll do the bestwe can, kids.Hang i
Well, we'll do the bestwe can, kids.Hang in th
Well, we'll do the bestwe can, kids.Hang in ther
Well, we'll do the bestwe can, kids.Hang in there,
Well, we'll do the bestwe can, kids.Hang in there, k
Well, we'll do the bestwe can, kids.Hang in there, kiddo
Well, we'll do the bestwe can, kids.Hang in there, kiddo.
Uh..
Uh...
In
In t
In the
In the mea
In the meant
In the meantim
In the meantime.
In the meantime...
In the meantime...ca
In the meantime...can
In the meantime...can I
In the meantime...can I assu
In the meantime...can I assume
In the meantime...can I assume t
In the meantime...can I assume the
In the meantime...can I assume the Til
In the meantime...can I assume the Tille
In the meantime...can I assume the Tillerm
In the meantime...can I assume the Tillerman
In the meantime...can I assume the Tillermans
In the meantime...can I assume the Tillermansar
In the meantime...can I assume the Tillermansare
In the meantime...can I assume the Tillermansare stay
In the meantime...can I assume the Tillermansare stayin
In the meantime...can I assume the Tillermansare staying
In the meantime...can I assume the Tillermansare staying he
In the meantime...can I assume the Tillermansare staying here?
can I assume the Tillermansare staying here?
can I assume the Tillermansare staying here?>>
can I assume the Tillermansare staying here?>> O
can I assume the Tillermansare staying here?>> Oh
can I assume the Tillermansare staying here?>> Oh dear
can I assume the Tillermansare staying here?>> Oh dear.
are staying here?>> Oh dear.
are staying here?>> Oh dear.>>
are staying here?>> Oh dear.>> W
are staying here?>> Oh dear.>> We'
are staying here?>> Oh dear.>> We're c
are staying here?>> Oh dear.>> We're che
are staying here?>> Oh dear.>> We're check
are staying here?>> Oh dear.>> We're checkin
are staying here?>> Oh dear.>> We're checking on
are staying here?>> Oh dear.>> We're checking on s
are staying here?>> Oh dear.>> We're checking on som
are staying here?>> Oh dear.>> We're checking on some
>> Oh dear.>> We're checking on some
>> Oh dear.>> We're checking on somepo
>> Oh dear.>> We're checking on someposs
>> Oh dear.>> We're checking on somepossib
>> Oh dear.>> We're checking on somepossible a
>> Oh dear.>> We're checking on somepossible arr
>> Oh dear.>> We're checking on somepossible arran
>> Oh dear.>> We're checking on somepossible arrange
>> Oh dear.>> We're checking on somepossible arrangement
>> Oh dear.>> We're checking on somepossible arrangements.
>> We're checking on somepossible arrangements.
>> We're checking on somepossible arrangements.>>
>> We're checking on somepossible arrangements.>> T
>> We're checking on somepossible arrangements.>> Thi
>> We're checking on somepossible arrangements.>> This wh
>> We're checking on somepossible arrangements.>> This whol
>> We're checking on somepossible arrangements.>> This whole
>> We're checking on somepossible arrangements.>> This whole si
>> We're checking on somepossible arrangements.>> This whole situat
>> We're checking on somepossible arrangements.>> This whole situatio
>> We're checking on somepossible arrangements.>> This whole situation
possible arrangements.>> This whole situation
possible arrangements.>> This whole situationha
possible arrangements.>> This whole situationhas
possible arrangements.>> This whole situationhas ju
possible arrangements.>> This whole situationhas just b
possible arrangements.>> This whole situationhas just bee
possible arrangements.>> This whole situationhas just been
possible arrangements.>> This whole situationhas just been so
possible arrangements.>> This whole situationhas just been so str
possible arrangements.>> This whole situationhas just been so stres
possible arrangements.>> This whole situationhas just been so stressf
possible arrangements.>> This whole situationhas just been so stressful
possible arrangements.>> This whole situationhas just been so stressful.
>> This whole situationhas just been so stressful.
>> This whole situationhas just been so stressful.I'
>> This whole situationhas just been so stressful.I'm
>> This whole situationhas just been so stressful.I'm ju
>> This whole situationhas just been so stressful.I'm just n
>> This whole situationhas just been so stressful.I'm just not
>> This whole situationhas just been so stressful.I'm just not s
>> This whole situationhas just been so stressful.I'm just not sur
>> This whole situationhas just been so stressful.I'm just not sure ye
>> This whole situationhas just been so stressful.I'm just not sure yet.
has just been so stressful.I'm just not sure yet.
has just been so stressful.I'm just not sure yet.I
has just been so stressful.I'm just not sure yet.I ho
has just been so stressful.I'm just not sure yet.I hope y
has just been so stressful.I'm just not sure yet.I hope you
has just been so stressful.I'm just not sure yet.I hope you u
has just been so stressful.I'm just not sure yet.I hope you und
has just been so stressful.I'm just not sure yet.I hope you underst
has just been so stressful.I'm just not sure yet.I hope you understan
has just been so stressful.I'm just not sure yet.I hope you understand.
I'm just not sure yet.I hope you understand.
I'm just not sure yet.I hope you understand.>>
I'm just not sure yet.I hope you understand.>> T
I'm just not sure yet.I hope you understand.>> Tel
I'm just not sure yet.I hope you understand.>> Tell me
I'm just not sure yet.I hope you understand.>> Tell me a
I'm just not sure yet.I hope you understand.>> Tell me abo
I'm just not sure yet.I hope you understand.>> Tell me about
I'm just not sure yet.I hope you understand.>> Tell me about it.
I hope you understand.>> Tell me about it.
I hope you understand.>> Tell me about it.I'
I hope you understand.>> Tell me about it.I've
I hope you understand.>> Tell me about it.I've g
I hope you understand.>> Tell me about it.I've got f
I hope you understand.>> Tell me about it.I've got fou
I hope you understand.>> Tell me about it.I've got four
I hope you understand.>> Tell me about it.I've got four of
I hope you understand.>> Tell me about it.I've got four of my
I hope you understand.>> Tell me about it.I've got four of my ow
I hope you understand.>> Tell me about it.I've got four of my own.
(c
(clo
(clock
(clock tic
(clock ticki
(clock ticking
(clock ticking)
>>
>> Y
>> You
>> Your li
>> Your litt
>> Your little
>> Your little s
>> Your little siste
>> Your little sister
>> Your little sister ba
>> Your little sister bare
>> Your little sister barely
>> Your little sister barelyut
>> Your little sister barelyutte
>> Your little sister barelyuttere
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a wo
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word a
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word all e
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word all eve
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word all eveni
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word all evening
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word all evening.
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word all evening.Is
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word all evening.Is t
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word all evening.Is the
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word all evening.Is there s
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word all evening.Is there som
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word all evening.Is there somet
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word all evening.Is there somethi
>> Your little sister barelyuttered a word all evening.Is there something
uttered a word all evening.Is there something
uttered a word all evening.Is there somethingwr
uttered a word all evening.Is there somethingwron
uttered a word all evening.Is there somethingwrong
uttered a word all evening.Is there somethingwrong with
uttered a word all evening.Is there somethingwrong with h
uttered a word all evening.Is there somethingwrong with her
uttered a word all evening.Is there somethingwrong with her?
Po
Poor
Poor g
Poor gir
Poor girl.
I
I kn
I know
I know i
I know it ca
I know it can'
I know it can't
I know it can't be
I know it can't be eas
I know it can't be easy
I know it can't be easy fo
I know it can't be easy for
I know it can't be easy for you.
He
Here
Here n
Here now.
Th
Ther
There
There are
There are a
There are a fe
There are a few
There are a few thin
There are a few things
There are a few thingsI
There are a few thingsI fe
There are a few thingsI feel
There are a few thingsI feel obl
There are a few thingsI feel oblig
There are a few thingsI feel obligat
There are a few thingsI feel obligated
There are a few thingsI feel obligated to
There are a few thingsI feel obligated to te
There are a few thingsI feel obligated to tell
There are a few thingsI feel obligated to tell y
There are a few thingsI feel obligated to tell you.
There are a few thingsI feel obligated to tell you.Fi
There are a few thingsI feel obligated to tell you.Firs
There are a few thingsI feel obligated to tell you.Firstl
There are a few thingsI feel obligated to tell you.Firstly,
There are a few thingsI feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I g
There are a few thingsI feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I go
There are a few thingsI feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I go to
There are a few thingsI feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I go to m
There are a few thingsI feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I go to mass
I feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I go to mass
I feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I go to massev
I feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I go to massever
I feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I go to massevery
I feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I go to massevery morn
I feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I go to massevery mornin
I feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I go to massevery morning
I feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I go to massevery morning at
I feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:3
I feel obligated to tell you.Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.
Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.
Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.An
Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.And
Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.And I
Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.And I wa
Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.And I was ho
Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.And I was hopi
Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.And I was hoping
Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.And I was hoping t
Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that
Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that to
Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that tomo
Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that tomorr
Firstly, I go to massevery morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that tomorrow
every morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that tomorrow
every morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that tomorrowyou
every morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that tomorrowyou al
every morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that tomorrowyou all
every morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that tomorrowyou all mi
every morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that tomorrowyou all might
every morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that tomorrowyou all might jo
every morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that tomorrowyou all might join
every morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that tomorrowyou all might join m
every morning at 6:30.And I was hoping that tomorrowyou all might join me.
And I was hoping that tomorrowyou all might join me.
And I was hoping that tomorrowyou all might join me.>>
And I was hoping that tomorrowyou all might join me.>> O
And I was hoping that tomorrowyou all might join me.>> Oka
And I was hoping that tomorrowyou all might join me.>> Okay.
you all might join me.>> Okay.
you all might join me.>> Okay.>>
you all might join me.>> Okay.>> G
you all might join me.>> Okay.>> Good.
Se
Seco
Second
Secondly
Secondly, I'
Secondly, I'm
Secondly, I'm pl
Secondly, I'm plan
Secondly, I'm planning
Secondly, I'm planning t
Secondly, I'm planning to
Secondly, I'm planning tota
Secondly, I'm planning totake
Secondly, I'm planning totake t
Secondly, I'm planning totake the
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day o
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off t
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomor
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomorro
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomorrow.
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomorrow.It
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomorrow.It's
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomorrow.It's m
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomorrow.It's my fi
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomorrow.It's my firs
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomorrow.It's my first
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomorrow.It's my first in
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomorrow.It's my first in sev
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomorrow.It's my first in seven
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomorrow.It's my first in seven y
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomorrow.It's my first in seven yea
Secondly, I'm planning totake the day off tomorrow.It's my first in seven years.
take the day off tomorrow.It's my first in seven years.
take the day off tomorrow.It's my first in seven years.>>
take the day off tomorrow.It's my first in seven years.>> Y
take the day off tomorrow.It's my first in seven years.>> You
take the day off tomorrow.It's my first in seven years.>> You don
take the day off tomorrow.It's my first in seven years.>> You don't
take the day off tomorrow.It's my first in seven years.>> You don't h
take the day off tomorrow.It's my first in seven years.>> You don't hav
take the day off tomorrow.It's my first in seven years.>> You don't have to
take the day off tomorrow.It's my first in seven years.>> You don't have to.
It's my first in seven years.>> You don't have to.
It's my first in seven years.>> You don't have to.We
It's my first in seven years.>> You don't have to.We'l
It's my first in seven years.>> You don't have to.We'll
It's my first in seven years.>> You don't have to.We'll be
It's my first in seven years.>> You don't have to.We'll be oka
It's my first in seven years.>> You don't have to.We'll be okay.
>> You don't have to.We'll be okay.
>> You don't have to.We'll be okay.>>
>> You don't have to.We'll be okay.>> Y
>> You don't have to.We'll be okay.>> Yes
>> You don't have to.We'll be okay.>> Yes, we
>> You don't have to.We'll be okay.>> Yes, well
>> You don't have to.We'll be okay.>> Yes, well,
>> You don't have to.We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, yo
>> You don't have to.We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you se
>> You don't have to.We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you see,
We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you see,
We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you see,afte
We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you see,after
We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you see,after ma
We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you see,after mass
We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you see,after mass, we
We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you see,after mass, we'l
We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you see,after mass, we'll
We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you see,after mass, we'll be
We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you see,after mass, we'll be goi
We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you see,after mass, we'll be going
We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you see,after mass, we'll be going t
We'll be okay.>> Yes, well, you see,after mass, we'll be going to
>> Yes, well, you see,after mass, we'll be going to
>> Yes, well, you see,after mass, we'll be going toth
>> Yes, well, you see,after mass, we'll be going tothe
>> Yes, well, you see,after mass, we'll be going tothe re
>> Yes, well, you see,after mass, we'll be going tothe rector
>> Yes, well, you see,after mass, we'll be going tothe rectory.
after mass, we'll be going tothe rectory.
after mass, we'll be going tothe rectory.>>
after mass, we'll be going tothe rectory.>> W
after mass, we'll be going tothe rectory.>> Wha
after mass, we'll be going tothe rectory.>> What fo
after mass, we'll be going tothe rectory.>> What for?
the rectory.>> What for?
the rectory.>> What for?>>
the rectory.>> What for?>> O
the rectory.>> What for?>> Our d
the rectory.>> What for?>> Our dea
the rectory.>> What for?>> Our dear
the rectory.>> What for?>> Our dear Fa
the rectory.>> What for?>> Our dear Father
the rectory.>> What for?>> Our dear Father J
the rectory.>> What for?>> Our dear Father Jos
the rectory.>> What for?>> Our dear Father Josep
the rectory.>> What for?>> Our dear Father Joseph
>> What for?>> Our dear Father Joseph
>> What for?>> Our dear Father Josephha
>> What for?>> Our dear Father Josephhas
>> What for?>> Our dear Father Josephhas ar
>> What for?>> Our dear Father Josephhas arrang
>> What for?>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged
>> What for?>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged f
>> What for?>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged for
>> What for?>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged for sev
>> What for?>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged for sever
>> What for?>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged for several
>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged for several
>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged for severalof
>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged for severalof t
>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged for severalof the p
>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged for severalof the par
>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged for severalof the paris
>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged for severalof the parish
>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged for severalof the parish fami
>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged for severalof the parish famili
>> Our dear Father Josephhas arranged for severalof the parish families
has arranged for severalof the parish families
has arranged for severalof the parish familiesto
has arranged for severalof the parish familiesto m
has arranged for severalof the parish familiesto meet
has arranged for severalof the parish familiesto meet wi
has arranged for severalof the parish familiesto meet with
has arranged for severalof the parish familiesto meet with y
has arranged for severalof the parish familiesto meet with your
has arranged for severalof the parish familiesto meet with your br
has arranged for severalof the parish familiesto meet with your brot
has arranged for severalof the parish familiesto meet with your brothe
has arranged for severalof the parish familiesto meet with your brothers.
of the parish familiesto meet with your brothers.
of the parish familiesto meet with your brothers.>>
of the parish familiesto meet with your brothers.>> W
of the parish familiesto meet with your brothers.>> Why
of the parish familiesto meet with your brothers.>> Why?
to meet with your brothers.>> Why?
to meet with your brothers.>> Why?>>
to meet with your brothers.>> Why?>> B
to meet with your brothers.>> Why?>> Bec
to meet with your brothers.>> Why?>> Because
to meet with your brothers.>> Why?>> Because I
to meet with your brothers.>> Why?>> Because I a
to meet with your brothers.>> Why?>> Because I am
to meet with your brothers.>> Why?>> Because I am simp
to meet with your brothers.>> Why?>> Because I am simply
>> Why?>> Because I am simply
>> Why?>> Because I am simplyno
>> Why?>> Because I am simplynot
>> Why?>> Because I am simplynot eq
>> Why?>> Because I am simplynot equipp
>> Why?>> Because I am simplynot equipped
>> Why?>> Because I am simplynot equipped t
>> Why?>> Because I am simplynot equipped to
>> Why?>> Because I am simplynot equipped to harb
>> Why?>> Because I am simplynot equipped to harbor
>> Because I am simplynot equipped to harbor
>> Because I am simplynot equipped to harborfour
>> Because I am simplynot equipped to harborfour a
>> Because I am simplynot equipped to harborfour act
>> Because I am simplynot equipped to harborfour activ
>> Because I am simplynot equipped to harborfour active ch
>> Because I am simplynot equipped to harborfour active chil
>> Because I am simplynot equipped to harborfour active childr
>> Because I am simplynot equipped to harborfour active children
not equipped to harborfour active children
not equipped to harborfour active childrenun
not equipped to harborfour active childrenunde
not equipped to harborfour active childrenunder th
not equipped to harborfour active childrenunder this
not equipped to harborfour active childrenunder this t
not equipped to harborfour active childrenunder this tin
not equipped to harborfour active childrenunder this tiny ro
not equipped to harborfour active childrenunder this tiny roof
not equipped to harborfour active childrenunder this tiny roof.
four active childrenunder this tiny roof.
four active childrenunder this tiny roof.We
four active childrenunder this tiny roof.We g
four active childrenunder this tiny roof.We gir
four active childrenunder this tiny roof.We girls,
four active childrenunder this tiny roof.We girls, Go
four active childrenunder this tiny roof.We girls, God
four active childrenunder this tiny roof.We girls, God wi
four active childrenunder this tiny roof.We girls, God willin
four active childrenunder this tiny roof.We girls, God willing,
under this tiny roof.We girls, God willing,
under this tiny roof.We girls, God willing,wi
under this tiny roof.We girls, God willing,will
under this tiny roof.We girls, God willing,will m
under this tiny roof.We girls, God willing,will manag
under this tiny roof.We girls, God willing,will manage
under this tiny roof.We girls, God willing,will manage so
under this tiny roof.We girls, God willing,will manage some
under this tiny roof.We girls, God willing,will manage somehow.
We girls, God willing,will manage somehow.
We girls, God willing,will manage somehow.>>
We girls, God willing,will manage somehow.>> B
We girls, God willing,will manage somehow.>> But,
We girls, God willing,will manage somehow.>> But, Co
We girls, God willing,will manage somehow.>> But, Cous
We girls, God willing,will manage somehow.>> But, Cousin
We girls, God willing,will manage somehow.>> But, Cousin Eun
We girls, God willing,will manage somehow.>> But, Cousin Eunic
We girls, God willing,will manage somehow.>> But, Cousin Eunice,
will manage somehow.>> But, Cousin Eunice,
will manage somehow.>> But, Cousin Eunice,I
will manage somehow.>> But, Cousin Eunice,I pr
will manage somehow.>> But, Cousin Eunice,I prom
will manage somehow.>> But, Cousin Eunice,I promised
will manage somehow.>> But, Cousin Eunice,I promised t
will manage somehow.>> But, Cousin Eunice,I promised the
will manage somehow.>> But, Cousin Eunice,I promised them
will manage somehow.>> But, Cousin Eunice,I promised them that
>> But, Cousin Eunice,I promised them that
>> But, Cousin Eunice,I promised them thatwe'd
>> But, Cousin Eunice,I promised them thatwe'd s
>> But, Cousin Eunice,I promised them thatwe'd sta
>> But, Cousin Eunice,I promised them thatwe'd stay
>> But, Cousin Eunice,I promised them thatwe'd stay toge
>> But, Cousin Eunice,I promised them thatwe'd stay togeth
>> But, Cousin Eunice,I promised them thatwe'd stay together
>> But, Cousin Eunice,I promised them thatwe'd stay together.
I promised them thatwe'd stay together.
I promised them thatwe'd stay together.>>
I promised them thatwe'd stay together.>> Y
I promised them thatwe'd stay together.>> You k
I promised them thatwe'd stay together.>> You kno
I promised them thatwe'd stay together.>> You know,
I promised them thatwe'd stay together.>> You know, F
I promised them thatwe'd stay together.>> You know, Fathe
I promised them thatwe'd stay together.>> You know, Father
I promised them thatwe'd stay together.>> You know, Father Jo
I promised them thatwe'd stay together.>> You know, Father Jose
I promised them thatwe'd stay together.>> You know, Father Joseph
we'd stay together.>> You know, Father Joseph
we'd stay together.>> You know, Father Josephsaid
we'd stay together.>> You know, Father Josephsaid I
we'd stay together.>> You know, Father Josephsaid I w
we'd stay together.>> You know, Father Josephsaid I was
we'd stay together.>> You know, Father Josephsaid I was a s
we'd stay together.>> You know, Father Josephsaid I was a sai
we'd stay together.>> You know, Father Josephsaid I was a saint
>> You know, Father Josephsaid I was a saint
>> You know, Father Josephsaid I was a saintto t
>> You know, Father Josephsaid I was a saintto tak
>> You know, Father Josephsaid I was a saintto take
>> You know, Father Josephsaid I was a saintto take yo
>> You know, Father Josephsaid I was a saintto take you in
>> You know, Father Josephsaid I was a saintto take you in.
said I was a saintto take you in.
said I was a saintto take you in.He
said I was a saintto take you in.He s
said I was a saintto take you in.He sai
said I was a saintto take you in.He said an
said I was a saintto take you in.He said anyb
said I was a saintto take you in.He said anybod
said I was a saintto take you in.He said anybody
said I was a saintto take you in.He said anybody else
said I was a saintto take you in.He said anybody else w
said I was a saintto take you in.He said anybody else wou
said I was a saintto take you in.He said anybody else would
to take you in.He said anybody else would
to take you in.He said anybody else wouldturn
to take you in.He said anybody else wouldturn y
to take you in.He said anybody else wouldturn you
to take you in.He said anybody else wouldturn you o
to take you in.He said anybody else wouldturn you over
to take you in.He said anybody else wouldturn you over to
He said anybody else wouldturn you over to
He said anybody else wouldturn you over toso
He said anybody else wouldturn you over tosoci
He said anybody else wouldturn you over tosocial
He said anybody else wouldturn you over tosocial s
He said anybody else wouldturn you over tosocial servi
He said anybody else wouldturn you over tosocial service
He said anybody else wouldturn you over tosocial services.
turn you over tosocial services.
turn you over tosocial services.Bu
turn you over tosocial services.But
turn you over tosocial services.But I sa
turn you over tosocial services.But I said
turn you over tosocial services.But I said,
turn you over tosocial services.But I said, "I
turn you over tosocial services.But I said, "I can
turn you over tosocial services.But I said, "I can't
turn you over tosocial services.But I said, "I can't d
turn you over tosocial services.But I said, "I can't do
turn you over tosocial services.But I said, "I can't do that
turn you over tosocial services.But I said, "I can't do that.
social services.But I said, "I can't do that.
social services.But I said, "I can't do that.Th
social services.But I said, "I can't do that.They
social services.But I said, "I can't do that.They're
social services.But I said, "I can't do that.They're my
social services.But I said, "I can't do that.They're my f
social services.But I said, "I can't do that.They're my fle
social services.But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh a
social services.But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and
social services.But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and b
social services.But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blo
social services.But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blood."
But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blood."
But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blood.">>
But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blood.">> B
But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blood.">> But
But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blood.">> But you
But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blood.">> But you d
But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blood.">> But you don
But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blood.">> But you don't
But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blood.">> But you don't und
But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blood.">> But you don't under
But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blood.">> But you don't underst
But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blood.">> But you don't understan
But I said, "I can't do that.They're my flesh and blood.">> But you don't understand--
They're my flesh and blood.">> But you don't understand--
Th
Ther
There, I
There, I f
There, I fee
There, I feel
There, I feel so r
There, I feel so rel
There, I feel so relie
There, I feel so relieve
There, I feel so relieved
There, I feel so relievednow
There, I feel so relievednow we
There, I feel so relievednow we'v
There, I feel so relievednow we've
There, I feel so relievednow we've had
There, I feel so relievednow we've had th
There, I feel so relievednow we've had this
There, I feel so relievednow we've had thisli
There, I feel so relievednow we've had thislitt
There, I feel so relievednow we've had thislittle
There, I feel so relievednow we've had thislittle c
There, I feel so relievednow we've had thislittle chat,
There, I feel so relievednow we've had thislittle chat, d
There, I feel so relievednow we've had thislittle chat, don
There, I feel so relievednow we've had thislittle chat, don't
There, I feel so relievednow we've had thislittle chat, don't you
There, I feel so relievednow we've had thislittle chat, don't you?
♪
(d
(doo
(door
(door cr
(door creaki
(door creaking
(door creaking)
(s
(sno
(snori
(snoring)
(d
(doo
(door
(door crea
(door creaki
(door creaking
(door creaking)
(c
(cou
(cough
(coughing)
(coughing)>> B
(coughing)>> By
(coughing)>> By th
(coughing)>> By the
(coughing)>> By the time
(coughing)>> By the time C
(coughing)>> By the time Cou
(coughing)>> By the time Cousi
(coughing)>> By the time Cousin Eu
(coughing)>> By the time Cousin Euni
(coughing)>> By the time Cousin Eunice
(coughing)>> By the time Cousin Eunicewa
(coughing)>> By the time Cousin Eunicewake
(coughing)>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes
(coughing)>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up
(coughing)>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we
(coughing)>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we p
(coughing)>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pas
(coughing)>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass
(coughing)>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New
(coughing)>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New Yo
(coughing)>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New York
>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New York
>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New Yorkan
>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New Yorkand
>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New Yorkand on
>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the
>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the w
>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way
>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way t
>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Cr
>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Cris
>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfi
>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfiel
>> By the time Cousin Eunicewakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfield.
wakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfield.
wakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfield.>>
wakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfield.>> Y
wakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfield.>> You
wakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfield.>> You thi
wakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfield.>> You think
wakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfield.>> You think t
wakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfield.>> You think the
wakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfield.>> You think they're
wakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfield.>> You think they're g
wakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfield.>> You think they're gon
wakes up, we pass New Yorkand on the way to Crisfield.>> You think they're gonna
and on the way to Crisfield.>> You think they're gonna
and on the way to Crisfield.>> You think they're gonnatr
and on the way to Crisfield.>> You think they're gonnatry
and on the way to Crisfield.>> You think they're gonnatry to c
and on the way to Crisfield.>> You think they're gonnatry to cat
and on the way to Crisfield.>> You think they're gonnatry to catch
and on the way to Crisfield.>> You think they're gonnatry to catch u
and on the way to Crisfield.>> You think they're gonnatry to catch us?
>> You think they're gonnatry to catch us?
>> You think they're gonnatry to catch us?>>
>> You think they're gonnatry to catch us?>> A
>> You think they're gonnatry to catch us?>> Any
>> You think they're gonnatry to catch us?>> Anywa
>> You think they're gonnatry to catch us?>> Anyway...
try to catch us?>> Anyway...
try to catch us?>> Anyway...th
try to catch us?>> Anyway...they
try to catch us?>> Anyway...they k
try to catch us?>> Anyway...they know
try to catch us?>> Anyway...they know we
try to catch us?>> Anyway...they know we'r
try to catch us?>> Anyway...they know we're
try to catch us?>> Anyway...they know we're goin
try to catch us?>> Anyway...they know we're going.
>> Anyway...they know we're going.
>> Anyway...they know we're going.I le
>> Anyway...they know we're going.I left
>> Anyway...they know we're going.I left a
>> Anyway...they know we're going.I left a n
>> Anyway...they know we're going.I left a note.
they know we're going.I left a note.
they know we're going.I left a note.>>
they know we're going.I left a note.>> D
they know we're going.I left a note.>> Dic
they know we're going.I left a note.>> Dicey,
they know we're going.I left a note.>> Dicey, yo
they know we're going.I left a note.>> Dicey, you
they know we're going.I left a note.>> Dicey, you ru
they know we're going.I left a note.>> Dicey, you ruined
they know we're going.I left a note.>> Dicey, you ruined i
they know we're going.I left a note.>> Dicey, you ruined it.
I left a note.>> Dicey, you ruined it.
I left a note.>> Dicey, you ruined it.We c
I left a note.>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can
I left a note.>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't
I left a note.>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't b
I left a note.>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be ru
I left a note.>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be runn
I left a note.>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be runnin
I left a note.>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running
I left a note.>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running away
>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running away
>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running awayif
>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running awayif t
>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running awayif the
>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running awayif they
>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running awayif they know
>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running awayif they know w
>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running awayif they know whe
>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running awayif they know where
>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running awayif they know where we'
>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running awayif they know where we're
>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running awayif they know where we're g
>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running awayif they know where we're goi
>> Dicey, you ruined it.We can't be running awayif they know where we're going.
We can't be running awayif they know where we're going.
We can't be running awayif they know where we're going.>> A
We can't be running awayif they know where we're going.>> Are
We can't be running awayif they know where we're going.>> Are w
We can't be running awayif they know where we're going.>> Are we
We can't be running awayif they know where we're going.>> Are we runa
We can't be running awayif they know where we're going.>> Are we runawa
We can't be running awayif they know where we're going.>> Are we runaways
We can't be running awayif they know where we're going.>> Are we runaways?
if they know where we're going.>> Are we runaways?
if they know where we're going.>> Are we runaways?>> W
if they know where we're going.>> Are we runaways?>> We'
if they know where we're going.>> Are we runaways?>> We're
if they know where we're going.>> Are we runaways?>> We're n
if they know where we're going.>> Are we runaways?>> We're not r
if they know where we're going.>> Are we runaways?>> We're not run
if they know where we're going.>> Are we runaways?>> We're not runni
if they know where we're going.>> Are we runaways?>> We're not running
if they know where we're going.>> Are we runaways?>> We're not running awa
if they know where we're going.>> Are we runaways?>> We're not running away.
>> Are we runaways?>> We're not running away.
>> Are we runaways?>> We're not running away.We
>> Are we runaways?>> We're not running away.We'r
>> Are we runaways?>> We're not running away.We're
>> Are we runaways?>> We're not running away.We're just
>> Are we runaways?>> We're not running away.We're just g
>> Are we runaways?>> We're not running away.We're just goi
>> Are we runaways?>> We're not running away.We're just going
>> Are we runaways?>> We're not running away.We're just going to
>> Are we runaways?>> We're not running away.We're just going to se
>> Are we runaways?>> We're not running away.We're just going to see.
>> We're not running away.We're just going to see.
>> We're not running away.We're just going to see.>>
>> We're not running away.We're just going to see.>> W
>> We're not running away.We're just going to see.>> Wel
>> We're not running away.We're just going to see.>> Well, I
>> We're not running away.We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm
>> We're not running away.We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm r
>> We're not running away.We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm run
>> We're not running away.We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm running
>> We're not running away.We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm running a
>> We're not running away.We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm running awa
>> We're not running away.We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm running away.
We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm running away.
We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm running away.Be
We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm running away.Befo
We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm running away.Before,
We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we
We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we w
We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we wer
We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were al
We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were alwa
We're just going to see.>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were always
>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were always
>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were alwaysth
>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were alwaysthe
>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were alwaysthe ones
>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were alwaysthe ones p
>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were alwaysthe ones peo
>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were alwaysthe ones peopl
>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ra
>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran
>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran aw
>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away
>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away fro
>> Well, I'm running away.Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away from.
Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away from.
Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away from.Th
Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away from.This
Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away from.This t
Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away from.This time
Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away from.This time I
Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away from.This time I wa
Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away from.This time I want
Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away from.This time I want us
Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away from.This time I want us to
Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away from.This time I want us to d
Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away from.This time I want us to do
Before, we were alwaysthe ones people ran away from.This time I want us to do it.
the ones people ran away from.This time I want us to do it.
the ones people ran away from.This time I want us to do it.>>
the ones people ran away from.This time I want us to do it.>> Y
the ones people ran away from.This time I want us to do it.>> Yea
the ones people ran away from.This time I want us to do it.>> Yeah, m
the ones people ran away from.This time I want us to do it.>> Yeah, me
the ones people ran away from.This time I want us to do it.>> Yeah, me to
the ones people ran away from.This time I want us to do it.>> Yeah, me too.
This time I want us to do it.>> Yeah, me too.
This time I want us to do it.>> Yeah, me too.We
This time I want us to do it.>> Yeah, me too.We'r
This time I want us to do it.>> Yeah, me too.We're ru
This time I want us to do it.>> Yeah, me too.We're runa
This time I want us to do it.>> Yeah, me too.We're runawa
This time I want us to do it.>> Yeah, me too.We're runaways
This time I want us to do it.>> Yeah, me too.We're runaways.
>>
>> Y
>> You
>> You s
>> You scare
>> You scared?
So
So a
So am
So am I.
(sea
(seagu
(seagull
(seagulls
(seagulls squa
(seagulls squawk
(seagulls squawkin
(seagulls squawking)
>>
>> C
>> Crisf
>> Crisfie
>> Crisfield
>> Crisfield.
>> Crisfield.Cr
>> Crisfield.Cris
>> Crisfield.Crisfi
>> Crisfield.Crisfield,
>> Crisfield.Crisfield, f
>> Crisfield.Crisfield, fol
>> Crisfield.Crisfield, folks
>> Crisfield.Crisfield, folks.
(a
(air
(air b
(air bra
(air brakes
(air brakes hi
(air brakes hiss
(air brakes hissin
(air brakes hissing)
>>
>> H
>> Hi!
(d
(dis
(dista
(distant
(distant whi
(distant whist
(distant whistle
(distant whistle b
(distant whistle blowi
(distant whistle blowing
(distant whistle blowing)
>>
>>Ho
>>Howe
>>Howeve
>>However, t
>>However, the
>>However, there
>>However, there i
>>However, there is
>>However, there isa lo
>>However, there isa low-
>>However, there isa low-pr
>>However, there isa low-pres
>>However, there isa low-pressure
>>However, there isa low-pressure a
>>However, there isa low-pressure are
>>However, there isa low-pressure area
>>However, there isa low-pressure areaform
>>However, there isa low-pressure areaformin
>>However, there isa low-pressure areaforming
>>However, there isa low-pressure areaforming to
>>However, there isa low-pressure areaforming toward
>>However, there isa low-pressure areaforming towards
>>However, there isa low-pressure areaforming towards Ba
>>However, there isa low-pressure areaforming towards Balt
>>However, there isa low-pressure areaforming towards Baltimor
>>However, there isa low-pressure areaforming towards Baltimore.
a low-pressure areaforming towards Baltimore.
a low-pressure areaforming towards Baltimore.Th
a low-pressure areaforming towards Baltimore.The po
a low-pressure areaforming towards Baltimore.The poss
a low-pressure areaforming towards Baltimore.The possib
a low-pressure areaforming towards Baltimore.The possibil
a low-pressure areaforming towards Baltimore.The possibility
a low-pressure areaforming towards Baltimore.The possibility of
forming towards Baltimore.The possibility of
forming towards Baltimore.The possibility ofthun
forming towards Baltimore.The possibility ofthunde
forming towards Baltimore.The possibility ofthunders
forming towards Baltimore.The possibility ofthundersho
forming towards Baltimore.The possibility ofthundershowers
forming towards Baltimore.The possibility ofthundershowers a
forming towards Baltimore.The possibility ofthundershowers all
forming towards Baltimore.The possibility ofthundershowers all a
forming towards Baltimore.The possibility ofthundershowers all along
forming towards Baltimore.The possibility ofthundershowers all along..
forming towards Baltimore.The possibility ofthundershowers all along...
The possibility ofthundershowers all along...
The possibility ofthundershowers all along...Mo
The possibility ofthundershowers all along...Mostly
The possibility ofthundershowers all along...Mostly c
The possibility ofthundershowers all along...Mostly cle
The possibility ofthundershowers all along...Mostly clear
The possibility ofthundershowers all along...Mostly clear ski
The possibility ofthundershowers all along...Mostly clear skies
The possibility ofthundershowers all along...Mostly clear skies.
If
If you
If you'r
If you're
If you're th
If you're thinki
If you're thinking
If you're thinking o
If you're thinking of
If you're thinking of gett
If you're thinking of gettin
If you're thinking of getting
If you're thinking of gettingany
If you're thinking of gettingany sa
If you're thinking of gettingany sail
If you're thinking of gettingany sailin
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in,
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, to
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, toda
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, today wo
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, today woul
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, today would
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, today would be
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, today would bea
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, today would beaperf
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, today would beaperfec
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, today would beaperfect
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, today would beaperfect da
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, today would beaperfect day fo
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, today would beaperfect day for
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, today would beaperfect day for it
If you're thinking of gettingany sailing in, today would beaperfect day for it.
any sailing in, today would beaperfect day for it.
any sailing in, today would beaperfect day for it.>>
any sailing in, today would beaperfect day for it.>> S
any sailing in, today would beaperfect day for it.>> Som
any sailing in, today would beaperfect day for it.>> Somethi
any sailing in, today would beaperfect day for it.>> Something
any sailing in, today would beaperfect day for it.>> Something w
any sailing in, today would beaperfect day for it.>> Something wro
any sailing in, today would beaperfect day for it.>> Something wrong?
>>
>> I
>> I w
>> I was
>> I was loo
>> I was looki
>> I was looking
>> I was looking f
>> I was looking for
>> I was looking forth
>> I was looking forthe
>> I was looking forthe te
>> I was looking forthe teleph
>> I was looking forthe telephon
>> I was looking forthe telephone
>> I was looking forthe telephone nu
>> I was looking forthe telephone number
>> I was looking forthe telephone numberfor
>> I was looking forthe telephone numberfor Ab
>> I was looking forthe telephone numberfor Abig
>> I was looking forthe telephone numberfor Abigai
>> I was looking forthe telephone numberfor Abigail Ti
>> I was looking forthe telephone numberfor Abigail Till
>> I was looking forthe telephone numberfor Abigail Tiller
>> I was looking forthe telephone numberfor Abigail Tillerma
>> I was looking forthe telephone numberfor Abigail Tillerman.
the telephone numberfor Abigail Tillerman.
the telephone numberfor Abigail Tillerman.>> W
the telephone numberfor Abigail Tillerman.>> Why
the telephone numberfor Abigail Tillerman.>> Why w
the telephone numberfor Abigail Tillerman.>> Why wou
the telephone numberfor Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would y
the telephone numberfor Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you
the telephone numberfor Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you d
the telephone numberfor Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do
the telephone numberfor Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do that
the telephone numberfor Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do that?
for Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do that?
for Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do that?>>
for Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do that?>> I
for Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do that?>> I w
for Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do that?>> I was g
for Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do that?>> I was gon
for Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna
for Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna c
for Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call
for Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call he
for Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her
for Abigail Tillerman.>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her up
>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her up
>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her upan
>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her upand
>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her upand se
>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her upand see if
>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her upand see if s
>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her upand see if she
>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her upand see if she n
>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her upand see if she needs
>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her upand see if she needs s
>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her upand see if she needs som
>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her upand see if she needs some
>> Why would you do that?>> I was gonna call her upand see if she needs some help
>> I was gonna call her upand see if she needs some help
>> I was gonna call her upand see if she needs some helpon
>> I was gonna call her upand see if she needs some helpon h
>> I was gonna call her upand see if she needs some helpon her
>> I was gonna call her upand see if she needs some helpon her far
>> I was gonna call her upand see if she needs some helpon her farm.
and see if she needs some helpon her farm.
and see if she needs some helpon her farm.>>
and see if she needs some helpon her farm.>> A
and see if she needs some helpon her farm.>> Ab
and see if she needs some helpon her farm.>> Ab won'
and see if she needs some helpon her farm.>> Ab won't
and see if she needs some helpon her farm.>> Ab won't hi
and see if she needs some helpon her farm.>> Ab won't hire
and see if she needs some helpon her farm.>> Ab won't hire you
and see if she needs some helpon her farm.>> Ab won't hire you.
on her farm.>> Ab won't hire you.
on her farm.>> Ab won't hire you.Be
on her farm.>> Ab won't hire you.Besi
on her farm.>> Ab won't hire you.Beside
on her farm.>> Ab won't hire you.Besides,
on her farm.>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she
on her farm.>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she h
on her farm.>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she has
on her farm.>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she hasn'
on her farm.>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she hasn't ha
on her farm.>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she hasn't had
>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she hasn't had
>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she hasn't hada
>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she hasn't hada ph
>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she hasn't hada phon
>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she hasn't hada phone si
>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she hasn't hada phone sinc
>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she hasn't hada phone since
>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she hasn't hada phone since th
>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she hasn't hada phone since the da
>> Ab won't hire you.Besides, she hasn't hada phone since the day
Besides, she hasn't hada phone since the day
Besides, she hasn't hada phone since the daysh
Besides, she hasn't hada phone since the dayshe
Besides, she hasn't hada phone since the dayshe ca
Besides, she hasn't hada phone since the dayshe came i
Besides, she hasn't hada phone since the dayshe came int
Besides, she hasn't hada phone since the dayshe came into
Besides, she hasn't hada phone since the dayshe came into to
Besides, she hasn't hada phone since the dayshe came into town.
a phone since the dayshe came into town.
a phone since the dayshe came into town.Th
a phone since the dayshe came into town.Thre
a phone since the dayshe came into town.Threw
a phone since the dayshe came into town.Threw it t
a phone since the dayshe came into town.Threw it thr
a phone since the dayshe came into town.Threw it throu
a phone since the dayshe came into town.Threw it through
a phone since the dayshe came into town.Threw it through the
a phone since the dayshe came into town.Threw it through the b
a phone since the dayshe came into town.Threw it through the big
she came into town.Threw it through the big
she came into town.Threw it through the bigpl
she came into town.Threw it through the bigplat
she came into town.Threw it through the bigplate
she came into town.Threw it through the bigplate gl
she came into town.Threw it through the bigplate glass
she came into town.Threw it through the bigplate glass wi
she came into town.Threw it through the bigplate glass wind
she came into town.Threw it through the bigplate glass window
Threw it through the bigplate glass window
Threw it through the bigplate glass windowdo
Threw it through the bigplate glass windowdown
Threw it through the bigplate glass windowdown a
Threw it through the bigplate glass windowdown at th
Threw it through the bigplate glass windowdown at the
Threw it through the bigplate glass windowdown at the ph
Threw it through the bigplate glass windowdown at the phon
Threw it through the bigplate glass windowdown at the phone co
Threw it through the bigplate glass windowdown at the phone comp
Threw it through the bigplate glass windowdown at the phone compan
Threw it through the bigplate glass windowdown at the phone company.
plate glass windowdown at the phone company.
plate glass windowdown at the phone company.Yo
plate glass windowdown at the phone company.You
plate glass windowdown at the phone company.You do
plate glass windowdown at the phone company.You don't
plate glass windowdown at the phone company.You don't wa
plate glass windowdown at the phone company.You don't wann
plate glass windowdown at the phone company.You don't wanna
plate glass windowdown at the phone company.You don't wanna work
plate glass windowdown at the phone company.You don't wanna work f
plate glass windowdown at the phone company.You don't wanna work for
plate glass windowdown at the phone company.You don't wanna work for h
plate glass windowdown at the phone company.You don't wanna work for her.
(b
(bla
(blade
(blade scr
(blade scrap
(blade scrapin
(blade scraping,
(blade scraping, scr
(blade scraping, scree
(blade scraping, screech
(blade scraping, screechin
(blade scraping, screeching)
>>
>>Well
>>Well,
>>Well, th
>>Well, that
>>Well, that's t
>>Well, that's the
>>Well, that's theFi
>>Well, that's theFish
>>Well, that's theFisher
>>Well, that's theFisherma
>>Well, that's theFisherman's
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWo
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWord
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor to
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor toda
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today,
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm B
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob W
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob Wilso
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>>
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> W
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Whe
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where i
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is he
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm a
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm any
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm anywa
>>Well, that's theFisherman'sWordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm anyway?
Wordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm anyway?
Wordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm anyway?(k
Wordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm anyway?(kni
Wordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife
Wordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife thu
Wordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife thudd
Wordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife thuddin
Wordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife thudding
Wordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife thudding tabl
Wordfor today, I'm Bob Wilson.>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife thudding table)
>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife thudding table)
>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife thudding table)>> L
>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife thudding table)>> Lan
>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife thudding table)>> Land
>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife thudding table)>> Land an
>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife thudding table)>> Land and Ne
>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife thudding table)>> Land and Neck
>> Where is her farm anyway?(knife thudding table)>> Land and Neck.
(knife thudding table)>> Land and Neck.
(knife thudding table)>> Land and Neck.It
(knife thudding table)>> Land and Neck.It's
(knife thudding table)>> Land and Neck.It's o
(knife thudding table)>> Land and Neck.It's off S
(knife thudding table)>> Land and Neck.It's off Sou
(knife thudding table)>> Land and Neck.It's off South
(knife thudding table)>> Land and Neck.It's off South M
(knife thudding table)>> Land and Neck.It's off South Main,
>> Land and Neck.It's off South Main,
>> Land and Neck.It's off South Main,ma
>> Land and Neck.It's off South Main,mayb
>> Land and Neck.It's off South Main,maybe
>> Land and Neck.It's off South Main,maybe a mi
>> Land and Neck.It's off South Main,maybe a mile
>> Land and Neck.It's off South Main,maybe a mile.
It's off South Main,maybe a mile.
It's off South Main,maybe a mile.Th
It's off South Main,maybe a mile.Ther
It's off South Main,maybe a mile.There'
It's off South Main,maybe a mile.There's a
It's off South Main,maybe a mile.There's a be
It's off South Main,maybe a mile.There's a bend
It's off South Main,maybe a mile.There's a bend o
It's off South Main,maybe a mile.There's a bend out t
It's off South Main,maybe a mile.There's a bend out the
It's off South Main,maybe a mile.There's a bend out there
maybe a mile.There's a bend out there
maybe a mile.There's a bend out therewi
maybe a mile.There's a bend out therewith
maybe a mile.There's a bend out therewith a
maybe a mile.There's a bend out therewith a new
maybe a mile.There's a bend out therewith a new l
maybe a mile.There's a bend out therewith a new lit
maybe a mile.There's a bend out therewith a new littl
maybe a mile.There's a bend out therewith a new little ho
maybe a mile.There's a bend out therewith a new little hous
maybe a mile.There's a bend out therewith a new little house
There's a bend out therewith a new little house
There's a bend out therewith a new little houseri
There's a bend out therewith a new little houserigh
There's a bend out therewith a new little houseright
There's a bend out therewith a new little houseright on i
There's a bend out therewith a new little houseright on it.
with a new little houseright on it.
with a new little houseright on it.Th
with a new little houseright on it.The
with a new little houseright on it.The ne
with a new little houseright on it.The next m
with a new little houseright on it.The next mai
with a new little houseright on it.The next mailb
with a new little houseright on it.The next mailbox
with a new little houseright on it.The next mailbox is
with a new little houseright on it.The next mailbox is Ab
with a new little houseright on it.The next mailbox is Ab's
with a new little houseright on it.The next mailbox is Ab's.
right on it.The next mailbox is Ab's.
right on it.The next mailbox is Ab's.But
right on it.The next mailbox is Ab's.But it
right on it.The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's
right on it.The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's a
right on it.The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about
right on it.The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about s
right on it.The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about sev
right on it.The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about seven
right on it.The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about seven mil
right on it.The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about seven miles
right on it.The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about seven miles.
The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about seven miles.
The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about seven miles.I wo
The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about seven miles.I woul
The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about seven miles.I wouldn
The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about seven miles.I wouldn't
The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about seven miles.I wouldn't go
The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about seven miles.I wouldn't go ou
The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about seven miles.I wouldn't go out
The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about seven miles.I wouldn't go out th
The next mailbox is Ab's.But it's about seven miles.I wouldn't go out there.
But it's about seven miles.I wouldn't go out there.
But it's about seven miles.I wouldn't go out there.Craz
But it's about seven miles.I wouldn't go out there.Crazy
But it's about seven miles.I wouldn't go out there.Crazy as
But it's about seven miles.I wouldn't go out there.Crazy as a
But it's about seven miles.I wouldn't go out there.Crazy as a coo
But it's about seven miles.I wouldn't go out there.Crazy as a coot.
I wouldn't go out there.Crazy as a coot.
I wouldn't go out there.Crazy as a coot.Th
I wouldn't go out there.Crazy as a coot.That
I wouldn't go out there.Crazy as a coot.That's
I wouldn't go out there.Crazy as a coot.That's m
I wouldn't go out there.Crazy as a coot.That's my op
I wouldn't go out there.Crazy as a coot.That's my opin
I wouldn't go out there.Crazy as a coot.That's my opinio
I wouldn't go out there.Crazy as a coot.That's my opinion.
Crazy as a coot.That's my opinion.
Crazy as a coot.That's my opinion.We
Crazy as a coot.That's my opinion.We l
Crazy as a coot.That's my opinion.We leave
Crazy as a coot.That's my opinion.We leave h
Crazy as a coot.That's my opinion.We leave her
Crazy as a coot.That's my opinion.We leave here
Crazy as a coot.That's my opinion.We leave here alon
Crazy as a coot.That's my opinion.We leave here alone;
That's my opinion.We leave here alone;
That's my opinion.We leave here alone;yo
That's my opinion.We leave here alone;you
That's my opinion.We leave here alone;you shou
That's my opinion.We leave here alone;you should
That's my opinion.We leave here alone;you should,
That's my opinion.We leave here alone;you should, to
That's my opinion.We leave here alone;you should, too.
We leave here alone;you should, too.
We leave here alone;you should, too.>> M
We leave here alone;you should, too.>> May
We leave here alone;you should, too.>> Maybe
We leave here alone;you should, too.>> Maybe y
We leave here alone;you should, too.>> Maybe you'r
We leave here alone;you should, too.>> Maybe you're
We leave here alone;you should, too.>> Maybe you're ri
We leave here alone;you should, too.>> Maybe you're righ
We leave here alone;you should, too.>> Maybe you're right.
you should, too.>> Maybe you're right.
you should, too.>> Maybe you're right.No
you should, too.>> Maybe you're right.No "
you should, too.>> Maybe you're right.No "ma
you should, too.>> Maybe you're right.No "maybes
you should, too.>> Maybe you're right.No "maybes"
you should, too.>> Maybe you're right.No "maybes" ab
you should, too.>> Maybe you're right.No "maybes" abou
you should, too.>> Maybe you're right.No "maybes" about it
you should, too.>> Maybe you're right.No "maybes" about it.
(s
(sea
(seagu
(seagulls
(seagulls sq
(seagulls squa
(seagulls squawk
(seagulls squawking)
(seagulls squawking)(hor
(seagulls squawking)(horn
(seagulls squawking)(horn bl
(seagulls squawking)(horn blow
(seagulls squawking)(horn blowing)
(seagulls squawking)(horn blowing)>>
(seagulls squawking)(horn blowing)>> Y
(seagulls squawking)(horn blowing)>> You
(seagulls squawking)(horn blowing)>> You k
(seagulls squawking)(horn blowing)>> You know
(seagulls squawking)(horn blowing)>> You know wh
(seagulls squawking)(horn blowing)>> You know what
(seagulls squawking)(horn blowing)>> You know what t
(seagulls squawking)(horn blowing)>> You know what this
(seagulls squawking)(horn blowing)>> You know what this is
(seagulls squawking)(horn blowing)>> You know what this is l
(seagulls squawking)(horn blowing)>> You know what this is lik
(seagulls squawking)(horn blowing)>> You know what this is like?
(horn blowing)>> You know what this is like?
(horn blowing)>> You know what this is like?It
(horn blowing)>> You know what this is like?It's
(horn blowing)>> You know what this is like?It's l
(horn blowing)>> You know what this is like?It's like
(horn blowing)>> You know what this is like?It's like Pr
(horn blowing)>> You know what this is like?It's like Prov
(horn blowing)>> You know what this is like?It's like Provin
(horn blowing)>> You know what this is like?It's like Provinceto
(horn blowing)>> You know what this is like?It's like Provincetown
(horn blowing)>> You know what this is like?It's like Provincetown,
>> You know what this is like?It's like Provincetown,
>> You know what this is like?It's like Provincetown,is
>> You know what this is like?It's like Provincetown,isn'
>> You know what this is like?It's like Provincetown,isn't
>> You know what this is like?It's like Provincetown,isn't it?
It's like Provincetown,isn't it?
It's like Provincetown,isn't it?Sm
It's like Provincetown,isn't it?Smel
It's like Provincetown,isn't it?Smells
It's like Provincetown,isn't it?Smells l
It's like Provincetown,isn't it?Smells like
It's like Provincetown,isn't it?Smells like it
It's like Provincetown,isn't it?Smells like it.
isn't it?Smells like it.
isn't it?Smells like it.>> Y
isn't it?Smells like it.>> Yea
isn't it?Smells like it.>> Yeah,
isn't it?Smells like it.>> Yeah, s
isn't it?Smells like it.>> Yeah, so wh
isn't it?Smells like it.>> Yeah, so what
isn't it?Smells like it.>> Yeah, so what a
isn't it?Smells like it.>> Yeah, so what abo
isn't it?Smells like it.>> Yeah, so what about
Smells like it.>> Yeah, so what about
Smells like it.>> Yeah, so what aboutou
Smells like it.>> Yeah, so what aboutour
Smells like it.>> Yeah, so what aboutour gr
Smells like it.>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandm
Smells like it.>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandmot
Smells like it.>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandmothe
Smells like it.>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandmother?
>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandmother?
>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandmother?>>
>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandmother?>> S
>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandmother?>> She l
>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandmother?>> She liv
>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandmother?>> She lives
>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandmother?>> She lives s
>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandmother?>> She lives seven
>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandmother?>> She lives seven m
>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandmother?>> She lives seven mil
>> Yeah, so what aboutour grandmother?>> She lives seven miles
our grandmother?>> She lives seven miles
our grandmother?>> She lives seven milesout
our grandmother?>> She lives seven milesout of
our grandmother?>> She lives seven milesout of t
our grandmother?>> She lives seven milesout of tow
our grandmother?>> She lives seven milesout of town,
>> She lives seven milesout of town,
>> She lives seven milesout of town,on
>> She lives seven milesout of town,on L
>> She lives seven milesout of town,on Lan
>> She lives seven milesout of town,on Land
>> She lives seven milesout of town,on Land and
>> She lives seven milesout of town,on Land and Ne
>> She lives seven milesout of town,on Land and Neck
>> She lives seven milesout of town,on Land and Neck R
>> She lives seven milesout of town,on Land and Neck Road.
out of town,on Land and Neck Road.
out of town,on Land and Neck Road.>> H
out of town,on Land and Neck Road.>> How
out of town,on Land and Neck Road.>> How d
out of town,on Land and Neck Road.>> How do
out of town,on Land and Neck Road.>> How do we g
out of town,on Land and Neck Road.>> How do we get
out of town,on Land and Neck Road.>> How do we get t
out of town,on Land and Neck Road.>> How do we get the
out of town,on Land and Neck Road.>> How do we get there?
>>
>> L
>> Lis
>> Liste
>> Listen, J
>> Listen, Jam
>> Listen, James
>> Listen, James..
>> Listen, James...
>> Listen, James...I'
>> Listen, James...I'm
>> Listen, James...I'm go
>> Listen, James...I'm gonn
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go o
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go out
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go out t
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go out there
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go out there a
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go out there alo
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go out there alone
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go out there alone.
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go out there alone.Ju
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go out there alone.Just
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go out there alone.Just i
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go out there alone.Just in ca
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go out there alone.Just in case
>> Listen, James...I'm gonna go out there alone.Just in case.
I'm gonna go out there alone.Just in case.
I'm gonna go out there alone.Just in case.I
I'm gonna go out there alone.Just in case.I wa
I'm gonna go out there alone.Just in case.I want
I'm gonna go out there alone.Just in case.I want you
I'm gonna go out there alone.Just in case.I want you t
I'm gonna go out there alone.Just in case.I want you to
I'm gonna go out there alone.Just in case.I want you to st
I'm gonna go out there alone.Just in case.I want you to stay h
I'm gonna go out there alone.Just in case.I want you to stay her
I'm gonna go out there alone.Just in case.I want you to stay here
Just in case.I want you to stay here
Just in case.I want you to stay herewi
Just in case.I want you to stay herewith
Just in case.I want you to stay herewith t
Just in case.I want you to stay herewith the l
Just in case.I want you to stay herewith the lit
Just in case.I want you to stay herewith the littl
Just in case.I want you to stay herewith the little
Just in case.I want you to stay herewith the little kids
I want you to stay herewith the little kids
I want you to stay herewith the little kidsan
I want you to stay herewith the little kidsand
I want you to stay herewith the little kidsand I'll
I want you to stay herewith the little kidsand I'll c
I want you to stay herewith the little kidsand I'll com
I want you to stay herewith the little kidsand I'll come
I want you to stay herewith the little kidsand I'll come back
I want you to stay herewith the little kidsand I'll come back f
I want you to stay herewith the little kidsand I'll come back for
I want you to stay herewith the little kidsand I'll come back for y
I want you to stay herewith the little kidsand I'll come back for you
with the little kidsand I'll come back for you
with the little kidsand I'll come back for youwhen
with the little kidsand I'll come back for youwhen I
with the little kidsand I'll come back for youwhen I k
with the little kidsand I'll come back for youwhen I kno
with the little kidsand I'll come back for youwhen I know.
and I'll come back for youwhen I know.
and I'll come back for youwhen I know.>> K
and I'll come back for youwhen I know.>> Kno
and I'll come back for youwhen I know.>> Know
and I'll come back for youwhen I know.>> Know wh
and I'll come back for youwhen I know.>> Know what?
when I know.>> Know what?
when I know.>> Know what?>>
when I know.>> Know what?>> T
when I know.>> Know what?>> Tha
when I know.>> Know what?>> That it
when I know.>> Know what?>> That it's
when I know.>> Know what?>> That it's o
when I know.>> Know what?>> That it's oka
when I know.>> Know what?>> That it's okay fo
when I know.>> Know what?>> That it's okay for
when I know.>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us
when I know.>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us t
when I know.>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there
when I know.>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there.
>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there.
>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there.>>
>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there.>> I
>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there.>> I d
>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don
>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't l
>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't lik
>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like
>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like th
>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that,
>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Di
>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dice
>> Know what?>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dicey.
>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dicey.
>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dicey.Wh
>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dicey.What
>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dicey.What i
>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if yo
>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you
>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you ge
>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get
>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in t
>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in tro
>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in troub
>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in trouble
>> That it's okay for us there.>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in trouble?
>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in trouble?
>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in trouble?>> I
>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in trouble?>> It'
>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in trouble?>> It's
>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in trouble?>> It's be
>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in trouble?>> It's better
>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in trouble?>> It's better j
>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in trouble?>> It's better jus
>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in trouble?>> It's better just
>> I don't like that, Dicey.What if you get in trouble?>> It's better just me
What if you get in trouble?>> It's better just me
What if you get in trouble?>> It's better just methan
What if you get in trouble?>> It's better just methan a
What if you get in trouble?>> It's better just methan all
What if you get in trouble?>> It's better just methan all o
What if you get in trouble?>> It's better just methan all of us
What if you get in trouble?>> It's better just methan all of us,
What if you get in trouble?>> It's better just methan all of us, ri
What if you get in trouble?>> It's better just methan all of us, righ
What if you get in trouble?>> It's better just methan all of us, right?
>> It's better just methan all of us, right?
>> It's better just methan all of us, right?(d
>> It's better just methan all of us, right?(dis
>> It's better just methan all of us, right?(dista
>> It's better just methan all of us, right?(distant
>> It's better just methan all of us, right?(distant hor
>> It's better just methan all of us, right?(distant horn
>> It's better just methan all of us, right?(distant horn bl
>> It's better just methan all of us, right?(distant horn blow
>> It's better just methan all of us, right?(distant horn blowing)
than all of us, right?(distant horn blowing)
than all of us, right?(distant horn blowing)Here
than all of us, right?(distant horn blowing)Here's
than all of us, right?(distant horn blowing)Here's s
than all of us, right?(distant horn blowing)Here's som
than all of us, right?(distant horn blowing)Here's some mo
than all of us, right?(distant horn blowing)Here's some mone
than all of us, right?(distant horn blowing)Here's some money
than all of us, right?(distant horn blowing)Here's some money fo
than all of us, right?(distant horn blowing)Here's some money for lu
than all of us, right?(distant horn blowing)Here's some money for lunc
than all of us, right?(distant horn blowing)Here's some money for lunch
(distant horn blowing)Here's some money for lunch
(distant horn blowing)Here's some money for lunchan
(distant horn blowing)Here's some money for lunchand
(distant horn blowing)Here's some money for lunchand an
(distant horn blowing)Here's some money for lunchand anyt
(distant horn blowing)Here's some money for lunchand anything
(distant horn blowing)Here's some money for lunchand anything.
>>
>> O
>> Oka
>> Okay, b
>> Okay, but
>> Okay, but I
>> Okay, but I d
>> Okay, but I don't
>> Okay, but I don't l
>> Okay, but I don't lik
>> Okay, but I don't like
>> Okay, but I don't like it.
>> Okay, but I don't like it.>> I
>> Okay, but I don't like it.>> I'm
>> Okay, but I don't like it.>> I'm i
>> Okay, but I don't like it.>> I'm in
>> Okay, but I don't like it.>> I'm in char
>> Okay, but I don't like it.>> I'm in charge
>> Okay, but I don't like it.>> I'm in charge,
>> Okay, but I don't like it.>> I'm in charge, Ja
>> Okay, but I don't like it.>> I'm in charge, James.
>> Okay, but I don't like it.>> I'm in charge, James.Re
>> Okay, but I don't like it.>> I'm in charge, James.Reme
>> Okay, but I don't like it.>> I'm in charge, James.Rememb
>> Okay, but I don't like it.>> I'm in charge, James.Remember
>> Okay, but I don't like it.>> I'm in charge, James.Remember?
>> I'm in charge, James.Remember?
>> I'm in charge, James.Remember?Yo
>> I'm in charge, James.Remember?You
>> I'm in charge, James.Remember?You litt
>> I'm in charge, James.Remember?You little
>> I'm in charge, James.Remember?You little o
>> I'm in charge, James.Remember?You little one
>> I'm in charge, James.Remember?You little ones, y
>> I'm in charge, James.Remember?You little ones, you
>> I'm in charge, James.Remember?You little ones, you d
>> I'm in charge, James.Remember?You little ones, you do
Remember?You little ones, you do
Remember?You little ones, you dowhat
Remember?You little ones, you dowhat J
Remember?You little ones, you dowhat Jam
Remember?You little ones, you dowhat James
Remember?You little ones, you dowhat James say
Remember?You little ones, you dowhat James says,
Remember?You little ones, you dowhat James says, y
Remember?You little ones, you dowhat James says, you
Remember?You little ones, you dowhat James says, you hea
Remember?You little ones, you dowhat James says, you hear?
You little ones, you dowhat James says, you hear?
You little ones, you dowhat James says, you hear?That
You little ones, you dowhat James says, you hear?That's
You little ones, you dowhat James says, you hear?That's a
You little ones, you dowhat James says, you hear?That's all
You little ones, you dowhat James says, you hear?That's all rig
You little ones, you dowhat James says, you hear?That's all right
You little ones, you dowhat James says, you hear?That's all right t
You little ones, you dowhat James says, you hear?That's all right the
You little ones, you dowhat James says, you hear?That's all right then.
♪
(l
(lid
(lid c
(lid creak
(lid creaks)
(l
(lid
(lid c
(lid cre
(lid creakin
(lid creaking
(lid creaking sh
(lid creaking shut
(lid creaking shut)
(b
(bir
(birds
(birds c
(birds chirp
(birds chirpin
(birds chirping)
Mr
Mrs.
Mrs. T
Mrs. Til
Mrs. Tillerm
Mrs. Tillerman
Mrs. Tillerman?
>>
>> Y
>> You
>> You tre
>> You tresp
>> You trespas
>> You trespassi
>> You trespassing.
>>
>> W
>> Wel
>> Well, I
>> Well, I t
>> Well, I tho
>> Well, I thoug
>> Well, I thought
>> Well, I thoughtI
>> Well, I thoughtI he
>> Well, I thoughtI hear
>> Well, I thoughtI heard wh
>> Well, I thoughtI heard when
>> Well, I thoughtI heard when I
>> Well, I thoughtI heard when I k
>> Well, I thoughtI heard when I knock
>> Well, I thoughtI heard when I knocked
>> Well, I thoughtI heard when I knocked.
I
I di
I didn
I didn't
I didn't kno
I didn't know
I didn't know if
I didn't know if..
I didn't know if...
Well
Well,
Well, th
Well, the
Well, the fact
Well, the fact i
Well, the fact is,
Well, the fact is,I wo
Well, the fact is,I wond
Well, the fact is,I wonder
Well, the fact is,I wondered
Well, the fact is,I wondered if
Well, the fact is,I wondered if yo
Well, the fact is,I wondered if you'
Well, the fact is,I wondered if you'd
Well, the fact is,I wondered if you'd hire
Well, the fact is,I wondered if you'd hire m
Well, the fact is,I wondered if you'd hire me
Well, the fact is,I wondered if you'd hire meto
Well, the fact is,I wondered if you'd hire meto w
Well, the fact is,I wondered if you'd hire meto wor
Well, the fact is,I wondered if you'd hire meto work
Well, the fact is,I wondered if you'd hire meto work for
Well, the fact is,I wondered if you'd hire meto work for yo
Well, the fact is,I wondered if you'd hire meto work for you?
I wondered if you'd hire meto work for you?
I wondered if you'd hire meto work for you?>>
I wondered if you'd hire meto work for you?>> T
I wondered if you'd hire meto work for you?>> The
I wondered if you'd hire meto work for you?>> The fac
I wondered if you'd hire meto work for you?>> The fact
I wondered if you'd hire meto work for you?>> The fact is
to work for you?>> The fact is
to work for you?>> The fact isyo
to work for you?>> The fact isyou'
to work for you?>> The fact isyou're
to work for you?>> The fact isyou're tre
to work for you?>> The fact isyou're tresp
to work for you?>> The fact isyou're trespas
to work for you?>> The fact isyou're trespassi
to work for you?>> The fact isyou're trespassing.
>> The fact isyou're trespassing.
>> The fact isyou're trespassing.Wh
>> The fact isyou're trespassing.Who
>> The fact isyou're trespassing.Who to
>> The fact isyou're trespassing.Who told y
>> The fact isyou're trespassing.Who told you
>> The fact isyou're trespassing.Who told you t
>> The fact isyou're trespassing.Who told you to
>> The fact isyou're trespassing.Who told you to come
>> The fact isyou're trespassing.Who told you to come h
>> The fact isyou're trespassing.Who told you to come her
>> The fact isyou're trespassing.Who told you to come here?
you're trespassing.Who told you to come here?
you're trespassing.Who told you to come here?>>
you're trespassing.Who told you to come here?>> N
you're trespassing.Who told you to come here?>> Nob
you're trespassing.Who told you to come here?>> Nobody.
Who told you to come here?>> Nobody.
Who told you to come here?>> Nobody.I
Who told you to come here?>> Nobody.I he
Who told you to come here?>> Nobody.I hear
Who told you to come here?>> Nobody.I heard yo
Who told you to come here?>> Nobody.I heard you
Who told you to come here?>> Nobody.I heard you we
Who told you to come here?>> Nobody.I heard you were
Who told you to come here?>> Nobody.I heard you were alo
Who told you to come here?>> Nobody.I heard you were alone
>> Nobody.I heard you were alone
>> Nobody.I heard you were aloneso
>> Nobody.I heard you were aloneso I
>> Nobody.I heard you were aloneso I t
>> Nobody.I heard you were aloneso I thoug
>> Nobody.I heard you were aloneso I thought
>> Nobody.I heard you were aloneso I thought I
>> Nobody.I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd
>> Nobody.I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd try
>> Nobody.I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd try.
I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd try.
I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd try.>>
I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd try.>> I
I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd try.>> I don
I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd try.>> I don't
I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd try.>> I don't k
I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd try.>> I don't kno
I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd try.>> I don't know yo
I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd try.>> I don't know you,
I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd try.>> I don't know you, d
I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd try.>> I don't know you, do
I heard you were aloneso I thought I'd try.>> I don't know you, do I?
so I thought I'd try.>> I don't know you, do I?
so I thought I'd try.>> I don't know you, do I?>>
so I thought I'd try.>> I don't know you, do I?>> W
so I thought I'd try.>> I don't know you, do I?>> We'
so I thought I'd try.>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're
so I thought I'd try.>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new
so I thought I'd try.>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new h
so I thought I'd try.>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new her
so I thought I'd try.>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new here.
>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new here.
>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new here.>>
>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new here.>> W
>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new here.>> Why a
>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new here.>> Why are
>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new here.>> Why aren'
>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new here.>> Why aren't
>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new here.>> Why aren't you
>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new here.>> Why aren't you in
>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new here.>> Why aren't you in s
>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new here.>> Why aren't you in sch
>> I don't know you, do I?>> We're new here.>> Why aren't you in school?
>> We're new here.>> Why aren't you in school?
>> We're new here.>> Why aren't you in school?>>
>> We're new here.>> Why aren't you in school?>> I
>> We're new here.>> Why aren't you in school?>> It'
>> We're new here.>> Why aren't you in school?>> It's
>> We're new here.>> Why aren't you in school?>> It's summ
>> We're new here.>> Why aren't you in school?>> It's summer
>> We're new here.>> Why aren't you in school?>> It's summer.
>>
>> N
>> Not
>> Not f
>> Not for l
>> Not for lon
>> Not for long.
(d
(doo
(door
(door crea
(door creaki
(door creaking
(door creaking,
(door creaking, shut
(door creaking, shuts)
(foo
(foots
(footste
(footsteps
(footsteps app
(footsteps appro
(footsteps approac
(footsteps approachi
(footsteps approaching)
(footsteps approaching)(doo
(footsteps approaching)(door
(footsteps approaching)(door sh
(footsteps approaching)(door shut
(footsteps approaching)(door shuts)
(footsteps approaching)(door shuts)I di
(footsteps approaching)(door shuts)I didn
(footsteps approaching)(door shuts)I didn't
(footsteps approaching)(door shuts)I didn't s
(footsteps approaching)(door shuts)I didn't say c
(footsteps approaching)(door shuts)I didn't say com
(footsteps approaching)(door shuts)I didn't say come
(footsteps approaching)(door shuts)I didn't say come in
(footsteps approaching)(door shuts)I didn't say come in.
(door shuts)I didn't say come in.
(door shuts)I didn't say come in.>>
(door shuts)I didn't say come in.>> Y
(door shuts)I didn't say come in.>> You
(door shuts)I didn't say come in.>> You nev
(door shuts)I didn't say come in.>> You never
(door shuts)I didn't say come in.>> You never s
(door shuts)I didn't say come in.>> You never sai
(door shuts)I didn't say come in.>> You never said if
(door shuts)I didn't say come in.>> You never said if y
(door shuts)I didn't say come in.>> You never said if you
I didn't say come in.>> You never said if you
I didn't say come in.>> You never said if youwa
I didn't say come in.>> You never said if youwant
I didn't say come in.>> You never said if youwanted
I didn't say come in.>> You never said if youwanted me
I didn't say come in.>> You never said if youwanted me to
I didn't say come in.>> You never said if youwanted me to w
I didn't say come in.>> You never said if youwanted me to wor
I didn't say come in.>> You never said if youwanted me to work.
>> You never said if youwanted me to work.
>> You never said if youwanted me to work.>>
>> You never said if youwanted me to work.>> H
>> You never said if youwanted me to work.>> How
>> You never said if youwanted me to work.>> How d
>> You never said if youwanted me to work.>> How do I
>> You never said if youwanted me to work.>> How do I kn
>> You never said if youwanted me to work.>> How do I know
>> You never said if youwanted me to work.>> How do I know y
>> You never said if youwanted me to work.>> How do I know you'r
>> You never said if youwanted me to work.>> How do I know you're
>> You never said if youwanted me to work.>> How do I know you're no
>> You never said if youwanted me to work.>> How do I know you're not
wanted me to work.>> How do I know you're not
wanted me to work.>> How do I know you're notgo
wanted me to work.>> How do I know you're notgonn
wanted me to work.>> How do I know you're notgonna
wanted me to work.>> How do I know you're notgonna rob
wanted me to work.>> How do I know you're notgonna rob me
wanted me to work.>> How do I know you're notgonna rob me?
>> How do I know you're notgonna rob me?
>> How do I know you're notgonna rob me?>>
>> How do I know you're notgonna rob me?>> I
>> How do I know you're notgonna rob me?>> I'm n
>> How do I know you're notgonna rob me?>> I'm not
>> How do I know you're notgonna rob me?>> I'm not.
gonna rob me?>> I'm not.
gonna rob me?>> I'm not.An
gonna rob me?>> I'm not.And
gonna rob me?>> I'm not.And it
gonna rob me?>> I'm not.And it doe
gonna rob me?>> I'm not.And it doesn
gonna rob me?>> I'm not.And it doesn't
gonna rob me?>> I'm not.And it doesn't l
gonna rob me?>> I'm not.And it doesn't look
gonna rob me?>> I'm not.And it doesn't look li
gonna rob me?>> I'm not.And it doesn't look like
>> I'm not.And it doesn't look like
>> I'm not.And it doesn't look likeyo
>> I'm not.And it doesn't look likeyou
>> I'm not.And it doesn't look likeyou have
>> I'm not.And it doesn't look likeyou have m
>> I'm not.And it doesn't look likeyou have muc
>> I'm not.And it doesn't look likeyou have much
>> I'm not.And it doesn't look likeyou have much to s
>> I'm not.And it doesn't look likeyou have much to ste
>> I'm not.And it doesn't look likeyou have much to steal
>> I'm not.And it doesn't look likeyou have much to steal,
>> I'm not.And it doesn't look likeyou have much to steal, anyw
>> I'm not.And it doesn't look likeyou have much to steal, anyway
>> I'm not.And it doesn't look likeyou have much to steal, anyway.
>>
>> W
>> Where
>> Where d
>> Where do
>> Where do yo
>> Where do you li
>> Where do you live
>> Where do you live?
>> Where do you live?>> I
>> Where do you live?>> In
>> Where do you live?>> In to
>> Where do you live?>> In town
>> Where do you live?>> In town.
>> Where do you live?>> In town.I
>> Where do you live?>> In town.I ca
>> Where do you live?>> In town.I can
>> Where do you live?>> In town.I can work
>> Where do you live?>> In town.I can work h
>> Where do you live?>> In town.I can work har
>> Where do you live?>> In town.I can work hard.
Yo
Your
Your bar
Your barn
Your barn ne
Your barn need
Your barn needs to
Your barn needs to b
Your barn needs to be
Your barn needs to be pa
Your barn needs to be painte
Your barn needs to be painted
Your barn needs to be paintedan
Your barn needs to be paintedand
Your barn needs to be paintedand th
Your barn needs to be paintedand the gr
Your barn needs to be paintedand the gras
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass ne
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs to
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs to b
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs to be
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs to be cut.
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs to be cut.>> I
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs to be cut.>> I'm
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs to be cut.>> I'm t
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs to be cut.>> I'm too
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs to be cut.>> I'm too old
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs to be cut.>> I'm too old t
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs to be cut.>> I'm too old to
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs to be cut.>> I'm too old to do
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs to be cut.>> I'm too old to do tha
Your barn needs to be paintedand the grass needs to be cut.>> I'm too old to do that.
>>
>> W
>> Wel
>> Well,
>> Well, I c
>> Well, I can
>> Well, I can p
>> Well, I can pic
>> Well, I can pick an
>> Well, I can pick and
>> Well, I can pick and we
>> Well, I can pick and weed
>> Well, I can pick and weed.
>> Well, I can pick and weed.>>
>> Well, I can pick and weed.>> S
>> Well, I can pick and weed.>> So ca
>> Well, I can pick and weed.>> So can
>> Well, I can pick and weed.>> So can I!
>> Well, I can pick and weed.>> So can I!So
>> Well, I can pick and weed.>> So can I!So c
>> Well, I can pick and weed.>> So can I!So can
>> Well, I can pick and weed.>> So can I!So can any
>> Well, I can pick and weed.>> So can I!So can anybo
>> Well, I can pick and weed.>> So can I!So can anybody
>> Well, I can pick and weed.>> So can I!So can anybody.
You
You mi
You migh
You might
You might as w
You might as wel
You might as well
You might as well ge
You might as well get do
You might as well get down
You might as well get downa
You might as well get downa bo
You might as well get downa bowl
You might as well get downa bowl n
You might as well get downa bowl now t
You might as well get downa bowl now tha
You might as well get downa bowl now that
You might as well get downa bowl now that yo
You might as well get downa bowl now that you've
You might as well get downa bowl now that you'veinvi
You might as well get downa bowl now that you'veinvite
You might as well get downa bowl now that you'veinvited
You might as well get downa bowl now that you'veinvited yo
You might as well get downa bowl now that you'veinvited yourse
You might as well get downa bowl now that you'veinvited yourself
You might as well get downa bowl now that you'veinvited yourself t
You might as well get downa bowl now that you'veinvited yourself to
You might as well get downa bowl now that you'veinvited yourself to lunc
You might as well get downa bowl now that you'veinvited yourself to lunch.
(bow
(bowl
(bowl cl
(bowl clan
(bowl clanking
(bowl clanking)
Yo
You
You know
You know w
You know wha
You know what
You know what I so
You know what I some
You know what I someti
You know what I sometime
You know what I sometimes th
You know what I sometimes thin
You know what I sometimes think?
You know what I sometimes think?I
You know what I sometimes think?I so
You know what I sometimes think?I someti
You know what I sometimes think?I sometime
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes th
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes think
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes think pe
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes think peop
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes think people
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes think peoplemigh
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes think peoplemight
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes think peoplemight be
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes think peoplemight be g
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes think peoplemight be good
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes think peoplemight be good to
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes think peoplemight be good to e
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat
You know what I sometimes think?I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat.
I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat.
I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat.Yo
I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat.You
I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat.You kn
I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat.You know,
I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat.You know, co
I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat.You know, cows
I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat.You know, cows a
I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat.You know, cows and c
I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat.You know, cows and chi
I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat.You know, cows and chick
I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat.You know, cows and chicken
I sometimes think peoplemight be good to eat.You know, cows and chickens
might be good to eat.You know, cows and chickens
might be good to eat.You know, cows and chickensea
might be good to eat.You know, cows and chickenseat
might be good to eat.You know, cows and chickenseat corn
might be good to eat.You know, cows and chickenseat corn a
might be good to eat.You know, cows and chickenseat corn and
might be good to eat.You know, cows and chickenseat corn and g
might be good to eat.You know, cows and chickenseat corn and grass
You know, cows and chickenseat corn and grass
You know, cows and chickenseat corn and grassan
You know, cows and chickenseat corn and grassand
You know, cows and chickenseat corn and grassand tu
You know, cows and chickenseat corn and grassand turn
You know, cows and chickenseat corn and grassand turn it
You know, cows and chickenseat corn and grassand turn it in
You know, cows and chickenseat corn and grassand turn it into
You know, cows and chickenseat corn and grassand turn it into g
You know, cows and chickenseat corn and grassand turn it into good
You know, cows and chickenseat corn and grassand turn it into good me
You know, cows and chickenseat corn and grassand turn it into good meat
You know, cows and chickenseat corn and grassand turn it into good meat,
eat corn and grassand turn it into good meat,
eat corn and grassand turn it into good meat,so
eat corn and grassand turn it into good meat,so w
eat corn and grassand turn it into good meat,so when
eat corn and grassand turn it into good meat,so when pe
eat corn and grassand turn it into good meat,so when peop
eat corn and grassand turn it into good meat,so when people
eat corn and grassand turn it into good meat,so when people eat
eat corn and grassand turn it into good meat,so when people eat c
eat corn and grassand turn it into good meat,so when people eat cow
eat corn and grassand turn it into good meat,so when people eat cows
and turn it into good meat,so when people eat cows
and turn it into good meat,so when people eat cowsan
and turn it into good meat,so when people eat cowsand
and turn it into good meat,so when people eat cowsand ch
and turn it into good meat,so when people eat cowsand chicke
and turn it into good meat,so when people eat cowsand chickens
and turn it into good meat,so when people eat cowsand chickens,
and turn it into good meat,so when people eat cowsand chickens, th
and turn it into good meat,so when people eat cowsand chickens, they m
and turn it into good meat,so when people eat cowsand chickens, they mig
and turn it into good meat,so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might
and turn it into good meat,so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might t
and turn it into good meat,so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might turn
so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might turn
so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might turnit
so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might turnit i
so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might turnit into
so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might turnit into so
so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might turnit into some
so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might turnit into someth
so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might turnit into something
so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might turnit into something ev
so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might turnit into something even
so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might turnit into something even b
so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might turnit into something even bette
so when people eat cowsand chickens, they might turnit into something even better.
and chickens, they might turnit into something even better.
and chickens, they might turnit into something even better.Ev
and chickens, they might turnit into something even better.Ever
and chickens, they might turnit into something even better.Ever t
and chickens, they might turnit into something even better.Ever think
and chickens, they might turnit into something even better.Ever think a
and chickens, they might turnit into something even better.Ever think abo
and chickens, they might turnit into something even better.Ever think about
and chickens, they might turnit into something even better.Ever think about tha
and chickens, they might turnit into something even better.Ever think about that?
Mm
Mmm.
Mmm.Es
Mmm.Espe
Mmm.Especi
Mmm.Especially
Mmm.Especially b
Mmm.Especially bab
Mmm.Especially babie
Mmm.Especially babies.
Mmm.Especially babies.Or
Mmm.Especially babies.Or c
Mmm.Especially babies.Or chi
Mmm.Especially babies.Or childre
Mmm.Especially babies.Or children.
Especially babies.Or children.
Especially babies.Or children.Mm
Especially babies.Or children.Mmm.
Or children.Mmm.
Or children.Mmm.Mo
Or children.Mmm.More
Or children.Mmm.More t
Or children.Mmm.More tende
Or children.Mmm.More tender.
Mmm.More tender.
Mmm.More tender.(s
Mmm.More tender.(spo
Mmm.More tender.(spoon
Mmm.More tender.(spoon s
Mmm.More tender.(spoon scrap
Mmm.More tender.(spoon scrapin
Mmm.More tender.(spoon scraping)
More tender.(spoon scraping)
More tender.(spoon scraping)Yo
More tender.(spoon scraping)You
More tender.(spoon scraping)You got
More tender.(spoon scraping)You got an
More tender.(spoon scraping)You got any
More tender.(spoon scraping)You got any br
More tender.(spoon scraping)You got any brothe
More tender.(spoon scraping)You got any brothers
More tender.(spoon scraping)You got any brothers o
More tender.(spoon scraping)You got any brothers or
More tender.(spoon scraping)You got any brothers or sist
More tender.(spoon scraping)You got any brothers or sister
More tender.(spoon scraping)You got any brothers or sisters?
(spoon scraping)You got any brothers or sisters?
(spoon scraping)You got any brothers or sisters?>> N
(spoon scraping)You got any brothers or sisters?>> No.
>>
>> W
>> Who t
>> Who tol
>> Who told
>> Who told yo
>> Who told you I
>> Who told you I wa
>> Who told you I was
>> Who told you I was al
>> Who told you I was alone?
>> Who told you I was alone?>>
>> Who told you I was alone?>> T
>> Who told you I was alone?>> The l
>> Who told you I was alone?>> The lad
>> Who told you I was alone?>> The lady
>> Who told you I was alone?>> The lady in
>> Who told you I was alone?>> The lady inthe
>> Who told you I was alone?>> The lady inthe gr
>> Who told you I was alone?>> The lady inthe groc
>> Who told you I was alone?>> The lady inthe grocer
>> Who told you I was alone?>> The lady inthe grocery st
>> Who told you I was alone?>> The lady inthe grocery stor
>> Who told you I was alone?>> The lady inthe grocery store.
>> The lady inthe grocery store.
>> The lady inthe grocery store.>>
>> The lady inthe grocery store.>> M
>> The lady inthe grocery store.>> Mm,
>> The lady inthe grocery store.>> Mm, Mil
>> The lady inthe grocery store.>> Mm, Milli
>> The lady inthe grocery store.>> Mm, Millie.
the grocery store.>> Mm, Millie.
the grocery store.>> Mm, Millie.Sh
the grocery store.>> Mm, Millie.She'
the grocery store.>> Mm, Millie.She's th
the grocery store.>> Mm, Millie.She's the
the grocery store.>> Mm, Millie.She's the bu
the grocery store.>> Mm, Millie.She's the butc
the grocery store.>> Mm, Millie.She's the butcher,
>> Mm, Millie.She's the butcher,
>> Mm, Millie.She's the butcher,ca
>> Mm, Millie.She's the butcher,can
>> Mm, Millie.She's the butcher,can yo
>> Mm, Millie.She's the butcher,can you
>> Mm, Millie.She's the butcher,can you imag
>> Mm, Millie.She's the butcher,can you imagin
>> Mm, Millie.She's the butcher,can you imagine
>> Mm, Millie.She's the butcher,can you imagine th
>> Mm, Millie.She's the butcher,can you imagine that?
She's the butcher,can you imagine that?
She's the butcher,can you imagine that?A
She's the butcher,can you imagine that?A la
She's the butcher,can you imagine that?A lady
She's the butcher,can you imagine that?A lady but
She's the butcher,can you imagine that?A lady butch
She's the butcher,can you imagine that?A lady butcher
She's the butcher,can you imagine that?A lady butcher?
can you imagine that?A lady butcher?
can you imagine that?A lady butcher?>>
can you imagine that?A lady butcher?>> W
can you imagine that?A lady butcher?>> Why
can you imagine that?A lady butcher?>> Why not
can you imagine that?A lady butcher?>> Why not?
A lady butcher?>> Why not?
A lady butcher?>> Why not?>>
A lady butcher?>> Why not?>> W
A lady butcher?>> Why not?>> Wha
A lady butcher?>> Why not?>> What
A lady butcher?>> Why not?>> What did
A lady butcher?>> Why not?>> What did sh
A lady butcher?>> Why not?>> What did she
A lady butcher?>> Why not?>> What did she te
A lady butcher?>> Why not?>> What did she tell y
A lady butcher?>> Why not?>> What did she tell you
>> Why not?>> What did she tell you
>> Why not?>> What did she tell youab
>> Why not?>> What did she tell youabou
>> Why not?>> What did she tell youabout
>> Why not?>> What did she tell youabout me?
>> What did she tell youabout me?
>> What did she tell youabout me?>>
>> What did she tell youabout me?>> N
>> What did she tell youabout me?>> Not
>> What did she tell youabout me?>> Nothing
>> What did she tell youabout me?>> Nothing m
>> What did she tell youabout me?>> Nothing muc
>> What did she tell youabout me?>> Nothing much.
>>
>> S
>> She t
>> She tel
>> She tell
>> She tell yo
>> She tell you I
>> She tell you I wa
>> She tell you I was
>> She tell you I was cr
>> She tell you I was crazy?
>> She tell you I was crazy?(f
>> She tell you I was crazy?(fau
>> She tell you I was crazy?(fauce
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet cr
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet crea
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaki
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, wa
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, wate
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, water
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, water ru
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, water rushin
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, water rushing)
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, water rushing)(fau
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, water rushing)(fauce
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet cr
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaki
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaking
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaking s
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaking shu
>> She tell you I was crazy?(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaking shut)
(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaking shut)
(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaking shut)My
(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaking shut)My h
(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaking shut)My hus
(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaking shut)My husband
(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaking shut)My husband's
(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaking shut)My husband's b
(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaking shut)My husband's bee
(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaking shut)My husband's been de
(faucet creaking, water rushing)(faucet creaking shut)My husband's been dead
(faucet creaking shut)My husband's been dead
(faucet creaking shut)My husband's been deadth
(faucet creaking shut)My husband's been deadthes
(faucet creaking shut)My husband's been deadthese fo
(faucet creaking shut)My husband's been deadthese four
(faucet creaking shut)My husband's been deadthese four y
(faucet creaking shut)My husband's been deadthese four yea
(faucet creaking shut)My husband's been deadthese four years o
(faucet creaking shut)My husband's been deadthese four years or
(faucet creaking shut)My husband's been deadthese four years or mo
(faucet creaking shut)My husband's been deadthese four years or more
(faucet creaking shut)My husband's been deadthese four years or more.
My husband's been deadthese four years or more.
My husband's been deadthese four years or more.>>
My husband's been deadthese four years or more.>> I
My husband's been deadthese four years or more.>> I'm
My husband's been deadthese four years or more.>> I'm s
My husband's been deadthese four years or more.>> I'm sorry
My husband's been deadthese four years or more.>> I'm sorry.
these four years or more.>> I'm sorry.
these four years or more.>> I'm sorry.>>
these four years or more.>> I'm sorry.>> I
these four years or more.>> I'm sorry.>> I'm
these four years or more.>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not
these four years or more.>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not.
>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not.
>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not.I'
>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not.I've
>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not.I've b
>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not.I've been
>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not.I've been ha
>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not.I've been happ
>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not.I've been happy
>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not.I've been happy sinc
>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not.I've been happy since
>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not.I've been happy since he
>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not.I've been happy since he d
>> I'm sorry.>> I'm not.I've been happy since he died.
>> I'm not.I've been happy since he died.
>> I'm not.I've been happy since he died.>>
>> I'm not.I've been happy since he died.>> W
>> I'm not.I've been happy since he died.>> Why
>> I'm not.I've been happy since he died.>> Why?
I've been happy since he died.>> Why?
I've been happy since he died.>> Why?>>
I've been happy since he died.>> Why?>> K
I've been happy since he died.>> Why?>> Kep
I've been happy since he died.>> Why?>> Kept wa
I've been happy since he died.>> Why?>> Kept want
I've been happy since he died.>> Why?>> Kept wantin
I've been happy since he died.>> Why?>> Kept wanting
I've been happy since he died.>> Why?>> Kept wanting his
>> Why?>> Kept wanting his
>> Why?>> Kept wanting hissh
>> Why?>> Kept wanting hisshoe
>> Why?>> Kept wanting hisshoes
>> Why?>> Kept wanting hisshoes poli
>> Why?>> Kept wanting hisshoes polish
>> Why?>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished
>> Why?>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.
>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.
>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.Ne
>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.Neve
>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.Never
>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.Never did
>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.Never did po
>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.Never did poli
>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.Never did polish
>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.Never did polish his
>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.Never did polish his o
>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.Never did polish his own
>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.Never did polish his own s
>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.Never did polish his own shoes
>> Kept wanting hisshoes polished.Never did polish his own shoes.
shoes polished.Never did polish his own shoes.
shoes polished.Never did polish his own shoes.(s
shoes polished.Never did polish his own shoes.(sip
shoes polished.Never did polish his own shoes.(sipping
shoes polished.Never did polish his own shoes.(sipping)
(s
(set
(sets gl
(sets glas
(sets glass
(sets glass do
(sets glass down)
Do
Do y
Do you
Do you pla
Do you play
Do you play th
Do you play the
Do you play the pian
Do you play the piano?
>> N
>> No.
>> No.>>
>> No.>> T
>> No.>> Too
>> No.>> Too bad
>> No.>> Too bad,
>> No.>> Too bad, I
>> No.>> Too bad, I go
>> No.>> Too bad, I got on
>> No.>> Too bad, I got one.
(s
(sig
(sighi
(sighing
(sighing, bo
(sighing, bowl
(sighing, bowl r
(sighing, bowl rat
(sighing, bowl rattles
(sighing, bowl rattles)
(sighing, bowl rattles)Have
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven'
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't pl
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't played
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't played i
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't played it
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't played it my
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't played it myself
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't played it myself.
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't played it myself.Ne
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't played it myself.Neve
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't played it myself.Never ha
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't played it myself.Never had
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't played it myself.Never had th
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't played it myself.Never had the
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't played it myself.Never had the time
(sighing, bowl rattles)Haven't played it myself.Never had the time.
Haven't played it myself.Never had the time.
Haven't played it myself.Never had the time.My c
Haven't played it myself.Never had the time.My chi
Haven't played it myself.Never had the time.My child
Haven't played it myself.Never had the time.My childre
Haven't played it myself.Never had the time.My children di
Haven't played it myself.Never had the time.My children did.
Never had the time.My children did.
Never had the time.My children did.Hm
Never had the time.My children did.Hm,
Never had the time.My children did.Hm, bu
Never had the time.My children did.Hm, but th
Never had the time.My children did.Hm, but they
Never had the time.My children did.Hm, but they d
Never had the time.My children did.Hm, but they die
Never had the time.My children did.Hm, but they died, t
Never had the time.My children did.Hm, but they died, too
Never had the time.My children did.Hm, but they died, too.
All
All th
All thre
All three
All three of t
All three of the
All three of them.
All three of them.Hm
All three of them.Hm.
All three of them.Hm.He
All three of them.Hm.Heh,
All three of them.Hm.Heh, tha
All three of them.Hm.Heh, that
All three of them.Hm.Heh, that wa
All three of them.Hm.Heh, that was
All three of them.Hm.Heh, that was a re
All three of them.Hm.Heh, that was a reli
All three of them.Hm.Heh, that was a relief
All three of them.Hm.Heh, that was a relief.
What
What d
What do
What do yo
What do you th
What do you thin
What do you think
What do you think ab
What do you think about
What do you think about de
What do you think about deat
What do you think about death?
Or
Or d
Or don't
Or don't y
Or don't you
Or don't you t
Or don't you think
Or don't you think?
>>
>> I
>> I t
>> I think
>> I think i
>> I think it'
>> I think it's
>> I think it's a qu
>> I think it's a quie
>> I think it's a quiet
>> I think it's a quiet pl
>> I think it's a quiet place,
>> I think it's a quiet place,at t
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the e
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the end
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the end,
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the end,wh
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the end,wher
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the end,where yo
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the end,where you
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the end,where you ca
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the end,where you can
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the end,where you can rest
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the end,where you can rest a
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the end,where you can rest and
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the end,where you can rest and y
>> I think it's a quiet place,at the end,where you can rest and you
at the end,where you can rest and you
at the end,where you can rest and youdon'
at the end,where you can rest and youdon't
at the end,where you can rest and youdon't ha
at the end,where you can rest and youdon't have
at the end,where you can rest and youdon't have to
at the end,where you can rest and youdon't have to fi
at the end,where you can rest and youdon't have to figh
at the end,where you can rest and youdon't have to fight
at the end,where you can rest and youdon't have to fight anym
at the end,where you can rest and youdon't have to fight anymor
at the end,where you can rest and youdon't have to fight anymore.
>>
>> N
>> Not
>> Not qui
>> Not quite
>> Not quite.
>> Not quite.No
>> Not quite.Not
>> Not quite.Not with
>> Not quite.Not with t
>> Not quite.Not with the
>> Not quite.Not with the m
>> Not quite.Not with the maggo
>> Not quite.Not with the maggots
>> Not quite.Not with the maggotsand
>> Not quite.Not with the maggotsand wo
>> Not quite.Not with the maggotsand worm
>> Not quite.Not with the maggotsand worms.
>>
>> I
>> I w
>> I would
>> I wouldn'
>> I wouldn't
>> I wouldn't ca
>> I wouldn't care a
>> I wouldn't care abo
>> I wouldn't care about
>> I wouldn't care about t
>> I wouldn't care about that
>> I wouldn't care about thatif
>> I wouldn't care about thatif I
>> I wouldn't care about thatif I w
>> I wouldn't care about thatif I was d
>> I wouldn't care about thatif I was dea
>> I wouldn't care about thatif I was dead.
>> I wouldn't care about thatif I was dead.(s
>> I wouldn't care about thatif I was dead.(spo
>> I wouldn't care about thatif I was dead.(spoon
>> I wouldn't care about thatif I was dead.(spoon c
>> I wouldn't care about thatif I was dead.(spoon clank
>> I wouldn't care about thatif I was dead.(spoon clanks)
>> W
>> Wel
>> Well,
>> Well, y
>> Well, you'r
>> Well, you're
>> Well, you're go
>> Well, you're goin
>> Well, you're going.
Yo
You
You didn
You didn't
You didn't e
You didn't eve
You didn't even of
You didn't even offe
You didn't even offer
You didn't even offer to
You didn't even offer tohelp
You didn't even offer tohelp w
You didn't even offer tohelp wit
You didn't even offer tohelp with
You didn't even offer tohelp with the
You didn't even offer tohelp with the di
You didn't even offer tohelp with the dish
You didn't even offer tohelp with the dishes
You didn't even offer tohelp with the dishes.
(c
(cla
(clank
(clankin
(clanking)
(clanking)Do
(clanking)Don'
(clanking)Don't
(clanking)Don't both
(clanking)Don't bother
(clanking)Don't bother!
I
I kn
I know
I know w
I know what
I know what ch
I know what chil
I know what childr
I know what children a
I know what children are
I know what children are l
I know what children are lik
I know what children are like.
Do
Don'
Don't
Don't you
Don't you ev
Don't you even
Don't you even w
Don't you even wanna
Don't you even wanna k
Don't you even wanna kno
Don't you even wanna know
Don't you even wanna knowif
Don't you even wanna knowif I
Don't you even wanna knowif I wan
Don't you even wanna knowif I want
Don't you even wanna knowif I want yo
Don't you even wanna knowif I want you
Don't you even wanna knowif I want you to w
Don't you even wanna knowif I want you to wor
Don't you even wanna knowif I want you to work
Don't you even wanna knowif I want you to work fo
Don't you even wanna knowif I want you to work for me
Don't you even wanna knowif I want you to work for me?
We
Well
Well,
Well, I
Well, I don'
Well, I don't!
(d
(doo
(door
(door cr
(door creaki
(door creaking
(door creaking)
I kn
I know
I know w
I know who
I know who you
I know who you a
I know who you are
I know who you are.
I know who you are.Yo
I know who you are.You
I know who you are.You hear
I know who you are.You hear m
I know who you are.You hear me?
I know who you are.You hear me?I
I know who you are.You hear me?I kn
I know who you are.You hear me?I know
I know who you are.You hear me?I know w
I know who you are.You hear me?I know who y
I know who you are.You hear me?I know who you
I know who you are.You hear me?I know who you a
I know who you are.You hear me?I know who you are
You hear me?I know who you are
You hear me?I know who you arean
You hear me?I know who you areand
You hear me?I know who you areand yo
You hear me?I know who you areand you ca
You hear me?I know who you areand you can'
You hear me?I know who you areand you can't
You hear me?I know who you areand you can't st
You hear me?I know who you areand you can't stay h
You hear me?I know who you areand you can't stay her
You hear me?I know who you areand you can't stay here!
(d
(doo
(door
(door crea
(door creaki
(door creaking
(door creaking)
>> T
>> The
>> Then
>> Then wh
>> Then who am
>> Then who am I
>> Then who am I?
>> Then who am I?>>
>> Then who am I?>> I
>> Then who am I?>> I kne
>> Then who am I?>> I knew
>> Then who am I?>> I knew th
>> Then who am I?>> I knew the
>> Then who am I?>> I knew the minu
>> Then who am I?>> I knew the minute
>> Then who am I?>> I knew the minuteyou
>> Then who am I?>> I knew the minuteyou kn
>> Then who am I?>> I knew the minuteyou knoc
>> Then who am I?>> I knew the minuteyou knocke
>> Then who am I?>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at
>> Then who am I?>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at t
>> Then who am I?>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the
>> Then who am I?>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the d
>> Then who am I?>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the door.
>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the door.
>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the door.Th
>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the door.That
>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the door.That's
>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the door.That's why
>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the door.That's why I
>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the door.That's why I w
>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the door.That's why I wen
>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the door.That's why I went ou
>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the door.That's why I went outb
>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the door.That's why I went outbac
>> I knew the minuteyou knocked at the door.That's why I went outback.
you knocked at the door.That's why I went outback.
you knocked at the door.That's why I went outback.A po
you knocked at the door.That's why I went outback.A poli
you knocked at the door.That's why I went outback.A polite
you knocked at the door.That's why I went outback.A polite p
you knocked at the door.That's why I went outback.A polite perso
you knocked at the door.That's why I went outback.A polite person
you knocked at the door.That's why I went outback.A polite person wo
you knocked at the door.That's why I went outback.A polite person woul
you knocked at the door.That's why I went outback.A polite person would've
That's why I went outback.A polite person would've
That's why I went outback.A polite person would'vego
That's why I went outback.A polite person would'vegone
That's why I went outback.A polite person would'vegone a
That's why I went outback.A polite person would'vegone awa
That's why I went outback.A polite person would'vegone away.
(b
(bow
(bowl
(bowl clan
(bowl clanki
(bowl clanking
(bowl clanking)
(bowl clanking)Yo
(bowl clanking)You'
(bowl clanking)You're
(bowl clanking)You're the
(bowl clanking)You're the o
(bowl clanking)You're the old
(bowl clanking)You're the oldes
(bowl clanking)You're the oldest.
(bowl clanking)You're the oldest.(g
(bowl clanking)You're the oldest.(gla
(bowl clanking)You're the oldest.(glass
(bowl clanking)You're the oldest.(glass thu
(bowl clanking)You're the oldest.(glass thuds
(bowl clanking)You're the oldest.(glass thuds)
You're the oldest.(glass thuds)
You're the oldest.(glass thuds)I
You're the oldest.(glass thuds)I ca
You're the oldest.(glass thuds)I can'
You're the oldest.(glass thuds)I can't re
You're the oldest.(glass thuds)I can't reme
You're the oldest.(glass thuds)I can't rememb
You're the oldest.(glass thuds)I can't remember
You're the oldest.(glass thuds)I can't remember you
You're the oldest.(glass thuds)I can't remember your
You're the oldest.(glass thuds)I can't remember your na
You're the oldest.(glass thuds)I can't remember your name
You're the oldest.(glass thuds)I can't remember your name.
(glass thuds)I can't remember your name.
(glass thuds)I can't remember your name.>>
(glass thuds)I can't remember your name.>> Y
(glass thuds)I can't remember your name.>> You
(glass thuds)I can't remember your name.>> You don
(glass thuds)I can't remember your name.>> You don't
(glass thuds)I can't remember your name.>> You don't k
(glass thuds)I can't remember your name.>> You don't kno
(glass thuds)I can't remember your name.>> You don't know wh
(glass thuds)I can't remember your name.>> You don't know who
(glass thuds)I can't remember your name.>> You don't know who I
(glass thuds)I can't remember your name.>> You don't know who I am
(glass thuds)I can't remember your name.>> You don't know who I am.
I can't remember your name.>> You don't know who I am.
I can't remember your name.>> You don't know who I am.(c
I can't remember your name.>> You don't know who I am.(cla
I can't remember your name.>> You don't know who I am.(clank
I can't remember your name.>> You don't know who I am.(clankin
I can't remember your name.>> You don't know who I am.(clanking)
>>
>> Y
>> You
>> You'r
>> You're Li
>> You're Liza
>> You're Liza's
>> You're Liza's d
>> You're Liza's daugh
>> You're Liza's daughte
>> You're Liza's daughter.
So
Some
Some u
Some ungod
Some ungodly
Some ungodly n
Some ungodly nam
Some ungodly name sh
Some ungodly name she
Some ungodly name she ga
Some ungodly name she gave
Some ungodly name she gave you
Some ungodly name she gave you,
Some ungodly name she gave you,he
Some ungodly name she gave you,her
Some ungodly name she gave you,her and
Some ungodly name she gave you,her and th
Some ungodly name she gave you,her and that
Some ungodly name she gave you,her and that F
Some ungodly name she gave you,her and that Franc
Some ungodly name she gave you,her and that Francis
Some ungodly name she gave you,her and that Francis.
Some ungodly name she gave you,her and that Francis.>>
Some ungodly name she gave you,her and that Francis.>> W
Some ungodly name she gave you,her and that Francis.>> Who
Some ungodly name she gave you,her and that Francis.>> Who tol
Some ungodly name she gave you,her and that Francis.>> Who told
Some ungodly name she gave you,her and that Francis.>> Who told yo
Some ungodly name she gave you,her and that Francis.>> Who told you?
her and that Francis.>> Who told you?
her and that Francis.>> Who told you?(d
her and that Francis.>> Who told you?(dis
her and that Francis.>> Who told you?(dishe
her and that Francis.>> Who told you?(dishes
her and that Francis.>> Who told you?(dishes clan
her and that Francis.>> Who told you?(dishes clanki
her and that Francis.>> Who told you?(dishes clanking
her and that Francis.>> Who told you?(dishes clanking t
her and that Francis.>> Who told you?(dishes clanking throu
her and that Francis.>> Who told you?(dishes clanking through
her and that Francis.>> Who told you?(dishes clanking throughou
her and that Francis.>> Who told you?(dishes clanking throughout)
>> Who told you?(dishes clanking throughout)
>> Who told you?(dishes clanking throughout)>>
>> Who told you?(dishes clanking throughout)>> C
>> Who told you?(dishes clanking throughout)>> Con
>> Who told you?(dishes clanking throughout)>> Connect
>> Who told you?(dishes clanking throughout)>> Connectic
>> Who told you?(dishes clanking throughout)>> Connecticut
>> Who told you?(dishes clanking throughout)>> Connecticut.
(dishes clanking throughout)>> Connecticut.
(dishes clanking throughout)>> Connecticut.Wh
(dishes clanking throughout)>> Connecticut.What
(dishes clanking throughout)>> Connecticut.What's
(dishes clanking throughout)>> Connecticut.What's her
(dishes clanking throughout)>> Connecticut.What's her n
(dishes clanking throughout)>> Connecticut.What's her nam
(dishes clanking throughout)>> Connecticut.What's her name?
>> Connecticut.What's her name?
>> Connecticut.What's her name?Ju
>> Connecticut.What's her name?Just
>> Connecticut.What's her name?Just l
>> Connecticut.What's her name?Just lik
>> Connecticut.What's her name?Just like he
>> Connecticut.What's her name?Just like her
>> Connecticut.What's her name?Just like her mo
>> Connecticut.What's her name?Just like her moth
>> Connecticut.What's her name?Just like her mother,
What's her name?Just like her mother,
What's her name?Just like her mother,Ma
What's her name?Just like her mother,Maud
What's her name?Just like her mother,Maudli
What's her name?Just like her mother,Maudlin, s
What's her name?Just like her mother,Maudlin, sim
What's her name?Just like her mother,Maudlin, simpe
What's her name?Just like her mother,Maudlin, simperi
What's her name?Just like her mother,Maudlin, simpering f
What's her name?Just like her mother,Maudlin, simpering foo
What's her name?Just like her mother,Maudlin, simpering fool.
Just like her mother,Maudlin, simpering fool.
Just like her mother,Maudlin, simpering fool.>>
Just like her mother,Maudlin, simpering fool.>> C
Just like her mother,Maudlin, simpering fool.>> Cou
Just like her mother,Maudlin, simpering fool.>> Cousin
Just like her mother,Maudlin, simpering fool.>> Cousin Eu
Just like her mother,Maudlin, simpering fool.>> Cousin Euni
Just like her mother,Maudlin, simpering fool.>> Cousin Eunice
Just like her mother,Maudlin, simpering fool.>> Cousin Eunice.
Maudlin, simpering fool.>> Cousin Eunice.
Maudlin, simpering fool.>> Cousin Eunice.>>
Maudlin, simpering fool.>> Cousin Eunice.>> Y
Maudlin, simpering fool.>> Cousin Eunice.>> Yea
Maudlin, simpering fool.>> Cousin Eunice.>> Yeah.
>> Cousin Eunice.>> Yeah.
>> Cousin Eunice.>> Yeah.Th
>> Cousin Eunice.>> Yeah.That
>> Cousin Eunice.>> Yeah.That's
>> Cousin Eunice.>> Yeah.That's it.
>> Yeah.That's it.
>> Yeah.That's it.Se
>> Yeah.That's it.Sent
>> Yeah.That's it.Sent t
>> Yeah.That's it.Sent the c
>> Yeah.That's it.Sent the cop
>> Yeah.That's it.Sent the cops
>> Yeah.That's it.Sent the cops ar
>> Yeah.That's it.Sent the cops around
>> Yeah.That's it.Sent the cops around h
>> Yeah.That's it.Sent the cops around her
>> Yeah.That's it.Sent the cops around here
That's it.Sent the cops around here
That's it.Sent the cops around herelo
That's it.Sent the cops around herelook
That's it.Sent the cops around herelooking
That's it.Sent the cops around herelooking fo
That's it.Sent the cops around herelooking for
That's it.Sent the cops around herelooking for ya
That's it.Sent the cops around herelooking for ya.
Sent the cops around herelooking for ya.
Sent the cops around herelooking for ya.Th
Sent the cops around herelooking for ya.They
Sent the cops around herelooking for ya.They s
Sent the cops around herelooking for ya.They sai
Sent the cops around herelooking for ya.They said on
Sent the cops around herelooking for ya.They said one'
Sent the cops around herelooking for ya.They said one's
Sent the cops around herelooking for ya.They said one's re
Sent the cops around herelooking for ya.They said one's retard
Sent the cops around herelooking for ya.They said one's retarded
Sent the cops around herelooking for ya.They said one's retarded.
looking for ya.They said one's retarded.
looking for ya.They said one's retarded.Ne
looking for ya.They said one's retarded.Neve
looking for ya.They said one's retarded.Never
looking for ya.They said one's retarded.Never says
looking for ya.They said one's retarded.Never says b
looking for ya.They said one's retarded.Never says boo
looking for ya.They said one's retarded.Never says boo.
They said one's retarded.Never says boo.
They said one's retarded.Never says boo.Is
They said one's retarded.Never says boo.Is s
They said one's retarded.Never says boo.Is she
They said one's retarded.Never says boo.Is she?
Never says boo.Is she?
Never says boo.Is she?>>
Never says boo.Is she?>> N
Never says boo.Is she?>> No.
Is she?>> No.
Is she?>> No.Not
Is she?>> No.Not th
Is she?>> No.Not that
Is she?>> No.Not that i
Is she?>> No.Not that it co
Is she?>> No.Not that it conc
Is she?>> No.Not that it concer
Is she?>> No.Not that it concerns
Is she?>> No.Not that it concerns you
Is she?>> No.Not that it concerns you.
My
My n
My nam
My name'
My name's Di
My name's Dice
My name's Dicey.
>>
>> T
>> Tha
>> That'
>> That's ri
>> That's righ
>> That's right.
>> That's right.I
>> That's right.I re
>> That's right.I rememb
>> That's right.I remember
>> That's right.I remember n
>> That's right.I remember now
>> That's right.I remember now.
>>
>> I
>> I'm g
>> I'm goi
>> I'm going
>> I'm going.
>> I'm going.>> S
>> I'm going.>> Sui
>> I'm going.>> Suit
>> I'm going.>> Suit yo
>> I'm going.>> Suit yourse
>> I'm going.>> Suit yourself
>> I'm going.>> Suit yourself.
Wh
Wher
Where
Where you
Where you al
Where you all
Where you all pl
Where you all planni
Where you all planning
Where you all planning o
Where you all planning on
Where you all planning onsl
Where you all planning onslee
Where you all planning onsleepi
Where you all planning onsleeping t
Where you all planning onsleeping ton
Where you all planning onsleeping tonig
Where you all planning onsleeping tonight
Where you all planning onsleeping tonight?
Where you all planning onsleeping tonight?>>
Where you all planning onsleeping tonight?>> W
Where you all planning onsleeping tonight?>> We're
Where you all planning onsleeping tonight?>> We're m
Where you all planning onsleeping tonight?>> We're mov
Where you all planning onsleeping tonight?>> We're movin
Where you all planning onsleeping tonight?>> We're moving on
Where you all planning onsleeping tonight?>> We're moving on.
sleeping tonight?>> We're moving on.
sleeping tonight?>> We're moving on.We
sleeping tonight?>> We're moving on.We d
sleeping tonight?>> We're moving on.We don
sleeping tonight?>> We're moving on.We don't n
sleeping tonight?>> We're moving on.We don't nee
sleeping tonight?>> We're moving on.We don't need
sleeping tonight?>> We're moving on.We don't need a
sleeping tonight?>> We're moving on.We don't need a plac
sleeping tonight?>> We're moving on.We don't need a place
sleeping tonight?>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to
sleeping tonight?>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to s
sleeping tonight?>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to stay.
>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to stay.
>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to stay.>>
>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to stay.>> D
>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't
>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't l
>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie
>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie t
>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie to me
>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie to me,
>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie to me, gi
>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie to me, girl
>> We're moving on.We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie to me, girl,
We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie to me, girl,
We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie to me, girl,yo
We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie to me, girl,you'
We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're r
We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're run
We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're runaw
We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're runaway
We don't need a place to stay.>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're runaways.
>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're runaways.
>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're runaways.>>
>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're runaways.>> T
>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're runaways.>> The
>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're runaways.>> There
>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're runaways.>> There's n
>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're runaways.>> There's no
>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're runaways.>> There's no po
>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're runaways.>> There's no poin
>> Don't lie to me, girl,you're runaways.>> There's no point
you're runaways.>> There's no point
you're runaways.>> There's no pointin
you're runaways.>> There's no pointin s
you're runaways.>> There's no pointin stayi
you're runaways.>> There's no pointin staying
you're runaways.>> There's no pointin staying h
you're runaways.>> There's no pointin staying her
you're runaways.>> There's no pointin staying here.
>> There's no pointin staying here.
>> There's no pointin staying here.>>
>> There's no pointin staying here.>> I
>> There's no pointin staying here.>> I s
>> There's no pointin staying here.>> I said
>> There's no pointin staying here.>> I said sl
>> There's no pointin staying here.>> I said slee
>> There's no pointin staying here.>> I said sleep,
>> There's no pointin staying here.>> I said sleep, not
>> There's no pointin staying here.>> I said sleep, not s
>> There's no pointin staying here.>> I said sleep, not sta
>> There's no pointin staying here.>> I said sleep, not stay.
in staying here.>> I said sleep, not stay.
in staying here.>> I said sleep, not stay.No
in staying here.>> I said sleep, not stay.No r
in staying here.>> I said sleep, not stay.No rea
in staying here.>> I said sleep, not stay.No reaso
in staying here.>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason fo
in staying here.>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason for
in staying here.>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason for yo
in staying here.>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason for you
in staying here.>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason for you not
>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason for you not
>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason for you notto s
>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason for you notto sle
>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason for you notto sleep
>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason for you notto sleep h
>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason for you notto sleep here,
>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason for you notto sleep here, i
>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason for you notto sleep here, is
>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason for you notto sleep here, is th
>> I said sleep, not stay.No reason for you notto sleep here, is there?
No reason for you notto sleep here, is there?
No reason for you notto sleep here, is there?>>
No reason for you notto sleep here, is there?>> Y
No reason for you notto sleep here, is there?>> Yes,
No reason for you notto sleep here, is there?>> Yes, I
No reason for you notto sleep here, is there?>> Yes, I th
No reason for you notto sleep here, is there?>> Yes, I thin
No reason for you notto sleep here, is there?>> Yes, I think th
No reason for you notto sleep here, is there?>> Yes, I think ther
No reason for you notto sleep here, is there?>> Yes, I think there
No reason for you notto sleep here, is there?>> Yes, I think there is
No reason for you notto sleep here, is there?>> Yes, I think there is.
>>
>> Y
>> You'l
>> You'll
>> You'll sl
>> You'll slee
>> You'll sleep he
>> You'll sleep here
>> You'll sleep here b
>> You'll sleep here bec
>> You'll sleep here because
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou go
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got no
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got nowher
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got nowhere
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got nowhere el
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got nowhere else
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got nowhere else to
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got nowhere else to go
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got nowhere else to go.
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got nowhere else to go.>>
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got nowhere else to go.>> W
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got nowhere else to go.>> We
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got nowhere else to go.>> We do
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got nowhere else to go.>> We do, to
>> You'll sleep here becauseyou got nowhere else to go.>> We do, too.
you got nowhere else to go.>> We do, too.
you got nowhere else to go.>> We do, too.>>
you got nowhere else to go.>> We do, too.>> T
you got nowhere else to go.>> We do, too.>> Then
you got nowhere else to go.>> We do, too.>> Then wh
you got nowhere else to go.>> We do, too.>> Then why'
you got nowhere else to go.>> We do, too.>> Then why'd
you got nowhere else to go.>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you
you got nowhere else to go.>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you co
you got nowhere else to go.>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you come
>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you come
>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you cometrai
>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you cometraips
>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you cometraipsin
>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you cometraipsing
>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down
>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down h
>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down her
>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down here
>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down here 500
>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down here 500 mi
>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down here 500 mile
>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down here 500 miles.
>> We do, too.>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down here 500 miles...
>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down here 500 miles...
>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down here 500 miles...ju
>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down here 500 miles...just
>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down here 500 miles...just to
>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down here 500 miles...just to fi
>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down here 500 miles...just to find
>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down here 500 miles...just to find m
>> Then why'd you cometraipsing down here 500 miles...just to find me?!
traipsing down here 500 miles...just to find me?!
traipsing down here 500 miles...just to find me?!Huh?
just to find me?!Huh?
just to find me?!Huh?An
just to find me?!Huh?Answ
just to find me?!Huh?Answer
just to find me?!Huh?Answer m
just to find me?!Huh?Answer me th
just to find me?!Huh?Answer me that
just to find me?!Huh?Answer me that.
(chu
(chuck
(chuckli
(chuckling
(chuckling)
Well
Well?
Well?>>
Well?>> O
Well?>> Oka
Well?>> Okay.
Well?>> Okay.Bu
Well?>> Okay.But.
Well?>> Okay.But...
>> Okay.But...
>> Okay.But...>>
>> Okay.But...>> B
>> Okay.But...>> But
>> Okay.But...>> But wha
>> Okay.But...>> But what?
But...>> But what?
But...>> But what?Be
But...>> But what?Be n
But...>> But what?Be nic
But...>> But what?Be nice
But...>> But what?Be nice to t
But...>> But what?Be nice to the
But...>> But what?Be nice to them?
>> But what?Be nice to them?
>> But what?Be nice to them?Nice
>> But what?Be nice to them?Nicer
>> But what?Be nice to them?Nicer th
>> But what?Be nice to them?Nicer than
>> But what?Be nice to them?Nicer than I w
>> But what?Be nice to them?Nicer than I was
>> But what?Be nice to them?Nicer than I was t
>> But what?Be nice to them?Nicer than I was to
>> But what?Be nice to them?Nicer than I was to you?
Be nice to them?Nicer than I was to you?
Be nice to them?Nicer than I was to you?>>
Be nice to them?Nicer than I was to you?>> Y
Be nice to them?Nicer than I was to you?>> Yea
Be nice to them?Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.
Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.
Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.>>
Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.>> I
Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.>> I'm n
Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.>> I'm not
Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.>> I'm not m
Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.>> I'm not mak
Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.>> I'm not making
Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.>> I'm not making an
Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.>> I'm not making any
Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.>> I'm not making any pr
Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.>> I'm not making any promis
Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.>> I'm not making any promises
Nicer than I was to you?>> Yeah.>> I'm not making any promises.
>> Yeah.>> I'm not making any promises.
>> Yeah.>> I'm not making any promises.Le
>> Yeah.>> I'm not making any promises.Let'
>> Yeah.>> I'm not making any promises.Let's
>> Yeah.>> I'm not making any promises.Let's get
>> Yeah.>> I'm not making any promises.Let's get go
>> Yeah.>> I'm not making any promises.Let's get goin
>> Yeah.>> I'm not making any promises.Let's get going.
>> I'm not making any promises.Let's get going.
>> I'm not making any promises.Let's get going.♪
Let's get going.♪
Let's get going.♪(d
Let's get going.♪(doo
Let's get going.♪(door
Let's get going.♪(door crea
Let's get going.♪(door creaki
Let's get going.♪(door creaking
Let's get going.♪(door creaking)
(b
(bir
(birds
(birds chi
(birds chirp
(birds chirpin
(birds chirping)
(i
(ind
(indis
(indistinc
(indistinct
(indistinct ch
(indistinct chat
(indistinct chatter)
(b
(boa
(boat
(boat mo
(boat motor
(boat motor th
(boat motor thro
(boat motor thrott
(boat motor throttling
(boat motor throttling d
(boat motor throttling dow
(boat motor throttling down)
(boat motor throttling down)>>
(boat motor throttling down)>> J
(boat motor throttling down)>> Jam
(boat motor throttling down)>> James?!
>>
>> H
>> Hey
>> Hey, Ab
>> Hey, Ab,
>> Hey, Ab, lo
>> Hey, Ab, long
>> Hey, Ab, long tim
>> Hey, Ab, long time
>> Hey, Ab, long time no
>> Hey, Ab, long time no s
>> Hey, Ab, long time no see.
>> Hey, Ab, long time no see.>>
>> Hey, Ab, long time no see.>> J
>> Hey, Ab, long time no see.>> Jam
>> Hey, Ab, long time no see.>> James?
I
I do
I don'
I don't
I don't know
I don't know.
I don't know.I
I don't know.I le
I don't know.I left
I don't know.I left the
I don't know.I left them
I don't know.I left them ri
I don't know.I left them righ
I don't know.I left them right he
I don't know.I left them right here
I don't know.I left them right here.
(w
(whi
(whist
(whistle b
(whistle blo
(whistle blowi
(whistle blowing
(whistle blowing)
(whistle blowing)Ja
(whistle blowing)Jame
(whistle blowing)James?
>>
>> D
>> Dicey
>> Dicey!
>> Dicey!Di
>> Dicey!Dice
>> Dicey!Dicey!
>> Dicey!Dicey!>>
>> Dicey!Dicey!>> S
>> Dicey!Dicey!>> Sam
>> Dicey!Dicey!>> Sammy!
Dicey!>> Sammy!
Dicey!>> Sammy!>>
Dicey!>> Sammy!>> I
Dicey!>> Sammy!>> I t
Dicey!>> Sammy!>> I told
Dicey!>> Sammy!>> I told Ja
Dicey!>> Sammy!>> I told Jame
Dicey!>> Sammy!>> I told James.
>> Sammy!>> I told James.
>> Sammy!>> I told James.>>
>> Sammy!>> I told James.>> T
>> Sammy!>> I told James.>> Tol
>> Sammy!>> I told James.>> Told hi
>> Sammy!>> I told James.>> Told him
>> Sammy!>> I told James.>> Told him wh
>> Sammy!>> I told James.>> Told him what
>> Sammy!>> I told James.>> Told him what?
>> I told James.>> Told him what?
>> I told James.>> Told him what?I'
>> I told James.>> Told him what?I'll
>> I told James.>> Told him what?I'll t
>> I told James.>> Told him what?I'll tell
>> I told James.>> Told him what?I'll tell yo
>> I told James.>> Told him what?I'll tell you,
>> I told James.>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I
>> I told James.>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was
>> I told James.>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was s
>> I told James.>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was sca
>> I told James.>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was scare
>> I told James.>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was scared.
>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was scared.
>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was scared.>>
>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was scared.>> T
>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Tol
>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told hi
>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him
>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him yo
>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'
>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'd be
>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'd be b
>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'd be bac
>> Told him what?I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'd be back.
I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'd be back.
I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'd be back.>>
I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'd be back.>> W
I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'd be back.>> Wel
I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'd be back.>> Well,
I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'd be back.>> Well, whe
I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'd be back.>> Well, where
I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'd be back.>> Well, where i
I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'd be back.>> Well, where is
I'll tell you, I was scared.>> Told him you'd be back.>> Well, where is he?
>> Told him you'd be back.>> Well, where is he?
>> Told him you'd be back.>> Well, where is he?Wh
>> Told him you'd be back.>> Well, where is he?Wher
>> Told him you'd be back.>> Well, where is he?Where'
>> Told him you'd be back.>> Well, where is he?Where's
>> Told him you'd be back.>> Well, where is he?Where's Mayb
>> Told him you'd be back.>> Well, where is he?Where's Maybet
>> Told him you'd be back.>> Well, where is he?Where's Maybeth?
>> Well, where is he?Where's Maybeth?
>> Well, where is he?Where's Maybeth?>> T
>> Well, where is he?Where's Maybeth?>> The
>> Well, where is he?Where's Maybeth?>> They
>> Well, where is he?Where's Maybeth?>> They wa
>> Well, where is he?Where's Maybeth?>> They walked
>> Well, where is he?Where's Maybeth?>> They walked o
>> Well, where is he?Where's Maybeth?>> They walked out
Where's Maybeth?>> They walked out
Where's Maybeth?>> They walked outto
Where's Maybeth?>> They walked outto t
Where's Maybeth?>> They walked outto the
Where's Maybeth?>> They walked outto the f
Where's Maybeth?>> They walked outto the farm.
>> They walked outto the farm.
>> They walked outto the farm.We
>> They walked outto the farm.We w
>> They walked outto the farm.We wai
>> They walked outto the farm.We waited
>> They walked outto the farm.We waited a
>> They walked outto the farm.We waited a lo
>> They walked outto the farm.We waited a long
>> They walked outto the farm.We waited a long tim
>> They walked outto the farm.We waited a long time
to the farm.We waited a long time
to the farm.We waited a long timean
to the farm.We waited a long timeand
to the farm.We waited a long timeand Ja
to the farm.We waited a long timeand James
to the farm.We waited a long timeand James sa
to the farm.We waited a long timeand James said
to the farm.We waited a long timeand James said y
to the farm.We waited a long timeand James said you w
to the farm.We waited a long timeand James said you wer
to the farm.We waited a long timeand James said you were
to the farm.We waited a long timeand James said you were wr
to the farm.We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.
We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.
We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.We
We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.We s
We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.We sho
We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.We should'
We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.We should've
We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.We should've a
We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.We should've all
We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.We should've all gon
We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.We should've all gone
We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.We should've all gone to
We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.We should've all gone toge
We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.We should've all gone together
We waited a long timeand James said you were wrong.We should've all gone together.
and James said you were wrong.We should've all gone together.
and James said you were wrong.We should've all gone together.Then
and James said you were wrong.We should've all gone together.Then h
and James said you were wrong.We should've all gone together.Then he
and James said you were wrong.We should've all gone together.Then he sa
and James said you were wrong.We should've all gone together.Then he said I
and James said you were wrong.We should've all gone together.Then he said I h
and James said you were wrong.We should've all gone together.Then he said I had
and James said you were wrong.We should've all gone together.Then he said I had t
and James said you were wrong.We should've all gone together.Then he said I had to do
We should've all gone together.Then he said I had to do
We should've all gone together.Then he said I had to dowh
We should've all gone together.Then he said I had to dowhat
We should've all gone together.Then he said I had to dowhat h
We should've all gone together.Then he said I had to dowhat he
We should've all gone together.Then he said I had to dowhat he said
We should've all gone together.Then he said I had to dowhat he said.
Then he said I had to dowhat he said.
Then he said I had to dowhat he said.Bu
Then he said I had to dowhat he said.But
Then he said I had to dowhat he said.But I
Then he said I had to dowhat he said.But I said
Then he said I had to dowhat he said.But I said n
Then he said I had to dowhat he said.But I said no.
what he said.But I said no.
what he said.But I said no.He s
what he said.But I said no.He sai
what he said.But I said no.He said
what he said.But I said no.He said yo
what he said.But I said no.He said you sa
what he said.But I said no.He said you said
what he said.But I said no.He said you said t
what he said.But I said no.He said you said to.
But I said no.He said you said to.
But I said no.He said you said to.I sa
But I said no.He said you said to.I said
But I said no.He said you said to.I said,
But I said no.He said you said to.I said, "Y
But I said no.He said you said to.I said, "You s
But I said no.He said you said to.I said, "You sai
But I said no.He said you said to.I said, "You said
But I said no.He said you said to.I said, "You said to
But I said no.He said you said to.I said, "You said to sta
But I said no.He said you said to.I said, "You said to stay
But I said no.He said you said to.I said, "You said to stay he
But I said no.He said you said to.I said, "You said to stay here
He said you said to.I said, "You said to stay here
He said you said to.I said, "You said to stay here"a
He said you said to.I said, "You said to stay here"and
He said you said to.I said, "You said to stay here"and d
He said you said to.I said, "You said to stay here"and do wh
He said you said to.I said, "You said to stay here"and do what
He said you said to.I said, "You said to stay here"and do what h
He said you said to.I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he
He said you said to.I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said
He said you said to.I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.
I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.
I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.No
I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.Not
I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.Not go
I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.Not go off
I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.Not go off b
I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.Not go off bec
I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.Not go off becau
I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.Not go off because h
I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.Not go off because he
I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.Not go off because he sa
I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.Not go off because he said
I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.Not go off because he said to.
I said, "You said to stay here"and do what he said.Not go off because he said to."
"and do what he said.Not go off because he said to."
"and do what he said.Not go off because he said to."So h
"and do what he said.Not go off because he said to."So he
"and do what he said.Not go off because he said to."So he to
"and do what he said.Not go off because he said to."So he took
"and do what he said.Not go off because he said to."So he took May
"and do what he said.Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybe
"and do what he said.Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth
"and do what he said.Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth.
Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth.
Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth.>>
Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth.>> H
Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth.>> He
Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth.>> He thin
Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks
Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks h
Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks he'
Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks he's so
Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks he's so s
Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks he's so sma
Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks he's so smart
Not go off because he said to."So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks he's so smart.
So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks he's so smart.
So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks he's so smart.An
So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks he's so smart.And
So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks he's so smart.And he
So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is
So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is sm
So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is smar
So he took Maybeth.>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is smart.
>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is smart.
>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is smart.But
>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is smart.But I
>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is smart.But I to
>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is smart.But I told
>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is smart.But I told him
>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is smart.But I told him t
>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is smart.But I told him to
>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is smart.But I told him to st
>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is smart.But I told him to stay h
>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is smart.But I told him to stay her
>> He thinks he's so smart.And he is smart.But I told him to stay here.
And he is smart.But I told him to stay here.
And he is smart.But I told him to stay here.I to
And he is smart.But I told him to stay here.I told
And he is smart.But I told him to stay here.I told h
And he is smart.But I told him to stay here.I told him
And he is smart.But I told him to stay here.I told him.
But I told him to stay here.I told him.
But I told him to stay here.I told him.>> A
But I told him to stay here.I told him.>> Are
But I told him to stay here.I told him.>> Are y
But I told him to stay here.I told him.>> Are you
But I told him to stay here.I told him.>> Are you the
But I told him to stay here.I told him.>> Are you the g
But I told him to stay here.I told him.>> Are you the gra
But I told him to stay here.I told him.>> Are you the grand
But I told him to stay here.I told him.>> Are you the grandmoth
But I told him to stay here.I told him.>> Are you the grandmother
But I told him to stay here.I told him.>> Are you the grandmother?
I told him.>> Are you the grandmother?
I told him.>> Are you the grandmother?>> Y
I told him.>> Are you the grandmother?>> Yea
I told him.>> Are you the grandmother?>> Yeah.
>> Are you the grandmother?>> Yeah.
>> Are you the grandmother?>> Yeah.>>
>> Are you the grandmother?>> Yeah.>> W
>> Are you the grandmother?>> Yeah.>> Wha
>> Are you the grandmother?>> Yeah.>> What am
>> Are you the grandmother?>> Yeah.>> What am I
>> Are you the grandmother?>> Yeah.>> What am I s
>> Are you the grandmother?>> Yeah.>> What am I sup
>> Are you the grandmother?>> Yeah.>> What am I suppose
>> Are you the grandmother?>> Yeah.>> What am I supposed
>> Are you the grandmother?>> Yeah.>> What am I supposed to
>> Yeah.>> What am I supposed to
>> Yeah.>> What am I supposed toca
>> Yeah.>> What am I supposed tocall
>> Yeah.>> What am I supposed tocall you
>> Yeah.>> What am I supposed tocall you?
>> What am I supposed tocall you?
>> What am I supposed tocall you?>>
>> What am I supposed tocall you?>> L
>> What am I supposed tocall you?>> Let's
>> What am I supposed tocall you?>> Let's g
>> What am I supposed tocall you?>> Let's get
>> What am I supposed tocall you?>> Let's get b
>> What am I supposed tocall you?>> Let's get back.
call you?>> Let's get back.
call you?>> Let's get back.>>
call you?>> Let's get back.>> W
call you?>> Let's get back.>> Wha
call you?>> Let's get back.>> What
call you?>> Let's get back.>> What abou
call you?>> Let's get back.>> What about
call you?>> Let's get back.>> What about Ja
call you?>> Let's get back.>> What about Jame
call you?>> Let's get back.>> What about James an
call you?>> Let's get back.>> What about James and
call you?>> Let's get back.>> What about James and Ma
call you?>> Let's get back.>> What about James and Mayb
call you?>> Let's get back.>> What about James and Maybeth?
>> Let's get back.>> What about James and Maybeth?
>> Let's get back.>> What about James and Maybeth?We c
>> Let's get back.>> What about James and Maybeth?We can
>> Let's get back.>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't
>> Let's get back.>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't j
>> Let's get back.>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just
>> Let's get back.>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just le
>> Let's get back.>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just leav
>> Let's get back.>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just leave
>> Let's get back.>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just leave them
>> Let's get back.>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just leave them.
>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just leave them.
>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just leave them.>>
>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just leave them.>> Y
>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just leave them.>> You
>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just leave them.>> You alr
>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just leave them.>> You alrea
>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just leave them.>> You already
>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just leave them.>> You already d
>> What about James and Maybeth?We can't just leave them.>> You already did.
We can't just leave them.>> You already did.
We can't just leave them.>> You already did.Th
We can't just leave them.>> You already did.They
We can't just leave them.>> You already did.They'l
We can't just leave them.>> You already did.They'll fi
We can't just leave them.>> You already did.They'll find
We can't just leave them.>> You already did.They'll find t
We can't just leave them.>> You already did.They'll find the
We can't just leave them.>> You already did.They'll find there o
We can't just leave them.>> You already did.They'll find there own
We can't just leave them.>> You already did.They'll find there own w
We can't just leave them.>> You already did.They'll find there own way
We can't just leave them.>> You already did.They'll find there own way.
>> You already did.They'll find there own way.
>> You already did.They'll find there own way.>> W
>> You already did.They'll find there own way.>> Wha
>> You already did.They'll find there own way.>> What'
>> You already did.They'll find there own way.>> What's
>> You already did.They'll find there own way.>> What's it l
>> You already did.They'll find there own way.>> What's it lik
>> You already did.They'll find there own way.>> What's it like?
They'll find there own way.>> What's it like?
They'll find there own way.>> What's it like?♪
>> What's it like?♪
>> What's it like?♪>>
>> What's it like?♪>> R
>> What's it like?♪>> Run
>> What's it like?♪>> Rundo
>> What's it like?♪>> Rundown.
♪>> Rundown.
♪>> Rundown.>> A
♪>> Rundown.>> Are
♪>> Rundown.>> Are w
♪>> Rundown.>> Are we
♪>> Rundown.>> Are we gonn
♪>> Rundown.>> Are we gonna
♪>> Rundown.>> Are we gonna st
♪>> Rundown.>> Are we gonna stay
♪>> Rundown.>> Are we gonna stay?
>> Rundown.>> Are we gonna stay?
>> Rundown.>> Are we gonna stay?>> J
>> Rundown.>> Are we gonna stay?>> Jus
>> Rundown.>> Are we gonna stay?>> Just
>> Rundown.>> Are we gonna stay?>> Just to
>> Rundown.>> Are we gonna stay?>> Just tonigh
>> Rundown.>> Are we gonna stay?>> Just tonight.
>>
>> T
>> That'
>> That's
>> That's ok
>> That's okay
>> That's okay, Di
>> That's okay, Dice
>> That's okay, Dicey.
(bir
(birds
(birds c
(birds chi
(birds chirpin
(birds chirping)
(i
(ins
(insec
(insect
(insect buzz
(insect buzzin
(insect buzzing)
>>
>> J
>> Jam
>> James
>> James!
>> James!Ja
>> James!Jame
>> James!James!
>> James!James!I'
>> James!James!I'm
>> James!James!I'm gonn
>> James!James!I'm gonna
>> James!James!I'm gonna go
>> James!James!I'm gonna go f
>> James!James!I'm gonna go find
>> James!James!I'm gonna go find th
>> James!James!I'm gonna go find them
>> James!James!I'm gonna go find them.
James!I'm gonna go find them.
James!I'm gonna go find them.Do
James!I'm gonna go find them.Do y
James!I'm gonna go find them.Do you
James!I'm gonna go find them.Do you w
James!I'm gonna go find them.Do you wanna
James!I'm gonna go find them.Do you wanna c
James!I'm gonna go find them.Do you wanna com
James!I'm gonna go find them.Do you wanna come
James!I'm gonna go find them.Do you wanna come or s
James!I'm gonna go find them.Do you wanna come or sta
James!I'm gonna go find them.Do you wanna come or stay?
I'm gonna go find them.Do you wanna come or stay?
I'm gonna go find them.Do you wanna come or stay?>> I
I'm gonna go find them.Do you wanna come or stay?>> I'l
I'm gonna go find them.Do you wanna come or stay?>> I'll
I'm gonna go find them.Do you wanna come or stay?>> I'll st
I'm gonna go find them.Do you wanna come or stay?>> I'll stay.
Do you wanna come or stay?>> I'll stay.
Do you wanna come or stay?>> I'll stay.>> S
Do you wanna come or stay?>> I'll stay.>> She
Do you wanna come or stay?>> I'll stay.>> She's
Do you wanna come or stay?>> I'll stay.>> She's n
Do you wanna come or stay?>> I'll stay.>> She's not f
Do you wanna come or stay?>> I'll stay.>> She's not fri
Do you wanna come or stay?>> I'll stay.>> She's not frien
Do you wanna come or stay?>> I'll stay.>> She's not friendl
Do you wanna come or stay?>> I'll stay.>> She's not friendly.
>> I'll stay.>> She's not friendly.
>> I'll stay.>> She's not friendly.>>
>> I'll stay.>> She's not friendly.>> N
>> I'll stay.>> She's not friendly.>> Nei
>> I'll stay.>> She's not friendly.>> Neither
>> I'll stay.>> She's not friendly.>> Neither a
>> I'll stay.>> She's not friendly.>> Neither am
>> I'll stay.>> She's not friendly.>> Neither am I.
>>
>> S
>> Sammy
>> Sammy's
>> Sammy's a
>> Sammy's alo
>> Sammy's alone d
>> Sammy's alone dow
>> Sammy's alone downt
>> Sammy's alone downtow
>> Sammy's alone downtown.
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll g
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go ba
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back a
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back and
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back and get
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back and get h
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back and get him
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back and get himif e
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back and get himif eve
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back and get himif every
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back and get himif everyth
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back and get himif everything'
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back and get himif everything's
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back and get himif everything's ok
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back and get himif everything's okay
>> Sammy's alone downtown.I'll go back and get himif everything's okay.
I'll go back and get himif everything's okay.
I'll go back and get himif everything's okay.>>
I'll go back and get himif everything's okay.>> E
I'll go back and get himif everything's okay.>> Eve
I'll go back and get himif everything's okay.>> Everyth
I'll go back and get himif everything's okay.>> Everythin
I'll go back and get himif everything's okay.>> Everything'
I'll go back and get himif everything's okay.>> Everything's
I'll go back and get himif everything's okay.>> Everything's not
I'll go back and get himif everything's okay.>> Everything's not ok
I'll go back and get himif everything's okay.>> Everything's not okay
I'll go back and get himif everything's okay.>> Everything's not okay.
if everything's okay.>> Everything's not okay.
if everything's okay.>> Everything's not okay.Sa
if everything's okay.>> Everything's not okay.Samm
if everything's okay.>> Everything's not okay.Sammy'
if everything's okay.>> Everything's not okay.Sammy's he
if everything's okay.>> Everything's not okay.Sammy's here
if everything's okay.>> Everything's not okay.Sammy's here.
>> Everything's not okay.Sammy's here.
>> Everything's not okay.Sammy's here.Sh
>> Everything's not okay.Sammy's here.She
>> Everything's not okay.Sammy's here.She do
>> Everything's not okay.Sammy's here.She doesn'
>> Everything's not okay.Sammy's here.She doesn't
>> Everything's not okay.Sammy's here.She doesn't ha
>> Everything's not okay.Sammy's here.She doesn't have
>> Everything's not okay.Sammy's here.She doesn't have a c
>> Everything's not okay.Sammy's here.She doesn't have a car
>> Everything's not okay.Sammy's here.She doesn't have a car.
Sammy's here.She doesn't have a car.
Sammy's here.She doesn't have a car.Sh
Sammy's here.She doesn't have a car.She
Sammy's here.She doesn't have a car.She us
Sammy's here.She doesn't have a car.She uses
Sammy's here.She doesn't have a car.She uses a b
Sammy's here.She doesn't have a car.She uses a boa
Sammy's here.She doesn't have a car.She uses a boat.
She doesn't have a car.She uses a boat.
She doesn't have a car.She uses a boat.That
She doesn't have a car.She uses a boat.That w
She doesn't have a car.She uses a boat.That was
She doesn't have a car.She uses a boat.That wasn'
She doesn't have a car.She uses a boat.That wasn't ve
She doesn't have a car.She uses a boat.That wasn't very
She doesn't have a car.She uses a boat.That wasn't very s
She doesn't have a car.She uses a boat.That wasn't very sma
She doesn't have a car.She uses a boat.That wasn't very smart,
She doesn't have a car.She uses a boat.That wasn't very smart, Ja
She doesn't have a car.She uses a boat.That wasn't very smart, Jame
She doesn't have a car.She uses a boat.That wasn't very smart, James.
She uses a boat.That wasn't very smart, James.
She uses a boat.That wasn't very smart, James.>> N
She uses a boat.That wasn't very smart, James.>> No.
That wasn't very smart, James.>> No.
That wasn't very smart, James.>> No.We
That wasn't very smart, James.>> No.Well
That wasn't very smart, James.>> No.Well,
That wasn't very smart, James.>> No.Well, I
That wasn't very smart, James.>> No.Well, I thou
That wasn't very smart, James.>> No.Well, I though
That wasn't very smart, James.>> No.Well, I thought
That wasn't very smart, James.>> No.Well, I thought it
That wasn't very smart, James.>> No.Well, I thought it was
>> No.Well, I thought it was
>> No.Well, I thought it waswh
>> No.Well, I thought it waswhen
>> No.Well, I thought it waswhen w
>> No.Well, I thought it waswhen we fi
>> No.Well, I thought it waswhen we firs
>> No.Well, I thought it waswhen we first
>> No.Well, I thought it waswhen we first st
>> No.Well, I thought it waswhen we first starte
>> No.Well, I thought it waswhen we first started
>> No.Well, I thought it waswhen we first started ou
>> No.Well, I thought it waswhen we first started out.
Well, I thought it waswhen we first started out.
Well, I thought it waswhen we first started out.>>
Well, I thought it waswhen we first started out.>> W
Well, I thought it waswhen we first started out.>> Wel
Well, I thought it waswhen we first started out.>> Well,
Well, I thought it waswhen we first started out.>> Well, don
Well, I thought it waswhen we first started out.>> Well, don't
Well, I thought it waswhen we first started out.>> Well, don't w
Well, I thought it waswhen we first started out.>> Well, don't wor
Well, I thought it waswhen we first started out.>> Well, don't worry.
when we first started out.>> Well, don't worry.
when we first started out.>> Well, don't worry.Sh
when we first started out.>> Well, don't worry.She
when we first started out.>> Well, don't worry.She do
when we first started out.>> Well, don't worry.She doesn'
when we first started out.>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't
when we first started out.>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't wa
when we first started out.>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want
when we first started out.>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us
when we first started out.>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to
when we first started out.>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to s
when we first started out.>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to sta
when we first started out.>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to stay.
>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to stay.
>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to stay.Bu
>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to stay.But
>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to stay.But we c
>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to stay.But we can
>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to stay.But we can s
>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sle
>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep h
>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep her
>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here
>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here to
>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here tonigh
>> Well, don't worry.She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here tonight.
She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here tonight.
She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here tonight.>>
She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here tonight.>> T
She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here tonight.>> The
She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then wh
She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then wher
She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then where
She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then where do
She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then where do we
She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then where do we go
She doesn't want us to stay.But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then where do we go?
But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then where do we go?
But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then where do we go?>>
But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then where do we go?>> I
But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then where do we go?>> I d
But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then where do we go?>> I don't
But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then where do we go?>> I don't k
But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then where do we go?>> I don't kno
But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then where do we go?>> I don't know
But we can sleep here tonight.>> Then where do we go?>> I don't know yet.
An
Anyw
Anyway
Anyway, th
Anyway, this
Anyway, this i
Anyway, this is
Anyway, this is wher
Anyway, this is where
Anyway, this is whereMa
Anyway, this is whereMama
Anyway, this is whereMama l
Anyway, this is whereMama lived
Anyway, this is whereMama lived.
Anyway, this is whereMama lived.(pum
Anyway, this is whereMama lived.(pump
Anyway, this is whereMama lived.(pump ha
Anyway, this is whereMama lived.(pump hand
Anyway, this is whereMama lived.(pump handle c
Anyway, this is whereMama lived.(pump handle cre
Anyway, this is whereMama lived.(pump handle creak
Anyway, this is whereMama lived.(pump handle creakin
Anyway, this is whereMama lived.(pump handle creaking)
Mama lived.(pump handle creaking)
Mama lived.(pump handle creaking)>> I
Mama lived.(pump handle creaking)>> It'
Mama lived.(pump handle creaking)>> It's
Mama lived.(pump handle creaking)>> It's be
Mama lived.(pump handle creaking)>> It's beauti
Mama lived.(pump handle creaking)>> It's beautifu
Mama lived.(pump handle creaking)>> It's beautiful.
(pump handle creaking)>> It's beautiful.
(pump handle creaking)>> It's beautiful.>> I
(pump handle creaking)>> It's beautiful.>> It'
(pump handle creaking)>> It's beautiful.>> It's
(pump handle creaking)>> It's beautiful.>> It's a
(pump handle creaking)>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wrec
(pump handle creaking)>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wreck.
>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wreck.
>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wreck.Sh
>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wreck.She
>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wreck.She ha
>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wreck.She hasn't
>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wreck.She hasn't t
>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wreck.She hasn't tak
>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wreck.She hasn't taken
>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wreck.She hasn't taken car
>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wreck.She hasn't taken care
>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wreck.She hasn't taken care of
>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wreck.She hasn't taken care of i
>> It's beautiful.>> It's a wreck.She hasn't taken care of it.
>>
>> B
>> But i
>> But it'
>> But it's
>> But it's bi
>> But it's big.
>> But it's big.Bi
>> But it's big.Big
>> But it's big.Big en
>> But it's big.Big enou
>> But it's big.Big enough f
>> But it's big.Big enough for
>> But it's big.Big enough for a
>> But it's big.Big enough for all
>> But it's big.Big enough for all of
>> But it's big.Big enough for all of us
>> But it's big.Big enough for all of us.
>> But it's big.Big enough for all of us.>>
>> But it's big.Big enough for all of us.>> W
>> But it's big.Big enough for all of us.>> Who
>> But it's big.Big enough for all of us.>> Who car
>> But it's big.Big enough for all of us.>> Who cares
>> But it's big.Big enough for all of us.>> Who cares?
Big enough for all of us.>> Who cares?
Big enough for all of us.>> Who cares?We
Big enough for all of us.>> Who cares?We w
Big enough for all of us.>> Who cares?We won
Big enough for all of us.>> Who cares?We won't b
Big enough for all of us.>> Who cares?We won't be
Big enough for all of us.>> Who cares?We won't be st
Big enough for all of us.>> Who cares?We won't be stay
Big enough for all of us.>> Who cares?We won't be staying.
>> Who cares?We won't be staying.
>> Who cares?We won't be staying.>>
>> Who cares?We won't be staying.>> T
>> Who cares?We won't be staying.>> Tru
>> Who cares?We won't be staying.>> True
>> Who cares?We won't be staying.>> True enou
>> Who cares?We won't be staying.>> True enough
>> Who cares?We won't be staying.>> True enough.
We won't be staying.>> True enough.
We won't be staying.>> True enough.You'
We won't be staying.>> True enough.You'll
We won't be staying.>> True enough.You'll b
We won't be staying.>> True enough.You'll be
We won't be staying.>> True enough.You'll be here
We won't be staying.>> True enough.You'll be here f
We won't be staying.>> True enough.You'll be here for
We won't be staying.>> True enough.You'll be here for s
We won't be staying.>> True enough.You'll be here for suppe
We won't be staying.>> True enough.You'll be here for supper,
>> True enough.You'll be here for supper,
>> True enough.You'll be here for supper,so
>> True enough.You'll be here for supper,so t
>> True enough.You'll be here for supper,so the
>> True enough.You'll be here for supper,so there
>> True enough.You'll be here for supper,so there's w
>> True enough.You'll be here for supper,so there's wor
>> True enough.You'll be here for supper,so there's work
>> True enough.You'll be here for supper,so there's work to
>> True enough.You'll be here for supper,so there's work to be
>> True enough.You'll be here for supper,so there's work to be do
>> True enough.You'll be here for supper,so there's work to be done
>> True enough.You'll be here for supper,so there's work to be done.
You'll be here for supper,so there's work to be done.
You'll be here for supper,so there's work to be done.I
You'll be here for supper,so there's work to be done.I se
You'll be here for supper,so there's work to be done.I see yo
You'll be here for supper,so there's work to be done.I see you
You'll be here for supper,so there's work to be done.I see you fo
You'll be here for supper,so there's work to be done.I see you foun
You'll be here for supper,so there's work to be done.I see you found th
You'll be here for supper,so there's work to be done.I see you found them
You'll be here for supper,so there's work to be done.I see you found them.
Jame
James.
James.Ma
James.Mayb
James.Maybet
James.Maybeth.
I'
I've
I've g
I've got c
I've got cra
I've got crab
I've got crab po
I've got crab pots
I've got crab potsse
I've got crab potsset
I've got crab potsset down
I've got crab potsset down b
I've got crab potsset down by
I've got crab potsset down by th
I've got crab potsset down by the do
I've got crab potsset down by the dock
I've got crab potsset down by the dock.
I've got crab potsset down by the dock.Who'
I've got crab potsset down by the dock.Who'll
I've got crab potsset down by the dock.Who'll f
I've got crab potsset down by the dock.Who'll fet
I've got crab potsset down by the dock.Who'll fetch t
I've got crab potsset down by the dock.Who'll fetch the
I've got crab potsset down by the dock.Who'll fetch the c
I've got crab potsset down by the dock.Who'll fetch the cra
I've got crab potsset down by the dock.Who'll fetch the crabs?
set down by the dock.Who'll fetch the crabs?
set down by the dock.Who'll fetch the crabs?>>
set down by the dock.Who'll fetch the crabs?>> I
set down by the dock.Who'll fetch the crabs?>> I w
set down by the dock.Who'll fetch the crabs?>> I wil
set down by the dock.Who'll fetch the crabs?>> I will.
Who'll fetch the crabs?>> I will.
Who'll fetch the crabs?>> I will.>>
Who'll fetch the crabs?>> I will.>> M
Who'll fetch the crabs?>> I will.>> Me to
Who'll fetch the crabs?>> I will.>> Me too.
>> I will.>> Me too.
>> I will.>> Me too.>>
>> I will.>> Me too.>> J
>> I will.>> Me too.>> Jam
>> I will.>> Me too.>> James
>> I will.>> Me too.>> James and
>> I will.>> Me too.>> James and S
>> I will.>> Me too.>> James and Sam
>> I will.>> Me too.>> James and Sammy
>> I will.>> Me too.>> James and Sammy wil
>> I will.>> Me too.>> James and Sammy will.
>> Me too.>> James and Sammy will.
>> Me too.>> James and Sammy will.Ther
>> Me too.>> James and Sammy will.There'
>> Me too.>> James and Sammy will.There's
>> Me too.>> James and Sammy will.There's a
>> Me too.>> James and Sammy will.There's a bask
>> Me too.>> James and Sammy will.There's a basket
>> James and Sammy will.There's a basket
>> James and Sammy will.There's a basketout
>> James and Sammy will.There's a basketout by
>> James and Sammy will.There's a basketout by t
>> James and Sammy will.There's a basketout by the
>> James and Sammy will.There's a basketout by the bac
>> James and Sammy will.There's a basketout by the back
>> James and Sammy will.There's a basketout by the back st
>> James and Sammy will.There's a basketout by the back step
>> James and Sammy will.There's a basketout by the back steps.
Al
All
All ri
All right,
All right, I
All right, I e
All right, I eat
All right, I eat ear
All right, I eat early
All right, I eat earlyan
All right, I eat earlyand
All right, I eat earlyand so
All right, I eat earlyand so wil
All right, I eat earlyand so will
All right, I eat earlyand so will yo
All right, I eat earlyand so will you.
All right, I eat earlyand so will you.Yo
All right, I eat earlyand so will you.You
All right, I eat earlyand so will you.You tw
All right, I eat earlyand so will you.You two
All right, I eat earlyand so will you.You two come
All right, I eat earlyand so will you.You two come w
All right, I eat earlyand so will you.You two come wit
All right, I eat earlyand so will you.You two come with
All right, I eat earlyand so will you.You two come with me.
and so will you.You two come with me.
and so will you.You two come with me.Sh
and so will you.You two come with me.Show
and so will you.You two come with me.Show you
and so will you.You two come with me.Show you w
and so will you.You two come with me.Show you whe
and so will you.You two come with me.Show you where
and so will you.You two come with me.Show you where to
and so will you.You two come with me.Show you where to sl
and so will you.You two come with me.Show you where to slee
and so will you.You two come with me.Show you where to sleep.
Th
That
That's
That's m
That's my be
That's my bedr
That's my bedroo
That's my bedroom.
That's my bedroom.An
That's my bedroom.And
That's my bedroom.And th
That's my bedroom.And that
That's my bedroom.And that's
That's my bedroom.And that'smy
That's my bedroom.And that'smyba
That's my bedroom.And that'smybath
That's my bedroom.And that'smybathroom
That's my bedroom.And that'smybathroom.
Th
Ther
There's
There's a
There's a ba
There's a bath
There's a bathroom
There's a bathroom a
There's a bathroom at
There's a bathroom atth
There's a bathroom atthe
There's a bathroom atthe far
There's a bathroom atthe far en
There's a bathroom atthe far end.
There's a bathroom atthe far end.So
There's a bathroom atthe far end.Some
There's a bathroom atthe far end.Some she
There's a bathroom atthe far end.Some sheet
There's a bathroom atthe far end.Some sheets
There's a bathroom atthe far end.Some sheets in
There's a bathroom atthe far end.Some sheets in one
There's a bathroom atthe far end.Some sheets in one o
There's a bathroom atthe far end.Some sheets in one of
the far end.Some sheets in one of
the far end.Some sheets in one ofthe
the far end.Some sheets in one ofthe bu
the far end.Some sheets in one ofthe bure
the far end.Some sheets in one ofthe bureau
the far end.Some sheets in one ofthe bureaus--
Some sheets in one ofthe bureaus--
Some sheets in one ofthe bureaus--I ca
Some sheets in one ofthe bureaus--I can'
Some sheets in one ofthe bureaus--I can't
Some sheets in one ofthe bureaus--I can't re
Some sheets in one ofthe bureaus--I can't re-col
Some sheets in one ofthe bureaus--I can't re-colle
Some sheets in one ofthe bureaus--I can't re-collect
Some sheets in one ofthe bureaus--I can't re-collect w
Some sheets in one ofthe bureaus--I can't re-collect which
Some sheets in one ofthe bureaus--I can't re-collect which.
the bureaus--I can't re-collect which.
the bureaus--I can't re-collect which.Go o
the bureaus--I can't re-collect which.Go on.
>>
>> P
>> Per
>> Perhaps
>> Perhaps i
>> Perhaps it'
>> Perhaps it's
>> Perhaps it's like
>> Perhaps it's likea
>> Perhaps it's likea gh
>> Perhaps it's likea ghos
>> Perhaps it's likea ghost ho
>> Perhaps it's likea ghost hous
>> Perhaps it's likea ghost house.
Lo
Look
Look a
Look at it
Look at it t
Look at it thi
Look at it this
Look at it this way,
Look at it this way, M
Look at it this way, May
Look at it this way, Maybe
Look at it this way, Maybeth.
Look at it this way, Maybeth.It
Look at it this way, Maybeth.It's
Look at it this way, Maybeth.It's o
Look at it this way, Maybeth.It's only
Look at it this way, Maybeth.It's only fo
Look at it this way, Maybeth.It's only for
Look at it this way, Maybeth.It's only for on
Look at it this way, Maybeth.It's only for one ni
Look at it this way, Maybeth.It's only for one nigh
Look at it this way, Maybeth.It's only for one night.
♪
(d
(doo
(door
(door crea
(door creaki
(door creaking
(door creaking)
(b
(bir
(birds
(birds chi
(birds chirp
(birds chirpin
(birds chirping)
(d
(doo
(door
(door crea
(door creaki
(door creaking
(door creaking)
(win
(windo
(window
(window ra
(window rattli
(window rattling
(window rattling)
(l
(loc
(lock
(lock cl
(lock clicki
(lock clicking
(lock clicking)
(b
(bir
(birds
(birds c
(birds chirp
(birds chirpin
(birds chirping)
(b
(bli
(blind
(blind squ
(blind squea
(blind squeaki
(blind squeaking
(blind squeaking)
(bir
(birds
(birds c
(birds chi
(birds chirpin
(birds chirping)
(ins
(insec
(insects
(insects b
(insects buzzi
(insects buzzing
(insects buzzing)
(insects buzzing)>>
(insects buzzing)>> W
(insects buzzing)>> We
(insects buzzing)>> We can
(insects buzzing)>> We can do
(insects buzzing)>> We can do t
(insects buzzing)>> We can do tha
(insects buzzing)>> We can do that.
(insects buzzing)>> We can do that.>>
(insects buzzing)>> We can do that.>> A
(insects buzzing)>> We can do that.>> And s
(insects buzzing)>> We can do that.>> And so
(insects buzzing)>> We can do that.>> And so ca
(insects buzzing)>> We can do that.>> And so can
(insects buzzing)>> We can do that.>> And so can I.
>> We can do that.>> And so can I.
>> We can do that.>> And so can I.Th
>> We can do that.>> And so can I.They
>> We can do that.>> And so can I.They're
>> We can do that.>> And so can I.They're co
>> We can do that.>> And so can I.They're comi
>> We can do that.>> And so can I.They're coming
>> We can do that.>> And so can I.They're coming in
>> We can do that.>> And so can I.They're coming in to
>> We can do that.>> And so can I.They're coming in too
>> We can do that.>> And so can I.They're coming in too fa
>> We can do that.>> And so can I.They're coming in too fast.
>> And so can I.They're coming in too fast.
>> And so can I.They're coming in too fast.They
>> And so can I.They're coming in too fast.They a
>> And so can I.They're coming in too fast.They alw
>> And so can I.They're coming in too fast.They alway
>> And so can I.They're coming in too fast.They always do
They're coming in too fast.They always do
They're coming in too fast.They always doth
They're coming in too fast.They always dothis
They're coming in too fast.They always dothis t
They're coming in too fast.They always dothis tim
They're coming in too fast.They always dothis time of
They're coming in too fast.They always dothis time of y
They're coming in too fast.They always dothis time of yea
They're coming in too fast.They always dothis time of year.
They always dothis time of year.
They always dothis time of year.Go
They always dothis time of year.Got
They always dothis time of year.Got to
They always dothis time of year.Got to sta
They always dothis time of year.Got to start
They always dothis time of year.Got to start c
They always dothis time of year.Got to start can
They always dothis time of year.Got to start canning
They always dothis time of year.Got to start canning.
this time of year.Got to start canning.
this time of year.Got to start canning.Ca
this time of year.Got to start canning.Can
this time of year.Got to start canning.Can sh
this time of year.Got to start canning.Can she
this time of year.Got to start canning.Can she pick
this time of year.Got to start canning.Can she pick b
this time of year.Got to start canning.Can she pick bea
this time of year.Got to start canning.Can she pick beans
this time of year.Got to start canning.Can she pick beans?
Got to start canning.Can she pick beans?
Got to start canning.Can she pick beans?>>
Got to start canning.Can she pick beans?>> C
Got to start canning.Can she pick beans?>> Can
Got to start canning.Can she pick beans?>> Can you
Got to start canning.Can she pick beans?>> Can you?
Can she pick beans?>> Can you?
Can she pick beans?>> Can you?Su
Can she pick beans?>> Can you?Sure
Can she pick beans?>> Can you?Sure,
Can she pick beans?>> Can you?Sure, I
Can she pick beans?>> Can you?Sure, I gues
Can she pick beans?>> Can you?Sure, I guess
Can she pick beans?>> Can you?Sure, I guess so
Can she pick beans?>> Can you?Sure, I guess so.
>> Can you?Sure, I guess so.
>> Can you?Sure, I guess so.>>
>> Can you?Sure, I guess so.>> O
>> Can you?Sure, I guess so.>> Okay,
>> Can you?Sure, I guess so.>> Okay, o
>> Can you?Sure, I guess so.>> Okay, ove
>> Can you?Sure, I guess so.>> Okay, over
>> Can you?Sure, I guess so.>> Okay, over ther
>> Can you?Sure, I guess so.>> Okay, over there
>> Can you?Sure, I guess so.>> Okay, over there th
>> Can you?Sure, I guess so.>> Okay, over there then
>> Can you?Sure, I guess so.>> Okay, over there then.
Sure, I guess so.>> Okay, over there then.
Sure, I guess so.>> Okay, over there then.Uh..
Sure, I guess so.>> Okay, over there then.Uh...
>> Okay, over there then.Uh...
>> Okay, over there then.Uh...br
>> Okay, over there then.Uh...brin
>> Okay, over there then.Uh...bring
>> Okay, over there then.Uh...bring 'em
>> Okay, over there then.Uh...bring 'em ba
>> Okay, over there then.Uh...bring 'em back
>> Okay, over there then.Uh...bring 'em back h
>> Okay, over there then.Uh...bring 'em back here
>> Okay, over there then.Uh...bring 'em back here to
>> Okay, over there then.Uh...bring 'em back here to m
>> Okay, over there then.Uh...bring 'em back here to me.
Uh...bring 'em back here to me.
Uh...bring 'em back here to me.An
Uh...bring 'em back here to me.And
Uh...bring 'em back here to me.And ta
Uh...bring 'em back here to me.And take t
Uh...bring 'em back here to me.And take the
Uh...bring 'em back here to me.And take the b
Uh...bring 'em back here to me.And take the big
Uh...bring 'em back here to me.And take the biggest
Uh...bring 'em back here to me.And take the biggest.
Yo
You,
You, g
You, go
You, go into
You, go into t
You, go into the
You, go into the b
You, go into the barn.
You, go into the barn.Up
You, go into the barn.Up a
You, go into the barn.Up again
You, go into the barn.Up against
You, go into the barn.Up against t
You, go into the barn.Up against the
You, go into the barn.Up against the far
You, go into the barn.Up against the far w
You, go into the barn.Up against the far wal
You, go into the barn.Up against the far wall
You, go into the barn.Up against the far wallth
You, go into the barn.Up against the far wallther
You, go into the barn.Up against the far wallthere'
You, go into the barn.Up against the far wallthere's a
You, go into the barn.Up against the far wallthere's a bi
You, go into the barn.Up against the far wallthere's a bin
You, go into the barn.Up against the far wallthere's a bin of
You, go into the barn.Up against the far wallthere's a bin of pot
You, go into the barn.Up against the far wallthere's a bin of potat
You, go into the barn.Up against the far wallthere's a bin of potatoe
You, go into the barn.Up against the far wallthere's a bin of potatoes.
Up against the far wallthere's a bin of potatoes.
Up against the far wallthere's a bin of potatoes.Ge
Up against the far wallthere's a bin of potatoes.Get
Up against the far wallthere's a bin of potatoes.Get what
Up against the far wallthere's a bin of potatoes.Get what w
Up against the far wallthere's a bin of potatoes.Get what we
Up against the far wallthere's a bin of potatoes.Get what we ne
Up against the far wallthere's a bin of potatoes.Get what we need.
there's a bin of potatoes.Get what we need.
there's a bin of potatoes.Get what we need.An
there's a bin of potatoes.Get what we need.And
there's a bin of potatoes.Get what we need.And ke
there's a bin of potatoes.Get what we need.And keep y
there's a bin of potatoes.Get what we need.And keep you
there's a bin of potatoes.Get what we need.And keep your
there's a bin of potatoes.Get what we need.And keep your sh
there's a bin of potatoes.Get what we need.And keep your shoes
there's a bin of potatoes.Get what we need.And keep your shoes on
there's a bin of potatoes.Get what we need.And keep your shoes on.
Get what we need.And keep your shoes on.
Get what we need.And keep your shoes on.I
Get what we need.And keep your shoes on.I do
Get what we need.And keep your shoes on.I don'
Get what we need.And keep your shoes on.I don't kn
Get what we need.And keep your shoes on.I don't know
Get what we need.And keep your shoes on.I don't know w
Get what we need.And keep your shoes on.I don't know wha
Get what we need.And keep your shoes on.I don't know what al
Get what we need.And keep your shoes on.I don't know what all
And keep your shoes on.I don't know what all
And keep your shoes on.I don't know what allis
And keep your shoes on.I don't know what allis o
And keep your shoes on.I don't know what allis on
And keep your shoes on.I don't know what allis on that
And keep your shoes on.I don't know what allis on that f
And keep your shoes on.I don't know what allis on that flo
And keep your shoes on.I don't know what allis on that floor
And keep your shoes on.I don't know what allis on that floor.
♪
♪>>
♪>> O
♪>> Oh, m
♪>> Oh, man
♪>> Oh, man,
♪>> Oh, man, ho
♪>> Oh, man, how do
♪>> Oh, man, how do w
♪>> Oh, man, how do we
♪>> Oh, man, how do we ge
♪>> Oh, man, how do we get 'e
♪>> Oh, man, how do we get 'em
♪>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emou
♪>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emout
♪>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emout of
♪>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emout of the
♪>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emout of there
♪>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emout of there?
>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emout of there?
>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emout of there?>> T
>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emout of there?>> Thi
>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emout of there?>> Think
>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emout of there?>> Think t
>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emout of there?>> Think they
>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emout of there?>> Think they bi
>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emout of there?>> Think they bite
>> Oh, man, how do we get 'emout of there?>> Think they bite?
out of there?>> Think they bite?
out of there?>> Think they bite?>> H
out of there?>> Think they bite?>> Her
out of there?>> Think they bite?>> Here
out of there?>> Think they bite?>> Here th
out of there?>> Think they bite?>> Here they c
out of there?>> Think they bite?>> Here they com
out of there?>> Think they bite?>> Here they come.
>> Think they bite?>> Here they come.
>> Think they bite?>> Here they come.Lo
>> Think they bite?>> Here they come.Look
>> Think they bite?>> Here they come.Look o
>> Think they bite?>> Here they come.Look out,
>> Think they bite?>> Here they come.Look out, th
>> Think they bite?>> Here they come.Look out, they
>> Think they bite?>> Here they come.Look out, they'r
>> Think they bite?>> Here they come.Look out, they're go
>> Think they bite?>> Here they come.Look out, they're gonn
>> Think they bite?>> Here they come.Look out, they're gonna
>> Here they come.Look out, they're gonna
>> Here they come.Look out, they're gonnabi
>> Here they come.Look out, they're gonnabite
>> Here they come.Look out, they're gonnabite y
>> Here they come.Look out, they're gonnabite you!
Look out, they're gonnabite you!
Look out, they're gonnabite you!>>
Look out, they're gonnabite you!>> G
Look out, they're gonnabite you!>> Get o
Look out, they're gonnabite you!>> Get out
Look out, they're gonnabite you!>> Get out o
Look out, they're gonnabite you!>> Get out of
Look out, they're gonnabite you!>> Get out of the
Look out, they're gonnabite you!>> Get out of the wa
Look out, they're gonnabite you!>> Get out of the way!
bite you!>> Get out of the way!
bite you!>> Get out of the way!Lo
bite you!>> Get out of the way!Look
bite you!>> Get out of the way!Look at
bite you!>> Get out of the way!Look at 'e
bite you!>> Get out of the way!Look at 'em
bite you!>> Get out of the way!Look at 'em go
bite you!>> Get out of the way!Look at 'em go!
>> Get out of the way!Look at 'em go!
>> Get out of the way!Look at 'em go!(l
>> Get out of the way!Look at 'em go!(lat
>> Get out of the way!Look at 'em go!(latch t
>> Get out of the way!Look at 'em go!(latch thu
>> Get out of the way!Look at 'em go!(latch thuds
>> Get out of the way!Look at 'em go!(latch thuds)
Look at 'em go!(latch thuds)
Look at 'em go!(latch thuds)(d
Look at 'em go!(latch thuds)(doo
Look at 'em go!(latch thuds)(door cr
Look at 'em go!(latch thuds)(door crea
Look at 'em go!(latch thuds)(door creaki
Look at 'em go!(latch thuds)(door creaking
Look at 'em go!(latch thuds)(door creaking)
(w
(wat
(water
(water s
(water splas
(water splashi
(water splashing
(water splashing)
(doo
(door
(door cr
(door crea
(door creaking
(door creaking)
>>
>> T
>> Tak
>> Take th
>> Take thos
>> Take those
>> Take those to
>> Take those to the
>> Take those to the s
>> Take those to the sin
>> Take those to the sink.
>> Take those to the sink.Do
>> Take those to the sink.Don'
>> Take those to the sink.Don't
>> Take those to the sink.Don't yo
>> Take those to the sink.Don't you kn
>> Take those to the sink.Don't you know
>> Take those to the sink.Don't you know p
>> Take those to the sink.Don't you know pot
>> Take those to the sink.Don't you know potatoe
>> Take those to the sink.Don't you know potatoes
>> Take those to the sink.Don't you know potatoesha
>> Take those to the sink.Don't you know potatoeshave
>> Take those to the sink.Don't you know potatoeshave t
>> Take those to the sink.Don't you know potatoeshave to be
>> Take those to the sink.Don't you know potatoeshave to be s
>> Take those to the sink.Don't you know potatoeshave to be scr
>> Take those to the sink.Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrub
>> Take those to the sink.Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?
Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?
Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?Ca
Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?Can
Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?Can sh
Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?Can she ta
Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?Can she take
Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?Can she take t
Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?Can she take the
Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?Can she take the end
Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?Can she take the ends
Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?Can she take the ends of
Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?Can she take the ends off
Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?Can she take the ends off bean
Don't you know potatoeshave to be scrubbed?Can she take the ends off beans?
have to be scrubbed?Can she take the ends off beans?
have to be scrubbed?Can she take the ends off beans?>>
have to be scrubbed?Can she take the ends off beans?>> S
have to be scrubbed?Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sur
have to be scrubbed?Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sure.
Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sure.
Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sure.Th
Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sure.Ther
Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sure.There'
Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sure.There's a
Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sure.There's a bo
Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sure.There's a boat
Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sure.There's a boat i
Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sure.There's a boat in th
Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sure.There's a boat in the
Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sure.There's a boat in the ba
Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sure.There's a boat in the barn
Can she take the ends off beans?>> Sure.There's a boat in the barn.
>> Sure.There's a boat in the barn.
>> Sure.There's a boat in the barn.>>
>> Sure.There's a boat in the barn.>> I
>> Sure.There's a boat in the barn.>> I k
>> Sure.There's a boat in the barn.>> I know
>> Sure.There's a boat in the barn.>> I know th
>> Sure.There's a boat in the barn.>> I know that
>> Sure.There's a boat in the barn.>> I know that.
There's a boat in the barn.>> I know that.
There's a boat in the barn.>> I know that.Be
There's a boat in the barn.>> I know that.Been
There's a boat in the barn.>> I know that.Been the
There's a boat in the barn.>> I know that.Been there
There's a boat in the barn.>> I know that.Been there f
There's a boat in the barn.>> I know that.Been there for
There's a boat in the barn.>> I know that.Been there for yea
There's a boat in the barn.>> I know that.Been there for years
There's a boat in the barn.>> I know that.Been there for years.
>> I know that.Been there for years.
>> I know that.Been there for years.>>
>> I know that.Been there for years.>> W
>> I know that.Been there for years.>> Who
>> I know that.Been there for years.>> Whose
>> I know that.Been there for years.>> Whose boa
>> I know that.Been there for years.>> Whose boat
>> I know that.Been there for years.>> Whose boat is
>> I know that.Been there for years.>> Whose boat is i
>> I know that.Been there for years.>> Whose boat is it?
Been there for years.>> Whose boat is it?
Been there for years.>> Whose boat is it?>>
Been there for years.>> Whose boat is it?>> M
Been there for years.>> Whose boat is it?>> Min
Been there for years.>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.
>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.
>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.>>
>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.>> W
>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.>> Well,
>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.>> Well, I
>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.>> Well, I k
>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.>> Well, I kno
>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.>> Well, I know th
>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.>> Well, I know that
>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.>> Well, I know that,
>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.>> Well, I know that, bu
>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.>> Well, I know that, but wh
>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.>> Well, I know that, but whos
>> Whose boat is it?>> Mine.>> Well, I know that, but whose?
>>
>> O
>> One
>> One of
>> One of my
>> One of my b
>> One of my boy
>> One of my boys bu
>> One of my boys buil
>> One of my boys built
>> One of my boys built it
>> One of my boys built it.
>> One of my boys built it.Bu
>> One of my boys built it.Buil
>> One of my boys built it.Built it
>> One of my boys built it.Built it a
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and h
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sa
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sail
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sailed
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sailed i
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sailed it.
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sailed it.>>
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sailed it.>> W
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sailed it.>> Whe
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sailed it.>> Where a
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are t
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are the
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are the sai
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are the sails
>> One of my boys built it.Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are the sails?
Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are the sails?
Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are the sails?Wi
Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are the sails?Will
Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are the sails?Will i
Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are the sails?Will it
Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are the sails?Will it stil
Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are the sails?Will it still
Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are the sails?Will it still fl
Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are the sails?Will it still floa
Built it and he sailed it.>> Where are the sails?Will it still float?
>> Where are the sails?Will it still float?
>> Where are the sails?Will it still float?>> I
>> Where are the sails?Will it still float?>> I d
>> Where are the sails?Will it still float?>> I don
>> Where are the sails?Will it still float?>> I don't
>> Where are the sails?Will it still float?>> I don't kno
>> Where are the sails?Will it still float?>> I don't know
>> Where are the sails?Will it still float?>> I don't know if
>> Where are the sails?Will it still float?>> I don't know if i
>> Where are the sails?Will it still float?>> I don't know if it's
Will it still float?>> I don't know if it's
Will it still float?>> I don't know if it'sst
Will it still float?>> I don't know if it'sstil
Will it still float?>> I don't know if it'sstill
Will it still float?>> I don't know if it'sstill se
Will it still float?>> I don't know if it'sstill seawor
Will it still float?>> I don't know if it'sstill seaworth
Will it still float?>> I don't know if it'sstill seaworthy.
>> I don't know if it'sstill seaworthy.
>> I don't know if it'sstill seaworthy.It
>> I don't know if it'sstill seaworthy.It's
>> I don't know if it'sstill seaworthy.It's n
>> I don't know if it'sstill seaworthy.It's no
>> I don't know if it'sstill seaworthy.It's no conc
>> I don't know if it'sstill seaworthy.It's no concer
>> I don't know if it'sstill seaworthy.It's no concern
>> I don't know if it'sstill seaworthy.It's no concern of
>> I don't know if it'sstill seaworthy.It's no concern of you
>> I don't know if it'sstill seaworthy.It's no concern of yours
>> I don't know if it'sstill seaworthy.It's no concern of yours.
I
I ca
I can
I can hear
I can hear w
I can hear wha
I can hear what
I can hear what you'
I can hear what you're
I can hear what you're t
I can hear what you're thi
I can hear what you're thinkin
I can hear what you're thinking.
I can hear what you're thinking.>>
I can hear what you're thinking.>> M
I can hear what you're thinking.>> May
I can hear what you're thinking.>> Maybe y
I can hear what you're thinking.>> Maybe you
I can hear what you're thinking.>> Maybe you c
I can hear what you're thinking.>> Maybe you can
I can hear what you're thinking.>> Maybe you can.
>>
>> Y
>> You
>> You s
>> You shoul
>> You should'
>> You should've
>> You should've s
>> You should've seen
>> You should've seen 'e
>> You should've seen 'em!
>> You should've seen 'em!Th
>> You should've seen 'em!They
>> You should've seen 'em!They l
>> You should've seen 'em!They loo
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at t
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at the
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at the doo
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at the door,
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at the door,th
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at the door,then
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at the door,then t
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at the door,then they
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at the door,then they lo
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at the door,then they look
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at the door,then they looked
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at the door,then they looked at
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at the door,then they looked at us
>> You should've seen 'em!They looked at the door,then they looked at us,
They looked at the door,then they looked at us,
They looked at the door,then they looked at us,th
They looked at the door,then they looked at us,then
They looked at the door,then they looked at us,then g
They looked at the door,then they looked at us,then gone!
then they looked at us,then gone!
then they looked at us,then gone!I
then they looked at us,then gone!I di
then they looked at us,then gone!I didn
then they looked at us,then gone!I didn't
then they looked at us,then gone!I didn't kno
then they looked at us,then gone!I didn't know
then they looked at us,then gone!I didn't know th
then they looked at us,then gone!I didn't know thin
then they looked at us,then gone!I didn't know things c
then they looked at us,then gone!I didn't know things cou
then they looked at us,then gone!I didn't know things could
then they looked at us,then gone!I didn't know things could g
then they looked at us,then gone!I didn't know things could go
then gone!I didn't know things could go
then gone!I didn't know things could goside
then gone!I didn't know things could gosidewa
then gone!I didn't know things could gosideways
then gone!I didn't know things could gosideways s
then gone!I didn't know things could gosideways so fa
then gone!I didn't know things could gosideways so fast
then gone!I didn't know things could gosideways so fast.
I didn't know things could gosideways so fast.
I didn't know things could gosideways so fast.Boy,
I didn't know things could gosideways so fast.Boy, a
I didn't know things could gosideways so fast.Boy, are
I didn't know things could gosideways so fast.Boy, are t
I didn't know things could gosideways so fast.Boy, are they
I didn't know things could gosideways so fast.Boy, are they sm
I didn't know things could gosideways so fast.Boy, are they smar
I didn't know things could gosideways so fast.Boy, are they smart.
sideways so fast.Boy, are they smart.
sideways so fast.Boy, are they smart.>>
sideways so fast.Boy, are they smart.>> W
sideways so fast.Boy, are they smart.>> We cl
sideways so fast.Boy, are they smart.>> We clos
sideways so fast.Boy, are they smart.>> We closed
sideways so fast.Boy, are they smart.>> We closed t
sideways so fast.Boy, are they smart.>> We closed the d
sideways so fast.Boy, are they smart.>> We closed the doo
sideways so fast.Boy, are they smart.>> We closed the doors
Boy, are they smart.>> We closed the doors
Boy, are they smart.>> We closed the doorsan
Boy, are they smart.>> We closed the doorsand
Boy, are they smart.>> We closed the doorsand set
Boy, are they smart.>> We closed the doorsand set th
Boy, are they smart.>> We closed the doorsand set the
Boy, are they smart.>> We closed the doorsand set the tr
Boy, are they smart.>> We closed the doorsand set the traps
Boy, are they smart.>> We closed the doorsand set the traps ba
Boy, are they smart.>> We closed the doorsand set the traps back
>> We closed the doorsand set the traps back
>> We closed the doorsand set the traps backwh
>> We closed the doorsand set the traps backwher
>> We closed the doorsand set the traps backwhere th
>> We closed the doorsand set the traps backwhere they
>> We closed the doorsand set the traps backwhere they w
>> We closed the doorsand set the traps backwhere they wer
>> We closed the doorsand set the traps backwhere they were.
and set the traps backwhere they were.
and set the traps backwhere they were.Is t
and set the traps backwhere they were.Is tha
and set the traps backwhere they were.Is that
and set the traps backwhere they were.Is that ri
and set the traps backwhere they were.Is that right?
where they were.Is that right?
where they were.Is that right?>>
where they were.Is that right?>> R
where they were.Is that right?>> Rig
where they were.Is that right?>> Right
where they were.Is that right?>> Right eno
where they were.Is that right?>> Right enoug
where they were.Is that right?>> Right enough.
Is that right?>> Right enough.
Is that right?>> Right enough.What
Is that right?>> Right enough.What d
Is that right?>> Right enough.What did
Is that right?>> Right enough.What did y
Is that right?>> Right enough.What did you u
Is that right?>> Right enough.What did you use
Is that right?>> Right enough.What did you use f
Is that right?>> Right enough.What did you use for
Is that right?>> Right enough.What did you use for bai
Is that right?>> Right enough.What did you use for bait?
>> Right enough.What did you use for bait?
>> Right enough.What did you use for bait?>>
>> Right enough.What did you use for bait?>> W
>> Right enough.What did you use for bait?>> What
>> Right enough.What did you use for bait?>> What sh
>> Right enough.What did you use for bait?>> What shou
>> Right enough.What did you use for bait?>> What should
>> Right enough.What did you use for bait?>> What should we
>> Right enough.What did you use for bait?>> What should we us
>> Right enough.What did you use for bait?>> What should we use?
What did you use for bait?>> What should we use?
What did you use for bait?>> What should we use?>>
What did you use for bait?>> What should we use?>> F
What did you use for bait?>> What should we use?>> Fis
What did you use for bait?>> What should we use?>> Fish.
>> What should we use?>> Fish.
>> What should we use?>> Fish.Go
>> What should we use?>> Fish.Gott
>> What should we use?>> Fish.Gotta
>> What should we use?>> Fish.Gotta catc
>> What should we use?>> Fish.Gotta catch
>> What should we use?>> Fish.Gotta catch th
>> What should we use?>> Fish.Gotta catch the
>> What should we use?>> Fish.Gotta catch the fish
>> What should we use?>> Fish.Gotta catch the fish.
>> Fish.Gotta catch the fish.
>> Fish.Gotta catch the fish.>>
>> Fish.Gotta catch the fish.>> G
>> Fish.Gotta catch the fish.>> Goo
>> Fish.Gotta catch the fish.>> Good-oh
>> Fish.Gotta catch the fish.>> Good-oh!
Gotta catch the fish.>> Good-oh!
Gotta catch the fish.>> Good-oh!Ca
Gotta catch the fish.>> Good-oh!Can
Gotta catch the fish.>> Good-oh!Can I go
Gotta catch the fish.>> Good-oh!Can I go d
Gotta catch the fish.>> Good-oh!Can I go dow
Gotta catch the fish.>> Good-oh!Can I go down
Gotta catch the fish.>> Good-oh!Can I go down afte
Gotta catch the fish.>> Good-oh!Can I go down after
Gotta catch the fish.>> Good-oh!Can I go down after di
Gotta catch the fish.>> Good-oh!Can I go down after dinn
Gotta catch the fish.>> Good-oh!Can I go down after dinner?
>> Good-oh!Can I go down after dinner?
>> Good-oh!Can I go down after dinner?Do
>> Good-oh!Can I go down after dinner?Do y
>> Good-oh!Can I go down after dinner?Do you h
>> Good-oh!Can I go down after dinner?Do you hav
>> Good-oh!Can I go down after dinner?Do you have
>> Good-oh!Can I go down after dinner?Do you have an
>> Good-oh!Can I go down after dinner?Do you have any li
>> Good-oh!Can I go down after dinner?Do you have any line
>> Good-oh!Can I go down after dinner?Do you have any line?
>>
>> T
>> The
>> There's
>> There's n
>> There's no
>> There's no po
>> There's no point
>> There's no point to
>> There's no point to i
>> There's no point to it.
>> There's no point to it.>>
>> There's no point to it.>> S
>> There's no point to it.>> So
>> There's no point to it.>> So wh
>> There's no point to it.>> So what?
>> There's no point to it.>> So what?I'
>> There's no point to it.>> So what?I'll
>> There's no point to it.>> So what?I'll go
>> There's no point to it.>> So what?I'll go wi
>> There's no point to it.>> So what?I'll go with
>> There's no point to it.>> So what?I'll go with y
>> There's no point to it.>> So what?I'll go with you,
>> There's no point to it.>> So what?I'll go with you, Sa
>> There's no point to it.>> So what?I'll go with you, Samm
>> There's no point to it.>> So what?I'll go with you, Sammy.
>> So what?I'll go with you, Sammy.
>> So what?I'll go with you, Sammy.(s
>> So what?I'll go with you, Sammy.(set
>> So what?I'll go with you, Sammy.(sets
>> So what?I'll go with you, Sammy.(sets knif
>> So what?I'll go with you, Sammy.(sets knife
>> So what?I'll go with you, Sammy.(sets knife do
>> So what?I'll go with you, Sammy.(sets knife down
>> So what?I'll go with you, Sammy.(sets knife down)
(b
(buc
(bucket
(bucket ra
(bucket ratt
(bucket rattli
(bucket rattling)
(bucket rattling)(l
(bucket rattling)(lou
(bucket rattling)(loud cl
(bucket rattling)(loud clan
(bucket rattling)(loud clanki
(bucket rattling)(loud clanking
(bucket rattling)(loud clanking, sp
(bucket rattling)(loud clanking, spla
(bucket rattling)(loud clanking, splash
(bucket rattling)(loud clanking, splashin
(bucket rattling)(loud clanking, splashing)
(c
(cra
(crabs
(crabs cla
(crabs clatt
(crabs clatter
(crabs clatterin
(crabs clattering in
(crabs clattering in p
(crabs clattering in pot
(crabs clattering in pot)
(c
(cra
(crab cl
(crab clan
(crab clanki
(crab clanking
(crab clanking on
(crab clanking on pl
(crab clanking on plat
(crab clanking on plate)
(crab clanking on plate)(she
(crab clanking on plate)(shell
(crab clanking on plate)(shells
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cr
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracki
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking t
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking thr
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking through
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking throughou
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking throughout)
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking throughout)>>
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking throughout)>> S
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking throughout)>> So wh
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking throughout)>> So wher
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking throughout)>> So where
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking throughout)>> So where is
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking throughout)>> So where is you
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking throughout)>> So where is your
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking throughout)>> So where is your mo
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking throughout)>> So where is your moth
(crab clanking on plate)(shells cracking throughout)>> So where is your mother?
(shells cracking throughout)>> So where is your mother?
(shells cracking throughout)>> So where is your mother?>> W
(shells cracking throughout)>> So where is your mother?>> We
(shells cracking throughout)>> So where is your mother?>> We do
(shells cracking throughout)>> So where is your mother?>> We don'
(shells cracking throughout)>> So where is your mother?>> We don't kn
(shells cracking throughout)>> So where is your mother?>> We don't know
(shells cracking throughout)>> So where is your mother?>> We don't know.
>> So where is your mother?>> We don't know.
>> So where is your mother?>> We don't know.>>
>> So where is your mother?>> We don't know.>> P
>> So where is your mother?>> We don't know.>> Pol
>> So where is your mother?>> We don't know.>> Police
>> So where is your mother?>> We don't know.>> Police ca
>> So where is your mother?>> We don't know.>> Police can'
>> So where is your mother?>> We don't know.>> Police can't
>> So where is your mother?>> We don't know.>> Police can't find
>> So where is your mother?>> We don't know.>> Police can't find h
>> So where is your mother?>> We don't know.>> Police can't find her
>> So where is your mother?>> We don't know.>> Police can't find her?
>> We don't know.>> Police can't find her?
>> We don't know.>> Police can't find her?>>
>> We don't know.>> Police can't find her?>> N
>> We don't know.>> Police can't find her?>> Not
>> We don't know.>> Police can't find her?>> Not yet
>> We don't know.>> Police can't find her?>> Not yet.
>> Police can't find her?>> Not yet.
>> Police can't find her?>> Not yet.>>
>> Police can't find her?>> Not yet.>> S
>> Police can't find her?>> Not yet.>> So
>> Police can't find her?>> Not yet.>> So you
>> Police can't find her?>> Not yet.>> So you ru
>> Police can't find her?>> Not yet.>> So you run
>> Police can't find her?>> Not yet.>> So you run of
>> Police can't find her?>> Not yet.>> So you run off fr
>> Police can't find her?>> Not yet.>> So you run off from
>> Not yet.>> So you run off from
>> Not yet.>> So you run off fromso
>> Not yet.>> So you run off fromsome
>> Not yet.>> So you run off fromsomebo
>> Not yet.>> So you run off fromsomebody t
>> Not yet.>> So you run off fromsomebody tha
>> Not yet.>> So you run off fromsomebody that
>> Not yet.>> So you run off fromsomebody that wa
>> Not yet.>> So you run off fromsomebody that was tr
>> Not yet.>> So you run off fromsomebody that was tryi
>> Not yet.>> So you run off fromsomebody that was trying
>> Not yet.>> So you run off fromsomebody that was trying t
>> Not yet.>> So you run off fromsomebody that was trying to
>> So you run off fromsomebody that was trying to
>> So you run off fromsomebody that was trying tohe
>> So you run off fromsomebody that was trying tohelp
>> So you run off fromsomebody that was trying tohelp you
>> So you run off fromsomebody that was trying tohelp you.
somebody that was trying tohelp you.
somebody that was trying tohelp you.Wh
somebody that was trying tohelp you.Why'
somebody that was trying tohelp you.Why'd
somebody that was trying tohelp you.Why'd yo
somebody that was trying tohelp you.Why'd you do
somebody that was trying tohelp you.Why'd you do t
somebody that was trying tohelp you.Why'd you do tha
somebody that was trying tohelp you.Why'd you do that?
help you.Why'd you do that?
help you.Why'd you do that?>>
help you.Why'd you do that?>> I
help you.Why'd you do that?>> It
help you.Why'd you do that?>> It wa
help you.Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't
help you.Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't r
help you.Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't rig
help you.Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right
help you.Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for
help you.Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for u
help you.Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us
help you.Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us th
help you.Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us there.
Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us there.
Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us there.>>
Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us there.>> Y
Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You t
Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You thi
Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think
Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think o
Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other
Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other p
Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other peo
Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other peopl
Why'd you do that?>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other people
>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other people
>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other peoplehave
>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other peoplehave t
>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other peoplehave to
>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other peoplehave to ju
>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other peoplehave to just j
>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other peoplehave to just jum
>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other peoplehave to just jump
>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other peoplehave to just jump up
>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other peoplehave to just jump up and
>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other peoplehave to just jump up and d
>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other peoplehave to just jump up and dow
>> It wasn't right for us there.>> You think other peoplehave to just jump up and down
>> You think other peoplehave to just jump up and down
>> You think other peoplehave to just jump up and down'c
>> You think other peoplehave to just jump up and down'cau
>> You think other peoplehave to just jump up and down'cause
>> You think other peoplehave to just jump up and down'cause you
>> You think other peoplehave to just jump up and down'cause you s
>> You think other peoplehave to just jump up and down'cause you say
>> You think other peoplehave to just jump up and down'cause you say s
>> You think other peoplehave to just jump up and down'cause you say so?
have to just jump up and down'cause you say so?
have to just jump up and down'cause you say so?(s
have to just jump up and down'cause you say so?(sig
have to just jump up and down'cause you say so?(sighi
have to just jump up and down'cause you say so?(sighing)
'cause you say so?(sighing)
'cause you say so?(sighing)Wh
'cause you say so?(sighing)What
'cause you say so?(sighing)What a
'cause you say so?(sighing)What about
'cause you say so?(sighing)What about y
'cause you say so?(sighing)What about you
'cause you say so?(sighing)What about your
'cause you say so?(sighing)What about your fath
'cause you say so?(sighing)What about your father
'cause you say so?(sighing)What about your father?
(sighing)What about your father?
(sighing)What about your father?He
(sighing)What about your father?He r
(sighing)What about your father?He run a
(sighing)What about your father?He run awa
(sighing)What about your father?He run away,
(sighing)What about your father?He run away, t
(sighing)What about your father?He run away, too?
>>
>> Y
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah.Righ
>> Yeah.Right
>> Yeah.Right af
>> Yeah.Right afte
>> Yeah.Right after Sa
>> Yeah.Right after Samm
>> Yeah.Right after Sammy
>> Yeah.Right after Sammy wa
>> Yeah.Right after Sammy was bo
>> Yeah.Right after Sammy was born
>> Yeah.Right after Sammy was born.
>>
>> S
>> She
>> She sho
>> She shoul
>> She should'
>> She should've
>> She should've com
>> She should've come
>> She should've come ba
>> She should've come back
>> She should've come back her
>> She should've come back here
>> She should've come back herewh
>> She should've come back herewhen
>> She should've come back herewhen he
>> She should've come back herewhen he ru
>> She should've come back herewhen he run
>> She should've come back herewhen he run ou
>> She should've come back herewhen he run out on
>> She should've come back herewhen he run out on h
>> She should've come back herewhen he run out on her
>> She should've come back herewhen he run out on her.
>> She should've come back herewhen he run out on her.>> S
>> She should've come back herewhen he run out on her.>> She
>> She should've come back herewhen he run out on her.>> She d
>> She should've come back herewhen he run out on her.>> She did
>> She should've come back herewhen he run out on her.>> She didn't
>> She should've come back herewhen he run out on her.>> She didn't wa
>> She should've come back herewhen he run out on her.>> She didn't want
>> She should've come back herewhen he run out on her.>> She didn't want t
>> She should've come back herewhen he run out on her.>> She didn't want to.
when he run out on her.>> She didn't want to.
when he run out on her.>> She didn't want to.>>
when he run out on her.>> She didn't want to.>> H
when he run out on her.>> She didn't want to.>> How
when he run out on her.>> She didn't want to.>> How d
when he run out on her.>> She didn't want to.>> How do yo
when he run out on her.>> She didn't want to.>> How do you
when he run out on her.>> She didn't want to.>> How do you kn
when he run out on her.>> She didn't want to.>> How do you know
when he run out on her.>> She didn't want to.>> How do you know?
>> She didn't want to.>> How do you know?
>> She didn't want to.>> How do you know?>>
>> She didn't want to.>> How do you know?>> I
>> She didn't want to.>> How do you know?>> I can
>> She didn't want to.>> How do you know?>> I can't
>> She didn't want to.>> How do you know?>> I can't r
>> She didn't want to.>> How do you know?>> I can't rem
>> She didn't want to.>> How do you know?>> I can't remembe
>> She didn't want to.>> How do you know?>> I can't remember,
>> How do you know?>> I can't remember,
>> How do you know?>> I can't remember,but
>> How do you know?>> I can't remember,but it
>> How do you know?>> I can't remember,but it m
>> How do you know?>> I can't remember,but it mad
>> How do you know?>> I can't remember,but it made he
>> How do you know?>> I can't remember,but it made her
>> How do you know?>> I can't remember,but it made her cr
>> How do you know?>> I can't remember,but it made her cry.
(s
(sig
(sighi
(sighing
(sighing)
(sighing)>>
(sighing)>> W
(sighing)>> Wha
(sighing)>> What's
(sighing)>> What's it
(sighing)>> What's it m
(sighing)>> What's it mat
(sighing)>> What's it matter
(sighing)>> What's it matter an
(sighing)>> What's it matter anyw
(sighing)>> What's it matter anyway
(sighing)>> What's it matter anyway?
(sighing)>> What's it matter anyway?>>
(sighing)>> What's it matter anyway?>> M
(sighing)>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mam
(sighing)>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama
(sighing)>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matt
(sighing)>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matter
(sighing)>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters
(sighing)>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to
(sighing)>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.
>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.
>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.>>
>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.>> S
>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.>> She
>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.>> She w
>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.>> She went
>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.>> She went of
>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off
>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off an
>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and le
>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left
>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left y
>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you
>> What's it matter anyway?>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you.
>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you.
>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you.>>
>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you.>> S
>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you.>> She
>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you.>> She w
>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you.>> She wante
>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted
>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to
>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to c
>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come
>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come ba
>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come back
>> Mama matters to me.>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come back.
>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come back.
>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come back.>>
>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come back.>> H
>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come back.>> How
>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come back.>> How do
>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come back.>> How do yo
>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you
>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you kn
>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you know t
>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you know tha
>> She went off and left you.>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you know that?
>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you know that?
>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you know that?>>
>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you know that?>> '
>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you know that?>> 'Caus
>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause
>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause sh
>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause she
>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause she love
>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause she loved
>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause she loved me
>> She wanted to come back.>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause she loved me.
>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause she loved me.
>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause she loved me.Di
>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause she loved me.Didn
>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause she loved me.Didn't s
>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause she loved me.Didn't she
>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause she loved me.Didn't she,
>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause she loved me.Didn't she, Di
>> How do you know that?>> 'Cause she loved me.Didn't she, Dicey?
>> 'Cause she loved me.Didn't she, Dicey?
>> 'Cause she loved me.Didn't she, Dicey?>>
>> 'Cause she loved me.Didn't she, Dicey?>> Y
>> 'Cause she loved me.Didn't she, Dicey?>> Yes
>> 'Cause she loved me.Didn't she, Dicey?>> Yes, sh
>> 'Cause she loved me.Didn't she, Dicey?>> Yes, she
>> 'Cause she loved me.Didn't she, Dicey?>> Yes, she di
>> 'Cause she loved me.Didn't she, Dicey?>> Yes, she did.
Didn't she, Dicey?>> Yes, she did.
Didn't she, Dicey?>> Yes, she did.Sh
Didn't she, Dicey?>> Yes, she did.She
Didn't she, Dicey?>> Yes, she did.She love
Didn't she, Dicey?>> Yes, she did.She loved
Didn't she, Dicey?>> Yes, she did.She loved us
Didn't she, Dicey?>> Yes, she did.She loved us a
Didn't she, Dicey?>> Yes, she did.She loved us all.
>> Yes, she did.She loved us all.
>> Yes, she did.She loved us all.>>
>> Yes, she did.She loved us all.>> H
>> Yes, she did.She loved us all.>> Hm.
She loved us all.>> Hm.
She loved us all.>> Hm.♪
(chi
(child
(childre
(children
(children play
(children playin
(children playing)
(children playing)(r
(children playing)(roc
(children playing)(rocks
(children playing)(rocks ski
(children playing)(rocks skipp
(children playing)(rocks skippin
(children playing)(rocks skipping,
(children playing)(rocks skipping, spl
(children playing)(rocks skipping, splas
(children playing)(rocks skipping, splashi
(children playing)(rocks skipping, splashing
(children playing)(rocks skipping, splashing)
(children playing)(rocks skipping, splashing)(b
(children playing)(rocks skipping, splashing)(bir
(children playing)(rocks skipping, splashing)(bird
(children playing)(rocks skipping, splashing)(bird ch
(children playing)(rocks skipping, splashing)(bird chirpi
(children playing)(rocks skipping, splashing)(bird chirping
(children playing)(rocks skipping, splashing)(bird chirping)
(rocks skipping, splashing)(bird chirping)
(rocks skipping, splashing)(bird chirping)(ind
(rocks skipping, splashing)(bird chirping)(indis
(rocks skipping, splashing)(bird chirping)(indisti
(rocks skipping, splashing)(bird chirping)(indistinc
(rocks skipping, splashing)(bird chirping)(indistinct ch
(rocks skipping, splashing)(bird chirping)(indistinct chat
(rocks skipping, splashing)(bird chirping)(indistinct chatte
(rocks skipping, splashing)(bird chirping)(indistinct chatter)
>>
>> G
>> Goo
>> Good
>> Good nigh
>> Good night.
>> Good night.>>
>> Good night.>> G
>> Good night.>> Goo
>> Good night.>> Good ni
>> Good night.>> Good nigh
>> Good night.>> Good night.
>> Good night.>> Good night.>>
>> Good night.>> Good night.>> G
>> Good night.>> Good night.>> Goo
>> Good night.>> Good night.>> Good ni
>> Good night.>> Good night.>> Good nigh
>> Good night.>> Good night.>> Good night.
>>
>> W
>> Wha
>> What
>> What are
>> What are we
>> What are we g
>> What are we gon
>> What are we gonna
>> What are we gonnado
>> What are we gonnado t
>> What are we gonnado tom
>> What are we gonnado tomorro
>> What are we gonnado tomorrow?
>> What are we gonnado tomorrow?>> S
>> What are we gonnado tomorrow?>> She
>> What are we gonnado tomorrow?>> She d
>> What are we gonnado tomorrow?>> She doe
>> What are we gonnado tomorrow?>> She doesn't
>> What are we gonnado tomorrow?>> She doesn't w
>> What are we gonnado tomorrow?>> She doesn't wan
>> What are we gonnado tomorrow?>> She doesn't want
>> What are we gonnado tomorrow?>> She doesn't want us t
>> What are we gonnado tomorrow?>> She doesn't want us to
>> What are we gonnado tomorrow?>> She doesn't want us to st
>> What are we gonnado tomorrow?>> She doesn't want us to stay
>> What are we gonnado tomorrow?>> She doesn't want us to stay.
do tomorrow?>> She doesn't want us to stay.
do tomorrow?>> She doesn't want us to stay.Sh
do tomorrow?>> She doesn't want us to stay.She
do tomorrow?>> She doesn't want us to stay.She said
do tomorrow?>> She doesn't want us to stay.She said s
do tomorrow?>> She doesn't want us to stay.She said so.
>> She doesn't want us to stay.She said so.
>> She doesn't want us to stay.She said so.>>
>> She doesn't want us to stay.She said so.>> W
>> She doesn't want us to stay.She said so.>> Wel
>> She doesn't want us to stay.She said so.>> Well, n
>> She doesn't want us to stay.She said so.>> Well, nei
>> She doesn't want us to stay.She said so.>> Well, neith
>> She doesn't want us to stay.She said so.>> Well, neither
>> She doesn't want us to stay.She said so.>> Well, neither do
>> She doesn't want us to stay.She said so.>> Well, neither do I,
She said so.>> Well, neither do I,
She said so.>> Well, neither do I,ev
She said so.>> Well, neither do I,even
She said so.>> Well, neither do I,even i
She said so.>> Well, neither do I,even if it
She said so.>> Well, neither do I,even if it i
She said so.>> Well, neither do I,even if it is
She said so.>> Well, neither do I,even if it is fu
She said so.>> Well, neither do I,even if it is fun.
>> Well, neither do I,even if it is fun.
>> Well, neither do I,even if it is fun.>>
>> Well, neither do I,even if it is fun.>> W
>> Well, neither do I,even if it is fun.>> Wha
>> Well, neither do I,even if it is fun.>> What ab
>> Well, neither do I,even if it is fun.>> What abou
>> Well, neither do I,even if it is fun.>> What about
>> Well, neither do I,even if it is fun.>> What about yo
>> Well, neither do I,even if it is fun.>> What about you, J
>> Well, neither do I,even if it is fun.>> What about you, Jam
>> Well, neither do I,even if it is fun.>> What about you, James
>> Well, neither do I,even if it is fun.>> What about you, James?
even if it is fun.>> What about you, James?
even if it is fun.>> What about you, James?>>
even if it is fun.>> What about you, James?>> W
even if it is fun.>> What about you, James?>> Wel
even if it is fun.>> What about you, James?>> Well, I
even if it is fun.>> What about you, James?>> Well, I'd
even if it is fun.>> What about you, James?>> Well, I'd b
even if it is fun.>> What about you, James?>> Well, I'd be
even if it is fun.>> What about you, James?>> Well, I'd be okay
even if it is fun.>> What about you, James?>> Well, I'd be okay h
even if it is fun.>> What about you, James?>> Well, I'd be okay her
even if it is fun.>> What about you, James?>> Well, I'd be okay here.
>>
>> M
>> May
>> Maybeth
>> Maybeth?
>> Maybeth?>>
>> Maybeth?>> Y
>> Maybeth?>> You
>> Maybeth?>> You wan
>> Maybeth?>> You want
>> Maybeth?>> You want to
>> Maybeth?>> You want to,
>> Maybeth?>> You want to, don'
>> Maybeth?>> You want to, don't
>> Maybeth?>> You want to, don't yo
>> Maybeth?>> You want to, don't you?
>> (
>> (si
>> (sigh
>> (sighin
>> (sighing)
>> (sighing)In
>> (sighing)In t
>> (sighing)In the
>> (sighing)In the mor
>> (sighing)In the morni
>> (sighing)In the morning
>> (sighing)In the morning,
>> (sighing)In the morning, I sa
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say we
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say we g
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say we get
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say we getstar
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say we getstarte
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say we getstarted
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say we getstarted on
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say we getstarted on som
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say we getstarted on somet
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say we getstarted on somethi
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say we getstarted on something
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say we getstarted on something use
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say we getstarted on something usefu
>> (sighing)In the morning, I say we getstarted on something useful,
In the morning, I say we getstarted on something useful,
In the morning, I say we getstarted on something useful,be
In the morning, I say we getstarted on something useful,befo
In the morning, I say we getstarted on something useful,before s
In the morning, I say we getstarted on something useful,before she
In the morning, I say we getstarted on something useful,before she w
In the morning, I say we getstarted on something useful,before she wak
In the morning, I say we getstarted on something useful,before she wakes u
In the morning, I say we getstarted on something useful,before she wakes up.
started on something useful,before she wakes up.
started on something useful,before she wakes up.Th
started on something useful,before she wakes up.That
started on something useful,before she wakes up.That w
started on something useful,before she wakes up.That way s
started on something useful,before she wakes up.That way she
started on something useful,before she wakes up.That way she'l
started on something useful,before she wakes up.That way she'll
started on something useful,before she wakes up.That way she'll have
started on something useful,before she wakes up.That way she'll have t
started on something useful,before she wakes up.That way she'll have to
started on something useful,before she wakes up.That way she'll have to ke
started on something useful,before she wakes up.That way she'll have to keep u
started on something useful,before she wakes up.That way she'll have to keep us
before she wakes up.That way she'll have to keep us
before she wakes up.That way she'll have to keep ushere
before she wakes up.That way she'll have to keep ushere f
before she wakes up.That way she'll have to keep ushere for
before she wakes up.That way she'll have to keep ushere for t
before she wakes up.That way she'll have to keep ushere for the d
before she wakes up.That way she'll have to keep ushere for the day
before she wakes up.That way she'll have to keep ushere for the day.
That way she'll have to keep ushere for the day.
That way she'll have to keep ushere for the day.If
That way she'll have to keep ushere for the day.If s
That way she'll have to keep ushere for the day.If she
That way she'll have to keep ushere for the day.If she tel
That way she'll have to keep ushere for the day.If she tells
That way she'll have to keep ushere for the day.If she tells u
That way she'll have to keep ushere for the day.If she tells us
That way she'll have to keep ushere for the day.If she tells us to g
That way she'll have to keep ushere for the day.If she tells us to go,
here for the day.If she tells us to go,
here for the day.If she tells us to go,we
here for the day.If she tells us to go,we c
here for the day.If she tells us to go,we can
here for the day.If she tells us to go,we can s
here for the day.If she tells us to go,we can say w
here for the day.If she tells us to go,we can say we
here for the day.If she tells us to go,we can say we wi
here for the day.If she tells us to go,we can say we will
here for the day.If she tells us to go,we can say we will as
here for the day.If she tells us to go,we can say we will as so
here for the day.If she tells us to go,we can say we will as soon
If she tells us to go,we can say we will as soon
If she tells us to go,we can say we will as soonas
If she tells us to go,we can say we will as soonas w
If she tells us to go,we can say we will as soonas we
If she tells us to go,we can say we will as soonas we fini
If she tells us to go,we can say we will as soonas we finish
If she tells us to go,we can say we will as soonas we finish t
If she tells us to go,we can say we will as soonas we finish the
If she tells us to go,we can say we will as soonas we finish the job
If she tells us to go,we can say we will as soonas we finish the job.
we can say we will as soonas we finish the job.
we can say we will as soonas we finish the job.>>
we can say we will as soonas we finish the job.>> W
we can say we will as soonas we finish the job.>> What
we can say we will as soonas we finish the job.>> What if
we can say we will as soonas we finish the job.>> What if s
we can say we will as soonas we finish the job.>> What if she
we can say we will as soonas we finish the job.>> What if she mea
we can say we will as soonas we finish the job.>> What if she means
we can say we will as soonas we finish the job.>> What if she means i
we can say we will as soonas we finish the job.>> What if she means it?
as we finish the job.>> What if she means it?
as we finish the job.>> What if she means it?>> S
as we finish the job.>> What if she means it?>> She
as we finish the job.>> What if she means it?>> She d
as we finish the job.>> What if she means it?>> She doe
as we finish the job.>> What if she means it?>> She does me
as we finish the job.>> What if she means it?>> She does mean
as we finish the job.>> What if she means it?>> She does mean i
as we finish the job.>> What if she means it?>> She does mean it.
>> What if she means it?>> She does mean it.
>> What if she means it?>> She does mean it.Th
>> What if she means it?>> She does mean it.That
>> What if she means it?>> She does mean it.That's t
>> What if she means it?>> She does mean it.That's the
>> What if she means it?>> She does mean it.That's the t
>> What if she means it?>> She does mean it.That's the tro
>> What if she means it?>> She does mean it.That's the trouble
>> What if she means it?>> She does mean it.That's the trouble,
>> What if she means it?>> She does mean it.That's the trouble, is
>> What if she means it?>> She does mean it.That's the trouble, isn'
>> What if she means it?>> She does mean it.That's the trouble, isn't it
>> What if she means it?>> She does mean it.That's the trouble, isn't it?
Look
Look,
Look, we
Look, we'l
Look, we'll pr
Look, we'll pret
Look, we'll preten
Look, we'll pretend
Look, we'll pretend that
Look, we'll pretend that w
Look, we'll pretend that we'
Look, we'll pretend that we're
Look, we'll pretend that we'reno
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot ev
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even t
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thi
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even think
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinkin
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking ab
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking abou
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about st
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about stayin
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about staying,
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about staying,but
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about staying,but ev
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about staying,but ever
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about staying,but every
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about staying,but every day
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about staying,but every day we
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about staying,but every day we d
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about staying,but every day we do
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about staying,but every day we do some
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about staying,but every day we do some w
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about staying,but every day we do some wor
Look, we'll pretend that we'renot even thinking about staying,but every day we do some work
not even thinking about staying,but every day we do some work
not even thinking about staying,but every day we do some workth
not even thinking about staying,but every day we do some workthat
not even thinking about staying,but every day we do some workthat n
not even thinking about staying,but every day we do some workthat needs
not even thinking about staying,but every day we do some workthat needs t
not even thinking about staying,but every day we do some workthat needs to
not even thinking about staying,but every day we do some workthat needs to be
not even thinking about staying,but every day we do some workthat needs to be don
not even thinking about staying,but every day we do some workthat needs to be done,
but every day we do some workthat needs to be done,
but every day we do some workthat needs to be done,so
but every day we do some workthat needs to be done,so i
but every day we do some workthat needs to be done,so it's
but every day we do some workthat needs to be done,so it's wo
but every day we do some workthat needs to be done,so it's wort
but every day we do some workthat needs to be done,so it's worth
but every day we do some workthat needs to be done,so it's worth her
but every day we do some workthat needs to be done,so it's worth her wh
but every day we do some workthat needs to be done,so it's worth her whil
but every day we do some workthat needs to be done,so it's worth her while
that needs to be done,so it's worth her while
that needs to be done,so it's worth her whileto k
that needs to be done,so it's worth her whileto kee
that needs to be done,so it's worth her whileto keep
that needs to be done,so it's worth her whileto keep us
that needs to be done,so it's worth her whileto keep us.
so it's worth her whileto keep us.
so it's worth her whileto keep us.If
so it's worth her whileto keep us.If w
so it's worth her whileto keep us.If we
so it's worth her whileto keep us.If we ge
so it's worth her whileto keep us.If we get he
so it's worth her whileto keep us.If we get her
so it's worth her whileto keep us.If we get her to
so it's worth her whileto keep us.If we get her to p
so it's worth her whileto keep us.If we get her to put i
so it's worth her whileto keep us.If we get her to put it
so it's worth her whileto keep us.If we get her to put it of
so it's worth her whileto keep us.If we get her to put it off,
to keep us.If we get her to put it off,
to keep us.If we get her to put it off,ma
to keep us.If we get her to put it off,mayb
to keep us.If we get her to put it off,maybe
to keep us.If we get her to put it off,maybe sh
to keep us.If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll
to keep us.If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll g
to keep us.If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get
to keep us.If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get u
to keep us.If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used
to keep us.If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to
to keep us.If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to u
to keep us.If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to us
If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to us
If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to usan
If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to usand
If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to usand fo
If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to usand forget
If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to usand forget t
If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to usand forget tha
If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to usand forget that
If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to usand forget that she
If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to usand forget that she wa
If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to usand forget that she want
If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to usand forget that she wants
If we get her to put it off,maybe she'll get used to usand forget that she wants us
maybe she'll get used to usand forget that she wants us
maybe she'll get used to usand forget that she wants usto
maybe she'll get used to usand forget that she wants usto g
maybe she'll get used to usand forget that she wants usto go
maybe she'll get used to usand forget that she wants usto go away
maybe she'll get used to usand forget that she wants usto go away.
and forget that she wants usto go away.
and forget that she wants usto go away.>> I
and forget that she wants usto go away.>> I d
and forget that she wants usto go away.>> I don
and forget that she wants usto go away.>> I don't
and forget that she wants usto go away.>> I don't thi
and forget that she wants usto go away.>> I don't think
and forget that she wants usto go away.>> I don't think s
and forget that she wants usto go away.>> I don't think she
and forget that she wants usto go away.>> I don't think she lik
and forget that she wants usto go away.>> I don't think she likes
and forget that she wants usto go away.>> I don't think she likes m
and forget that she wants usto go away.>> I don't think she likes me.
to go away.>> I don't think she likes me.
to go away.>> I don't think she likes me.>>
to go away.>> I don't think she likes me.>> T
to go away.>> I don't think she likes me.>> Tha
to go away.>> I don't think she likes me.>> That
to go away.>> I don't think she likes me.>> That does
to go away.>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn'
to go away.>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't
to go away.>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't ma
to go away.>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter
to go away.>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter,
to go away.>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sa
to go away.>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Samm
to go away.>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.
>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.
>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It
>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's
>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's n
>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's not h
>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's not her
>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's not her I
>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's not her I'm
>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's not her I'm thi
>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's not her I'm think
>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's not her I'm thinkin
>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's not her I'm thinking
>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's not her I'm thinking abou
>> I don't think she likes me.>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's not her I'm thinking about.
>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's not her I'm thinking about.
>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's not her I'm thinking about.It's
>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's not her I'm thinking about.It's u
>> That doesn't matter, Sammy.It's not her I'm thinking about.It's us.
It's not her I'm thinking about.It's us.
It's not her I'm thinking about.It's us.This
It's not her I'm thinking about.It's us.This w
It's not her I'm thinking about.It's us.This was
It's not her I'm thinking about.It's us.This was o
It's not her I'm thinking about.It's us.This was our m
It's not her I'm thinking about.It's us.This was our mam
It's not her I'm thinking about.It's us.This was our mama'
It's not her I'm thinking about.It's us.This was our mama's
It's not her I'm thinking about.It's us.This was our mama's hous
It's not her I'm thinking about.It's us.This was our mama's house.
Okay
Okay?
We
Well
Well,
Well, th
Well, that's
Well, that's o
Well, that's oka
Well, that's okay
Well, that's okay then
Well, that's okay then.
(cri
(crick
(cricket
(crickets
(crickets chir
(crickets chirpi
(crickets chirping
(crickets chirping)
(crickets chirping)♪
(b
(bir
(birds c
(birds chi
(birds chirp
(birds chirpin
(birds chirping)
>>
>> G
>> Great
>> Great.
>> Great.>>
>> Great.>> L
>> Great.>> Let
>> Great.>> Let's d
>> Great.>> Let's do
>> Great.>> Let's do it
>> Great.>> Let's do it.
(g
(gru
(grunt
(gruntin
(grunting)
>>
>> O
>> Ouc
>> Ouch!
(d
(dis
(dista
(distant g
(distant gru
(distant grunt
(distant gruntin
(distant grunting, c
(distant grunting, cla
(distant grunting, clatt
(distant grunting, clatter
(distant grunting, clattering)
(distant grunting, clattering)>>
(distant grunting, clattering)>> T
(distant grunting, clattering)>> Thi
(distant grunting, clattering)>> This on
(distant grunting, clattering)>> This one'
(distant grunting, clattering)>> This one's
(distant grunting, clattering)>> This one's to
(distant grunting, clattering)>> This one's tough.
>>
>> P
>> Pul
>> Pull ha
>> Pull hard
>> Pull harder
>> Pull harder.
>> Pull harder.>>
>> Pull harder.>> Y
>> Pull harder.>> You
>> Pull harder.>> You'r
>> Pull harder.>> You're go
>> Pull harder.>> You're gonn
>> Pull harder.>> You're gonna
>> Pull harder.>> You're gonna wa
>> Pull harder.>> You're gonna wake h
>> Pull harder.>> You're gonna wake her
>> Pull harder.>> You're gonna wake her u
>> Pull harder.>> You're gonna wake her up.
>>
>> (
>> (la
>> (laughi
>> (laughing
>> (laughing)
>> (laughing) Pu
>> (laughing) Pull!
>> (laughing) Pull!Come
>> (laughing) Pull!Come o
>> (laughing) Pull!Come on.
(s
(scr
(scrapin
(scraping)
(scraping)>>
(scraping)>> W
(scraping)>> Was
(scraping)>> Wash yo
(scraping)>> Wash your
(scraping)>> Wash your h
(scraping)>> Wash your han
(scraping)>> Wash your hands.
(scraping)>> Wash your hands.I
(scraping)>> Wash your hands.I se
(scraping)>> Wash your hands.I see
(scraping)>> Wash your hands.I see you
(scraping)>> Wash your hands.I see you do
(scraping)>> Wash your hands.I see you don'
(scraping)>> Wash your hands.I see you don't
(scraping)>> Wash your hands.I see you don't make
>> Wash your hands.I see you don't make
>> Wash your hands.I see you don't makeyo
>> Wash your hands.I see you don't makeyour
>> Wash your hands.I see you don't makeyour own
>> Wash your hands.I see you don't makeyour own b
>> Wash your hands.I see you don't makeyour own bed
>> Wash your hands.I see you don't makeyour own beds.
I see you don't makeyour own beds.
I see you don't makeyour own beds.>>
I see you don't makeyour own beds.>> I
I see you don't makeyour own beds.>> I'l
I see you don't makeyour own beds.>> I'll do
I see you don't makeyour own beds.>> I'll do t
I see you don't makeyour own beds.>> I'll do tha
I see you don't makeyour own beds.>> I'll do that.
your own beds.>> I'll do that.
your own beds.>> I'll do that.>>
your own beds.>> I'll do that.>> N
your own beds.>> I'll do that.>> No.
>> I'll do that.>> No.
>> I'll do that.>> No.Yo
>> I'll do that.>> No.You'
>> I'll do that.>> No.You'll
>> I'll do that.>> No.You'll eac
>> I'll do that.>> No.You'll each
>> I'll do that.>> No.You'll each do
>> I'll do that.>> No.You'll each do y
>> I'll do that.>> No.You'll each do your
>> I'll do that.>> No.You'll each do your ow
>> I'll do that.>> No.You'll each do your own.
(cla
(clank
(clankin
(clanking,
(clanking, scr
(clanking, scrap
(clanking, scrapin
(clanking, scraping)
(s
(sil
(silve
(silverwar
(silverware
(silverware cl
(silverware clan
(silverware clanking
(silverware clanking)
I
I li
I liked
I liked th
I liked that
I liked that h
I liked that honey
I liked that honeysu
I liked that honeysuck
I liked that honeysuckle
I liked that honeysuckle.
I liked that honeysuckle.Ho
I liked that honeysuckle.Hone
I liked that honeysuckle.Honeys
I liked that honeysuckle.Honeysuc
I liked that honeysuckle.Honeysuckle'
I liked that honeysuckle.Honeysuckle's
I liked that honeysuckle.Honeysuckle's be
I liked that honeysuckle.Honeysuckle's been
I liked that honeysuckle.Honeysuckle's been the
I liked that honeysuckle.Honeysuckle's been there
I liked that honeysuckle.Honeysuckle's been therefo
I liked that honeysuckle.Honeysuckle's been therefor
I liked that honeysuckle.Honeysuckle's been therefor ye
I liked that honeysuckle.Honeysuckle's been therefor year
I liked that honeysuckle.Honeysuckle's been therefor years.
Honeysuckle's been therefor years.
Honeysuckle's been therefor years.It
Honeysuckle's been therefor years.It's
Honeysuckle's been therefor years.It's k
Honeysuckle's been therefor years.It's kin
Honeysuckle's been therefor years.It's kind of
Honeysuckle's been therefor years.It's kind of a
Honeysuckle's been therefor years.It's kind of a t
Honeysuckle's been therefor years.It's kind of a ten
Honeysuckle's been therefor years.It's kind of a tenacio
Honeysuckle's been therefor years.It's kind of a tenacious
Honeysuckle's been therefor years.It's kind of a tenacious p
Honeysuckle's been therefor years.It's kind of a tenacious pla
Honeysuckle's been therefor years.It's kind of a tenacious plant
for years.It's kind of a tenacious plant
for years.It's kind of a tenacious plantI
for years.It's kind of a tenacious plantI ha
for years.It's kind of a tenacious plantI have
for years.It's kind of a tenacious plantI have to
for years.It's kind of a tenacious plantI have to re
for years.It's kind of a tenacious plantI have to resp
for years.It's kind of a tenacious plantI have to respec
for years.It's kind of a tenacious plantI have to respect.
>>
>> H
>> Hon
>> Honeysu
>> Honeysuck
>> Honeysuckle
>> Honeysuckle i
>> Honeysuckle is pa
>> Honeysuckle is para
>> Honeysuckle is parasi
>> Honeysuckle is parasiti
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It c
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be tr
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trai
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be traine
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained an
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained and
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained and cu
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained and cut
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained and cut back
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained and cut back.
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained and cut back.Bu
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained and cut back.But
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained and cut back.But if
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained and cut back.But if it
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained and cut back.But if it pr
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained and cut back.But if it prol
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained and cut back.But if it prolif
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained and cut back.But if it proliferat
>> Honeysuckle is parasitic.It can be trained and cut back.But if it proliferates
It can be trained and cut back.But if it proliferates
It can be trained and cut back.But if it proliferateswi
It can be trained and cut back.But if it proliferateswith
It can be trained and cut back.But if it proliferateswithout
It can be trained and cut back.But if it proliferateswithout be
It can be trained and cut back.But if it proliferateswithout bein
It can be trained and cut back.But if it proliferateswithout being
It can be trained and cut back.But if it proliferateswithout being cont
It can be trained and cut back.But if it proliferateswithout being contro
It can be trained and cut back.But if it proliferateswithout being controll
It can be trained and cut back.But if it proliferateswithout being controlled
It can be trained and cut back.But if it proliferateswithout being controlled...
But if it proliferateswithout being controlled...
But if it proliferateswithout being controlled...it
But if it proliferateswithout being controlled...it c
But if it proliferateswithout being controlled...it cho
But if it proliferateswithout being controlled...it chokes
But if it proliferateswithout being controlled...it chokes ou
But if it proliferateswithout being controlled...it chokes out
But if it proliferateswithout being controlled...it chokes out ot
But if it proliferateswithout being controlled...it chokes out other
But if it proliferateswithout being controlled...it chokes out other gr
But if it proliferateswithout being controlled...it chokes out other grow
But if it proliferateswithout being controlled...it chokes out other growth
But if it proliferateswithout being controlled...it chokes out other growth.
without being controlled...it chokes out other growth.
without being controlled...it chokes out other growth.>>
without being controlled...it chokes out other growth.>> I
without being controlled...it chokes out other growth.>> It'
without being controlled...it chokes out other growth.>> It's ba
without being controlled...it chokes out other growth.>> It's bad.
>>
>> W
>> Where
>> Where d
>> Where did
>> Where did y
>> Where did you l
>> Where did you lea
>> Where did you learn
>> Where did you learna wo
>> Where did you learna word
>> Where did you learna word l
>> Where did you learna word lik
>> Where did you learna word like "p
>> Where did you learna word like "pro
>> Where did you learna word like "proli
>> Where did you learna word like "prolife
>> Where did you learna word like "proliferate
>> Where did you learna word like "proliferate"?
(sig
(sighi
(sighing
(sighing)
(sighing)Th
(sighing)That
(sighing)That h
(sighing)That hon
(sighing)That honeysu
(sighing)That honeysuck
(sighing)That honeysuckle
(sighing)That honeysuckle w
(sighing)That honeysuckle will
(sighing)That honeysuckle will ta
(sighing)That honeysuckle will take
(sighing)That honeysuckle will take y
(sighing)That honeysuckle will take you
(sighing)That honeysuckle will take youal
(sighing)That honeysuckle will take youall
(sighing)That honeysuckle will take youall da
(sighing)That honeysuckle will take youall day, a
(sighing)That honeysuckle will take youall day, at
(sighing)That honeysuckle will take youall day, at le
(sighing)That honeysuckle will take youall day, at leas
(sighing)That honeysuckle will take youall day, at least.
That honeysuckle will take youall day, at least.
That honeysuckle will take youall day, at least.Ca
That honeysuckle will take youall day, at least.Can'
That honeysuckle will take youall day, at least.Can't
That honeysuckle will take youall day, at least.Can't just
That honeysuckle will take youall day, at least.Can't just l
That honeysuckle will take youall day, at least.Can't just let
That honeysuckle will take youall day, at least.Can't just let t
That honeysuckle will take youall day, at least.Can't just let the v
That honeysuckle will take youall day, at least.Can't just let the vin
That honeysuckle will take youall day, at least.Can't just let the vines
all day, at least.Can't just let the vines
all day, at least.Can't just let the vinespi
all day, at least.Can't just let the vinespile
all day, at least.Can't just let the vinespile up.
Can't just let the vinespile up.
Can't just let the vinespile up.They
Can't just let the vinespile up.They h
Can't just let the vinespile up.They hav
Can't just let the vinespile up.They have
Can't just let the vinespile up.They have to g
Can't just let the vinespile up.They have to go
Can't just let the vinespile up.They have to go ou
Can't just let the vinespile up.They have to go out
pile up.They have to go out
pile up.They have to go outon
pile up.They have to go outon t
pile up.They have to go outon the
pile up.They have to go outon the mar
pile up.They have to go outon the marsh
pile up.They have to go outon the marsh.
♪
(c
(cri
(crick
(cricket
(crickets ch
(crickets chir
(crickets chirpi
(crickets chirping
(crickets chirping)
(crickets chirping)(Dov
(crickets chirping)(Dove
(crickets chirping)(Dove ca
(crickets chirping)(Dove call
(crickets chirping)(Dove calling,
(crickets chirping)(Dove calling, b
(crickets chirping)(Dove calling, bir
(crickets chirping)(Dove calling, birds
(crickets chirping)(Dove calling, birds chi
(crickets chirping)(Dove calling, birds chirp
(crickets chirping)(Dove calling, birds chirpin
(crickets chirping)(Dove calling, birds chirping)
(b
(bus
(bushes
(bushes ra
(bushes ratt
(bushes rattli
(bushes rattling)
>>
>> J
>> James
>> James,
>> James, go
>> James, go h
>> James, go help
>> James, go help he
>> James, go help her.
>> James, go help her.>>
>> James, go help her.>> F
>> James, go help her.>> Fro
>> James, go help her.>> Front m
>> James, go help her.>> Front mus
>> James, go help her.>> Front must
>> James, go help her.>> Front must be
>> James, go help her.>> Front must be cle
>> James, go help her.>> Front must be clear
>> James, go help her.>> Front must be clearby
>> James, go help her.>> Front must be clearby t
>> James, go help her.>> Front must be clearby the
>> James, go help her.>> Front must be clearby the siz
>> James, go help her.>> Front must be clearby the size
>> James, go help her.>> Front must be clearby the size of
>> James, go help her.>> Front must be clearby the size of t
>> James, go help her.>> Front must be clearby the size of that
>> James, go help her.>> Front must be clearby the size of that pi
>> James, go help her.>> Front must be clearby the size of that pile
>> Front must be clearby the size of that pile
>> Front must be clearby the size of that pilein
>> Front must be clearby the size of that pilein t
>> Front must be clearby the size of that pilein the
>> Front must be clearby the size of that pilein the mar
>> Front must be clearby the size of that pilein the marsh
>> Front must be clearby the size of that pilein the marsh.
by the size of that pilein the marsh.
by the size of that pilein the marsh.Th
by the size of that pilein the marsh.Ther
by the size of that pilein the marsh.There'
by the size of that pilein the marsh.There's mo
by the size of that pilein the marsh.There's more
by the size of that pilein the marsh.There's more i
by the size of that pilein the marsh.There's more in
by the size of that pilein the marsh.There's more in the
by the size of that pilein the marsh.There's more in the bo
by the size of that pilein the marsh.There's more in the boat
by the size of that pilein the marsh.There's more in the boat.
in the marsh.There's more in the boat.
in the marsh.There's more in the boat.(b
in the marsh.There's more in the boat.(bir
in the marsh.There's more in the boat.(bird
in the marsh.There's more in the boat.(bird squa
in the marsh.There's more in the boat.(bird squawk
in the marsh.There's more in the boat.(bird squawkin
in the marsh.There's more in the boat.(bird squawking)
♪
♪Wh
♪When
♪When y
♪When you
♪When you're
♪When you're do
♪When you're done
♪When you're done y
♪When you're done you b
♪When you're done you bet
♪When you're done you bette
♪When you're done you better
♪When you're done you betterru
♪When you're done you betterrub
♪When you're done you betterrub do
♪When you're done you betterrub down t
♪When you're done you betterrub down tho
♪When you're done you betterrub down those
♪When you're done you betterrub down those t
♪When you're done you betterrub down those tools
When you're done you betterrub down those tools
When you're done you betterrub down those toolswi
When you're done you betterrub down those toolswith
When you're done you betterrub down those toolswith a
When you're done you betterrub down those toolswith a tac
When you're done you betterrub down those toolswith a tack
When you're done you betterrub down those toolswith a tack cl
When you're done you betterrub down those toolswith a tack clot
When you're done you betterrub down those toolswith a tack cloth
rub down those toolswith a tack cloth
rub down those toolswith a tack clothor
rub down those toolswith a tack clothor t
rub down those toolswith a tack clothor the
rub down those toolswith a tack clothor they'll
rub down those toolswith a tack clothor they'll r
rub down those toolswith a tack clothor they'll rus
rub down those toolswith a tack clothor they'll rust.
with a tack clothor they'll rust.
with a tack clothor they'll rust.I'
with a tack clothor they'll rust.I've
with a tack clothor they'll rust.I've got
with a tack clothor they'll rust.I've got g
with a tack clothor they'll rust.I've got gro
with a tack clothor they'll rust.I've got groce
with a tack clothor they'll rust.I've got groceries
or they'll rust.I've got groceries
or they'll rust.I've got groceriesto
or they'll rust.I've got groceriesto p
or they'll rust.I've got groceriesto put
or they'll rust.I've got groceriesto put a
or they'll rust.I've got groceriesto put away.
>>
>> R
>> Rah
>> Rah!
>> Rah!Oo
>> Rah!Ooh.
(chu
(chuck
(chuckli
(chuckling
(chuckling)
>> Y
>> You
>> You d
>> You did
>> You did a g
>> You did a goo
>> You did a good
>> You did a good da
>> You did a good day's
>> You did a good day's wo
>> You did a good day's work
>> You did a good day's work.
>> You did a good day's work.I
>> You did a good day's work.I su
>> You did a good day's work.I supp
>> You did a good day's work.I suppose
>> You did a good day's work.I suppose yo
>> You did a good day's work.I suppose you'
>> You did a good day's work.I suppose you'll
>> You did a good day's work.I suppose you'll be
>> You did a good day's work.I suppose you'll bemo
>> You did a good day's work.I suppose you'll bemovi
>> You did a good day's work.I suppose you'll bemoving o
>> You did a good day's work.I suppose you'll bemoving on
>> You did a good day's work.I suppose you'll bemoving on to
>> You did a good day's work.I suppose you'll bemoving on tomo
>> You did a good day's work.I suppose you'll bemoving on tomorrow
>> You did a good day's work.I suppose you'll bemoving on tomorrow.
>>
>> T
>> The
>> There's
>> There's s
>> There's sti
>> There's still
>> There's still hon
>> There's still honey
>> There's still honeysu
>> There's still honeysuck
>> There's still honeysuckle
>> There's still honeysuckleto
>> There's still honeysuckleto b
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pu
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pull
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled.
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled.>>
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled.>> I
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled.>> I d
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled.>> I don
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled.>> I don't k
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled.>> I don't kno
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled.>> I don't know
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled.>> I don't know wh
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled.>> I don't know why yo
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled.>> I don't know why you
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled.>> I don't know why you ca
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled.>> I don't know why you carr
>> There's still honeysuckleto be pulled.>> I don't know why you carried
to be pulled.>> I don't know why you carried
to be pulled.>> I don't know why you carriedit
to be pulled.>> I don't know why you carriedit s
to be pulled.>> I don't know why you carriedit so
to be pulled.>> I don't know why you carriedit so far
to be pulled.>> I don't know why you carriedit so far in
to be pulled.>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into
to be pulled.>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into t
to be pulled.>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the m
to be pulled.>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the mar
to be pulled.>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh
to be pulled.>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh.
>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh.
>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh.Can
>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh.Can le
>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh.Can leav
>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh.Can leave
>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh.Can leave it a
>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh.Can leave it at
>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh.Can leave it at th
>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh.Can leave it at the
>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh.Can leave it at the fron
>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh.Can leave it at the front
>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh.Can leave it at the front en
>> I don't know why you carriedit so far into the marsh.Can leave it at the front end.
it so far into the marsh.Can leave it at the front end.
it so far into the marsh.Can leave it at the front end.It
it so far into the marsh.Can leave it at the front end.It'd
it so far into the marsh.Can leave it at the front end.It'd r
it so far into the marsh.Can leave it at the front end.It'd rot b
it so far into the marsh.Can leave it at the front end.It'd rot by
it so far into the marsh.Can leave it at the front end.It'd rot by sp
it so far into the marsh.Can leave it at the front end.It'd rot by spri
it so far into the marsh.Can leave it at the front end.It'd rot by spring.
Ja
Jame
James,
James, y
James, you l
James, you loo
James, you look
James, you look li
James, you look like y
James, you look like you
James, you look like youco
James, you look like youcoul
James, you look like youcould
James, you look like youcould us
James, you look like youcould use tw
James, you look like youcould use two
James, you look like youcould use two pi
James, you look like youcould use two piec
James, you look like youcould use two pieces o
James, you look like youcould use two pieces of
James, you look like youcould use two pieces of ch
James, you look like youcould use two pieces of chic
James, you look like youcould use two pieces of chicken.
>>
>> ♪
>> ♪ G
>> ♪ Goi
>> ♪ Going t
>> ♪ Going to
>> ♪ Going to th
>> ♪ Going to the
>> ♪ Going to the ocea
>> ♪ Going to the ocean
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ G
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Goi
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going t
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to th
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the be
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beac
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ G
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gon
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna w
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna wal
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on th
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sa
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand
>> ♪ Going to the ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ I
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my b
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare fe
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm g
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going s
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going sha
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shall
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow w
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow wal
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walki
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walking
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ G
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Goi
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going sha
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shall
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow w
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walki
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪
♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪
♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ A
♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are
♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are y
♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you
♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you goi
♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going
♪ I'm going shallow walking ♪♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ S
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Sha
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shall
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow wal
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walki
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking w
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me?
♪ Going shallow walking ♪♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪
♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪
♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪
♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ G
♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Goi
♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going
♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going dow
♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down
♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to
♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to C
♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisf
♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfie
♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield
♪ Are you going ♪♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪
♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪
♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ G
♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Goi
♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going
♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going d
♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down
♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to
♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to C
♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Cri
♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfie
♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield
♪ Shallow walking with me? ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ G
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Goi
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going d
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to C
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Cri
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfie
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ W
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Wit
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With bl
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blis
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With bliste
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my h
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my hee
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my heels
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my heels ♪
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my heels ♪
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ A
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are y
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you goi
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going d
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going dow
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going down to
♪ Going down to Crisfield ♪♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going down to ♪
♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going down to ♪
♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ C
♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Cri
♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisf
♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfie
♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield w
♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield wit
♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield with
♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield with me
♪ With blisters on my heels ♪♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield with me? ♪
♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield with me? ♪
♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪
♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ '
♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Ca
♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Caus
♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Cause I'
♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Cause I'm
♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Cause I'm go
♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Cause I'm goin
♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Cause I'm going to
♪ Are you going down to ♪♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪
♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪
♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪
♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ T
♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ The
♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ The oce
♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ The ocean
♪ Crisfield with me? ♪♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ G
♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Goi
♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going
♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going t
♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to th
♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the
♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the be
♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beac
♪ 'Cause I'm going to ♪♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ G
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna w
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna wal
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up o
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on th
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand
♪ The ocean ♪♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ I
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my b
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bar
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare fe
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet
♪ Going to the beach ♪♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm g
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goi
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' s
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' sha
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shall
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow wal
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walki
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin'
♪ Gonna walk up on the sand ♪♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin' ♪
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin' ♪
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin' ♪♪ G
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin' ♪♪ Goi
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin' ♪♪ Goin'
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin' ♪♪ Goin' s
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin' ♪♪ Goin' shall
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin' ♪♪ Goin' shallow
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin' ♪♪ Goin' shallow w
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin' ♪♪ Goin' shallow wal
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin' ♪♪ Goin' shallow walkin'
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin' ♪♪ Goin' shallow walkin'..
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin' ♪♪ Goin' shallow walkin'...
♪ In my bare feet ♪♪ I'm goin' shallow walkin' ♪♪ Goin' shallow walkin'... ♪
>>
>> G
>> Give
>> Give yo
>> Give you
>> Give you th
>> Give you this m
>> Give you this muc
>> Give you this much,
>> Give you this much, y
>> Give you this much, you'r
>> Give you this much, you're
>> Give you this much, you'remama
>> Give you this much, you'remama t
>> Give you this much, you'remama tau
>> Give you this much, you'remama taugh
>> Give you this much, you'remama taught yo
>> Give you this much, you'remama taught you
>> Give you this much, you'remama taught you ho
>> Give you this much, you'remama taught you how
>> Give you this much, you'remama taught you how to s
>> Give you this much, you'remama taught you how to sin
>> Give you this much, you'remama taught you how to sing.
>>
>> D
>> Did y
>> Did you
>> Did you e
>> Did you eve
>> Did you ever si
>> Did you ever sing
>> Did you ever sing t
>> Did you ever sing to
>> Did you ever sing toou
>> Did you ever sing toour
>> Did you ever sing toour mama
>> Did you ever sing toour mama?
>> Did you ever sing toour mama?>>
>> Did you ever sing toour mama?>> I
>> Did you ever sing toour mama?>> I d
>> Did you ever sing toour mama?>> I don't
>> Did you ever sing toour mama?>> I don't r
>> Did you ever sing toour mama?>> I don't rec
>> Did you ever sing toour mama?>> I don't recal
>> Did you ever sing toour mama?>> I don't recall.
our mama?>> I don't recall.
our mama?>> I don't recall.If
our mama?>> I don't recall.If y
our mama?>> I don't recall.If you w
our mama?>> I don't recall.If you wan
our mama?>> I don't recall.If you wanna
our mama?>> I don't recall.If you wanna w
our mama?>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash
our mama?>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash an
our mama?>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash any
our mama?>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash any cl
our mama?>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash any clothe
our mama?>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash any clothes,
>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash any clothes,
>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash any clothes,toni
>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash any clothes,tonigh
>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight'
>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's
>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the
>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the ti
>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the time
>> I don't recall.If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the time.
If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the time.
If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the time.I'
If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the time.I'll
If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the time.I'll b
If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the time.I'll be
If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the time.I'll be usin
If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the time.I'll be using
If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the time.I'll be using th
If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the time.I'll be using the
If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the time.I'll be using the sink
If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the time.I'll be using the sink f
If you wanna wash any clothes,tonight's the time.I'll be using the sink for
tonight's the time.I'll be using the sink for
tonight's the time.I'll be using the sink forca
tonight's the time.I'll be using the sink forcann
tonight's the time.I'll be using the sink forcannin
tonight's the time.I'll be using the sink forcanning to
tonight's the time.I'll be using the sink forcanning tomo
tonight's the time.I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorr
tonight's the time.I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow
tonight's the time.I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow.
I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow.
I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow.Wh
I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow.Wher
I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow.Where'
I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow.Where'd yo
I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow.Where'd you
I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow.Where'd you he
I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow.Where'd you hear
I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow.Where'd you hear tha
I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that
I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that so
I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that song
I'll be using the sink forcanning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that song?
canning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that song?
canning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that song?>> A
canning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that song?>> A f
canning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that song?>> A fri
canning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that song?>> A frien
canning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend ta
canning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taug
canning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught
canning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught i
canning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to
canning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to u
canning tomorrow.Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to us,
Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to us,
Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to us,so
Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to us,some
Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to us,someone
Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to us,someone we
Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to us,someone we m
Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to us,someone we met
Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to us,someone we met alo
Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to us,someone we met along
Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to us,someone we met along t
Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to us,someone we met along the
Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to us,someone we met along the way
Where'd you hear that song?>> A friend taught it to us,someone we met along the way.
>> A friend taught it to us,someone we met along the way.
>> A friend taught it to us,someone we met along the way.>>
>> A friend taught it to us,someone we met along the way.>> W
>> A friend taught it to us,someone we met along the way.>> Windy
>> A friend taught it to us,someone we met along the way.>> Windy.
someone we met along the way.>> Windy.
someone we met along the way.>> Windy.>>
someone we met along the way.>> Windy.>> W
someone we met along the way.>> Windy.>> Win
someone we met along the way.>> Windy.>> Windy
someone we met along the way.>> Windy.>> Windy who
someone we met along the way.>> Windy.>> Windy who?
>> Windy.>> Windy who?
>> Windy.>> Windy who?>>
>> Windy.>> Windy who?>> I
>> Windy.>> Windy who?>> I d
>> Windy.>> Windy who?>> I don't
>> Windy.>> Windy who?>> I don't k
>> Windy.>> Windy who?>> I don't kno
>> Windy.>> Windy who?>> I don't know,
>> Windy.>> Windy who?>> I don't know, it
>> Windy.>> Windy who?>> I don't know, it wa
>> Windy.>> Windy who?>> I don't know, it was
>> Windy who?>> I don't know, it was
>> Windy who?>> I don't know, it wasat
>> Windy who?>> I don't know, it wasat a
>> Windy who?>> I don't know, it wasat a c
>> Windy who?>> I don't know, it wasat a colle
>> Windy who?>> I don't know, it wasat a college
>> Windy who?>> I don't know, it wasat a college.
>> I don't know, it wasat a college.
>> I don't know, it wasat a college.>>
>> I don't know, it wasat a college.>> W
>> I don't know, it wasat a college.>> Wha
>> I don't know, it wasat a college.>> What we
>> I don't know, it wasat a college.>> What were
>> I don't know, it wasat a college.>> What were y
>> I don't know, it wasat a college.>> What were you
>> I don't know, it wasat a college.>> What were you doi
>> I don't know, it wasat a college.>> What were you doing
at a college.>> What were you doing
at a college.>> What were you doingat
at a college.>> What were you doingat a
at a college.>> What were you doingat a c
at a college.>> What were you doingat a colle
at a college.>> What were you doingat a college
at a college.>> What were you doingat a college?
>>
>> W
>> Well,
>> Well, w
>> Well, we
>> Well, we ha
>> Well, we had ju
>> Well, we had just
>> Well, we had justcome
>> Well, we had justcome i
>> Well, we had justcome int
>> Well, we had justcome into
>> Well, we had justcome into New
>> Well, we had justcome into New Ha
>> Well, we had justcome into New Have
>> Well, we had justcome into New Haven.
>> Well, we had justcome into New Haven.It w
>> Well, we had justcome into New Haven.It was
>> Well, we had justcome into New Haven.It was l
>> Well, we had justcome into New Haven.It was lat
>> Well, we had justcome into New Haven.It was late
come into New Haven.It was late
come into New Haven.It was lateand
come into New Haven.It was lateand it
come into New Haven.It was lateand it w
come into New Haven.It was lateand it was
come into New Haven.It was lateand it was rai
come into New Haven.It was lateand it was raini
come into New Haven.It was lateand it was raining
come into New Haven.It was lateand it was raining.
It was lateand it was raining.
It was lateand it was raining.We
It was lateand it was raining.We f
It was lateand it was raining.We fin
It was lateand it was raining.We finally
It was lateand it was raining.We finally f
It was lateand it was raining.We finally fou
It was lateand it was raining.We finally found
It was lateand it was raining.We finally found a p
It was lateand it was raining.We finally found a pla
It was lateand it was raining.We finally found a place
and it was raining.We finally found a place
and it was raining.We finally found a placeto
and it was raining.We finally found a placeto s
and it was raining.We finally found a placeto sle
and it was raining.We finally found a placeto sleep b
and it was raining.We finally found a placeto sleep beh
and it was raining.We finally found a placeto sleep behin
and it was raining.We finally found a placeto sleep behind
and it was raining.We finally found a placeto sleep behind this
and it was raining.We finally found a placeto sleep behind this d
and it was raining.We finally found a placeto sleep behind this dum
and it was raining.We finally found a placeto sleep behind this dumps
and it was raining.We finally found a placeto sleep behind this dumpster.
and it was raining.We finally found a placeto sleep behind this dumpster...
(i
(ind
(indis
(indistinc
(indistinct
(indistinct ch
(indistinct chat
(indistinct chatter)
(w
(win
(wind
(wind blow
(wind blowin
(wind blowing)
>> G
>> Goo
>> Good
>> Good ni
>> Good night.
>>
>> G
>> Goo
>> Good
>> Good nigh
>> Good night.
(b
(bir
(birds
(birds c
(birds chirp
(birds chirpin
(birds chirping)
(birds chirping)(kno
(birds chirping)(knock
(birds chirping)(knockin
(birds chirping)(knocking)
♪
(l
(lau
(laughin
(laughing)
(laughing)>>
(laughing)>> A
(laughing)>> Ah!
(b
(bli
(blind s
(blind sli
(blind slidi
(blind sliding
(blind sliding ope
(blind sliding open)
(lid
(lid c
(lid cre
(lid creak
(lid creaking)
(p
(pla
(playi
(playing
(playing pia
(playing piano
(playing piano)
(playing piano)(v
(playing piano)(veh
(playing piano)(vehicle
(playing piano)(vehicle a
(playing piano)(vehicle app
(playing piano)(vehicle appro
(playing piano)(vehicle approachi
(playing piano)(vehicle approaching
(playing piano)(vehicle approaching)
(m
(man
(man whi
(man whist
(man whistli
(man whistling
(man whistling)
>>
>> W
>> Wil
>> Will
>> Will you
>> Will you be
>> Will you be m
>> Will you be mov
>> Will you be moving
>> Will you be moving on
>> Will you be moving onto
>> Will you be moving ontomo
>> Will you be moving ontomorr
>> Will you be moving ontomorrow?
>> Will you be moving ontomorrow?>>
>> Will you be moving ontomorrow?>> Y
>> Will you be moving ontomorrow?>> You
>> Will you be moving ontomorrow?>> Your ma
>> Will you be moving ontomorrow?>> Your mail
>> Will you be moving ontomorrow?>> Your mailbo
>> Will you be moving ontomorrow?>> Your mailbox
>> Will you be moving ontomorrow?>> Your mailbox need
>> Will you be moving ontomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs
>> Will you be moving ontomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs br
>> Will you be moving ontomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs brac
>> Will you be moving ontomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs bracing,
tomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs bracing,
tomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs bracing,an
tomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and
tomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and th
tomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there'
tomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's
tomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's so
tomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some
tomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some pat
tomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some patch
tomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some patchin
tomorrow?>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some patching
>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some patching
>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some patchingto
>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some patchingto b
>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some patchingto be
>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some patchingto be done
>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some patchingto be done i
>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some patchingto be done in
>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some patchingto be done in th
>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some patchingto be done in the ba
>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some patchingto be done in the barn
>> Your mailbox needs bracing,and there's some patchingto be done in the barn.
and there's some patchingto be done in the barn.
and there's some patchingto be done in the barn.Yo
and there's some patchingto be done in the barn.You
and there's some patchingto be done in the barn.You ha
and there's some patchingto be done in the barn.You have w
and there's some patchingto be done in the barn.You have woo
and there's some patchingto be done in the barn.You have wood
and there's some patchingto be done in the barn.You have wood in
and there's some patchingto be done in the barn.You have wood in the
and there's some patchingto be done in the barn.You have wood in there
and there's some patchingto be done in the barn.You have wood in there,
to be done in the barn.You have wood in there,
to be done in the barn.You have wood in there,do
to be done in the barn.You have wood in there,don'
to be done in the barn.You have wood in there,don't yo
to be done in the barn.You have wood in there,don't you?
You have wood in there,don't you?
You have wood in there,don't you?(sig
You have wood in there,don't you?(sighi
You have wood in there,don't you?(sighing
You have wood in there,don't you?(sighing)
don't you?(sighing)
don't you?(sighing)>>
don't you?(sighing)>> I
don't you?(sighing)>> It's
don't you?(sighing)>> It's go
don't you?(sighing)>> It's gonn
don't you?(sighing)>> It's gonna
don't you?(sighing)>> It's gonna rain
don't you?(sighing)>> It's gonna rain.
(sighing)>> It's gonna rain.
(sighing)>> It's gonna rain.Th
(sighing)>> It's gonna rain.Ther
(sighing)>> It's gonna rain.There'
(sighing)>> It's gonna rain.There's
(sighing)>> It's gonna rain.There's stor
(sighing)>> It's gonna rain.There's storms
(sighing)>> It's gonna rain.There's storms b
(sighing)>> It's gonna rain.There's storms bre
(sighing)>> It's gonna rain.There's storms brewing
(sighing)>> It's gonna rain.There's storms brewing.
>> It's gonna rain.There's storms brewing.
>> It's gonna rain.There's storms brewing.(c
>> It's gonna rain.There's storms brewing.(cla
>> It's gonna rain.There's storms brewing.(clatt
>> It's gonna rain.There's storms brewing.(clatter
>> It's gonna rain.There's storms brewing.(clattering,
>> It's gonna rain.There's storms brewing.(clattering, c
>> It's gonna rain.There's storms brewing.(clattering, cho
>> It's gonna rain.There's storms brewing.(clattering, chopp
>> It's gonna rain.There's storms brewing.(clattering, chopping)
(s
(set
(sets kn
(sets knif
(sets knife
(sets knife do
(sets knife down)
(w
(whi
(whimp
(whimperin
(whimpering)
(thu
(thund
(thunder
(thunderin
(thundering)
(f
(foo
(foots
(footsteps
(footsteps a
(footsteps app
(footsteps appro
(footsteps approachi
(footsteps approaching
(footsteps approaching)
I
I gu
I gues
I guess
I guess ever
I guess everyb
I guess everybod
I guess everybody
I guess everybody know
I guess everybody knows
I guess everybody knowsI
I guess everybody knowsI go
I guess everybody knowsI got
I guess everybody knowsI got a le
I guess everybody knowsI got a lett
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter f
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from yo
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your c
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your cousi
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your cousin.
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your cousin.Ap
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your cousin.Appa
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your cousin.Appare
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your cousin.Apparently
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your cousin.Apparently,
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, sh
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, she
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, she feel
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, she feels
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, she feels it
I guess everybody knowsI got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, she feels it's
I got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, she feels it's
I got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, she feels it'she
I got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, she feels it'sher
I got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, she feels it'sher Go
I got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, she feels it'sher God-gi
I got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, she feels it'sher God-give
I got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, she feels it'sher God-given
I got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, she feels it'sher God-given du
I got a letter from your cousin.Apparently, she feels it'sher God-given duty
Apparently, she feels it'sher God-given duty
Apparently, she feels it'sher God-given dutyto l
Apparently, she feels it'sher God-given dutyto loo
Apparently, she feels it'sher God-given dutyto look
Apparently, she feels it'sher God-given dutyto look af
Apparently, she feels it'sher God-given dutyto look after
Apparently, she feels it'sher God-given dutyto look after yo
Apparently, she feels it'sher God-given dutyto look after you.
her God-given dutyto look after you.
her God-given dutyto look after you.Sh
her God-given dutyto look after you.She'
her God-given dutyto look after you.She's
her God-given dutyto look after you.She's maki
her God-given dutyto look after you.She's making
her God-given dutyto look after you.She's making a
her God-given dutyto look after you.She's making arr
her God-given dutyto look after you.She's making arrange
her God-given dutyto look after you.She's making arrangeme
her God-given dutyto look after you.She's making arrangement
her God-given dutyto look after you.She's making arrangements.
to look after you.She's making arrangements.
to look after you.She's making arrangements.I do
to look after you.She's making arrangements.I don'
to look after you.She's making arrangements.I don't
to look after you.She's making arrangements.I don't kn
to look after you.She's making arrangements.I don't know w
to look after you.She's making arrangements.I don't know wha
to look after you.She's making arrangements.I don't know what
to look after you.She's making arrangements.I don't know what al
to look after you.She's making arrangements.I don't know what all.
She's making arrangements.I don't know what all.
She's making arrangements.I don't know what all.So
She's making arrangements.I don't know what all.Some
She's making arrangements.I don't know what all.Someth
She's making arrangements.I don't know what all.Somethin
She's making arrangements.I don't know what all.Something ab
She's making arrangements.I don't know what all.Something abou
She's making arrangements.I don't know what all.Something about
She's making arrangements.I don't know what all.Something about yo
She's making arrangements.I don't know what all.Something about you gi
She's making arrangements.I don't know what all.Something about you girl
She's making arrangements.I don't know what all.Something about you girls
I don't know what all.Something about you girls
I don't know what all.Something about you girlswi
I don't know what all.Something about you girlswith
I don't know what all.Something about you girlswith h
I don't know what all.Something about you girlswith her
Something about you girlswith her
Something about you girlswith heran
Something about you girlswith herand
Something about you girlswith herand th
Something about you girlswith herand the bo
Something about you girlswith herand the boys
Something about you girlswith herand the boys w
Something about you girlswith herand the boys wit
Something about you girlswith herand the boys with...
with herand the boys with...
with herand the boys with...wi
with herand the boys with...with
with herand the boys with...with a f
with herand the boys with...with a fam
with herand the boys with...with a famil
with herand the boys with...with a family
with herand the boys with...with a family not
with herand the boys with...with a family not to
with herand the boys with...with a family not too
with herand the boys with...with a family not too fa
with herand the boys with...with a family not too far aw
with herand the boys with...with a family not too far away
with herand the boys with...with a family not too far away.
and the boys with...with a family not too far away.
and the boys with...with a family not too far away.>>
and the boys with...with a family not too far away.>> B
and the boys with...with a family not too far away.>> But--
with a family not too far away.>> But--
>> No "buts," girl.What happens in life isn't
>> No "buts," girl.What happens in life isn'tal
>> No "buts," girl.What happens in life isn'talwa
>> No "buts," girl.What happens in life isn'talways
>> No "buts," girl.What happens in life isn'talways u
>> No "buts," girl.What happens in life isn'talways up to
>> No "buts," girl.What happens in life isn'talways up to u
>> No "buts," girl.What happens in life isn'talways up to us.
And
And th
And ther
And there'
And there's ne
And there's news
And there's news a
And there's news abo
And there's news about
And there's news aboutyo
And there's news aboutyou
And there's news aboutyou moth
And there's news aboutyou mother
And there's news aboutyou mother..
And there's news aboutyou mother...
And there's news aboutyou mother...an
And there's news aboutyou mother...and
And there's news aboutyou mother...and I'
And there's news aboutyou mother...and I'm af
And there's news aboutyou mother...and I'm afra
And there's news aboutyou mother...and I'm afraid
And there's news aboutyou mother...and I'm afraid i
And there's news aboutyou mother...and I'm afraid it's
And there's news aboutyou mother...and I'm afraid it's no
And there's news aboutyou mother...and I'm afraid it's not
And there's news aboutyou mother...and I'm afraid it's not go
And there's news aboutyou mother...and I'm afraid it's not good.
Th
They
They f
They fou
They found h
They found her
They found her.
They found her.>> W
They found her.>> Who
They found her.>> Who d
They found her.>> Who did
They found her.>> Who did?
They found her.>> Who did?Wher
They found her.>> Who did?Where?
>> Who did?Where?
>> Who did?Where?>>
>> Who did?Where?>> T
>> Who did?Where?>> The p
>> Who did?Where?>> The pol
>> Who did?Where?>> The polic
>> Who did?Where?>> The police,
>> Who did?Where?>> The police, up
>> Who did?Where?>> The police, up ar
>> Who did?Where?>> The police, up arou
>> Who did?Where?>> The police, up around
>> Who did?Where?>> The police, up around Bos
>> Who did?Where?>> The police, up around Bosto
>> Who did?Where?>> The police, up around Boston.
Where?>> The police, up around Boston.
Where?>> The police, up around Boston.They
Where?>> The police, up around Boston.They g
Where?>> The police, up around Boston.They got
Where?>> The police, up around Boston.They got h
Where?>> The police, up around Boston.They got her i
Where?>> The police, up around Boston.They got her in
>> The police, up around Boston.They got her in
>> The police, up around Boston.They got her insome
>> The police, up around Boston.They got her insome s
>> The police, up around Boston.They got her insome sta
>> The police, up around Boston.They got her insome state
>> The police, up around Boston.They got her insome state hos
>> The police, up around Boston.They got her insome state hospi
>> The police, up around Boston.They got her insome state hospita
>> The police, up around Boston.They got her insome state hospital.
They got her insome state hospital.
They got her insome state hospital.A
They got her insome state hospital.A me
They got her insome state hospital.A ment
They got her insome state hospital.A mental w
They got her insome state hospital.A mental war
They got her insome state hospital.A mental ward.
some state hospital.A mental ward.
some state hospital.A mental ward.Sh
some state hospital.A mental ward.She'
some state hospital.A mental ward.She's.
some state hospital.A mental ward.She's...
Yo
You
You kn
You know
You know wha
You know what
You know what ca
You know what cata
You know what catatoni
You know what catatonic
You know what catatonic me
You know what catatonic mean
You know what catatonic means?
>>
>> I
>> It me
>> It mean
>> It means
>> It means sh
>> It means she wo
>> It means she won'
>> It means she won't
>> It means she won'tresp
>> It means she won'trespon
>> It means she won'trespond
>> It means she won'trespond to
>> It means she won'trespond to any
>> It means she won'trespond to anyth
>> It means she won'trespond to anythin
>> It means she won'trespond to anything.
>> T
>> Tha
>> That'
>> That's
>> That's righ
>> That's right.
Yo
Your
Your m
Your mothe
Your mother.
Your mother...
We
Well
Well,
Well, she.
Well, she...
do
does
doesn'
doesn't
doesn't spea
doesn't speak,
doesn't speak, d
doesn't speak, doe
doesn't speak, doesn't
doesn't speak, doesn't s
doesn't speak, doesn't see
doesn't speak, doesn't seem
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto h
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hea
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear wh
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's s
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's said
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's said to
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's said to h
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's said to her
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's said to her,
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's said to her,wo
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's said to her,won'
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's said to her,won't
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's said to her,won't fe
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's said to her,won't feed h
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's said to her,won't feed her
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's said to her,won't feed herse
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's said to her,won't feed herself
doesn't speak, doesn't seemto hear what's said to her,won't feed herself.
to hear what's said to her,won't feed herself.
to hear what's said to her,won't feed herself.Wo
to hear what's said to her,won't feed herself.Won'
to hear what's said to her,won't feed herself.Won't mo
to hear what's said to her,won't feed herself.Won't move
to hear what's said to her,won't feed herself.Won't move a
to hear what's said to her,won't feed herself.Won't move at
to hear what's said to her,won't feed herself.Won't move at all.
won't feed herself.Won't move at all.
won't feed herself.Won't move at all.No
won't feed herself.Won't move at all.Noth
won't feed herself.Won't move at all.Nothin
won't feed herself.Won't move at all.Nothing.
Won't move at all.Nothing.
Won't move at all.Nothing.>>
Won't move at all.Nothing.>> A
Won't move at all.Nothing.>> Are t
Won't move at all.Nothing.>> Are the
Won't move at all.Nothing.>> Are they
Won't move at all.Nothing.>> Are they su
Won't move at all.Nothing.>> Are they sure i
Won't move at all.Nothing.>> Are they sure it'
Won't move at all.Nothing.>> Are they sure it's
Won't move at all.Nothing.>> Are they sure it's Ma
Won't move at all.Nothing.>> Are they sure it's Mama?
Th
They
They c
They cut
They cut her
They cut her h
They cut her hai
They cut her hair.
(w
(whi
(whimp
(whimperin
(whimpering)
(whimpering)Is
(whimpering)Is s
(whimpering)Is she
(whimpering)Is she gon
(whimpering)Is she gonna
(whimpering)Is she gonna g
(whimpering)Is she gonna get
(whimpering)Is she gonna get bet
(whimpering)Is she gonna get bette
(whimpering)Is she gonna get better?
>>
>> T
>> The
>> They
>> They don'
>> They don't
>> They don't th
>> They don't thin
>> They don't think so
>> They don't think so.
>>
>> Y
>> You
>> You mea
>> You mean
>> You mean ol
>> You mean old
>> You mean old lady
>> You mean old lady!
(t
(thu
(thund
(thunderin
(thundering)
Sh
She'
She'll
She'll get
She'll get b
She'll get bet
She'll get bette
She'll get better ma
She'll get better mayb
She'll get better maybe.
She'll get better maybe.I do
She'll get better maybe.I don'
She'll get better maybe.I don't
She'll get better maybe.I don't ca
She'll get better maybe.I don't care w
She'll get better maybe.I don't care wha
She'll get better maybe.I don't care what
She'll get better maybe.I don't care what th
She'll get better maybe.I don't care what they s
She'll get better maybe.I don't care what they say
She'll get better maybe.I don't care what they say.
She'll get better maybe.I don't care what they say.I
She'll get better maybe.I don't care what they say.I wo
She'll get better maybe.I don't care what they say.I won't
She'll get better maybe.I don't care what they say.I won't be
She'll get better maybe.I don't care what they say.I won't beli
She'll get better maybe.I don't care what they say.I won't believ
She'll get better maybe.I don't care what they say.I won't believe th
She'll get better maybe.I don't care what they say.I won't believe them
She'll get better maybe.I don't care what they say.I won't believe them.
I don't care what they say.I won't believe them.
I don't care what they say.I won't believe them.(t
I don't care what they say.I won't believe them.(thu
I don't care what they say.I won't believe them.(thund
I don't care what they say.I won't believe them.(thunderin
I don't care what they say.I won't believe them.(thundering)
I won't believe them.(thundering)
I won't believe them.(thundering)>>
I won't believe them.(thundering)>> S
I won't believe them.(thundering)>> Sorry
I won't believe them.(thundering)>> Sorry,
I won't believe them.(thundering)>> Sorry, Di
I won't believe them.(thundering)>> Sorry, Dice
I won't believe them.(thundering)>> Sorry, Dicey.
(thundering)>> Sorry, Dicey.
(thundering)>> Sorry, Dicey.>>
(thundering)>> Sorry, Dicey.>> M
(thundering)>> Sorry, Dicey.>> Me
(thundering)>> Sorry, Dicey.>> Me to
(thundering)>> Sorry, Dicey.>> Me too.
>> Sorry, Dicey.>> Me too.
>> Sorry, Dicey.>> Me too.I'm
>> Sorry, Dicey.>> Me too.I'm so
>> Sorry, Dicey.>> Me too.I'm sorr
>> Sorry, Dicey.>> Me too.I'm sorry
>> Sorry, Dicey.>> Me too.I'm sorry too.
♪
(w
(wat
(water
(water spl
(water splas
(water splashi
(water splashing
(water splashing)
>>
>> Y
>> You c
>> You can
>> You can h
>> You can hel
>> You can help me
>> You can help me.
>> You can help me.I
>> You can help me.I ne
>> You can help me.I need
>> You can help me.I need the
>> You can help me.I need the r
>> You can help me.I need the rip
>> You can help me.I need the ripe
>> You can help me.I need the ripe toma
>> You can help me.I need the ripe tomato
>> You can help me.I need the ripe tomatoes
>> You can help me.I need the ripe tomatoespi
>> You can help me.I need the ripe tomatoespick
>> You can help me.I need the ripe tomatoespicked
>> You can help me.I need the ripe tomatoespicked.
I need the ripe tomatoespicked.
I need the ripe tomatoespicked.An
I need the ripe tomatoespicked.And
I need the ripe tomatoespicked.And th
I need the ripe tomatoespicked.And the sq
I need the ripe tomatoespicked.And the squa
I need the ripe tomatoespicked.And the squash
I need the ripe tomatoespicked.And the squashes
I need the ripe tomatoespicked.And the squashes and
I need the ripe tomatoespicked.And the squashes and c
I need the ripe tomatoespicked.And the squashes and cuk
I need the ripe tomatoespicked.And the squashes and cukes
picked.And the squashes and cukes
picked.And the squashes and cukesar
picked.And the squashes and cukesare
picked.And the squashes and cukesare al
picked.And the squashes and cukesare alon
picked.And the squashes and cukesare along th
picked.And the squashes and cukesare along the
picked.And the squashes and cukesare along the gr
picked.And the squashes and cukesare along the grou
picked.And the squashes and cukesare along the ground.
And the squashes and cukesare along the ground.
And the squashes and cukesare along the ground.Th
And the squashes and cukesare along the ground.The
And the squashes and cukesare along the ground.The dr
And the squashes and cukesare along the ground.The drai
And the squashes and cukesare along the ground.The drainage
And the squashes and cukesare along the ground.The drainage i
And the squashes and cukesare along the ground.The drainage is
And the squashes and cukesare along the ground.The drainage is so
And the squashes and cukesare along the ground.The drainage is so bad
are along the ground.The drainage is so bad
are along the ground.The drainage is so badth
are along the ground.The drainage is so badthey
are along the ground.The drainage is so badthey'l
are along the ground.The drainage is so badthey'll ro
are along the ground.The drainage is so badthey'll rot
are along the ground.The drainage is so badthey'll rot if
are along the ground.The drainage is so badthey'll rot if y
are along the ground.The drainage is so badthey'll rot if you d
are along the ground.The drainage is so badthey'll rot if you don
are along the ground.The drainage is so badthey'll rot if you don't
The drainage is so badthey'll rot if you don't
The drainage is so badthey'll rot if you don'tge
The drainage is so badthey'll rot if you don'tget
The drainage is so badthey'll rot if you don'tget 'e
The drainage is so badthey'll rot if you don'tget 'em in
The drainage is so badthey'll rot if you don'tget 'em in.
they'll rot if you don'tget 'em in.
they'll rot if you don'tget 'em in.>>
they'll rot if you don'tget 'em in.>> D
they'll rot if you don'tget 'em in.>> Dic
they'll rot if you don'tget 'em in.>> Dicey
they'll rot if you don'tget 'em in.>> Dicey, it
they'll rot if you don'tget 'em in.>> Dicey, it's
they'll rot if you don'tget 'em in.>> Dicey, it's r
they'll rot if you don'tget 'em in.>> Dicey, it's rea
they'll rot if you don'tget 'em in.>> Dicey, it's really
get 'em in.>> Dicey, it's really
get 'em in.>> Dicey, it's reallywe
get 'em in.>> Dicey, it's reallywet
get 'em in.>> Dicey, it's reallywet ou
get 'em in.>> Dicey, it's reallywet out
get 'em in.>> Dicey, it's reallywet out here
get 'em in.>> Dicey, it's reallywet out here!
>> Dicey, it's reallywet out here!
>> Dicey, it's reallywet out here!(l
>> Dicey, it's reallywet out here!(lau
>> Dicey, it's reallywet out here!(laugh
>> Dicey, it's reallywet out here!(laughing)
>>
>> G
>> Giv
>> Give th
>> Give them
>> Give them h
>> Give them her
>> Give them here,
>> Give them here,I'
>> Give them here,I'll
>> Give them here,I'll tak
>> Give them here,I'll take
>> Give them here,I'll take 'e
>> Give them here,I'll take 'em.
(gig
(giggl
(gigglin
(giggling)
(giggling)>>
(giggling)>> W
(giggling)>> Whee!
(giggling)>> Whee!(l
(giggling)>> Whee!(lau
(giggling)>> Whee!(laugh
(giggling)>> Whee!(laughing)
>> C
>> Cat
>> Catch
>> Catch!
>>
>> W
>> Whoo!
>>
>> N
>> No!
>> I
>> Is
>> Is th
>> Is that
>> Is that the
>> Is that the l
>> Is that the las
>> Is that the last
>> Is that the last one?
Wh
Who
Who ne
Who needs
Who needs a
Who needs a to
Who needs a towe
Who needs a towel?
Who needs a towel?>>
Who needs a towel?>> I
Who needs a towel?>> I do.
Who needs a towel?>> I do.>> W
Who needs a towel?>> I do.>> Wip
Who needs a towel?>> I do.>> Wipe
Who needs a towel?>> I do.>> Wipe yo
Who needs a towel?>> I do.>> Wipe your f
Who needs a towel?>> I do.>> Wipe your fee
Who needs a towel?>> I do.>> Wipe your feet.
>> I do.>> Wipe your feet.
>> I do.>> Wipe your feet.Yo
>> I do.>> Wipe your feet.You
>> I do.>> Wipe your feet.You go
>> I do.>> Wipe your feet.You go ahe
>> I do.>> Wipe your feet.You go ahead
>> I do.>> Wipe your feet.You go ahead n
>> I do.>> Wipe your feet.You go ahead now
>> I do.>> Wipe your feet.You go ahead now.
>> Wipe your feet.You go ahead now.
>> Wipe your feet.You go ahead now.>>
>> Wipe your feet.You go ahead now.>> Y
>> Wipe your feet.You go ahead now.>> Yay.
(d
(doo
(door
(door crea
(door creaki
(door creaking
(door creaking)
(g
(gla
(glass
(glass cla
(glass clank
(glass clanks)
(glass clanks)>>
(glass clanks)>> C
(glass clanks)>> Can
(glass clanks)>> Can't
(glass clanks)>> Can't you
(glass clanks)>> Can't you e
(glass clanks)>> Can't you eve
(glass clanks)>> Can't you even
(glass clanks)>> Can't you evenfe
(glass clanks)>> Can't you evenfeed
(glass clanks)>> Can't you evenfeed you
(glass clanks)>> Can't you evenfeed yours
(glass clanks)>> Can't you evenfeed yoursel
(glass clanks)>> Can't you evenfeed yourself?
>> Can't you evenfeed yourself?
>> Can't you evenfeed yourself?Mop
>> Can't you evenfeed yourself?Mop it
>> Can't you evenfeed yourself?Mop it u
>> Can't you evenfeed yourself?Mop it up.
Wh
What
What's t
What's the
What's the m
What's the mat
What's the matter
What's the matter wi
What's the matter with
What's the matter with y
What's the matter with you?
What's the matter with you?An
What's the matter with you?Answ
What's the matter with you?Answer
What's the matter with you?Answer m
What's the matter with you?Answer me!
Or
Or i
Or is th
Or is this
Or is this t
Or is this the
Or is this the way
Or is this the way s
Or is this the way she
Or is this the way sheusua
Or is this the way sheusuall
Or is this the way sheusually
Or is this the way sheusually is
Or is this the way sheusually is and
Or is this the way sheusually is and i
Or is this the way sheusually is and it'
Or is this the way sheusually is and it's
Or is this the way sheusually is and it's all
Or is this the way sheusually is and it's all be
Or is this the way sheusually is and it's all been
Or is this the way sheusually is and it's all beenan
Or is this the way sheusually is and it's all beenan a
Or is this the way sheusually is and it's all beenan act
Or is this the way sheusually is and it's all beenan act up
Or is this the way sheusually is and it's all beenan act up un
Or is this the way sheusually is and it's all beenan act up unti
Or is this the way sheusually is and it's all beenan act up until
Or is this the way sheusually is and it's all beenan act up until now?
usually is and it's all beenan act up until now?
usually is and it's all beenan act up until now?>>
usually is and it's all beenan act up until now?>> S
usually is and it's all beenan act up until now?>> Som
usually is and it's all beenan act up until now?>> Somethi
usually is and it's all beenan act up until now?>> Something
usually is and it's all beenan act up until now?>> Something's
usually is and it's all beenan act up until now?>> Something's w
usually is and it's all beenan act up until now?>> Something's wrong
an act up until now?>> Something's wrong
an act up until now?>> Something's wrongwi
an act up until now?>> Something's wrongwith
an act up until now?>> Something's wrongwith h
an act up until now?>> Something's wrongwith her a
an act up until now?>> Something's wrongwith her arm
an act up until now?>> Something's wrongwith her arm.
>>
>> W
>> What'
>> What's
>> What's wr
>> What's wron
>> What's wrong?
>> What's wrong?>>
>> What's wrong?>> I
>> What's wrong?>> I don
>> What's wrong?>> I don't
>> What's wrong?>> I don't k
>> What's wrong?>> I don't kno
>> What's wrong?>> I don't know.
>> What's wrong?>> I don't know.She
>> What's wrong?>> I don't know.She sa
>> What's wrong?>> I don't know.She says
>> What's wrong?>> I don't know.She says i
>> What's wrong?>> I don't know.She says it hu
>> What's wrong?>> I don't know.She says it hurt
>> What's wrong?>> I don't know.She says it hurts.
>> I don't know.She says it hurts.
>> I don't know.She says it hurts.>>
>> I don't know.She says it hurts.>> H
>> I don't know.She says it hurts.>> How
>> I don't know.She says it hurts.>> How l
>> I don't know.She says it hurts.>> How long
>> I don't know.She says it hurts.>> How long ha
>> I don't know.She says it hurts.>> How long has
>> I don't know.She says it hurts.>> How long has it
>> I don't know.She says it hurts.>> How long has it hur
>> I don't know.She says it hurts.>> How long has it hurt?
She says it hurts.>> How long has it hurt?
She says it hurts.>> How long has it hurt?>> S
She says it hurts.>> How long has it hurt?>> Sin
She says it hurts.>> How long has it hurt?>> Since
She says it hurts.>> How long has it hurt?>> Since y
She says it hurts.>> How long has it hurt?>> Since yeste
She says it hurts.>> How long has it hurt?>> Since yesterd
She says it hurts.>> How long has it hurt?>> Since yesterday
She says it hurts.>> How long has it hurt?>> Since yesterday m
She says it hurts.>> How long has it hurt?>> Since yesterday morni
She says it hurts.>> How long has it hurt?>> Since yesterday morning
She says it hurts.>> How long has it hurt?>> Since yesterday morning.
>>
>> W
>> Why d
>> Why did
>> Why didn'
>> Why didn't
>> Why didn't you
>> Why didn't you sa
>> Why didn't you say
>> Why didn't you say so
>> Why didn't you say someth
>> Why didn't you say somethin
>> Why didn't you say something?
Come
Come o
Come on,
Come on, c
Come on, come
Come on, come on
Come on, come on.
Come on, come on.Co
Come on, come on.Come
Come on, come on.Come w
Come on, come on.Come wit
Come on, come on.Come with me
Come on, come on.Come with me.
Co
Come
Come o
Come on,
Come on, com
Come on, come
Come on, come wi
Come on, come with
Come on, come with me.
Mo
Most
Most lik
Most likel
Most likely
Most likely ju
Most likely just
Most likely justa
Most likely justa pu
Most likely justa pulled
Most likely justa pulled t
Most likely justa pulled ten
Most likely justa pulled tendo
Most likely justa pulled tendon.
Most likely justa pulled tendon.Yo
Most likely justa pulled tendon.You'
Most likely justa pulled tendon.You'd
Most likely justa pulled tendon.You'd real
Most likely justa pulled tendon.You'd really
Most likely justa pulled tendon.You'd really b
Most likely justa pulled tendon.You'd really be
Most likely justa pulled tendon.You'd really be yell
Most likely justa pulled tendon.You'd really be yellin
Most likely justa pulled tendon.You'd really be yelling
a pulled tendon.You'd really be yelling
a pulled tendon.You'd really be yellingif
a pulled tendon.You'd really be yellingif y
a pulled tendon.You'd really be yellingif you b
a pulled tendon.You'd really be yellingif you bro
a pulled tendon.You'd really be yellingif you broke
a pulled tendon.You'd really be yellingif you broke i
a pulled tendon.You'd really be yellingif you broke it.
You'd really be yellingif you broke it.
You'd really be yellingif you broke it.Un
You'd really be yellingif you broke it.Unle
You'd really be yellingif you broke it.Unless
You'd really be yellingif you broke it.Unless y
You'd really be yellingif you broke it.Unless you y
You'd really be yellingif you broke it.Unless you yel
You'd really be yellingif you broke it.Unless you yell
You'd really be yellingif you broke it.Unless you yell as
You'd really be yellingif you broke it.Unless you yell as muc
You'd really be yellingif you broke it.Unless you yell as much
if you broke it.Unless you yell as much
if you broke it.Unless you yell as muchas
if you broke it.Unless you yell as muchas y
if you broke it.Unless you yell as muchas you
if you broke it.Unless you yell as muchas you tal
if you broke it.Unless you yell as muchas you talk.
No
Now
Now pl
Now please
Now please s
Now please sta
Now please stand
Now please stand sti
Now please stand still
Now please stand still w
Now please stand still whe
Now please stand still when
Now please stand still whenso
Now please stand still whensome
Now please stand still whensomebody
Now please stand still whensomebody's
Now please stand still whensomebody's t
Now please stand still whensomebody's try
Now please stand still whensomebody's trying
Now please stand still whensomebody's trying to
Now please stand still whensomebody's trying to h
Now please stand still whensomebody's trying to hel
Now please stand still whensomebody's trying to help yo
Now please stand still whensomebody's trying to help you.
>>
>> Y
>> Yan
>> Yanking
>> Yanking o
>> Yanking on
>> Yanking on th
>> Yanking on that h
>> Yanking on that hon
>> Yanking on that honey
>> Yanking on that honey s
>> Yanking on that honey suckl
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it d
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't s
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't sur
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surpris
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise me
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise me.
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise me.Why
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise me.Why yo
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise me.Why you
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise me.Why you we
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise me.Why you were o
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out t
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out the
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there a
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at al
>> Yanking on that honey suckle,it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at all
it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at all
it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at allth
it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at allthis
it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at allthis m
it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at allthis morni
it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at allthis morning
it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at allthis morning,
it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at allthis morning, is
it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at allthis morning, is bey
it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyon
it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond
it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me
it doesn't surprise me.Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me.
Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me.
Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me.Th
Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me.Then
Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me.Then y
Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me.Then you d
Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me.Then you don
Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me.Then you don't
Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me.Then you don't s
Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me.Then you don't say a
Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me.Then you don't say any
Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me.Then you don't say anyth
Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me.Then you don't say anythin
Why you were out there at allthis morning, is beyond me.Then you don't say anything,
this morning, is beyond me.Then you don't say anything,
this morning, is beyond me.Then you don't say anything,do
this morning, is beyond me.Then you don't say anything,do y
this morning, is beyond me.Then you don't say anything,do you
this morning, is beyond me.Then you don't say anything,do you?
Then you don't say anything,do you?
Then you don't say anything,do you?>> S
Then you don't say anything,do you?>> She
Then you don't say anything,do you?>> She d
Then you don't say anything,do you?>> She doe
Then you don't say anything,do you?>> She does.
do you?>> She does.
do you?>> She does.If
do you?>> She does.If y
do you?>> She does.If you
do you?>> She does.If you l
do you?>> She does.If you liste
do you?>> She does.If you listen.
>> She does.If you listen.
>> She does.If you listen.>>
>> She does.If you listen.>> D
>> She does.If you listen.>> Don
>> She does.If you listen.>> Don't
>> She does.If you listen.>> Don't you
>> She does.If you listen.>> Don't you s
>> She does.If you listen.>> Don't you see
>> She does.If you listen.>> Don't you see I
>> She does.If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm t
>> She does.If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm try
>> She does.If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm tryin
>> She does.If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm trying
>> She does.If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm trying to
If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm trying to
If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm trying toge
If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm trying toget
If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm trying toget your
If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm trying toget your s
If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm trying toget your sis
If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm trying toget your siste
If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm trying toget your sister to
If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm trying toget your sister to s
If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm trying toget your sister to spe
If you listen.>> Don't you see I'm trying toget your sister to speak
>> Don't you see I'm trying toget your sister to speak
>> Don't you see I'm trying toget your sister to speakfo
>> Don't you see I'm trying toget your sister to speakfor
>> Don't you see I'm trying toget your sister to speakfor he
>> Don't you see I'm trying toget your sister to speakfor hers
>> Don't you see I'm trying toget your sister to speakfor herself?
get your sister to speakfor herself?
get your sister to speakfor herself?>>
get your sister to speakfor herself?>> W
get your sister to speakfor herself?>> Why
get your sister to speakfor herself?>> Why d
get your sister to speakfor herself?>> Why don't
get your sister to speakfor herself?>> Why don't y
get your sister to speakfor herself?>> Why don't you
get your sister to speakfor herself?>> Why don't you j
get your sister to speakfor herself?>> Why don't you just
get your sister to speakfor herself?>> Why don't you just le
get your sister to speakfor herself?>> Why don't you just let
get your sister to speakfor herself?>> Why don't you just let me
get your sister to speakfor herself?>> Why don't you just let me--
for herself?>> Why don't you just let me--
Yo
Your
Your c
Your cousi
Your cousin
Your cousin in
Your cousin in B
Your cousin in Bridg
Your cousin in Bridgep
Your cousin in Bridgepor
Your cousin in Bridgeport,
Your cousin in Bridgeport,sh
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she thin
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she thinks
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she thinks y
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she thinks you
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she thinks you're
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she thinks you're re
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she thinks you're reta
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she thinks you're retard
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she thinks you're retarded.
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she thinks you're retarded.Is
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she thinks you're retarded.Is i
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she thinks you're retarded.Is it tr
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she thinks you're retarded.Is it true
Your cousin in Bridgeport,she thinks you're retarded.Is it true?
I'
I'm
I'm as
I'm aski
I'm asking,
I'm asking, Ma
I'm asking, Mayb
I'm asking, Maybet
I'm asking, Maybeth.
I'
I'm
I'm as
I'm asking
I'm asking y
I'm asking you
I'm asking you..
I'm asking you...
I'm asking you...is i
I'm asking you...is it
I'm asking you...is it tr
I'm asking you...is it true
I'm asking you...is it true?
>>
>> I
>> I d
>> I don't
>> I don't t
>> I don't thi
>> I don't think
>> I don't think I a
>> I don't think I am.
>> I don't think I am.I
>> I don't think I am.I do
>> I don't think I am.I don'
>> I don't think I am.I don't kn
>> I don't think I am.I don't know
>> I don't think I am.I don't know j
>> I don't think I am.I don't know jus
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just wh
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what i
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it mean
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it means.
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it means.Bu
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it means.But
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it means.But if
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it means.But if it'
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it means.But if it's
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it means.But if it's su
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it means.But if it's such
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a b
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad t
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thi
>> I don't think I am.I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thing
I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thing
I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thingto
I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thingto b
I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thingto be,
I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thingto be, why
I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thingto be, why d
I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thingto be, why do
I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thingto be, why do yo
I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thingto be, why do you wa
I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thingto be, why do you want
I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thingto be, why do you want t
I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thingto be, why do you want to
I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thingto be, why do you want to know
I don't know just what it means.But if it's such a bad thingto be, why do you want to know?
(t
(thu
(thunder
(thunderin
(thundering)
(thundering)>>
(thundering)>> Y
(thundering)>> You
(thundering)>> You'll
(thundering)>> You'll ha
(thundering)>> You'll have
(thundering)>> You'll have t
(thundering)>> You'll have to ta
(thundering)>> You'll have to take
(thundering)>> You'll have to take i
(thundering)>> You'll have to take it
(thundering)>> You'll have to take it easy
(thundering)>> You'll have to take it easyfo
(thundering)>> You'll have to take it easyfor
(thundering)>> You'll have to take it easyfor a
(thundering)>> You'll have to take it easyfor a coup
(thundering)>> You'll have to take it easyfor a couple
(thundering)>> You'll have to take it easyfor a couple o
(thundering)>> You'll have to take it easyfor a couple of
(thundering)>> You'll have to take it easyfor a couple of week
(thundering)>> You'll have to take it easyfor a couple of weeks,
(thundering)>> You'll have to take it easyfor a couple of weeks, o
(thundering)>> You'll have to take it easyfor a couple of weeks, oka
(thundering)>> You'll have to take it easyfor a couple of weeks, okay?
Me
Me,
Me, my
Me, myself
Me, myself,
Me, myself, I
Me, myself, I sh
Me, myself, I shut u
Me, myself, I shut up
Me, myself, I shut up mo
Me, myself, I shut up more
Me, myself, I shut up moreti
Me, myself, I shut up moretime
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I c
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I car
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I care to
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I care to r
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I care to rem
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I care to remem
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I care to remember.
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I care to remember.(s
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I care to remember.(she
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I care to remember.(sheet
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I care to remember.(sheet r
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I care to remember.(sheet rippi
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I care to remember.(sheet ripping
Me, myself, I shut up moretimes than I care to remember.(sheet ripping)
times than I care to remember.(sheet ripping)
times than I care to remember.(sheet ripping)Mo
times than I care to remember.(sheet ripping)Most
times than I care to remember.(sheet ripping)Mostly
times than I care to remember.(sheet ripping)Mostly jus
times than I care to remember.(sheet ripping)Mostly just
times than I care to remember.(sheet ripping)Mostly just af
times than I care to remember.(sheet ripping)Mostly just afra
times than I care to remember.(sheet ripping)Mostly just afraid,
times than I care to remember.(sheet ripping)Mostly just afraid, I
times than I care to remember.(sheet ripping)Mostly just afraid, I gu
times than I care to remember.(sheet ripping)Mostly just afraid, I gues
times than I care to remember.(sheet ripping)Mostly just afraid, I guess.
If
If y
If you
If you don
If you don't
If you don't s
If you don't spe
If you don't speak u
If you don't speak up
If you don't speak upwh
If you don't speak upwhen
If you don't speak upwhen y
If you don't speak upwhen you s
If you don't speak upwhen you sho
If you don't speak upwhen you shoul
If you don't speak upwhen you should,
If you don't speak upwhen you should, you
If you don't speak upwhen you should, you m
If you don't speak upwhen you should, you mig
If you don't speak upwhen you should, you might
If you don't speak upwhen you should, you mightne
If you don't speak upwhen you should, you mightneve
If you don't speak upwhen you should, you mightnever
If you don't speak upwhen you should, you mightnever get
If you don't speak upwhen you should, you mightnever get th
If you don't speak upwhen you should, you mightnever get the
If you don't speak upwhen you should, you mightnever get the ch
If you don't speak upwhen you should, you mightnever get the chance
If you don't speak upwhen you should, you mightnever get the chance t
If you don't speak upwhen you should, you mightnever get the chance to
when you should, you mightnever get the chance to
when you should, you mightnever get the chance toma
when you should, you mightnever get the chance tomake
when you should, you mightnever get the chance tomake i
when you should, you mightnever get the chance tomake it ri
when you should, you mightnever get the chance tomake it righ
when you should, you mightnever get the chance tomake it right.
>>
>> D
>> Did
>> Did y
>> Did you l
>> Did you lov
>> Did you love
>> Did you love ou
>> Did you love our ma
>> Did you love our mama
>> Did you love our mama?
>>
>> Y
>> Yes.
>> Yes.Ye
>> Yes.Yes,
>> Yes.Yes, I
>> Yes.Yes, I did
>> Yes.Yes, I did.
>> Yes.Yes, I did.>>
>> Yes.Yes, I did.>> I
>> Yes.Yes, I did.>> I'm
>> Yes.Yes, I did.>> I'm gla
>> Yes.Yes, I did.>> I'm glad.
>> W
>> Wel
>> Well,
>> Well, t
>> Well, that'
>> Well, that's
>> Well, that's al
>> Well, that's all
>> Well, that's all righ
>> Well, that's all right
>> Well, that's all right th
>> Well, that's all right then
>> Well, that's all right then.
Th
Than
Thank
Thank you.
>>
>> I
>> It'
>> It's ok
>> It's okay
>> It's okay,
>> It's okay, Di
>> It's okay, Dicey.
>> It's okay, Dicey.I'm
>> It's okay, Dicey.I'm be
>> It's okay, Dicey.I'm bett
>> It's okay, Dicey.I'm better
>> It's okay, Dicey.I'm better now
>> It's okay, Dicey.I'm better now.
>>
>> W
>> Wha
>> What ar
>> What are
>> What are yo
>> What are your
>> What are your pla
>> What are your plans
>> What are your plansfo
>> What are your plansfor
>> What are your plansfor th
>> What are your plansfor the da
>> What are your plansfor the day?
>> What are your plansfor the day?>> C
>> What are your plansfor the day?>> Cle
>> What are your plansfor the day?>> Clean
>> What are your plansfor the day?>> Clean o
>> What are your plansfor the day?>> Clean out t
>> What are your plansfor the day?>> Clean out the
>> What are your plansfor the day?>> Clean out the b
>> What are your plansfor the day?>> Clean out the bar
>> What are your plansfor the day?>> Clean out the barn.
for the day?>> Clean out the barn.
for the day?>> Clean out the barn.>>
for the day?>> Clean out the barn.>> N
for the day?>> Clean out the barn.>> No, n
for the day?>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not
for the day?>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not w
for the day?>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not wit
for the day?>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without
for the day?>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without s
for the day?>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without sun
for the day?>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without sunli
for the day?>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without sunlight.
>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without sunlight.
>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without sunlight.It's
>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without sunlight.It's a
>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without sunlight.It's as
>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without sunlight.It's as da
>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without sunlight.It's as dark a
>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without sunlight.It's as dark as
>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without sunlight.It's as dark as a
>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without sunlight.It's as dark as a to
>> Clean out the barn.>> No, not without sunlight.It's as dark as a tomb
>> No, not without sunlight.It's as dark as a tomb
>> No, not without sunlight.It's as dark as a tombin
>> No, not without sunlight.It's as dark as a tombin t
>> No, not without sunlight.It's as dark as a tombin the
>> No, not without sunlight.It's as dark as a tombin there
>> No, not without sunlight.It's as dark as a tombin there.
It's as dark as a tombin there.
It's as dark as a tombin there.>>
It's as dark as a tombin there.>> W
It's as dark as a tombin there.>> We'
It's as dark as a tombin there.>> We'll
It's as dark as a tombin there.>> We'll was
It's as dark as a tombin there.>> We'll wash
It's as dark as a tombin there.>> We'll wash wi
It's as dark as a tombin there.>> We'll wash wind
It's as dark as a tombin there.>> We'll wash windows.
in there.>> We'll wash windows.
in there.>> We'll wash windows.>>
in there.>> We'll wash windows.>> I
in there.>> We'll wash windows.>> In
in there.>> We'll wash windows.>> In th
in there.>> We'll wash windows.>> In the ra
in there.>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain
in there.>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain?
>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain?
>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain?>>
>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain?>> I
>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain?>> It'
>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain?>> It's no
>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain?>> It's not
>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain?>> It's not ra
>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain?>> It's not rain
>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain?>> It's not raining
>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain?>> It's not raining in
>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain?>> It's not raining insi
>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain?>> It's not raining inside
>> We'll wash windows.>> In the rain?>> It's not raining inside.
>>
>> I
>> I c
>> I can u
>> I can use
>> I can use s
>> I can use som
>> I can use some he
>> I can use some help
>> I can use some helpin
>> I can use some helpin t
>> I can use some helpin the
>> I can use some helpin the kit
>> I can use some helpin the kitch
>> I can use some helpin the kitchen
>> I can use some helpin the kitchen.
>>
>> ♪
>> ♪ L
>> ♪ Lost
>> ♪ Lost my
>> ♪ Lost my p
>> ♪ Lost my par
>> ♪ Lost my partner
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ W
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ Wha
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I d
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I do?
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I do? ♪
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I do? ♪♪
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ S
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to m
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my Lou
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my d
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my dar
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin'
>> ♪ Lost my partner ♪♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪
♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪
♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪
♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ S
♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ Skip,
♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ Skip, s
♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ Skip, ski
♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ Skip, skip
♪ What'll I do? ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ S
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Ski
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to m
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lo
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ S
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Ski
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip,
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, ski
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ S
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to m
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ S
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Ski
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip,
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, ski
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ S
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Ski
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to m
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lo
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ S
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Ski
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to m
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lo
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my d
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my dar
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darli
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin'
♪ Skip, skip ♪♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll ge
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get an
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get anothe
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get another
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get another on
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get another one
♪ Skip to my Lou ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ P
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prett
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettie
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier th
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than y
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'l
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll ge
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get an
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get anot
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another on
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ P
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prett
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettie
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier th
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than y
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll ge
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get an
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get anothe
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another on
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ P
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prett
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettie
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier th
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than y
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ S
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Ski
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to m
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to my
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to my Lo
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my d
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my dar
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darli
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin'
♪ I'll get another one ♪♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>>
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>> S
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>> Sammy
♪ Prettier than you ♪♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>> Sammy?
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>> Sammy?
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>> Sammy?Yo
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>> Sammy?You
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>> Sammy?You al
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>> Sammy?You almost
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>> Sammy?You almost d
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>> Sammy?You almost don
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>> Sammy?You almost done
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>> Sammy?You almost done up h
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>> Sammy?You almost done up her
♪ Skip to my Lou my darlin' ♪>> Sammy?You almost done up here?
(b
(buc
(bucket
(bucket cl
(bucket clan
(bucket clanks
(bucket clanks)
Sa
Samm
Sammy?
Ha
Have
Have y
Have you
Have you see
Have you seen
Have you seen Sa
Have you seen Samm
Have you seen Sammy?
Have you seen Sammy?>>
Have you seen Sammy?>> H
Have you seen Sammy?>> He
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ra
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran th
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran thro
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran throug
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran through
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran through awhi
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran through awhile
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran through awhile b
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran through awhile bac
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran through awhile back.
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran through awhile back.More
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran through awhile back.More t
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran through awhile back.More tha
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran through awhile back.More than
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran through awhile back.More than an h
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran through awhile back.More than an hou
Have you seen Sammy?>> He ran through awhile back.More than an hour.
>> He ran through awhile back.More than an hour.
>> He ran through awhile back.More than an hour.Di
>> He ran through awhile back.More than an hour.Didn
>> He ran through awhile back.More than an hour.Didn't h
>> He ran through awhile back.More than an hour.Didn't he
>> He ran through awhile back.More than an hour.Didn't he sa
>> He ran through awhile back.More than an hour.Didn't he say
>> He ran through awhile back.More than an hour.Didn't he say wher
>> He ran through awhile back.More than an hour.Didn't he say where
More than an hour.Didn't he say where
More than an hour.Didn't he say wherehe w
More than an hour.Didn't he say wherehe was
More than an hour.Didn't he say wherehe was g
More than an hour.Didn't he say wherehe was goi
More than an hour.Didn't he say wherehe was going?
(c
(cho
(choppin
(chopping)
(chopping)(pia
(chopping)(piano
(chopping)(piano p
(chopping)(piano pla
(chopping)(piano playing
(chopping)(piano playing)
(chopping)(piano playing)>> W
(chopping)(piano playing)>> Wha
(chopping)(piano playing)>> What
(chopping)(piano playing)>> What ar
(chopping)(piano playing)>> What are yo
(chopping)(piano playing)>> What are you
(chopping)(piano playing)>> What are you do
(chopping)(piano playing)>> What are you doin
(chopping)(piano playing)>> What are you doing?
(piano playing)>> What are you doing?
(piano playing)>> What are you doing?Yo
(piano playing)>> What are you doing?You'
(piano playing)>> What are you doing?You're
(piano playing)>> What are you doing?You're s
(piano playing)>> What are you doing?You're suppo
(piano playing)>> What are you doing?You're suppose
(piano playing)>> What are you doing?You're supposed
(piano playing)>> What are you doing?You're supposed to
(piano playing)>> What are you doing?You're supposed to be
>> What are you doing?You're supposed to be
>> What are you doing?You're supposed to bewa
>> What are you doing?You're supposed to bewash
>> What are you doing?You're supposed to bewashin
>> What are you doing?You're supposed to bewashing wi
>> What are you doing?You're supposed to bewashing wind
>> What are you doing?You're supposed to bewashing window
>> What are you doing?You're supposed to bewashing windows.
You're supposed to bewashing windows.
You're supposed to bewashing windows.>>
You're supposed to bewashing windows.>> W
You're supposed to bewashing windows.>> We'
You're supposed to bewashing windows.>> We're
You're supposed to bewashing windows.>> We're fin
You're supposed to bewashing windows.>> We're finis
You're supposed to bewashing windows.>> We're finishe
You're supposed to bewashing windows.>> We're finished.
washing windows.>> We're finished.
washing windows.>> We're finished.>> W
washing windows.>> We're finished.>> Wel
washing windows.>> We're finished.>> Well,
washing windows.>> We're finished.>> Well, d
washing windows.>> We're finished.>> Well, do th
washing windows.>> We're finished.>> Well, do them
washing windows.>> We're finished.>> Well, do them a
washing windows.>> We're finished.>> Well, do them aga
washing windows.>> We're finished.>> Well, do them again.
>> We're finished.>> Well, do them again.
>> We're finished.>> Well, do them again.We
>> We're finished.>> Well, do them again.We g
>> We're finished.>> Well, do them again.We got
>> We're finished.>> Well, do them again.We gotta
>> We're finished.>> Well, do them again.We gotta loo
>> We're finished.>> Well, do them again.We gotta look
>> We're finished.>> Well, do them again.We gotta look bu
>> We're finished.>> Well, do them again.We gotta look busy
>> We're finished.>> Well, do them again.We gotta look busy.
>> Well, do them again.We gotta look busy.
>> Well, do them again.We gotta look busy.Wh
>> Well, do them again.We gotta look busy.Wher
>> Well, do them again.We gotta look busy.Where's
>> Well, do them again.We gotta look busy.Where's Sa
>> Well, do them again.We gotta look busy.Where's Samm
>> Well, do them again.We gotta look busy.Where's Sammy?
We gotta look busy.Where's Sammy?
We gotta look busy.Where's Sammy?(yel
We gotta look busy.Where's Sammy?(yelli
We gotta look busy.Where's Sammy?(yelling
We gotta look busy.Where's Sammy?(yelling i
We gotta look busy.Where's Sammy?(yelling in th
We gotta look busy.Where's Sammy?(yelling in the
We gotta look busy.Where's Sammy?(yelling in the di
We gotta look busy.Where's Sammy?(yelling in the dist
We gotta look busy.Where's Sammy?(yelling in the distance
We gotta look busy.Where's Sammy?(yelling in the distance)
Where's Sammy?(yelling in the distance)
Where's Sammy?(yelling in the distance)>>
Where's Sammy?(yelling in the distance)>> Y
Where's Sammy?(yelling in the distance)>> You
Where's Sammy?(yelling in the distance)>> Your si
Where's Sammy?(yelling in the distance)>> Your sist
Where's Sammy?(yelling in the distance)>> Your sister
Where's Sammy?(yelling in the distance)>> Your sister w
Where's Sammy?(yelling in the distance)>> Your sister was w
Where's Sammy?(yelling in the distance)>> Your sister was wor
Where's Sammy?(yelling in the distance)>> Your sister was worri
Where's Sammy?(yelling in the distance)>> Your sister was worried
(yelling in the distance)>> Your sister was worried
(yelling in the distance)>> Your sister was worriedab
(yelling in the distance)>> Your sister was worriedabou
(yelling in the distance)>> Your sister was worriedabout yo
(yelling in the distance)>> Your sister was worriedabout you!
>> Your sister was worriedabout you!
>> Your sister was worriedabout you!>>
>> Your sister was worriedabout you!>> Y
>> Your sister was worriedabout you!>> You
>> Your sister was worriedabout you!>> You w
>> Your sister was worriedabout you!>> You weren
>> Your sister was worriedabout you!>> You weren't
>> Your sister was worriedabout you!>> You weren't,
>> Your sister was worriedabout you!>> You weren't, we
>> Your sister was worriedabout you!>> You weren't, were y
>> Your sister was worriedabout you!>> You weren't, were you
>> Your sister was worriedabout you!>> You weren't, were you?
about you!>> You weren't, were you?
about you!>> You weren't, were you?>> N
about you!>> You weren't, were you?>> No!
>> You weren't, were you?>> No!
>> You weren't, were you?>> No!>>
>> You weren't, were you?>> No!>> W
>> You weren't, were you?>> No!>> Why a
>> You weren't, were you?>> No!>> Why are
>> You weren't, were you?>> No!>> Why are y
>> You weren't, were you?>> No!>> Why are you
>> You weren't, were you?>> No!>> Why are you yel
>> You weren't, were you?>> No!>> Why are you yelli
>> You weren't, were you?>> No!>> Why are you yelling
>> No!>> Why are you yelling
>> No!>> Why are you yellingat m
>> No!>> Why are you yellingat me
>> No!>> Why are you yellingat me ab
>> No!>> Why are you yellingat me abou
>> No!>> Why are you yellingat me about it
>> No!>> Why are you yellingat me about it?
>> Why are you yellingat me about it?
>> Why are you yellingat me about it?>>
>> Why are you yellingat me about it?>> D
>> Why are you yellingat me about it?>> Don
>> Why are you yellingat me about it?>> Don't b
>> Why are you yellingat me about it?>> Don't be
>> Why are you yellingat me about it?>> Don't be ru
>> Why are you yellingat me about it?>> Don't be rude
>> Why are you yellingat me about it?>> Don't be rude, Sa
>> Why are you yellingat me about it?>> Don't be rude, Samm
>> Why are you yellingat me about it?>> Don't be rude, Sammy.
at me about it?>> Don't be rude, Sammy.
at me about it?>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> B
at me about it?>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But
at me about it?>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But i
at me about it?>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But it'
at me about it?>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But it's th
at me about it?>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But it's the
at me about it?>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But it's the tr
at me about it?>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But it's the trut
at me about it?>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But it's the truth.
>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But it's the truth.
>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But it's the truth.I'm
>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But it's the truth.I'm so
>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But it's the truth.I'm sorr
>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry,
>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry, Dic
>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry, Dicey
>> Don't be rude, Sammy.>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry, Dicey.
>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry, Dicey.
>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry, Dicey.I
>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry, Dicey.I go
>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry, Dicey.I got
>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tire
>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired
>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of
>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of w
>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windo
>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windows
>> But it's the truth.I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windows.
I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windows.
I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windows.So
I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windows.So I
I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windows.So I bai
I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windows.So I baile
I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windows.So I bailed
I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windows.So I bailed ou
I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windows.So I bailed out th
I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windows.So I bailed out the
I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windows.So I bailed out the bo
I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windows.So I bailed out the boat
I'm sorry, Dicey.I got tired of windows.So I bailed out the boats
I got tired of windows.So I bailed out the boats
I got tired of windows.So I bailed out the boatsso
I got tired of windows.So I bailed out the boatsso t
I got tired of windows.So I bailed out the boatsso the
I got tired of windows.So I bailed out the boatsso the mot
I got tired of windows.So I bailed out the boatsso the motor
I got tired of windows.So I bailed out the boatsso the motor w
I got tired of windows.So I bailed out the boatsso the motor won
I got tired of windows.So I bailed out the boatsso the motor won't
So I bailed out the boatsso the motor won't
So I bailed out the boatsso the motor won'tge
So I bailed out the boatsso the motor won'tget
So I bailed out the boatsso the motor won'tget co
So I bailed out the boatsso the motor won'tget covere
So I bailed out the boatsso the motor won'tget covered
So I bailed out the boatsso the motor won'tget covered wi
So I bailed out the boatsso the motor won'tget covered with
So I bailed out the boatsso the motor won'tget covered with wat
So I bailed out the boatsso the motor won'tget covered with water
So I bailed out the boatsso the motor won'tget covered with water.
so the motor won'tget covered with water.
so the motor won'tget covered with water.Th
so the motor won'tget covered with water.Then
so the motor won'tget covered with water.Then I
so the motor won'tget covered with water.Then I c
so the motor won'tget covered with water.Then I check
so the motor won'tget covered with water.Then I checked
so the motor won'tget covered with water.Then I checked t
so the motor won'tget covered with water.Then I checked the
so the motor won'tget covered with water.Then I checked the cra
so the motor won'tget covered with water.Then I checked the crab
so the motor won'tget covered with water.Then I checked the crab po
so the motor won'tget covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots
so the motor won'tget covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots.
get covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots.
get covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots.>>
get covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots.>> N
get covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots.>> Nex
get covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next ti
get covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time
get covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time,
get covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, te
get covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell m
get covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell me
get covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell me wh
get covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell me wher
get covered with water.Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell me where
Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell me where
Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell me whereyo
Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell me whereyou'
Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell me whereyou're
Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell me whereyou're g
Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell me whereyou're going
Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell me whereyou're going,
Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell me whereyou're going, ok
Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell me whereyou're going, okay
Then I checked the crab pots.>> Next time, tell me whereyou're going, okay?
>> Next time, tell me whereyou're going, okay?
>> Next time, tell me whereyou're going, okay?>>
>> Next time, tell me whereyou're going, okay?>> O
>> Next time, tell me whereyou're going, okay?>> Okay.
you're going, okay?>> Okay.
you're going, okay?>> Okay.An
you're going, okay?>> Okay.And
you're going, okay?>> Okay.And go
you're going, okay?>> Okay.And go get
you're going, okay?>> Okay.And go get o
you're going, okay?>> Okay.And go get on
you're going, okay?>> Okay.And go get on so
you're going, okay?>> Okay.And go get on some d
you're going, okay?>> Okay.And go get on some dry
you're going, okay?>> Okay.And go get on some dry c
you're going, okay?>> Okay.And go get on some dry clo
you're going, okay?>> Okay.And go get on some dry clothes
you're going, okay?>> Okay.And go get on some dry clothes.
>> Okay.And go get on some dry clothes.
>> Okay.And go get on some dry clothes.Hang
>> Okay.And go get on some dry clothes.Hang u
>> Okay.And go get on some dry clothes.Hang up
>> Okay.And go get on some dry clothes.Hang up th
>> Okay.And go get on some dry clothes.Hang up the to
>> Okay.And go get on some dry clothes.Hang up the towe
>> Okay.And go get on some dry clothes.Hang up the towel.
>>
>> D
>> Doe
>> Doesn't
>> Doesn't h
>> Doesn't he
>> Doesn't he ge
>> Doesn't he get pu
>> Doesn't he get puni
>> Doesn't he get punish
>> Doesn't he get punished
>> Doesn't he get punished?
>> Doesn't he get punished?>> N
>> Doesn't he get punished?>> No.
>> Doesn't he get punished?>> No.Wh
>> Doesn't he get punished?>> No.Why
>> Doesn't he get punished?>> No.Why shou
>> Doesn't he get punished?>> No.Why should
>> Doesn't he get punished?>> No.Why should h
>> Doesn't he get punished?>> No.Why should he?
>> No.Why should he?
>> No.Why should he?He w
>> No.Why should he?He was
>> No.Why should he?He was j
>> No.Why should he?He was jus
>> No.Why should he?He was just tr
>> No.Why should he?He was just tryi
>> No.Why should he?He was just trying
>> No.Why should he?He was just trying t
>> No.Why should he?He was just trying to he
>> No.Why should he?He was just trying to help
>> No.Why should he?He was just trying to help.
>> Y
>> You
>> You'l
>> You'll
>> You'll ruin
>> You'll ruin h
>> You'll ruin him
>> You'll ruin him.
>> You'll ruin him.He
>> You'll ruin him.He's
>> You'll ruin him.He's w
>> You'll ruin him.He's willf
>> You'll ruin him.He's willful
>> You'll ruin him.He's willful.
>> You'll ruin him.He's willful.Ne
>> You'll ruin him.He's willful.Need
>> You'll ruin him.He's willful.Needs
>> You'll ruin him.He's willful.Needs to l
>> You'll ruin him.He's willful.Needs to lea
>> You'll ruin him.He's willful.Needs to learn
>> You'll ruin him.He's willful.Needs to learn.
He's willful.Needs to learn.
He's willful.Needs to learn.>>
He's willful.Needs to learn.>> N
He's willful.Needs to learn.>> No,
He's willful.Needs to learn.>> No, he
He's willful.Needs to learn.>> No, he do
He's willful.Needs to learn.>> No, he does
He's willful.Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn'
He's willful.Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't ne
He's willful.Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need
He's willful.Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need t
He's willful.Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need to
He's willful.Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need to lear
He's willful.Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need to learn
Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need to learn
Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need to learnto g
Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need to learnto giv
Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give
Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in
Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and
Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and g
Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and giv
Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and give
Needs to learn.>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and give up.
>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and give up.
>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and give up.Th
>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and give up.That
>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and give up.That's
>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and give up.That's wha
>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and give up.That's what
>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and give up.That's what yo
>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and give up.That's what you
>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and give up.That's what you mean
>> No, he doesn't need to learnto give in and give up.That's what you mean,
to give in and give up.That's what you mean,
to give in and give up.That's what you mean,is
to give in and give up.That's what you mean,isn'
to give in and give up.That's what you mean,isn't it
to give in and give up.That's what you mean,isn't it?
That's what you mean,isn't it?
That's what you mean,isn't it?Th
That's what you mean,isn't it?The
That's what you mean,isn't it?The wa
That's what you mean,isn't it?The way
That's what you mean,isn't it?The way Samm
That's what you mean,isn't it?The way Sammy
That's what you mean,isn't it?The way Sammy is
That's what you mean,isn't it?The way Sammy is,
isn't it?The way Sammy is,
isn't it?The way Sammy is,he
isn't it?The way Sammy is,he's
isn't it?The way Sammy is,he's n
isn't it?The way Sammy is,he's not
isn't it?The way Sammy is,he's not per
isn't it?The way Sammy is,he's not perfe
isn't it?The way Sammy is,he's not perfect
isn't it?The way Sammy is,he's not perfect.
The way Sammy is,he's not perfect.
The way Sammy is,he's not perfect.But
The way Sammy is,he's not perfect.But he
The way Sammy is,he's not perfect.But he's
The way Sammy is,he's not perfect.But he's a
The way Sammy is,he's not perfect.But he's all r
The way Sammy is,he's not perfect.But he's all rig
The way Sammy is,he's not perfect.But he's all right
The way Sammy is,he's not perfect.But he's all right.
he's not perfect.But he's all right.
he's not perfect.But he's all right.St
he's not perfect.But he's all right.Stub
he's not perfect.But he's all right.Stubbo
he's not perfect.But he's all right.Stubbornne
he's not perfect.But he's all right.Stubbornness
he's not perfect.But he's all right.Stubbornness i
he's not perfect.But he's all right.Stubbornness isn
he's not perfect.But he's all right.Stubbornness isn't b
he's not perfect.But he's all right.Stubbornness isn't bad
he's not perfect.But he's all right.Stubbornness isn't bad.
But he's all right.Stubbornness isn't bad.
But he's all right.Stubbornness isn't bad.>>
But he's all right.Stubbornness isn't bad.>> H
But he's all right.Stubbornness isn't bad.>> He
But he's all right.Stubbornness isn't bad.>> He figh
But he's all right.Stubbornness isn't bad.>> He fights
But he's all right.Stubbornness isn't bad.>> He fights.
Stubbornness isn't bad.>> He fights.
Stubbornness isn't bad.>> He fights.>>
Stubbornness isn't bad.>> He fights.>> S
Stubbornness isn't bad.>> He fights.>> So
Stubbornness isn't bad.>> He fights.>> So do I
Stubbornness isn't bad.>> He fights.>> So do I.
>> He fights.>> So do I.
>> He fights.>> So do I.I'
>> He fights.>> So do I.I'm
>> He fights.>> So do I.I'm gl
>> He fights.>> So do I.I'm glad
>> He fights.>> So do I.I'm glad he
>> He fights.>> So do I.I'm glad he kn
>> He fights.>> So do I.I'm glad he know
>> He fights.>> So do I.I'm glad he knows
>> He fights.>> So do I.I'm glad he knows how.
(sig
(sighi
(sighing
(sighing)
(sighing)>>
(sighing)>> I
(sighing)>> If
(sighing)>> If you
(sighing)>> If you di
(sighing)>> If you didn
(sighing)>> If you didn't
(sighing)>> If you didn't kno
(sighing)>> If you didn't know
(sighing)>> If you didn't know it
(sighing)>> If you didn't know ital
(sighing)>> If you didn't know italre
(sighing)>> If you didn't know italready,
(sighing)>> If you didn't know italready, y
(sighing)>> If you didn't know italready, you
(sighing)>> If you didn't know italready, you c
(sighing)>> If you didn't know italready, you can't
(sighing)>> If you didn't know italready, you can't b
(sighing)>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be
(sighing)>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be wo
(sighing)>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be workin
(sighing)>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be working
>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be working
>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be workinga
>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be workinga si
>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be workinga six-
>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be workinga six-year
>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be workinga six-year-o
>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be workinga six-year-old
>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be workinga six-year-old a
>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be workinga six-year-old all d
>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be workinga six-year-old all day
>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be workinga six-year-old all day l
>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be workinga six-year-old all day lon
>> If you didn't know italready, you can't be workinga six-year-old all day long.
In
In t
In the
In the bar
In the barn
In the barn I
In the barn I th
In the barn I think
In the barn I think th
In the barn I think ther
In the barn I think there'
In the barn I think there's
In the barn I think there'sa
In the barn I think there'sa bi
In the barn I think there'sa bike
In the barn I think there'sa bike som
In the barn I think there'sa bike somew
In the barn I think there'sa bike somewhe
In the barn I think there'sa bike somewhere
In the barn I think there'sa bike somewhere nea
In the barn I think there'sa bike somewhere near
In the barn I think there'sa bike somewhere near hi
In the barn I think there'sa bike somewhere near his
In the barn I think there'sa bike somewhere near his size
In the barn I think there'sa bike somewhere near his size.
♪
♪(d
♪(doo
♪(door
♪(door cr
♪(door creaki
♪(door creaking
♪(door creaking)
♪(door creaking)Co
♪(door creaking)Come
♪(door creaking)Come o
♪(door creaking)Come on!
(door creaking)Come on!
(door creaking)Come on!>>
(door creaking)Come on!>> K
(door creaking)Come on!>> Keep
(door creaking)Come on!>> Keep pu
(door creaking)Come on!>> Keep pump
(door creaking)Come on!>> Keep pumpin
(door creaking)Come on!>> Keep pumping.
Come on!>> Keep pumping.
Come on!>> Keep pumping.Don'
Come on!>> Keep pumping.Don't
Come on!>> Keep pumping.Don't le
Come on!>> Keep pumping.Don't lean
Come on!>> Keep pumping.Don't lean.
>> Keep pumping.Don't lean.
>> Keep pumping.Don't lean.Keep
>> Keep pumping.Don't lean.Keep o
>> Keep pumping.Don't lean.Keep on
>> Keep pumping.Don't lean.Keep on mo
>> Keep pumping.Don't lean.Keep on moving
>> Keep pumping.Don't lean.Keep on moving.
Don't lean.Keep on moving.
Don't lean.Keep on moving.St
Don't lean.Keep on moving.Stay
Don't lean.Keep on moving.Stay on.
Don't lean.Keep on moving.Stay on...
Keep on moving.Stay on...
Keep on moving.Stay on...Th
Keep on moving.Stay on...That
Keep on moving.Stay on...That a
Keep on moving.Stay on...That a way
Keep on moving.Stay on...That a way!
Stay on...That a way!
Stay on...That a way!Pu
Stay on...That a way!Pump
Stay on...That a way!Pump,
Stay on...That a way!Pump, pump
Stay on...That a way!Pump, pump,
Stay on...That a way!Pump, pump, pu
Stay on...That a way!Pump, pump, pump
Stay on...That a way!Pump, pump, pump!
That a way!Pump, pump, pump!
That a way!Pump, pump, pump!That
That a way!Pump, pump, pump!That's
That a way!Pump, pump, pump!That's i
That a way!Pump, pump, pump!That's it!
Pump, pump, pump!That's it!
Pump, pump, pump!That's it!Do
Pump, pump, pump!That's it!Don'
Pump, pump, pump!That's it!Don't
Pump, pump, pump!That's it!Don't lean
Pump, pump, pump!That's it!Don't lean!
That's it!Don't lean!
That's it!Don't lean!>> O
That's it!Don't lean!>> Ow!
Don't lean!>> Ow!
Don't lean!>> Ow!(l
Don't lean!>> Ow!(lau
Don't lean!>> Ow!(laugh
Don't lean!>> Ow!(laughin
Don't lean!>> Ow!(laughing)
>> Ow!(laughing)
>> Ow!(laughing)I'
>> Ow!(laughing)I'm
>> Ow!(laughing)I'm okay
>> Ow!(laughing)I'm okay!
(laughing)I'm okay!
(laughing)I'm okay!>> W
(laughing)I'm okay!>> Way
(laughing)I'm okay!>> Way t
(laughing)I'm okay!>> Way to
(laughing)I'm okay!>> Way to go.
I'm okay!>> Way to go.
I'm okay!>> Way to go.(lau
I'm okay!>> Way to go.(laugh
I'm okay!>> Way to go.(laughin
I'm okay!>> Way to go.(laughing)
>> Way to go.(laughing)
>> Way to go.(laughing)>> D
>> Way to go.(laughing)>> Don
>> Way to go.(laughing)>> Don't
>> Way to go.(laughing)>> Don't g
>> Way to go.(laughing)>> Don't go to
>> Way to go.(laughing)>> Don't go too
>> Way to go.(laughing)>> Don't go too fa
>> Way to go.(laughing)>> Don't go too far,
>> Way to go.(laughing)>> Don't go too far, Sam
>> Way to go.(laughing)>> Don't go too far, Sammy
>> Way to go.(laughing)>> Don't go too far, Sammy.
>>
>> D
>> Dic
>> Dicey!
>> Dicey!Sa
>> Dicey!Samm
>> Dicey!Sammy!
>> Dicey!Sammy!It's
>> Dicey!Sammy!It's t
>> Dicey!Sammy!It's tim
>> Dicey!Sammy!It's time
>> Dicey!Sammy!It's time for
>> Dicey!Sammy!It's time for su
>> Dicey!Sammy!It's time for supp
>> Dicey!Sammy!It's time for supper
>> Dicey!Sammy!It's time for supper.
Di
Dice
Dicey!
Dicey!Sa
Dicey!Samm
Dicey!Sammy!
(d
(doo
(door
(door cr
(door creaki
(door creaking
(door creaking)
(door creaking)(w
(door creaking)(wat
(door creaking)(water
(door creaking)(water s
(door creaking)(water splas
(door creaking)(water splashi
(door creaking)(water splashing
(door creaking)(water splashing)
>>
>> A
>> At
>> At le
>> At least
>> At least th
>> At least the
>> At least the ma
>> At least the majori
>> At least the majority
>> At least the majority o
>> At least the majority of
>> At least the majority of us
>> At least the majority of usma
>> At least the majority of usmade
>> At least the majority of usmade i
>> At least the majority of usmade it on
>> At least the majority of usmade it on t
>> At least the majority of usmade it on tim
>> At least the majority of usmade it on time.
>> At least the majority of usmade it on time.Yo
>> At least the majority of usmade it on time.You
>> At least the majority of usmade it on time.You ch
>> At least the majority of usmade it on time.You childr
>> At least the majority of usmade it on time.You children
>> At least the majority of usmade it on time.You children s
>> At least the majority of usmade it on time.You children sav
>> At least the majority of usmade it on time.You children saved
made it on time.You children saved
made it on time.You children savedth
made it on time.You children savedthe
made it on time.You children savedthe ve
made it on time.You children savedthe vegeta
made it on time.You children savedthe vegetabl
made it on time.You children savedthe vegetables
made it on time.You children savedthe vegetables t
made it on time.You children savedthe vegetables to me
made it on time.You children savedthe vegetables to me t
made it on time.You children savedthe vegetables to me tod
made it on time.You children savedthe vegetables to me today
made it on time.You children savedthe vegetables to me today.
You children savedthe vegetables to me today.
You children savedthe vegetables to me today.An
You children savedthe vegetables to me today.And
You children savedthe vegetables to me today.And fo
You children savedthe vegetables to me today.And for th
You children savedthe vegetables to me today.And for that
You children savedthe vegetables to me today.And for that I
You children savedthe vegetables to me today.And for that I g
You children savedthe vegetables to me today.And for that I give
You children savedthe vegetables to me today.And for that I give yo
You children savedthe vegetables to me today.And for that I give you
You children savedthe vegetables to me today.And for that I give you th
You children savedthe vegetables to me today.And for that I give you thanks
You children savedthe vegetables to me today.And for that I give you thanks.
the vegetables to me today.And for that I give you thanks.
the vegetables to me today.And for that I give you thanks.>> Y
the vegetables to me today.And for that I give you thanks.>> You
the vegetables to me today.And for that I give you thanks.>> You'r
the vegetables to me today.And for that I give you thanks.>> You're
the vegetables to me today.And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welc
the vegetables to me today.And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welcom
the vegetables to me today.And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welcome.
And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welcome.
And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welcome.>>
And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welcome.>> N
And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welcome.>> Now
And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welcome.>> Now, le
And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welcome.>> Now, let'
And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's
And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's ea
And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's eat, f
And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's eat, fol
And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's eat, folks
And for that I give you thanks.>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's eat, folks,
>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's eat, folks,
>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's eat, folks,be
>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's eat, folks,befo
>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's eat, folks,before
>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it
>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it ge
>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it gets
>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it gets c
>> You're welcome.>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it gets cold.
>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it gets cold.
>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it gets cold.>>
>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it gets cold.>> H
>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it gets cold.>> How c
>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it gets cold.>> How com
>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it gets cold.>> How come
>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it gets cold.>> How come yo
>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it gets cold.>> How come you do
>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it gets cold.>> How come you don'
>> Now, let's eat, folks,before it gets cold.>> How come you don't
before it gets cold.>> How come you don't
before it gets cold.>> How come you don'thave
before it gets cold.>> How come you don'thave a
before it gets cold.>> How come you don'thave a p
before it gets cold.>> How come you don'thave a pho
before it gets cold.>> How come you don'thave a phone?
>> How come you don'thave a phone?
>> How come you don'thave a phone?>>
>> How come you don'thave a phone?>> I
>> How come you don'thave a phone?>> I too
>> How come you don'thave a phone?>> I took
>> How come you don'thave a phone?>> I took it
>> How come you don'thave a phone?>> I took it o
>> How come you don'thave a phone?>> I took it out y
>> How come you don'thave a phone?>> I took it out yea
>> How come you don'thave a phone?>> I took it out years
>> How come you don'thave a phone?>> I took it out years a
>> How come you don'thave a phone?>> I took it out years ago.
have a phone?>> I took it out years ago.
have a phone?>> I took it out years ago.>>
have a phone?>> I took it out years ago.>> W
have a phone?>> I took it out years ago.>> Why
have a phone?>> I took it out years ago.>> Why wou
have a phone?>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would
have a phone?>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would y
have a phone?>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would you
have a phone?>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would you do
have a phone?>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would you do th
have a phone?>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would you do that
have a phone?>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would you do that?
>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would you do that?
>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would you do that?>> Y
>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would you do that?>> You
>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would you do that?>> You'r
>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would you do that?>> You're
>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would you do that?>> You're too
>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would you do that?>> You're too yo
>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would you do that?>> You're too youn
>> I took it out years ago.>> Why would you do that?>> You're too young,
>> Why would you do that?>> You're too young,
>> Why would you do that?>> You're too young,yo
>> Why would you do that?>> You're too young,you
>> Why would you do that?>> You're too young,you wo
>> Why would you do that?>> You're too young,you woul
>> Why would you do that?>> You're too young,you wouldn't
>> Why would you do that?>> You're too young,you wouldn't u
>> Why would you do that?>> You're too young,you wouldn't und
>> Why would you do that?>> You're too young,you wouldn't under
>> Why would you do that?>> You're too young,you wouldn't understan
>> Why would you do that?>> You're too young,you wouldn't understand.
At l
At lea
At least
At least I
At least I use
At least I used
At least I used to
At least I used to u
At least I used to under
At least I used to underst
At least I used to understan
At least I used to understand.
Yo
You
You se
You see, m
You see, my
You see, my bo
You see, my boy
You see, my boy Bull
You see, my boy Bullet
You see, my boy Bullet,
You see, my boy Bullet,he
You see, my boy Bullet,he w
You see, my boy Bullet,he was i
You see, my boy Bullet,he was in
You see, my boy Bullet,he was in th
You see, my boy Bullet,he was in the
You see, my boy Bullet,he was in the army
You see, my boy Bullet,he was in the army.
You see, my boy Bullet,he was in the army.>>
You see, my boy Bullet,he was in the army.>> W
You see, my boy Bullet,he was in the army.>> What
You see, my boy Bullet,he was in the army.>> What ki
You see, my boy Bullet,he was in the army.>> What kind
You see, my boy Bullet,he was in the army.>> What kind o
You see, my boy Bullet,he was in the army.>> What kind of na
You see, my boy Bullet,he was in the army.>> What kind of name
he was in the army.>> What kind of name
he was in the army.>> What kind of nameis B
he was in the army.>> What kind of nameis Bul
he was in the army.>> What kind of nameis Bulle
he was in the army.>> What kind of nameis Bullet?
>> What kind of nameis Bullet?
>> What kind of nameis Bullet?>>
>> What kind of nameis Bullet?>> I
>> What kind of nameis Bullet?>> It
>> What kind of nameis Bullet?>> It was
>> What kind of nameis Bullet?>> It was a
>> What kind of nameis Bullet?>> It was a ni
>> What kind of nameis Bullet?>> It was a nick
>> What kind of nameis Bullet?>> It was a nickname
>> What kind of nameis Bullet?>> It was a nickname.
is Bullet?>> It was a nickname.
is Bullet?>> It was a nickname.>>
is Bullet?>> It was a nickname.>> W
is Bullet?>> It was a nickname.>> Wha
is Bullet?>> It was a nickname.>> What wa
is Bullet?>> It was a nickname.>> What was
is Bullet?>> It was a nickname.>> What was hi
is Bullet?>> It was a nickname.>> What was his
is Bullet?>> It was a nickname.>> What was his real
is Bullet?>> It was a nickname.>> What was his real n
is Bullet?>> It was a nickname.>> What was his real nam
is Bullet?>> It was a nickname.>> What was his real name?
>> It was a nickname.>> What was his real name?
>> It was a nickname.>> What was his real name?>>
>> It was a nickname.>> What was his real name?>> S
>> It was a nickname.>> What was his real name?>> Sam
>> It was a nickname.>> What was his real name?>> Sam.
>> What was his real name?>> Sam.
>> What was his real name?>> Sam.Sa
>> What was his real name?>> Sam.Samu
>> What was his real name?>> Sam.Samuel.
>> Sam.Samuel.
>> Sam.Samuel.>>
>> Sam.Samuel.>> O
>> Sam.Samuel.>> Oh,
>> Sam.Samuel.>> Oh, lik
>> Sam.Samuel.>> Oh, like
>> Sam.Samuel.>> Oh, like Sa
>> Sam.Samuel.>> Oh, like Samm
>> Sam.Samuel.>> Oh, like Sammy.
Samuel.>> Oh, like Sammy.
Samuel.>> Oh, like Sammy.Ma
Samuel.>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama
Samuel.>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama m
Samuel.>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama mus
Samuel.>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama must ha
Samuel.>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama must have
Samuel.>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama must have n
Samuel.>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama must have nam
Samuel.>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama must have named h
Samuel.>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama must have named him
>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama must have named him
>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama must have named himafte
>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama must have named himafter
>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama must have named himafter he
>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama must have named himafter her
>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama must have named himafter her brot
>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama must have named himafter her brothe
>> Oh, like Sammy.Mama must have named himafter her brother.
Mama must have named himafter her brother.
Mama must have named himafter her brother.Wa
Mama must have named himafter her brother.Was
Mama must have named himafter her brother.Was he l
Mama must have named himafter her brother.Was he lik
Mama must have named himafter her brother.Was he like
Mama must have named himafter her brother.Was he like Sa
Mama must have named himafter her brother.Was he like Sammy
Mama must have named himafter her brother.Was he like Sammy is
Mama must have named himafter her brother.Was he like Sammy is?
after her brother.Was he like Sammy is?
after her brother.Was he like Sammy is?>>
after her brother.Was he like Sammy is?>> Y
after her brother.Was he like Sammy is?>> You
after her brother.Was he like Sammy is?>> You wan
after her brother.Was he like Sammy is?>> You want
after her brother.Was he like Sammy is?>> You want th
after her brother.Was he like Sammy is?>> You want this
after her brother.Was he like Sammy is?>> You want this sto
after her brother.Was he like Sammy is?>> You want this story
after her brother.Was he like Sammy is?>> You want this story o
after her brother.Was he like Sammy is?>> You want this story or
after her brother.Was he like Sammy is?>> You want this story or not?
Was he like Sammy is?>> You want this story or not?
Was he like Sammy is?>> You want this story or not?>>
Was he like Sammy is?>> You want this story or not?>> Y
Was he like Sammy is?>> You want this story or not?>> Yeah.
>> You want this story or not?>> Yeah.
>> You want this story or not?>> Yeah.>>
>> You want this story or not?>> Yeah.>> O
>> You want this story or not?>> Yeah.>> Oka
>> You want this story or not?>> Yeah.>> Okay.
>> Yeah.>> Okay.
>> Yeah.>> Okay.Bu
>> Yeah.>> Okay.Bull
>> Yeah.>> Okay.Bullet w
>> Yeah.>> Okay.Bullet was
>> Yeah.>> Okay.Bullet was i
>> Yeah.>> Okay.Bullet was in
>> Yeah.>> Okay.Bullet was in the
>> Yeah.>> Okay.Bullet was in the ar
>> Yeah.>> Okay.Bullet was in the army
>> Okay.Bullet was in the army
>> Okay.Bullet was in the armyan
>> Okay.Bullet was in the armyand
>> Okay.Bullet was in the armyand I
>> Okay.Bullet was in the armyand I gu
>> Okay.Bullet was in the armyand I guess
>> Okay.Bullet was in the armyand I guess so
>> Okay.Bullet was in the armyand I guess some
>> Okay.Bullet was in the armyand I guess somebo
>> Okay.Bullet was in the armyand I guess somebody,
Bullet was in the armyand I guess somebody,
Bullet was in the armyand I guess somebody,so
Bullet was in the armyand I guess somebody,some
Bullet was in the armyand I guess somebody,somewh
Bullet was in the armyand I guess somebody,somewhere
Bullet was in the armyand I guess somebody,somewhere th
Bullet was in the armyand I guess somebody,somewhere thou
Bullet was in the armyand I guess somebody,somewhere though
Bullet was in the armyand I guess somebody,somewhere thought it
Bullet was in the armyand I guess somebody,somewhere thought it w
Bullet was in the armyand I guess somebody,somewhere thought it was
and I guess somebody,somewhere thought it was
and I guess somebody,somewhere thought it wasim
and I guess somebody,somewhere thought it wasimpo
and I guess somebody,somewhere thought it wasimport
and I guess somebody,somewhere thought it wasimportant
and I guess somebody,somewhere thought it wasimportant th
and I guess somebody,somewhere thought it wasimportant that
and I guess somebody,somewhere thought it wasimportant that h
and I guess somebody,somewhere thought it wasimportant that he go
and I guess somebody,somewhere thought it wasimportant that he go f
and I guess somebody,somewhere thought it wasimportant that he go fig
and I guess somebody,somewhere thought it wasimportant that he go fight
somewhere thought it wasimportant that he go fight
somewhere thought it wasimportant that he go fightin
somewhere thought it wasimportant that he go fightin s
somewhere thought it wasimportant that he go fightin some
somewhere thought it wasimportant that he go fightin some fo
somewhere thought it wasimportant that he go fightin some fool
somewhere thought it wasimportant that he go fightin some foolis
somewhere thought it wasimportant that he go fightin some foolish wa
somewhere thought it wasimportant that he go fightin some foolish war.
important that he go fightin some foolish war.
important that he go fightin some foolish war.>>
important that he go fightin some foolish war.>> V
important that he go fightin some foolish war.>> Vie
important that he go fightin some foolish war.>> Vietn
important that he go fightin some foolish war.>> Vietnam?
in some foolish war.>> Vietnam?
in some foolish war.>> Vietnam?>>
in some foolish war.>> Vietnam?>> Y
in some foolish war.>> Vietnam?>> Yeah.
>> Vietnam?>> Yeah.
>> Vietnam?>> Yeah.Th
>> Vietnam?>> Yeah.They
>> Vietnam?>> Yeah.They cal
>> Vietnam?>> Yeah.They calle
>> Vietnam?>> Yeah.They called
>> Vietnam?>> Yeah.They called me
>> Vietnam?>> Yeah.They called me up
>> Vietnam?>> Yeah.They called me up on
>> Vietnam?>> Yeah.They called me up on t
>> Vietnam?>> Yeah.They called me up on tha
>> Vietnam?>> Yeah.They called me up on that
>> Yeah.They called me up on that
>> Yeah.They called me up on thattele
>> Yeah.They called me up on thatteleph
>> Yeah.They called me up on thattelephon
>> Yeah.They called me up on thattelephone
>> Yeah.They called me up on thattelephone to t
>> Yeah.They called me up on thattelephone to tel
>> Yeah.They called me up on thattelephone to tell
>> Yeah.They called me up on thattelephone to tell me
They called me up on thattelephone to tell me
They called me up on thattelephone to tell mehe
They called me up on thattelephone to tell mehe w
They called me up on thattelephone to tell mehe was k
They called me up on thattelephone to tell mehe was kil
They called me up on thattelephone to tell mehe was kille
They called me up on thattelephone to tell mehe was killed.
telephone to tell mehe was killed.
telephone to tell mehe was killed.I
telephone to tell mehe was killed.I ha
telephone to tell mehe was killed.I had
telephone to tell mehe was killed.I had to
telephone to tell mehe was killed.I had to do
telephone to tell mehe was killed.I had to do so
telephone to tell mehe was killed.I had to do some
telephone to tell mehe was killed.I had to do someth
telephone to tell mehe was killed.I had to do something.
he was killed.I had to do something.
he was killed.I had to do something.Yo
he was killed.I had to do something.You
he was killed.I had to do something.You know
he was killed.I had to do something.You know w
he was killed.I had to do something.You know wha
he was killed.I had to do something.You know what
he was killed.I had to do something.You know what I di
he was killed.I had to do something.You know what I did
he was killed.I had to do something.You know what I did wa
he was killed.I had to do something.You know what I did was?
I had to do something.You know what I did was?
I had to do something.You know what I did was?I we
I had to do something.You know what I did was?I went
I had to do something.You know what I did was?I went d
I had to do something.You know what I did was?I went dow
I had to do something.You know what I did was?I went downtow
I had to do something.You know what I did was?I went downtown
I had to do something.You know what I did was?I went downtown an
I had to do something.You know what I did was?I went downtown and
I had to do something.You know what I did was?I went downtown and I th
I had to do something.You know what I did was?I went downtown and I thre
I had to do something.You know what I did was?I went downtown and I threw
You know what I did was?I went downtown and I threw
You know what I did was?I went downtown and I threwit
You know what I did was?I went downtown and I threwit r
You know what I did was?I went downtown and I threwit rig
You know what I did was?I went downtown and I threwit right
You know what I did was?I went downtown and I threwit right thr
You know what I did was?I went downtown and I threwit right throu
You know what I did was?I went downtown and I threwit right through
I went downtown and I threwit right through
I went downtown and I threwit right throughth
I went downtown and I threwit right throughthe
I went downtown and I threwit right throughthe ph
I went downtown and I threwit right throughthe phone
I went downtown and I threwit right throughthe phone co
I went downtown and I threwit right throughthe phone comp
I went downtown and I threwit right throughthe phone compan
I went downtown and I threwit right throughthe phone company wi
I went downtown and I threwit right throughthe phone company wind
I went downtown and I threwit right throughthe phone company window
I went downtown and I threwit right throughthe phone company window.
it right throughthe phone company window.
it right throughthe phone company window.(c
it right throughthe phone company window.(chu
it right throughthe phone company window.(chuck
it right throughthe phone company window.(chuckling
it right throughthe phone company window.(chuckling)
They
They w
They wer
They were
They were surp
They were surpri
They were surprise
They were surprised,
They were surprised,I
They were surprised,I ca
They were surprised,I can
They were surprised,I can te
They were surprised,I can tell y
They were surprised,I can tell you
They were surprised,I can tell you.
They were surprised,I can tell you.Didn
They were surprised,I can tell you.Didn't
They were surprised,I can tell you.Didn't d
They were surprised,I can tell you.Didn't do
They were surprised,I can tell you.Didn't do any
They were surprised,I can tell you.Didn't do any go
They were surprised,I can tell you.Didn't do any good
They were surprised,I can tell you.Didn't do any good,
They were surprised,I can tell you.Didn't do any good, of c
They were surprised,I can tell you.Didn't do any good, of cou
They were surprised,I can tell you.Didn't do any good, of cours
They were surprised,I can tell you.Didn't do any good, of course.
I can tell you.Didn't do any good, of course.
I can tell you.Didn't do any good, of course.But
I can tell you.Didn't do any good, of course.But it
I can tell you.Didn't do any good, of course.But it w
I can tell you.Didn't do any good, of course.But it was
I can tell you.Didn't do any good, of course.But it was bet
I can tell you.Didn't do any good, of course.But it was bette
I can tell you.Didn't do any good, of course.But it was better
Didn't do any good, of course.But it was better
Didn't do any good, of course.But it was betterth
Didn't do any good, of course.But it was betterthan
Didn't do any good, of course.But it was betterthan d
Didn't do any good, of course.But it was betterthan doi
Didn't do any good, of course.But it was betterthan doing n
Didn't do any good, of course.But it was betterthan doing not
Didn't do any good, of course.But it was betterthan doing nothi
Didn't do any good, of course.But it was betterthan doing nothing
Didn't do any good, of course.But it was betterthan doing nothing.
But it was betterthan doing nothing.
But it was betterthan doing nothing.(s
But it was betterthan doing nothing.(sil
But it was betterthan doing nothing.(silve
But it was betterthan doing nothing.(silverwar
But it was betterthan doing nothing.(silverware
But it was betterthan doing nothing.(silverware cl
But it was betterthan doing nothing.(silverware clan
But it was betterthan doing nothing.(silverware clanking
But it was betterthan doing nothing.(silverware clanking)
Mo
Mosq
Mosqui
Mosquitoes
Mosquitoes a
Mosquitoes are
Mosquitoes are p
Mosquitoes are prett
Mosquitoes are pretty
Mosquitoes are pretty ba
Mosquitoes are pretty bad
Mosquitoes are pretty badth
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis tim
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of y
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of year.
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of year.I th
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of year.I thin
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of year.I think
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of year.I think it
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of year.I think it wou
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of year.I think it would
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of year.I think it would b
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of year.I think it would be
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of year.I think it would be a go
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of year.I think it would be a good
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of year.I think it would be a good i
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of year.I think it would be a good ide
Mosquitoes are pretty badthis time of year.I think it would be a good idea
this time of year.I think it would be a good idea
this time of year.I think it would be a good ideato
this time of year.I think it would be a good ideato p
this time of year.I think it would be a good ideato pat
this time of year.I think it would be a good ideato patch t
this time of year.I think it would be a good ideato patch tho
this time of year.I think it would be a good ideato patch those
this time of year.I think it would be a good ideato patch those u
this time of year.I think it would be a good ideato patch those upsta
this time of year.I think it would be a good ideato patch those upstair
this time of year.I think it would be a good ideato patch those upstairs
this time of year.I think it would be a good ideato patch those upstairs sc
this time of year.I think it would be a good ideato patch those upstairs screen
this time of year.I think it would be a good ideato patch those upstairs screens.
I think it would be a good ideato patch those upstairs screens.
I think it would be a good ideato patch those upstairs screens.>> J
I think it would be a good ideato patch those upstairs screens.>> Jam
I think it would be a good ideato patch those upstairs screens.>> James
I think it would be a good ideato patch those upstairs screens.>> James a
I think it would be a good ideato patch those upstairs screens.>> James and I
to patch those upstairs screens.>> James and I
to patch those upstairs screens.>> James and Ica
to patch those upstairs screens.>> James and Ican
to patch those upstairs screens.>> James and Ican do
to patch those upstairs screens.>> James and Ican do t
to patch those upstairs screens.>> James and Ican do that
to patch those upstairs screens.>> James and Ican do that to
to patch those upstairs screens.>> James and Ican do that tomo
to patch those upstairs screens.>> James and Ican do that tomorr
to patch those upstairs screens.>> James and Ican do that tomorrow.
>> James and Ican do that tomorrow.
>> James and Ican do that tomorrow.(b
>> James and Ican do that tomorrow.(bik
>> James and Ican do that tomorrow.(bike ra
>> James and Ican do that tomorrow.(bike ratt
>> James and Ican do that tomorrow.(bike rattli
>> James and Ican do that tomorrow.(bike rattling
>> James and Ican do that tomorrow.(bike rattling)
can do that tomorrow.(bike rattling)
can do that tomorrow.(bike rattling)(d
can do that tomorrow.(bike rattling)(doo
can do that tomorrow.(bike rattling)(door
can do that tomorrow.(bike rattling)(door crea
can do that tomorrow.(bike rattling)(door creaki
can do that tomorrow.(bike rattling)(door creaking
can do that tomorrow.(bike rattling)(door creaking)
(bike rattling)(door creaking)
(bike rattling)(door creaking)>>
(bike rattling)(door creaking)>> I
(bike rattling)(door creaking)>> I c
(bike rattling)(door creaking)>> I can r
(bike rattling)(door creaking)>> I can rid
(bike rattling)(door creaking)>> I can ride.
(door creaking)>> I can ride.
(door creaking)>> I can ride.What
(door creaking)>> I can ride.What's
(door creaking)>> I can ride.What's f
(door creaking)>> I can ride.What's for
(door creaking)>> I can ride.What's for sup
(door creaking)>> I can ride.What's for suppe
(door creaking)>> I can ride.What's for supper?
>> I can ride.What's for supper?
>> I can ride.What's for supper?>>
>> I can ride.What's for supper?>> W
>> I can ride.What's for supper?>> Was
>> I can ride.What's for supper?>> Wash yo
>> I can ride.What's for supper?>> Wash your
>> I can ride.What's for supper?>> Wash your h
>> I can ride.What's for supper?>> Wash your han
>> I can ride.What's for supper?>> Wash your hands.
>>
>> W
>> Whe
>> When yo
>> When you'
>> When you've
>> When you've d
>> When you've done
>> When you've done th
>> When you've done that
>> When you've done that,
>> When you've done that,go
>> When you've done that,go t
>> When you've done that,go to
>> When you've done that,go to your
>> When you've done that,go to your r
>> When you've done that,go to your roo
>> When you've done that,go to your room.
>> When you've done that,go to your room.>>
>> When you've done that,go to your room.>> B
>> When you've done that,go to your room.>> But
>> When you've done that,go to your room.>> But I'm
>> When you've done that,go to your room.>> But I'm h
>> When you've done that,go to your room.>> But I'm hun
>> When you've done that,go to your room.>> But I'm hungr
>> When you've done that,go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.
go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.
go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.>>
go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.>> T
go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.>> That'
go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll
go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll h
go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll hel
go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll help yo
go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll help you
go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll help you to
go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll help you to r
go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll help you to remem
go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll help you to remembe
go to your room.>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll help you to remember.
>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll help you to remember.
>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll help you to remember.Ge
>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll help you to remember.Get
>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll help you to remember.Get me
>> But I'm hungry.>> That'll help you to remember.Get me?!
>> That'll help you to remember.Get me?!
>> That'll help you to remember.Get me?!Did
>> That'll help you to remember.Get me?!Did yo
>> That'll help you to remember.Get me?!Did you
>> That'll help you to remember.Get me?!Did you te
>> That'll help you to remember.Get me?!Did you tell y
>> That'll help you to remember.Get me?!Did you tell you
>> That'll help you to remember.Get me?!Did you tell your
>> That'll help you to remember.Get me?!Did you tell your si
>> That'll help you to remember.Get me?!Did you tell your sister
Get me?!Did you tell your sister
Get me?!Did you tell your sisterwher
Get me?!Did you tell your sisterwhere
Get me?!Did you tell your sisterwhere yo
Get me?!Did you tell your sisterwhere you
Get me?!Did you tell your sisterwhere you were
Get me?!Did you tell your sisterwhere you were g
Get me?!Did you tell your sisterwhere you were goi
Get me?!Did you tell your sisterwhere you were going
Get me?!Did you tell your sisterwhere you were going?
Di
Did
Did he
Did he t
Did he tell
Did he tell ya
Did he tell ya?
Did he tell ya?Di
Did he tell ya?Did
Did he tell ya?Did he
Did he tell ya?Did he h
Did he tell ya?Did he have
Did he tell ya?Did he have yo
Did he tell ya?Did he have your
Did he tell ya?Did he have your p
Did he tell ya?Did he have your permi
Did he tell ya?Did he have your permiss
Did he tell ya?Did he have your permissio
Did he tell ya?Did he have your permission?
Did he tell ya?Did he have your permission?>>
Did he tell ya?Did he have your permission?>> S
Did he tell ya?Did he have your permission?>> Sor
Did he tell ya?Did he have your permission?>> Sort of
Did he tell ya?Did he have your permission?>> Sort of.
Did he have your permission?>> Sort of.
Did he have your permission?>> Sort of.>>
Did he have your permission?>> Sort of.>> S
Did he have your permission?>> Sort of.>> Sor
Did he have your permission?>> Sort of.>> Sort of
Did he have your permission?>> Sort of.>> Sort of?
>> Sort of.>> Sort of?
>> Sort of.>> Sort of?Ho
>> Sort of.>> Sort of?How
>> Sort of.>> Sort of?How do y
>> Sort of.>> Sort of?How do you
>> Sort of.>> Sort of?How do you s
>> Sort of.>> Sort of?How do you sor
>> Sort of.>> Sort of?How do you sort of
>> Sort of.>> Sort of?How do you sort of g
>> Sort of.>> Sort of?How do you sort of giv
>> Sort of.>> Sort of?How do you sort of give
>> Sort of?How do you sort of give
>> Sort of?How do you sort of givepe
>> Sort of?How do you sort of giveperm
>> Sort of?How do you sort of givepermissi
>> Sort of?How do you sort of givepermission
>> Sort of?How do you sort of givepermission t
>> Sort of?How do you sort of givepermission to
>> Sort of?How do you sort of givepermission to go g
>> Sort of?How do you sort of givepermission to go gal
>> Sort of?How do you sort of givepermission to go galli
>> Sort of?How do you sort of givepermission to go galliva
>> Sort of?How do you sort of givepermission to go gallivantin
>> Sort of?How do you sort of givepermission to go gallivanting
How do you sort of givepermission to go gallivanting
How do you sort of givepermission to go gallivantingal
How do you sort of givepermission to go gallivantingall
How do you sort of givepermission to go gallivantingall da
How do you sort of givepermission to go gallivantingall day lo
How do you sort of givepermission to go gallivantingall day long
permission to go gallivantingall day long
permission to go gallivantingall day longan
permission to go gallivantingall day longand
permission to go gallivantingall day longand then
permission to go gallivantingall day longand then m
permission to go gallivantingall day longand then mis
permission to go gallivantingall day longand then miss
permission to go gallivantingall day longand then miss supp
permission to go gallivantingall day longand then miss supper
permission to go gallivantingall day longand then miss supper?
all day longand then miss supper?
all day longand then miss supper?Do
all day longand then miss supper?Do y
all day longand then miss supper?Do you
all day longand then miss supper?Do you s
all day longand then miss supper?Do you say,
all day longand then miss supper?Do you say, "O
all day longand then miss supper?Do you say, "Oka
all day longand then miss supper?Do you say, "Okay,
all day longand then miss supper?Do you say, "Okay, Sam
all day longand then miss supper?Do you say, "Okay, Sammy
all day longand then miss supper?Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,
and then miss supper?Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,
and then miss supper?Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"g
and then miss supper?Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go
and then miss supper?Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go so
and then miss supper?Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort o
and then miss supper?Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort of
and then miss supper?Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort of ru
and then miss supper?Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort of run
and then miss supper?Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort of run wild
Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort of run wild
Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort of run wild"a
Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort of run wild"and
Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort of run wild"and t
Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort of run wild"and then
Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort of run wild"and then so
Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort of run wild"and then sort
Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort of run wild"and then sort o
Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort of run wild"and then sort of le
Do you say, "Okay, Sammy,"go sort of run wild"and then sort of let
"go sort of run wild"and then sort of let
"go sort of run wild"and then sort of letpe
"go sort of run wild"and then sort of letpeop
"go sort of run wild"and then sort of letpeople w
"go sort of run wild"and then sort of letpeople wor
"go sort of run wild"and then sort of letpeople worry
"go sort of run wild"and then sort of letpeople worry"?
"and then sort of letpeople worry"?
"and then sort of letpeople worry"?Wh
"and then sort of letpeople worry"?What
"and then sort of letpeople worry"?What,
"and then sort of letpeople worry"?What, are
"and then sort of letpeople worry"?What, are yo
"and then sort of letpeople worry"?What, are you
"and then sort of letpeople worry"?What, are you st
"and then sort of letpeople worry"?What, are you stupid
"and then sort of letpeople worry"?What, are you stupid,
"and then sort of letpeople worry"?What, are you stupid, gi
"and then sort of letpeople worry"?What, are you stupid, girl
"and then sort of letpeople worry"?What, are you stupid, girl?
people worry"?What, are you stupid, girl?
people worry"?What, are you stupid, girl?>>
people worry"?What, are you stupid, girl?>> I
people worry"?What, are you stupid, girl?>> It'
people worry"?What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's
people worry"?What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's not
people worry"?What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's not he
people worry"?What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's not her
people worry"?What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's not her fa
people worry"?What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's not her fault.
What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's not her fault.
What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's not her fault.Do
What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's not her fault.Don'
What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's not her fault.Don't ye
What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's not her fault.Don't yell
What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's not her fault.Don't yell a
What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at
What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dice
What, are you stupid, girl?>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.
>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.
>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.>>
>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.>> I
>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'l
>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll
>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell
>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell a
>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at
>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at wh
>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I
>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I p
>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I ple
>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I pleas
>> It's not her fault.Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I please,
Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I please,
Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I please,an
Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I please,and
Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I'
Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I've t
Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I've tol
Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I've told
Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I've told yo
Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I've told you to
Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I've told you to g
Don't yell at Dicey.>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I've told you to go
>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I've told you to go
>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I've told you to goto
>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I've told you to goto y
>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I've told you to goto you
>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I've told you to goto your ro
>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I've told you to goto your room
>> I'll yell at whom I please,and I've told you to goto your room.
>>
>> N
>> No.
>> No.>>
>> No.>> D
>> No.>> Dic
>> No.>> Dicey.
>> No.>> Dicey.>> I
>> No.>> Dicey.>> It'
>> No.>> Dicey.>> It's
>> No.>> Dicey.>> It's no
>> No.>> Dicey.>> It's not ri
>> No.>> Dicey.>> It's not righ
>> No.>> Dicey.>> It's not right,
>> No.>> Dicey.>> It's not right, J
>> No.>> Dicey.>> It's not right, James
>> No.>> Dicey.>> It's not right, James.
>> Dicey.>> It's not right, James.
>> Dicey.>> It's not right, James.It
>> Dicey.>> It's not right, James.It's
>> Dicey.>> It's not right, James.It's n
>> Dicey.>> It's not right, James.It's not r
>> Dicey.>> It's not right, James.It's not rig
>> Dicey.>> It's not right, James.It's not right
>> Dicey.>> It's not right, James.It's not right t
>> Dicey.>> It's not right, James.It's not right to se
>> Dicey.>> It's not right, James.It's not right to send
>> It's not right, James.It's not right to send
>> It's not right, James.It's not right to sendhi
>> It's not right, James.It's not right to sendhim
>> It's not right, James.It's not right to sendhim to b
>> It's not right, James.It's not right to sendhim to bed
>> It's not right, James.It's not right to sendhim to bed h
>> It's not right, James.It's not right to sendhim to bed hun
>> It's not right, James.It's not right to sendhim to bed hungry.
It's not right to sendhim to bed hungry.
It's not right to sendhim to bed hungry.Ca
It's not right to sendhim to bed hungry.Can'
It's not right to sendhim to bed hungry.Can't
It's not right to sendhim to bed hungry.Can't let
It's not right to sendhim to bed hungry.Can't let it
It's not right to sendhim to bed hungry.Can't let it h
It's not right to sendhim to bed hungry.Can't let it hap
It's not right to sendhim to bed hungry.Can't let it happen.
him to bed hungry.Can't let it happen.
him to bed hungry.Can't let it happen.Si
him to bed hungry.Can't let it happen.Sit
him to bed hungry.Can't let it happen.Sit down
him to bed hungry.Can't let it happen.Sit down,
him to bed hungry.Can't let it happen.Sit down, Sa
him to bed hungry.Can't let it happen.Sit down, Samm
him to bed hungry.Can't let it happen.Sit down, Sammy.
Yo
You
You do
You don't
You don't un
You don't unde
You don't unders
You don't understand
You don't understand,
You don't understand,no
You don't understand,not
You don't understand,not wh
You don't understand,not what
You don't understand,not what it
You don't understand,not what it is
You don't understand,not what it is t
You don't understand,not what it is to
You don't understand,not what it is to be h
You don't understand,not what it is to be hun
You don't understand,not what it is to be hungr
You don't understand,not what it is to be hungry.
You don't understand,not what it is to be hungry.It
You don't understand,not what it is to be hungry.It d
You don't understand,not what it is to be hungry.It doesn
You don't understand,not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't
You don't understand,not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't s
You don't understand,not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't ser
You don't understand,not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve a
You don't understand,not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve any
You don't understand,not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve any p
You don't understand,not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve any pur
You don't understand,not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve any purpose
not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve any purpose
not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve any purposeto p
not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve any purposeto pun
not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve any purposeto punis
not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve any purposeto punish
not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve any purposeto punish him
not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve any purposeto punish him th
not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve any purposeto punish him that
not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve any purposeto punish him that w
not what it is to be hungry.It doesn't serve any purposeto punish him that way.
Sit
Sit do
Sit down
Sit down,
Sit down, Samm
Sit down, Sammy.
Sit down, Sammy.But
Sit down, Sammy.But yo
Sit down, Sammy.But you'
Sit down, Sammy.But you're
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not t
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ri
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ride y
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ride you
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ride your
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ride yourbi
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ride yourbike
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ride yourbike a
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ride yourbike aga
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ride yourbike again u
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ride yourbike again unt
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ride yourbike again until
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ride yourbike again until I
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ride yourbike again until I say
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ride yourbike again until I say s
Sit down, Sammy.But you're not to ride yourbike again until I say so.
But you're not to ride yourbike again until I say so.
But you're not to ride yourbike again until I say so.>>
But you're not to ride yourbike again until I say so.>> O
But you're not to ride yourbike again until I say so.>> Oh,
But you're not to ride yourbike again until I say so.>> Oh, Dic
But you're not to ride yourbike again until I say so.>> Oh, Dicey
But you're not to ride yourbike again until I say so.>> Oh, Dicey--
bike again until I say so.>> Oh, Dicey--
Yo
You
You ha
You have t
You have to
You have to sa
You have to say
You have to say when
You have to say whenyo
You have to say whenyou'
You have to say whenyou're
You have to say whenyou're goi
You have to say whenyou're going
You have to say whenyou're going o
You have to say whenyou're going off
You have to say whenyou're going off.
You have to say whenyou're going off.>> I
You have to say whenyou're going off.>> I k
You have to say whenyou're going off.>> I kno
You have to say whenyou're going off.>> I know,
You have to say whenyou're going off.>> I know, I w
You have to say whenyou're going off.>> I know, I wil
You have to say whenyou're going off.>> I know, I will.
you're going off.>> I know, I will.
you're going off.>> I know, I will.I'
you're going off.>> I know, I will.I'm
you're going off.>> I know, I will.I'm sorr
you're going off.>> I know, I will.I'm sorry,
you're going off.>> I know, I will.I'm sorry, D
you're going off.>> I know, I will.I'm sorry, Dic
you're going off.>> I know, I will.I'm sorry, Dicey.
>> I know, I will.I'm sorry, Dicey.
>> I know, I will.I'm sorry, Dicey.I'
>> I know, I will.I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm
>> I know, I will.I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorr
>> I know, I will.I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry
>> I know, I will.I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to
>> I know, I will.I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to y
>> I know, I will.I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you t
>> I know, I will.I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too
>> I know, I will.I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,
I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,
I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,bu
I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,but
I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,but it
I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,but it's m
I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,but it's my
I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,but it's my fa
I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,but it's my faul
I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,but it's my fault, n
I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,but it's my fault, not
I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,but it's my fault, not D
I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,but it's my fault, not Dic
I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,but it's my fault, not Dicey's
I'm sorry, Dicey.I'm sorry to you too,but it's my fault, not Dicey's.
>>
>> Y
>> You
>> You're
>> You're a
>> You're a ch
>> You're a chil
>> You're a child.
>> You're a child.>>
>> You're a child.>> S
>> You're a child.>> So
>> You're a child.>> So is D
>> You're a child.>> So is Dic
>> You're a child.>> So is Dicey
>> You're a child.>> So is Dicey.
>> W
>> Who
>> Whose
>> Whose h
>> Whose house
>> Whose house i
>> Whose house is
>> Whose house is th
>> Whose house is this?
>> Whose house is this?Wh
>> Whose house is this?Whos
>> Whose house is this?Whose fo
>> Whose house is this?Whose food
>> Whose house is this?Whose food,
>> Whose house is this?Whose food, wh
>> Whose house is this?Whose food, whose
>> Whose house is this?Whose food, whose ta
>> Whose house is this?Whose food, whose tabl
>> Whose house is this?Whose food, whose table?
>> Whose house is this?Whose food, whose table?>> Y
>> Whose house is this?Whose food, whose table?>> You
>> Whose house is this?Whose food, whose table?>> You'r
>> Whose house is this?Whose food, whose table?>> You're
>> Whose house is this?Whose food, whose table?>> You're righ
>> Whose house is this?Whose food, whose table?>> You're right.
Whose food, whose table?>> You're right.
Whose food, whose table?>> You're right.It
Whose food, whose table?>> You're right.It's
Whose food, whose table?>> You're right.It's n
Whose food, whose table?>> You're right.It's not o
Whose food, whose table?>> You're right.It's not our
Whose food, whose table?>> You're right.It's not our h
Whose food, whose table?>> You're right.It's not our hou
Whose food, whose table?>> You're right.It's not our house,
>> You're right.It's not our house,
>> You're right.It's not our house,an
>> You're right.It's not our house,and
>> You're right.It's not our house,and that
>> You're right.It's not our house,and that's
>> You're right.It's not our house,and that's w
>> You're right.It's not our house,and that's wha
>> You're right.It's not our house,and that's what yo
>> You're right.It's not our house,and that's what you
>> You're right.It's not our house,and that's what you sa
>> You're right.It's not our house,and that's what you said
>> You're right.It's not our house,and that's what you said fro
>> You're right.It's not our house,and that's what you said from
It's not our house,and that's what you said from
It's not our house,and that's what you said fromthe
It's not our house,and that's what you said fromthe ve
It's not our house,and that's what you said fromthe very
It's not our house,and that's what you said fromthe very b
It's not our house,and that's what you said fromthe very begin
It's not our house,and that's what you said fromthe very beginni
It's not our house,and that's what you said fromthe very beginning
It's not our house,and that's what you said fromthe very beginning.
and that's what you said fromthe very beginning.
and that's what you said fromthe very beginning.Bu
and that's what you said fromthe very beginning.But
and that's what you said fromthe very beginning.But we
and that's what you said fromthe very beginning.But we're
and that's what you said fromthe very beginning.But we're no
and that's what you said fromthe very beginning.But we're not
and that's what you said fromthe very beginning.But we're not yo
and that's what you said fromthe very beginning.But we're not your f
and that's what you said fromthe very beginning.But we're not your fam
and that's what you said fromthe very beginning.But we're not your famil
and that's what you said fromthe very beginning.But we're not your family!
the very beginning.But we're not your family!
the very beginning.But we're not your family!Yo
the very beginning.But we're not your family!You
the very beginning.But we're not your family!You me
the very beginning.But we're not your family!You mean
the very beginning.But we're not your family!You meant th
the very beginning.But we're not your family!You meant that
the very beginning.But we're not your family!You meant that t
the very beginning.But we're not your family!You meant that too
the very beginning.But we're not your family!You meant that too,
But we're not your family!You meant that too,
But we're not your family!You meant that too,di
But we're not your family!You meant that too,didn
But we're not your family!You meant that too,didn't
But we're not your family!You meant that too,didn't you
But we're not your family!You meant that too,didn't you?
You meant that too,didn't you?
You meant that too,didn't you?>>
You meant that too,didn't you?>> I
You meant that too,didn't you?>> I w
You meant that too,didn't you?>> I wil
You meant that too,didn't you?>> I will no
You meant that too,didn't you?>> I will not
You meant that too,didn't you?>> I will not ha
You meant that too,didn't you?>> I will not have
You meant that too,didn't you?>> I will not have thi
You meant that too,didn't you?>> I will not have this
didn't you?>> I will not have this
didn't you?>> I will not have thista
didn't you?>> I will not have thistalk
didn't you?>> I will not have thistalkin
didn't you?>> I will not have thistalking ba
didn't you?>> I will not have thistalking back
didn't you?>> I will not have thistalking back.
>> I will not have thistalking back.
>> I will not have thistalking back.>> B
>> I will not have thistalking back.>> But
>> I will not have thistalking back.>> But i
>> I will not have thistalking back.>> But it'
>> I will not have thistalking back.>> But it's no
>> I will not have thistalking back.>> But it's not
>> I will not have thistalking back.>> But it's not ta
>> I will not have thistalking back.>> But it's not talk
>> I will not have thistalking back.>> But it's not talking
>> I will not have thistalking back.>> But it's not talking ba
>> I will not have thistalking back.>> But it's not talking back
>> I will not have thistalking back.>> But it's not talking back.
talking back.>> But it's not talking back.
talking back.>> But it's not talking back.It
talking back.>> But it's not talking back.It's
talking back.>> But it's not talking back.It's e
talking back.>> But it's not talking back.It's expla
talking back.>> But it's not talking back.It's explain
talking back.>> But it's not talking back.It's explainin
talking back.>> But it's not talking back.It's explaining.
>> But it's not talking back.It's explaining.
>> But it's not talking back.It's explaining.We
>> But it's not talking back.It's explaining.We'r
>> But it's not talking back.It's explaining.We're
>> But it's not talking back.It's explaining.We're ju
>> But it's not talking back.It's explaining.We're just t
>> But it's not talking back.It's explaining.We're just try
>> But it's not talking back.It's explaining.We're just tryin
>> But it's not talking back.It's explaining.We're just trying
>> But it's not talking back.It's explaining.We're just trying to
It's explaining.We're just trying to
It's explaining.We're just trying toge
It's explaining.We're just trying toget
It's explaining.We're just trying toget to
It's explaining.We're just trying toget to the
It's explaining.We're just trying toget to the t
It's explaining.We're just trying toget to the tru
It's explaining.We're just trying toget to the truth
It's explaining.We're just trying toget to the truth.
We're just trying toget to the truth.
We're just trying toget to the truth.>>
We're just trying toget to the truth.>> Y
We're just trying toget to the truth.>> You
We're just trying toget to the truth.>> You're
We're just trying toget to the truth.>> You're in
We're just trying toget to the truth.>> You're in m
We're just trying toget to the truth.>> You're in my
We're just trying toget to the truth.>> You're in my home
We're just trying toget to the truth.>> You're in my home.
get to the truth.>> You're in my home.
get to the truth.>> You're in my home.My
get to the truth.>> You're in my home.My h
get to the truth.>> You're in my home.My hom
get to the truth.>> You're in my home.My home!
>> You're in my home.My home!
>> You're in my home.My home!Not
>> You're in my home.My home!Not yo
>> You're in my home.My home!Not your
>> You're in my home.My home!Not yours.
My home!Not yours.
My home!Not yours.>>
My home!Not yours.>> A
My home!Not yours.>> Are
My home!Not yours.>> Are you
My home!Not yours.>> Are you e
My home!Not yours.>> Are you exp
My home!Not yours.>> Are you expec
My home!Not yours.>> Are you expecting
My home!Not yours.>> Are you expecting u
My home!Not yours.>> Are you expecting us
Not yours.>> Are you expecting us
Not yours.>> Are you expecting usto
Not yours.>> Are you expecting usto s
Not yours.>> Are you expecting usto sta
Not yours.>> Are you expecting usto stay, t
Not yours.>> Are you expecting usto stay, the
Not yours.>> Are you expecting usto stay, then?
>> N
>> No.
>> No.(k
>> No.(kni
>> No.(knife
>> No.(knife scr
>> No.(knife scrap
>> No.(knife scrapin
>> No.(knife scraping)
>> No.(knife scraping)(cla
>> No.(knife scraping)(clatt
>> No.(knife scraping)(clatter
>> No.(knife scraping)(clatterin
>> No.(knife scraping)(clattering)
(p
(pla
(plates
(plates cl
(plates clan
(plates clanki
(plates clanking l
(plates clanking lou
(plates clanking loudl
(plates clanking loudly)
(plates clanking loudly)(d
(plates clanking loudly)(doo
(plates clanking loudly)(door
(plates clanking loudly)(door cr
(plates clanking loudly)(door creaki
(plates clanking loudly)(door creaking
(plates clanking loudly)(door creaking)
(cri
(crick
(cricket
(crickets
(crickets chir
(crickets chirpi
(crickets chirping
(crickets chirping)
(crickets chirping)♪
>>
>> C
>> Could
>> Couldn'
>> Couldn't
>> Couldn't sl
>> Couldn't sleep
>> Couldn't sleep so
>> Couldn't sleep so I
>> Couldn't sleep so I w
>> Couldn't sleep so I was
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswr
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswrit
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswritin
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswriting
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswriting that
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswriting that s
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswriting that sil
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswriting that silly
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswriting that silly cou
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswriting that silly cousi
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswriting that silly cousin
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswriting that silly cousinof y
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswriting that silly cousinof you
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswriting that silly cousinof yours
>> Couldn't sleep so I waswriting that silly cousinof yours.
Wh
What
What a
What are
What are you
What are you s
What are you sta
What are you stari
What are you staring a
What are you staring at,
What are you staring at, g
What are you staring at, gir
What are you staring at, girl?
What are you staring at, girl?>> Y
What are you staring at, girl?>> You
What are you staring at, girl?>> You.
What are you staring at, girl?>> You.Yo
What are you staring at, girl?>> You.You'
What are you staring at, girl?>> You.You're
What are you staring at, girl?>> You.You're p
What are you staring at, girl?>> You.You're prett
What are you staring at, girl?>> You.You're pretty.
>> You.You're pretty.
>> You.You're pretty.I
>> You.You're pretty.I ne
>> You.You're pretty.I neve
>> You.You're pretty.I never no
>> You.You're pretty.I never noti
>> You.You're pretty.I never notice
>> You.You're pretty.I never noticed.
>>
>> S
>> Sit
>> Sit dow
>> Sit down.
Ge
Get
Get a
Get a glas
Get a glass
Get a glass of
Get a glass of m
Get a glass of milk
Get a glass of milk fi
Get a glass of milk firs
Get a glass of milk first.
Get a glass of milk first.Ther
Get a glass of milk first.There'
Get a glass of milk first.There's
Get a glass of milk first.There's so
Get a glass of milk first.There's someth
Get a glass of milk first.There's somethin
Get a glass of milk first.There's something
Get a glass of milk first.There's somethingI
Get a glass of milk first.There's somethingI sh
Get a glass of milk first.There's somethingI shou
Get a glass of milk first.There's somethingI should
Get a glass of milk first.There's somethingI should say
Get a glass of milk first.There's somethingI should say t
Get a glass of milk first.There's somethingI should say to
Get a glass of milk first.There's somethingI should say to yo
Get a glass of milk first.There's somethingI should say to you.
There's somethingI should say to you.
There's somethingI should say to you.>>
There's somethingI should say to you.>> I
There's somethingI should say to you.>> It'
There's somethingI should say to you.>> It's ok
There's somethingI should say to you.>> It's okay
There's somethingI should say to you.>> It's okay.
I should say to you.>> It's okay.
I should say to you.>> It's okay.I'
I should say to you.>> It's okay.I'm
I should say to you.>> It's okay.I'm no
I should say to you.>> It's okay.I'm not
I should say to you.>> It's okay.I'm not gonn
I should say to you.>> It's okay.I'm not gonna
I should say to you.>> It's okay.I'm not gonna ar
I should say to you.>> It's okay.I'm not gonna argu
I should say to you.>> It's okay.I'm not gonna argue
>> It's okay.I'm not gonna argue
>> It's okay.I'm not gonna argueab
>> It's okay.I'm not gonna argueabou
>> It's okay.I'm not gonna argueabout
>> It's okay.I'm not gonna argueabout stay
>> It's okay.I'm not gonna argueabout stayin
>> It's okay.I'm not gonna argueabout staying.
I'm not gonna argueabout staying.
I'm not gonna argueabout staying.>>
I'm not gonna argueabout staying.>> W
I'm not gonna argueabout staying.>> Wou
I'm not gonna argueabout staying.>> Wouldn'
I'm not gonna argueabout staying.>> Wouldn't
I'm not gonna argueabout staying.>> Wouldn't do
I'm not gonna argueabout staying.>> Wouldn't do y
I'm not gonna argueabout staying.>> Wouldn't do you a
I'm not gonna argueabout staying.>> Wouldn't do you any
I'm not gonna argueabout staying.>> Wouldn't do you any g
I'm not gonna argueabout staying.>> Wouldn't do you any goo
I'm not gonna argueabout staying.>> Wouldn't do you any good.
about staying.>> Wouldn't do you any good.
about staying.>> Wouldn't do you any good.(p
about staying.>> Wouldn't do you any good.(pou
about staying.>> Wouldn't do you any good.(pouri
about staying.>> Wouldn't do you any good.(pouring
about staying.>> Wouldn't do you any good.(pouring mil
about staying.>> Wouldn't do you any good.(pouring milk)
>> Wouldn't do you any good.(pouring milk)
>> Wouldn't do you any good.(pouring milk)I wa
>> Wouldn't do you any good.(pouring milk)I want
>> Wouldn't do you any good.(pouring milk)I want t
>> Wouldn't do you any good.(pouring milk)I want to
>> Wouldn't do you any good.(pouring milk)I want to expl
>> Wouldn't do you any good.(pouring milk)I want to explai
>> Wouldn't do you any good.(pouring milk)I want to explain.
An
And
And I
And I neve
And I never
And I never ex
And I never expl
And I never explaine
And I never explained
And I never explained be
And I never explained befo
And I never explained before.
And I never explained before.To
And I never explained before.To a
And I never explained before.To any
And I never explained before.To anyone.
Bu
But
But I
But I have
But I have t
But I have to
But I have to no
But I have to now, b
But I have to now, bec
But I have to now, becau
But I have to now, because
But I have to now, because,
But I have to now, because,in
But I have to now, because,in a
But I have to now, because,in a w
But I have to now, because,in a way,
But I have to now, because,in a way, I
But I have to now, because,in a way, I do
But I have to now, because,in a way, I do w
But I have to now, because,in a way, I do wanna
But I have to now, because,in a way, I do wannakeep
But I have to now, because,in a way, I do wannakeep y
But I have to now, because,in a way, I do wannakeep you
But I have to now, because,in a way, I do wannakeep you h
But I have to now, because,in a way, I do wannakeep you here.
in a way, I do wannakeep you here.
in a way, I do wannakeep you here.Bu
in a way, I do wannakeep you here.But
in a way, I do wannakeep you here.But I
in a way, I do wannakeep you here.But I can'
in a way, I do wannakeep you here.But I can't.
I'
I'm
I'm ol
I'm old.
I'm old.No
I'm old.Not
I'm old.Not ve
I'm old.Not very o
I'm old.Not very old
I'm old.Not very old,
I'm old.Not very old, ye
I'm old.Not very old, yet.
I'm old.Not very old, yet.But
I'm old.Not very old, yet.But I'
I'm old.Not very old, yet.But I'm
I'm old.Not very old, yet.But I'm ge
I'm old.Not very old, yet.But I'm gettin
I'm old.Not very old, yet.But I'm getting
I'm old.Not very old, yet.But I'm getting ol
I'm old.Not very old, yet.But I'm getting olde
I'm old.Not very old, yet.But I'm getting older.
Not very old, yet.But I'm getting older.
Not very old, yet.But I'm getting older.Wh
Not very old, yet.But I'm getting older.When
Not very old, yet.But I'm getting older.When m
Not very old, yet.But I'm getting older.When my hu
Not very old, yet.But I'm getting older.When my husb
Not very old, yet.But I'm getting older.When my husban
Not very old, yet.But I'm getting older.When my husband
Not very old, yet.But I'm getting older.When my husband died
Not very old, yet.But I'm getting older.When my husband died,
But I'm getting older.When my husband died,
But I'm getting older.When my husband died,he
But I'm getting older.When my husband died,he l
But I'm getting older.When my husband died,he lef
But I'm getting older.When my husband died,he left so
But I'm getting older.When my husband died,he left some
But I'm getting older.When my husband died,he left some i
But I'm getting older.When my husband died,he left some ins
But I'm getting older.When my husband died,he left some insuran
But I'm getting older.When my husband died,he left some insurance
But I'm getting older.When my husband died,he left some insurance m
But I'm getting older.When my husband died,he left some insurance mon
But I'm getting older.When my husband died,he left some insurance money.
When my husband died,he left some insurance money.
When my husband died,he left some insurance money.En
When my husband died,he left some insurance money.Enou
When my husband died,he left some insurance money.Enough
When my husband died,he left some insurance money.Enough f
When my husband died,he left some insurance money.Enough for m
When my husband died,he left some insurance money.Enough for me
When my husband died,he left some insurance money.Enough for me to
When my husband died,he left some insurance money.Enough for me to g
When my husband died,he left some insurance money.Enough for me to go on
he left some insurance money.Enough for me to go on
he left some insurance money.Enough for me to go onif
he left some insurance money.Enough for me to go onif I
he left some insurance money.Enough for me to go onif I l
he left some insurance money.Enough for me to go onif I liv
he left some insurance money.Enough for me to go onif I live ca
he left some insurance money.Enough for me to go onif I live care
he left some insurance money.Enough for me to go onif I live carefu
he left some insurance money.Enough for me to go onif I live carefull
he left some insurance money.Enough for me to go onif I live carefully.
Enough for me to go onif I live carefully.
Enough for me to go onif I live carefully.Wh
Enough for me to go onif I live carefully.What
Enough for me to go onif I live carefully.What w
Enough for me to go onif I live carefully.What with
Enough for me to go onif I live carefully.What with th
Enough for me to go onif I live carefully.What with the
Enough for me to go onif I live carefully.What with the gr
Enough for me to go onif I live carefully.What with the grocer
Enough for me to go onif I live carefully.What with the grocery
Enough for me to go onif I live carefully.What with the grocery bi
Enough for me to go onif I live carefully.What with the grocery bill
if I live carefully.What with the grocery bill
if I live carefully.What with the grocery billth
if I live carefully.What with the grocery billthis
if I live carefully.What with the grocery billthis wee
if I live carefully.What with the grocery billthis week,
if I live carefully.What with the grocery billthis week, I
if I live carefully.What with the grocery billthis week, I'm
if I live carefully.What with the grocery billthis week, I'm gon
if I live carefully.What with the grocery billthis week, I'm gonna
if I live carefully.What with the grocery billthis week, I'm gonna h
if I live carefully.What with the grocery billthis week, I'm gonna hav
if I live carefully.What with the grocery billthis week, I'm gonna have to
What with the grocery billthis week, I'm gonna have to
What with the grocery billthis week, I'm gonna have todi
What with the grocery billthis week, I'm gonna have todie
What with the grocery billthis week, I'm gonna have todie a
What with the grocery billthis week, I'm gonna have todie a mont
What with the grocery billthis week, I'm gonna have todie a month
What with the grocery billthis week, I'm gonna have todie a month so
What with the grocery billthis week, I'm gonna have todie a month soon
What with the grocery billthis week, I'm gonna have todie a month sooner
this week, I'm gonna have todie a month sooner
this week, I'm gonna have todie a month soonerth
this week, I'm gonna have todie a month soonerthan
this week, I'm gonna have todie a month soonerthan I
this week, I'm gonna have todie a month soonerthan I pla
this week, I'm gonna have todie a month soonerthan I plann
this week, I'm gonna have todie a month soonerthan I planned
this week, I'm gonna have todie a month soonerthan I planned.
die a month soonerthan I planned.
die a month soonerthan I planned.>> T
die a month soonerthan I planned.>> Tha
die a month soonerthan I planned.>> That'
die a month soonerthan I planned.>> That's
die a month soonerthan I planned.>> That's craz
die a month soonerthan I planned.>> That's crazy.
than I planned.>> That's crazy.
than I planned.>> That's crazy.>>
than I planned.>> That's crazy.>> T
than I planned.>> That's crazy.>> That'
than I planned.>> That's crazy.>> That's
than I planned.>> That's crazy.>> That's a
than I planned.>> That's crazy.>> That's a jo
than I planned.>> That's crazy.>> That's a joke.
>> That's crazy.>> That's a joke.
>> That's crazy.>> That's a joke.Wh
>> That's crazy.>> That's a joke.What
>> That's crazy.>> That's a joke.What I m
>> That's crazy.>> That's a joke.What I mea
>> That's crazy.>> That's a joke.What I mean
>> That's crazy.>> That's a joke.What I mean to
>> That's crazy.>> That's a joke.What I mean to exp
>> That's crazy.>> That's a joke.What I mean to expla
>> That's crazy.>> That's a joke.What I mean to explain
>> That's crazy.>> That's a joke.What I mean to explain i
>> That's crazy.>> That's a joke.What I mean to explain is,
>> That's a joke.What I mean to explain is,
>> That's a joke.What I mean to explain is,I do
>> That's a joke.What I mean to explain is,I don'
>> That's a joke.What I mean to explain is,I don't
>> That's a joke.What I mean to explain is,I don't ha
>> That's a joke.What I mean to explain is,I don't have t
>> That's a joke.What I mean to explain is,I don't have the
>> That's a joke.What I mean to explain is,I don't have the m
>> That's a joke.What I mean to explain is,I don't have the mon
>> That's a joke.What I mean to explain is,I don't have the money
What I mean to explain is,I don't have the money
What I mean to explain is,I don't have the moneyto
What I mean to explain is,I don't have the moneyto r
What I mean to explain is,I don't have the moneyto rai
What I mean to explain is,I don't have the moneyto raise m
What I mean to explain is,I don't have the moneyto raise mor
What I mean to explain is,I don't have the moneyto raise more
What I mean to explain is,I don't have the moneyto raise more ki
What I mean to explain is,I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.
I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.
I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.>>
I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.>> B
I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.>> But
I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.>> But w
I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.>> But with
I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.>> But with a
I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.>> But with a fa
I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.>> But with a farm
I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.>> But with a farm, th
I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.>> But with a farm, ther
I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there
I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there mu
I don't have the moneyto raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there must
to raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there must
to raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there mustbe
to raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there mustbe l
to raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots
to raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of
to raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of w
to raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of way
to raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to
to raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to g
to raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get
to raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get m
to raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get money
to raise more kids.>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get money.
>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get money.
>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get money.Jame
>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get money.James
>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get money.James sa
>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get money.James said
>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get money.James said you
>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get money.James said you c
>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get money.James said you cou
>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get money.James said you could
>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get money.James said you could gro
>> But with a farm, there mustbe lots of ways to get money.James said you could grow
be lots of ways to get money.James said you could grow
be lots of ways to get money.James said you could growCh
be lots of ways to get money.James said you could growChri
be lots of ways to get money.James said you could growChrist
be lots of ways to get money.James said you could growChristma
be lots of ways to get money.James said you could growChristmas tr
be lots of ways to get money.James said you could growChristmas tree
be lots of ways to get money.James said you could growChristmas trees.
James said you could growChristmas trees.
James said you could growChristmas trees.Ever
James said you could growChristmas trees.Everyb
James said you could growChristmas trees.Everybod
James said you could growChristmas trees.Everybody
James said you could growChristmas trees.Everybody buys
James said you could growChristmas trees.Everybody buys a
James said you could growChristmas trees.Everybody buys a C
James said you could growChristmas trees.Everybody buys a Chr
James said you could growChristmas trees.Everybody buys a Christm
James said you could growChristmas trees.Everybody buys a Christmas
James said you could growChristmas trees.Everybody buys a Christmas t
James said you could growChristmas trees.Everybody buys a Christmas tre
James said you could growChristmas trees.Everybody buys a Christmas tree.
Christmas trees.Everybody buys a Christmas tree.
Christmas trees.Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>>
Christmas trees.Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> T
Christmas trees.Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> The
Christmas trees.Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's
Christmas trees.Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's m
Christmas trees.Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's mor
Christmas trees.Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more.
Christmas trees.Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...
Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...
Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...wh
Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...whic
Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...which
Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...which if
Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...which if you
Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...which if you c
Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...which if you can
Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...which if you can't
Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...which if you can't und
Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...which if you can't under
Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...which if you can't underst
Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...which if you can't understan
Everybody buys a Christmas tree.>> There's more...which if you can't understand
>> There's more...which if you can't understand
>> There's more...which if you can't understandno
>> There's more...which if you can't understandnow,
>> There's more...which if you can't understandnow, the
>> There's more...which if you can't understandnow, there
>> There's more...which if you can't understandnow, there's
>> There's more...which if you can't understandnow, there's a
>> There's more...which if you can't understandnow, there's alway
>> There's more...which if you can't understandnow, there's always
>> There's more...which if you can't understandnow, there's always la
>> There's more...which if you can't understandnow, there's always late
>> There's more...which if you can't understandnow, there's always later.
which if you can't understandnow, there's always later.
which if you can't understandnow, there's always later.I
which if you can't understandnow, there's always later.I wa
which if you can't understandnow, there's always later.I was
which if you can't understandnow, there's always later.I was marr
which if you can't understandnow, there's always later.I was marrie
which if you can't understandnow, there's always later.I was married
which if you can't understandnow, there's always later.I was married fo
which if you can't understandnow, there's always later.I was married for 38
which if you can't understandnow, there's always later.I was married for 38 y
which if you can't understandnow, there's always later.I was married for 38 yea
which if you can't understandnow, there's always later.I was married for 38 years
which if you can't understandnow, there's always later.I was married for 38 years.
Wh
When
When y
When you
When you mar
When you marry
When you marry s
When you marry som
When you marry someone
When you marry someone,
When you marry someone,you
When you marry someone,you ma
When you marry someone,you make
When you marry someone,you make p
When you marry someone,you make promi
When you marry someone,you make promise
When you marry someone,you make promises.
When you marry someone,you make promises.I
When you marry someone,you make promises.I ke
When you marry someone,you make promises.I kept
When you marry someone,you make promises.I kept tho
When you marry someone,you make promises.I kept those
When you marry someone,you make promises.I kept those p
When you marry someone,you make promises.I kept those pro
When you marry someone,you make promises.I kept those promise
When you marry someone,you make promises.I kept those promises.
you make promises.I kept those promises.
you make promises.I kept those promises.Lo
you make promises.I kept those promises.Love
you make promises.I kept those promises.Love, ho
you make promises.I kept those promises.Love, hono
you make promises.I kept those promises.Love, honor,
you make promises.I kept those promises.Love, honor, a
you make promises.I kept those promises.Love, honor, and o
you make promises.I kept those promises.Love, honor, and obe
you make promises.I kept those promises.Love, honor, and obey.
I kept those promises.Love, honor, and obey.
I kept those promises.Love, honor, and obey.Even
I kept those promises.Love, honor, and obey.Even w
I kept those promises.Love, honor, and obey.Even whe
I kept those promises.Love, honor, and obey.Even when
I kept those promises.Love, honor, and obey.Even when I di
I kept those promises.Love, honor, and obey.Even when I didn
I kept those promises.Love, honor, and obey.Even when I didn't
I kept those promises.Love, honor, and obey.Even when I didn't w
I kept those promises.Love, honor, and obey.Even when I didn't want
I kept those promises.Love, honor, and obey.Even when I didn't want to
I kept those promises.Love, honor, and obey.Even when I didn't want to.
Love, honor, and obey.Even when I didn't want to.
Love, honor, and obey.Even when I didn't want to.I
Love, honor, and obey.Even when I didn't want to.I ke
Love, honor, and obey.Even when I didn't want to.I kept t
Love, honor, and obey.Even when I didn't want to.I kept the
Love, honor, and obey.Even when I didn't want to.I kept them.
Even when I didn't want to.I kept them.
Even when I didn't want to.I kept them.Alwa
Even when I didn't want to.I kept them.Always
Even when I didn't want to.I kept them.Always w
Even when I didn't want to.I kept them.Always wen
Even when I didn't want to.I kept them.Always went hi
Even when I didn't want to.I kept them.Always went his
Even when I didn't want to.I kept them.Always went his wa
Even when I didn't want to.I kept them.Always went his way.
I kept them.Always went his way.
I kept them.Always went his way.>> T
I kept them.Always went his way.>> Tha
I kept them.Always went his way.>> That'
I kept them.Always went his way.>> That's
I kept them.Always went his way.>> That's hard
I kept them.Always went his way.>> That's hard t
I kept them.Always went his way.>> That's hard to
I kept them.Always went his way.>> That's hard to be
I kept them.Always went his way.>> That's hard to believ
I kept them.Always went his way.>> That's hard to believe.
>>
>> (
>> (la
>> (laughs
>> (laughs)
>> (laughs)It
>> (laughs)It i
>> (laughs)It is,
>> (laughs)It is, isn
>> (laughs)It is, isn't
>> (laughs)It is, isn't i
>> (laughs)It is, isn't it?
My
My h
My hus
My husband
My husband w
My husband was
My husband was a
My husband was a man
My husband was a manal
My husband was a manalwa
My husband was a manalways
My husband was a manalways sur
My husband was a manalways sure
My husband was a manalways sure he
My husband was a manalways sure he w
My husband was a manalways sure he was r
My husband was a manalways sure he was rig
My husband was a manalways sure he was right
My husband was a manalways sure he was rightan
My husband was a manalways sure he was rightand
My husband was a manalways sure he was rightand you
My husband was a manalways sure he was rightand you we
My husband was a manalways sure he was rightand you were
My husband was a manalways sure he was rightand you were w
My husband was a manalways sure he was rightand you were wrong
My husband was a manalways sure he was rightand you were wrong,
always sure he was rightand you were wrong,
always sure he was rightand you were wrong,an
always sure he was rightand you were wrong,and
always sure he was rightand you were wrong,and I
always sure he was rightand you were wrong,and I gues
always sure he was rightand you were wrong,and I guess
always sure he was rightand you were wrong,and I guess I
always sure he was rightand you were wrong,and I guess I le
always sure he was rightand you were wrong,and I guess I learne
always sure he was rightand you were wrong,and I guess I learned
always sure he was rightand you were wrong,and I guess I learned ea
always sure he was rightand you were wrong,and I guess I learned earl
always sure he was rightand you were wrong,and I guess I learned early on
and you were wrong,and I guess I learned early on
and you were wrong,and I guess I learned early onho
and you were wrong,and I guess I learned early onhow
and you were wrong,and I guess I learned early onhow to
and you were wrong,and I guess I learned early onhow to giv
and you were wrong,and I guess I learned early onhow to give
and you were wrong,and I guess I learned early onhow to give up
and you were wrong,and I guess I learned early onhow to give up,
and you were wrong,and I guess I learned early onhow to give up, give
and you were wrong,and I guess I learned early onhow to give up, give i
and you were wrong,and I guess I learned early onhow to give up, give in.
Si
Sinc
Since
Since he
Since he die
Since he died,
Since he died,I'
Since he died,I've
Since he died,I've b
Since he died,I've been
Since he died,I've been di
Since he died,I've been diff
Since he died,I've been differ
Since he died,I've been different.
Since he died,I've been different.It
Since he died,I've been different.It's
Since he died,I've been different.It's m
Since he died,I've been different.It's my ow
Since he died,I've been different.It's my own
Since he died,I've been different.It's my own li
Since he died,I've been different.It's my own life
I've been different.It's my own life
I've been different.It's my own lifeI'm
I've been different.It's my own lifeI'm li
I've been different.It's my own lifeI'm livi
I've been different.It's my own lifeI'm living
I've been different.It's my own lifeI'm living now
I've been different.It's my own lifeI'm living now.
No
No l
No lie
No lies.
No lies.No
No lies.No p
No lies.No pre
No lies.No pretend
No lies.No pretendin
No lies.No pretending.
No
No s
No sta
No standin
No standing
No standing in
No standing in b
No standing in back,
No standing in back, q
No standing in back, qui
No standing in back, quiet
No standing in back, quiet,
No standing in back, quiet,wh
No standing in back, quiet,when
No standing in back, quiet,when I
No standing in back, quiet,when I wan
No standing in back, quiet,when I wanna
No standing in back, quiet,when I wanna f
No standing in back, quiet,when I wanna fig
No standing in back, quiet,when I wanna fight.
No standing in back, quiet,when I wanna fight.>> I
No standing in back, quiet,when I wanna fight.>> It'
No standing in back, quiet,when I wanna fight.>> It's
No standing in back, quiet,when I wanna fight.>> It's ok
No standing in back, quiet,when I wanna fight.>> It's okay.
when I wanna fight.>> It's okay.
when I wanna fight.>> It's okay.I
when I wanna fight.>> It's okay.I un
when I wanna fight.>> It's okay.I unde
when I wanna fight.>> It's okay.I understa
when I wanna fight.>> It's okay.I understand
when I wanna fight.>> It's okay.I understand.
>> It's okay.I understand.
>> It's okay.I understand.>>
>> It's okay.I understand.>> I
>> It's okay.I understand.>> I n
>> It's okay.I understand.>> I never
>> It's okay.I understand.>> I never g
>> It's okay.I understand.>> I never got
>> It's okay.I understand.>> I never got a
>> It's okay.I understand.>> I never got a cha
>> It's okay.I understand.>> I never got a chanc
>> It's okay.I understand.>> I never got a chance
I understand.>> I never got a chance
I understand.>> I never got a chanceto
I understand.>> I never got a chanceto s
I understand.>> I never got a chanceto sho
I understand.>> I never got a chanceto show
I understand.>> I never got a chanceto show that
I understand.>> I never got a chanceto show that t
I understand.>> I never got a chanceto show that to
I understand.>> I never got a chanceto show that to yo
I understand.>> I never got a chanceto show that to your m
I understand.>> I never got a chanceto show that to your mam
I understand.>> I never got a chanceto show that to your mama.
Sh
She
She st
She stuc
She stuck ar
She stuck arou
She stuck around
She stuck around h
She stuck around here
She stuck around here fo
She stuck around here for
She stuck around here fora
She stuck around here fora lo
She stuck around here fora long
She stuck around here fora long t
She stuck around here fora long time
She stuck around here fora long time ju
She stuck around here fora long time just
She stuck around here fora long time just '
She stuck around here fora long time just 'caus
She stuck around here fora long time just 'cause
She stuck around here fora long time just 'cause sh
She stuck around here fora long time just 'cause she
She stuck around here fora long time just 'cause shefe
She stuck around here fora long time just 'cause shefelt
She stuck around here fora long time just 'cause shefelt s
She stuck around here fora long time just 'cause shefelt sorry
She stuck around here fora long time just 'cause shefelt sorry f
She stuck around here fora long time just 'cause shefelt sorry for
She stuck around here fora long time just 'cause shefelt sorry for m
She stuck around here fora long time just 'cause shefelt sorry for me.
a long time just 'cause shefelt sorry for me.
a long time just 'cause shefelt sorry for me.Di
a long time just 'cause shefelt sorry for me.Did
a long time just 'cause shefelt sorry for me.Did you
a long time just 'cause shefelt sorry for me.Did you kn
a long time just 'cause shefelt sorry for me.Did you know
a long time just 'cause shefelt sorry for me.Did you know t
a long time just 'cause shefelt sorry for me.Did you know that?
felt sorry for me.Did you know that?
felt sorry for me.Did you know that?>>
felt sorry for me.Did you know that?>> N
felt sorry for me.Did you know that?>> No.
Did you know that?>> No.
Did you know that?>> No.She
Did you know that?>> No.She ne
Did you know that?>> No.She neve
Did you know that?>> No.She never
Did you know that?>> No.She never talk
Did you know that?>> No.She never talked
Did you know that?>> No.She never talked a
Did you know that?>> No.She never talked abo
Did you know that?>> No.She never talked about y
Did you know that?>> No.She never talked about you
Did you know that?>> No.She never talked about you.
>>
>> Y
>> You
>> You k
>> You know
>> You know wh
>> You know what
>> You know what I
>> You know what I sai
>> You know what I said
>> You know what I said to
>> You know what I said to h
>> You know what I said to her
>> You know what I said to herju
>> You know what I said to herjust
>> You know what I said to herjust b
>> You know what I said to herjust befor
>> You know what I said to herjust before
>> You know what I said to herjust before sh
>> You know what I said to herjust before she
>> You know what I said to herjust before she left
>> You know what I said to herjust before she left t
>> You know what I said to herjust before she left thi
>> You know what I said to herjust before she left this
>> You know what I said to herjust before she left this hous
>> You know what I said to herjust before she left this house?
>> You know what I said to herjust before she left this house?Sh
>> You know what I said to herjust before she left this house?She
>> You know what I said to herjust before she left this house?She wa
>> You know what I said to herjust before she left this house?She was
>> You know what I said to herjust before she left this house?She was 21
just before she left this house?She was 21
just before she left this house?She was 21an
just before she left this house?She was 21and
just before she left this house?She was 21and preg
just before she left this house?She was 21and pregna
just before she left this house?She was 21and pregnant
just before she left this house?She was 21and pregnant w
just before she left this house?She was 21and pregnant with
just before she left this house?She was 21and pregnant with yo
just before she left this house?She was 21and pregnant with you.
She was 21and pregnant with you.
She was 21and pregnant with you.I
She was 21and pregnant with you.I sa
She was 21and pregnant with you.I said
She was 21and pregnant with you.I said, "W
She was 21and pregnant with you.I said, "We
She was 21and pregnant with you.I said, "We do
She was 21and pregnant with you.I said, "We don'
She was 21and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wa
She was 21and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wann
She was 21and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wanna
She was 21and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wanna he
She was 21and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wanna here
and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wanna here
and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wanna here"a
and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wanna here"any
and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wanna here"anyth
and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wanna here"anything
and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wanna here"anything fr
and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from
and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from y
and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you '
and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'ti
and pregnant with you.I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'til
I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'til
I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'tilwe
I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'tilwe h
I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'tilwe hea
I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'tilwe hear
I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'tilwe hear you'
I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'tilwe hear you've
I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'tilwe hear you've b
I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'tilwe hear you've bee
I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'tilwe hear you've been ma
I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'tilwe hear you've been marr
I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'tilwe hear you've been marrie
I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'tilwe hear you've been married.
I said, "We don't wanna here"anything from you 'tilwe hear you've been married."
(s
(sig
(sighing
(sighing)
(sighing)My
(sighing)My h
(sighing)My hus
(sighing)My husband
(sighing)My husband w
(sighing)My husband was
(sighing)My husband was r
(sighing)My husband was right
(sighing)My husband was right b
(sighing)My husband was right bes
(sighing)My husband was right besid
(sighing)My husband was right beside me
(sighing)My husband was right beside mean
(sighing)My husband was right beside meand
(sighing)My husband was right beside meand I
(sighing)My husband was right beside meand I knew
(sighing)My husband was right beside meand I knew t
(sighing)My husband was right beside meand I knew tha
(sighing)My husband was right beside meand I knew that'
(sighing)My husband was right beside meand I knew that's wh
(sighing)My husband was right beside meand I knew that's what
My husband was right beside meand I knew that's what
My husband was right beside meand I knew that's whathe
My husband was right beside meand I knew that's whathe w
My husband was right beside meand I knew that's whathe would
My husband was right beside meand I knew that's whathe would s
My husband was right beside meand I knew that's whathe would say
My husband was right beside meand I knew that's whathe would say.
and I knew that's whathe would say.
and I knew that's whathe would say.Bu
and I knew that's whathe would say.But
and I knew that's whathe would say.But I wa
and I knew that's whathe would say.But I was
and I knew that's whathe would say.But I was th
and I knew that's whathe would say.But I was the
and I knew that's whathe would say.But I was the one
and I knew that's whathe would say.But I was the one to
and I knew that's whathe would say.But I was the one to s
and I knew that's whathe would say.But I was the one to say
and I knew that's whathe would say.But I was the one to say it.
he would say.But I was the one to say it.
he would say.But I was the one to say it.Yo
he would say.But I was the one to say it.You
he would say.But I was the one to say it.You kn
he would say.But I was the one to say it.You know w
he would say.But I was the one to say it.You know wha
he would say.But I was the one to say it.You know what
he would say.But I was the one to say it.You know what sh
he would say.But I was the one to say it.You know what she sa
he would say.But I was the one to say it.You know what she said
he would say.But I was the one to say it.You know what she said?
But I was the one to say it.You know what she said?
But I was the one to say it.You know what she said?Sh
But I was the one to say it.You know what she said?She
But I was the one to say it.You know what she said?She said
But I was the one to say it.You know what she said?She said,
You know what she said?She said,
You know what she said?She said,"I'l
You know what she said?She said,"I'll
You know what she said?She said,"I'll ne
You know what she said?She said,"I'll neve
You know what she said?She said,"I'll never ge
You know what she said?She said,"I'll never get
You know what she said?She said,"I'll never get ma
You know what she said?She said,"I'll never get marr
You know what she said?She said,"I'll never get married.
You know what she said?She said,"I'll never get married."
She said,"I'll never get married."
She said,"I'll never get married."Sh
She said,"I'll never get married."She
She said,"I'll never get married."She wa
She said,"I'll never get married."She wasn't
She said,"I'll never get married."She wasn't a
She said,"I'll never get married."She wasn't ang
She said,"I'll never get married."She wasn't angry
She said,"I'll never get married."She wasn't angry.
"I'll never get married."She wasn't angry.
"I'll never get married."She wasn't angry.She
"I'll never get married."She wasn't angry.She sa
"I'll never get married."She wasn't angry.She said
"I'll never get married."She wasn't angry.She said i
"I'll never get married."She wasn't angry.She said it ge
"I'll never get married."She wasn't angry.She said it gent
"I'll never get married."She wasn't angry.She said it gentle
"I'll never get married."She wasn't angry.She said it gentle.
She wasn't angry.She said it gentle.
She wasn't angry.She said it gentle.Li
She wasn't angry.She said it gentle.Like
She wasn't angry.She said it gentle.Like May
She wasn't angry.She said it gentle.Like Maybe
She wasn't angry.She said it gentle.Like Maybeth
She wasn't angry.She said it gentle.Like Maybeth.
She said it gentle.Like Maybeth.
She said it gentle.Like Maybeth.>> W
She said it gentle.Like Maybeth.>> Why
She said it gentle.Like Maybeth.>> Why d
She said it gentle.Like Maybeth.>> Why did
She said it gentle.Like Maybeth.>> Why didn't
She said it gentle.Like Maybeth.>> Why didn't sh
She said it gentle.Like Maybeth.>> Why didn't she
Like Maybeth.>> Why didn't she
Like Maybeth.>> Why didn't shewann
Like Maybeth.>> Why didn't shewanna
Like Maybeth.>> Why didn't shewanna ge
Like Maybeth.>> Why didn't shewanna get
Like Maybeth.>> Why didn't shewanna get marr
Like Maybeth.>> Why didn't shewanna get marrie
Like Maybeth.>> Why didn't shewanna get married?
>> Why didn't shewanna get married?
>> Why didn't shewanna get married?>> '
>> Why didn't shewanna get married?>> 'Ca
>> Why didn't shewanna get married?>> 'Caus
>> Why didn't shewanna get married?>> 'Cause
>> Why didn't shewanna get married?>> 'Cause she'
>> Why didn't shewanna get married?>> 'Cause she'd
>> Why didn't shewanna get married?>> 'Cause she'd se
>> Why didn't shewanna get married?>> 'Cause she'd seen
wanna get married?>> 'Cause she'd seen
wanna get married?>> 'Cause she'd seenwh
wanna get married?>> 'Cause she'd seenwhat
wanna get married?>> 'Cause she'd seenwhat h
wanna get married?>> 'Cause she'd seenwhat hap
wanna get married?>> 'Cause she'd seenwhat happens
wanna get married?>> 'Cause she'd seenwhat happens.
Th
They
They all
They all l
They all lef
They all left.
They all left.Ev
They all left.Ever
They all left.Everyo
They all left.Everyone.
They all left.Everyone.Th
They all left.Everyone.They
They all left.Everyone.They c
They all left.Everyone.They cou
They all left.Everyone.They couldn'
They all left.Everyone.They couldn't
They all left.Everyone.They couldn't st
They all left.Everyone.They couldn't stay
They all left.Everyone.They couldn't stay her
They all left.Everyone.They couldn't stay here.
Ev
Ever
Everyo
Everyone
Everyone of
Everyone of my
Everyone of my c
Everyone of my chi
Everyone of my childre
Everyone of my children.
Everyone of my children...
Everyone of my children...th
Everyone of my children...they
Everyone of my children...they r
Everyone of my children...they ran a
Everyone of my children...they ran as
Everyone of my children...they ran as fa
Everyone of my children...they ran as fast
Everyone of my children...they ran as fastan
Everyone of my children...they ran as fastand
Everyone of my children...they ran as fastand as
Everyone of my children...they ran as fastand as far
Everyone of my children...they ran as fastand as far a
Everyone of my children...they ran as fastand as far as
Everyone of my children...they ran as fastand as far as th
Everyone of my children...they ran as fastand as far as they c
Everyone of my children...they ran as fastand as far as they cou
Everyone of my children...they ran as fastand as far as they could
Everyone of my children...they ran as fastand as far as they could.
My
My S
My Sam
My Sammy.
My Sammy.He
My Sammy.He d
My Sammy.He died
My Sammy.He died of
My Sammy.He died of i
My Sammy.He died of it.
An
And
And th
And that w
And that was
And that was h
And that was har
And that was hard.
An
And
And th
And then
And then Joh
And then John
And then Johnan
And then Johnand
And then Johnand th
And then Johnand then y
And then Johnand then you
And then Johnand then your
And then Johnand then your po
And then Johnand then your poor m
And then Johnand then your poor mam
And then Johnand then your poor mama.
And then Johnand then your poor mama.(s
And then Johnand then your poor mama.(sni
And then Johnand then your poor mama.(sniff
And then Johnand then your poor mama.(sniffli
And then Johnand then your poor mama.(sniffling)
and then your poor mama.(sniffling)
and then your poor mama.(sniffling)I
and then your poor mama.(sniffling)I fa
and then your poor mama.(sniffling)I fail
and then your poor mama.(sniffling)I failed t
and then your poor mama.(sniffling)I failed the
and then your poor mama.(sniffling)I failed them.
(sniffling)I failed them.
(sniffling)I failed them.I
(sniffling)I failed them.I wa
(sniffling)I failed them.I was
(sniffling)I failed them.I was resp
(sniffling)I failed them.I was respon
(sniffling)I failed them.I was responsi
(sniffling)I failed them.I was responsibl
(sniffling)I failed them.I was responsible.
I failed them.I was responsible.
I failed them.I was responsible.I
I failed them.I was responsible.I ca
I failed them.I was responsible.I can'
I failed them.I was responsible.I can't ha
I failed them.I was responsible.I can't have
I failed them.I was responsible.I can't have t
I failed them.I was responsible.I can't have tha
I failed them.I was responsible.I can't have that
I was responsible.I can't have that
I was responsible.I can't have thatre
I was responsible.I can't have thatresp
I was responsible.I can't have thatresponsi
I was responsible.I can't have thatresponsibi
I was responsible.I can't have thatresponsibili
I was responsible.I can't have thatresponsibility
I was responsible.I can't have thatresponsibility aga
I was responsible.I can't have thatresponsibility again
I was responsible.I can't have thatresponsibility again.
No
No,
No, no
No, not to
No, not to f
No, not to fai
No, not to fail
No, not to fail agai
No, not to fail again.
No, not to fail again.>> B
No, not to fail again.>> But
No, not to fail again.>> But w
No, not to fail again.>> But we'
No, not to fail again.>> But we'll h
No, not to fail again.>> But we'll hel
No, not to fail again.>> But we'll help
No, not to fail again.>> But we'll help yo
No, not to fail again.>> But we'll help you
No, not to fail again.>> But we'll help youth
No, not to fail again.>> But we'll help youthis
No, not to fail again.>> But we'll help youthis t
No, not to fail again.>> But we'll help youthis tim
No, not to fail again.>> But we'll help youthis time.
>> But we'll help youthis time.
>> But we'll help youthis time.>>
>> But we'll help youthis time.>> N
>> But we'll help youthis time.>> No.
this time.>> No.
this time.>> No.Yo
this time.>> No.You
this time.>> No.You he
this time.>> No.You help y
this time.>> No.You help you
this time.>> No.You help your
this time.>> No.You help your co
this time.>> No.You help your cousin
this time.>> No.You help your cousin i
this time.>> No.You help your cousin ins
this time.>> No.You help your cousin inste
this time.>> No.You help your cousin instead.
>> No.You help your cousin instead.
>> No.You help your cousin instead.>>
>> No.You help your cousin instead.>> B
>> No.You help your cousin instead.>> But
>> No.You help your cousin instead.>> But she
>> No.You help your cousin instead.>> But she's
>> No.You help your cousin instead.>> But she's o
>> No.You help your cousin instead.>> But she's onl
>> No.You help your cousin instead.>> But she's only ta
>> No.You help your cousin instead.>> But she's only taki
>> No.You help your cousin instead.>> But she's only taking
>> No.You help your cousin instead.>> But she's only taking u
>> No.You help your cousin instead.>> But she's only taking us
You help your cousin instead.>> But she's only taking us
You help your cousin instead.>> But she's only taking usbe
You help your cousin instead.>> But she's only taking usbeca
You help your cousin instead.>> But she's only taking usbecause
You help your cousin instead.>> But she's only taking usbecause sh
You help your cousin instead.>> But she's only taking usbecause she
You help your cousin instead.>> But she's only taking usbecause she th
You help your cousin instead.>> But she's only taking usbecause she thinks
>> But she's only taking usbecause she thinks
>> But she's only taking usbecause she thinksit's
>> But she's only taking usbecause she thinksit's h
>> But she's only taking usbecause she thinksit's her
>> But she's only taking usbecause she thinksit's her d
>> But she's only taking usbecause she thinksit's her duty.
because she thinksit's her duty.
because she thinksit's her duty.He
because she thinksit's her duty.Her
because she thinksit's her duty.Her jo
because she thinksit's her duty.Her job
because she thinksit's her duty.Her job or s
because she thinksit's her duty.Her job or som
because she thinksit's her duty.Her job or somet
because she thinksit's her duty.Her job or somethi
because she thinksit's her duty.Her job or something.
>>
>> M
>> Maybe
>> Maybe t
>> Maybe thi
>> Maybe this
>> Maybe this will
>> Maybe this will h
>> Maybe this will hel
>> Maybe this will help
>> Maybe this will help to
>> Maybe this will help tostra
>> Maybe this will help tostraig
>> Maybe this will help tostraight
>> Maybe this will help tostraighten
>> Maybe this will help tostraighten her
>> Maybe this will help tostraighten her o
>> Maybe this will help tostraighten her out
>> Maybe this will help tostraighten her out o
>> Maybe this will help tostraighten her out on
>> Maybe this will help tostraighten her out ona
>> Maybe this will help tostraighten her out ona fe
>> Maybe this will help tostraighten her out ona few th
>> Maybe this will help tostraighten her out ona few thin
>> Maybe this will help tostraighten her out ona few things
>> Maybe this will help tostraighten her out ona few things,
straighten her out ona few things,
straighten her out ona few things,ma
straighten her out ona few things,make
straighten her out ona few things,make i
straighten her out ona few things,make it a
straighten her out ona few things,make it a li
straighten her out ona few things,make it a litt
straighten her out ona few things,make it a little
a few things,make it a little
a few things,make it a littleeasi
a few things,make it a littleeasier
a few things,make it a littleeasier f
a few things,make it a littleeasier for
a few things,make it a littleeasier for you
a few things,make it a littleeasier for you.
Yo
You'
You'd
You'd best
You'd best g
You'd best get
You'd best get t
You'd best get to be
You'd best get to bed
You'd best get to bed no
You'd best get to bed now.
You'd best get to bed now.Yo
You'd best get to bed now.You
You'd best get to bed now.You can
You'd best get to bed now.You can ta
You'd best get to bed now.You can take
You'd best get to bed now.You can take t
You'd best get to bed now.You can take this
You'd best get to bed now.You can take thiswith
You'd best get to bed now.You can take thiswith y
You'd best get to bed now.You can take thiswith you
You'd best get to bed now.You can take thiswith you i
You'd best get to bed now.You can take thiswith you in th
You'd best get to bed now.You can take thiswith you in the
You'd best get to bed now.You can take thiswith you in the mo
You'd best get to bed now.You can take thiswith you in the morn
You'd best get to bed now.You can take thiswith you in the morning.
You can take thiswith you in the morning.
You can take thiswith you in the morning.>>
You can take thiswith you in the morning.>> B
You can take thiswith you in the morning.>> But
You can take thiswith you in the morning.>> But w
You can take thiswith you in the morning.>> But we ha
You can take thiswith you in the morning.>> But we have
You can take thiswith you in the morning.>> But we haven'
You can take thiswith you in the morning.>> But we haven't
You can take thiswith you in the morning.>> But we haven't fini
You can take thiswith you in the morning.>> But we haven't finish
You can take thiswith you in the morning.>> But we haven't finished
with you in the morning.>> But we haven't finished
with you in the morning.>> But we haven't finishedth
with you in the morning.>> But we haven't finishedthe
with you in the morning.>> But we haven't finishedthe ba
with you in the morning.>> But we haven't finishedthe barn y
with you in the morning.>> But we haven't finishedthe barn yet
with you in the morning.>> But we haven't finishedthe barn yet.
>> But we haven't finishedthe barn yet.
>> But we haven't finishedthe barn yet.>>
>> But we haven't finishedthe barn yet.>> T
>> But we haven't finishedthe barn yet.>> The
>> But we haven't finishedthe barn yet.>> The bus
>> But we haven't finishedthe barn yet.>> The bus l
>> But we haven't finishedthe barn yet.>> The bus lea
>> But we haven't finishedthe barn yet.>> The bus leave
>> But we haven't finishedthe barn yet.>> The bus leaves at
the barn yet.>> The bus leaves at
the barn yet.>> The bus leaves at8:
the barn yet.>> The bus leaves at8:00
the barn yet.>> The bus leaves at8:00 s
the barn yet.>> The bus leaves at8:00 sharp
the barn yet.>> The bus leaves at8:00 sharp.
>> The bus leaves at8:00 sharp.
>> The bus leaves at8:00 sharp.So w
>> The bus leaves at8:00 sharp.So we
>> The bus leaves at8:00 sharp.So we le
>> The bus leaves at8:00 sharp.So we leav
>> The bus leaves at8:00 sharp.So we leave he
>> The bus leaves at8:00 sharp.So we leave here
>> The bus leaves at8:00 sharp.So we leave here a
>> The bus leaves at8:00 sharp.So we leave here at
>> The bus leaves at8:00 sharp.So we leave here at 7:30
>> The bus leaves at8:00 sharp.So we leave here at 7:30.
8:00 sharp.So we leave here at 7:30.
8:00 sharp.So we leave here at 7:30.Tu
8:00 sharp.So we leave here at 7:30.Turn
8:00 sharp.So we leave here at 7:30.Turn off
8:00 sharp.So we leave here at 7:30.Turn off t
8:00 sharp.So we leave here at 7:30.Turn off the
8:00 sharp.So we leave here at 7:30.Turn off the l
8:00 sharp.So we leave here at 7:30.Turn off the light
8:00 sharp.So we leave here at 7:30.Turn off the lights
So we leave here at 7:30.Turn off the lights
So we leave here at 7:30.Turn off the lightswhen
So we leave here at 7:30.Turn off the lightswhen y
So we leave here at 7:30.Turn off the lightswhen you
So we leave here at 7:30.Turn off the lightswhen you'r
So we leave here at 7:30.Turn off the lightswhen you're do
So we leave here at 7:30.Turn off the lightswhen you're done
So we leave here at 7:30.Turn off the lightswhen you're done.
Turn off the lightswhen you're done.
Turn off the lightswhen you're done.>>
Turn off the lightswhen you're done.>> Y
Turn off the lightswhen you're done.>> You
Turn off the lightswhen you're done.>> You sho
Turn off the lightswhen you're done.>> You shoul
Turn off the lightswhen you're done.>> You should
Turn off the lightswhen you're done.>> You should le
Turn off the lightswhen you're done.>> You should let us
Turn off the lightswhen you're done.>> You should let us s
Turn off the lightswhen you're done.>> You should let us sta
Turn off the lightswhen you're done.>> You should let us stay,
when you're done.>> You should let us stay,
when you're done.>> You should let us stay,yo
when you're done.>> You should let us stay,you
when you're done.>> You should let us stay,you know
when you're done.>> You should let us stay,you know.
>> You should let us stay,you know.
>> You should let us stay,you know.Yo
>> You should let us stay,you know.You
>> You should let us stay,you know.You sh
>> You should let us stay,you know.You should
>> You should let us stay,you know.You should.
you know.You should.
you know.You should.>>
you know.You should.>> D
you know.You should.>> Don
you know.You should.>> Don't y
you know.You should.>> Don't you
you know.You should.>> Don't you l
you know.You should.>> Don't you lis
you know.You should.>> Don't you listen,
you know.You should.>> Don't you listen, g
you know.You should.>> Don't you listen, gir
you know.You should.>> Don't you listen, girl?
You should.>> Don't you listen, girl?
You should.>> Don't you listen, girl?I sa
You should.>> Don't you listen, girl?I said
You should.>> Don't you listen, girl?I said n
You should.>> Don't you listen, girl?I said no.
An
And
And th
And there'
And there's
And there's an
And there's an e
And there's an end t
And there's an end to
And there's an end to it
And there's an end to it.
(doo
(door
(door op
(door open
(door opening)
(b
(ban
(bangi
(banging)
♪
(doo
(door
(door cr
(door crea
(door creaking
(door creaking)
(bir
(birds
(birds c
(birds chi
(birds chirpin
(birds chirping)
Ho
How
How ma
How many e
How many egg
How many eggs
How many eggs do
How many eggs does
How many eggs doesev
How many eggs doesever
How many eggs doeseveryb
How many eggs doeseverybody
How many eggs doeseverybody wa
How many eggs doeseverybody want
How many eggs doeseverybody want?
How many eggs doeseverybody want?>>
How many eggs doeseverybody want?>> W
How many eggs doeseverybody want?>> We'
How many eggs doeseverybody want?>> We're n
How many eggs doeseverybody want?>> We're not
How many eggs doeseverybody want?>> We're not h
How many eggs doeseverybody want?>> We're not hun
How many eggs doeseverybody want?>> We're not hungry.
>> S
>> Sui
>> Suit
>> Suit yo
>> Suit yourse
>> Suit yourselv
>> Suit yourselves
>> Suit yourselves.
(i
(ins
(insec
(insects
(insects chi
(insects chirp
(insects chirpin
(insects chirping,
(insects chirping, buz
(insects chirping, buzzi
(insects chirping, buzzing
(insects chirping, buzzing)
♪
(s
(sea
(seagull
(seagulls
(seagulls sq
(seagulls squa
(seagulls squawkin
(seagulls squawking)
(m
(mot
(motor
(motor shu
(motor shutt
(motor shuttin
(motor shutting
(motor shutting down
(motor shutting down)
(d
(doo
(door
(door cr
(door creaki
(door creaking
(door creaking)
>> M
>> Mor
>> Morni
>> Morning
>> Morning, Ab
>> Morning, Ab.
>> Morning, Ab.Wh
>> Morning, Ab.What
>> Morning, Ab.What c
>> Morning, Ab.What can
>> Morning, Ab.What can I..
>> Morning, Ab.What can I...
(d
(doo
(door
(door crea
(door creaki
(door creaking
(door creaking)
(b
(bus
(bus a
(bus app
(bus approac
(bus approachi
(bus approaching
(bus approaching)
(a
(air
(air bra
(air brake
(air brakes
(air brakes hi
(air brakes hissin
(air brakes hissing)
(b
(bra
(brake
(brakes sq
(brakes sque
(brakes squeal
(brakes squealin
(brakes squealing)
(brakes squealing)(h
(brakes squealing)(his
(brakes squealing)(hissi
(brakes squealing)(hissing)
(l
(lig
(light
(lighter f
(lighter fli
(lighter flick
(lighter flicks,
(lighter flicks, clo
(lighter flicks, close
(lighter flicks, closes)
(doo
(door
(door cr
(door crea
(door creaking
(door creaking)
♪
(bra
(brake
(brakes
(brakes hi
(brakes hissin
(brakes hissing)
(i
(ind
(indis
(indistinc
(indistinct
(indistinct ch
(indistinct chat
(indistinct chatter)
>>
>> M
>> Mil
>> Millie?
>> Millie?>>
>> Millie?>> H
>> Millie?>> Hol
>> Millie?>> Hold on
>> Millie?>> Hold on.
>> Millie?>> Hold on.>>
>> Millie?>> Hold on.>> I
>> Millie?>> Hold on.>> I'd
>> Millie?>> Hold on.>> I'd lik
>> Millie?>> Hold on.>> I'd like
>> Millie?>> Hold on.>> I'd like yo
>> Millie?>> Hold on.>> I'd like you
>> Millie?>> Hold on.>> I'd like you to m
>> Millie?>> Hold on.>> I'd like you to mee
>> Millie?>> Hold on.>> I'd like you to meet
>> Hold on.>> I'd like you to meet
>> Hold on.>> I'd like you to meetmy
>> Hold on.>> I'd like you to meetmy g
>> Hold on.>> I'd like you to meetmy grand
>> Hold on.>> I'd like you to meetmy grandch
>> Hold on.>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchil
>> Hold on.>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildr
>> Hold on.>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildren.
>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildren.
>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildren.Th
>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildren.This
>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildren.This i
>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildren.This is Di
>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildren.This is Dice
>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildren.This is Dicey,
>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildren.This is Dicey, J
>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildren.This is Dicey, James
>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildren.This is Dicey, James,
>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildren.This is Dicey, James, Ma
>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildren.This is Dicey, James, Mayb
>> I'd like you to meetmy grandchildren.This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.
my grandchildren.This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.
my grandchildren.This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.An
my grandchildren.This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.And
my grandchildren.This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.And th
my grandchildren.This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.And this o
my grandchildren.This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.And this one
my grandchildren.This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.And this one's
my grandchildren.This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.And this one's S
my grandchildren.This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.And this one's Sammy
my grandchildren.This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.And this one's Sammy.
This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.And this one's Sammy.
This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.And this one's Sammy.>>
This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.And this one's Sammy.>> W
This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.And this one's Sammy.>> Wel
This is Dicey, James, Maybeth.And this one's Sammy.>> Well...
And this one's Sammy.>> Well...
And this one's Sammy.>> Well...th
And this one's Sammy.>> Well...the
And this one's Sammy.>> Well...the plea
And this one's Sammy.>> Well...the pleasu
And this one's Sammy.>> Well...the pleasure
And this one's Sammy.>> Well...the pleasure's
And this one's Sammy.>> Well...the pleasure's min
And this one's Sammy.>> Well...the pleasure's mine,
And this one's Sammy.>> Well...the pleasure's mine, I
And this one's Sammy.>> Well...the pleasure's mine, I'm
And this one's Sammy.>> Well...the pleasure's mine, I'm sur
And this one's Sammy.>> Well...the pleasure's mine, I'm sure.
>>
>> W
>> Well,
>> Well, o
>> Well, oka
>> Well, okay,
>> Well, okay, Til
>> Well, okay, Tille
>> Well, okay, Tillerm
>> Well, okay, Tillerman
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Le
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let'
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let's
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let's keep
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let's keep i
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let's keep it
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let's keep it go
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let's keep it going.
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let's keep it going.Ca
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let's keep it going.Can'
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let's keep it going.Can't be
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let's keep it going.Can't be g
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let's keep it going.Can't be gro
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let's keep it going.Can't be growi
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let's keep it going.Can't be growing o
>> Well, okay, Tillermans.Let's keep it going.Can't be growing old
Let's keep it going.Can't be growing old
Let's keep it going.Can't be growing oldin a
Let's keep it going.Can't be growing oldin a d
Let's keep it going.Can't be growing oldin a dam
Let's keep it going.Can't be growing oldin a damn
Let's keep it going.Can't be growing oldin a damn groc
Let's keep it going.Can't be growing oldin a damn grocer
Let's keep it going.Can't be growing oldin a damn grocery
Let's keep it going.Can't be growing oldin a damn grocery st
Let's keep it going.Can't be growing oldin a damn grocery store.
(d
(doo
(door
(door crea
(door creaki
(door creaking
(door creaking)
Mi
Mill
Millie
Millie,
Millie, you
Millie, you ev
Millie, you ever
Millie, you ever b
Millie, you ever buy
Millie, you ever buya Ch
Millie, you ever buya Chri
Millie, you ever buya Christ
Millie, you ever buya Christma
Millie, you ever buya Christmas tr
Millie, you ever buya Christmas tree
Millie, you ever buya Christmas tree?
Millie, you ever buya Christmas tree?>>
Millie, you ever buya Christmas tree?>> Y
Millie, you ever buya Christmas tree?>> Yea
Millie, you ever buya Christmas tree?>> Yeah,
Millie, you ever buya Christmas tree?>> Yeah, eve
Millie, you ever buya Christmas tree?>> Yeah, every
Millie, you ever buya Christmas tree?>> Yeah, every y
Millie, you ever buya Christmas tree?>> Yeah, every yea
Millie, you ever buya Christmas tree?>> Yeah, every year.
a Christmas tree?>> Yeah, every year.
a Christmas tree?>> Yeah, every year.Wh
a Christmas tree?>> Yeah, every year.Why?
>>
>> Y
>> You
>> You lik
>> You like
>> You like us
>> You like us,
>> You like us, don'
>> You like us, don't
>> You like us, don't yo
>> You like us, don't you?
>> You like us, don't you?Yo
>> You like us, don't you?You
>> You like us, don't you?You do
>> You like us, don't you?You do, no
>> You like us, don't you?You do, no m
>> You like us, don't you?You do, no mat
>> You like us, don't you?You do, no matte
>> You like us, don't you?You do, no matter wh
>> You like us, don't you?You do, no matter what
>> You like us, don't you?You do, no matter what y
>> You like us, don't you?You do, no matter what you
>> You like us, don't you?You do, no matter what you say
>> You like us, don't you?You do, no matter what you say,
>> You like us, don't you?You do, no matter what you say,I
>> You like us, don't you?You do, no matter what you say,I kn
>> You like us, don't you?You do, no matter what you say,I know
>> You like us, don't you?You do, no matter what you say,I know.
You do, no matter what you say,I know.
You do, no matter what you say,I know.>>
You do, no matter what you say,I know.>> N
You do, no matter what you say,I know.>> Nev
You do, no matter what you say,I know.>> Never s
You do, no matter what you say,I know.>> Never sai
You do, no matter what you say,I know.>> Never said
You do, no matter what you say,I know.>> Never said I
You do, no matter what you say,I know.>> Never said I didn
You do, no matter what you say,I know.>> Never said I didn't
You do, no matter what you say,I know.>> Never said I didn't.
I know.>> Never said I didn't.
I know.>> Never said I didn't.(hor
I know.>> Never said I didn't.(horn
I know.>> Never said I didn't.(horn ho
I know.>> Never said I didn't.(horn honk
I know.>> Never said I didn't.(horn honking)
(f
(fog
(fog h
(fog horn
(fog horn ho
(fog horn honk
(fog horn honkin
(fog horn honking)
(m
(mot
(motor
(motor s
(motor start
(motor startin
(motor starting)
>>
>> R
>> Rea
>> Ready t
>> Ready to
>> Ready to go
>> Ready to go h
>> Ready to go home?
>> Ready to go home?>>
>> Ready to go home?>> R
>> Ready to go home?>> Rea
>> Ready to go home?>> Ready.
>> Ready to go home?>> Ready.♪
When
When S
When Sam
When Sammy
When Sammy ask
When Sammy asked
When Sammy asked w
When Sammy asked wha
When Sammy asked what
When Sammy asked whatwe
When Sammy asked whatwe s
When Sammy asked whatwe sho
When Sammy asked whatwe shoul
When Sammy asked whatwe should ca
When Sammy asked whatwe should call
When Sammy asked whatwe should call h
When Sammy asked whatwe should call her
When Sammy asked whatwe should call her,
When Sammy asked whatwe should call her,she
When Sammy asked whatwe should call her,she sa
When Sammy asked whatwe should call her,she said
When Sammy asked whatwe should call her,she said,
When Sammy asked whatwe should call her,she said, "Cal
When Sammy asked whatwe should call her,she said, "Call
When Sammy asked whatwe should call her,she said, "Call me
When Sammy asked whatwe should call her,she said, "Call me '
When Sammy asked whatwe should call her,she said, "Call me 'Gram
When Sammy asked whatwe should call her,she said, "Call me 'Gram.'
When Sammy asked whatwe should call her,she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"
we should call her,she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"
we should call her,she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I
we should call her,she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I gu
we should call her,she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I gues
we should call her,she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess yo
we should call her,she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you
we should call her,she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you ne
we should call her,she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you neve
we should call her,she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you never kn
we should call her,she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you never know
she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you never know
she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you never knowwh
she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you never knowwher
she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you never knowwhere
she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you never knowwhere road
she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you never knowwhere roads
she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you never knowwhere roads wi
she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you never knowwhere roads will
she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you never knowwhere roads will end
she said, "Call me 'Gram.'"I guess you never knowwhere roads will end.
I guess you never knowwhere roads will end.
I guess you never knowwhere roads will end.Yo
I guess you never knowwhere roads will end.You
I guess you never knowwhere roads will end.You ju
I guess you never knowwhere roads will end.You just k
I guess you never knowwhere roads will end.You just kno
I guess you never knowwhere roads will end.You just know
I guess you never knowwhere roads will end.You just know th
I guess you never knowwhere roads will end.You just know that t
I guess you never knowwhere roads will end.You just know that the
I guess you never knowwhere roads will end.You just know that they
I guess you never knowwhere roads will end.You just know that they do
I guess you never knowwhere roads will end.You just know that they do.
>>
>> ♪ T
>> ♪ The
>> ♪ The w
>> ♪ The wat
>> ♪ The water i
>> ♪ The water is
>> ♪ The water is wi
>> ♪ The water is wide
>> ♪ The water is wide ♪
>> ♪ The water is wide ♪♪
>> ♪ The water is wide ♪♪ I
>> ♪ The water is wide ♪♪ I c
>> ♪ The water is wide ♪♪ I can't
>> ♪ The water is wide ♪♪ I can't c
>> ♪ The water is wide ♪♪ I can't cro
>> ♪ The water is wide ♪♪ I can't cross
>> ♪ The water is wide ♪♪ I can't cross ove
>> ♪ The water is wide ♪♪ I can't cross over
>> ♪ The water is wide ♪♪ I can't cross over ♪
♪
♪ A
♪ And n
♪ And nei
♪ And neith
♪ And neither
♪ And neither hav
♪ And neither have
♪ And neither have ♪
♪ And neither have ♪♪
♪ And neither have ♪♪ I
♪ And neither have ♪♪ I w
♪ And neither have ♪♪ I wings
♪ And neither have ♪♪ I wings t
♪ And neither have ♪♪ I wings to
♪ And neither have ♪♪ I wings to fl
♪ And neither have ♪♪ I wings to fly ♪
♪
♪ G
♪ Giv
♪ Give me
♪ Give me a
♪ Give me a b
♪ Give me a boa
♪ Give me a boat ♪
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ T
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ Tha
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That ca
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can ca
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carr
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry tw
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ A
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And bot
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both sh
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shal
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall ro
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪ M
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪ My
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪ My lo
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪ My love
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪ My love and
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪ My love and I
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪ My love and I ♪
♪ G
♪ Giv
♪ Give
♪ Give me
♪ Give me a b
♪ Give me a boa
♪ Give me a boat
♪ Give me a boat ♪
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ T
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ Tha
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That ca
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can ca
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carr
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry tw
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ A
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And bot
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both sh
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shal
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall ro
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row
♪ Give me a boat ♪♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪ M
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪ My
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪ My love
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪ My love a
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪ My love and
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪ My love and I
♪ That can carry two ♪♪ And both shall row ♪♪ My love and I ♪
♪