[FILM REEL PLAYS]
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
The catastrophic death
of a star
brings new life
to the universe.
In order for us to live
a star must die.
We are all stardust.
Do you know your place
in the universe?
And for so long we thought
that Earth was the center
of the solar system
and the Milky Way
like spilled milk
across the sky
but we discovered we aren't
the center of the universe.
Do you know where you are?
What kind of neighborhood does
our galaxy live in?
What other kinds
of neighborhoods exist
in the universe?
Can you explain your place
Most people can't
get out of New Orleans,
Louisiana.
Ninety percent of the matter
in the universe
is invisible.
It's unidentified.
There is much we can't see
detect or comprehend
yet we spend our lives
trying to get to the heart
of this dark energy.
This dark matter.
And you can tell a lot
by looking.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Two one, two one,
anyone on this frequency?
Go ahead.
Hey, good morning, we got
a call of a person down.
Oluseyi Observatory.
I got here a body on the floor,
looks like gunshot.
Copy. Homicide will be there.
I'll call the coroner.
[SIREN WAILING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO]
- Hey, y'all.
- Hey.
- Good morning.
- Oh, you getting them for you?
- Yeah, the big one's mine.
- Of course.
- These boots I'm wearing.
Roof was open.
The observatory manager covered
the telescope on arrival.
ID'd the body as
Associate Professor
Jennifer Rockwell.
No sign of forced entry.
Officer posted to the external
ladder to the north side..
One of the Rockwells?
Yes, daughter of Councilman
Colonel Tom Rockwell.
War hero, Rockwell Electrics.
She held an open all lecture
last night.
We got a list of attendees,
crime scene
waiting for instruction.
It's the signature
of the .38 caliber killer.
Weren't even born yet,
Silvero.
Usually a sock stuffed
in the mouth
to keep her from talking.
What do you reckon, Hooli?
Mike?
What's up?
She never gets affected.
No, it's, uh..
...it's a burger last night,
it's not sitting right.
[SIGHS]
The observatory manager
call it in?
Yes.
Dr. Ian Strammi, he's waiting
in his office downstairs.
English dude
looks like he's been
in a fight.
Attacked her, she fought back?
Open roof.
So rain could drench
the evidence.
- Tony, get talking.
- Mm-hm.
So you guys work
pretty closely together?
We're colleagues.
And you went home last night
from here?
W... well, I... I didn't go
straight home.
I was with Sabrina White,
J... Jennifer's assistant.
Sabrina White?
Yes, w... we, we drove
to the lake
to look at the stars.
We were talking all night.
Poor Jennifer.
She just..
Excuse me.
I'm Detective Mike Hoolihan.
I'm leading this investigation.
Oh.
Ab..
A... abscess.
Came on overnight.
It's... agony.
I don't, don't know why
I'm talking about my teeth..
Jennifer, Jesus Christ.
I don't think Jesus had much
to do with this, Dr. Strammi.
You got one on the go.
You covered the telescope?
Well, w... what was I
supposed to do?
It was raining.
Telescope would have been
wrecked.
It was raining cats and dogs.
I... it was clear last night.
Jennifer was... so happy.
Seven lima yankee echo
one four two
victims vehicle secured
white Thunderbird convertible,
red interior..
[INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO]
[STATIC]
♪ I'll be seeing you ♪
♪ In every lovely
summer's day ♪
♪ In everything
that's light and gay ♪
♪ Ah I'll always think ♪
♪ Of you that way ♪
♪ I'll find you ♪
♪ In the morning sun.. ♪♪
[BANGS ON DOOR]
[MUSIC STOPS]
- Don't touch anything.
- Sorry.
Nice to make your acquaintance,
Detective Hoolihan.
Yeah, you're a case closing
legend.
I'm Stella Honey,
new reporter for Channel Two.
We'd like a statement.
Hm. I'm not the one to see.
You sure about that?
[GRUNTS]
You ever think about retiring?
[SIGHS]
Why don't you just wheel me out
into the sun, Janey?
My whole life's been homicide.
[CHUCKLES]
Now, that's no Ian Strammi.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
Oh!
Afraid of the dark, detective?
It's merely an absence
of electro magnetic waves.
Oh.
Hm.
Are you sure
you don't want a lawyer?
Yes, ma'am, thank you.
I don't think I need one.
[SIGHS]
Everything hidden, hm?
Cameras, microphones.
[YAWNS]
- Excuse me.
- I think you need that, professor.
Busted.
Hot, I... I've been obsessing
all night over an idea.
If I may I'd like to get back
to that idea.
Idea?
Not... not too much an idea
as an extremely speculative
proposition
to do with time dilation.
W... what's your subject?
My subject involves
considering the possibility
that ours may just be one
of many universes.
Call me the down to earth type.
[LAUGHS]
We didn't used to accept
the Earth went
round the sun, detective.
What happened to your sock?
What's this about?
You are a person of interest.
[SIGHS]
How long can you keep me for?
How long you and Jenifer
Rockwell been going together?
What?
Um..
Wait, J... Jen..
J... Jennifer's okay, right?
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry to inform you
that Jennifer Rockwell
was found dead this morning.
Why?
Who says why?
You say how.
How did it happen?
And who. Who did it?
Over controlled hostility
type. Yeah.
Duncan Reynolds is that dude.
Everyone's shocked, says
what a nice polite guy he is.
Well, he ain't cooperating
so, we're gonna have
to hold him overnight.
Make him sweat.
I still got my money
on Ian Strammi.
You believe his teeth story?
He'd lie about his hide
if he could.
He'd lie through his teeth.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
- I was with him.
- Ah.
Not like that.
We were just talking.
Discussing
Schrodinger's cat all night.
I'm super fond of my cat,
but I don't think I'd be able
to have a conversation
about her all night.
It's not a real cat.
It's a thought experiment.
Cat in a sealed box.
In my experience,
usually what's in a sealed box
is dead, Miss White.
She..
She gave me this.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
God, grant me the serenity
to accept the things
I cannot change
the courage
to change the things I can
and the wisdom to know
the difference.
Pardon me if you think
I'm shadowing you
Detective Hoolihan.
All the meetings in this city
and you walk into this one.
Not many held this late.
Started drinking as a kid.
Saw my brother get shot
and killed.
Gave up drinking a year ago
for good
but today I wanted a drink
so bad.
Never tried this before.
Your first meeting.
Some creepy guy's already
hit on me.
Told me to fake it
till I make it.
They say women
in these meetings
can find men police can't find.
That true?
You hungry?
Always.
Mm, I drink to be reckless,
crazy, trashy.
I loved it.
End of story.
More to it than that?
Always is.
Mm, um, let's see.
I was, uh,
fostered out repeatedly
you know, that kind of thing.
- Ever trace your birth parents?
- Mm-hm.
Funny, you being a detective
be easy for you.
I... I just know it ain't pretty
where I'm from.
So you detect the hell out
of other people's lives
but your own's a mystery.
Why did you become a cop?
Felt safe.
Safe she says.
I thought it was danger money
you guys got paid.
I... I never wanted any
other job.
My real life began the day
I got into the academy.
You remember nothing?
I got this,
it's all I've..
I've had this all my life.
That's it,
I... I can't remember
where it's from.
I couldn't live like that
remembering nothing.
Positive you can?
I'm, I'm not giving you a scoop
and I'm not gonna
be your sponsor.
[LAUGHS]
Hey, I got jamais vu today.
Congratulations.
What is it?
Jamais vu is the opposite
feeling of deja vu.
When I woke up, felt
like I was seeing things
for the first time.
Even though it was
the same things
in my same old apartment.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ON TV]
Right now reporting live
Channel Two
this is Stella Honey.
You're here.
Now you're there.
Right now
it's a bit of a whodunit
and that's all
I'm at liberty to say.
We are here
at an active crime scene
where police are trying
to look for clues.
Professor Jennifer Rockwell
was the daughter
of decorated Vietnam veteran
and prisoner of war survivor
Councilman Colonel Tom Rockwell
owner of Rockwell Electrics.
Run by his sons
Bray and Walt Rockwell
past winners of Louisiana's
family company
of the year award.
Jennifer's mother just received
a Woman of Substance award
for her charity work.
Associate Professor
Jennifer Rockwell was recently
the recipient of an award
for her research
into black holes.
Police do say that they have
suspects in this case
but the investigation is
still ongoing.
You know..
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIREN WAILING AT A DISTANCE]
Colonel.
I... I understand you have
a suspect in custody..
...and I'd very much like
to see him.
Colonel, you... you know
I can't let you do that.
Yes, I know, I'm..
I'm just talking like
a quick look.
I just..
[SIGHS]
You see, um..
...see your daughter
laid out like that..
[MUMBLES]
In the face, uh..
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Well, you know, she, uh..
...pretty much
was my whole life.
Whoever did this will be brought
to justice
I promise you.
I just want to, um..
I think I'll ever, uh..
Um, you know that love,
I won't..
I won't have that again.
Did you discover Jennifer
was seeing someone else?
This is important
to establish.
If she was,
they could be involved.
Maybe I should get a lawyer.
We are vigilant
about protecting your right.
Getting an attorney
we have to stop
this conversation.
But if we can continue talking
getting to important details
about Jennifer..
...maybe you can help me
figure out
who could have done this
horrific thing.
Uh..
She, um..
What?
- What?
- S... she..
She wanted to make..
...make love under the stars.
I... I was in a rush..
[CRYING]
I was in a rush thinking
about my idea and, uh..
...after I... I, I ran
all the way back to the house.
I must have gone
and forgot my sock.
Did she ever use drug?
Mnm-mnm.
No.
Do you?
Get me a lawyer.
- What?
- Get me a lawyer!
We don't get you lawyers.
You make a goddamn call
and you get yourself one.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR SLAMS]
So the coroner said
the last meal was burrito
uh... shot at close range.
Ah.
Angle of trajectory,
undetermined.
Oh. Shame, no joy
in finding the weapon.
- What about intimate injuries?
- Mm-mm.
- Defensive wounds?
- Mnm-mnm.
But he did find semen.
[SIGHS]
I asked him to look
for traces of cream.
- Cream?
- Moisturizing cream.
Cream?
Did you find if anything
was missing from the scene?
A... scarf.
Red scarf?
Yeah.
How did you know that?
No one mentioned it
and Sabrina White's
only just given up
her cell phone
with the footage.
No.
Jennifer's a
w... well-coordinated woman.
I... I... I won't share
the scarf with suspects yet.
Yeah.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Mm.. The scar..
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
The catastrophic death
of a star
brings new life
to the universe.
In order for us to live,
a star must die.
We are all stardust.
[KEY CLACKS]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
"We are all stardust."
Clearly had money to burn.
Hm.
Did you see this?
Only pictures of them.
There's... there's no photos
of the family.
Hm.
I mean, what do you do
with all this?
I mean, you can't take it
with you.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[MARBLES CLINKING]
[GROANS]
The smell..
Oh, Sorry, Hooli.
It's the only thing I could find
to revive you.
- Mm.
- What happened?
I skipped breakfast.
- Ugh.
- Easy.
You okay?
[SIGHS]
I'm good.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay.
Did, did Jennifer ever run
with the wrong kind of crowd?
Jennifer?
Oh. No.
Is there something or anything
that you know that you
don't want to tell us about? Hm?
When she was
in the eighth grade
she wrote an essay called
"We Are All Stardust"
and it's true.
She educated me.
Heh. She..
She told me that your hand
can come from a different star
than your n... nose can.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
So you see we are all... stars.
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
There is much we can't see
detect or comprehend
but we spend our lives
trying to get to the heart
of this dark energy.
This dark matter.
[KEY CLACKS]
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Janey?
- Hey.
- I gotta go. Bye.
- What you got?
- It's a hat.
That is Colonel Tom.
That's a hat, but it's no proof
that that is Colonel Tom.
But it definitely belongs
to somebody unaccounted for,
that's for sure.
Watch this.
I saw something similar
to this brooch
pinned to a victim
of the .38 caliber killer.
Okay
Silvero thought this scene
had similarities
to .38 historics, too.
I did.
Face blown off like a mask.
All victims female,
same age, type.
Well, look here y'all,
I think we need
to keep our focus
on Duncan Reynolds
and Ian Strammi.
Especially Strammi.
I just feel this one here's
closer to home, Hooli.
- Okay.
- Hm.
[SIGHS]
Hit me with your theory.
.38 caliber killer.
If he was in his early 20s
back at the start of the spates,
he'd be old now.
Guess he could have died
back in the '80s
when the killing stopped.
Constitution ran a story
about it.
Leaving a sock on the scene.
Mm-hmm.
The sock at the crime scene
was Duncan Reynolds'.
Doesn't rule the .38 killer out.
Or a copycat
could have used the sock
that Reynolds left behind.
.38 killer always took
an excess of souvenirs
trophies, the killer's way
of nourishing his fantasies
to relive his crimes
over and over again.
This isn't some
one-on-one crime scene class.
Just saying.
You sure there's nothing missing
from the crime scene?
Done plenty of news stories
on cops fucking up.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
Cream.
Where the hell is it?
Where the hell?
What?
[SIGHS]
My grandmother swears
by this stuff and always has.
[CHUCKLES]
[BEEPS]
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
You were up
all of the night in question
in your car, by the lake,
looking at the stars
with Sabrina..
...talking about a cat?
Yes, well, Schrodinger's cat
can get quite complex.
It's a cat in a sealed box.
You do understand
that it's not done for real.
Oh, I know
what people do for real.
It's just something we,
we think about.
Yeah, I've seen those types too.
Again, you were up
all of the night in question
talking to Sabrina,
and your cheek goes boom.
[IMITATES EXPLOSION]
Look, I swear to you,
on my children's lives
I spent the evening
with Sabrina White.
I don't know
how else to say that.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
So the question now is,
what is the difference between
this location and this, for us?
It collapses
into a definite particle?
Yes.
That is what happens
but why?
Observation changes the result.
Exactly, very good, Miss White.
Very good.
We could, we could say
it's an indication
that the universe only exists
and behaves the way it does
because we're looking at..
[DOOR OPENS]
Class dismissed.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
What? What's Schrodinger's cat?
You kidding me?
[DOOR CLOSES]
A cat in the sealed box
with a radioactive force
and poison.
Waiting for it
to release or not.
Could be alive or dead.
In my quantum mechanics world
the cat could be alive
and dead.
I guess it could take all night
to understand that.
It's kind of quick
to be back at work.
Shouldn't you be at work,
detective?
I am at work.
The lawyer says
I shouldn't be talking to you.
When you saw Jennifer
that night
what was she wearing?
Don't you wanna help me
get whoever did this?
What... what was she wearing?
A... a, a... a vintage dress.
Red shoes.
You know all this.
What else was she wearing?
Uh.. Panties.
Uh..
An old silk scarf
that her father gave her.
You took the scarf?
Why? Why would I do that?
When you're always
looking for ideas
it surprises me you had no ideas
as to who killed her.
[HUMMING]
I hope it's going to rain
on Sunday.
I gotta turn on
my soccer mum routine.
Feel like
I'm leading a double life.
Me too.
You?
What you see is what you get
with Mike Hoolihan.
[LIGHTS BUZZING]
Oh, my gosh, these damn lights.
- What's up?
- Did y'all see this?
Walt, the... the brother?
He said
"I did wonder if there
were people in Jennifer's life
we didn't know."
What does that mean?
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Rockwell Electrics,
please hold.
Can I help you?
Oh.
You're that detective person.
Oh, that's a dime a dozen
I reckon it's paste,
mass-produced, '50s, early '60s.
When I'm not working my fingers
to the bones around here
I'm an online auction carrier.
Oh, is... is, is this yours?
Oh, who knows? You can't account
for everything around here.
Did you get it out of that box?
That's my yard sale box.
Probably mine, I guess.
How well did you know Jennifer?
I never really paid her
much attention.
You know, until this.
This put her
in a different light.
Who did it?
And why?
Well, what do you think?
Jealousy? She had it all.
I mean, she was brought up
in a diamond encrusted bubble.
You know, Miriam smothered them
with her nerves.
Just sickly kids. Colonel Tom,
you gotta respect him.
He's a decorated soldier.
All those medals.
He was a prisoner of war
for three years.
I can't imagine the things
that he's seen.
You know, he tried to give them
a backbone.
They married twins, them two.
Anyway, toodle-oo.
Are... are Walt and Bray here?
Oh, yeah,
we have not stopped working.
There's no time for mourning.
[FINGER SNAPS]
No.
New to me.
Doesn't look like
it's worth much.
Laurel Ann's?
I'm always finding her junk.
Must be a hard life,
seeing what you see
breaking bad news all the time?
I wanted to ask, Walt,
y... you said you thought
there were people
in Jennifer's life
y... you didn't know?
I..
It..
It seemed to me
there had to be people
other than us.
Other than you?
Yeah. Pretty straightforward.
You wanna expand?
The thing is, uh..
What?
Walt meant
someone we don't know.
Some kind of a freak
she came into contact with.
No one that knew Jennifer
would hurt her.
You want it?
Not sure it's your thing.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
Stop. Stop.
What is it?
I'm not sure yet.
Just play it again.
Play it again.
Stop it.
Folks, the past is messy.
It intrudes like
a unwanted relative
spilling wine and gravy
at the supper table.
But we cannot grow as a city
or a people
without honest contemplation
of our messy past.
Besides, street re-namings
are costly
and disruptive.
If we hide away everything
it brings into discussion
not so much are we the city
that care forgot
but more along the lines,
are we the city that forgot?
With eyes wide open
we should
truly remember our past
and not create
a false version of it.
William Faulkner said it best,
he said
"The past is not dead,
it's not even past."
Beginning what astronomers
believe is a dance of death.
Black holes have shaped
the universe we know.
It's like we're following
the energy.
Like a trail of clues
leading closer and closer
to this black hole's dark heart.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
Dark heart.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
She wanted to be cremated.
So she talked about this?
Oh, yeah.
"No mausoleum or shallow grave
for me," she said
and she was laughing,
she was just a kid.
She was always... adventurous.
Even as a baby,
she loved spicy food
and she was always trying
to get me to try it.
I can't abide spicy food.
Do you recognize this?
Should I?
And I keep thinking that
Walt wants to tell me something.
Walt was the first to talk.
As a child,
he... he beat Bray to it.
Oh.
This empty feeling, hollow
it's... it's like a fluttering.
I can't think straight,
I can't concentrate
can't see things
right in front of your eyes.
You get these images
in your head and you...
You need to rinse
them from your mind.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
You think that's Jennifer?
Everyone thinks that,
it's my husband's mother.
He was just a child when she..
When she..
Come on, come on.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
When she..
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS]
[EXHALES]
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
There is much we can't see
detect or comprehend
yet we spend our lives
trying to get to the heart
of this dark energy..
...this dark matter.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Tony, Tony.
Did you know that your nose
could come from a different star
than your hand
and that we're all here
because a star died?
It would be against God
to believe that.
It's not a belief,
it's a fact.
I don't buy it.
I thought you believed
you were a bit of a star
Silvero, a '70s star.
[HUMMING]
You're one to talk, Joan Jett.
What's your special interest
in the .38 caliber killer?
One of his victims was murdered
in the apartment house
I live in.
All the women had the look
of Jennifer Rockwell.
White, blond, of similar age
their faces blown off
at close range.
He was dormant for decades
so I thought
came out of retirement maybe?
But now... my bet's
on Duncan Reynolds.
Motive, jealousy.
And nothing, nothing
came of your interviews?
No. Not a witness in sight.
Okay, sir, stay on the line
for me, hon
I've got an ambulance
and a rescue unit
and a police officer en route.
Yes, okay.
Where is she bleeding from?
Ah, all over, uh, her face..
Do you see a gun, sir?
No, no gun. No..
[INTENSE MUSIC]
Caroline.
Do you see that?
What is that?
[SIGHS]
[EXHALES]
Jesus.
I... I should have searched
myself, what were these guys doin'?
Playing with their drones.
- To the right and..
- Hey, hey, hold it, excuse me.
- What do you want?
- And I want you, you...
Hey, hey, get off me
I haven't done anything.
- Tony, get him off..
- Get him off.
- Colonel.
- Hey.
- Hey, Colonel.
- Fuck!
Colonel..
Get him out of here,
get him out.
- Watch my leg.
- Colonel, please come with us.
I got to the scene
to... to Jennifer and..
...the gun was just lying there
and I don't know,
I don't know what I was doing
but I... I panicked.
I recognized the gun
because it was mine.
I kept it in the drawer
of the desk.
Someone must have known
it was there..
...and they took it
so they could pin this
terrible thing on me.
I had to bury it. I mean,
what would you have done?
You wiped the gun down?
Why leave the gun behind?
Yeah, that's unusual
for a perp to leave the weapon
on the scene,
no matter what's at stake.
I guess that's why
Strammi took it
'cause he did it.
But there's no sign
of a struggle, none.
And that's likely to be
somebody she knows.
Doctor.
I'm surprised
he's even a doctor.
Strammi's so stupid..
I can't believe
he didn't shoot her twice
and put the gun in her hand
set her up.
What, what?
Strammi.
- What, what?
- And he's such a dope.
I'm surprised
he didn't shoot her
and then give Jennifer the gun
and make it look like
she did it.
The one person I never..
...put in the frame.
The only person
we know for sure..
...who was there.
And what if..
...the powerful recoil
when Jennifer...
Now, if Jennifer...
The recoil forced
the gun to be thrown..
...from her.
Strammi..
...sees his gun
so far from the body
he waited this whole time
and he takes the gun.
Jennifer killed herself.
There's no suicide letter.
Don't need one.
It's a myth,
two-thirds never leave one.
Shit.
Shit!
♪ I'll be looking ♪
♪ At the moment ♪
♪ But I'll be seeing ♪
♪ You.. ♪♪
This is the only thing
that seems right.
I'd like my ashes
put in the trash
and I, I am sorry
but hey, it's all relative.
[SIGHS]
Hey, uh, Ballistics called
got a partial print
of Jennifer's
on one of the bullets.
You were right.
And I should have
got to this sooner.
You did it by the book.
Well, let me see your pen thing
that little knife thing.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
Hey.
Hmm?
Case closed.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
You may have pulled
the trigger..
...but something..
...someone got you there.
[SOBBING]
The only way we can enter
into a black hole
is, is with our minds.
I guess it went and blew hers.
I don't want your ashes..
...thrown in... in the garbage..
...that's... it's brutal.
A cosmic nod to Hugh Everett.
Everett developed
the theory of parallel universes
he requested the same.
It's all in that, uh... he sung..
...he fronts that band..
...they did that,
they did that song, Railroad
"Railroad Man."
Eels.
It's a cool band.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
♪ Feel like an old ♪
♪ Railroad man ♪
♪ Ridin' out on
the Bluemont line ♪
♪ Hummin' along
old dominion blues ♪
♪ Not much to see ♪
♪ And not much left to lose ♪
♪ And I know I can walk
along the tracks ♪
♪ It may take a little longer
but I'll know.. ♪
- Are you sure you're okay?
- Yes.
It's fine.
♪ I feel like an old ♪
♪ Railroad man ♪
♪ Who's really tried
the best that he can ♪
♪ To make his life add up
to something good.. ♪♪
[DOOR SLAMS]
[EXHALES]
Are we allowed to be in here?
It's not a crime scene.
It seems like one.
I blame my father.
What?
For jump starting her interest
in vintage
and giving her stuff.
Do you think he gave her this?
Maybe.
It's quite a statement,
it's all relative.
Einstein.
Typical Jennifer.
I mean, you don't think
her family life played any part?
She seemed pretty well adjusted
when it came to them.
♪ I'll be seeing you ♪
♪ In every
lovely summer's day ♪
♪ In everything
that's light and gay.. ♪♪
[INTENSE MUSIC]
This is her writing.
It's, uh..
...from a psychology book.
"He may only know himself
as persona
"this is all that is shown
to society..
...persona."
Facade.
Public image.
Guys, you know
what that says to me?
I never knew the real Jennifer.
How pitiful is that?
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
In this stunning case,
there's now been a twist
from homicide to suicide.
She was an inspirational figure
in the department
and she would have wanted us
to carry on.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
That first semester she seems..
...uh, something was up,
I don't know.
I went to dinner with her
and her parents
and the twins wins..
Yeah.
Her father like presided
over the table
like a high pressure
quiz master.
Mm.
And he literally, like
firing questions.
You know one of the twins cried
because he got
a question wrong.
But she was a total go-gettter
and won every prize going,
just perfect.
But..
...it was as though
she was some..
...you know, um..
...wearing a mask.
An episode of crime
is a police matter.
I mean, to... to survive
a prisoner of war camp
it... it takes
a... a... a certain kind of man.
I think something happened
between Jennifer
and your father that night.
Why would she go and do this?
Listen..
...she may have thought
she was only killin' herself.
But you know what?
It's as though she went
and killed everyone around her.
Why?
Why would she do this?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[CAT MEWING]
[CAR APPROACHING]
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
♪ I'll ♪
♪ Be seeing you ♪
♪ In all the old ♪
♪ Familiar places ♪
♪ That this heart
of mine embraces ♪
♪ All day through ♪
♪ In that small cafe ♪
♪ The park across the way ♪
♪ The children's carousel ♪
♪ The chestnut tree ♪
♪ And the wishing well ♪♪
[CAT MEWING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
I remember when you solved
your first
how it felt..
...giving the victim's families
a chance to know
to grieve..
...giving them closure.
I hate that word.
Look I don't mean
to pull rank
but I had a complaint
come in from Bray Rockwell.
Lay off the Rockwells.
Jeez, Hooli, uh..
I'd feel like
I was doin' my job
if you pay a visit
to the doctor.
You're right.
- Yeah?
- I'll go.
You'll go?
I'd like to ask you
about the state of mind
of a former patient,
Jennifer Rockwell.
Were you surprised
by her suicide?
Every 30 seconds someone
in the world kills themselves.
Many mask their depression.
Could be personality disorders
that went undetected,
childhood trauma.
Hmm.
[SIGHS]
Can I help you
with anything else, detective?
Hmm.
I'm all set.
[KEYS JINGLING]
[DOOR SLAMS]
[GASPS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
[GUNSHOTS]
Jennifer served as a model
of intellectual power..
...kindness..
...and honesty.
It's heart breaking
to reach the point
where someone
we thought we knew
well and loved..
...must remain fundamentally
mysterious to us
in their passing.
I'd like you to take a moment..
...and look at the person
next to you.
Who is that person?
Do you really know?
That person
is the biggest mystery
and the greatest miracle
you'll ever meet.
[EXHALES]
You're not naturally
a brunette, are you?
You were blond?
Yeah.
Is there something you need
to tell me, Mrs. Rockwell?
Ever dress like a woman?
There's many ways
to be a woman.
Miriam, wh... why do you think
she did this?
Did she find something out
something to do
with her father?
You know what happens
to nosey girls, eh?
They lose their noses.
Ow!
[MIRIAM LAUGHS]
I used to do that to her
when she was little.
She was the sweetest baby.
[CRYING]
He wanted her
to love him so much.
He was always trying
to... to get her to love him.
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
What if she hid something
that happened to her
like, when she was a kid
or... or something?
Like, with her father.
I don't think
it's that simple.
What's so simple about that?
When we saw water we thought
of surface tension,
fluid motion
protons, molecules.
Most people... stop
and smell the flowers
enjoy the colors.
We thought of spirals..
...symmetry..
...golden angles.
You know, you two aren't
as different as you seem.
Really, you're both..
You're both lookin'
for clues.
You, on the ground.
Her, in space.
If a universe
can be imagined..
...it exists.
Jennifer's in another universe.
She believed
in the multiverse.
It comforts me.
She only killed
one of herself.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
[RECORD PLAYER CLICKS]
[BLOWS AIR]
[BUTTON CLICKS]
♪ I'll be seeing you ♪
♪ In every lovely
summer's day ♪
♪ In everything ♪
♪ That's light and gay ♪
♪ Oh I'll always think ♪
♪ Of you that way ♪
♪ I'll find you ♪
♪ In the morning sun ♪
♪ And when the night is new ♪
♪ I'll be looking ♪
♪ I'll be looking.. ♪♪
It's like we're following
the energy
like a trail of clues
leading closer and closer
to this black hole's
dark heart.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[DOG BARKING]
It's okay. Okay.
I need to talk
to the colonel now.
He's not here.
I need your help.
Here.
And here,
can you take this?
Uh, I'm really, really hungry.
Uh... uh, I wanna go
to that place
that Jennifer goes to,
her favorite, okay?
Did you see the way
she looked at me?
Like I couldn't feed
my own daughter.
Mrs. Rockwell..
Miriam.
I wanted my daughter..
...to have the life
I never had.
I did it all for her.
I am not the woman
people see.
Just like my husband
is not the man people see.
What do you..
What do you know?
Only choice,
put on a brave face.
Like a mask.
[MIRIAM GIGGLES]
[RING CLANKING]
[CHUCKLES]
He never gonna believe
I've left him.
[METAL CLINKING]
[METAL THUDDING]
[SOBBING]
They that love beyond the world
cannot be separated by it.
Death cannot kill
what never dies.
There... she got
what she wanted.
Miriam..
...you're in denial.
Is that what it's called?
I thought
they called it grief.
You need this to end.
You can make it end.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
I'm going back..
...back to where I came from.
Seems you should
do that too... hm?
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey, hey.
[ENGINE REVVING]
Man trouble?
You got it.
[SIGHS]
[SHIP HORN BLARING]
Suicide of successful
beautiful woman, ka-ching.
Got me enough brownie points
to finally get a commission
on the .38 caliber killer
got public interest
written all over it
deserves a new angle.
You play hunches, you gotta.
So much evidence washed away
destroyed over the years
never collected.
Cast your eyes on this.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Sorry.
Never been attributed..
...but thinking maybe this was
the .38 caliber killer, too.
"Sarah Fenton, 17, a volunteer
at the Bywater Blind Society
"was accompanying a blind woman,
Heather Tolkington
when she saw a man
flee the victim's home."
[SIGHS]
Sarah got interviewed.
Nobody cared before
about what I saw that day.
Ma'am, I'm here
to re-address that.
Never took serious by no one.
But in my eyes..
[TAPPING]
...double steps.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
"Handmade mask."
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
"One of a kind."
You're not back
on the sauce again, are you?
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STOMPS FEET]
[KEYS CLACKING]
Right.
Left.
Right, left
right, left, whoa!
.38 revolver, J-frame.
Now this one's
a little heavier than most
so you could use it
to bludgeon.
The great thing about
a revolver is it never jams
it's always gonna
work for you.
The first thing you wanna do
is this release here
like that, this is where
the shells go in here.
I'll take it.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- Bywater, Gretna.
- Where's that?
Elmwood, Hopedale,
all those places
should mean something
to you, colonel
a war hero, with war wounds
to prove it.
I'm not a hero.
The heroes are the ones
that have their names
written on the wall.
Hey. Hey!
What are you, nuts?
What are you doin'?
It's crazy that
a war wound can change sides.
Cane here, cane there.
Okay, listen to me,
Sherlock, okay?
You can use
a cane in either hand.
Jennifer said,
"We spend our lives
getting to the heart
of this dark matter."
She found out about you.
You pushed her to it.
Now you just take it easy.
I'm warning you.
You stopped killing
when Jennifer was born. Why?
'Cause like those women,
she had the look of your mother.
- Now just keep my mother...
- She had the looks of your...
Just keep my mother
out of it!
- Leave my mother out of it...
- Oh, what are you gonna do?
What are you gonna do?
What are you gonna do, huh?
She had the looks of your..
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Oh..
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GROANS]
I guess you got a little
overheated.
[SIGHS]
One of those incidents.
I'm sorry,
I have them myself. Um..
[HOOLIHAN GROANS]
I get a little sensitive
about my mother.
Jennifer, uh..
...she... she... she
didn't mean to do it.
No way. Um..
Didn't mean to do it.
Impossible.
That night
I don't know what..
I mean, there was something
that just..
[EXHALES]
...just, um, like it grabbed me,
some..
- A feeling, like a feeling?
- Yeah.
An overwhelming feeling..
...of dread.
Yes.
And... I don't know why I..
I mean, you and I
have seen things
that... thankfully other people
don't have to see.
But we're forced to hold back
our... our feelings.
But I still,
for the life of me
don't know
why I didn't follow..
...follow, you know,
my instincts.
Oh, I've..
...spent my whole life
you know, just trying
to take care of everybody
my whole life.
Hmm.
It's all I wanted to do.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
No. No.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm on the wrong track.
[SOBBING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm sorry.
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
I might have guessed
this was your type of place.
Bourbon, double.
I'm wrong. I'm just wrong.
We're all human.
Jennifer used to say that.
She... she couldn't believe
that the universe
was here solely
for our benefit.
I mean, does it all
come down to this?
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
♪ Strange as it now seems ♪
♪ Of zombie voodoo
gris gris ♪
♪ And the witch-queen
of New Orleans ♪
♪ She lived
in a world of magic ♪
♪ Possessed
by the devil's skew ♪
♪ From a shack
near the swamp lands ♪
♪ Made of mud and brick ♪
♪ Marie stirred
her witches brew ♪
♪ Marie Marie
la voodoo veau ♪
♪ She'll put a spell on you ♪
♪ Marie Marie
la voodoo veau ♪
♪ She'll put a spell on you ♪
♪ Marie Marie
la voodoo veau ♪
♪ She's the witch-queen ♪
♪ Of New Orleans.. ♪♪
Come on, come on.
[INDISTINCT SONG ON STEREO]
What's the story, Mike?
There's always a story.
[HOOLIHAN SIGHS]
I just..
I screwed up.
[SOBBING]
I just..
I screwed up.
- Hmm.
- Just wrong.
- I reckon you are.
Yeah.
The kind that drinks
to forget..
...just like I used to, hm?
[SIGHS]
- Perhaps.
- How did you find me, huh?
I'm always in the wrong
place at the wrong time.
[CHUCKLES]
Maybe it's a story of a woman
who began to believe
there was only one way
to really know
the darkness of the cosmos.
Or maybe, it's a story
of a woman
with such a severe
personality disorder
and nobody even knew
who she was.
Or she just didn't wanna be
visible anymore.
Maybe she just snapped.
Couldn't take the things
she saw anymore.
Thought she was goin' crazy.
Or maybe, underneath it all..
...she really knew.
[CHUCKLES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Ah.
[GROANING]
[TAP CREAKING]
[WATER SPLASHING]
Hey-hey!
[RATTLING]
- Whoa, whoa.
- Whoo!
- What?
- Oh.
- Janey.
- Okay, I'm coming for that.
Did you finally pay the bill?
Hey, Tony. Trouble maker.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- Well, yes.
It look like
we're back in business.
- Yeah.
- Yes. Thank you.
Now I can see him.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Well, don't you wanna know
if it's dead or alive
or dead and alive?
Can't take your cat, Mike.
Well, think of it
as a... a thought experiment..
...for a little while.
Lola.
[HOOLIHAN CLICKS TONGUE]
[KEYS JINGLING]
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
[DEVICE BEEPS]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Observation changes the result.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
Like a trail of clues
leading closer and closer
to this black hole's
dark heart.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOORBELL BUZZES]
I need to see somethin'.
You're nothin' more
than cosmic contamination!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Goddammit!
I gotta see somethin'.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Oh, I knew it.
I knew it.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Look closely at that,
look at it, look! Look at that.
Through the eyes
of a fuckin' crazy lady cop!
[HOOLIHAN BREATHING HEAVILY]
It's from a murder victim.
My father collects
all kinds of objects.
It's one of a kind.
And he has lots of objects
from his victims.
He gave Jennifer things
to wear from these women.
Putting them in plain sight..
...gave him a sick kick!
I think you all
knew about this..
...for a long time.
Bray.
Bray..
...what did your father
do to you?
He didn't do anything.
He didn't touch..
...us.
But he always kept you thinking
that he might.
Like Schrodinger's cat.
Will it happen?
Won't it happen?
Won't it happen? Will it happen?
He's a psychopath!
He fooled us all.
But not Jennifer.
No.
I thought she killed herself..
...because she found out
what he was.
[INTENSE MUSIC]
But I think
she wanted to show him..
...the perfect daughter
he made..
...so she blew her
perfect face right off.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TRAIN HORN BLARING]
[INTENSE MUSIC]
[DOOR CREAKING]
♪ I'll ♪
♪ Be seeing you ♪
♪ In every lovely
summer's day ♪
♪ In everything ♪
♪ That's light and gay ♪
♪ Oh I'll always think ♪
♪ Of you that way ♪
♪ I'll find you ♪
♪ In the morning sun ♪
♪ And when the night is new ♪
♪ I'll be looking
at the moon ♪
♪ But I'll be seeing you ♪♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUNSHOTS]
[MARBLES RATTLING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mama.
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
[SOBBING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mama.
Hey, sweetheart,
wanna come with me?
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBBING]
[CAMERA SHUTTERS]
[EXHALES]
[SNIFFLES]
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
♪ Sometimes when this place
gets kinda empty ♪
♪ Sound of their breath
fades with the light ♪
♪ I think about ♪
♪ The loveless fascination ♪
♪ Under the Milky Way tonight ♪
♪ Lower the curtain
down on Memphis ♪
down alright ♪
♪ I got no time ♪
♪ For private consultation ♪
♪ Under the Milky Way tonight ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
♪ Wish I knew
what you were looking for ♪
♪ Might have known
what you would find ♪
♪ And it's something
quite peculiar ♪
♪ Something shimmering
and white ♪
♪ It leads you here ♪
♪ Despite your destination ♪
♪ Under the Milky Way tonight ♪
♪ Wish I knew
what you were looking for ♪
♪ Might have known
what you would find ♪
♪ Wish I knew
what you were looking for ♪
♪ Might have known
what you would find ♪
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
♪ And it's something
quite peculiar ♪
♪ Something shimmering
and white ♪
♪ Leads you here ♪
♪ Despite your destination ♪
♪ Under the Milky Way tonight ♪
♪ Wish I knew
what you were looking for ♪
♪ Might have known
what you would find ♪
♪ Wish I knew
what you were looking for ♪
♪ Might have known
what you would find ♪
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
♪ Under the Milky Way
tonight ♪
tonight ♪♪
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]