♪ [ "I'm Flying High"
Performed By Colin Hay ]
♪ It's easier
to love somebody ♪
than to be loved ♪
♪ You say you wanna
be somebody ♪
♪ Why don't you be yourself ♪
♪ If you wait
for an answer ♪
♪ From somewhere
up above ♪
♪ You may never
hear the laughter ♪
♪ You've been dreaming of ♪
♪ Now we're flying
so high ♪
♪ With the world
down below ♪
♪ Spread your wings
across the sky ♪
♪ Fly ♪
♪ It's easier
to love somebody ♪
than to be loved ♪
♪ You say you wanna
trust somebody ♪
♪ Why don't
you trust yourself ♪
♪ If a wave
rolls down from heaven ♪
♪ With the turning
of the tide ♪
♪ You're pulled
in all directions ♪
♪ Only for a while ♪
♪ Then we're flying
so high ♪
♪ With the world
down below ♪
♪ Spread your wings
across the sky ♪
♪ Fly ♪
[ Beth Narrating ]
This is the story of how my best friend Jody and I got rich.
No matter how many
rags-to-riches stories you've heard before,
believe me,
this one tops them all.
That's me, back in 1980,
the day Jody and I first met. Are we there yet?
Maybe we're lost.
We're not lost.
Just relax
and enjoy the scenery.
Isn't it beautiful?
♪ Now we're flying
so high ♪
♪ With the world
down below ♪
♪ Spread your wings
across the sky ♪
♪ Fly ♪
♪ Yeah, we're flying
so high ♪
♪ With the world
down below ♪
♪ Spread your wings
across the sky ♪
♪ Fly ♪
♪ You say you wanna ♪
♪ Mmm, you say you wanna ♪
♪ You say you wanna
be somebody ♪
♪ Trust somebody
Love somebody ♪
See, every summer
when I used to come here...
my Aunt Alice
used to greet me right there on the front porch...
with this big pitcher
of lemonade and this plate of piping-hot muffins.
Mom,
you've really lost it. [ Chuckles ]
Where's the mall?
[ TV Indistinct ]
Great! Two channels and we don't get either of them.
Honey, you don't want
to watch TV anyway.
Go outside
and explore the town.
I'll finish unpacking.
Go on.
It's a beautiful day.
It'll be fun.
[ Birds Twittering ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Beth ]
We left L.A. for this?
[ Sighs ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Beth Narrating ]
That was my first glimpse of Jody,
the finest woman I know.
[ Rooster Crows ]
[ Crowing Continues ]
Hey.
Get up and at 'em!
Come on.
Rise and shine!
I can't believe it.
I heard a rooster crow.
I'm used to hearing traffic.
I miss traffic.
Oh, honey, come on.
Remember our deal.
We're gonna try it out
for the summer. If we don't like it, we'll go back.
But you're not
gonna want to leave.
Hey, you know,
[ Clears Throat ]
sometimes it's scary
for me too without your father.
Sometimes I feel like
I'm walking across a big, shaky suspension bridge...
with nothing
to hold onto.
But we'll hold onto
each other. Okay?
Okay? Come on.
Okay, Mom.
[ Truck Horn Honking,
Brakes Screeching ]
Oh, my God!
[ Screaming ]
- Huh?
- I can't stop! Get out of the way!
Run faster!
Move over!
Whoa!
[ Gasping ]
Who do you think you are,
Evel Knievel?
Are you okay?
I'm really sorry. It's a miracle I'm alive.
At least I think I am.
I'm really sorry.
- Ow! Oh, my God!
- What's wrong?
- The pain is awful.
- You don't look like you're hurt.
It takes 24 hours for bruises
to show. I'll wake up looking like an eggplant.
- This could cost you
major dollars. - I'm not giving you a cent!
- I'll see you in court.
- [ Sighs ]
Relax.
I'm not suing you.
Yeah, I knew that.
No, you didn't. I had you squirming.
- How dumb do you think I am?
- Dumb enough to let a lizard crawl up your leg.
- And dumb enough to look.
- [ Groans ]
I'm gonna gain 30 pounds
living next door to you.
It's third generation.
My grandmother's recipe with one of my own special secrets.
[ Kate ] It's so nice
of you to do this. That's how we do things.
She's here!
Hey, honey!
Beth, these are
our next-door neighbors.
This is Mrs. Briggs
and her daughter Tracy.
Hello. Hello.
Hello!
- [ Snickering ]
- [ Door Slams Shut ]
Excuse me.
[ Girl ] The mall's
about 45 minutes from here.
Even if we can't get rides
from our parents, a bus goes there.
Great. At least
we're not completely stranded.
I can't believe anyone
can just come out here and pick these.
You're really into this,
aren't you?
I'm dying to go to L.A.
All those beach parties. It must be so cool.
Do you guys start dating
when you're nine down there?
Date? No.
Do you guys date?
My mother would kill me.
So when do we start dating?
Eighth grade.
That's when you start shaving under your arms.
I'm not going to.
Date? Or shave under your arms?
Sam, the men don't have to,
so why should we?
Italian women
don't either.
Tracy, I'm not having
hairy pits.
Guys hate it
if you have hairy pits.
Do you guys see my pail?
I left it over there. It's gone.
[ Tracy ]
Isn't that it over there?
Ow! Wha--
Great. The redneck.
You must be in good shape
to climb up there,
especially with
a busted shoulder.
-Don't eat those berries.
You'll get sick. -There's nothing wrong with 'em.
These are okay,
but those are bad.
Which?
Those.
Which are "these"
and which are "those"?
Those are these
and these are those.
and these are those?
"On Tuesday when it hails
and snows, the feeling on me grows and grows--"
"That hardly anybody knows
that those are these and these are those."
- You know Winnie-the-Pooh?
- Yeah. I read it with my dad.
Yeah, me too.
With my dad.
[ Groans ]
"On Wednesday when
the sky is blue and I have nothing else to do--"
"I sometimes wonder if it's true
that who is which and which is who."
No. "What"
and "what is who." What?
- That's right. "What."
- No. "Which."
- What!
- Which!
It's "which."
"What."
- "What."
- What?
- What.
- [ Laughing ]
Beth, come on.
We have to go.
What are you,
her mother? No, Jody.
Her friend.
Something you don't know anything about.
You're not worth it.
Let's get out of here.
Beth?
We need to talk
to you.
That's Jody Salerno.
She's really trashy! Bad news. She steals.
She fights about everything.
She's always getting people into trouble.
She never goes to school.
She always gets left back. Her mother is a boozer.
And she lies
about everything. Nobody goes to her house.
Not even Jody.
I hear she sleeps in the woods.
I appreciate the warning.
Thanks for showing me
the berries. I'll see you later.
Don't forget.
You heard it here first.
Be careful!
[ Tarzan Yell ]
Yes, ma'am.
Your turn.
- Forget it.
- What's wrong, city girl? Scared?
- No.
- Oh, yeah, you are.
- I am not.
- You are too.
Am no-o-o-ot!
[ Chuckles ]
City girls.
♪ [ Humming ]
Oh, look at you.
A week ago you were convinced
you'd never make any friends,
and now you're
out the door again.
Where're you off to
this time? I'm going to meet Jody.
I thought you said
you were going to start working on your book today.
I can't write
when the floors are dirty.
So, what happened
to Tracy and Samantha?
They don't get along
with Jody.
But they're wrong.
I like her.
There's something about her.
I don't know.
She knows Winnie-the-Pooh.
She can't be all that bad then.
[ Horn Honks ]
Oh. It's my mom
and her boyfriend.
Hey, girls.
Hi.
I'm taking your mom
to River Point for dinner. You want to come?
You can bring
your friend too.
Hey, baby.
These kids don't want to sit
in a stuffy old restaurant.
- Jody's having fun
with her new little friend. - Well.
I'm Beth... Easton.
It's nice to meet you.
Well, thank you. You're a little doll.
I'm Lynette.
This is Ray. Ray Karnisak.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
Look at these two.
They're ready to catch
lightning in a bottle.
Have fun, girls.
Bye, bye. Bye, bye.
They're nice.
Does he live with you?
No, but he
comes over a lot.
What about your dad?
He died when I was seven.
So did mine.
Last year.
Does your mom
have a boyfriend? No.
It's too soon for her.
Do you think
she misses it? Hmm?
It. You know!
[ Laughs ]
Well...
they always miss it,
don't they?
Why do you think grown-ups
make such a big deal out of it?
Probably because
you gotta get naked.
Ever seen a guy naked?
Babies don't count.
No. You?
In the movies.
A "P.G."?
No, an "R."
How'd you get in?
It was a drive-in. I watched through binoculars.
Can we go?
They tore it down.
Were they doing it...
in the movie?
No, but people
in the cars were.
What do people do
for excitement around here? They move somewhere else.
My mom loves it here.
She says it's better for her work.
What does she do?
She's writing a children's book.
It's about an ostrich
who gets lost. A "lostrich."
[ Gagging ]
[ Laughing ] Yeah.
Sorry there isn't
more to do, except for tomorrow of course.
What's tomorrow?
June 21.
What's so special
about June 21?
Sorry. I'm not sure
I can trust you yet.
You're fakin' me out, right?
There's nothing happening tomorrow.
It just happens to be
the first day of summer and the longest day of the year.
The summer solstice?
So?
So, at high noon
we could be rich.
How?
Billionaires, Easton. Trillionaires, even.
That's all I can tell you now,
except this will be the greatest adventure you'll ever have.
Meet me
tomorrow morning outside the elementary school...
on Dogwood and Third
at 7:30 sharp.
Hi.
Can I help you?
- No. I'm waiting for someone.
- Mind if I ask who?
Jody Salerno.
Ahh.
[ Chuckles ]
And Jody's late, huh?
Yeah.
- Did you check her house?
- I don't know where she lives.
- Hop in. I'll take you.
- Okay.
That's the one.
You want me to wait?
No. Thanks.
[ Knocking ]
[ Footsteps, Bottle Clanking ]
Yes?
Um, it's Beth,
Jody's friend.
We met yesterday.
Hi. Is Jody here?
No.
I was supposed to meet her
and she didn't show.
I told you, baby.
She's not here.
No luck, huh?
- Jody isn't a bad kid.
She's just not too dependable. - You're tellin' me.
- Come on.
I'll give you a ride home. - Thanks.
You look familiar.
You sure we've never met?
I've never been here before.
You and your mother
just bought Alice Young's old place, didn't ya?
Well, she inherited it.
Alice Young was her aunt.
- Is your mother's name Kate?
- Mm-hmm.
[ Laughs ]
Hey, what's going on?
Nothing. Jody never showed,
so the Sheriff gave me a ride home.
- Oh, thanks.
- I thought you were going to work on your book today.
I am. I have to do
some painting first, okay?
[ Sheriff ]
The last time I saw you, our legs were tied together.
Excuse me?
It's Matt... Hollinger.
I know who you are.
We would have won that race if you hadn't tripped.
[ Phone Rings ]
Wait a second.
I'll be right back.
- You're hitting on my mother,
aren't you? - Now wait a minute!
Beth, there's someone
on the phone for you disguising her voice.
Jody.
I'll be right down.
Okay.
[ Door Slams,
Footsteps Running ]
Mom, you can hang up now.
Where were you?
Do you know how long I waited for you?
[ Jody ]
What time do you have? 9:47.
At 9:57 look out
your bedroom window and I'll signal my location.
Look for the flashing light.
Tell no one of my whereabouts.
Jody, wha--
[ Dial Tone ]
I'm meeting Jody.
I'll be back early.
Wait, wait. Beth?
Where are you two going?
You know.
Just... around.
I don't want you
getting into any trouble. Mrs. Briggs says Jody is--
She's got some problems.
She--
She just doesn't have
any friends, Mom. Trust me, okay?
Yeah, okay. Okay.
You know, have fun.
Just be sure you come back before dinner.
I will. Bye.
Bye, honey.
Are you there?
Where are you?
Jody?
Jody!
[ Muffled Scream ]
What's the matter with you?
Why don't you shout louder
so they can hear my name in Canada?
- Who cares who hears
your name anywhere? - Is anyone with you?
Of course not.
Where were you this morning?
- I was at the school.
- No, you weren't. I waited there for you like you said.
I was inside
getting supplies.
How'd you get all that?
I didn't pay for it.
You stole it?
Yeah, and when I saw you with the Sheriff, I hid.
The Sheriff didn't know
you broke into the school.
Does he know
where we're going? You didn't tell, did you?
How could I tell
when I don't know?
Look at this
and you'll know.
Bear Mountain and
the Legend of Molly Morgan?
It's one of the books
from the Historical Society.
How'd you get it?
One good thing about living in this place,
a lot of buildings
close down, and when they do you can get some great stuff.
It was bizarre, Beth.
Like someone followed me there and made sure I found this.
- See that picture?
- Uh-huh.
- That was taken
over a hundred years ago. - Wow.
Know what's in that sack?
Gold.
And there's plenty more where that came from.
- After a hundred years?
- The mountain's still there, isn't it?
My dad used to tell me
the legend just like his father told him.
There's secrets in this
that no one else knows... except me.
- Who's Molly Morgan?
- The greatest woman who ever lived.
Come on.
I'll tell you about it later.
How far is it
to the mountain? About 15 miles.
We can't walk
that far. Who says we're walking?
Why do they call it
Bear Mountain?
Why do you think?
Wait.
Where are you?
Jody?
[ Loud Growl ]
Ow! Ow!
[ Laughing ]
Sound effects.
Great, isn't it?
It was a joke.
No. You're the joke.
No wonder you've no friends. No wonder you got left back.
They should've put you
all the way back to nursery school!
[ Sighs ]
Jody, wait up.
I--
Jody, wait.
Jody, wait up.
Who told you
I was left back?
I know.
That brownnose Tracy Briggs.
I don't want you thinkin'
I'm dumb. I'm not dumb.
But I am...
for saying it.
Are you comin'
to the mountain or not?
I really thought
that was a bear. No more animal noises.
Promise?
Sorry if
I scared you before. I wasn't that scared.
Oh, no? Your eyeballs
went "boing"... like that.
[ Laughing ]
You laugh like a horse.
You look like one.
[ Laughing ]
Here we are.
The Jody River.
It oughta be named
after me. I'm the only one who ever comes here.
Wait there. I've got
a surprise for you. Okay.
All aboard,
me hearties!
Holy--
Where did you get this?
There used to be
a paper mill near here.
When they closed,
a lot of boats got left behind.
All this one needed
was a new motor, so I got one.
You "got" one?
Whose motor was it?
Are you accusing me
of theft, Easton? I paid 20 bucks for it.
Where'd you get
the money? I stole it from my mom's purse.
[ Laughs ]
I don't believe you.
♪ Yeah
You should be dancin', yeah ♪
♪ Dancin', yeah ♪
♪ She's juicy
and she's trouble ♪
♪ She gets it to me good ♪
- ♪ My woman give me power ♪
- Go, Jody!
♪ Go right down
to my blood ♪
♪ What you doin'
in your bed on your back ♪
Whoo!
♪ You should be dancin'
Yeah ♪
♪ Dancin', yeah ♪
[ Jody ]
I know the whole book by heart.
"It was 1849
and the rush was on.
"Farmers, teachers,
mill hands and preachers...
"all heading to California
and the search for gold.
"Oregon was next.
Then it was our turn.
The biggest strike up here
was inside Bear Mountain." Hold it. Stop the party.
Everybody go home.
You only happened to leave out the most important part.
There's no gold left
in Bear Mountain. It says so right there.
No. Look at this.
"Whenever miners gather around campfires,
"they tell the story
of Bear Mountain's most famous prospector,
a girl named Molly Morgan."
[ Jody ]
Molly was born in Scotland in 1900.
She was exactly our age, Beth,
when her father was killed in a factory explosion.
Molly stole a loaf of bread
to feed her family.
She was arrested and sent
to a workhouse where they worked you till you dropped.
[ Whistle Blowing ]
[ Barking ]
But they couldn't
keep her caged up.
Not Molly Morgan.
They never caught her.
They thought she drowned in the falls.
But nothing could stop her.
She stowed aboard a freighter
and crossed the Atlantic to Canada.
It was hard
for a girl traveling alone.
But she didn't care.
She crossed the entire continent.
She dreamed of getting rich.
She dreamed of gold.
Back then
girls couldn't be miners.
So she cut off her hair,
smudged up her face, and next thing you knew...
a boy who called himself Morgan
was one of the miners riding a boat to Bear Mountain.
She was sailing
on this very river, Beth. The same one we're on now.
She worked as hard
as any man ever did.
And then one day
the mine caved in.
[ Yelling ]
No one could have survived,
or so they said. What happened?
No one ever saw
Molly Morgan again. Or did they?
She survived?
In 1931,
right before
the book came out,
the police arrested
a crazy mountain woman for making moonshine whiskey.
The mountain woman
called herself Molly Morgan.
No, it's true.
All those years she lived inside the mountain.
She told the police,
"Set me free and I'll show you how to find a fortress of gold.
I'll even draw a map."
You're making all this up.
You don't know any such thing.
You can't be sure that was the real Molly.
No, Beth. It's her.
Sometimes when I'm in the woods,
I can feel her watching.
Look what
she's got me doing.
I've got more gold in my teeth
than there is in that mountain.
Even if that crazy woman was
telling the truth, someone would have found the gold by now.
That's just it.
No one ever looked because they thought she was crazy.
[ Jody ] What if she was
really Molly Morgan?
What if there really is
a fortress of gold? And what if it's waiting for us...
right there
inside Bear Mountain?
This is my river...
and that's my mountain.
And now it's finally here.
June 21.
But isn't that mountain
full of caves and mines?
Yep. And one of 'em
is gonna lead us to the fortress of gold.
Which one?
There must be so many.
We'll know...
in 12 minutes.
In the book...
Molly Morgan says
you can find the cave at high noon...
on the day
of the summer solstice.
It's the only time
when the sun's rays are the exact angle...
to shine inside the cave
and bounce back.
We'll see the reflection
from here. Molly said it was so bright she nearly went blind.
As soon as I get my hands
on that gold, I'm outta here.
I'm taking a gondola
down the Grand Canal and a camel across the Sahara.
I'm going surfing
on the Black Sea and skinny-dipping...
in the Gulf of Mexico,
and then I'm going up... to outer space.
You're already there.
11:51.
Nine more minutes.
You better hope those clouds
don't get in your way.
Ten.
[ Together ]
Nine, eight, seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one.
That's it.
Start counting the money. It's real.
It's all ours!
Look out world, here I come!
[ Horn Honking ]
Say something.
You're shocked, right?
It could be an illusion.
The sun could be bouncing off some rocks.
Yeah, the rocks in your head.
Why can't you believe...
what's in front of your eyes?
There's only one way to find out, and we're not going to.
- Why not?
- You can't expect us to climb up there.
Come on, Jody. We can't.
My mother. I promised her we'd be home early.
If you were on the boat
with Christopher Columbus when he spotted land,
you'd tell him to turn around
because your mom wants you home early?
Okay. Don't get hysterical.
I hear you.
But that mountain
is still way too dangerous.
No, it isn't.
Just trust me. That's what I told my mother.
Hello!
[ Voices Echoing "Hello" ]
Good. Now the bats
know we're here. Bats? Oh, my God!
Relax.
Where're you taking us?
It looks like it's easy to get lost in here.
Get down from there.
Okay, if you insist.
- Say you'll climb the mountain.
- No.
You're gonna crash!
Jody?
Stop messing around.
What are you doing
upside down?
Yeah, right.
Take the boat over there
and we'll tie it up.
Grab my backpack.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Okay, let's go.
Follow me. Where?
I told you.
My condo.
Wipe your feet.
The condo.
Please do come into
the sitting room. Won't you?
Looks like real furniture.
They're antiques.
Been in the family for years.
Four trillion years.
This is amazing. You're amazing.
Running water, free rent.
What more could I want?
I don't know. A TV?
Of course.
"Property of
Wheaton Elementary School"?
Does your mother
know you come here?
My mother?
My mother probably thinks
that I'm still in the next room.
- You've heard about her,
haven't you? - Heard what?
Beth, when you lie
your whole face twitches.
Well, I heard
she's not well.
Not well?
Every door you open,
bottles come rolling out. The house smells like a brewery.
What about Ray?
Ray?
He's even worse.
That's why she likes him.
The two of them can get plastered together.
Oh, my God!
Jody, what happened to you?
Um, that's from
when you almost killed me with your bike.
That was your right shoulder,
and that was a week ago. Come on, what happened?
Don't worry about me.
I'm tough. I know how to take care of myself.
What are you
talking about?
[ Sighs ]
Ray and my mom
got smashed.
He treats her pretty bad
when he gets like that.
She used to fight back,
but she doesn't anymore.
It's worse now
'cause he's out of work.
This monster
comes out of him. That's when I split.
I come to the woods
or to my condo.
Anywhere just to get away
from those sounds. Those... awful sounds.
Last night
there was something new.
There was no sound.
I was so scared for her.
I had to help her.
I had to help her. What'd you do?
I was scared,
but I went back.
My mom was lying
on the floor. He was coming at her.
I thought this time
he was gonna kill her.
I grabbed my fishing pole
and I went at him.
Everything was a blur.
I felt the pole
go into him like a spear. Then it snapped, broken.
He threw me
and I hit my shoulder against something sharp.
The corner of a table
or something.
I got up
and ran like hell.
I could hear him
running after me, screaming.
Then I couldn't hear him
anymore.
Then I saw him fall.
I knew he was dead.
Dead? You mean--
Well, was there blood?
You're sure he was dead?
He wasn't moving.
He wasn't breathing. I walked around him three times.
I called his name.
I leaned over him.
Trust me. Worm food.
So there's a dead body
just lying out there in the woods?
Until someone finds him.
What about your mom?
She saw the whole thing.
- She was out cold. I told you.
- Tell my mom. She'll know what to do.
- No, Beth.
Swear you won't say anything. - Ridiculous. You need help.
Come back with me.
Tell them the truth. It was self-defense.
Tell them how Ray
was treating your mother. They'll take Ray's side.
They'll say he was trying
to straighten me out and I killed him.
- They'd never say that.
- Oh, no? Everybody likes him.
You liked him too. But they
don't feel that way about me. They'd never believe me.
Look at the stuff Tracy
and Samantha told you. You'll hear from your mom too.
You wait.
Everybody says I'll end up
in jail. Sorry, folks.
I'll have to disappoint you.
But I'm staying here the way Molly Morgan did... free.
She had a hard life too.
She escaped from the workhouse and came to the mountain.
She did not die in that cave-in.
That mountain woman was Molly Morgan.
She lived inside these walls
and she found that fortress of gold, and I'll find it too.
You can steer the boat
yourself, can't you?
Yeah, I think so. Why?
I was hoping you'd bring me food if I run out.
Or just visit if I need
someone to talk to. You know I'll help you.
Good.
That's the second promise you made to me today.
What's the first?
Climb up to the cave.
No. No way.
It's not like we have to climb up the side of the mountain.
We'll use the passageways
the miners used. They wind all the way inside the mountain.
Then let us out of the cave
with the gold. We'll go right through there.
Here, look.
This is a map of the passageway.
No one has laid eyes on this for years.
The passageway
looks like a spider's web.
It leads to many caves.
And now we know which cave we want to go to,
this is how we get there.
No. I've never driven
a boat alone before.
I've got to give myself
plenty of time while there's still daylight.
You're not gonna tell them
where I am, are you?
I told you I wouldn't.
Are you angry at me?
You are.
I can tell.
I'm angry
this happened to you!
You didn't do anything wrong.
You shouldn't have to hide.
I never meant to kill him.
I'll come visit you
every week.
I cross my heart.
[ Loud Thunderclap ]
Don't be scared.
It's just a little rain.
The echoes make it sound
much worse than it is.
I'll go get you something
to keep you dry.
Wait for me in the boat.
I'll be right back.
[ Thunderclaps, Lightning ]
Just a little rain?
Jody,
the boat's getting away! [ Echoing ]
[ Motor Revving ]
[ Screams ]
Jody?
[ Jody ]
Beth?
Jody? Jody!
[ Screams ]
Hold on!
Grab the wheel.
- Watch out! Watch out!
- [ Screams ]
Get these off me.
My leg's stuck, and I can't move my arm.
Ow! Ow!
[ Crying ]
Can you move it?
No.
I can't do it.
It's like trying to move the whole mountain.
You'll have to go for help.
I'll just have to lay here.
You can't just lay there.
What about the tide?
How much time do I have
before I could drown?
You're not going to drown.
We have till after dark. It's the longest day of the year.
About eight or nine hours,
maybe even more.
How far are we
from civilization?
There's a highway west
of here on the other side of the forest.
- How far?
- I'm not sure, but I know I can reach it before dark.
Four or five hours tops.
Maybe less if the rain stops.
I've got supplies
and a great plan.
It's all set in my mind.
We'll have you out of here
in no time.
I think the rain's stopping.
I'll stop the first car I see
and tell them to call the cops.
I'll ride with them to
the phone to make sure nothing goes wrong with the call.
Then I'll skedaddle.
I can't call the cops myself
or let 'em find me.
They'll arrest me
so I have to disappear. Where will you go?
No one knows the woods
like I do. My dad taught me well.
When they come,
tell them we went boating and got lost.
Nothing about Ray
and nothing about the gold.
I swear
I'll come through for you. You can count on me.
- Just be strong like Molly.
- Strong like Molly.
[ Footsteps Running Away ]
[ Bats Squeaking ]
[ Panting ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Bats Squeaking ]
Just be strong, Beth.
I'll make it.
I won't let you down.
Just be strong like Molly.
[ Growls ]
[ Growling ]
[ Panting ]
Hey!
[ Brakes Squealing ]
What are you doing
way out here?
[ Gasps ]
My friend. My friend. Please help my friend.
She's trapped under a
rock slide at Bear Mountain. You gotta help her.
You walked all the way here
from Bear Mountain? My God.
Where in the mountain
is she? The entrance.
This is Weller.
I've got a female teenager
reporting a rock slide at the entrance to Bear Mountain.
- And you are?
- What?
Your name.
Molly Morgan.
The subject's name
is Molly Morgan.
Female teenager.
I'll be bringing her into the shop.
[ Bats Squeaking ]
[ Beth Panting ]
[ Pilot ] Air to ground,
we're approaching from the east. Have Bear Mountain in sight.
We have a good spot
for the drop.
[ Police Dispatcher ]
We copy.
[ Pilot ]
Air to ground. Man in the water.
I'm in the area.
[ Diver ]
Beth, can you hear me? [ Echoing ]
Beth?
[ Echoing ]
[ Dispatcher ]
Ground to air. Copy that.
[ Diver ]
Beth? I'm here. I'm down here.
I hear her.
This way. Over there.
You made it!
I knew you'd make it.
Right over there.
Nothing's broken, but
you've got mild hypothermia and some cuts.
Let's get you home.
Rescue to air.
We're ready for pickup.
[ Pilot ]
Air to rescue. We copy that.
[ Weller ]
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
[ Chuckling ]
Yeah.
Hold on just a minute. How's our Molly?
That's a mean-looking bruise
on her shoulder. They'll get a better look at the hospital.
I'll do the honors.
Thanks, Mike.
All right.
Bye now, Molly. Great goin'.
They oughta give you
a medal for saving your friend's life.
I'll bet you're starvin'.
This oughta hold you over
till we get you home.
By the way.
Your friend? She's gonna be fine.
Sorry for the interruption,
Matt.
Paramedics just had a look
at Molly. She's okay.
Molly. The girl here.
Molly Morgan.
Yeah. I get the picture.
Right.
I'll take care of it.
Oh, my God.
Hi, baby. Give 'em some room.
Sweetie, baby.
Look at you! I'm okay.
I'm okay! I'm okay!
I'm really okay.
Can't I just go home?
Not until a doctor
gets a look at the two of you. The two of us?
- You and Jody.
- Jody?
- Jody!
- Beth!
I never thought
I'd see you again.
Let me get her mother.
Kate?
They didn't get anything
out of you, did they? Good. We gotta make this quick.
They still don't know about Ray.
They haven't found the body.
I gotta disappear.
Remember our plan. Keep your mouth shut.
That the TV set
from the school?
I gotta make a break for it.
When the time's right, I'll head back to the condo.
Please come with me.
Just humor me.
Come with me.
Just get on it,
and stay on it.
Ray!
Matt, thanks
for calling.
Well, young lady.
Looks like you had quite an adventure.
I'm glad to see you're okay.
I'll give your mom a call, have her come over.
I'm Ray Karnisak.
I'm awfully sorry about all this.
You okay, honey?
Wait. Where are we going?
No, we can't leave her!
Jody!
Mom, listen to me.
We can't leave her! Jody!
Thank you.
Honey, you stay here. I'm gonna get the car.
I can make it, Mom.
No, stay where you are.
I'm gonna bring the car around.
Mom, I'm not a baby.
I see! You almost
get yourself killed and that makes you a grown-up?
Just stay where you are.
[ Crying ]
Don't cry, Mom.
I'm sorry.
I didn't--
It was an accident.
If anything
ever happened to you, I don't know what I'd do.
I'm sorry.
I am just keeping you
so far away from that girl.
I can't see Jody?
After what happened yesterday, no.
She saved my life!
Wrong, Beth. She almost got you killed.
I can't believe I didn't
listen to the things people kept telling me about her.
The two of you alone
on a boat on a dangerous mountain!
I thought
you had more sense.
You have no idea what
an incredible person she is.
She saved my life!
She's a hero!
According to the Sheriff,
your hero doesn't seem able
to walk into a building without stealing.
Does the Sheriff know
about the drunken fights that go on in her house?
It got so bad, Jody thought Ray
was gonna kill her mom.
What are you saying?
When Jody tried to stop him,
he went after her. See the marks on her shoulder.
- Ray tried to kill Lynette?
- Yes!
How do you know
she's telling the truth this time?
Because I know her.
And she wouldn't lie to me.
I talked to Judge Gould
about the thefts at the school.
And you're just gonna have
to keep an eye on her.
You can't let her run wild
the way she used to.
She's on a
sort of probation.
She's gonna do
community service work under my supervision.
I'm gonna have her help
the school custodian.
I've done everything
I can for her.
Maybe this'll do her some good.
It's a shame, though.
Well,
I gotta get going.
[ Lynette ]
Thanks, Matt.
Remember how high Frank
used to toss her in the air?
I never saw a kid
so fearless. She's fearless, all right.
You should've seen her
the night before she was causing all the trouble.
Yeah, what did happen
that night?
We caught her red-handed
stealing from her mom's purse.
She looked us right in the eye
and denied it.
When I told her her mom didn't
want her disappearing again, she went nuts.
Matt,
I mean she went nuts.
Ranting, raving, screaming.
Took her fishing rod, stabbed me in the ribs.
At least we know where
she was running off to... that mountain. The "gold."
See you around.
Later.
I don't believe this.
Don't you get it? He's lying!
Beth.
This is exactly what Jody said you'd say.
You twist everything around
so it's all her fault.
Have you seen her?
Is she okay?
She's fine!
She's working at the school to make up for stealing.
This is incredible.
Ray causes all the trouble, and Jody gets punished!
When Jody's father died,
the only person
Lynette and Jody could count on was Ray Karnisak.
Lynette went through
a terrible time, and Ray got her back on her feet.
There's nothing he wouldn't
do for her or Jody!
- That's the Ray I know.
- He's a liar!
[ Kate ]
Beth, honey. Jody is my friend.
You can keep us apart,
but nothing you say...
will ever change the way
I feel about her... ever!
Hi!
Smile.
It's wonderful to see you
looking so well. Thank you.
Come on.
Everybody is dying to talk to you.
Hi, Beth.
How are you?
We heard that Jody
almost got you killed.
No. Actually, I wouldn't
be here if it weren't for her.
Is it true she had
thousands of dollars...
of stolen equipment
stashed in a hiding place? I heard it was jewelry.
How could you go with her?
She's a total mental case.
She's not a mental case.
She saved my life.
Excuse me.
[ Doug ]
Hot dog?
Hamburger?
Thanks.
- I'm gonna get a drink.
- [ Together ] I'll get it!
No, that's okay.
I'll be right back.
City girl!
Jody! I was going crazy.
I didn't know when
I was gonna see you again. It's been the longest two weeks.
I snuck out.
I gotta get back before they notice I'm gone.
- It's like
I'm under house arrest. - Me too. It's so childish.
I was telling you the truth
about Ray. I'd hate it if you thought I was lying.
-I don't. Total trust.
-I couldn't believe it when I saw him in the hospital.
Tell me about it.
My heart stopped.
I told my mom
what happened to you.
She didn't believe me.
Neither did Matt.
They don't want to know
the truth. It's easier for everyone that way.
Actually, Ray's been
pretty nice to me lately. No kidding?
He keeps asking me
about the mountain and my map. I think he wants the gold.
I gotta split.
Wait.
Where are yogoing?
Don't you want to get back
to the party? Don't get weird on me.
Though... there are
a couple of cute boys there. They're just after your money.
-What money?
-The money we'll get when we dig up Molly Morgan's treasure.
I didn't mean
to make her run.
She knows
how you feel about her.
- Beth? You can see her.
- When?
When?
Tomorrow?
Okay, tomorrow.
I'll drive you over, okay?
Okay.
Now will you come back
to the party?
[ Car Horn Honking ]
[ Beth ]
Mom!
[ Horn Honking ]
Mom, come on!
You're in a hurry.
[ Knocking ]
It's open.
[ Kate ]
Hello? Jody?
Hello?
Jody?
There's no one here.
I feel weird about doing this.
[ Gasps ]
Look at this!
Jody!
Mom!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Mom!
I'm gonna call
an ambulance.
I'm goin' to the hospital
with 'em.
When Lynette comes out of this,
maybe she'll be able to tell us where Jody is.
Or Ray...
for that matter.
They went to the mountain.
I'm positive.
Ray wanted Jody
to take him to the gold.
Beth, there is no gold!
Everybody knows that's just a myth.
That's not the point!
Not if Ray thinks she can lead him to it.
Let's wait and talk
to Lynette.
We can't wait!
That's all you ever do is wait. I know what happened.
Ray got drunk and told Jody
to take him to the gold.
Lynette must've tried
to stop him and he smashed her!
Jody's in danger
and you're not doing anything!
I think we should listen to her
this time, Matt.
Go on,
get outta here.
Ted? Where's Ted?
[ Siren Wailing ]
Ted, call the state police.
Have them do an aerial
surveillance of Bear Mountain and surrounding areas.
See if they
can spot anything...
that might suggest
that a man and a girl have been there.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
I have known that guy my whole life!
Go on home now.
I promise you...
the minute I know anything
I'll call.
Wait, Sheriff,
there's one more thing.
You have to have a boat
to get to the mountain.
Maybe you could ask Ted
to see if any boats were stolen.
Come on.
Ted?
One more thing for you.
Honey, let's go home.
There's nothing more we can do.
No, we have to go
to the hospital.
[ Machines Beeping ]
She's still unconscious,
but the doctors feel she's going to pull through.
Oh, my God.
The poor woman. [ Ted ] Sheriff?
Did you talk
to the state police yet?
They've made several passes
over the mountain, but there's no sign anyone's there.
All right, Beth?
No, that doesn't prove anything.
They have to look inside the mountain.
She was right about
the stolen boat.
- Walter Guthrie shows up
at the river to go fishing-- - And his boat's gone?
- It was kind of obvious.
- Guthrie found this on the dock.
It's Jody's.
She must've left it for us to find.
I'm goin' out
to the mountain.
You stay here, Ted,
and mind the store. [ Beth ] I'm going with you.
No, no.
You're not going anywhere.
Mom, he doesn't know where
to go inside the mountain and I do.
Jody showed me a passageway
that led to the cave where she thought the gold was.
Okay, fine.
Can't you just tell the Sheriff this?
No! I wouldn't know how
to explain it. I have to be there to show you.
Come on!
We're wasting time.
[ Pilot ]
We have you in our sights.
We'll follow you
to Bear Mountain, orbit the area and wait for your call.
Look! They're here.
That's Guthrie's boat.
That's another one for you, Beth.
Beth?
This is Matt.
We found the missing boat. Bring the team in here.
[ Radio ] Rescue team en route.
Copy. We're heading in the mountain. Out.
Watch your step.
[ Kate ]
Oh, my God.
No!
Where are you going?
Mom, it's okay.
I'm just gonna show the Sheriff the way.
You go right through here.
I see it. Come on back.
- Beth, stop!
- Matt, come with me.
Mom, go to the entrance.
When the others get here, you can show 'em the way.
Jody saved my life,
and I save hers. That's how it works.
- No, no.
- Just do what she says. I'll go with her.
Beth!
Oh, my God.
[ Panting ]
You all right?
Keep goin'. I'm with ya.
Hey, slow down!
Geez! Don't they make you guys exercise?
I'm waiting!
Okay, I'm comin'!
You look awful.
How nice of you.
Okay, now...
which way do we go? I don't know.
What do you mean?
I thought Jody showed you the way.
Yeah, but you need a map
once you get this far. Okay, where's the map?
Ray must have it.
Oh, great.
Wait.
Isn't that a footprint?
Yeah. It looks fresh too.
If we follow where it came from--
Beth?
Come on!
Beth,
would you wait a second?
[ Bats Squeaking ]
Thank you, God.
Oh, no.
What?
[ Matt ]
Whoa!
Whoo!
Beth, oh, no!
God! Are you crazy?
How could you do that?
It was kind of easy. Now it's your turn.
- Come on!
- Okay. Yeah.
Come on.
Nice jump.
Beth?
Okay, slow down.
Beth, wait up.
Look.
What?
I switched this off.
Where's the light
coming from? I don't know. Come on.
Come on.
This is amazing.
[ Echoing ]
Beth?
Holy!
Beth? Beth?
[ Echoing ]
Matt?
Where are you?
[ Echoing ]
Over here.
[ Echo ]
Where's here?
[ Echoing ]
I don't know.
Matt?
[ Matt ]
Where are you?
Matt?
Wait for me, Beth. Beth, I can't hear you.
Jody!
It's okay.
Take a deep breath.
It's gonna be okay.
Sit down.
Take a deep breath.
It's okay.
Be strong... like Molly.
- Where's Ray?
- Back there somewhere. He's drunk and crazy.
I got away. I ran
and just kept running.
That's good.
He's probably lost.
My mom.
Do you know if she's okay? When we left, I couldn't tell.
She's okay.
She's gonna be fine.
They're taking care of her
in the hospital.
He took my map.
Then he said I had to go with him.
She tried to stop him
with my dad's gun. He grabbed it and hit her.
She tried so hard
to stop him.
I know, I know.
Let's go.
Let's try and find our way
out of here.
Matt's here somewhere.
And a rescue squad is on the way.
Beth, look.
That light we saw.
It was crystals!
Look.
- Molly Morgan's gold.
- You were right, Jody!
I always knew
it was here.
[ Screams ]
Worms!
Glowworms.
The gold's
gotta be here somewhere.
You found it!
- There's no gold here.
- No gold, huh? What do you call that?
Glowworms!
You tried to make a damn fool outta me!
[ Ray ]
Where's the gold?
Get back here!
Jody!
[ Ray ]
Jody?
Honey!
Jody, where are you?
Come on, hon.
I think it's time we had
just a little talk.
We've always been friends,
haven't we, huh? Jody.
[ Ray ]
Come on.
Beth?
[ Ray ]
Jody? [ Gasps ]
Jody? Jody?
Jody! Jody!
I'm not mad at you.
I just wanna help you find the gold.
[ Ray ]
Where are you?
[ Chuckling ]
You're making it awful tough on me.
Jody.
[ Muffled Screams ]
Shh.
There you are.
You've been playing games
with me all along, haven't you?
No, I haven't.
You've been nothing
but trouble since the day you were born.
I'm gonna have to teach you
a little lesson.
Jody? Jody!
What happened?
Molly hit him in the head with a shovel.
Molly's here?
She was right here.
I swear, she was right there.
Beth, where are you?
Jody, geez!
You two okay?
Wh--
[ Matt ]
What the hell happened to him?
- Molly hit him in the head.
- Molly?
Yeah. Molly Morgan.
She was right there. I swear she was right there.
[ Ted ]
Matt? Over here! Come on in.
Come on in, guys.
[ Police Radio Indistinct ]
Can you believe that kid?
Said she wanted to come look for the gold.
I told her no,
but there's no arguing with her.
Figured it'd be safer
if I came along.
What's the gun for?
Safety?
Well, yeah, sure.
[ Sighs ]
Hey, Matt...
it's me, Ray.
You're looking at me
like you don't even know me.
- Come on, let's go.
- Why?
[ Beth Narrating ]
The next time we saw Ray was in a courtroom.
It was quite
a media event.
Poor Ray.
They sent him to prison.
Mom?
Oh, Jody.
I'm so sorry!
It's okay.
I love you so much.
[ Beth Narrating ]
That was the first moment when I realized...
the three of us
were becoming a family.
Jody stayed with us all summer
while Lynette recovered.
The scars that were invisible
took the longest to heal.
Finally she came home
to Jody.
And on that day--
Jody?
Beth?
Hi.
Someone in my office
wants to talk to you two. Someone very important.
I knew it!
I knew it! You knew what?
I don't know,
but I just knew it. Mom!
Come on.
Keep going, keep going.
Girls,
this is Mr. Everett Graham.
You're Jody.
And you are Beth.
I recognize you both.
I couldn't turn on my TV without seeing you.
And these are the girls'
mothers. Mrs. Salerno and Mrs. Easton.
Pleased to meet you.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Well, let me tell you
why I'm here.
I'm an attorney
and I represent a client who wishes to remain anonymous.
My client would like
to present a gift to Miss Beth Easton...
and Miss Jody Salerno.
Would you please sign these
documents to acknowledge receipt of the gift?
Thank you.
Congratulations,
young ladies.
Oh, my God!
I told you so!
They're rich!
My God, Jody!
[ Applauding ]
[ Beth Narrating ]
Who was our mysterious benefactor?
Jody, of course, swears
it was the woman who saved her, Molly Morgan.
But was the woman who saved her
the real Molly?
We never saw her again.
I guess we'll never know
for sure.
♪ It's easier
to love somebody ♪
than to be loved ♪
♪ You say you wanna
be somebody ♪
♪ Why don't
you be yourself ♪
♪ If you wait
for an answer ♪
♪ From somewhere
up above ♪
♪ You may never
hear the laughter ♪
♪ You've been dreaming of ♪
♪ Now we're flying
so high ♪
♪ With the world
down below ♪
♪ Spread your wings
across the sky ♪
♪ Fly ♪
♪ It's easier
to love somebody ♪
than to be loved ♪
♪ You say you wanna
trust somebody ♪
♪ Why don't
you trust yourself ♪
♪ If a wave
rolls down from heaven ♪
♪ With the turning
of the tide ♪
♪ You're pulled
in all directions ♪
♪ Only for a while ♪
♪ Then we're flying
so high ♪
♪ With the world
down below ♪
♪ Spread your wings
across the sky ♪
♪ Fly ♪
♪
♪ It's easier
to love somebody ♪
than to be loved ♪
♪ You say you wanna
be somebody ♪
♪ Why don't
you be yourself ♪
♪ Now we're flying
so high ♪
♪ With the world
down below ♪
♪ Spread your wings ♪
♪ Across the sky ♪
♪ Yeah, we're flying
so high ♪
♪ With the world
down below ♪
♪ Spread your wings
across the sky ♪
♪ Fly ♪
♪ We're flying
so high ♪
♪ Fly ♪
♪ Spread your wings
across the sky ♪
♪ You say you wanna ♪
♪ Mmm, you say you wanna ♪
♪ You say you wanna
be somebody ♪
♪ Trust somebody ♪
♪ Love somebody ♪
♪ [ Fades ]