Watch out there, sir...
Excuse me.
Ooh...
Ooh...Oh...
I'm sorry.
Careful.
Thanks.
Oop! We meet again.
Woman:It's still
my favorite animal.
You draggedthis old bear around
till most of the stuffingfell out.
Maybe he's skinnierbut I still have it.
Till mostyou know whatingfell out.Else I have?
Maybe hthe best dadbin the whole world.
Till mostyou know whatingi'm going to miss you, Jen.
I'm going to missyou, too, dad.
Oh, it's hard to believeit's been 16 years
since we movedinto this house.
The strange thing is
we thought whenwe were moving in
we would betaking care of Mary.
It turned out she wastaking care of us.
I don't remembera lot about Mary.
Just how much I loved itwhen she used to read to me.
She loved it evenmore than you did.
That's why sheleft us this house.
So you couldgrow up here and...
One day getmarried here.
So you couldjust before she died...
Mary asked meto save this.
For you.
Oh, dad, it's so beautiful.
She wanted youto have it
on your wedding day.
I wonder how sheted youmetherhusband.Ve it
you never knew anythingabout davidon your wedding day.
Did you, dad?
No, just fromthat portraitup in the attic.
But their love storywas... amazing.
They met duringthe second world war.
The company that David owned
had just won a contratto build a stock plane engie
for the U.S. arm.
So, naturally,he was working around the clock
to methis production deadlin.
Look, boss...
Yeah.
I know you're busy
but we got to do somethingabout the bottleneck.
We're designingthe finishing operation
to solve that.
You'll have the newgrinders by next week.
Great.
Oh, excuse me, sir.
Where do I go to applyfor the secretarial position?
Mr. parkin isn't seeingany more girls today.
Has the positionbeen filled?
I have experiencein references.
I take shorthandand I type 90 words a minute.
I have experiencei'm very organized
and I do really needthis job.
I'm sorry.
Why don't you justcome back tomorrow.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Are you herefor the secretarial position?
Well, I was,but I got here too late
so I never gotto speak to Mr. parkin.
I... well...
Maybe you still can.
No, he's not seeinganyone else today.
Don't give upso easily.
Let's go talk to him.
It's all right.
I can come backtomorrow.
No, no. You madea special trip.
I can come backtomorrow.He'll see you.
No, no. You madea spei promise.
I can come backare you sure?L see you.
Absolutely.
What sort of manis he?
Well, uh...
I might as wellwarn you.
He's, uh...He's a bear to work for.
Maybe it'dbe better...No, no, no.
He's, uh...Please, take a seat.For.
Maybe it'di'm sure he'll be happyto meet with you. No.
How do you know?
Well, I...
H(Chuckling)W?
I'm... David parkin.
I-I'm sorry.
You-you seemedso earnest
and I was just being playful.
No!And I was being foolish.
Well, uh...
Let's start all over again.
Hello. I'm David parkin.
Mary Chandler.
It's a pleasu...It's a pleasu...
It's a pleasureto meet you, Mr. parkin.
The pleasure is mine,miss Chandler.
It's a pleasureto meet you,please, take a seat.
The pleasure is mine,how are we doing?
It's a pleasureto meet yoany better?Ake a seat.
I, uh... I broughtmy employment record.
So, what brings youto America, miss Chandler?
Oh, well, after my mother died,my father and I came...
(Two clocks chiming)
Oh, well, after my mother died,my fat(Chuckles)Me...
My father and I came over...
Oh, well, after my mother died,(More clocks chiming)
As you can hear,
I collect timepieces.
(Chuckles)
Go on, miss Chandler.
Yes, we came overfrom england
because he wanted to finda new life over here
but with jobs so scarceduring the depression
he never really could findsteady work.
But with jobs so scarceduring thi understand.
Unfortunately,my father wasa failure too.
I don't consider my fatherto be a failure
Mr. parkin.
Now, I believe I've told youall you need to know.
Thank you for considering me.
Miss Chandler...
I'm sorry ifi've offended you
and I hopethis doesn't mean
you won't cometo work for me.
You mean, I have the job?
Monday morning, 8:00 sharp.
(Phone ringing)
Good morning,mr. Parkin's office.
Parkin:We oil machineslike this back here.
Little by little,going all the way...
Parkin:We oil machinesmr. Parkin...Ike this back here.
(Typewriter keys clacking)
I hear your typewriterin my dreams, miss Chandler.
And no matter how earlyi get here
you stillbeat me to it.
I couldn't sleep very welllast night
so I decided to come in early.
There's so muchcatching up to do.
You're a great secretary.
There's so muchcati'm lucky to have you.
Thank you, Mr. parkin.
You're welcome.
Call Washington--see if you can get
someone in the procurementoffice, miss Chandler.
Oh... would you mindif I called you Mary?
Give me a counton blade 14.
Yes, sir.
Brand new specson the gearbox
for the a-57 multibank.
Oh, and the tank arsenalis stepping up its production.
So to match it
we'll have to be adding2,000 more units a week.
Hey, you betterget out of here.
You missed the last busthe other night.
Yes, I lose trackof the time.Ere.
I don't know howyou can do that
with all these clocksaround here.
I know the pressureyou're under
and I hate to leaveanything undone.
Good night, Mr. parkin.
Good night, Mary.
Good night,mr. Gibbs.
Miss Chandler.
Awfully familiar, aren't we?
Miss Chandler.Hmm?
I mean, you hardlyknow this "Mary."
You're alreadytoo fond of her, Dave.
I'm not "fond" of her.
I just admireher competence and efficiency.
Are you sureit's her work ethic
that you admire?
It's not like you to haveyour head turned by a woman.
I just want to make sureshe makes the last bus.
And besides, this womanis different.
Yeah, that's whatevery man says
and besides,just before he makesis different.A fool of himself.
Just remember yourown words of wisdom
concerning marriage.
Just remember youryeah, yeah.Own words of wisdom
"marriage is the wormthat conceals the hook."
And I haven't changedmy mind, okay?
Mary?
Father Mike.
What... what am igoing to do?
Well... just whatyou're doing.
Putting your trustin God.
I don't know how muchtrust I have left.
You're a strongwoman, Mary.
You're goingto be all right.
May I help you?
Ah, you must bethat English voice
I heard on the phone.
Yes. Mary Chandler...
Mr. parkin's secretary.
Barbara Hayworth...
And you don't needto announce me, Mary.
David and I are old friends.
Miss hay...
David.Barbara.
You look beautiful.
Didn't your new girlgive you my message?
She did.
I was going to call youwhen I had a free moment.
Put me down for a sizablecontribution to the u.S.O.
Oh, we want morethan just your money, David.
We've decidedto hold the dance
right down therein your parking lot.
What better connectionto the war effort, hmm?
I suppose that might work.
I knew you'dlove the idea.
Now, don't worryabout the decor.
My committee will takecare of everything.
Have to run.
Already late for my stintat the canteen.
Nice to see you again, Barbara..
With a little effort
you could see memore often, you know.
You must be lookingwith a littlfor the hiring hall.
It's downstairs.
Actually, Mr. parkinwas expecting Mr. Flynn.
You can go in now, sir.
Thank you, ma'am.
Mr. parkin,mr. Flynn to see you.
Lawrence.
Mr. p.
Mary, I want youto meet someone.
We have already met.
I've been watching her
trying to make sensewe out of your mess.
Yeah, my mess.
Lawrence is godfather make senseto most of my clocks. Your mess.
Yeah, my mess.I never realized
there were somany differenttypes of clocks.
Should I holdall your calls?
Unless it's f.D.R.
Should I holdthank you.L your calls?
All right...
What are you goingto tempt me with today?
The owner...Wants $200 for it.
I'd offer him one.
The owner...Interested?200 for it.
It's a beautiful piece...
But it's a woman's watch.
What would I do with it?
It's ararepiece.
But you're right.
It is a kind of gift
a man would givehis sweetheart.
If a manhada sweetheart, right?
Do you ever think man would giveabout getting married?Weetheart.
Not really.
Do you ever thinki guess I neverabout gettinfound the right one.
Take a lookat our new grinder design.
We've got to cutki guess I neverproduction time in halfight one.
Without affectingour quality.
Hmm.
You could set the axisof the cutter
at just a hairmore of an angle.
Yeah. That would improveprofile accuracy.
Why didn't I see that?
You would haveif those Washington people
would give you enough timeto take a deep breath.
Well, I'd best be going
so you can get backto winning the war.
The war will go onwell, I'd best bewithout me.
Always time for you,lawrence.
Be good to yourself.
If I don't,who will?
Yeah.
Likewise, Mr. p.
Well... miss Chandler,it's nice knowing
you're taking careof my old friend.
Make sure he doesn't work youto the bonenowing
like he does himself.
I'll try not to,mr. Flynn.
God bless you both.
Take care, Lawrence.
Thank you.
There you are, ma'am.
(Footsteps approaching)
(Knocking)
Miss maud,how nice to see you.
Come on in.
I was just wondering
if that bavarian clockwas ready.
Yes, indeed.
Sit down, please.
Thanks, althoughi don't know
why I bother to ask.
It doesn't matter, really.
It's just goodto get out and about
while I still can.
It's just goodlord willing and about
we both havea lot of good years left.
Oh, I'm not sureyears
are what the lordhas in mind for me, Lawrence.
You look wonderful, miss maud.
Anything wrong?
Um... the doctor just told me
that I havewhat my father used to call...
A "bad ticker."
That I havewhat my (Chuckles)To call...
Oh...
Miss maud, I'm so sorry.
Don't be.
It's just life.
How come a taxibrought you?
Your car in the garage?
Oh, no, it's my nephew.
It's always everen, isn't it?
I came downstairsall dressed and ready to go
and the car was gone.
I guess he's out joyridingwith that friend of his
Cal Avery.
It worries me.
If I'd known, I could havesaved you the trouble
and dropped it offat your place.
Well, everen ismyproblem,lawrence, not yours.
I don't want that taxirunning up the meter on you.
I thinkyou'll like the chimes now.
I know I will.
But... if there's any problem...
I'm sure there won't be.
Be good to yourself,but... if there's any miss maud.
Thank you, Lawrence.
Be good to yourself,but... ifmr. Parkin...Miss maud.
If you couldjust sign this...
And if you don't need mefor anything else
I'll see youin the morning?
I'm sorry.
I got so busydown here
I've made youlate again.
Let me give youa ride home.
Maybe we can stop off
and get a bite to eatalong the way.
Thank you.
That's... very nice.
I, um... ireally can't.
You have... other plans?
Yes... I mean, no...
Actually...
I'm going to church.
Church?But it's Wednesday night.
Yes. It's a prayer service.
But y-you could join me,if you'd like.
Tonight our hearts go out
but y-you could jto the familiesif you'd like.Of those young men
about to invadenazi-occupied France.
For themand for all those
who face a great trialin their lives
let us say together
the powerful wordsof the 23rd psalm:
The lord is my Shepherd;
all:I shall not want.
He maketh meto lie down ingreen pastures...
Sorry if I seemed uncomfortablein there.
Never been very religious.
You don't have to bevery religious
to talk to God.N very religious.
That's just it.
I don't even knowif there is a God.
I guess I'm too muchof a cynic.
You said your fatherwas a failure.
Is that whatmade you cynical?
I-I probably shouldn'thave said that.
Is that whatmy father was reallymade you cynicala wonderful man.
Unfortunately,he let my mother destroy him.
Is that whatmy father was reallywhat do you mean? Wonderful man.
She walked out on uswhen I was four.
He never got over it.
She walked out on usdid he never remarry?I was four.
No. It was justthe two of us.
I guess I turned out on usdid he neveall right.I was four.
(Chuckling)
But...
A child really shouldhave two parents.
I admire your faith.
I wish I had it.
There's no real wayto explain faith.
All I know is that
sometimes godis the only friend you have.
The whole idea of a deityi find incomprehensible.
But a clock...
Nowthati understand.
A clock I can see,I can touch
I can eventake it apart
discoverits mysteries--
I cthen have lawrencetaput it back together.
(Chuckling)
I don't know.
This is my place.
Oh.
I'll see you in the morning.
Hey... y-you...You don't get away that easy.
I mean, at least, not untili tell you what a, uh...
Hey... y-you...Special night this was. Easy.
Not once--
not one single,solitary momentdid I think...
(Door closing)
...about the planor the war production board
or cost overruns, or...
Good evening.
All I thought about was...
You...
And...
God, I mean,it's...
Thank you.
Good night.
Where's David?
He'll be backin a moment.
What are you doingstill working?
You're supposed to bedown at the dance.
Oh, I didn't thinkanyone would miss me.
Imissed yo.
You know, you have beenas remote as mount Everest
for the last week
but you're notgetting out ofat least one dance
with me, Mary Chandler.
Well, I'll be downa little later.
I'll be waiting.
Men have been knownto fight wars
for the privilegeof holding me in their arms
and all you had to do
was give us the placefor our charity dance.
Evening, miss Chandler.
May I havethe pleasure?
David,I'll save the last dance.
You work too hard,mary Chandler.
Those w.P.B. Reports haveto go out in the morning.
They're overdue.
Those w.P.B. Reportwe'reoverdeto go out I for our first dance.
Please do me the honor.
(Music stopsand dancers applaud)
Mary...
Tell me what's wrong.
Please, just...
I respect you too much
to ever do anythingthat would hurt you in any way.
If that's whyyou've been so... much
no, it's...It's not that at all.
If that's whyyou've beenyou don't understand.
Idounderstand.
What we felt for each otheras we danced...
Was real.
What we felt for each otheri'm in love with you.
I'm in love with you.
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
It'swonderful.
It's impossible.
David,I should have told you.
It's imposthere's somebody else?
David,I should have told yowhat, then?
It's impomary... what?Body else?
I'm pregnant, David.
There was...
Someone...
A soldier and...
And I was foolish.
Does he know?
He was killed...
Five weeks ago in Italy...
And that's why I came here.
To get a new start.
I should have told you,but I really needed this job.
David, I'll never forgive myselffor deceiving you.
You're the last personin the world
I'd ever want to hurt.
David, there'st persona phone call.
I'll have to call them back.
It's urgent.
I said I'dcall him back.
David,it's Washington.
Mary... wait here.
I'm goingto be right back.
All right?
Wait here.
David:I know that, Bob
but I still can'tfly out tomorrow.
Look, Bob... Bob, why can't wedo this over the phone?
I know it's important
but I have a priorityof my own right here, now.
Bob, I got to go.
I'll call you first thingin the morning.
I will, I promise.
Right, bye.
They're going to makea decision within 24 hours.
Why can't you fly out?
George, please.
It's Mary Chandler,isn't it?
I told you notto get involved.
George, why don't youjust shut up.
David, you look frantic.
Have you seen Mary?
Well, that poor girlran out of here in tears.
Come on, the fireworksare about to start.
Well, that poor girlran out of here in tearsdavid...
Where are you going?
I can't stay here.
Where arei have to go.
You can't leave.
We need to talk.
You can't lthis is the only way.
Listen to me...
You belong here with me.
Listi don't know where I belong.
When I couldn't find you
and I thought I mightnever see you again
I felt like everything thatwas good in my life was gone.
And I thought I mightnever see yhow can you say that?
I know what I want...
And what I wantis to marry you.
I'm going to haveanother man's baby.
Why would you everwant to marry me?
It doesn't matter, Mary.
It doesn't matter.
I'm asking you to marry me.
I don't want your pity.
It's not about pity.
It's about love. Want your pity.
I can't do that to you.
What would people think?
Mary...
I don't care what people think.
All that matters to me...
All that mattersis being with you.
Catherine!
I want youto meet someone.
Mary, thisis Catherine--
I want youto meetcatherine Taylor.
Mshe has been with meis catherineeight years
I want youand she isto mthe best housekeeper
any bachelor ever had.
Catherine, Mary Chandler.
The best secretaryany boss ever had.Hello.
And she's agreedcatto marry me next week.
The best secretaryany boss ever had.Married?
Next week?
The best secretaryany boss ever had.Married?Yeah.
Mr. parkin,you've lostyour senses.
The best secretarysorry, ma'am, and it'sa pleasure to meet you
but next weekis impossible.
Sir, think of yoursocial position.
But next weekyou owe your friends
andyour future wifea proper wedding.
But nethen, we'll make ityou owe youtwo weeks.
(Door opens)
David:Hello, hello.
Come in, Mr. p.
Hmm.
Lawrence,you would not believe
what I'm here for.
That rose-gold woman's watch
you said you hadno need for.
You know, I...I have always suspected you
of being a mind reader.
And you foundthe right woman
right, Mr. p.?
Miss Chandler,isn't it?
Well, I, I can't believe it.
I hire a girlto straighten out my files.
I find the onlywomanwho can straighten out my life.
I knew it when I firstsaw you two together.
I'm very happyfor you, Mr. p.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
It's all going to bein a bit of a rush
so you won't getyour invitation
until just a few daysbefore the wedding.
Are you sureso you won't getyou want me there?Our invitation
you know betterthan to even askthat question.
What's this?
A new acquisition?
No clock.
That's my angel.
Your angel?
Yes.
I thought I'droll it out
so I could see it.
It's beautiful.
Where'd you find it?
It found me.
I spent most of the summerrepairing the steeple clock
and apparentlythe church treasurer
ran off with the building money
so the minister asked me
if I'd take that insteadfor payment.
(Both chuckling)
I was tempted to sell itonce during the depression.
But now, I'mkind of glad I didn't.
I'm going to have that putell iton my grave after I'm gonession.
So that people around herewill know
that I was worthsomething.
Minister:Will thou, David,take Mary as your wife
to have and to holdfrom this day forward
for better, for worse,for richer, for poorer
in sickness and in health
to love and to cherish
till death do you part?
I do.
Will thou, Mary,take David as your husband
to have and to holdfrom this day forward
for better, for worse
to have and to holdfor richer, for poorer
in sickness and in healthorse
to have and to holdfor rto love and to cherish
itill death do you part?Horse
I do.
Itill rings, please?Art?Horse
with this ring,I thee wed.
Mary:With this ring
I thee wed.
(Laughs)
Those whom godhath joined together
let no man put asunder.
You may kiss the bride.
Woman:Let ncongratulations, David.
Thank you, dede.
Barbara, thank youso much for coming.
Dear David, I can'ttell you how pleased I am
that you've finallyfound a young woman
dear David, I can'tteworthy of you.Ased I am
I hope you have
a very happy life,my dear.
Thank you.Hope you have
thank you, Barbara.
I mean, we don't even knowwhere she came from
or who her people are.
Dede:You're absolutely right.
Everen, I asked younot to do that.
If I had knownthe libations were this good
I'd have come to oneof these weddings
alongtime ago.
I hope you don't expect meto drive with you
in your condition.
Lawrence:I'd be happyto drop you off
on the way home,miss maud.
Thank you, Lawrence.
Maud:You certainly dida wonderful job
resurrecting that oldbavarian clock.
The chimes havethe sweetest sound now
resurrecting that oldbavarian thanks to you.
The sweetnesswas in there all along
just waiting that oldto be brought out. You.
What a wonderfulway to put it.
Have you been throughthe reception line?
No. I liketo sort of hang back
until everybody elsebeen throughgets their time. Reception line?
I think I willtake this time.
Thank you.
I think I wmiss gannon,take this tihow are you?
Mary, I want youto meet maud gannon.
The gracious ladywho made me feel welcome
and was so helpful
when I firstgot to this city.
Miss maud, my wife, Mary.
You can tell how muchi love saying "my wife."
Well, it would takean exceptional woman
you cto win the hearti love sof David parkin.
Well, he'San exceptional man.
He's sucha perfectionist
in everything
so I know he tookall the time he needed
to find exactlythe perfect one.
My best wishes to you.
Thank you.
Take good careof her.
Best to you both.
Thank you.Thank you.
I have something for you.
It's your.Wedding gift.
David!
It's exquisite.
It's to remind you
every minute
of every hour
how much I love you.
Wherever did you find it?
Come here.
(Men laughing)
Comlawrence found it.
Lawrence,it's beautiful.Aughing)
Not nearlyas beautifulas the bride. Found it.
Lawrence,oh!S beautiful.Aughing)
Thank you.
Dave. I can't tell youhow happy I am
about you and Mary.
Oh, thanks.
But it's been six months.
When are you going to stopacting like a newlywed
and get back to business?
We're cash-starved.
We've got allthis work here
and the money'scoming in down the road
webut you've got to getout there and get a job
that pays right now.
George, I told you
I'm not taking anybusiness trips for a while.
Mary needs me too muchright now. Okay?
Mary:Catherine!
Catherine!
Dear lord,what's happened?
Call the doctor.
(Groaning)
George:Dave.
Dave, telephone.
Thanks, George.
Hello.
Wait... Catherine, slow down.
What is it?
Wait...Oh, my God. Slow down.
(Mary panting loudly)
(Mary groaning)
Catherine:Mr. Parkin,you can't come in. Loudly)
No! David, stay, David...
Catherine,you know what to do.
I'm having difficultystopping the bleeding....
I'm afraid the babycould suffocate
in the birth canal.
(Panting)
God...
God, if you're there, please...
The baby's turned.
Push, Mrs. parkin.
You're doing great!Aby's turned.
The head's out.
(Groaning)
Doctor:One more push.
Just one more.Oaning)
Doctor:One more p(Groaning)
Doctor:That's it.
(Baby crying)
Doctor:Congratulations.
You have a beautifulbaby girl.
Here's mommy.
Hello!
And daddy.My.
Hello!(Baby crying)
Hi. Daddy.My.
Hi, sweetie.
My beautiful Andrea.
Happy Birthday,miss Andrea.
Andrea:You made it.
You made my bird feeder.
Oh, thank you, Lawrence.
Well, there's still somework to be done on it.
You think youoh, thank can help me?E.
Well, there's still someworkyes.Be done on it.
Catherine:Too bad Mr. parkincouldn't get back
for the party.
I'm sure he tried.
He must'vegotten tied up.
Look how much funshe's having.
She's never happier thanwhen Lawrence is around.
(Whistling)
Let's paint it red.
Oh, no, missy.
Birds don't like bright colors..
You'll scare them away.
When are theygoing to come?
It takes some time.
You see, birds...
Here.Kes some time.
Birds are suspicious...
Like some people.E.
What's suspicious?
(Laughing)
Well, it means havinga lot of questions like you.
Oh.
Well, it meanswhat kind of birdsa lot of queare we going to get?
Oh, bluebirds, redbirds.
Everybodymeanswhat kind of birdsin the rainbow is welcome.O get?
Why are birdsdifferent colors?
Well...
Because God made them that way.
Is that why yourskin's brown?
My skin?
Yeah.
That's right, missy--
because God made it that way.
Hey!
Daddy! Daddy!
Hi, sweetie.
Oh, it's so goodto have you home.
It's good to be home.
This is for you,princess.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Was the trip successful?
I'd say hopeful.
I missed my girls.
I wish I could'vegotten home sooner.
Well, you did your best
and you do havea business to run.
What's that?
Mama, it's a doll.
Daddy, she's so pretty.
Well, now I havethree pretty girls.
(Laughing)
David:Well, now I havetime's up.Three pretty girls.
There you go.
Good night, sweetheart.
Daddy?
Hmm?
Don't leave.
Time to go to sleep.
Stay justa little longer.
Okay.
But then you gotto go night-night.
Okay.Daddy?
But then you gotto go night-nihmm?
Why do you haveto go away to work
all the time?
Because daddy has to findnew customers for his business.
I miss youwhen you're away.
I miss you, too, princess.
Oh, I miss you too.
Mary:What's the matter?
Something'son your mind.
Mary:What's the maoh...
I guessi'm just feeling guilty
Mary:About being away so much and...
I'm just dreading the day
we have to tell andreai'm not her real father.
Oh, David, you areher real father.
Being a fatherdoesn't happen
at the momentof conception.
It happensover the years
when you love and carefor a child--.
All the things you've done.
Oh...
I've failed you,haven't I?
Mary,it's not about that.
If only I could have given youyour own child.
I couldn't love Andrea more
if she wasmy own flesh and blood.
You know that.
I feel privilegedto be her father.
And she's lucky to have you.
I feel privilegedto be her and so am I.
Have I told you latelyhow much I love you?
Hmm...
Have I told you latelyhow much once or twice.
(Tapping)
Oh.
Miss maud, let megive you a hand with this.
Thank you.
Actually, I enjoydoing things for myself.
It's a good thing, too
seeing as howi don't have anyone
who's willing to help me.
What about your nephew?
Oh, I don't evenwant his help.
In the caron the way over hereyour nephew?
He asked mefor another temporary loan.
He and that Avery boyare always trying
to weasel money out of me.
Here.
He thinks he's goingto inherit my estate.F me.
I'm not goingto leave him a cent.
I'm going to leave itall to the church.
Oh, well...Enough complaining.
I'm gmiss maud, do you knowthis is an original Seth Thomas?
Yes.
Worth apretty penny.
Look at that workmanship.
You'll never seea finer piece.
Well, at least not outsideof the workshop
of Mr. Lawrence Flynn.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll get on to itby the end of the week
yeif that's all right.
Oh, that'll be fine.
Here she comes.
Lawrence...
I enjoy our visits.
Yes, indeed.
I'll see younext week?
It will be ready,miss maud.
I'll see youthank you.Next week?
It will be ready,miss maud.Good day, gentlemen.
(Gasps)
What is it?
Are you all right?
I just had the mostwhat is it?Horrible nightmare.
Oh, sweet.
What was it?
I dreamt I was holdingandrea in my arms
and I was rockingher to sleep
when this angel camethrough the window
and took her from me.
Oh, honey.
It was just a dream.
I have to see her, David.
Oh, Mary...
You know she's fine. Her, David.
Thank God.
She's sleepinglike a lamb.
It just felt so real.
She's sleepingtry to get some sleep.
I'm sorry I woke you.
She's sleepingno, that's okay.Sleep.
The alarm would've gone offin ten minutes anyhow. Woke you.
She's sleepingmy flight's at 7:00.P.
Darling...
Yeah?
Hold me for a moment.
Everything's all right.
Time to wake up,sweetheart.
Catherine has a lovely breakfastwaiting for you.
Andrea?
Mama, my neck hurts.
Good girl.
Good girl.Mm-hmm.
Mary...
I'm afraid it's meningitis.
How bad is it?
Well, it's too earlyto tell how serious.
What can I do?
Well, it's too earlyjust what you're doing--
bed rest, try to keepthe fever down.An I do?
The first two weeksyare critical.'Re doing--
could she...?
Severe caseso weeksycan lead to deathdoing--
but we'll keepa close watch on her.Uld she...?
Meningitisis highly contagious
so I'm going to haveto quarantine the house.
What is it?
Meningitis.
And Mr. parkin hasalready left for Europe.
Catherine, I knew somethingterrible was going to happen.
I had this dream.
It can't come true.
I won't let it.
(Clocks ticking)
Gentlemen.
What can I do for you?
"Gentlemen"?
What can I do you hear that, ev?
He called us "gentlemen."
I think you got somethingbelonging to my aunt.
Miss maud send you?
Yeah, she did.
Where is it?
I hope you don't mindif I don't believe you.
Miss maud knows that clockwon't be ready till next week.
Now, if you fellows are thinkingabout selling miss maud's clock
just to get yourselves
now, isome drinking money,inkingayou got another thing coming.K
I'm thinkingthis fella don't know his places
is what I'm thinking.
I know my place,and this is it
so unless you fellas
got some other businessto transact
there's the door.
Mary:Lawrence...
You can't come in.
Andrea has meningitis.
Meningitis?
How long has she been sick?
Over a week now, and we stillcan't get her fever down.
Maybe I can pick her spirits up.
You always do, Lawrence...
But this timeyou can't come in.
Well, I can come in, Mrs. p.,I just can't come back out.
Besides, I suspect you could usesome help yourself.
Mary:Andrea?
Look who's here.
(Chuckles)
I knew it would brighten my dayonce I saw you, missy.
Can you tell me a story,lawrence?
Sure.
(Clears throat)
Do you knowthe bluebird story?
No. Tell me.
Do you knowwell, once upon a time
no. Tell there was this bluebird
do you knowwwho had a little girl
as a very special friend.
Do you knowwhat her name was?
Andrea?As a very special friend.
Right as rain.
Andrea?Asandrea got sick one day
and nobody knewwhat to do.
But Mr. bluebird knewandrea?Asandrea gojust the thing
that would make herfeel all better.
I'm sorry, ma'am. I justird knewput her right off to sleep.Thing
that's just whatshe needs now--
as much restas possible.
Maybe you shouldget some rest, too, Mrs. p.
I can sit here with her.
No, Lawrence,I can't leave her.
I just can't.
(Phone ringing)
Catherine:Excuse me.
Mr. parkin'son the phone.
Catherine:David.Excuse me.
Hi, sweetheart.
I just landed in Washington
and I've gotone more meeting tomorrow
then I'll fly home.
You have no idea
how much I miss you both.
Mary? You still there?
Darling...Andrea has meningitis
and she's not respondingto the medication.
I'll fly home right away.
It's going to be all right,I promise.
I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
Hi, honey.I'm scared.
How is she?
At least she's resting.
Look, I'm sorry I wasn't hereto help you through this.
Catherine tells methat you haven't left her side
since she got sick.
Catherine tellshe shouldn't havethat you haven't ltold you that.
She and lawrencesince she got sicworry too much.
I'm fine.
She and lawrenceyou'renotfine.Cworry too much.
You look worn out
and your resistance is low,so you could get sick, too.
Well, I'm notyou look worn oworried about me.
I'm worried about Andrea.
Suppose somethingyou look worn owhappened to her?
Mary...I'm worried about Andrea.
Suppose somethingstop doing this to yourself.Her?
It's that dream, isn't it?Ndrea.
Mama.
Mama?
David? David!
Her fever's gone.
Where's Lawrence?
You stay with her.
You're the first personshe asked for.
That missy sure knowshow to stealmyheart.
There you go.
Lawrence:Dog my cats,look at you.
Lawrence, what happenedto the little girl?
Lawrence:Dog my cats,what little girl?Look at you.
The little girlnamed Andrea
who got sick.
Oh.
Well, let's see...
The bluebird gotall the other birds together
and they searched all overuntil they found her daddy
the bluebird gotand brought him home.Ds together
daddy?
Hmm?
Did you bring me candy?
What do you think?
(Laughs)
Now I knowshe's better.You think?
(Giggles)(Laughs)
Lawrence, I can't tell youhow much Mary and I thank younk?
For all you've done.
No.
I'mthe one that should be thankingyou,mr. P.
I never realizedhow much joy
one little spiritcould bring into this world.
Man:Mr. Flynn?
Yes, sir.
Man:Mr. Lawrence Flynn?
Do you have somethingythat identifies you?
I know who I am.
Yes. Well, um...
Do you have somewherewe can talk?
This a... clockthat needs repairing?
No. This belongs to you.
This a... clockmy name is Donald Potter.Airing?
I'm an attorneyand executorongs to you.
Of the estatethis a... clockof the late maud gannon..Airing?
Miss maud is dead?
You didn't know?
I'm sorry.
One of the provisionsof her will
was that thisbe left to you.
Did you knowmiss maud?
Was that thisnot really.You.
Only as her attorney,that is.
Was that thisnot really.You.Not really?
Dear miss maud.
I guess she wentabout the time
that the good lorddear spared miss Andrea.
If you'll sign here...
Acknowledging receipt
our businesswill be concluded.
That surely doesconclude our business.
Good day, Mr. Potter.
Good day, sir.
Look, mama.
It's a dress.
Oh, how pretty.
Go show itto Catherine.
Thanks, daddy..
You're welcome, sweetie.
David, it's lovely
but it's Miles too big.
Maybe when she's ten.
I'm not good at this, am I?
Well... otherwise,you'd be perfect.
Thank you.
And now, a giftfor my big girl.
Here.
I hope you like it.
Nice paper.
I wrapped it myself.
Really?
What, you don't believe me?
Oh, David, it's beautiful.
I found it in an antique shopin London.
Look inside.
A Bible.
Turn to the pagewith the bookmarker.
"The lord is my Shepherd;I shall not want."
Remember the prayer serviceyou took me to?
It was our first date.
Only date.
Oh, this is the mostwonderful christmasi've ever had.
Are you goingto kiss mommy?
I sure am.
And don't think you're goingto get away without one.
Merry Christmas,sweetheart.
Merry Christmas.
(All laughing)
You got a moment?
If it's about losingthat contract
we're not going back in againwith a lowball bid.
I'm not goingto let them force me
into cutting the wagesof my people.
Then what arewe going to do?
If we don't getsome new business,we're going under.
Then what's going tohappen toyourpeople?
I built this businessduring the depression.
We made it through the war,and I won't let anything
happen to this companyor to those people down there.
We made sue? Call Mary. Tell herand I woni'll see her for dinner
but I'm going to stopby Lawrence's placeon the way home.
Hey, George, get thatworried look off your face.
(Dog barking)
(Gunshot)
Oh, my God.
Lawrence...
Lawrence,it's me.
What happened?
He came inwith that gun...
Mad because miss maudcut him out of her will.
He said that I had castsome sort of a spell over her
and cheated himout of a valuable clock.
I've been in war
and I know the lookin a man's eyes
when he's fixing to kill, but...
Wasn't no clockthat man was after.
It was me.
I tried to...
Tear the gun out of his hand...
Iit went off.
Tear the gun out of his hanokay.
All right.
What the hell happened here?
Did you kill him?
David:No.
I did.
Mary:I thought you mightlike some tea.
Why did you tellthem you did it?
Why don't you think I did?
Why did you tellbecause you're my husband
and I know you.
You're not capableof killing anyone.
Everyone's capableof killing.
It was Lawrence who shot him,wasn't it?
I knewhe'd never get a fair trial
and even if he was acquitted
gannon's friendswould come after him.
The only way to protect him
was to keep him out of italtogether.
How can he meanso much to you...
That you're willingto put everything--
everything we haveso muin jeopardy?
That you're willingduring world war it everything--
my father wasthe white captain
of a negrorifle company
and lawrencewas his sergeant.
Of a negrothere was a battle in France...
And my father's companywas in the middle of it.
They were gettingcut to pieces
and in the middleof this battle
Lawrence...
Repaired a machine gun
and used it
and allowed the wholecompany to escape.
He saved my father's life.
Dad proposed him
for the congressionalmedal of honor.Her's life.
Of course,he never received it.
It was unthinkablenalfor a negronor.Her's life.
To receive such an honorin those daysived it.
But...
My father never forgot...
And neither can I.
I'd alreadylost my mother. Forgot...
Without Lawrence, I wouldhave lost my father, too.
I owe him.
I owe this man.
We give the drill cuttershalf their previous area.
We set up the production sitefor the new prototype drill
we give the drill cuttersover in that quadrant.Ea.
That'd work.
David, thetrial's tomorrow.
It's stillnot too late.
George, please.
How can I beyour friend
if I don't tellyou what I feel?
How can I belook, I know what I'm doing.Iend
if I don't telli don't think you do.
A self-defense pleamight get Lawrence off
but in any case,he's an old manwith few years left.
You've got your wholelife ahead of you.
What kind of a lifewould I have
if I betrayed a friend?
What kind of a lifewouldyou haven't betrayed anyone
and even if you had,if I betrayed the man's a negro.
You've got to thinkofyourfamily first.
I have work.
So do you.
David, Lawrence is here.
I'm sorry to drop byso late, Mr. p, but...
No. Come onin, Lawrence.
I'm sorry to drop bywe got to talk.R. P, but...
Here, have a seat.
No, sir. Thank you.
I can't let you do this. A seat.
Lawrence, you're not goingno, sir. To talk me out of this.
Mr. p-- now, don'tget me wrong--u do this. A seat.
I appreciate whatyou're trying to do for me
but a man's conscienceis a powerful thing.
The fact is,I can't live with this.
The fact is
if you put yourfate in the hands
of the law around here,you might not live at all.
What if something goes wrongyourand they put you away? The hands
what about Mrs. p and missy?What happens to them?
Nothing's goingto happen.
Nothing's goingto go wrong.
I've never known any goodto come of telling a lie.
I'm doing thisto protect you.
I don't need protection.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I've always put my trustin the man upstairs.
All I have to dois tell the truth.
Lawrence...
You know and I know
that sometimes, thetruth isn't enough.
When you crouched bythe body of the shooting victim
did you ascertainthat he wasalready dead?
When you crouched bythe body of the shootyes, I did.
What else didyou determine?
Well, ev gannon,the victim
had been drinking.
I got quite a whiffof 90 proof.
Officer Brooks
would you please usethe pointer again
to show the jury wheremr. Parkin was standing
in relationto the victim?
Right about there.
He had the gunin his hands?
Right yes, he did.
Who did that gunthe gunbelong to?N his hands?
It was purchasedby everen gannon.
And where waslawrence Flynn
the owner ofthe property?
And where wahe was sitting rightlawrence flynnthere on the bed.
And how did Lawrence flynnappear to you, officer Brooks?
Like he was in shock.
I figured since gannon hadtrespassed on his place
that he'dkilled the man
and Mr. parkin hadtaken the gun from him.
Objection.
Conjecture.
Sustained.
You'll disregard
officer Brooks'sustained.Comment.
Go on.
Forget what was Brooks'in your mind, sir.T.
Just tell us exactly whatyou said to Lawrence Flynn.
I said, "whathappened here?
Did you kill him?"
And what didflynn say?
He didn't say anything.
Anmr. Parkinspoke up instead.
And what didmr. Parkin say?N't say anything.
He said that he did it--
that he shotthe man himself.
Please examinethe pistol, Mr. parkin.
Is that the weaponin question?
Yes, it is.
Will you please tell the courtexactly what you saw
and what happened
when you enteredflynn's workshop?
When I enteredthe shop
Mr. gannonhad the gun
when I enteredpointed at Mr. Flynn.
When he saw me, heaimed the gun at me
when ibut I knocked thepoinbarrel in the air
before he could fire.
And in the fightfor the gun
it discharged, andmr. Gannon was shot.
May I remind you, sir
of the testimony ofthe forensic expert?
That there were three setsof prints on that gun--
yours, the victim's,and Lawrence Flynn's.
Thatmr. Parkin, three setscan you explainhat gun--
how Lawrence victim's,flynn's prints Flynn's.
Got on that gun?
Yes, sir, I can.
As Mr. flynnhas already testified
Mr. gannon came into the shopand pulled the gun.
They struggledover the gun.
Isn't it more likely, sir
that you concoctedthis whole story
just to protectisn't it mlawrence Flynn?
No, sir.
Mr. parkin
you're an intelligent man.
I'm sure I don't haveto explain perjury to you.Parkin
so let me just remind you, sir,that you are under oath.
I'm sure I don't haveto explaare you the manou.Parkin
who fired the shotthat killed everen gannon?
Yes, I am.
Will the defendantplease rise?
The juryhas reached a verdict.
The jury findsdavid parkin...
Not guilty.
That he acted inself-defense.
The defendant is herebyreleased from custody
and this court is adjourned.
Thank God it's over.
Your lies ain'tfooling nobody, parkin.
You and your black friend
your lies athink you canfooling noboget by with this
but somebody'syogoing to haveack friend
to teach you a lesson.
What is hetalking about?
Hey, don't worryabout him.
Look, I've gotto get to the plant.
You take the car
and George will give mea ride home.
Okay?
Hey...
Cheer up.
We won.
I guess so.
I don't know what to say.
Just say thank God.
I didn't know youbelieved in God.
Mama, can we hae
a picnic tomorrow?
That's a good idea.
We'll do that.
Can daddy come to?
I'm afraid daddyhas to work, sweetheart.
What time willhe be home?
I'm not sure.
Can you tell daddyto come kiss megood night
I'm not sure.Even if I'm asleep?
Can you tell daddyhow about I kiss youbefore you go to sleep?
Daddy!
Come here.
Scoot backdown here, huh?
I'm going to tellyou something.
I'm going to makedyou a promise.
I'm going to telli promise from now on
I'm going to tryi'm going tand spend moredyou time at home, okay?
Okay.
Good night,sweetheart.
Sleep tight.
Don't let thosebedbugs bite.
Good night, daddy.
Good night, mama.
Good night, sweetheart.
(Banging)
(Thuds)
(Groans)
(Sniffs)
David, the houseis on fire.
Dear God! Andrea!
David, the houseis on fire.Mary!
Mary!
(Coughing)
Andrea.
Andrea!
Come on, baby.
Get some help! Come on!
Andrea, come on, baby.
(Crying)
It's impossible for us
to understandthe death of a child--
this precious life
that we have nurturedfrom the moment of birth.
She's becomeso much a part of us.
So we must reach outfrom the darkness
of our very human grief
with the light we must reach outof faithfrom the darkness
as the scripturespromisedur very human grief
"come unto me
"all ye that laborand are heavy laden
and I will give you rest."
Mary and David,let me assure you
that the only love
greater than a parents' love
is the love that God hasfor his children.
May it give you peace
in knowingthat your sweet Andrea
will forever rest
in the loving armsof our heavenly father.
You sureyou're all right?
We appreciateeverything
you've done, George.
Don't worry.
I'll take careof things at the plant.
Thank you.
I'll take carei don't understand it, Mr. p.
We spent this last yeargetting rid of the clocks
we spent all those yearsi don't understandcollecting.
We spent this last yearare you sure you want to...S
we spent all those yearsget rid of this last one?Ecting.
It's a beautiful piece.
That's not quitethe last one.
Mary won't let goof the rose gold watch.
Can you blame her?
You gave her that watchon your wedding day.
Can you blami guess I'm not much
on sentiment thesedays, Lawrence.
She was, uh...
She was a very special girl,that little missy.
Not a day goes by thati don't think about her.
I used to look forward
to every day I couldspend with her.
I don't havei usmany sunrises left
but I'll alwaysbe sorry that...
Little miss Andrea hadto die because of me.
Lawrence...
Andrea didn't diebecause of you.
If Cal Avery hadn'thated me so much
this would nothave happened.
Nobody brought more joy
into Andrea's lifethan you did.
And if anybody isresponsible for her death,
it's me.
I think we finally decidedto sell the house.
Mary, I know how muchyou love it here.
But I'm ready to let go.
The only way David willever find peace of mind
is if we leave this house.
Then he's notdoing any better?
Oh, he's doing better
if you'retalking about work.
The business is thriving
but he's never home.
Whenever I tryto talk about andreaving
he says nothing.Ome.
Wheneveryou know, he hasn't evento talk aboubeen to the cemetery
since we buried her.
I'm sorry.
Please, sit down.
And it isn't grief
I see in his eyes.
It's... it's anger.
You know, it wasn'tjust Andrea's life
that was taken away from me.
You know, it wasn'ti lost David, tooe
and nowit's Christmas, and...Om me.
No matter how hard I try
there's nothing to celebrate.
Are you sure you won'thave some tea?Hard I try
Mary...
I'm sorry,father Mike.
I wish I had a little moreof the Christmas spirit.
Mary, in time, you'll learnto live with your grief
but not beforeyou learn to forgive.
Mary, ingod's love is basedto live won forgiveness
and he forgives us
and, in turn, he expects usto forgive our fellow man.
How can we?Forgives us
maybe it's time to thinkabout someone else.
Time to do somethingfor another child.
I know a little girlnamed Martha
who isn't going to havemuch of a Christmas.
Father Mike.
How you doing, Ruth?
This is Mary
a friend of mine.
This could we come in?
Sorry about the house.
It's sort of a mess.
Oh, it's fine.
Did Martha do this?
Yes. She likesto make things.
It's very pretty.
Where is she?
Martha, you don'thave to hide.It's very pretty.
It's just father mikeand a friend of his.
Martha Anne!
I like your Christmas tree.
This is my friend Mary.
Hello, Martha.
She brought you something.
It's for you.
It's all right.It's yours to keep.
(Rattling and jangling)
David.
I didn't expect youhome so early.
Hi, sweetheart.
I didn't expect youhello, David. So early.
Father.
I've had the mostmarvelous afternoon.
Father Mike took meto meet the dearest little girl.
I gave herad the mosta Christmas giftternoon.
Father Mike took meto and her face just lit up.Irl.
I wish you'd been there.
For the first timesince Andrea died, I...
I found myself smiling
and her poor motherhas two other children
and no money to givethem a Christmas. Smiling
who is this family?
The mother's
really trying hard
but things have beenvery difficult for them
ever since her husbandwent to prison.
Martha's last nameis Avery.
She's Cal Avery's daughter.
I wasn't tryingto deceive you, Mary.
I just wanted you to feelthe spirit of Christmas again.
I hope you and David canfind it in your hearts
to forgive.
Forgive?
(Short exhale)
I've spent my whole life
trying to forgive.
First, my motherfor leaving us
and now, Cal Avery...
And as hard as that's been
it could never be as hardas forgiving myself.
I let my little girl down.
I let her down.
I was supposedto take care of her
I lprotect her.
I failed her.
David.
Come with me.
Merry Christmas.
Thank you.
Merry Christmas.Merry Christmas.
Thank yomerry Christmas.
Richard:How do you measure time?
Is it in hours and years
or is it more likelyin love and relationships?
For Mary and davi,is it the lesson was clea:
Or is it more likelyin time is precious.Hips?
For Mary and davi,it is also elusive and finite.
Orbut the thingselyinthat give us hope--ips?
For Mary and davi,it is love and family finite.
Orbut the thingselyfaith and forgiveness--s?
Somehow transcendd davi,even the boundaries of time..