♪ Countdown to our theme ♪
- ♪ I'm Gluko ♪
- ♪ I'm Lennon ♪
♪ We're very best of friends
indeed ♪
♪ Scientists have measured
our friendship at infinity ♪
♪ Oh-oh Oh-oh-oh Oh ♪
♪ Little Big Awesome ♪
♪ Living in Townopolis ♪
♪ We do what's right
and not what's wrong ♪
♪ Hey! That deer
just kissed my head ♪
♪ I guess that means
he likes this song ♪
♪ Oh-oh Oh-oh-oh Oh ♪
♪ Little Big Awesome ♪
- You're so awesome.
- Ha ha! Both.
- Never leave me.
[ music playing ]
Both: Roll, roll, roll,
roll, roll, roll!
I loooouuurrvvve
the snow, Gluko.
Don't you?
Totally, except...
[ grunting ]
[ squeak ]
[ deep sigh ]
That's better-ful.
Operation Giant Snow Rhombus
starts now.
- One...
- Two...
Both: Third number!
Yay!
[ panting ]
Whoo-whoa.
- Whoa!
- Yeah!
Whoa!
[ laughing ]
We're alive!
Bro, all this snow means
we're gonna have to shovel,
and arms day
isn't until tomorrow.
[ kiss ]
Let's do this!
Shoveling isn't so hard.
In fact, this is
the perfect time to...
shovel and strut.
♪ Look at us strut,
strut, strut ♪
♪ We're shovelin',
strut, strut, strut ♪
♪ Look at us strut,
strut, strut ♪
♪ We're shovelin',
strut, strut, strut ♪
All right!
Attaboy, bros.
[ arcade beeping ]
We got an "Attaboy."
Our hard work
is paying off big time.
[ music resumes ]
Hey, guys.
[ music continues ]
[ arcade beeping ]
Lennon, what's this feeling
I'm feel-if-eye-ing?
I think it's the "attaboys."
- Oh, we gotta get more.
- Yeah.
No need to worry, citizens,
and definitely no need to be mad
at me and think I stink.
As mayor, I'm going to scoop
this snow out of here
with my trusty snowplow pal.
- [ elephant trumpets ]
- Ahh!
Ahh! I mean, uh, good boy.
[ panting ]
Hey, Mayor, no need to plow.
We will shovel the town for you.
Oh, well, then.
[ arcade beeping ]
[ panting ]
- Ready, Gluko?
- Ready.
Ready, shovel?
I was forged ready.
[ grunting ]
Maybe we should have
asked for help.
No. [ shivering ]
What about those "attaboys"?
We need them all.
But if we try to shovel
all this snow alone,
we could pull a bloop muscle.
[ Lennon chattering ]
Nah, this will be easy.
[ wind blowing ]
Singers: ♪ They should
have asked for help ♪
Flap, flap, flap.
[ yelps ]
[ gasps ] Huh?
Gluko?
Ahh!
Stuhven, I need 500 cc's
of hot sauce, stat!
[ sizzling ]
[ teapot whistles ]
We can't--Ahh!
[ blubbering ]
Whoa!
Ohh! Spicy-ful.
[ exhales ]
What happened, Lennon?
We were frozen solid.
We never finished shoveling.
[ Gluko gasps ]
This is on you two.
I got a rep to protect.
[ hopping away ]
[ music playing ]
[ grunting ]
Both: Huh?
[ together ]
Gluko, Lennon.
Long time, no see.
Mord, Gord! We're so sorry
we didn't finish
shoveling the town.
We'll get started
on it right now.
Nah, don't even worry about it.
Frozen water under the bridge.
Yeah, we've had
the snow so long,
it's now part
of our town history.
Wait. How long have we been out?
[ together ]
Years.
Jinx.
Jinx again.
Jinx again again.
You owe me a castle.
Years?
But we're the town heroes.
We get all the "attaboys."
Gluko, gotta move.
Townopolis must be a hot mess
without our help.
Yeah.
Ugh. Make that a cold mess.
Singers:
♪ That's a play on words ♪
Huh. Come to think of it,
if it's been years,
shouldn't the snow have melted?
Oh, this is high-quality
slow-melting snow,
the very best.
We gotta go.
We have to buy
each other castles.
Hey, can we get
adjoining castles?
I wouldn't have it
any other way.
Both: Struggle, struggle,
struggle, struggle.
Hey, Gluko, notice something
different about the future?
Yes, and it's huge!
Both: Ho Cho Jo's.
By Jove, that's the biggest
Ho Cho Jo's I've ever seen!
Well, next to that one.
Gluko and Lennon: Ho--
And all of those.
Gluko and Lennon: Cho--
That's not the only change.
Gluko and Lennon: Jo's.
♪ And pants ♪
This is bad, real bad.
Ho Cho Jo normally
only sells hot chocolate.
We weren't here,
and now maybe someone
is making Ho Cho Jo sell...
Both: Pants!
No!
It's all our faults.
Future Ho Cho Jo
must be feeling awful-fied.
Ho Cho Jo:
Future me feels great.
With all this snow,
hot chocolate sales
have never been better.
But not as good as pants sales.
Ahh.
Yeah, about that,
aren't those pants a little...
Cozy? Agreed.
Being a licensed cozeologist,
I thought nothing was cozier
than my ho cho.
That was until I snapped
the seam of these pants.
- [ snap ]
- They're great for keeping
the high-quality snow
outta your undies.
You want a pair? Maybe two?
Buy four, get one free?
Maybe later.
So you're saying
the future is great,
even though Gluko and I
weren't around to help everyone?
Yeah.
But that makes no sense.
We got all the "attaboys."
Oh, there's the Mayor.
He's always been a mess.
Maybe he's been needing
our help-ifying.
Well, don't forget your pants.
[ grunting ]
Well, snap my seam.
- [ snap ]
- Ah.
It's Lennon and Gluko.
We were wondering
if anything terrible happened
since we were gone,
something we would have stopped
as the attaboy-getting
heroes of Townopolis.
Anything that's making
the future really bad-iful?
Hmm. That sounds like
a mayor question, fo sho,
but I'm not the mayor no mo.
Just call me Mayort.
I think the T gives me sass.
That's what ruined the future.
We weren't here
to save the Mayor's job.
So who's the Mayor now, Mayort?
Why, Geremy, of course.
So the future's
weird and horrible,
because Geremy's in control.
Actually, Geremy's the best
Mayor this town's ever seen,
much better than I ever was,
but that's okay,
because I found my true calling.
I just love my cart
and my pants.
[ snap ]
Ah, what a sweetie.
Citizens: Thanks, Mayor Geremy.
You're great.
Thanks, Mayor Geremy.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Mayor Geremy.
Attaboy, Geremy.
[ arcade beeping ]
But we used to get
the "attaboys."
How about some pants to turn
those sour faces into smiles?
Uh, no, thanks, Mayor.
Yeah, we're not really pants...
guys.
Ha ha. What a funny joke, guys.
But come on. Take the pants.
What is it with these pants?
Why is everyone so into them?
Huh?
Don't you say a thing.
Ahh! No, no, no!
Spill, Geremy.
What's going on?
Why is there a pair of pants
giving us the stink-eye?
Okay, fine.
The future is awful.
It all started with that snow.
It wouldn't melt.
Everything was so cold,
we had to get pants.
Little did we know, the pants
were plotting the whole thing.
Sure, yes, I wanted power,
but not like this,
not with pants!
[ echoing ]
Pants, pants.
Then why is everyone
so happy-ful?
It's all an act.
The pants make us do it.
I knew we couldn't trust him.
He's too cute.
[ screams ]
Ahh!
Both: We were right.
Townopolis is terrible,
because we weren't here.
♪ Oh, it's right to be right ♪
♪ Always right to be right ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, it's right
to be right ♪
♪ When you're right,
it's all right ♪
- ♪ It's right ♪
- ♪ Right ♪
♪ We were ri-i-ight ♪
Wear us.
Uhh! Ahh!
Maybe we'd better run.
[ grunting ]
You're gonna wear us!
The reign of evil parasite pants
must end, Gluko,
and we're the ones to fix it.
Let's go back in time and
stop all this from happening.
Lennon: Hey, Mr. Sun.
Hey, Lennon.
Hey, I haven't seen you
in a while.
- What's been going on?
- Uh, nothing much.
Little bit of this.
Little bit of that.
- Um...
- Oh, say,
think you could do us a solid
and go backwards
so we can time travel
to the past
and stop the pants
before they start?
Anything to get these pants off.
[ rewinding ]
Not to worry, slushy citizens.
As your Mayor, I'm gonna scoop
this snow outta here.
[ panting ]
Mayor!
Oh, are you guys gonna do it?
Attabo--
No, no, no.
Don't finish that praise.
Townopolis needs another hero,
someone who doesn't care
about "attaboys,"
someone who just wants to help,
and we know just who.
[ citizens
calling out, "Attaboy" ]
Attaboy, Mayor.
[ arcade beeping ]
Isn't this great, Lennon?
Listen to all
the Mayor's "attaboys."
Everyone's so happy-ful,
especially him. He needed this
way more than we did.
You're right, Gluko.
The Mayor's doing great.
Attaboy, Mayor,
and attaboy, snowplow.
- Oh, no! We missed a spot.
- Snow: Hey.
Pfft! It's just
a little high-quality snow.
No need to worry.
[ sinister music ]
Singer: ♪ Uh-oh ♪
[ music playing ]
- Tweezers.
- Jar.
- Vinegar.
Almost got it.
[ squish ]
Hoo! Awesome
pickle-ectomy, Gluko.
You're totally ready
for your pickling license exam.
I'm so excited!
I've waited for this day
ever since
I was a little jelly boy.
I just love to pickle things.
What other stuff can you pickle?
Oh, all kinds of stuff.
Carrots, beets, bicycles,
cherries, other pickles, ginger,
swim trunks, parsnips, clocks,
and that's just the tip
of the pickled iceberg.
Also, you can pickle an iceberg.
Singers: ♪ Yum ♪
- Query?
- Lennon?
Do you need a wand or
a magic spell to make pickles?
Nope. You just take
whatever yummy thing you want.
I love my new office.
Things are finally looking up
for Radford Ishmael Daddington.
Ooh, a radish.
And spoke too soon.
- Let me outta here.
- Sorry, sir.
I was just trying
to teach Lennon
that you can pickle anything.
Ow! I'm so glad you two
keep using me to learn things.
Both: Thanks.
Um, since you love
helping us so much
and since I already pickled you,
- can we eat you now?
- No.
I don't think he likes pickling
as much as you do.
Maybe he just doesn't get it.
Only a few are called.
Pickling is so cool,
'cause we get to see one thing
changing into another thing.
Oh, I'm becoming something more.
And then we eat that thing.
Oh, man, I can't wait to be
a certifercated pickler.
- I'll be a new jelly.
- New jelly?
As in, you'll be different?
Well, yeah, I guess so.
But I don't want you to change.
You're the jelly-est giant
I know.
[ yelps ] I change my mind.
I don't like pickling,
and you can't go to your test.
I'll still be the same fun dude,
just certifercated.
Are you sure?
Of course, buddy,
or you can call me...
Leon.
Okay, thanks, Leon.
Wait. Leon?
Not me. Him.
Whah! Hah!
No way! Leon, is that you?
You betcha. Any way you
could help this little acorn
get a squirrel off his back?
Craft, craft, craft.
[ squirrel chittering ]
I'm not real.
[ laughing ]
Buddy, it's so good to see you.
You, too. It's been so long.
I haven't seen you
since toupee school.
[ computer beeps ]
Go, Comb-overs!
You haven't changed one bit,
General Potato Shirt.
You got that right,
Dr. Shiitake Shorts.
I'm still the same old nut.
Well, what you been up to?
Well, recently
I was running for my life.
- [ laughing ]
- [ alarm clock rings ]
Ooh. I gotta get
to my pickling exam.
You gonna be okay?
I think so.
Wanna catch up like old times?
Well, what's this tell you?
A-whee, a-whee, a-whee.
Ah, the shinbone shimmy.
I haven't seen that in forever.
You go get
that pickling license.
We've got lots
of friending to do.
Serious face.
Action close-up.
Time to get my pickle on.
Singers: ♪ Get that pickle on ♪
- Buffalo.
- [ elephant trumpets ]
This is the greatest ever.
- Bunny with a mustache!
- [ rooster crows ]
We're having fun
just like we used to.
You got that right, buddy.
Hmm, that cloud doesn't
really look like anything.
Uh, yeah, well, you look
like a wonderful, caring guy
who always helps out
his friends.
Oh! Wow, insightful cloud. What?
[ stammering ] What's happening?
I got you, buddy.
[ grunts ]
You okay?
What was that?
I don't know,
but I don't like it.
Uh, Lennon!
[ stammering ] Oh.
Oh, this actually feels
kinda nice.
I don't know what the deal is.
All I know is I'm gonna keep on
saving you when that happens.
It's weird and different,
and I don't want you to change.
We need to stop this
from happening.
Do we, Admiral Kale Pants?
Maybe I need to grow?
I think my cousin Forest
had a similar thing
happen to him, and--
Oh, no, trust me.
You're great the way you are.
- You don't need to change.
- If you say so.
Hmm, how do we fix this?
[ music playing ]
[ chorus vocalizing ]
[ moans ]
[ panting ]
And here we have
the pickled cabbage.
[ swallows ]
[ music playing ]
Next, level four pickling.
Hey!
[ chorus vocalizing ]
I see that you added peppercorn
to those bicycles.
Can you explain
what inspired that?
Well, sir, I wanted to retain
the deliciousness
of a bicycle as a whole
while highlighting the
all-important handlebar flavor.
I call it a taste-cycle.
[ pen clicks, scribbles ]
[ moans ]
Was it bad?
It was bad, huh?
Time for your
final pickling test.
[ chorus vocalizing ]
[ gulps ]
Lennon: There we go.
Now you can sit comfortably
in this flowerpot,
and we can still have fun
like nothing's changed.
Yeah. It's--
It's kinda cramped in here.
Maybe I could stretch
my roots out in the grass?
No way!
Who knows what would happen
if we let your roots take hold.
[ sighs ]
Sad sigh.
Whoa, whoa...
Why the sad face, little acorn?
[ stammers ]
Well, I started rooting,
and I'm not sure if it's safe,
so my friend Lennon gave me this
to keep me from changing.
It gets better, little dude.
I started rooting when I
was your age. I was nervous,
but then I let myself
branch out, and now look at me.
- Huh.
- This is all natural, kiddo.
If you're ready,
let your roots grow,
and let nature take its course.
- Oh, I don't know.
- Whoa, whoa, whoo-hoo.
Lennon's my friend, and he
seems to know what's best.
- [ crash ]
- [ grunts ]
Well, do you think you're ready?
♪ Everything is going
through changes ♪
♪ Every day, a dusk,
a night, and a dawn ♪
♪ Springtime's turning,
from summer to fall ♪
♪ And then to winter
back to springtime ♪
♪ And on and on ♪
♪ Everything is
always in motion ♪
♪ While the planet
goes around and around ♪
♪ And with every little second
that's skipping along ♪
♪ There's something new
and different to be found ♪
♪ For example,
rain turning into a rainbow ♪
♪ A bunch of twigs
fashioned into a nest ♪
♪ Caterpillars
turning into butterflies ♪
♪ While the wind just whistles
through whatever comes next ♪
♪ Everything is going
through changes ♪
♪ Like the ever-flowing
tides of the sea ♪
♪ Don't be afraid,
just follow your instincts ♪
♪ You'll find yourself
right where you need to be ♪
♪ Changes ♪
♪ Going through changes ♪
Hey, Corporal Pasta Pants.
Oh, hey, uh,
Sergeant Cheese Socks.
What's wrong?
Do you need a new flowerpot?
So, yeah, about that, uh...
I think I should root
outside the pot.
No way,
Second Lieutenant Lentil Loops.
What could be better than this?
Come on! Let's go.
[ music playing ]
[ chorus vocalizing ]
And, now,
for your last pickling,
the ingredient is...
a skyscraper!
[ Gluko gasps ]
[ chorus vocalizing ]
[ grunts ]
Serious face.
[ chorus vocalizing ]
Yeah!
Ta-da!
[ muffled cries of pain ]
Oh, no!
I crushified my judges.
Hmm. [ laughing ]
You're making the yum noise.
I want to make yum noises, too.
Singers: ♪ These dudes
are eating a building ♪
That was the most delicious
building I have ever tasted.
- Bravo, Gluko.
- [ applause ]
You have positively
pickled my heart.
Yeah!
I'm an official pickler.
Who has 10 thumbs
and can pickle anything?
This, this, this, this, this,
this, this, this,
this, this guy.
[ tires screech ]
Singers: ♪ Cool pickle car ♪
Lennon, I'm a certified pickler.
[ stammers, sighs ]
Oh, wha-what's going on, buddy?
First of all, congratulations.
You make me so proud,
I could just burst.
Secondly, Leon won't talk to me.
He keeps rooting,
and I think he's mad at me
for keeping him in his pot.
Well, why not
just let him root outside?
'Cause he'll change,
and he doesn't have to.
He's great the way he is.
He--Wait a second.
Maybe you've changed, too,
since you got your license.
Oh, no.
Are you still the same Gluko?
I know how to squish the squash.
Here. Try this cucumber.
Mmm, delightful.
Now take a bite
of this pickled cucumber,
or "pickle"
for the uninformed layperson.
Hmm. Whoo-wow!
This is delicious.
I used to think
cucumbers were just good.
Now, since they've changed,
I love 'em even more.
That means you can change
for the better.
[ music playing ]
Yes. Ah, oh, whoo.
[ chuckles ] whoo!
I feel so a-live.
Whoo! Yeah!
Gluko: Lennon, look.
Lennon: More friends.
[ off-tune piano chord ]
[ sinister laugh ]
[ music playing ]
Chirp.