your mother sent her down she wants to
see
so you've grown tonight the flavor it's
melodramatic claptrap the provinces are
tiresome by it pays and there are a few
even out here all married
you know what dr. Freud I'd have to say
about that
yeah just fine didn't it football hadn't
run off we'd never have you for an
auntie her mother really my angel far
more entertaining one no no you didn't
know her before
it's not for travel I know but your
mother simply could not be dissuaded she
had to see her Angelica straight away
how is she Nora I've never seen her in
such a state I don't you make us all a
nice cup of tea she's coming one coming
right up
Jenica wait angel mine's not what he was
no no listen
she has become more troubled by the past
and by magic no you're not mom are you
young still and healthy who must tell
you I must clear my conscience
Constance it's after noon it I can't
your conscience wait until the morning
oh I'll fetch your sleeping draught
I'm staying tonight meanwhile all day
tomorrow you sleep now it's a battle for
he did not and my son did not disappear
it is not precisely as I've always told
you day I met your father
Oh
yeah
mr. Bertoni sir welcome to you its
Barton now Pendleton officially and I
should like stationery to reflect it of
course also pen nibs Inc and you're new
here I answer well then congratulations
from one of mr. peniston's customers you
are a most welcome
presence constants assist mr. Barton if
you please shall mr. Pendleton deliver
your stationery when it is ready no I
shall come myself
it cannot be absolutely what you had me
bring the naturalist follow the Beagle
fellow she says we are well behaved Apes
it was you who believed this and now you
say the opposite not the opposite merely
to point out the limits of it just as
we'd more than bananas in other ways
clearly we are not X and in this
this distribution of desire British
otherwise italian british as much as you
we are british because of how we are yes
when I think of the fools who believe in
such things there it is mr. Bartel
notice a photograph you may believe what
you see with your own eyes may you not I
believe what I see in you miss Douglas
dear your sweet beauty and noble
simplicity I should have told you I mean
often
first my siblings they wasted away
finally your mother is to be sentient
simply to watch never to prevent only to
wait for something horrible to happened
to your child
one after another they melted away from
her
and she too was taken and fatherless
they slept too deeply all of them these
are your enemies these are the beasts
that still lives
these stole them all I expect so
however a doctor's expected to catch
such tiny little sissies they cannot be
caught one can only deny them the
conditions that favor their growth might
you discover an end to all sickness we
might we very well my dear
I don't know what we do but we all live
forever miss Douglas you have no
protector none at all will you have me
as protector will you
well you showed me your place of work
the laboratory is no place for a woman
in gone someday someday perhaps he will
be my life's adventure he's a man Connie
most hide no more mister in them than
that chair come inside my dear are you
afraid of your Joseph
you are so lovely
Oh
Joseph
that's all know I've done a fine job of
making your home while we've been away I
suppose you'll be wanting to take your
pleasure now you have until nightfall
again that's a duck disturbing my
slumber in the middle of the night no
wonder I'm idle all day
no our finally most useless talk about
more
I'm wanted at the laboratory my love you
will make life safe about children right
now indeed that is our one aim
of course you are people girlfriend
Pendleton's you are exquisite flattened
over forgive James Pendleton if he's
reduced you to making deliveries no no I
reside here now I'm married to mr.
Joseph fat indeed
counter-jumper
and it's true you might have done better
do you know why I married your car for
the same reason I hope you married me
like in the fairy stories
you are no longer needed nothing to do
with you are very fortunate to be alive
you and your child both God does not
intend all women to be mothers
you must not risk it again I'm not you
are to desist entirely
find your pleasure elsewhere
it is not your fault let's give your
sweet mother arrest
as the grown departed baker's shop the
wolf left him and lifted and ground from
distant
time to sleep my dog come to me please
thank you
Angelica it's time to go home do you
wish your surviving daughter to be
motherless do you I told her that the
girl's birth you must make of yourself a
Hortis conclusive a closed garden you
understand unless you find a to greater
strain on a lascivious and intemperate
will you pursue your own desire at your
family's expense I will have a word with
mr. Barton good evening sir
your wife will live by the grace of God
is Angelica wealth God with Laura
bring her to me your strength dear
academic is my strength
there are Senora
it is her monthly day away my love seems
to come around nearly every week your
father fought very bravely and darkest
Africa he was awarded this for courage
sorry member
you've an even more morose expression
than usual
I will not tire you with my domestic
trials too
she shuns me
then how often you calling on our tender
friends I do not consult my than and
neither should you come you tell me your
wife refuses to participate up to one's
a reasonable contractual expectations
she has been I know I know
her health all the more reason not to
play poke an undignified brutish pursuit
of a very fleeting pleasure do you know
other kinds I have suffered this insult
too long Angelica Satan her nursery
tonight hmm
the young man climbed up onto the Swans
back then the Swan spread its great blue
wings and flew up into the sky and they
never did come back to her then what you
think I never saw his family again there
he is the young man is flying I see
shall I stay with you my Duff until you
fall asleep
No thank you mama the princess denies
the Sun is he doing very well my love
shall I leave the door open
shall we Rosen baby you went to her
slept there the whole night she cried
out to me and when you do not come she
will learn to comfort herself comfort
herself I cannot recall opening a debate
on the point what's what I welcome is
that oh if he Alice no he has only come
for a brief visit see quite tame
friendly even no know it colleague he's
handsome
what is his name I do not know can't we
keep him
no dear as you'll hear he has his own
home then you must go back to it
Oh Tara's gone we've been torn asunder
by doctors in fear to live
seek elsewhere what you must know there
are solutions solutions there are other
ways there is no danger there is no
danger at this oh you are my only con we
have been tested both of us when we are
apart in our hearts the space is filled
with coals dark thoughts
it's papyrus Anna no he was a soldier
once but now he works what is work work
is what every man must do what must a
party you must care for us to protect us
you must cure disease but you like to
visit the post poetry perhaps we could
go and visit him one day soon
dr. Joseph Barton yes just down there
dr. Bart Observatory the doctor's
entrance is down the passage on the
right mark is this doctor button the
bartering visitors are generally not
permitted he's my husband
and he is a senior man
once it's come back it is nobody reduce
the benefits of science Constance
right
breathing
you
it was right there it seems to be very
directly
it was wet what are you special
I cannot say nothing at present do you
concur Angelica is safe my dear how did
you sleep Angelica no visitors in the
night last night
just one mom she was part of the night
but then she butter to her own bed I
think she visits you in the night
because she was worried for you need
mother worry do you think Angelica I
think this is right she worried is what
mothers do
sometimes you're not here I'm sorry for
this times the pieces we shall run in
the park
I think sometimes he is pink and
sometimes blue did he no no he will
never hurt you because I would protect
you I love you so much let me see your
beautiful face what is the matter now
one can scarcely catch one's breath in
this house Christine bent on maintaining
chaos there's nothing feel out of
balance
I hesitate to answer I suspect you would
appreciate neither my words nor my tone
I saw it again last night something
remover my god you thought you know I
had this notion no I didn't think of
this and besides you what I seen so you
confirmed infantile fancy blue lights
hovering masculine dangerous you spout
nonsense I've seen limits you and you
take a mimicry for wisdom for God's sake
I've doctor when it gives you a sleeping
draught
I'm sorry
please could you leave a ketchup if I
might leave anything I know I know it's
not my place of course Nora please yeah
thanks to me welcome if there's anything
in my power
something is hurt Angelica I sort to
give that last night as plain as I see
you now
it is unspeakable what it wants
Madame I feared to speak but do you know
someone this woman she understands all
of them dark things but Jesus fearless
as any man I can fetch her please yes
come tell her I have been desperate need
I just bring her here at once and if
there's a mr. Barton inquires just I
don't know just tell him don't tell him
anything
usual terms of course I mean precisely
is the disturbance I don't know do you
light a float man ain't never seen any
what's it to you and if the woman's got
bad she's you come in and you wave your
parsley all about it that's it isn't it
and I get my 20% do you know the
crocodiles look today just as they
looked when dinosaurs trot the earth
whereas other animals have transformed
so as to be scarcely recognizable man
for instance man and woman both we were
animals now we are something higher
nobler they do not mean that is folks
forget the jobs
I'm afraid I've lost my touch after so
many years mr. practice it is perfectly
edible my dear Nora will be healed one
hopes by breakfast time
where this is mrs. Montague as I
described and you and mrs. Bartman
Joshua you poor lovely creature
I am grateful well you're not sleeping
well my dear I must appear dreadful I'm
the country only somewhat fatigued you
must forgive my making a personal remark
I find it very difficult to hide my
feelings from people I like
do you know me so soon come give us your
hand please come in take my hand and
lead me in mrs. Burton the evil that
troubles your home must see that I am
your invited guest
so relieved to have him canceled
precisely two women together can
withstand quite anything oh he's very
handsome yes and his profession your
home is very elegant and enviable thank
you
he's a scientist he seeks to find the
course of disease and animals a
veterinarian no I mean he looks inside
of animals to find the cause of all
diseases delicious sexiest he has
arguments to defend his actions I mean
kind of help their natures mrs. Barton
we must not fold them
Nora leave us now your walls sing with
the unseen I'm at your service
mrs. Barton I've heard all manner of
Horrors in my ears open ladies such as
yourself can I be shocked
I am also I wish to make this caring
everybody not a man I do not think like
a man and nor do I wish to so do not
tell me what you know or what you can
prove
tell me what you feel from the beginning
something seems to have snapped
fractured in him his desires seemed
there are cracks all of the house yeah
and they're all in there and here and to
which that unholy thing fled
I try to please cost that I cannot never
forgive well of course you will forgive
you are a woman and a wife my child
suffers payables the precise moment I am
submissive to my ass do you understand I
do
he can pass me to compel myself all
right
I compel him to come in Jesus that is
beyond homeless too resistant much my
chance
screaming yeah brave fine down and we
will clear these noxious s from your
beautiful huh and all will be well
I promise
hmm army ain't it just like I said she's
nothing like you said what you mean okay
you should consider yourself lucky to be
in such a fine ladies employ courage my
dear and above all faith in your own
pure innocence
beloved Angelica say hello to the nice
lady just true to her name
tonight past
what incident I am relieved beyond
reckoning your spell's and protections
have succeeded oh sure hey you your fee
mrs. Monti q400 misses all this yeah oh
my dear we have only just begun last
night's rest by Mamie and we were on the
correct path or it may mean nothing at
all
you do have a responsibility to your
husband but it is not too bad child
after child and nor is it to pander to
his every hourly whim not some poor
slave girl in the sheiks harem husbands
are not meant to burn light use defiling
their surroundings with their bottomless
thirsts we mean from him to unleash with
least and as much modesty and shame as
they can possibly muster those
incarnations a few times the
multiplication of our race
name's then tape you're so well-spoken
missus Montague where did you learn such
eloquence my education was in the
theater an actress for time you
disapprove they chose me but they must
never tell lies child quite so quite so
but then again you must never fear
telling the truth now let us discuss
this as three ladies did you truly see
him in the trees just now I do not like
it when you are frightened I do not
suppose that you do well you protect my
mommy I will indeed
I am to York overnight mrs. Barton my
laughter bah he loves you as well my
darling I do not
she's quite asleep oh dear what a
splendid title come we mustn't let Laura
Tsukiko Sacre
treat me like a royal like a dear friend
have you ever wondered why it is that
women should appear to be lied it's
quite simple really
you see if we glide then we have no legs
and if we have no legs then men need not
be tormented by the thought of our lives
by here amongst ourselves anywhere
really that women live free of men they
live with legs me ladies are you I
thought you might enjoy a sip of the
Masters port wine to go with the cheese
will he not detect its depletion he
never has before madam all right
tomorrow you tense if the night should
pass without incident and is that not
proved his role perhaps not certainly
that there is not your husband in body
you see him evil and may be projected
without will even without money
yeah
sleep my death you're in terrible native
it
I'll keep watch
be assured
you have allowed this crisis to fester
beyond all bounds now you talk of
shattered nerves we you're a senior and
hallucination
truth be told none of this is terribly
uncommon button in women of your wife's
class now in your sorry case your wife
is determined to let herself go
it appears and with that surrender of
character she has exposed to you your
home and your child to a grave infection
and I fear we have passed the point of
easy treatment
varam am i permitted out of my own home
dearest Nora sir was quite plain about
your need for peace rest today I could
do you work while you brought you need
never know please madam I see
get out please madam this will calm your
nerves this sir requested you drink it
you deserve the rest wrench if I could
at least report to mr. Barton that I
gave it to your mom please
am I not to your liking
no no I know it will not because it's
just keep coming forward I promise II
you can't find us whose stage we were to
get this Mustang to muster constants
constants
what I dream enough to awaken your we've
only got a few minutes as the carriage
waiting outside no no you know you must
I can't
you must what if he wakes up and finds
that you fled he will track you down
he will take Angelika he will most
likely send you to bedlam Constance you
must return home and you must play your
part I will come to you he will not
allow you through the door I will find a
way and we will destroy this demon
together and we will restore peace to
your home it's just too late for that do
you remember the tenderness with which
you showed me as likeness here in your
locket do you recall it once and you
will again but until then you must have
courage you must be bold and fear not
I will make you proud
you have again exhausted yourself asleep
in the chair he cried out to me in the
night I should have returned here I know
you should have done but as you say the
child needed you she did and you spent
all night in this chair
yes yeah
where is Angelica she is with Nora she
had very odd dreams she's just as you
say
you want another day's rest at least I
should instruct Nora I'm sorry to be
late for tea
it's the Princess Elizabeth the very
effectively concerts here is a colleague
I have long intended you to meet dr.
Douglas miles how delighted I am to meet
you dr. Marrs my dearest pleasure to
have your home so soon
Nora take the child and bring some tea
for our guests right away mom I must
compliment you mrs. Barton on your sense
of decoration Constance please make dr.
Myles comfortable I unfortunately have
forgotten my apologies poor dear I hope
you will excuse an old man's curiosity
what a friend's curiosity I hope you
will see me as a friend of course
now most wives have some permissible
complaint to make and please be assured
of my absolute discretion well I do have
one complaint Joseph's work such long
hours I have not enough the pleasure of
his company have you any worries
do you fear him what an amusing question
who I ever should I have any fear of mr.
Barton told me that you saw his work did
that upset you it may well disorient one
do I seem disoriented dr. miles
Joseph's work is a vital import but you
cannot ask me to explain it very well
hmm I only know how proud I am of his
efforts will you have another piece of
cake of it
yes thank you you are queen of the
domestic arts
I wonder what it is God
you know there are times when you may
excuse yourself for acquiring arrest I
know very well our women toil on our
path under emotional burdens that are
quite unknown to us a time away to
refresh one spirits could be arranged in
a trice just for the asking
arrest what English woman could accept
such unmerited chat
well our husbands have withstood
sufferings we soft women have not to
crave rest I should find it a disgrace
if I may speak plainly as a friend
doctor do you think I could speak with
your daughter
would be an honor
to display her conversation
perfection and Jerrica button you truly
are a small duplicate of your gracious
mother thank you sir
Mama's very lovely yes I think I have
let me see yes I do I have a piece a
very special licorice for the little
girl who can tell me how was it that
your bedroom caught fire
we cause accidents confess pokes me my
trip to put my doll and I truly am sorry
sir hmm a wise child and you mrs. Barton
you were a delightful hostess and I fear
I've taken up too much of your time mrs.
Barton
Oh
no more fear
I always stop and oh well
nobody
I know that donation awaits before
laughter what made you believe and I am
prepared for it I don't know what
Angelica angels
she's known the right mind this is
different she's I remember now the fire
you and the man with the licorice your
father did disappear as we've always
told you I
constants look how you've worked
yourself
gently
you