(UPBEAT MUSIC)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
(BELL RINGING)
Dammit!
First day.
What'd you do?
Excuse me.
What are you seeing
the principal for?
Vandalism?
Smoking pot in the boys room?
Bring a weapon to school? What?
No, it's personal.
Ooh, personal.
Wait.
You're the new kid, aren't ya?
Busted.
Tonya Michaels?
Consider me the
welcoming committee.
Follow me.
So what brings you
to Willow Falls?
Kinda late in the
year, don't you think?
Well, my parents split.
My mom's a nurse and
this is the only place
that she could find work.
Meaning what?
Huh?
What are you implying? This
place is just some shit hole?
- No, no, I...
- Not good enough for you?
I didn't mean that
it was some shit hole.
Relax.
I'm just fucking with ya.
Welcome, new fish.
You got some major balls
coming to this town.
Most of us just wanna
get the hell out.
Yeah, why is that?
(BELL RINGING)
♪ I'm lonely ♪
(PHONE RINGING)
It's a pleasure
being your tour guide.
Before I forget.
Mr. Mitchell.
We pride ourselves on
punctuality at this school.
Ain't that right, Ms. Michaels?
I was just
showing him the way.
That's sweet of you.
Class.
Now.
Look, I know why you
called me down here.
Maybe we should talk
about this in private.
There's not really
much to talk about.
I talked to your
principal at your old school
about what happened.
Past is the past.
And sir, I'd really appreciate
if we could keep it there.
I hear you.
Let's talk about it anyway.
After you.
Nice office.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(UPBEAT MUSIC)
(MUFFLED MOANING)
TJ: Damn!
Hey, honey.
I didn't know you would be home.
My shift ends at 10.
Oh!
Yeah.
Right.
How was your first shift?
It was okay.
Listen, I really need
to get some sleep.
Can you and Patrick-
- TJ!
He works at the bank.
He took me to Dairy Queen.
He's a really, really nice guy.
You're really gonna like him.
Can you do me a favor, hun?
When you meet him,
could you call him, dad?
Okay.
Goodnight.
Night.
Swing the hammer.
Challenge the strong man.
(GROWLING)
Pussies.
Challenge the strong man.
Swing the hammer.
(GROWLING)
Three in a row is a winner.
Okay. Okay.
Bon Jovi, that's enough.
Come on over, that's enough.
You're not a winner?
You're a loser.
Take off.
So what are your
friends? Carnies?
Funny.
Let me guess.
In your old town,
you and your friends
got drunk in the McDonald's
parking lot and did wheelies.
(METAL RATTLING)
Top that, bitches.
What's up, babe?
I was wondering
when you'd get here.
Fuck off.
I decided to drag the new kid
out to have some fun with us.
This is Chris Mitchell.
Tonya does love her strays.
This is Zack.
He seems like a big jerk,
but then you find out, he is.
You used to love jerking it.
Now you jerk yourself.
(LAUGHING)
Shut up.
You look like a laffy taffy
in that, you know that?
What is it? A buck a piece?
Yes, sir. Buck a piece.
Three in a row, big time winner.
Today, please.
You got this.
How about you, tough guy?
Number three?
(CHUCKLING)
- Jeez!
- Mr. Chuckles here is Brett.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, you too.
Cotton candy?
Nah, I'm good.
(SPOOKY MUSIC)
You know it.
- Let's go.
- Cotton candy?
Yeah.
See you after the carnival.
Come.
Come, my friend.
Come inside.
What do you want, man?
What are your
future, my friend.
Sit down.
I'm not paying you.
It's free.
Yes.
Your hand.
There's a man from your past.
You need to reconnect with him.
What are you talking about?
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
You will have a long and
prosperous life, my friend.
Get off me, you freak?
- (LAUGHING)
- What's the hold up?
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
You want some?
Yeah, I didn't think so.
The way you're drinking
that beer, like a pussy?
All right, hand it over.
(COUGHS)
(LAUGHING)
We should do a toast to Laura.
Bro.
Dick move.
What?
Who's Laura?
Tonya's little sister.
Oh, you never mentioned
you have a sister.
Had a sister.
What happened?
She went missing.
Missing.
We all know what happened.
Edith Cranston got to her.
What?
She used to run
this daycare center.
One day Laura was there and
then no one ever saw her again.
(SOMBER MUSIC)
Look, I don't want
to talk about that.
It's okay, babe.
It's not okay.
It's never gonna be okay.
Look, we can't
get her to confess,
but we can make
that old hag suffer.
Oh yeah.
I'm feelin' it.
I think it's time we
pay her another visit.
Where are we going?
It's an old tradition.
You'll see.
(LAUGHS)
All right, Mr. Chuckles.
So, fill me in on
this little tradition.
You'll see.
We're going to Cranston's.
Cranston's? Why?
We like to remind her
what kinda monster she is.
CHRIS: Yeah?
We flooded her
basement, cut her tires.
One time we left flaming
shit on her porch,
which is classic.
And you know, she
really is a monster.
- She's a witch.
- Bro.
She is.
Everyone knows it.
Your sister.
What happened?
We don't know for sure.
That's the hard part.
On her birthday,
she was at Cranston's daycare
and she just never came home.
The police questioned Cranston.
They shut down her
daycare completely,
but they never
found Laura's body.
And that rich bitch,
she hired a fancy lawyer
and just got away with it.
I'm sorry.
Me too.
The police forgot about Laura.
But we never did,
and we won't let her either.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
For Laura.
- (GLASS BREAKING)
- For Laura.
For Laura.
I'm sorry.
- (BRETT LAUGHS)
- Pussy.
Move your ass.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Oh, shit.
Going somewhere?
Yeah.
So get the hell out of our way.
This is my property,
and you are trespassing.
You're lucky my
husband is not here.
He would shoot you
right where you stand.
And there's a little
more blood on your hands.
I am not going to be
run out of my own home.
You can shatter my windows
and I will replace them.
You can throw a dead
animal and I will bury it.
You can slash my tires,
I will get new ones.
But I'm staying right here.
You wanna know why?
Do you wanna know why?
Because as much as you
hate me, I hate you more.
I hate you more.
Then leave, 'cause
we're never gonna stop.
Not until you leave or die.
I'm not afraid of you,
but you,
you should be very,
very afraid of me.
Where did you get
that necklace, Tonya?
See you in hell,
you old woman.
Yes, you will.
And I'm gonna save you a seat.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Now, get out.
- (HOWLING)
- Oh my God.
(LAUGHING)
(SOMBER MUSIC)
Penny for your thoughts.
A penny.
That's it?
A kiss then.
I'm trying to remember
the adventures we had.
The hopes,
dreams,
the children.
But it's all gone.
Edith, what are you...
There's only darkness.
Look at me.
My dream was to be
with you forever.
And I am.
So I'm happy as a clam.
Good.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(MUTTERING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Are you okay, Chris?
I'm fine, ma.
You don't seem like yourself.
Are you sure everything's okay?
You know, if you need to
talk to someone, I'm here.
(SOFT MUSIC)
(UPBEAT PLAYFUL MUSIC)
Hey.
Hey, you.
I got your call.
Haven't seen you at
school the last few days.
I got worried.
You got worried.
Actually I was
a little worried.
Are you okay?
Not really.
You do feel a little hot.
Is this about Cranston?
We were there the night she...
- What if...
- What if what?
I don't know, man.
What if she had a heart attack?
- What if we were the reason?
- We didn't do anything.
And if anybody asks, you
keep your mouth shut.
Or what?
You're gonna throw a rock at me?
You think you're such a badass?
Well, I'm not some
little old lady
you can just push around.
I'm not afraid of you.
Maybe you should be.
Maybe you should come
up with a better line.
Relax. Relax.
You're both pretty.
Hey.
You're a good guy.
I like that about you.
You're sweet.
She's gone.
And the world is a
better place for it.
Yeah, she was into
some dark stuff.
I'm telling you, man.
She was a witch.
What?
You saw how she was that night.
Acting all crazy.
Fucking witch.
It doesn't matter.
She's dead.
And we can't change that.
And we,
we're alive.
We've got our whole
lives ahead of us.
So we should just bury
the past and enjoy it.
Hey, are we good?
Yeah.
I guess.
Then say it.
Tell me we're good.
Yeah, we're good.
We're good.
(UPBEAT MUSIC)
Hey, you wanna play Pac-Man?
I wanna play Pac-Man.
(TV STATIC BUZZING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello.
Hello, Christopher.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(DOORBELL RINGING)
Come with me.
Hold on.
We're not going
anywhere with you
until you tell us
why we're here.
Patience is a virtue.
We're not exactly the
virtuous type, old man.
Have a seat.
Tonya.
(SOFT MUSIC)
Zack.
Brett.
And Chris.
You must be new.
Doesn't matter.
I'm sorry to hear
about your wife.
I'm sure you're heartbroken.
And I know you all are
because whose house are
you gonna terrorize now?
Look, we don't
want any trouble.
No one wants trouble.
Sometimes it just finds them.
Look, enough with
the small talk.
What do you want?
Tonya, Tonya.
If I got what I wanted, Tonya,
this meeting would be
a whole lot less civil.
Edith was different.
She was more forgiving.
So it seems like she
surprised everyone
when she included
you in her will.
Bullshit.
She hated us.
That's what I thought.
Yet, here we are.
For what?
Read.
You can read, can't you?
Or was your school too far
from your trailer park?
We don't have to take this.
Sit down.
I don't want anything of hers.
Really?
Not even $100,000?
Did you just say $100,000?
What's the catch?
Pardon me?
With people like you,
there's always a catch.
People like me.
You don't know
anything about me.
You don't know anything
about me or my wife.
We know all we need to know.
So you think.
If you knew anything
about Edith,
you'd know there was
one thing she liked.
And that was to play games.
I like games.
What kind of game?
Simple ones, really?
Now, are any of
you superstitious?
Not afraid of ghosts or things
that go bump in the night?
I don't believe
in any of that shit.
So the answer would be no.
It's a no for me too.
And what about you boys?
(CHUCKLES)
Good.
Well, the game's simple really?
There's a phone
upstairs in the study
at the end of the hall.
All four of you must go
up there one at a time.
There's a number
next to the phone.
You call it.
You stay on the
phone for one minute,
you get $100,000.
That's it?
That's it.
Easy as pie.
Who are we calling?
You're calling Edith.
See, she had me bury
a phone with her.
Okay, now that's crazy.
Edith was always
a little eccentric.
Wait, so all we gotta do
is stay on the
phone for a minute?
One minute.
That's it.
Then you exit out the back door
and the money will be
yours in the morning.
And what if we hang up early?
Then your money will be split
between the people
who stay on the call.
I still call bullshit.
I don't know what you're up to.
Read the contract.
It's all legal.
Legal or not, I
don't want your money.
Hey, speak for yourself.
If I get this, we're set.
Zack, there is no we.
You gotta get that
through your head.
And I'm outta here.
Screw your game.
Tonya, before you leave, dear,
there's one more thing
I need to tell you.
What?
Edith's death was
not an accident.
The paper was kind enough
to omit the details,
but Edith killed herself.
That sucks.
What does it have to do with us?
Everything.
You see, she left
a suicide note.
And in that note, she
made it very clear
that your constant
threats to her,
you and your little
friends over the years
was more than she could bear.
She was a strong woman,
but she was depressed.
And all those years of torture-
- They were just pranks.
They were pranks to you.
They were devastating to her.
Devastating.
Then your little confrontation
with her the other night.
That was the final straw.
I was traveling.
I wish to God I was
here, but I wasn't.
She was all alone.
She was afraid for her life.
And she knew that not
one person in this town
would protect her from
you or you or you.
Oh God!
I didn't even know her.
But you were here.
You saw it.
Yeah.
What are you saying?
I'm saying, you let me
honor my wife's last wish
by making the call.
Otherwise, I'll go to
the police with the note.
Make sure that you all
pay for what you did.
I loved Edith more than life.
Even more than revenge.
That's why I'm
giving you a choice.
Now, I'm gonna pour
myself a drink.
When I get back, I
expect an answer.
TONYA: You guys aren't
seriously considering this,
are you?
Hell yeah.
We may not wanna grow
up in the shit hole,
we'll tell him about
this (INDISTINCT)
Right now I need this
money to get outta here.
CHRIS: Crazy
as you say she is,
I have to admit I've
seen stranger things.
I can't get the
police on my tail.
TONYA: Why?
You got a record?
I just can't.
A one minute phone call.
There's four of us.
We each call, we could
be gone in five minutes.
So what's it gonna be?
Do you make your call
or do I make mine?
We're gonna do it, but
if you try anything...
You don't have
to worry about me.
I'll be outside
the back entrance
waiting to greet you
when you're done.
Just one of you can
go upstairs at a time.
The rest of you have
to wait down here.
Don't go snooping around.
Once one of you has
completed the call,
the Lira clock
upstairs, it will chime.
Then the next person
can take their turn.
Zack.
You're such a tough
guy. You go first.
Brett, you like following
your brother's footsteps.
You'll be second.
Chris, you follow Brett.
Tonya, you'll make
the final call.
Lucky me.
So good.
I know that Edith's
looking down on us.
Smiling knowing that her
final wish has been granted.
Once we're done with all this,
we can put the
ugliness behind us
and we can start to heal.
Well, that wasn't
creepy at all.
Hey, bro.
It's just a phone call.
I know that, dumb ass.
Zack.
You don't have to do this
if you don't want to.
I'm fine.
We're not all pussies like you.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Let's do this.
This house is whack.
(CLOCK TICKING)
(PHONE RINGING)
(SPOOKY, OMINOUS MUSIC)
(CROWS CAWING)
(PHONE RINGING)
EDITH: What the hell!
Hello.
Who is this?
EDITH: I'm so
glad you called.
Okay.
Fine, I'll bite.
How're you doing this?
EDITH: Let's not waste
time with questions.
Can you do me a favor?
Yes ma'am.
And what is it that
I can do for you?
EDITH: Be a dear
and look in the mirror.
(SPOOKY MUSIC)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SCREAMING)
What the hell is this?
EDITH: You're
in my world now.
You know what?
The hell with this?
(SPOOKY, DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(SOMBER MUSIC)
HARLISS: Boys.
Brett, get under the bed.
No, Zack.
I can't.
There's monsters under the bed.
Just do it.
Come on.
Unlock this damn door.
How many times have I told you
about locking the goddam
door in my house, huh?
Oh, you're gonna
stand up to me now?
Yeah.
Let's see it then.
Come here, you
little piece of shit.
I'm not afraid of you.
Are you a big man now?
Yeah?
Why don't you show me?
Take your best shot.
You're pathetic.
Both of ya.
Come on.
You know what time it is.
I don't know why you
make me do this to you.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
BRETT: Zack.
Zack.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(OMINOUS GROWLING)
(SPOOKY, OMINOUS MUSIC)
(GROWLING)
(SOFT MUSIC)
Zack.
Zack, Zack, Zack.
You know you cannot run from me,
because I am always
gonna find you.
Dad.
You.
So just like I thought.
You are still too much
of a pussy to fight back.
Dad...
You're a complete
embarrassment, Zack.
I'm embarrassed
to be your father
I'm gonna give you
one last chance
to hit me, you piece of shit.
I can't.
I'm sorry, I can't.
(SOBBING)
You can't?
I can't.
It's okay.
That's a good boy.
I just wanna go home.
It's all right.
That's a good boy.
You're gonna go home.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Son of a bitch.
(SPOOKY MUSIC)
What kinda door
doesn't have handles?
He's taking too long.
I want my money.
Simmer down.
It's only been a few minutes.
Yeah. Yeah.
All right.
(CLOCK CHIMES)
It's my turn.
- Wait.
- I am not pussy.
If Zack can do it, so can I.
See you when I'm rich.
Hey, would you
mind holding this?
Yeah, sure.
You can have it if you want.
Weird day.
You're fine.
You're not weak, and
you're not a pussy.
(SOFT HISSING)
Shit.
It's just a phone call.
(PHONE RINGING)
(CLOCK TICKING)
Hello.
Hey, I'm calling about my money.
EDITH: You've called
the right place, Brett.
Mrs. Cranston?
EDITH: Yes.
(BRETT CHUCKLES)
You're alive.
Holy crap.
So this is all a joke?
Wait, so you faked your death,
and now you're fucking with us?
EDITH: Fucking with you
was the last thing I wanna do.
And speaking of fucking
with you, Brett,
how's your daddy?
(SOMBER MUSIC)
What did you say?
EDITH: How's Harliss?
Where are you?
EDITH: I'm everywhere,
and that is the amazing
thing about being dead.
The things you learn.
The things you see.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
EDITH: Really?
I mean, I knew your
dad was a horrible man.
The way he beat your brother,
I can't imagine treating
a child with my likeness-
- Shut up.
Shut up.
EDITH: But you,
after his wife died,
he started hurting you,
in unimaginable ways.
I said, shut up.
EDITH: Do you remember
your favorite
nursery rhyme, Brett.
♪ Something very scary
is underneath my bed ♪
Could it be a monster
underneath my bed?
All you have to do
is stay on the call.
And?
EDITH: Check to see if
the monster is under the bed.
What bed?
BRETT: No, Zack.
There's monsters under the bed.
You can run but
you can't hide.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
How many times have I told you
about locking the goddam
door in my house, huh?
Oh, you're gonna
stand up to me now?
Why don't you show me?
Go ahead. Take your best shot.
Pathetic.
Both of ya.
Zack.
(HORSE BRAYING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Son.
(LOUD BANGING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
She wants you.
You're so sick.
(SOMBER, OMINOUS MUSIC)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
I'm not afraid.
You're scared your
little friends can hear ya?
You know why this happens?
Because you're too weak
to do anything about it.
(SOBBING)
(OMINOUS GROWLING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Have you seen this?
(CLOCK CHIMES)
Don't tell me he
actually made it.
CHRIS: I didn't hear
the back door open.
Me neither.
But...
It's your turn.
All right.
Weird or not, let's do this.
See you on the other side.
Hey.
Good luck, new fish.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(PHONE RINGING)
EDITH: Hello, Chris.
So many secrets, so much pain.
How do you handle it?
Handle what?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(SOMBER MUSIC)
I love you.
Me too.
What's wrong?
I wanna tell mom and dad.
You're not having
second thoughts, right?
No.
No, I just...
Can't we wait a little longer?
What?
Just until the
semester is over.
We've got finals and that
big trip with my mom.
She's gonna totally
flip when she finds out.
She's gonna flip?
My dad's gonna
ground me for life?
He's probably gonna
make us get married.
But you wanna do it?
After we graduate.
Look, this isn't
just about you.
We didn't plan this.
It's happening and we
have to deal with it.
Bat can we just deal with
it whenever the time is right?
Now.
Now is the right time.
I'm already showing.
What am I supposed to do?
Just wear baggy clothes
and just tell people
I'm gaining weight till
you feel comfortable
to tell your mom?
No.
Can we talk about this?
There's nothing to talk about?
I have to tell them, and if
you can't support me then...
Sarah.
Sarah, I...
I do...
(SOMBER MUSIC)
What did you fucking do?
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(GASPING HEAVILY)
(OMINOUS GROWLING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(GROWLING)
Christopher.
Christopher Michael.
Hey.
Come, hold my hand.
(SOFT MUSIC)
Listen, we don't have much time.
We've gotta hurry.
It's not over yet.
I missed you so much.
I missed you too.
The way you got in is
the way you get out.
What do you mean?
Find the phone.
I love you.
Always.
Now go.
Go now.
Find the phone.
(SOMBER MUSIC)
(PHONE RINGING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Brett.
You're alive.
What's happening?
The phone.
It's the only way out.
I think I saw it this way.
What are you talking about?
The phone is right here.
(LAUGHING)
Brett.
(LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY)
(CLOCK CHIMES)
Tonya.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(SOFT CHIMING)
(SOFT MUSIC)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SCREAMING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(TV STATIC BUZZING)
EDITH: Everything ready?
CHRIS: Yeah.
They bought it.
The contract, your
death, everything.
EDITH: Good.
Two down, one to go.
And once you take care
of the little slut,
the money will be yours
just like I promised.
Good boy.
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Tonya.
I'm right here.
Where is it, you bastard?
Well, calm down.
Where is the gun?
The only gun I see is
the one you're holding.
- Yeah, right.
- I came back for you.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Don't move.
I saw you and Edith on the TV.
You saw her?
TONYA: Yes.
On the TV?
Yeah.
And I know what you're planning.
I swear. I don't know what...
Put the gun down.
You're right.
You saw Edith, but
she's not alive.
She's something else.
What?
I know it sounds crazy.
I know this all sounds
crazy, but there's no game.
There's no money.
The call.
It's just a trap.
She tricked me.
She tricked all of us.
Where are Brett and Zack?
They're dead.
We've gotta get outta here.
They were into some
really twisted stuff.
When I made the call, it
was like I was transported.
I don't understand.
Where?
Darkest reaches of my mind.
I don't know.
It's hard to explain.
But what I saw there...
But you're still here.
You're alive.
'cause I didn't give up.
Maybe you should have.
You all...
You all took the only thing
that I cared about
in this world.
But we figured out a
way to stay in touch.
CHRIS: The phone.
Technology's a
wonderful thing.
It can bring people together
or it can tear 'em apart.
(PHONE RINGING)
Yes, dear.
Yes, I know.
The boy came back.
It's a pity really?
Yes, my love.
She wants to talk to you.
Fuck you.
Get on the phone.
(GUNSHOT BLARES)
(WACKY, DRAMATIC MUSIC)
We gotta get outta here.
The door's open.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(GASPING HEAVILY)
Dammit.
Dammit!
There's an exit
in the call room.
Go!
(LOUD BANGING)
Tonya.
No, please.
(PHONE RINGING)
Tonya.
Leave me alone.
EDITH: No.
You should have left me alone.
But you couldn't, could you?
Because you needed
someone to blame.
Shut up.
Shut up, you fucking witch.
So innocent, so pretty.
(SOFT MUSIC)
Laura.
Sit down.
A little birdie told me
today is someone's birthday.
For your special day,
I got you something special.
What is it?
(SOMBER MUSIC)
Tonya.
Why are we going this way?
It's a shortcut.
Did you see what
Mrs. Cranston gave me?
She said I was special.
Yeah. Everyone
thinks you're special.
So special.
Hey, give it back.
No.
I'll tell dad.
Tonya.
Daddy's little girl.
I hate you.
EDITH: She was his favorite
and you couldn't stand it.
Now I'm daddy's little girl.
(SOMBER MUSIC)
Hello, Tonya.
When I saw you wearing the
necklace that I gave Laura,
I knew she was dead,
and I knew it was you.
When they told us she was
missing and I was blamed,
I died inside.
The demons, they swirled
around me and I joined them.
And they took me down,
and they took me down
and they took me down.
Until nothing was left in
me but hatred and rage.
And you know what's
so interesting?
You're in the same boat.
You and your stupid
little friends,
you're all gonna suffer,
and you're gonna die violently
with your own hatred
and your own rage.
Please, leave me alone.
Oh, you don't have to worry.
You are very alone.
There's a special place in
hell for you, little girl.
Do you know what hell is?
There's a special place for you,
and it's not what
the good book says.
It is not fire and brimstone.
It's reliving your
worst nightmares
over and over and over.
(SCREAMING)
(SPOOKY DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(CHILD VOCALIZING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
Tonya.
Come play with me.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
I told you we'd be
together forever.
(SCREAMING)
Tonya.
(PHONE RINGING)
Mrs. Cranston.
What do you want?
Vengeance.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You're not sorry
about anything.
Certainly not about me.
My husband.
(LAUGHING)
You're in my world now.
(SCREAMING)
Christopher.
Sarah.
Why'd you leave me?
Why?
I was coming right back.
Liar.
(SCREAMING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(PHONE RINGING)
EDITH: Hello.
(CHILD VOCALIZING)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
(SPOOKY UPBEAT MUSIC)
(SOMBER OMINOUS MUSIC)