Hi.
John: Hey, how are you?
Alexa:
Good, how are you?
Good.
This is my wife, Alexa.
Hi, it's so nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I was just telling John
how great he's done
for the company.
And we appreciate it.
A good calculator does help,
but thank you.
What do you do?
Well, John and I have twins.
My son is the star
of the football team.
My daughter is valedictorian.
That's correct!
We have a winner!
And John, well,
clearly John is doing great.
You're a stay-at-home mom.
I always wanted to do that.
Work just got in the way.
I guess you can't do both.
John: Let's eat, huh?
You hungry?
-Mm-hmm.
-John: Good.
-Ravyn: Beau!
-Beau: Ravyn!
Ravyn: Cut it out.
Give it.
John: Both teams
struggle for the hat.
Ravyn's got it.
Beau's going for it but wait!
Dad's in the middle
for the sack.
What's on your mind?
Football!
Same as yesterday.
Dear lord, bless
our day today.
Be with Beau for his game.
And be with ravyn for
her ap Latin class.
Most of all be sure you
give my amazing wife
some quality time today.
-Amen.
See you at the game!
-See you.
-Thanks, dad.
John: How are
you this morning?
What do you think?
This pillow or this one?
The green one.
So, I've got something for you.
I saw you eye this at the store.
-Thank you!
-Can I put it on?
Yes.
Hello, may I help you?
Yes, can I exchange this,
for this one?
Perfect.
Hi.
Ravyn, honey, before I forget,
this came for you today.
-Hi, dad.
-Hey.
So glad you could make it.
Mom said you weren't
feeling well.
I haven't missed a game yet.
Mom, I got early acceptance.
I got early acceptance to mit.
-Alexa: Good, good.
-That's great, honey.
Don't throw a party yet.
You have to keep your grades up.
I'm so proud of you.
Oh, wow.
You know, grandma's right.
You worked so hard to get
to this point, but now...
Now the pressure
is really on you.
You have to maintain your
gpa to stay valedictorian.
Okay?
Alexa.
Both your kids are about
to go off to college.
I still remember
when you graduated.
It seems like just yesterday.
Pay attention.
Or you're gonna miss it.
I know.
Alexa, come here!
Alexa: Jezi!
How are you?
Announcer: And that touchdown will make the score--
I mean, how amazing
is Nathan and Beau,
together out there?
I know, I know.
Our boys are gonna take US all
the way to the championship.
Mmm, it's about time
this town had one.
Okay, so did you see margo?
No.
Yeah, she gained like 10 pounds
since Paul left her.
-What?
-Mm-hmm, it's horrible.
Oh, my goodness, honey!
-Your necklace is gorgeous.
-Shh!
-Hi, John.
-Hey, baby.
John: Hi, guys.
Shh, don't tell John.
I changed the one he
gave me, for this one.
Oh, good choice.
It's stunning and it's
our little secret.
But to be honest, I
don't like this vest.
Really?
I don't know what's going on.
It looks like you borrowed
it from your mother.
-Really?
-Just being honest.
-But i-
-i gotta go!
Let's get
coffee this week, honey!
-Bye!
-Okay, bye!
Hey, coming to the party?
I have to go home and
finish my study cards.
Come on, it'll be fun.
You don't drink.
That's why it's fun.
Weirdo.
-Have fun!
-Thanks, see ya.
Bye.
Nice game, Beau.
Beau: Thanks, thanks
it was a long one.
How about some
ice cream, my treat.
Grandma: I'm cold and
you're not feeling real well.
Let's go home.
Grandpa: Maybe next time.
John: I'm in,
how about you guys?
-Ravyn: Yeah.
-John: Yeah?
I'd love to, but I
gotta join the team.
What's up Taylors?
John: Hey, Nathan.
What's up guys?
I'll see you guys
at home, alright?
John: Alright, be safe!
Ravyn: Thank you.
John: Alexa!
You coming?
Beau: You're positive
that their parents
are not gonna be here, right?
I'm serious.
-I'm nervous!
-They are in Europe.
They're not gonna be here.
Alright, alright dude.
He has the house to himself.
I trust you, I trust you.
They've got beer
here, don't they?
We wouldn't be here, guys,
if there was no beer.
Ladies and gentlemen!
The party has arrived.
-Hey Beau!
-Beau, you are awesome.
You were amazing at the game.
Here you go.
Alexa: Thank you.
John: Oh, sorry.
Hi, mom.
What?
Oh, no.
John: Honey, what's wrong?
Ravyn, grab her bag.
Got it.
John: Alexa, what's
going on, what's wrong?
Alexa: Just go.
I don't know where I'm going.
Dad, he's at Saint Mary's.
He had a heart attack.
Call Beau.
Dude, I challenge you.
Yeah, what do you
challenge me to?
I challenge you to
an age-old contest.
Dude, this guy is
challenging me to a contest!
Who does he think he is, huh?
I can't get through.
Hey, are you coming?
Yes, is Beau there?
He's kinda busy right now.
Tell Beau we're coming.
Okay, hun, we gotta get Beau.
Then we'll go straight
to your dad, okay?
Alexa, honey?
Girl: Cops!
Officer: Sheriff's
office, stop, stop!
Over here.
ID's gentlemen.
Turn around.
Mom?
Grandma: Not
like that, ravyn.
Cut it length-wise.
Keep it trim and unison.
Presentation is everything.
It's not what's on the plate.
It's how it looks on the plate.
And you know, maybe you should
have had your hair trimmed.
You're beautiful,
if you'd only try.
Can I carry something
into the dining room?
Really wish your
mother would have
had you work more
in the kitchen.
Ravyn, will you help me?
Don't take it personally.
She's going through
a rough time.
It's always better to lift
people up than cut them down.
That's a nice photo.
I really miss him.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Alexa, what can I do for you?
Nothing, I have
it under control.
Here, why don't
you let me do this.
No I got it.
-I think--
-i got it!
It's okay.
No, it's not okay.
It's all wrong.
It should look different.
It should be different.
Jael: I know.
Oh, no, no, no.
Honey, no, excuse me.
Your mascara's gonna run.
Come here, let me look at you.
Okay, you don't wanna
be seen like this.
What did you say to my friend?
Don't hide your grief.
You should if it makes
your face fall off.
It's my fault we didn't make
it to the hospital in time.
I should've got arrested too.
Why didn't you?
Well, they don't put
their star player in jail.
You're lucky.
-Jael: Hi.
-Hi, so sorry I'm late.
No problem, how are you?
I'm fine.
Good, do you want some coffee?
-Please.
-Okay.
Hi.
Jessica: How are you?
Fine.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Alexa: Thank you.
Jael: There you go.
-Alexa: Thank you.
-Jael: Sure.
I know we all loved, loved,
loved our last study.
And I am so excited to
introduce our newest project.
This time we get to be artists.
I'm a terrible drawer.
Me too, I haven't colored
since the second grade,
when my art teacher
told me I stunk.
-Aww.
-Kelly: Yeah.
Well, how many times in life
do we question
what god is doing?
Exactly.
There are many
people in the Bible,
like Elijah,
who couldn't see what
god was doing either.
God's plans for US don't always
look like we think they should.
But the good news is,
questioning doesn't mean that
we failed as his followers.
In your life,
who would you say that
you neglect the most?
My husband.
He works so hard and I'm not
always understanding to him.
Kelly: My son's goldfish.
Jessica: That's funny.
I would be willing to
bet, it's probably you.
That's why this is different.
We're gonna get to
learn about ourselves.
And we're gonna see how
god protects and provides
for our emotional health.
So, if you'll turn to page nine,
our first activity
is called who am I.
The directions say,
using colors, images, and words,
express how you're
feeling today.
Okay?
Alright.
Have any of you
ever felt cursed?
The red in my drawing represents
frustration and anger.
I have struggled my entire life
with not knowing
who my real dad is.
And sometimes, I
wonder where god is.
And my drawing has
blocks on its feet.
Because I feel stuck.
My family is well-off,
and I have everything I
need and nothing I want.
The problem is, I can't
figure out what it is I want.
Well, god sent
Elijah on an adventure,
that would eventually
change him.
And hopefully that's
what this will do for US.
Before next week,
you'll want to read
first kings, 17 through 19.
Okay?
-Thanks ladies.
-Ladies: Thank you.
Alexa: Was just
looking at your drawing.
That's beautiful.
Alexa: Thank you.
Jael:
I'll call you this week.
Okay?
-Bye, Kelly.
-Kelly: Thank you.
Jael: Good to see you.
Coach z: Oh, hello ravyn.
I was just thinking about
you and your family.
How you doing?
Fine, thanks.
Actually I just wanna
check my ranking.
Again?
Ravyn, we just checked
it two weeks ago.
I thought you might
wanna talk about--
can you just check
it again, please?
Okay, have a seat.
How's your day so far?
Ravyn: Okay.
Alright, well as of today,
you are number two.
What?
Coach z: Ravyn, salutatorian
is a wonderful achievement.
You're number two,
out of 220 kids.
Between me and you,
Beau's also two.
A hundred and two.
But he's number
one on your team.
You okay?
It's just this stupid class
is bringing my gpa down.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
I can help you study.
It's not even like I'm ever
gonna use Latin, in my life.
B+ is not the
end of the world.
It would be for me.
I have a b+.
Teacher: Alright
everybody, settle down.
Exams are coming up.
And next class you'll all
get your study guides.
This midterm exam
will be comprehensive
of everything this semester.
It's worth 25 percent
of your final grade.
Nathan: I overheard coach
talking on the phone yesterday.
Oh, what about, cliff?
Cliff is an idiot.
All the running we do,
you'd think he'd be
able to outrun a cop.
But he's off the team.
What, did he quit?
He didn't wanna
sit on the bench,
but he was a
bench-warmer anyway,
so I don't really get it.
So what'd you hear
coach talking about?
Coach wants to get
some college scouts
out to one of our games.
Really, when?
Yeah, I don't know which one.
Well, we gotta
play good out there.
Don't mess this up for me.
Teacher: Ravyn, could
you come here for a second?
Would you make copies of
the study guide for me?
Beau: That's quite a load.
Here, let me help you out.
Beau, move that a
little bit to the left.
No, no, maybe a quarter
of an inch to the right.
Here, try this one.
- Alexa: John?
- John: Yeah?
I can't take this.
Okay, alright, alright.
She is making me crazy.
I know.
It wasn't supposed
to be like this.
I'm supposed to
move my kids out,
before moving in my mother.
She's taking over my house.
I know, babe, I know.
Look, this is how
she's dealing with it.
It's the only thing
she can control.
We've got to talk
about Beau's drinking.
Wait, what drinking?
The other night when we picked
him up, he'd been drinking.
How do you know?
Alexa, trust me,
he smelled like it.
He was drunk.
What's there to talk about?
Our responsibility as parents?
Beau's responsibility?
We all signed that
athletic code.
John, look around you.
Look at this mess.
I can't deal with
anything else right now.
I can't.
Organizing those boxes,
is not as important
as your family.
Look, I've been
praying about this.
Hi, honey.
Hi!
I made you a casserole.
I just know how hard can
be in times like these.
So I made you my favorite,
cheese and broccoli.
How's it going in there?
Oh, I'm sure it's
just a crazy time.
It sounds like a
lot of commotion.
Are you reorganizing?
Really, how are you?
Hi, jezi!
Come in and see our
new arrangement.
I'd love to.
We're not done,
so maybe later.
Oh, I want her opinion.
Thank you for the
casserole, jezi.
Nice chat!
Oh, I'll come back later.
No need.
Grandma: Well, I
think this household
could use some organizing.
If you wanna leave,
and take your statues with you,
I'm okay with that.
Excuse me.
Who wants to say grace?
You okay?
Fine.
Jael: So if you
had a chance to read
first kings this week,
then you know that
god protected Elijah
from a lot of people.
In your workbooks,
you'll see that
you have three
concentric circles.
The center circle
is for your closest
and safest relationships.
The second is for
people who know you,
but not your most
intimate details.
And then the third
is for acquaintances.
The first time I
did this exercise,
I had a tenancy to try to
lump everyone into the center.
I wasn't recognizing that
there were a lot of
people in my life
that weren't treating me well.
And it had been that
way for so long,
I wasn't really noticing.
So this is a really good
way for US to recognize
who and when to let someone
close to our hearts.
Is anyone in the wrong place?
If so, use an arrow
and move that person
closer to or further
away from your heart.
Is anyone missing?
I think i'm
valuing my friend's opinions
more than my family.
I have a few friends who
don't like my husband
and they keep reinforcing
negatives about him.
I moved them out of
the inner circle,
to the second ring.
I so get you.
The light just went on.
I'm realizing that I value
what other moms think of me,
more than what my family thinks.
Same here.
Jael: Oh, I almost forgot.
This is a game that goes
along with our study.
It's wonderful.
It's really helped my
family to open up and share.
I'd love for you
to all try it out.
Alexa would you like
to take it home first?
Oh, well...
My family doesn't really
have a problem communicating.
-Jessica: Take it!
-It'll be fun.
Jessica: Yeah, it's a game.
It's really something
for everyone.
Beau: Yeah, come on in.
Alexa: Hi.
Hey mom, what's up?
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm just
watching the predators.
Gotta figure out a
way to beat them.
Impressive.
I didn't know how much
preparation went into your game.
Can you pause that?
Yeah, what's up?
Well, they were
going in for the kick,
but they made a touchdown.
Oh, yeah, I know.
Okay, so this is called
a two point conversion.
Instead of lining
up for the kicker,
you've got the center
and the quarterback.
He gets the snap, runs
back to the back field,
cuts off to the right
field, throws the football,
is waiting for the
receiver in the end zone.
Boom, two points instead of one.
It's genius.
You are so smart.
Grandpa gave you this.
Yeah, he did.
Everything I know, I
learned from that guy.
-Alrighty...
-Okay.
I'll see you at dinner.
Okay, see ya.
Now is not really a good time.
It's never gonna
be a good time.
I can't believe we
have paper napkins.
What happened to the cloth
ones I gave you for Christmas?
I have a sharing game.
Would anyone like to play?
That's a good idea.
I think I'm a little
old to play games.
I love puzzle games.
That's because you are
a smart, studious kid.
Yeah, she does
have all the answers.
Grandma: I love games.
Alexa, do you remember
when we played games,
when you were younger
and I always won?
Well, I'm going to win today.
I don't think anybody wins.
I'll start.
What is the hardest thing that
has happened in your life?
We have to answer
the card we were dealt.
I don't like the question.
You know I don't
think I need a card,
to tell me that
I'm feeling anxious
about winning the championship.
Nonsense, Beau.
You're a winner, you're
a winner just like me.
Beau, about the game.
Whoever has the
card, has the floor.
Okay.
Like I was saying...
-One second.
-Beau, wait.
-Nate's here, I gotta go.
-Beau!
We're not done talking...
We've gotta deal with this.
Remember when our
biggest parenting dilemma
was how much Saturday morning
cartoons he could watch?
John, he's a good kid.
I can't turn him in.
There are other football
players at the party.
We have to teach him to
do the right things, now.
I think he dodged a bullet
when he didn't get caught.
Really?
Can't we just leave it alone?
Can we pray about this?
Grandma: Give it to me!
Guys, give it to
me, give it to me!
Beau, do something.
Oh, come on, grandma.
We're football players, we
gotta practice sometime.
Boys: Whoa!
Uh-oh.
What?
Can I come in?
Mom, I'm busy studying.
What do you need?
I just wanted to say hi.
Why?
Can't a mom say
hi to her daughter?
That would be a first.
Did you know that
your name means
dark-haired wise one?
I hope that's on the test.
What are you studying?
Ap Latin, it's impossible.
Really, even for you?
You're very intelligent,
you're valedictorian.
Mom.
Can you please
just let me study?
Ravyn...
What's going on?
I'm just really stressed out.
What's the sudden
interest in my life?
I am interested.
Really, because
you didn't even
seem to notice me at
grandpa's funeral.
Jael cared more about
me than you did,
and I don't even know her.
Do you want to
talk about it now?
I just don't have
time for anything.
Jessica: I never thought
of god as the refresher.
That's what I mean.
The refresher, I
really like that.
Jessica: That's what I need.
My in-laws have been
in my house for a week.
I'm exhausted.
I can't handle my
in-laws at sunday dinner,
let alone a week.
Yesterday, I
yelled at my husband,
for leaving his
dishes in the sink.
That's nothing, my husband
leaves his socks everywhere.
Under seat cushions.
Why would he leave his
socks under a cushion?
So that you can clean it up.
Jessica: Well,
he had just finished
a 24 hour shift at the hospital.
The point is, I need
to pray for Patience.
Be careful, when
you pray for Patience,
god gives you more
opportunity to practice.
That means more dishes.
And socks.
Peace, I meant peace.
So god can refresh me.
Well, then we will
pray for peace for you.
Jessica: What did you write?
I highlighted almighty,
majesty, and father.
That's a very eloquent
way to describe god.
Anything else?
I don't know
what that would be.
Oh, Alexa, I just feel like
you have god in
such a small box.
You're making me feel
like I'm not good enough.
Like my answers
aren't good enough.
Sorry, I'm not
as perfect as you.
Not everybody has all
the answers all the time.
There is no right answer,
it's a personal thing.
Exactly.
Everything's fine, it's fine.
We caught Beau
drinking at a party.
He wasn't arrested but
now my husband doesn't think
he should get away with it.
What are people gonna think?
I don't want to
ruin my reputation.
Alexa, how does
Beau feel about this?
He doesn't even know
we're talking about it.
Hey, you okay?
We have to do the
right thing about Beau.
Like right now?
Not right now, now but...
I've been thinking.
I agree with you.
John: The student
must refrain
from socially
unacceptable behavior,
that is discrediting in nature
to the ideals, principles,
and standards of the
community and school.
Such activities would
include, but are not limited
to theft, burglary,
assault, battery,
vandalism, possession
or use of a weapon,
or being under the influence of,
and or possession of alcohol.
I was really hoping
that wasn't in there.
Consequences for violating
the code of conduct
shall result in
immediate suspension
from competitive activities
for the next 25 percent
of the total number of
competitions scheduled.
John, that's
the rest of the season.
Beau: What's the
rest of the season?
Nothing, Beau, don't
ruin your appetite.
Beau: I'm a football player.
That's pretty much impossible.
Yeah, about that.
Do you remember when we
picked you up at the party?
What, the night grandpa died?
The night we
caught you drinking.
Yeah, it was a party,
what's the big deal?
It was going against
the code of conduct.
I think it's a really big deal.
What's a big deal?
Nothing, ravyn, don't
ruin your appetite.
What's the big deal?
-There isn't one.
-Yes there is.
Did someone do
something wrong?
-Beau: No.
-Alexa: Yes.
Yes.
I haven't even opened it.
Opened what?
This.
Good, I'm hungry.
Why am I even cooking?
Well, I'm glad this is over.
Hey, no, we're not finished.
Your mom and I
believe you have to
honor that code of conduct.
We all signed it.
You have to turn yourself in.
Well, why?
I mean, everybody
drinks all the time.
I know, that's why we've
been struggling with this.
Look, if you believe in god,
then you have to tell the truth.
Well, we've never
done that before.
We do now.
This is stupid.
What?
Do you know what integrity is?
Yes, it's doing
the right thing.
It's not just that.
It's doing the right thing
when nobody's watching you.
God is always watching.
I want our family
to have integrity,
where our words and
our actions match up.
You serious?
This is so embarrassing.
Being chauffeured
around by my mom.
I can't believe that
you took my car away.
You know, they can't
win without me.
Everyone will hate me.
They'll know it was you,
who made me tell them.
You know what, you
can't make me tell them.
You're absolutely
right, I can't.
I know.
But I can go in
there and tell them.
It's your choice.
Coach z: Hey, Beau.
Cover my roots, my gray
is showing more and more.
We just colored it.
It's dry and brittle and i'm
afraid it's gonna fall out.
My son just called me.
Beau Taylor turned himself
in for drinking at a party.
Alexa is getting
so self-righteous.
I mean, everybody knows
that teenagers drink.
Do you wanna know what I think?
I think she made him do it.
I would never do that to my son.
I'm sure he drinks, you know.
But as long as he's safe,
and doesn't get
caught by the police,
I'm fine with it.
I'm sorry, I just can't
color your hair, it's so dry.
Just do it!
Who does she think she is?
Without Beau, we can't win
the championship this year.
How could she do this to me?
I thought that
she was my friend.
Obviously, she is not.
Aren't you gonna change?
I don't even get to practice.
Alexa: Beau, Beau?
Beau!
Beau, get back in the car!
Leave me alone.
What are you doing?
I'm driving you home.
You're just
embarrassing yourself.
I don't care.
It's okay to be angry.
We can even be angry at god.
Good, because I am.
Oh, honey, this must
be so hard for you.
It is.
You're right.
Alexa, if you would
have parented them,
like I told you when they
were three years old,
you wouldn't be experiencing
these behavioral problems at 17.
What are you
doing to my kitchen?
I'm organizing.
Nothing's in the right place
and it's a mess.
Beau's angry.
But it's okay.
I don't blame him.
But it's not an excuse
to treat you poorly.
But you did just ruin
his sports career.
John: Honey?
Come back to bed.
I feel like we made
a horrible mistake.
Well, we didn't.
We did the right thing.
I'm glad my father's
not here to see this.
It would have broken his heart.
Your father would
have been proud.
He was the kind of
parent that I wanted to be.
I feel like my heart
is gonna break.
Let it break.
Hey, how you doing?
Well, mom and dad
are mad at me.
The team hates me.
I can't play football
my senior year.
Things are awesome.
Sorry, Beau.
I'm gonna go home and study.
I'm gonna go home too.
What about practice?
I'm sure the bench
won't miss me.
So you
wanna walk with me?
Yeah, you're
my only friend now.
Plus, I think we
should talk about you.
I should've known.
Beau: What are you
doing cheating, ravyn?
I haven't read it.
Then why do you still have it?
You don't understand
the pressure I'm under.
But it's good to
be under pressure.
It means you're
still in the game.
I haven't done anything wrong.
You should keep it that way.
I don't know how I'm gonna
sit on the bench,
for the rest of the season.
You know what?
You wanna go play some
catch or what, huh?
Let's do it.
I see some green.
-Jael: Hi.
-Hi.
Sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
I'm sorry I snapped
at you the other day.
I'm just going through
a lot right now.
And I know that's not an excuse.
But I am really sorry, jael.
I'm not perfect, Alexa.
I am far from perfect.
I just wanted to create a
safe space for women to share.
I know and I love our group.
It's just my life
is falling apart.
And...
I took it out on you, I'm sorry.
I know.
I really admired what
you did with Beau.
That was a very
brave thing to do.
You must be very
proud of your son.
I am.
Thank you.
Are we okay?
Yes, of course.
Set, hut!
He's open, he's
open, he's open!
Hit him, hit him, throw it!
Nathan...
The guy in the same
color Jersey...
Why'd you miss
practice yesterday?
You sick?
Nope.
If it happens again,
you're off the team.
It's not my call.
Feel like i'm
already off, coach.
No, no you are still
a part of this team.
All the guys on
the team hate me,
for something that
they're all guilty of.
You still have to
take responsibility
for yourself, son.
2 Samuel 12:7 says
"you're the man".
That's what Nathan the
prophet said to David.
David made a lot of bad choices.
And when he got caught,
he was accused of being the man.
You got caught, Beau.
And there are consequences.
Now you can either let those
consequences define you,
or you can let god define you.
I don't know how
to do that, coach.
Yeah, you do.
Just trust that he'll work
it all out for your good.
Alright, let me ask you this.
When the football's snapped,
what's your job?
Make that catch and score.
There you go.
But, now you don't always
know you're gonna get a pass.
Right, I guess the football's
either there or it isn't.
But if you'd watch the
quarterback, you'd know.
Yeah but, if I'm watching him,
I can't find my Mark.
Son, the quarterback
sees the whole field.
He knows where the
defense will intercept it.
Or he knows where the
pass will be complete.
That's his job.
Your job's just to run the play.
You understand what
I'm trying to tell you?
I'm talking about god, son.
Have a little faith in him.
He's been doing
this a long time.
Have a little faith in him.
Jimmy, Jimmy, the game's on
the field not in the stands!
Let's go, get it together!
Alright.
Nice job, Alexa, way to
break up the dream team.
Alexa: It's okay, Nathan!
You're doing great,
just settle down!
Oh, you're just so much better
than the rest of US aren't you?
Come on, boys, we got this.
Come on, Nate, you got this.
Come on, buddy.
You've got this!
Coach z: Well, that's
it, get them together.
Hey, babe.
Sorry I missed dinner.
It's okay.
Work's been crazy with
that merger coming up.
I just hate missing the games.
Mmm.
John?
Yeah?
Never mind.
Right?
Good play, bud!
Jezi: We already
have a coach!
Beau should be
out there playing.
Honey, you gotta stop,
these are our friends.
Come on 20.
Trust me on this, it works
every time, every time!
Let's go boys!
Alright, let's go, pick it up!
If you have something to say,
you can say it to my face!
Teacher: Students, as
I previously explained,
this exam will be
weighted as 25 percent
of your final term grade.
So read the questions
thoroughly, take your time.
Okay, everyone grab
your pencils and begin.
Mom?
Walt would want me to go.
Coach z: Last night I
wrote out this big speech,
about what I was
gonna say to you boys.
Then I thought, you know what?
They understand football, you
understand the x's and o's.
What I wanna talk to
you about today is
that I'm proud of each
and every one of you.
Not for what you've
achieved on the field,
but what you have
achieved off the field.
You've become a
family, become a team.
When we first started this,
we were just individuals.
We've learned to
work with each other.
When your brother gets down,
you picked him up.
And I'm really proud of that.
Now this is a big day for US.
A big day for this town.
We haven't had a championship
here in well over six years.
I'd like to win that thing.
But if we don't,
I want you to know that I'll be
just as proud of you,
as if you hadn't.
So before you go
out on that field,
I don't want you
to pray for a win.
I want you to pray that
your friends stay safe,
that the other team stays safe.
And if you play like a family,
like the team you've become,
nobody's gonna stop you.
Are you with me?
Everybody go get dressed out.
See Donnie for
your game jerseys,
and I'll see you
out on the field.
There's something I
gotta tell you, son.
Turns out that the district
doesn't consider a
championship game
part of the regular season.
And since you fulfilled
your obligation,
I guess you're gonna need that.
What's this?
It's our new team jerseys.
You're playing tonight, son.
No way.
Oh, alright, alright,
now go get dressed,
cause you'll look silly
playing in your underwear.
Announcer: Welcome
to Carson park.
For the championship
game between
the crush and the predators.
It's going to be
an exciting game.
Mom, mom, it's Beau!
Beau's on the field!
Don't mess this
up for me, man.
Alright, let's go,
everybody hustle up, let's go!
Didn't need Beau to get here.
We certainly don't need him now.
Girl: Coach, get
him out of there!
Yeah, he's ruining it!
Ladies, settle down with that.
Peter, they're right.
He is ruining it.
Dude, you were more
helpful on the bench.
Announcer: And the
extra point is good,
making it 7-0, predators.
Alright men, let's go!
Wake up out there now!
Use your head, think.
Huddle, huddle, huddle!
Alright guys,
Texas stack, 85-58.
I'll be watching
for you deep, okay?
Ready, break!
Let's go guys!
Announcer: That's
second down for the crush.
And the predators
team in good form.
Announcer: Third down.
The crush has a chance
to get that third down,
they desperately need.
They're not passing the ball.
They will.
Announcer: So far today,
it's just not crush's ball.
Set, hut!
Girls: Come on!
He can get open
but he can't catch.
I know, this is so unfair.
He really shouldn't
even be playing.
I mean, my son got US here
and he shouldn't have to
share the field with Beau.
Jezi...
You're right.
You're so right,
he did get US here.
You think that you are so
high and mighty,
don't you Alexa?
Well, you know what?
I can tell the truth too.
Honestly, I thought
it was horrible,
the day that you
told me that you
returned John's necklace
for something better.
What about the necklace?
Jezi: Oh, wait,
you didn't tell him?
You know what that makes you?
It makes you a hypocrite.
What's she talking about?
She exchanged your necklace
for something better.
Jezi, no she didn't, okay?
It's right here.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell you,
I was embarrassed.
You've been hiding
this the whole time?
See, she's a hypocrite.
Jezi, hush up.
Everyone can see your roots.
They're brittle and
frosty and falling out.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
There was just never
the right time.
Nothing's good enough for you.
I don't wanna be
that way anymore.
I don't.
I'm sorry.
I know.
Beau, Beau!
I know I gotta
settle down out there.
Listen, I know it wasn't your
choice to turn yourself in.
But I'm glad it happened.
I didn't cheat because
of your example.
You're back in the game.
Use the pressure to win.
Alright.
Way to go, that's it!
Come on, defense!
Here we go, here we go.
Alright, alright, here we go.
Yes, alright, nice
play, nice play!
Announcer: 14-7 predators.
It's a deep hail Mary pass.
And it's complete!
45 yard completion.
It's up, he's in the
air and it's good!
Oh, my goodness, it's good!
That's touchdown crush!
That's it, that's
how it's done.
Alright, Nathan, one!
Let's go! Go on in after him.
Let's go.
Announcer: 14-13 predators.
If the crush can make
this extra point,
it's a tie game and we're
going into overtime.
Hey, hey.
-Come here man.
-What's up?
Beau: You gotta
call a timeout.
I've got a play that's
gonna help US win this game.
You gotta have faith in me, bro.
Alright, alright.
Timeout!
What are they doing?
Timeout, timeout!
What is going on out there?
I've got an idea.
A play that we can win with.
We're gonna fake
the extra point,
and we're gonna go in for
the two point conversion.
No, no, we're gonna
kick the extra point,
tie it up, and win
it in overtime.
Nathan: No, coach.
Beau's right on this one.
We can do this,.
This is our time.
What do you say?
Your call.
Alright then.
Bring me a championship.
That's a two point conversion.
What?
Beau. Look, he's out there.
He's a lineman.
They're going for a
two point conversion.
Here we go.
Hut!
-You heard it?
-Of course.
Teacher: John, Alexa!
Alexa: Hi.
You guys should be so proud.
We are, Beau did
awesome, didn't he?
I meant ravyn.
There was a lot to
know on that final.
You earned the highest
grade in the class.
Sweetie!
Isn't my ravyn brilliant?
Thanks, have a great night.
Hey, Beau. Coach is
buying pizza. You coming?
Yeah, let's go, I'm starving!
Nah, maybe next time, guys.
Boy: All right. That's cool.
Hi, good morning. How are you?
Good, how may I help you?
Good. I was wondering
if I could return this.
Is that okay?
I think I can
help you with that.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Grandma: Thank you.
Jael: You're welcome.
This has been an
incredible study.
The Elijah project was
really hard for me,
but incredibly rewarding.
Do any of you have a highlight
from your journey that
you'd like to share?
I would.
Jael: Yes, please.
I used to love to control
the world around me,
and the people in it.
But I never enjoyed anything,
because there was
always something else
that needed to be improved.
There was always
something else to perfect.
Then I discovered the need
for god, truth teacher.
And I realized...
...that life is messy.
And I don't have to
keep everything so tidy.
The crazy thing is,
the thing that I was
the most afraid of,
ended up making me feel free.
I'm just trusting in god.
And just breathing.
I can see the change.
I wanna share
something with you.
You know, in life you
can have all the answers,
and not really know the problem.
I thought each milestone,
accomplishment,
like getting married,
having you,
would fill me up.
I'm learning that god created
me just to be his child.
And that is enough.
I wish-- I wish someone would
have shared that with me,
when I was your age.
Dear god, this has
been a tough year on US.
Thank you for working all
things together for our good.
And we continue to trust in you.
In Jesus' name, amen.
All: Amen.
Let's eat!