[ Thunder Rumbling ]
[ Wind Whistling ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Girl ] Just a minute!
[ Boy ] Hurry up in there!
[ Girl ] I am. [ Boy ] You've
been in there for a half hour.
[ Girl ] I have not.
[ Woman ] Come on, you two. Dinner's ready.
[ Man ] Hey, Steve, check the windows
up there. Make sure they're shut.
[ Steve ] Dad, Carrie's
hoggin' the bathroom again.
[ Woman ] Steve,
check the windows and come on down.
[ Steve ] In a minute.
[ Man ] Hurry up, you two.
[ Woman ]
Honey.
[ Boy ] Go!
[ Overlapping Shouts ]
Come on. Come on.
Get up! Get up!
[ Shouting Continues ]
[ Man ] Yeah. [ Man #2 ] All right.
All right. Good game. Good game.
You coming next week?
We'll see you.
Hey, you're on my towel.
Hey.
Oh, I'm... I'm sorry.
Here.
What's the matter?
Hello?
[ Woman ] State lotto.
Hi. Is it true that you can't collect on a
winning lotto ticket if you're a minor?
[ Woman ] That's correct, sir.
You must be 18 years of age to play.
I see. And can you tell me...
if 7-11-13-16-18 is really
a winning number?
[ Filtered Female Voice ]
One moment, please.
Uh, yes, sir. That's right.
You've won $100. You can come down to...
2211 West...
[ Static ]
[ Interference Continues,
Stops ]
- That's 2211 West Salem.
- Thank you.
[ Receiver Clanks ]
Yes.
Well, you're right.
Here you go.
You know,
ever since my mom died,
you know, I feel like I'm
not pulling my own weight.
Today I'm bringing home
the groceries.
- Hey, 50 bucks is 50 bucks, right?
- Yeah.
- Josh? - Mom.
- Huh?
Dad's gonna be so happy
to see you.
I lost you, Josh.
Somewhere along the way, I lost you.
I don't know how.
- It wasn't like this when Daddy was still around.
- [ Groans ]
I remember when your saying that
used to make me feel guilty...
and dissolve
like a bowl of Jell-O.
Well, you'd better find some new routines,
champ, 'cause I got news for you.
Even when your father
was around, he wasn't around.
- Because he was bored, like me.
- Because he was 13 years old, like you.
- Stop sign, Ma.
- What?
- Stop sign!
- [ Brakes Screech ] - [ Horn Honks ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
[ Thunderclap On TV ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Engine Starts ]
[ Man ]
Hi. Could I help you?
[ Woman ] I'm looking for
a gift for my boss, Frank.
What's that called, Josh?
Desktop software.
Right. I work around computers all day.
I'll never understand 'em.
- This guy, my boss, he's very, um...
- Anal.
Organized.
We've got just the thing.
The Paper Warrior. Designed by anal
retentives for anal retentives.
No kidding.
Yeah. And then...
for your address book function, you
just scan the entries right in.
- You got an address book on ya?
- Oh, sure.
Oh, you might wanna consider
one of these for yourself.
Man, this is cool.
What is it?
- Yo, you got your printer cable...
- Don't touch that.
[ Electrical Arcing ]
You'll get a shock.
Chill, homey.
[ Whirring ] Just draw from
top to bottom across the page.
Hey, Josh, come over here
and take a look at this.
[ Computer Tabulating ]
[ Beeping ]
- [ Woman ] That's great.
- And you just repeat the procedure for each page.
It's perfect.
I'll take it.
Uh, Mom, I'm gonna
go wait in the car, okay?
Okay.
Thanks.
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Grunting ]
Phil Stewart? Bram Walker, your new
systems manager, reporting for duty.
- You're late.
- I'm bad with maps.
I hope your computers
are less complicated.
- Joke.
- I have no sense of humor.
That's the first thing people notice about
me. And you're drippin' all over my rug.
Good eye. Harvard man?
No. No. Ohio Tech,
same as you.
No shit?
I can't place you.
Well, you know, I'm not surprised, because
while you were training on mainframes...
and smashing atoms
in the particle accelerator,
the rest of us were pretty much
pullin' our puds.
And now I'm your boss.
God's been good to me.
You know something, Walker?
Just between you and me... I know some people
think you're some kind of computer hero...
because of that virus shit
you pulled over at the I.R.S.,
but I ain't one of 'em.
- I didn't go to jail.
- No, no. You came here.
Around here, no one's gonna treat
you like a damn Robin Hood.
I like you too, Phil, but I make
it a rule never to date coworkers.
[ Chuckling ] Oh, man.
So, Phil, what's your core business?
You know, um, mailing lists.
What kind of mailing lists?
This stuff pisses off
more people than Howard Stern.
Look, I gotta go. You be back here
tomorrow morning, 8:30 sharp. And, Walker,
try to find somethin'
respectable to wear, will you?
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Sniffing ]
- Karl, what are you doin'?
- Um,
the woman who, um, bought
that Paper Warrior today,
she, um, forgot her address
book, so I was thinkin'...
maybe I'd go down there
and return it.
How'd I get lucky enough to find you?
That is a terrific gesture, Karl.
It'd be a real pleasure.
And you're all alone. No one
to share the burden with.
No one to curl up to at night, who'll
hold you and make everything okay.
- You should feel good about yourself.
- I did until two minutes ago.
You should expose yourself to social
situations. You're still a beautiful w...
Not that it's not great to see you,
Mom, but did you drop by for a reason?
I went shopping.
I bought Josh some pants that actually fit.
- He'll never wear them.
- [ Thunderclap ]
[ Police Radio Chatter ]
[ Engine Accelerating ]
Axl?
[ Whimpering ]
[ Grandmother ] Oh, Axl,
I have something for you too.
[ Woman ] Oh, Mom.
[ Whines ]
How is Bill?
I don't know.
And in the future,
would you please refer
to him as "that schmuck."
Any man who turns his back on
his own son... Not now, Mom.
Josh is fine.
[ Stereo ] ♪ Don't call me nigga ♪
♪ Whitey, whitey ♪
I can tell.
[ Horns Honking ]
[ Honking Continues ]
[ Truck Horn Honking ]
[ Honking ]
[ Laughing Maniacally ]
[ Continues Laughing ]
[ Rescuer #1 ] Is he okay? [ Rescuer #2
] Yeah. All right. Let's get him out.
Okay.
All right. We'll give you a hand.
Let's get him out of there.
Is he alone?
Come on. Move it. Move it.
[ Police Radio Chatter,
Indistinct ]
[ Man Talking, Muffled ]
[ Exaggerated Breathing ]
[ Man Shouting, Indistinct ]
[ Nurse ] What do we got?
[ EMT ] I don't know.
[ Nurse ] Get him to ER, through
the double doors. Is he stable?
[ Woman Over P.A.,
Indistinct ]
[ Labored Breathing ]
[ Man ] Patient has massive bruising
on the left side of the body.
Apply the protocols now, please.
Scan the head parameters
and perform a brain scan.
Locate any swelling or hemorrhaging in
the brain stem and brain parameters.
Proceed to the cervical spine region and scan
for compression of any damaged vertebrae.
Five seconds to total scan.
- Scan's complete.
- [ Static ]
[ Thunderclap ]
- [ Static Continues ]
- Shit.
What is it?
This storm keeps surging the power.
[ Electrical Arcing ]
- [ Grunting ]
- [ Rapid Beeping ]
- We're losing him.
- [ Continuous Tone ]
[ Nurse ]
He's dying. Let's get him.
[ Continuous Tone ]
Check his vitals.
[ Echoing ] He's gone.
Notify next of kin.
[ Electrical Arcing ]
[ Feedback ]
[ Arcing Continues ]
Where the hell did that go?
♪ Sittin' back thinkin' about what to do ♪
♪ Boy, I'm thinkin' 'bout callin' you ♪
♪ It's in my nature ♪
♪ Ooh, my temperature starts to rise ♪
♪ And that's no surprise ♪
♪ It's in my nature ♪
Ma.
What?
You probably just
wiped out my new program.
You never put computer disks
near a magnet.
Sorry. Oh, honey, don't
drink Coke for breakfast.
Hmm. I forgot
the cargo files.
[ Girl ]
Recycling!
♪ Can you feel it ♪
♪ The temperature's risin' ♪
♪ In the winter months you go into hiding ♪
♪ But spring is next then
summer, then fall ♪
♪ Yo, man I can't wait until tomorrow ♪
♪ Yo, Robbie G. ♪
♪ Yo, what's up, Mr. Lee ♪
♪ Save me a C-U-T-I-E ♪
♪ So let's get it straight ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm gonna ♪ ♪ tell the world,
if there's ♪ ♪ one thing I like the most ♪
♪ I like the girls ♪
♪ We like the girls ♪
♪ We like the girls Carol. ♪
Hey, Josh.
You know,
was your daddy a thief,
'cause he took the stars from the
heavens and put 'em in your eyes.
Thanks.
No, serious, Carol, baby, you're so fine.
You know, I've been thinkin'...
thinkin' that we should...
I'm kind of busy
right now, Josh.
Yeah, well, uh, me too.
So, what do you say?
Friday night, you and me?
It's gonna be large.
Hi, Carol.
Hi, Mrs. Munroe.
- Bye, sweetheart.
- Mom! Dang.
What the hell
could've done this?
Must've been a power surge
caused by last night's storm.
Wiped out
the whole password file.
And what? You don't think someone
could've got into the system?
Well, when you leave it wide open
like that for the last 12 hours...
no self-respecting hacker
is just gonna pass it by.
- And that ain't gonna be pretty.
- Aw, goddamn it! Oh, geez!
Oh, goddamn it!
Get the hell out of my way!
You know, Phil, you don't
handle stress well at all.
[ Banging ]
[ Phil ] Ow, ow, ow!
He's gonna love this.
Come on.
This thing is just...
[ Ringing ]
[ Tabulating ]
[ Barking, Snarling ]
[ Growling ]
[ Mrs. Munroe ] I don't care what your
computer says. I didn't order all this stuff,
and I certainly didn't write the sick
little notes that came with them.
So you tell someone to come over and pick this
stuff up, or I'm gonna call Consumer Affairs.
Christ.
[ Sighs ]
Where's my address book?
- Pajama party?
- Don't you start.
[ Female Reporter ] Now back to you, Bob.
In local news,
the authorities are now saying that a local
man who died in a car accident late Monday...
may have been the serial murderer
they've been hunting for three years.
He has been identified
as Karl Hochman of Lindhurst,
nicknamed
the Address Book Killer...
because he would steal an address
book and kill those listed.
Wow. That's scary stuff. Bob, you ever
wonder how many address books you're in?
Never do, Kelly. It's one of the
advantages of having no friends.
Who's Terry Munroe?
Terry Munroe.
Terry Munroe. Terry Munroe.
Terry Munroe. I have no idea.
Well, somebody's searchin'
awfully hard for her records.
Oh, Jesus, is this some third-rate hacker
tryin' to get back at an ex-girlfriend?
No. This guy is good, Phil.
I mean really good. Ohh.
Not elegant, but creative,
with a mean streak.
He's jumping through systems
faster than I can track him.
Faster than you can track him?
How do we get rid of the son of a bitch?
- I don't know.
- [ Phil ] How do we catch this son of a bitch?
What... What the hell is that?
What is that? Dental records?
[ Beeping ]
[ Machine Whirring ]
[ Machine Beeping ]
[ Warning Buzzer ]
- Come on, lady.
- Look, I'm sorry.
- [ Warning Buzzer ]
- What? Great.
- [ Yelps ]
- [ Man ] Oh, great.
[ Woman ] Great.
[ Man ] Way to go.
Unbelievable.
[ Josh ] Look, Fraze, I was just
searching around on my computer.
I found this great sex program.
Uh-huh. Yeah, it's great.
Uh-huh. Yeah, I'm tellin' ya,
Fraze, this girl is so fine.
Yeah, I call her butt an onion
'cause it makes you wanna cry.
[ Female Voice ]
Join me at the Love Corral.
I gotta go, Fraze.
My computer wants me. Bye.
[ Voice ]
Choose a partner.
[ Josh ]
All right. I'll choose you.
- Oh, yeah.
- Would you like to remove my breast shields?
- Please touch them now.
- [ Josh ] I like this.
- Yeah.
- [ Warning Buzzer ]
Who knows my number?
[ Josh ]
Who are you?
What do you want?
Log me off.
[ Computer Beeping ]
What are you doing, Josh?
Um, nothing.
The phone company just called. Somebody
dialed $700 worth of 900 numbers...
in the last 24 hours.
Come on. Think about it.
700 bucks in 24 hours?
I'd have laryngitis.
- How do you explain it then?
- I don't know. Maybe it was Axl.
- He humps anything that moves.
- Don't get smart with me.
I'm sorry you lost your address book, but can
you please take it out on somebody else?
And turn off that damn computer.
You think electricity is free?
It was a green address book
about this big.
Could you wait just a moment?
I'm with a customer.
It had little scraps of paper
sticking out all over it.
I'm sorry, but you know how it is
when you lose your address book.
Sure. Especially
with what happened.
Now, the new PowerBooks are fantastic.
The scary thing...
It's not like they wear a sign or anything.
They pretty much look like you and me.
- Who does?
- People who thought they couldn't work the 170.
No. No, no. No, no.
The Address Book Killer who worked here.
What?
Don't be silly.
Excuse me. Which locker
was Karl Hochman's?
- [ Exhales ]
- Will someone please tell me what's going on here?
[ Rapper On Radio ] ♪ I was coolin' at
a jam ♪ ♪ with my boys in Nelson Park ♪
♪ Up in the Bronx where ♪
♪ the suckers get stomped ♪
♪ It was me, Reed, James Bob and Mick ♪
Oh, Josh. Oh,
I'm so glad you're here.
♪ But I was tryin' to debate ♪
♪ should I pick up the mike ♪
Can I get you anything? Another glass
of milk, a piece of cake? Anything?
Ma, are you sure
you're feeling okay?
[ Doorbell Rings ]
I'll be back in a minute, okay?
Yes?
Um, Miss Munroe?
I'm sorry to bother you.
Uh, my name's Walker.
Datanet?
It's a mainframe computer company.
Look, I'm sorry, but if you're selling
something, I'm really not interested.
It's nothing like that. See, we've been having
problems with our system the last couple days,
and we think it might have
something to do with you.
Me? Yeah. See, all this stuff about
you keeps coming up in our files.
Look, you're not
making any sense at all,
and I hate computers,
so if you'll excuse me...
No, wait.
Teresa Margaret Munroe?
Arrested April, 1972,
Washington, D.C., civil disobedience?
What the hell is this?
Not a Nixon fan, huh?
I was at
that same demonstration.
Were you one of the girls who jumped
naked into the reflecting pool?
No. My driving record?
My son's medical record?
Who are you?
Bram Walker?
The Bram Walker?
Ma, do you have any idea
who this guy is?
Boy, oh, boy.
You get some trade-off.
You give us Ticketron
and bank machines,
but then we get some sort of Big Brother who
keeps a record of every time you sneeze.
I'll tell you.
Paranoia is underrated.
Look. This is so cool.
This guy infected the I.R.S.
with a herpex virus.
He sent everybody in Rhode
Island a five-cent refund.
Shoplifting?
I was 17.
It was peer pressure.
Okay. My mom
was a shoplifter.
All right, all right.
Big news flash.
So I'm not perfect.
I'm so glad you came.
Believe it or not, Mrs. Munroe, I'm not responsible
for your bank machine or arrest record.
Can you think of anything you
might've done to piss a hacker off?
Reject a science geek
in high school maybe?
Ma, what's
the Davy Jones Fan Club?
- Give me that.
- I hate to interrupt. Look, I have to go.
If you get anything that looks like computer
error, just give me a call, all right?
Thanks.
[ Humming ]
[ Radio: Classical ]
No, no, no, no. Yes.
Ah.
[ Continues Humming ]
Pa, pa, pow.
[ Resumes Humming ]
Hmm. Now.
[ Ringing, Connection Static ]
[ Voice ]
Log on. Log on. Log on.
[ Vocalizing ]
[ Overlapping Voices ]
[ Voices Continue ]
- Hey. Hey! - [ Tapping ]
- [ Computer Screen Beeps ]
Thank you.
[ Electricity Buzzing ]
[ Buzzing Continues ]
[ Rapid Beeping ]
[ Rapid Beeping Continues ]
[ Electrical Arcing ]
[ Sniffs ]
[ Rapid Beeping Continues ]
[ Sniffing ]
- [ Rapid Beeping, Faint ]
- Hmm.
Ah.
Hot. [ Mutters, Indistinct ]
Shit.
Damn. Damn. Damn.
[ Electrical Arcing ]
[ Screaming ]
Oh, no! [ Yells ]
[ Yelping ]
God.
[ Groaning ]
[ Grunting, Groaning ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Static ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Metallic Scraping ]
[ Telephone Ringing ]
Hello?
What?
Oh, my God.
[ Sighs ]
Oh, no.
[ Organ ]
And so we commit Frank's body to the love
and grace of Jesus Christ, our Lord.
Amen.
♪ ♪
[ Ominous Vocalizing ]
Huh?
[ Gasps, Screams ]
[ Yelps ]
Oh.
[ Woman ] Oh, yeah.
We had four TV crews here yesterday...
and a couple of reporters from
People magazine the day before.
It's been crazy. Crazy.
[ Sighs ]
All that time he was killin' people,
I didn't have a clue.
Course, I hardly knew him.
He never talked
to nobody anyhow.
[ Exhales Strongly ]
[ Woman ] You know,
when he got people's address books,
he'd play with 'em,
you know, tease 'em.
Where'd he keep the address books?
The police said touch nothin'.
They already took what they wanted,
including all the address books.
You know, he was a genius
at the computer.
He used to sit in stone silence
just starin' at the screen.
Hey, are you through
up here yet, huh?
I guess.
Come on.
I got things to do.
This place gives me the creeps.
Boy, is it... weird.
You know,
hatred of caring systems...
That's what this big Ph.D.
said on the news.
That Karl hated his friends.
He hated his family.
It's a long life, ma'am.
You can make a lot of mistakes.
You could marry the wrong men, men you
should never let anywhere near your kids.
You gotta be careful
with your caring systems.
I thought you were
meeting Elliot at 8:00?
[ Sighs ] I think I'm gonna cancel.
I'm just not up to it.
[ Sighs ]
Ma, I miss Frank too,
but you think he'd want his friends
hanging around the house all night...
thinking about him?
I'm just feeling a little sad
tonight, that's all.
What about
every other night, hmm?
You used to protest in Washington.
Now look at you.
[ Sighs ]
Okay. When's the last time you bought
a dress that wasn't from a catalog?
Anything you can get in a store,
you can get in a catalog for less.
Oh, yeah?
It's true.
Ooh, this is nice, if you
wanna attract a golfer.
I'm getting style tips from
somebody with 87 black T-shirts?
Ma, you're not getting any younger.
Get your hands dirty.
[ Sighs ]
[ Stereo: Rap ]
Fraze? Yeah, she's gone.
Okay. I'll meet you at the mall in 15.
Great. Bye.
♪ You'd better just check yourself ♪
♪ 'Cause in these days ♪
♪ we don't go for that ♪
♪ So you better try someone else ♪
[ Beep ]
[ Ringing ]
[ Answering Machine Clicks ]
Hi. This is Terry.
Josh and I aren't here right now,
but leave a message, and
we'll get right back to you.
[ Beep ]
[ Connection Static ]
[ Whimpers ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Man ]
Good catch, Barbara.
[ Woman Chuckles ]
My.
[ Man ] Although many dogs are
frightened of water at first...
[ Barks ] - Once they learn to
swim, they may never want to come out.
- Dogs are born with natural ability to swim.
- [ Whimpers ]
Why do you think
they call it the dog paddle?
[ Yelps ]
[ Sniffing ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Jazz ]
[ Gasps ]
Sorry.
[ Sighs ]
Hurry up, Josh.
Josh Munroe.
Gonna dice you, Fraze.
[ Josh ]
Hey, Fraze. I'm ready.
Looking for you.
[ Echoes ]
[ Grunting ]
Can't hide too long, can ya?
There you are.
All right.
I got you, man.
I got you.
[ Frazer ]
Come on, Josh. Where you at?
There you are.
All right.
I got you.
I got you nailed.
[ Gasps ]
Damn.
- That's not fair.
- Stop whining, Munroe,
and prepare to die.
[ Grunts ]
Hey!
I'm comin' for ya.
[ Josh ] Yes! You're dead meat.
Your ass is mine.
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
Gonna get you back for that, Josh.
Come on.
Fraze, you see that?
See what?
[ Echoes ]
Looked like there was someone
else in here with us.
I'm gonna go check it out, okay?
[ Footsteps Clanking ]
Josh, the fun's
hardly even started.
[ Groans ]
[ Yelling ]
[ Laughs ]
You okay, Josh?
[ Door Opens ]
Axl?
Axl.
Here, boy.
[ Sighs ]
Axl?
Axl.
Axl!
Who closed the cover?
[ Whirring ]
Shit. Come on.
Damn.
Not again.
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Panting ]
Josh.
It was my fault, wasn't it?
No. Axl was an accident.
Come here.
Will you just
leave me alone, please?
Hello.
Ms. Munroe.
I know it's late,
but I need to talk to you.
I'll be right with you, okay?
[ Terry ]
I've been so worried about Josh,
and these awful things
just keep happening.
Look, I'm sorry. I shouldn't be
unloading all of this on you.
Sure you don't want a beer?
No, really, I don't drink.
I just need to know
what's going on.
Well,
all I know is that, uh,
someone's hacking
into our system.
And he's good.
Really good.
And the only thing he seems
to want is to get at you.
I just keep thinking.
What if some hacker...
found out that I was supposed
to be the next victim,
and he decided to pick up where
the Address Book Killer left off?
What if he killed Frank?
A hacker this good can
mess with your credit cards,
he can wipe out your bank accounts, he
can even cancel your driver's license,
but there's no way anyone can
kill somebody with a computer.
[ Beeping ]
- [ Klaxon Blares ]
- Oh, come on, Terry.
How many times have I asked you
to come by the safety lab?
- Mr. Miller.
- Wait. Hold on one second. Yeah.
1,700 at 6.35.
Let's move it back.
All right.
Crumple zone's holding up fine.
Let's try one at 20.
So what do you think?
Go out to dinner. There's a great
salad bar just across the street.
That's... It's...
That's a really sweet offer,
but, um, I'm just swamped.
I don't think I can get out of here.
Terry, the...
system is backed up, and the whole
mid-Atlantic region is out.
Hurry!
Elliot?
No. This is the last time
we're in the lab this month.
Look, it's fascinating stuff
we're doing here.
Come on, Terry. I mean...
Elliot, I really have to go.
[ Line Clicks ]
[ Beeping ]
Oh, God.
What now?
Looks like the front brake.
Want me to take a look?
Oh, great reasoning.
No, I'll do it.
Oh, goddamn it.
[ Beeps ]
Jesus.
[ Man ]
Mr. Miller.
- [ Beeps ]
- That video camera's acting up again.
[ Elliot ]
Hey, this isn't a coffee break.
[ Beeps ]
Hey, you.
Get me a ladder.
[ Beeps ]
Sir, your ladder.
What the hell is this?
What are you trying to do,
kill me?
Go get another ladder.
Make sure you fill out the right form.
12-M.
That's "M" as in "moron."
Well, go.
No, no. Not the side sensors.
For Chrissakes.
We're doing another head-on.
Get out of the way. Come on. Move.
Come on. Let me do it. Out. Out.
[ Beeping ]
- [ Tires Screeching ]
- Wha... Wha...
Hey. Whoa. Wait.
Help! Help!
Oh, God! Help me!
[ Klaxon Blares ]
[ Woman On P.A. ]
All clear.
[ Man ] Is he all right?
[ Man #2 ] I don't know.
[ Man ]
You all right, sir?
Jesus Christ.
You're all fired.
[ Man ] What?
[ Chattering ]
Jesus. God.
Oh! Goddamn stupid
sons of bitches.
Ah.
Oh. Jesus. God.
[ Woman ]
Mr. Miller.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll be right there.
[ Screaming ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Phone Rings ]
[ Ringing ]
Hello. [ Male Voice ] Your number
has been randomly selected...
for this computer-generated survey
by the Heartland Insurance...
[ Phone Rings ]
God.
Yeah?
Did you know that Heartland Insurance...
offers a free, no obligation
insurance assessment?
Up yours.
[ Ringing ]
Hello.
Are you concerned...
with what will happen to your
family after you're gone?
Please answer after the beep.
[ Beep ]
Did you know you just reached the
Consumer Affairs Department,
and we are now going to start
a harassment investigation?
Thank you for your response.
[ Computerized Male Voice ] Terry. I want
to lick the tears from your eyes, Terry.
I want to taste your blood.
Who is this?
I stole your
address book, Terry.
Who is this?
I'm killing your friends.
I'm going to savor killing you.
I don't want to go to Frazer's.
Don't argue, Josh.
I have to go see Bram, and I'm
not gonna leave you here alone.
[ Woman ]
Boys, the babysitter's here.
The babysitter?
That is so humiliating.
Look. It's your fault.
The only reason she's here...
is because I snuck out
with you last time.
The babysitter.
[ Hip-hop On Stereo ]
[ Woman ] And I've left the
phone numbers... Oh, my God.
What is it?
[ Chuckles ]
She's so cute.
- Carol Maibaum.
- Have a great time tonight.
Thanks, Carol. I will.
Good night.
[ Country On Speakers ]
Another mai tai
with a beer back.
I'm fine.
I thought you said you didn't drink.
Only on holidays...
and when computers come to
life and call me on the phone.
Couldn't have been, Terry.
Must have been the hacker.
You didn't hear his voice.
It wasn't a hacker.
No, I can't come over, Greg.
I'm babysitting.
Besides, I got my stupid
driver's license suspended.
Had to take the bus.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Phone Rings ]
[ Answering Machine Clicks ]
Hi, this is Carol.
I'm not here right now,
but if you want to talk to me,
and I'd love to hear from you,
call 555-2048.
That's just tonight, okay?
See you.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, Carol.
Josh, would you go watch TV
or something. Mm-hmm.
[ Beeping ]
[ Line Ringing ]
Wait just a second, Greg.
I'm beeping.
- Hello.
- [ Connection Static ]
Hello?
[ Loud Static ]
I don't know.
Must have been a wrong number.
Right. No.
No. He said he'd get me
another one.
Unless I could use yours.
[ Chuckles ] Do you have one?
No?
[ Giggles ]
Uh-huh.
Yeah. Well, did you
see her hair?
No, you brought her up.
No.
[ Carol Chattering ]
Mm-hmm.
[ Giggles ]
I might.
I don't know.
- Mm-hmm. [ Giggles ]
- [ Beeps ]
Why do you care?
When? Tomorrow?
[ Giggles ]
I don't...
I don't know.
How about... How about next week?
We can get together,
like, with Darryl and Chris.
Why does she have to come?
[ Giggles ]
I'm not good enough?
I am? Okay.
[ Baby Screams ]
[ Gasps ]
- Oh, my God.
- [ Murmuring ]
Oh.
[ Murmuring ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Laughing ]
- Who turned on the stove?
- I don't know.
One of you guys turned on the stove,
and I want to know who it was.
- I didn't turn on the stove.
- I didn't do it.
Wanna play hardball? Fine. Get into the
kitchen and start by doing the dishes.
Look, we didn't do anything.
Come on.
[ Groans ]
Come on, Josh.
Come on. It's a great idea.
Hey, look, Josh. It's my house, and she's
babysitting for me and my sister, and I say no.
The only reason she's here is 'cause
my mom gave your mom her number,
and second of all,
I think she'd go for it.
[ Garbage Disposal Whirring,
Clicks ]
Damn.
What's wrong?
Something's jammed.
Let me see.
Hey, Josh. Are you crazy?
[ Switch Clicks ]
Look, nothing's gonna
happen, okay?
- Oh! Fraze!
- J-Josh!
- No.
- Damn it! It's got my hand!
- Pull your hand out!
- I can't!
You punk.
Dang, I thought your hand was stuck.
I got you.
Hey, man.
Yo, I can't believe
you actually fell for that.
♪ And that's no surprise ♪
Thirteen dollars.
Okay. That makes $37 and...
28 cents.
[ Frazer ] Come on, Carol.
Who's gonna know?
Even if we tell anybody,
they're not gonna believe us.
We're hackers, Carol.
We can fix your driving record.
Okay. I'll unbutton my shirt.
Yes. Uh, what about
your bra?
Your insurance will go down.
My shirt. That's it.
Good? Okay. Deal.
♪ An overnight guest ♪
♪ Just a good time ♪
You boys are definitely getting
too old for babysitting.
♪ Sittin' back thinkin' about what to do ♪
♪ Boy, I'm thinkin' about calling you ♪
♪ It's in my nature ♪
- [ Frazer ] Ooh.
- ♪ Ooh, my temperature starts to rise ♪
♪ And that's no surprise ♪
♪ It's in my nature ♪
- Ah!
- Oh!
[ Both Yelling ]
Come on. That's not it. Hey.
That can't be it.
Come on. Get over here.
I have a list of names
I want you to look at.
This is everybody who's logged into Datanet's
computer since this whole thing started.
Our guy's gotta be in here someplace.
Take a look.
See if you see
anything familiar.
Anything you recognize.
- This.
- Southside General?
That's the hospital they took the
killer to the night he died.
They probably run their big machines
off our memory... MRI's, CAT scans.
The killer died
in this hospital.
And it was plugged
into your computer.
- [ Beeps ]
- [ Whirring ]
♪ Ain't nothin' but a party ♪
♪ Everybody come along ♪
♪ Keep your body movin' ♪
♪ while I'm groovin' with the song ♪
♪ I got funky rhythms ♪ ♪ Funky rhythms
with a beat ♪ ♪ Funk, funk, funk ♪
♪ Funky rhythms for the street ♪
♪ Keep clappin' while I'm rappin' ♪
♪ While I'm rappin' ♪
♪ clap your hands ♪
♪ Listen to the ♪ ♪ Listen to
the ♪ ♪ Listen to the man ♪
♪ Turn the party out Without ♪
♪ a doubt I'm in the house ♪
♪ Kick it to the beat is ♪
♪ what it's really all about ♪
♪ Party, party people ♪
♪ if you're ready listen up ♪
♪ 'Cause I can get the lyrics ♪
♪ Easy Lee can get the cut ♪
♪ An automatic,
systematic "rhythmatic" sound ♪
♪ If you ain't with the program ♪
♪ you gotta get it down ♪
[ Humming ]
[ Whistling ]
You're gonna be all right,
you know.
How's my mom?
She's okay.
She's worried about you though.
You can talk to her
about what happened to Carol.
You know that.
Look, I can't even talk to her
about what happens in gym class.
Look, it's no biggie, okay?
Pretty tough, huh?
So are you.
Not me.
Yeah, right.
You're an outlaw.
You're the toughest, smartest hacker alive.
Look, Josh.
That tax refund stunt...
Sure, it felt great
being an outlaw...
for about a day.
But I blew my whole career.
See, guys like us,
we have to be careful.
Sometimes we're too smart
for our own good.
[ Man ] Because they've only
been household accidents.
[ Terry ] Accidents?
That's insane!
Someone or something is coming
after my son and my friends. Terry.
How many more people have to die before
someone starts taking this seriously?
[ Man ] As far as we're concerned,
those have all been accidents.
[ Terry ] He doesn't think there's a problem.
Three people have died in the last week.
What has to happen before you're willing to
get involved? [ Man ] You're just getting...
[ Terry ] Don't tell me to calm down!
[ Man ] Terry. Terry.
There's an order.
Shit.
These guys...
Mom.
I was just sitting down, and this is
from your book. There's an order here.
[ Terry ]
Hurry up, and get everything unplugged.
I know. It sounds crazy,
but something is after me,
and I'm not about to sit around
debating how that could be.
[ Bram ] Okay, you finish up here.
I'm gonna go over to Datanet...
and violate a few hundred
federal statutes...
by putting a trace
on the hacker's next call.
That'll give us the guy's number,
and we'll nail the bastard.
[ Gasps ]
Not my curling iron.
[ Beeping ]
For the ring and the car.
Ooh. So close.
Oh, God.
♪ Who to blame ♪
♪ I'm living with a stranger ♪
[ Sighs ]
I'm waiting. I'm waiting.
Okay. All the money
in the world.
[ Groans ]
Oh, God.
I'll be back in a few hours.
Just gonna go downtown and see Bram.
Okay.
You keep an eye on Grandma, okay?
Yeah.
And don't let her plug anything in.
Mm-hmm.
And don't believe anything she tells
you about me when I was a child.
Oh, honey.
[ Sighs ]
See ya, Ma.
Okay.
[ Beeps ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Phone Rings ]
[ Gasps ]
- Hello.
- [ Buzzing ]
- All right.
- [ Connection Static ]
[ Beeping ]
I'm waitin' for you,
Mr. Hacker.
Come on, come on.
I know you're in there.
[ Beeping ]
Yes!
555-3371.
Be there. Be there.
You're hooked.
We got ya.
Be there.
[ Rings ]
That's impossible.
[ Ringing Continues ]
- [ Ringing ]
- What the...
[ Multiple Phones Ringing ]
[ Ringing Continues ]
- [ Beeping ]
- Datanet?
[ Ringing Continues ]
[ Man ]
Okay. Line five, you're on the air.
[ Man #2 ] I'd like "Sit Tight
Tonight" by the Serial Killers.
[ Man #1 ]
Is that for anyone special?
[ Man #2 ]
It's for Bram Walker,
who I know
is all alone right now.
[ Beeping ]
[ Phone Rings ]
[ Gulps ]
Yeah.
[ Man #2 ]
Sit tight tonight, Bram.
Don't forget to scream.
Pain makes me sing.
[ Busy Signal ]
Shit.
[ Buzzing ]
Oh, good.
Go right!
[ Tires Screeching ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Rings ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Horn Honks ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Humming ]
[ Door Opens ]
[ Woman On Police Radio ]
Euclid and 39th, man down.
Car 12, respond to car vandals,
1433 Main Street.
[ Twittering ]
Shit. We got an officer down.
You're gonna have a hell of
a first night on the force.
- 1227 Lakeview Drive.
- [ Engine Starts ]
[ Woman On Police Radio ]
Suspect has no name.
[ Siren Wailing ]
- [ Beeping ]
- Hey, Mike.
What do ya got?
Domestic violence, Lakeview Drive.
- We're gonna have to take it.
- Here. Take this. Let's roll.
[ Woman On Radio ]
6-10, hostage situation.
[ Man On Radio ]
6-14, shots fired.
- [ Woman ] 6-27, armed robbery.
- [ Siren Wailing ]
[ Man ]
6-11, break-in at 1227 Lakeview Drive.
Holy shit.
[ Woman ]
Car 12, robbery in progress.
[ Siren Wailing ]
[ Helicopter Whirring ]
What we got here is a goddamn mess,
and nobody knows what's going on.
Suspects are
armed and dangerous.
It's a domestic dispute.
Go easy.
Jesus Christ.
[ Gasps ] Grandma,
have you seen what's going on outside?
[ Man ]
Ready? Over here.
Listen, rookie.
It's a whole new ball game since I.A.
We don't play that
sitting duck shit anymore.
[ Man ] Come on, everybody.
Take your positions. Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Come on!
Take your positions!
Let's go! Let's go!
[ Humming ]
Hold your fire! Hold your fire!
Hold your fire!
[ Gunshots ]
Hey.
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Machine Beeping ]
You're gonna be fine, Mom.
You're in shock.
They just want to keep you
overnight for some tests.
Thank God
the two of you are okay.
[ Machine Beeping ]
[ Thunderclap ]
An MRI makes a record of all the
electrical activity in a person's brain...
and stores it in a computer.
So when that storm caused
that electrical surge,
it actually shot
the killer's scan...
out of the hospital computer,
straight into Datanet.
You mean there's an exact impression of
the killer inside of Datanet's computers?
It's not just an impression now.
I guess, if you're religious,
you'd call it his soul.
Man, that really freaks me out.
So, if he's computer-based...
I got it.
We exorcise him, right?
We get a priest, go down to
Datanet, throw his soul into hell.
No, what we do is we take...
Wait. H-Hold on. How about...
we send him back through
the MRI and into his body?
You stay here, and me and Bram will
go drive a stake through his heart.
Yeah, great.
That's... That's great.
Why can't we just delete him?
When you delete something on a
computer, it doesn't go away, Mom.
It's still in there.
You just can't find it anymore.
Unfortunately, he's right.
I could program...
- Fridge magnets.
- Fridge magnets?
Josh, didn't you tell me
not to put fridge magnets...
next to your disks
because they'd erase them?
Yeah.
Oh, come on. You can't erase a computer
the size of Datanet with a fridge magnet.
Too bad. He's right.
But he's not.
What?
We just need a slightly bigger magnet.
Ohio Tech.
Josh, hand me that.
Here.
Thanks.
So, how exactly is your virus gonna
get the killer to Ohio Tech?
Right now he's roving free
through the system.
He can jump into
any network he wants to.
Once I run my virus,
this will eat up all the available
memory, forcing him out of Datanet.
I've only left one route open:
into the particle accelerator.
- [ Beeping ]
- Excellent. I can't wait to ice this skeezer.
So, the virus chases him into the
particle accelerator, then what?
We just push a button
and erase him?
The accelerator is
one huge mother of a magnet.
We ramp the magnetism
up as far as it'll go.
That'll pull him
into the accelerator.
No matter what he is, it'll
smash his atoms into oblivion.
Cool.
You really think this is gonna work?
[ Electronic Twittering ]
[ Terry ] You make a habit of breaking
into scientific facilities, Bram?
More like a hobby. Wouldn't all
these places have guards and stuff?
No, this is only
a particle accelerator.
All they have to protect
themselves from is drunk students.
It's right up here.
Dope! Whoa.
Come on.
Which part's the magnet? This tube is the
accelerator, and all of it's a magnet.
When we shoot him into these coils, we're gonna
blow him into a billion bits of nothin'.
Over here is the control booth.
It's okay.
Go on in.
The walls in here are sealed.
As long as we stay in the control booth,
we're safe from the magnetic field.
- [ Click ]
- When we crank the accelerator, don't leave the booth.
The magnetism can pull the
fillings right out of your teeth.
[ Electronic Twitter ]
Great.
[ Whirring ]
- Throw all these toggle switches along here and these here.
- Okay.
[ Bram ]
Great. It's kickin' in.
We're ready for him.
[ Beeping ]
He's almost here.
What's happening?
I don't know.
It's surging out of the system.
Whoa!
[ Neck Cracking ]
[ Computerized Voice ]
Excuse me. A little stiff.
Caught a bitch of a virus.
Josh, no.
Aaah!
[ Groans ]
Bram, are you okay?
Yeah.
Shit.
[ Bram ]
Shit. He's shutting it down.
[ Gasps ]
Terry, what's your hurry?
We have all the time
in the world.
Go help your mom.
Okay. Okay.
I'm gonna try
to rewire this sucker.
[ Karl ] I've been looking forward
to killing you for so long,
but I want to
do it slowly, baby.
I want to taste your pain.
[ Coughs ]
All right. We can fix this.
Twist. Ow! [ Groans ] Damn.
[ Karl ] I want to feel your ribs crack
while I suck the breath from your lungs.
Work, will ya?
Damn!
No power here.
Patch in downstairs.
[ Gasps ]
No good deed
goes unpunished, Terry.
Nice try.
[ Karl ]
Don't try to fight with me, bitch.
Enough playing around.
You can't run. You can't hide.
You can't win. Come on!
[ Typing ]
Yes! We're back in.
The board is up.
Oh!
- Josh!
- [ Panting ]
- Come on.
- Let me in.
[ Bram ]
Get back! Get back!
Ma.
All right.
Terry, get off the grate.
Terry, Josh.
Stay there.
I'll be right up, okay?
[ Groaning, Yells ]
[ Panting ]
[ Klaxon Blaring ]
[ Female Voice On P.A. ]
Magnetic field overload.
Evacuate to shielded areas
immediately.
Magnetic field overload.
[ Gagging ]
Evacuate to shielded areas
immediately.
Magnetic field overload.
Evacuate to shielded areas
immediately.
[ Panting ]
[ Klaxon Blaring ]
[ Groans ]
[ Beeping ]
Come on. Come on.
[ Gasps ]
- You're next.
- [ Panting ]
[ Buzzing ]
[ Panting ]
[ Computerized Growl ]
[ Groaning Softly ]
[ Josh ]
Mom, help!
Please! Please! No! No!
Get your fucking hands
off my son.
Guess again.
I'm dead already, Einstein.
[ Laughing ]
I wouldn't waste
that last bullet.
[ Wind Whistling ]
Frankly, Terry, I'm sick of
all this family values crap.
[ Alarm Blaring ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Yelling ]
[ Distorted Screaming ]
[ Beeping ]
Thanks.
- Terry.
- Hmm?
Do me a favor?
Anything.
Turn off that damn machine.
[ Beeping Continues ]
[ Click ]