Subtitles by Kay Cee
conversion https://subtitletools.com
You play in a band?
I'm kind of a guitar player for hire
Oh, what band were you playing with?
I played with Albert King, Skinner,
No, No
Muddy Waters, B B King.
hey, hey, hey, you put down! /You play this thing?
Put my damn guitar down.  he don't play.
Why wont you just shut up! you give his...
Put my guitar back/Shut up Lonna
Why don't you put my guitar down/ Want your guitar?
Yeah ...here it is!
Jesus.. guys
Did you get that approved?
Oh, come on. You have diet house bands out the Wazoo.
Don't call it diet house. Everybody calls it that.
Well is derogatory. It's a nutrition center.
Now listen Ed, we got to huddle about this band.
I'm getting complaints and plenty of them.
Nobody likes to see a bunch of convicts... skulking around the campus.
Beside that the band sounds terrible.
You're the most annoying brother alive.
All we need is a little practice.
Oh no!
And look, here's my new guitar player.
You guys got a tub here?
Nothing like a good long soak. You know what I'm saying?
Wesley Benfield. You have been arrested 13 times.
Only five convictions.
I got blamed for a lot of shit did not do.
Watch your mouth.
This is a house of the Lord. I will not tolerate foul language.
That is rule number one.
Sorry,The Lord is my shepherd.
Are you being sarcastic? Because if you are the deputy will march you right back to jail.
No, I'm not. I'm sorry. I've been to Sunday school. I read the Bible a lot.
Yeah, take a look at my file there sir. It'll tell you where I was raised up
At the orphanage down in Bonneville.
They made us read the bible
I've written out whole sections out by hand...
In detention.
I bet that was quite often.
That was the old me.
Look sir, if you could just find a mustard seed of forgiveness,
I promise you won't regret it.
OK, Rhodell. He's a keeper.
Listen, you screw this up.
I'm going to come up here,
Take off my jewelry and whip your little white ass.
Oh, language Rhodell.
That's why I started a band. Healing criminal minds through music is my main focus.
This is the girls wing. The boys are down here.
We have an honor system, but I will be checking.
What kind of music y'all play.
Hymns, Hello Raymond.
Hymms?
Yes Hymms, I thought you went to church.
Oh my Ben, you're supposed to be down painting the porch.
Man.. I don't feel good. Well, clean off that bed. You've got a new roommate?
Come on, get busy.
Whoa, Whoa, Whoa, look now. Okay.
This, this, this cat right here, He just got out of jail right
Okay. now this is no good.
Okay, hold on man. Hey, what are you putting us on the floor?
Why? Cause Mr. Ned told me to
Listen, man. This is no good. Okay. How am me and Lonnie supposed to get clean?
How am me and Lonnie supposed to get all back on track again
If you keep bringing troublemakers up in here,
Alright? Taken him down the hall, let Raymond deal with him.
You Know Raymond lives in a closet....is gonna mess me up
Man I'm already messed up.
I decide who goes where, not you.
And remember a soft answer turns away wrath,
But a harsh word stirs up anger.
That's proverbs
Yes,... it is.
Make yourself comfortable.
You some kind of Jesus Freak.
You know, Jesus comes out a lot different when you read the Bible straight through
He caused some trouble,
He stirred up some things.
Okay, thank you.
Let's go Lonnie./ Alright.
You did that last week, man. A smart man...You did that last week.
This was mama's favorite.
You may have to share.
Hello Raymond, ladies.
Raymond why don't you try the bongos today?
Oh, Wesley welcome,  oh you've met Ben and Lonnie.
This is Raymond, Shanita and Angie.
And where's your guitar? I'll just play that one.
Would you be more comfortable with your guitar?.... You know what?
It's old and beat up. I just rather play that one.
But we're not fancy here.
That one's fine, Mr. S. /Very well. Okay, kids follow me.
Blessed Assurance
Sing out Raymond.
Not too fast, slow down.
I can't hear you singing Lonnie
Get up, get up, Wesley wake up
Get up and put on this tee shirt.
What on earth is wrong with Ben?/What on earth is wrong with you Mr.
Get dressed/ Mr. Seers/ and get downstairs. We are waiting.
His Majesty is coming down now.
And you going to leave the door. you going to close the door?
No, he going to break the door.
Can you have some respect for the van please?
it's not your van
I know it's not my van, slamming like it's dominoes, man.
But Mr. Seer put me in charge of it,/ ooh watch out
Hey girl....Shake that ass, Shake that ass ,
Hey, hey... you all stop it!
Clean the eggs up, man
What, what, what,
Shanita who going to clean this up... /ah ah, that's not my problem, that's not my problem.
Here he comes the little sorry ass, look, look at him, look at him.
Asshole egg slopping fool
Oh y'all going to be like that, fine!
Watch it, hey.
Need to watch where you're going, bro.
Hey. I'm talking to you. You need to slow down, man. you are going to run somebody over.
It'll do about a hundred.
What is it a rocket ship.../its a Plymouth.
Oh yeah, sure. Yeah, it's a Plymouth. What year is it, buddy? Maybe it's worth the money.
It's 1963,
4 door hardtop. 318 cubic inch  twin valves, and Torqueflite transmission.
What color is it?
What do you think?
I have no idea. There's nothing there.
Desert Beige Caramel,
er, er, er, er, er, er, er.
Hey buddy you miss a spot
No buddy right here
er, er, er, er, er, er, er.
Is a clean windshield.
Where is he? He got a new owl.
Careful. Careful gingerly now. Very good.  That's nice. Careful. Now
Since we put it in that box, I think a whole...the fish always stinks from the head,
Hey ain't she a beauty Ned... we're supposed to be playing a Spring Fling.
Boys give me Just a moment. Keep your voice down.
Keep your voice down. I signed us up over a month ago. We were playing.
Spring fling is from Ballard student body. Not those convicts. They're not enrolled.
Don't say convicts. It's derogatory. They're at risk youth.
Oh, too bad. They're not fat, Maybe then you care.
Do you have any idea how much money that nutrition center brings into this college?
I'm glad mom is not alive to see this.
How is it every time I bring up, excuse me. How is it every time I bring up something, it don't matter,
Hey, hold on we all eat together.
Where is Wesley Benfield?
Ben, you are the designated driver.
Um, I don't know.
Mr. Seer, he just disappeared
And you just left. Why wasn't I notified?
But I thought I could count on you. I am disappointed.
I am extremely disappointed.
Hey, Mr Sears. It's, it wasn't his fault. I was walking.
That is against the rules.
I have to know where you are at all times.
Every second of the day. Is that clear?
Yes sir. It had better be.
May I remind you all that you are in a halfway house,
Which means you are halfway in jail already
And you will be all the way in unless you straighten up.
I just got word today. They might pull our funding
Jail? Yes, from whence you cometh.
Raymond, let me have that.
Now, people, let's get serious. We have five days until spring fling
This our chance to show the whole school...Wait a minute, Wait a minute, the whole school?
Yes. Everyone will be there.
So let's get busy. Let's practice, Let's get better...
And lets us pray.
Tell me how we're supposed to get up in front of the whole damn school
And play this butt Numbing crap...Do you think we like it
But don't come over here s starting all this trouble. You heard what the man said? We could go back to jail.
What did you guys go to jail for anyway?
That's none of your business.
Well, I got in a fight with my boyfriend
So.
So I shot him.
In the leg, He's fine. You know he's not dead.
They said that it was attempted manslaughter.
But I say asshole slaughter is more like it.
So I guess you better just played a guitar and shut up.
Wesley, That is not funny.
Yeah, I know. It's not funny...you got to walking around here like a bunch of organ grinder Monkeys,
Ooh, who you calling monkeys?
Hey Man I called us all, monkeys
Pipe down Wesley. Nobody flies solo here. We're a team.
I can't do it.
I'll do anything else. Give me another job. I'll paint the whole house.
Oh No. If you're not in the band, you're not in the house.
Sorry, Kid shows the over. Wrap up equipment. I'll be in the van.
Mr S . Wait a minute, , Can we talk about this?
I can believe he said that...Slow down...Mr S, come on.. freaking Wesley, man
Wesley. yo, I left my music in there. Go get it.
Fine. Whatever...
Hey thou I Walk through the Valley of the shadow of bad music
Hey man who is that? Vernon.
Hey  Is that the only song you know how to play?
Hey, wait a minute. Wait a minute. I want to talk to you. Get back here.
Hey, wait up
He's making a run for it.
This is what, This is what,... I told you this was gonna happen.
Hey!
Hey, wait up, hey park that Plymouth, i want to talk to you
Turn left, Mr Ned,  call him Mr. S, ill call him Mr. Ned if i want to, ain't that right Mr. Ned.
Guys, guys, look for Wesley. I don't see him anywhere
Hey, hey man
Right this way. Brad and Terri, boy couldn't ask for a better day. Huh?
Watch your step on that cement, we're looking at it.
We're gonna. Fix that pretty soon, well, here it is. Isn't it pretty?
I know your daughter will be very, very comfortable and happy here.
Dr Mill's here is Brad and Carrie Gaines.
Welcome. Come on in.
Come inside
Where is safe.
Well, well
Look what the dog's done Drug in, get in here before I take off my jewelry.
Okay. Rhodell, take him in. man.
Here is your music?
You ran away. I did not run away. You all left me.
You're lying. I saw you with my own eyes.
I did.. I'm not... here I am, ready to go, Spring fling. Look at me. I'm right here.
Too. Late Wesley. Woe to them who strays from me.
Oh, I did not stray. I met this kid. He a genius piano player. He probably like an angel.
He a genius piano player. He probably like an angel.
Do what you must all. Come on now, I ain't lying to you, please
You know I know about. No, I did. I'm not lying. That kid can play his ass off
Ned what happened? What's going on?
Nothing. Everything is fine. We're getting ready to head over to spring fling.
Well, I've got a new client over there, a high roller from Kansas City
All of a sudden I got these lights flashing and deputies running around. You know what that looks like.
This is not working out.
We had the first group to perform. What do you think of a noble defenders of the word?
I think it was the last nail in your coffin.
Thanks. Lot.
Hello? Hey Man. whats Going on. Hey, can I come inside?
Look, I know this is gonna sound really crazy,
But you think maybe you can come down there with me and play that song you just played.
Just one time.
Come on man, you gotta come down here and if you don't come down there, with me
Them People down there, They don't put me back in jail.
I gotta go ask my dad. He's at the  shop,
No you don't. We just go right now. Nobody didn't have to know.
Well, he's the boss of me. That's okay. Just come do this with me please.
Well, I liked drive myself.
Well, cool means when we done with this thing, how am I owe you?
I'm going to take you out for supper or something.
Blam..We don't eat out.
Well, that cool, i can cook something, , some. It don't matter, what you guys like.
Hey Man, what do you guys like to eat? Pork chops. Hey Man, Wait up,
He left here, i don't trust him...Here's your robes.
Oh no man, Mr. S. No... thought we discuss this
We discuss, oh man...  this is chance for you to really stand out
Those are old fashion, i don't want to stand out
Noooo...we'll discuss this later
Anyway is what I say, what do you say?
Raymond can not be on guitar.
Too many people
Hey...What are you doing Vernon?
Since when do board members go to spring fling?   Is a special occasion Ned.
The board might want to see the band in action.
No, it's perfectly fine. If you're walking backwards, see, then nobody out here can see
Don t leave me by myself, I promise I wont leave you by yourself.
Promise... Vernon, Jesus Christ. I promise. I won't leave you by yourself. All right,
They got a piano? Yeah. All you gotta do is get up and play.
I bet it ain't tuned
Watch your step to step up with your foot. Don't turn. Don't turn around.
See
Tell me when you're ready
We like to give everyone a chance, but some people are just not Ballard material
Guys, come on,  yo guys get up here!
Wesley, who is that? This my friend Vernon, he is going to play with us.
Come on, lets go... what's going on?
Vernon, where you going, where you going, what do you doing?... the bushes, I got to pee,... well finish the song first.
I have to pee bad, What do you want me to do, Vernon, look is full
Guys? Excuse me from a buddy here. You really have to go to the bathroom.
Ah Vernon, what the hell, I told you had to go, you weren't kidding
But is OK, its happened to everybody in some time
I don't think so, we are not special.
Yes you are. You are a special kind of asshole.
What you call me, you heard What I said? Aren't you in enough trouble?
What's going on? The board of trustees out there loving this music.
See, I told you he could play... my pants are wet.
OK boys get out of here. Go on. That's enough.
I'll see you later... I'll be waiting.
He's got to get back up there. We're here at Vernon. Take my pants.
You have to come... No, no, no. You're killing them up there.
You do not need me...Yes I do, You promised.
Oh Lord. Take my pants,
Hurry on boys, get a move on.
Here Vernon,  take these pants, go in there and put them on please.
We have to sign this young man, I see you around town
Driving... a Plymouth...4 door, hard top, 318 cubic inch
Wonderful. Wonderful. I think the band should be all young people.
My god Wesley, I've got to hand it to you. Seek and Ye shall find.
Let's see. You had to go to jail. No Sir. Not Today.
Great job Ned...Ned the band they were terrific. Thank you. Luther
Thanks,...What about using it for founders day? Well, let's not get carried away here.
That's an excellent idea. Luther, the kids that come such a long way.
You know, they had a whole new dimension to Ballard. Might even attract new money.
Listen yo. I'm only gonna say this once, You save us man.
Yeah, you did. I appreciate it., No problem. But it wasn't me. It was him.
What is up man. Thanks...I'm Ben.
Alright, you going to be in band... OK
Hello. Hi. I'm the executive director of the Back On Track Again house.
Oh Great. Do you mind if I ask you some questions? I'm doing a story for the Democrat leader.
Absolutely. We need to drum up some support. Our funding is about to be cut.
That band is the most exciting thing to happen to Ballard in a long time.
You'll have to ask Deermont. He's the big cheese around here.
Who? Ellen, I'm sure we can work something out.
I'll leave you two alone. Ned why don't you Put some pants on
I'm getting accustomed to these.
Anyway, I started this program called Christian criminal rehabilitation
Are the criminals, all Christian.
Oh yes. They just don't know it yet
And you have to understand the band is not just a band.
I am perfecting the use of Christian music to infiltrate and heal the criminal mind.
It just pauses it just blowing my focus. Oh, okay.
Hey Vernon, please. You have to stop that rocking
You gotta get your hands on. you just need you to be still for a minute.
Hey, wait wait, wait...hey Vernon, Vernon
Is he alright, i don't have Any idea what is happening? what do you want me to do. Vernon, Vernon, Vernon,
Daddy... Well, he went crazy. Something going wrong. You say something about his rocking.
Daddy...It's alright. It's alright...daddy... It's alright. Come on. i got some tomatoes in the house, Come on. Come
Come on man. Something's wrong with him. We can't just go. Okay. I'm not going anywhere. Not going anywhere. Not going anywhere
Slashed. I just calm down, I'm not about this man.
What are y'all doing with him? You need to tell me or you can tell the sheriff
Nothing, sir. We were just. He was down at the school helping us have plants in music. That's all
How that happened
You're on special ed. No. No. Wait.
We're in a band. Yeah, kind of a Christian man. \I hate that crap.
Go on get outta here.
Actually sir, we was kind of hoping that maybe Vernon could come play music with us.
There's about a dog's chance in hell of that happening.
Vernon's music is for Vernon. He don't play with nobody.
He played with us and he's got a gift. He ought to be out in the world.
You trying to tell me how to raise my son. No Sir.
Well you best not, and where the hell are his bridges.
He peed them
You know? I think you two done enough for Vernon.
You church boys. Just get back in truck., Go back where you come from...now
Yes sir
Where's my Plymouth? It's right over there. Vernon. We towed it.
Is Vernon. Okay? Yeah, he's okay. What did his parents say.
Hmm... I only met his dad, and...
And?... and we can't talk about is rocking anymore because that's why I got upset.
Okay, fine. We can handle that.
I've been thinking what a tremendous asset he is going to be. You were so right. He's already made such a great change.
Uh, you know what? I'm gonna head upstairs because I don't feel too good. Well, take care of yourself.
Good Work Benjamin. Thank you. Mr. S.
I am going to have to speak with his father and get his permission.
No, that's probably not good idea, Mr. let me take care of that. Okay, fine. You were handling.
Wesley I told the sheriff I'm giving you another chance. I don't want any problems.
You got that? Yes sir. Especially since Verdun is not a resident of BOTA house,
Although he is definitely disadvantaged, in which case he'll fit right in. Do you know what I mean?
Yeah. He'll fit right in.
Wesley, I'm glad to see you getting back on track. I know we had our little misunderstandings, but you really came through for the band
Guide me in my efforts to help the noble defenders of the word. Glorify your name. Amen.
Raymond your Turn to help to Flip.
I'm Serious, I think we can do with this kid. With Vernon?
Look men you know you don't even know this kid already. Did you see what he did.
Ben? Seriously how you guys can in your life out selling coke
So now you see that, that is some to serious racial profiling, yes it is.
For your information. We were real musicians, we was raised in the church.
Long before we wrote them. Bad checks.
If you guys are real musicians and you should be primed to play the blues.
Wesley, The Blues is Wax Museum. It's not wax museum.
Vernon, look at the Muscles on that, that too much. that just sick.
Why the numbers on the clock and the circle.
I don't know
Oh,  She is new
Seemed like they always go in  circle.
Each one by itself
They never line up together or nothing....
That's what think kid...sundial
Just kind of caught on.
Want some bread.
Why can't I play with anybody?
Cause You can't
That boy say I  Could
You know I'm going to do today.
I'm going to start on that bus
Oh yeah, I'm going to get it running right.
Let me get this straight. Go in there and cook his daddy port chops to us and then he's going to sign a permission slip
Aha, that's exactly what I'm going to do. no wonder you in a halfway house.
Hey here, here,...thanks... hey don't sit with your back to the door... thanks a lot
Hello, anybody here
Hello
Car horn ............
ha ha ha, Yeah Vernon
Are we going play... I was fixing on making those pork chops
10-4.... where is  your daddy?
No he went to the store, we got nothing but froze fish, I don't want no froze fish
Daddy likes to listen to him, that's what we are going to play
Come on man,  just scared the crap out me... Vernon
That bus is ours
We going drive it to the Grand Canyon. Live on it on the way there and on the way back. The horn works.
This is quite a spread. thanks!
You got a cutting board... we use that
No for ??, to cut stuff, You know what I'm saying?
We've got stuff that Mama left is we don't use it much
All i need is a frying pan and two pots
Oh God Vern, ....rat turds
We got roaches too
You got any soap?
We use this
Vernon, where you mamma go?... heaven.
Vernon, you know how to peel potato.
Vernon, We need the whole potato. The whole white part of the potato.
But you didn't say that. Come on Vernon.
Whats the bag for....  Vernon stop.
Vernon, Just give me the wrong. Please cut it out already.
You got to quit with this rocket man. You're making me dizzy now. Go sit yourself down. All right.
No Vernon, V, V, V, no no, Daddy, ah, daddy,
Vernon, ah,
Here the Tomato, I Got It.
Fine
I' thought I've told you to get.
I just. I came down here because I promised Vernon I would come cook something for him.
Is that right? Vernon. You asked him to come cook?
Pork chops.
You got some nerve. I'm cooking something for you too.
I ain't going to be ready for about a half hour
Then you call me, when is done.
I didn't slice it.
Hey, better be some tasty pork chops.
Don't let Vernon around no electricity.
No Sir.
I blow up some things.
So Vernon, I was kind of hoping maybe later you can come by and maybe we can do some planning, you know,
With your permission. Of course. I play guitar.
Whereabouts do you live exactly,
Down over on ninth street.
Over by the Christian college.
You live in that halfway house? Yup. Near
Yeah
I do Sir.
It's really more like a dorm.
I mean, I don't really take anybody down there unless they're okay.
I mean most people on their bachelors or women and people who don't pose no threat.
How do I know you don't pose no threat.
He just wander into a guy's house.
What you do?
Can I have some ice cream? No, not right now.
I want to know what he did.
Mainly cars, but that was then. I mean, sure...
Look at that burden we got as a guitar picking bandit Car thief right here.
Guitar man, a killer dealers,...no no, your Keller dealer.
That's a good thing, right?
It is to him. It don't mean crap to me.
See, I don't want you and your kind around my son.
So I think you better just get on back to your house now.
Go on, now.
At least get halfway to your house.
Take it easy.
By the way, you do make a good port job. Thanks. You do
Vernon. He ain't no account.
He's my friend.
Yeah, you need a higher class of friends.
Goodnight Vernon,... Nite
Stays there.  I don't know.
Hello? What's its that men?
Hello? WHO's out there?
I'm doing Morse Code.
Vernon
We don't know Mars Code.
It's a message.
What is it?
I want to play that music.
If you'll stand next to me
I'll stand next to you. I'll be there the whole time.
Promise?
I'll never leave you by yourself.
Roger!
Vernon, You got to get the paper signed.
Copy that.
Hey, There goes my future boys.
Yeah man, There goes your future Black.
Daddy, will you sign this where I can be in a band?
Well, I guess that would do. And just in time they want your kids to play on the radio. Great PR.
Hello? Vernon,     I'll bet it needs tuning.
Oh No, Lester' already stopped by, no Mr.. S
Okay. Wesley round them up? You can go ahead and practice.
I want to hear on the concert when I get back, see you later Mr.. S
He cant be playing that wild stuff, got to strictly stay with the spirituals.
Why you talk like a boss.
Well son, I'm not anybody's boss, but I am the head of boathouse if that's what you mean
You sound like a boss.
Well, it's my job to make sure the van does their job. How's that?
Fine. if you ain't my boss.
My Dad is the only boss i got.
I don't like to be sassed. Hey, you think Mozart was easy?
I got to pee...    Well, I'll let you deal with that.
Go on there, how about that we're going to be on radio
Hey guys, Vern is here.
Let's go. Oh Shit. What? Come on. Let's go play. Mr. S. has gone. It's kind of. Look, I don't feel good.
Whats up Vernon, how you doing? ********i don't feel good.
Well blessed are lazy for they shall get nowhere. Don't try that stuff on me.
Vernon Stop, It's not enough. It is nothing. I said it's nothing. It's nothing.
I see something.
Stop. Don't touch it like that. Where, where you Get that?
A man died and he left it to me. A guitar Man. A Killer Diller.
And you know, ain't nobody ever died and left me. Nothing
Well I wish he hadn't ....play it.
No it's not for now. It's for when we play real music. It's for when we played the blues man
Vernon, Stop it. Stop it. Vernon,  put it down,
Vernon, give me that, it. don't touch it. Vernon
Damn it    Vernon,
Vernon,  What are you doing?
I ain't got all day.
Here we go, well have to just give it a whirl.
More like water.
You know, like water.
You guys can play! Oh my goodness. Good Looking out for Wesley.
Okay. I get It's
Fine!
It's Mr. S, ... we was just starting to sound good,
Woohoo, shake that ass, shake that ass, we going to be on radio!!!
Shanita please, alright.
You ever did it with a fat man
Man look there is nothing wrong with a man of size.
Yeah, I agree. I love fat man. So grateful.
That's my girl
Bad chicks, see the
You don't got the meat, you cant feel the heat!
Good morning ******* you are on K W R T,
We'll be right back after this brief break when we're joined
By the global defenders of the world. Valid zone.
Alright kids, go on in, come on now ***********
Let's get this thing in gear, is a a live show.
Got to watch your back kid.
Hello everybody and welcome back to. Good Morning Charlie.
We have the noble pretenders in the studio this morning
And they will be playing ballads. Big Founder's Day ceremony this weekend.
So If you're ready, take it away. Kids.
Hold on, Hold on,
This is LIVE!!! One, two, three. Four
Vernon, come on...Wesley
Vernon, come on...Vern, Vern, oh Vern
Lets do it
Hello...These are my kids.
Tune in
Morning, Listen up!
We are very excited about our studio,
Thank you,Thank you, Thank you, the global defenders of the throne
Raising the roof at K W R T,  That's it folks. now to the news
Not Bad... Not Bad at all.
I seen this one before. Is he a the one that goes RRRRRRR,...Yeah
I thought so, hey look , you can't hold still.
Actually no he can't. He got the grove. You know what I'm saying?
He got to keep going. know what i mean, got to keep rolling.
Vern, you know I'm saying!!
I can use a Band like you on Saturday,  Don't touch him.
All right, Well, I had a band cancel, my club,
So we're a band.
I don't need no God squad
No  We played the blues
I don't think so...
But thanks. Anyway, I got to go
Got to vamoose... the blues.
Come on y'all. Let's play Judge Bushay...now...Vernon. You with me?
Yeah!
That was not the noble freaking contenders
Ah ah, That was the Killer Diller Blues Band
Blues  Band
Let me tell you something,...you are  going Saturday night. What? What?
Show is at 10 clock. .....What?
Don't want to have a seat.
Sit down, how you doing I'm Wesley Benfield
Hello there
Stop light
You got to explained things to him, that's all
You have to have a little patience
Not the two fingers. The whole damn hand. Vernon
What so funny dog, you got corny, and that was funny
Bless this man
Got him good.. what no...
I want My Daddy to see us play. Oh yeah, sure. Vernon,
Here you go J R ,That's a long way from the orphanage,
Jr. This is Vernon Jackson.
Jules Vernon Jackson... nice To meet you J R.
Okay people this is it, the big time.
Is this impressive or what? My gosh,
You got a chance to... is this where they play basketball.
Now remember, we're going to be playing for a lot more people.
Wesley, Wesley, Have you talked to Mr. Seer, no...
We are he's christian band, but I'm tell him what we going to play  He'll be a freaking out
Okay. Let me ask you another question. How are we going to get there?
I got a plan!
You have a plan,   I didn't know you had a plan that Just
Okay. You got. If you could just find a mustard seed of faith.
This Plan sucks, man. Man, you gonna mess around and get us right back to jail.
Oooowoohh, my call baby Oooowoohh
This is my best tube top, it is Rip. Now Wesley.
Where is he? I have no idea.
All right...I know i look good
Where you get that suit>...its my daddy's
Shaking him first, right? That's good. You Just gotta. Relax man.
Yeah man is kool, is kool.
Relax... its all good
Whats going on
Alright
I'm hot...I know it is...right here, you want me to back it in.
I'm right here. I'm standing right here.
Guitar player, go on go on...
Sorry were late... raise some hell
Alright lets stay for one more
You all ready?
Vernon, ready?
Lets go back...  He's going to go crazy. lets do it.
Vernon?, Vernon answer me. Dammit.
Peee time
I got to pee, in a short break well be right back to shake a tail feather.
In the bushes...yeah
Open this damn door
Who you looking for?
Vernon, where is he?
You must be as father welcomed
I was about to put one foot in the door, doubled up your act, and I've watched burden.
Mr Moker, I had heard that you give people about a 150, 200 bucks when it's packed like this
And you know since we brought everyone in, posters were hung up all over town.
Mr. Moker, I was wondering if you might give us a cut.
Mr. Moker... I was wondering... if you might give us a cut of the door,
Who the hell are you?    the roadie.
How come I never heard from you again
Because I went to jail. Defendant, your honor,
You went to jail defending your guitar
And it's a good thing. you look good enough to eat up on that stage.
What are y'all doing?
Vernon? Vernon, come on gimme a minute.
Why can I stay here?  Because I'm getting a little.
Would you just go on inside for a minute please? Come on.
No, I got him, I got him, I got him,  you promised
What's up rocking boy....yo leave him alone dog.
What's the matter? You cant stop that rocking.
Well Ned. This is a fine mess.
Just in time for founders day,
You're going to go on stage, you're going to play one song and that's it. It's over.
Come on boys, lets get a move on, i got a date with ????
Hey johnny,  going to be a man and sign . For eight  this time.
Well going for 4 weeks this time.
Whats your name sport?
You going to answer me or what?
Well you're going or not going. Oh,
Jackass
Hi, Mr. Jackson, I'm  	Dr. Gwen Bradley
What have you done to Vernon .
He don't even recognize me.
His medication is still wearing off. He arrived in a highly agitated state. No one could control him
I can control him.
He can't be around people.
We tried calling you. The deputy even went out to your house.
Well, I was out looking for Vernon.
All night?... Yeah.
Well, I had to pull over and sleep some.
Has Vernon been tested,the BSC or the aberrant behavior checklist.
Maybe in school.
Mr. Jackson. I would like to test Vernon.
I suspect that he has a high functioning degree of autism.
Vernon needs to learn how to interact. He needs to learn how to read social cues.
Takes time and patience, but it can be done.
And Mr. Jackson, I think that keeping him at home is not the answer.
Yeah, man, i tell you what, it sure was fun, greatest night of my life
Well I hope it was worth it. This house is closing.
Deermont says we have to play founders day since in the paper... where we going to go?
SOB
We just don't give up.
What did he do to you? He ain't got nothing but good for me. I just want to talk
You can't talk to him, cause they got him locked up and said
That's how you treat your friends,
You in the habit of leaving them behind in a club so they can get their ass whooped.
How do you like it? By? if I whooped your ass. Huh? How'd you like that?
I need to talk to Vernon Jackson. only family allowed, I'M sorry.
Can I just talk to a doctor on. I can explain what happened. Please.
You can leave your name and number to me.
Vernon come on, is me
Come on Vernon, what do I Gotta do?
I'm sorry. I'm really, really sorry.
I never should have left. You like that?
Come on Vernon, what do you expect men?
I cannot take care of you all the time. Every minute of the day.
I got to go.
Started all this. Didn't work out. But
Remember I told you my mom died.
I just tell people that,
She left me,
So if you don't want to talk to me, Vernon, that's fine.
Joined the freaking club
Where she go,
I have no idea
Alright we've got to get out of here.
Like I tow the Plymouth, you want to drive.
Come on, man. We got to go right now and everything. Beige and karma. dessert Beige
Oh my God,... come on baby
Easy....easy
Go. go. go. go. ....STOP!!!
Did we get away from them,... Yeah we did.
Nice car,....Yeah... I borrowed it
I'm just borrowing and I'm going to give it back
Where are we going,... taking you home Vernon, then I got to go.
Go where, don't know.
Why aren't we playing... where they play basketball?
If I go down there, those people, they gonna put me away.
I want my daddy to see us play
Vernon, I can't do it. I'm sorry. No,
We used to watch him play basketball.
No Vernon. You just told me. Okay. I can't do it.
Maybe someday.
All right Vernon. Come on then, you want to play. All right, let's go. Come on buddy. Let's go crop up.
Thank you very much, Welcome, one and all
We're here to celebrate 149 years of christian fellowship and service.
Well, let's get things started off by bringing on a group of kids whose lives have been transformed by the Ballard experience.
The noble defenders of the word.
Everyone.
If you want to see your son come to the field house right now!... Where they play basketball
Just don't look up. What? We meant to say, please, Mr. S
What are you doing? Can't you see were playing?
Sorry, Mr. S
You know you're going to be arrested. I know, but I made a promise to Vernon.
For love...
You guys ready? No! Take that robe off...  I told you he'd be back.
Yo. Y'all take them robes off. You bring the shirt back, right now... yes sir.
You guys ready to get crazy? Show this people who we are. Yes we do
Come on up here Mr. S, Mr. Ned Seer, the man who put all this together.
Isn't this band...Tremendous.
Oh Thank you, thank you
But , This is our last concert.
Sad. The powers that be. Have other plans.
Uh, yes we do. We do. We have big plans for them.
Why we're so happy for their success. Then we want to share the glory.
We're going to send them on a little tour
I want them gone ASAP... tell her
Well get ready you are going on tour... BOTA house baby
Congratulations man. We got to talk about your plans for BOTA house.
Hey Daddy!
This ain't no van , man .... Raymond you want to drive
3rd gear sticks a little bit, just eased off that clutch, you'd be all right.
Okay
I'm going to take real good care of my promise.
Got my word. Well its in him and is Has got to come out.
I didn't know you'd be good boy. Now. All right. Wesley here. He's the boss now. So you listened to what he says,
But you my daddy...Yeah, I'm always going to be your daddy, Son
You go on, Boogie Oogie... Bye Daddy
Lets move, man... that's right
We're towing the Plymouth      No Vernon that's not what bands do
Bands ride together to the gig... 10-4
Ladies & gentlemen, for the first time in Kansas city. please Welcome.
The Killer Diller Blues Band