This is the fourth fire this summer.
Benji...
Hello...
- Hey!
- Is that why you called me here, Ben?
What is the new boy?
- Alisha!
- Does this boy have a name?
He just moved here.
I watch them train
with Bryce every day.
- Bryce Hunter?
- The gorilla that Bryce Hunter hates you?
Bryce Hunter hates you!
You're fantasizing about him, aren't you?
Ben! Hello...
- Are you still in the land of fantasy?
- Oh, he did.
♪ They made a statue with us ♪
♪ and they set it on top of the mountain. ♪
♪ Now tourists are coming
and is staring at us. ♪
♪ People from the city are coming ♪
♪ to have some fun. ♪
♪ How much fun! ♪
♪ They will name a city with our names. ♪
♪ and then they will say everything
is our fault. ♪
♪ They're going to throw us one dying soon, ♪
♪ they will make it organized ♪
♪ because they have experience in this. ♪
♪ To live in the den of thieves, ♪
♪ digging for the answers between the pages. ♪
♪ and it is contagious,
and it is contagious, ♪
and it is contagious. ♪
♪ We wear our scarves like a loop, ♪
♪ but not because we want eternal sleep. ♪
♪ And although some of our parts
we barely use ♪
♪ slave labor keep it for yourself. ♪
♪ To live in the den of thieves, ♪
♪ digging for answers between pages. ♪
♪ and it is contagious,
and it is contagious, ♪
and it is contagious. ♪
♪ They made a statue with us,
they made a statue with us ♪
♪ Tourists come to stare at us. ♪
♪ The marble of the statue
designated for the Gods ♪
♪ They made a statue with us,
they made a statue with us. ♪
Okay, let's get out of here!
- No, Allison, wait.
- Oh, you cannot command Her Majesty.
- Is he the boy who...
- you are chasing...
you chase, all summer long?
I just admire him from afar.
You admire him every day
and not that far away.
You're a persecutor, a gay pursuer!
I'm not a gay persecutor.
Okay, we have to be in rehearsal.
Will you sing with us or not?
Give up. I will not sing in front of people.
Oh, God, he's leaving.
I will not follow you,
as you follow him.
All right!
See you at school tomorrow.
Enjoy the latter summer day.
Tim Wyman.
It is.
What?
Do you even know if he will study
at this school.
How can I know this?
And you will chase him every day?
- This is him!
- Who?
Blue shoes.
Nice ass.
That ass is the tip.
- He's a pretty good ass to them.
- Honey!
Okay, class, let's get started.
Welcome to Spanish Level 3.
My name is Mr Langdon.
I'm a student intern, but Mrs. Guerta
will be on hand to help us a lot.
Senor Langdon?
- Yes miss...
- Krista. My name is Krista Norman.
Yes, Krista.
Signor Langdon, how do you know
so good Spanish?
Yes, thank you, miss.
My parents and I lived in Colombia,
when I was a child.
So you can ask me
questions in Spanish.
What will you ask, for example... you.
Sir...
Benjamin, Ben Bentley.
All right, Benjamin. What would you like
to ask?
Where did you buy your...
shoes, Senor Langdon.
Very well, Benjamin,
but you didn't "buy",
Where you "bought" your shoes.
Someone else?
Okay, by the way.
Senor Langdon?
Can I ask you...
How is the Spanish "fagot"?
Excuse me, sir?
This is Spanish, 3rd year.
Don't we have to learn more
lingo this year?
Yes, there are a few words about...
There are a few words... that one can
to use... to say...
- meaning...
- And what is its name...
"mariposa" ("butterfly")
It's called "Mariposa".
Okay, now let's get started...
I'm tired of chasing him
every day.
I just have to go and meet you.
Watch out!
Oh my God! Oh!
Hell, you bastard!
- Hold on, I'm coming down!
- What's your problem?
I am learning now. I am incomplete.
- Tell me it's not broken.
- I don't know, but maybe my ankle is.
- You're bleeding, can you go?
- Of course I can't help without help.
- Okay, how do we do that?
- Just grab me from behind and pick me up.
I guess we have to jump to
the nearest house and ask for transportation.
- No, your house is across the street.
- My house?
Yes, well, let's go.
- Is there anyone home?
- My parents are away for a while.
Why... Okay, I hold you, I hold you.
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
- You're bleeding. It must be cleaned.
- I am fine.
- Give me the keys.
- You will not drive my car!
- To ride with that foot? Give me the keys.
Break my car and I'll kill you.
Hole! Hole!
- Change gear.
- The gear?
- Go to second.
- What to do?
Push the connector
and then lever forward.
- Who doesn't know how to change gears?
- Gay men? Probably.
- Do you know at least some brand of car?
- Yes.
Bentley, Bentley, but I don't know anything
more about them.
So, Benjamin, you know my name
and my address.
Ben, just Ben.
I'll tell you Benjamin.
You can't train at least
one week.
- And we need to call your parents.
- We are friends...
- roughly.
- My parents are in Switzerland.
Well, we have to call
to your parents, which is...
This is the boy who scares me.
He is my best friend.
- Ben Bentley.
- Tell him Benjamin.
I'll get my mother to call
to his parents.
That's great!
The Fettucines Alfredo are almost ready.
- I think they are enough.
- Can you cook?
Indian superpower!
Hey, can you bring a pillow
and my clothes from my room upstairs?
Yes of course.
Thanks.
- Love this song.
- Yes.
You sound great!
Try. I'll stop it.
Maybe I should prepare the tub
to change into clean clothes.
- Want to help me with this?
- Yes of course.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
Your bathtub is... ready.
Cool. I'll call you later.
Okay.
I guess usually
you don't spend your evenings so much.
Rarely heterosexual,
that are in the bath.
You really are...
What is it like to be gay?
Like you. To be...
- the way you are.
- Hetero.
It must be hard for you...
I mean... with sex.
Probably because of these difficulties.
I came out into the light.
- I understand...
- Really?
Sweet, you look good athlete with rich
parents and a sports car
understands what it's like to be me?
Okay, I understand people are judging you.
- You won't hear from me.
- Sorry...
- I know I shouldn't have...
- No problem.
Would it come to light again?
Before... before I admit it...
they invited me for a night's sleep.
These guys knew...
that I will not cause trouble,
but when I came out into the light...
they stopped.
But I... I wanted... to mean
something for someone.
I couldn't do that,
if I hide myself.
And I did it anyway.
And did that work?
Not yet.
Look, I have to go home.
Maybe you'll feel lonely, I'll watch
to rest a little and come back in the afternoon.
- Really? Will you do it for me?
- Yes, if you wish.
I'll go... first... clean up a bit in front.
- Look, Benjamin, I'm sorry...
- Your clothes are on the bed...
What is this observation for?
To make sure you don't disappear again,
like you've been doing all week.
Have Alison?
I'll take a shower.
Make a note of it.
Mom!
- What are you doing?
- Dear...
you and I need to talk.
- What? What you mean?
- Alison?
I told you, we're rehearsing that thing
for the talent show.
Yes, and Alison says you refuse
to sing in front of an audience.
You... talked to Alison?
You go to gay bars.
- I knew it.
- What?
- Honey...
- Oh my gosh.
I want you to read these
and I want you to use these...
I'm so shocked. How long
preparing for this?
I know your age is difficult.
You're so lonely... but if you go...
Oh my God, Mom, Mom I'm not walking
gay bars, only one boy...
- from school, his name is Tim.
- Okay...
No, it's not good. He is hetero.
I hit him with my roller skates and
I felt bad and was taking care of him.
I take care of him. And so much.
- Oh, you like him.
- Oh my gosh.
- You like it...
- Mom, will you stop this...
- Oh my God...
- All right, invite him to dinner.
- You give me condoms.
- I want you to use them, honey, is it okay?
- I love you.
- Hurry up. Get dressed.
- Do I really need to read this. God!
- He doesn't go to gay bars.
- All right.
Take care of some boy. From school.
- He is allowed everything.
- He doesn't miss everything. Relax.
Okay. Where did you get to with him.
- I gave him condoms.
- Are you serious?
If I told you I was gay,
you would not do it.
I'm sorry, you're not a lesbian.
You are not a lesbian.
Jane, you said you drove a Ferrari yesterday.
- Oh, really?
- Ferrari!
She saw you at the traffic light.
- I can't drive that kind of car.
- Is this your friend Tim's car?
- Tim, what's the big problem?
- Not a big problem.
When Jane saw you
was during school hours.
Oh, Ben!
Are you running out of school?
- Mom's not like that...
- Under Tim's influence, right?
- Quite clearly...
- You're lying, running away from school, Adam...
- From now on, you are punished. From now on.
- For what?
- Without computer!
- All right. And only at home!
You're not going anywhere, dating
with no one until we tell you the opposite.
- This is not fair...
- It's fair.
I hate you!
- Do not walk away...
- No, don't, don't act like that...
- What?
- Hello, friend.
- Listen, I just wanted to...
- Are you going to brag now?
God, don't tell me you're fucking
Krista Norman as we speak.
She left.
We quarreled a lot.
Yes, what dispute?
The guy you left me with
with blue balls.
Wouldn't you like to apologize to me?
Well...
would you like to come here?
Maybe we will continue,
what we started?
- Yes, of course, I mean, well...
- Goth.
I'll close now.
- Hi...
- Hello.
I... uh...
You can kiss me if you want...
- Are you sure...
- See for yourself...
Are you okay?
It was my first kiss...
Haven't you been with other guys?
Get ready for your second.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Are you okay?
My parents are coming home.
Calm down, there's still time.
Oh, no, no, my parents.
I'm being punished right now.
Hey, listen, listen...
- About last night...
- No, Tim, I understand...
Hey, hey, hey. You are amazing.
I just want it to be
only between you and me.
Right?
Yes, I just don't want people to think of me
about being gay when I'm not.
You're not... gay...
On one condition.
What is it?
Call me.
I'll call you.
♪ Occasionally, ♪
♪ if I could describe the need
in simple words. ♪
♪ There are so many things in history, ♪
♪ that I have never told ♪
♪ and the feeling is very cool. ♪
♪ With this shadow of life
it's hard to agree ♪
♪ I need you so much here
to help me see ♪
♪ my reflection in the mirror: ♪
♪ Who can this be? ♪
♪ and the dangers we encountered,
what they did to me. ♪
♪ Because every day and everywhere
there is someone who needs me, ♪
♪ beyond my own shadow. ♪
♪ The word that came to me today ♪
♪ that all my friends are gone. ♪
♪ There was no one left standing next to me ♪
♪ to save me from those wounds,
who once bled. ♪
♪ Bring your word, ♪
♪ bring your poison, ♪
♪ bring the knife that pierces my face. ♪
♪ Bring the pain, ♪
♪ bring the difficulties, ♪
♪ bring the name that burns me. ♪
♪ And all I need is ♪
♪ is to see that you are breathing. ♪
♪ And all I want is not to
you argue with me. ♪
♪ It was so hard,
it was so lonely, ♪
♪ and all I want ♪
♪ to let me in
in the shadow of your life. ♪
♪ It's hard to breathe, I still have it
need you here. ♪
♪ So help me see ♪
♪ my reflection in the mirror ♪
♪ Who can this be? ♪
♪ and the dangers we encountered,
what they did to me. ♪
♪ Because every day and everywhere
there is someone who needs me, ♪
♪ beyond my own shadow. ♪
Are you ready?
Ready to learn something new for you?
You are bad.
My mother insisted, and my father had
unnecessary place here.
My occupation can be
a little clammy.
This is my studio.
You have many secrets.
- This is fascinating!
- Oh, i do not know...
You have to be proud of that.
It certainly should.
You are amazing!
Take her!
- Really?
- Yes.
Really.
I think too...
that you have to sing in the talent show
with Alison's group.
- Yes?
- Yes.
I'll sing if you introduce me
to their parents.
- My parents are out of town.
- Again?
- Do they ever take you with them?
- I do not interfere with them, neither do they.
You are every teenager's dream.
But I had to go to Mexico
City, with my mother's family.
How was it?
Beautiful. Friends,
who I met,
they took me to the Popocatepetl volcano.
- Popo... what?
- Pop-cat-cock. It's a volcano.
With that Spanish accent
do you know the language well?
Perfect.
Then why do you study Spanish in school?
Easy Six.
- Oh, cheater.
- Yes and what?
Tell me something in... Spanish.
- I'm not your trained puppy.
- Come on, Tim.
Something good.
- Calling me a fagot is something nice?
- What?
- I'm not...
- You were there that hour...
Senor Langdon...
- Yes.
- Did I change?
I laughed because Mr Langdon
blushed like a virgin.
"Mariposa" means "butterfly" sort of our "fairy",
there is nothing offensive about this,
- unless you take it out of context.
- In Bryce's context, it's insulting.
You can't be serious.
Oh, hi, you must be Benjamin.
Yes, ma'am, I came to pick up
something from Tim...
Hey, what's up, Benjamin.
Ah, here's your notes.
Thanks, uh... what's that smell.
These are my mother's cheerleaders.
They are great.
Hey, Mom, can Benjamin
stay for dinner?
Oh, of course.
Yes, of course, Benjamin.
Dinner will be ready in 20 minutes.
- Ready for that?
- My homework is written.
God bless us and this food
in the name of our God Jesus Christ. Amen.
- Tim keeps his friends a secret.
- Mom!
I'm just saying it's nice to be
meet one of your friends.
And so charming.
Do you know his other friends?
His boyfriend?
Of course he knows Krista.
Yes, she's really great.
It is very popular.
What about you, Benjamin?
Which is your... beautiful girl.
I have a boyfriend.
It's very tasty. The food.
If I can find a restaurant that
offers so much delicious Mexican food,
I'll eat there every day.
They will make a fortune. Maybe you should
to open such a restaurant, Mrs. Wyman.
Oh, thank you, Benjamin.
Hello.
They don't want me to see you anymore.
Yes, but you see me...
Yes, but they don't let me
to see you more.
- I thought I liked them.
- Yes, that's right, Benjamin.
But they are also Catholic.
Hey Tim, hello.
- Is everything alright?
- Give us a minute.
Tim, maybe they just need it
time to realize it.
You will not fool them with your nonsense,
how authentic my mother's food is.
Okay, they won't see me again.
I knew it would.
So stupid.
Everything will be as before...
Oh, so, what if
caught us together?
- We'll figure out something if...
- That's not funny.
They will look at me
different now.
Why I invite a gay boy to dinner,
instead of your girlfriend.
- They will wonder.
- Stop it.
Tim, we can do that
to work. Got it?
We will be careful.
- Oh, is that Tim? I want to congratulate him.
- Oh, no, no, no, Mom...
Then tell me what to do...
Is this Khrista?
His boyfriend.
Oh, but I heard you...
Do you think I'm deaf?
Benjamin...
Really?
He was...
I was sentimental.
Come on, back. Go, go girl.
Here we go. Away from them.
- Hello.
- There is no one around.
- Great.
You're so sexy.
- And a little pot.
- You like me...
Yeah, but... Aren't you tired of hiding,
and not be like normal boyfriends?
For my parents' sake, I told you.
We do what we always do we did.
Who do you like more, me or Krista?
I like you more.
Yes, but who are you sleeping with?
Why with Krista?
I sleep with you.
Then drop it. Why do you need
when do you have me?
- You make it so hard.
- It's even harder for me.
The last birthday present.
I broke up with her.
Because of you.
- Because of me?
- Yes.
I like you.
And I want you.
No matter what happens.
The key to your home?
No, it's not right.
A romantic gesture, Benjamin.
- Tell me something?
- Yes?
Is that right what you told me
for the word "mariposa".
Of course.
Come on, say it again.
This is not at all offensive.
What does it mean?
Means: Teach me to fly,
my beautiful butterfly.
- So I'm a butterfly...
- Yes, yes.
You are a beautiful butterfly.
Oh my gosh! God, fire!
To split! Run there!
- Look what I found.
- What? Where did you get it from?
Bryce. He was there. He was watching us.
- Bryce?
- I ran into him, after we parted.
- He started the fire.
- What if the cops find us?
If Bryce was there, we're screwed.
- Tim, we're not...
- Yeah, we're fucked.
How could you do this to me?
I have not done anything.
This is who we are.
We, you, are one and the same.
I am not like you!
I have no parents who support me
no matter what.
I cannot live among the people who will
laughing and pointing at me constantly.
I'm not like you and never will be
to be. I have to hide.
You can't hide forever.
Don't act like Bryce.
He hates himself so much,
that he hates the whole world.
Fuck that. I can not.
Do not touch me.
I can't handle it.
Ola, Mariposa!
Seriously? Is this the best,
what can you do?
Stop it, look, Bryce,
don't create problems right now.
Oh no, you two "maripos" are the ones
you have a problem.
This means "butterfly". So much!
You just say "butterfly".
Senor Langdon, he made you a fool.
In fact, it's pretty sweet,
if you think about it.
- What the hell, motherfucker?
- Seriously?
- The baby cried.
- All right, everybody calm down.
I will not calm down. That you saw us
together, that's not what Bryce wants
- Come on, come on.
- Let's see how you do without a lighter.
- Enough!
- Give me the lighter!
Fuck you!
Let's make a deal. You're closing
mouth for us and we remain silent for you.
- Tim...
- We're done, Benjamin.
Everything is over.
Go away.
♪ I know what you're doing,
I see it very clearly. ♪
♪ I only feel the salty taste,
when I drink your tears. ♪
♪ You made me listen to the stars. ♪
♪ The black holes that surround you
did you think I'd find them? ♪
♪ I believed in your confusion,
completely torn. ♪
♪ It must have been yesterday
or the day I was born. ♪
♪ There's not much to check,
nothing was left to hide. ♪
♪ You can't be serious,
to ask me why. ♪
♪ Goodbye... ♪
♪ I can hardly breathe,
I can't find air. ♪
♪ I don't know who I'm fooling,
imagining you care. ♪
♪ And I can leave you waiting
like a fool another day. ♪
♪ I don't think it's worth the price,
it's worth it the price I would pay. ♪
♪ But I think about it again and again
anyway. ♪
♪ It occurred to me,
I even said it out loud: ♪
♪ change of opinion
is a friend of the fool. ♪
♪ Either I rise or I just fall ♪
♪ every time you enter the room. ♪
♪ Please do not enter the room. ♪
Hello?
He's dead, Ben.
My father is dead.
Please come. I need you.
A funeral?
Please?
Are you traveling to a funeral?
How do you know?
Professional eye.
Nobody looks sadder,
when it comes to a funeral.
Because it's the night before Christmas,
and you're flying right now...
not to mention the headache.
Everything is clear to you huh?
At the expense of the establishment.
It will help you.
Believe me, I have problems too
with the headache.
How did I do?
Yes, I'm traveling to a funeral;
I'm Jace, by the way.
Your nameplate says Jason.
Cruel bureaucracy.
I told them to write to Jace,
but they said I was confusing people.
Where do these things come from?
Any store?
If they had told me, I would have been alone
to buy it.
I'm... I'm Ben. Bentley.
If you were in our department, you would have
Benjamin plate.
- Yes, everyone calls me Ben.
- Ben be.
Only three letters. Very efficient.
Uh... tell me how it happened,
that you work at Christmas?
That is my only duty
is to serve people.
And serve drinks.
Where are you from, Ben.
Chicago.
Chicago...
But... I'll be in Houston in two weeks.
You know, we're forbidden
because of company policy, let's invite
meeting passengers.
- Right.
- Yes, that's right. I'm telling you.
But I can invite anyone.
You understand me... but
I could help you, Benjamin.
When Mom died... it was him
very sad.
He just started to go off.
But the worst part is, and I realize it,
that when I lost him too,
I started to go out too.
There is no.
Do you remember what you told me,
when we broke up with Tim and I was
sad for months?
- "Get over it!"
- Exactly.
Honey, I know you're sad now,
but if you continue like that,
it will hurt even more.
I'm glad that you're here.
Me too.
Do not walk away.
- You are here anyway.
- Come to Austin with me.
It's much more liberal there.
You shouldn't be gay there
to hide.
As you do, though.
- Are you sure about that?
- Think about this.
No more grumbling about the snow.
A new beginning after the case of the one
a Chicago loser.
- Is not...
- You'll be with your best friend again.
We need to find an apartment.
- Thanks, Ben.
- Everything is fine, everything is fine.
- I'll get the car.
- Let's go.
Hello?
I happen to know that funerals
are not made before New Year.
Jace, hello.
Thanks. Thanks for calling.
So, when will you see me?
Do I have the right to speak at all?
I just don't believe in waiting.
I also learned something about funerals.
The hard way.
Yes of course.
Okay.
Oh, God, that's not a good idea.
- Hold on...
- Oh, I'm getting up, I'm getting up...
I have to skate alone.
- Let's see if this is a great idea...
- All right.
I'll keep you light,
until you take it alone
I hold your hand.
We may be in a bit of a hurry,
if you get it.
- How was high school?
- It was not a very good experience.
You couldn't come out?!
Well, it wasn't me - him!
It was great for a while.
- Someone after him?
- Of course. Homophobes, heterosexual...
All the wrong choice.
- Hello?!
- Oh, well, well, well...
Does not apply to attendees.
Because I, on the other hand,
I can pick them well.
- Watch out.
- The gremlin's lair.
Oh, hello. Who is this?
This is Samson or Sam in short.
Hello. Oh, you mean
hello?
Say hello.
May have passed his exam.
- Now let's feed him.
- I will not bother you.
Biographies?!
Creators, poets...
Serial killers.
Hitler. I've read this book too.
- What a coincidence.
- I like to read about people's lives.
Oh, of those tiny bottles.
Tiny bottles
are very comfortable.
It's good that you get all this stuff
for free.
No, it's not safe for free.
Promise me the sheets and pillows
will be from the airline.
Let's drink about it...
and a new friendship.
Cheers.
- Explain to me why you are still alone.
- I'm not.
I have Sam. He never leaves me alone.
- I don't like loneliness.
- Seriously.
Steward.
You're gone for days. You sleep every night
n different bed.
This does not inspire confidence in anyone
boyfriend, a human being.
I can handle it.
To keep things... fresh...
It's not so bad...
Not for me.
I wanted to tell you personally.
- Sleeping pillows?!
- They won't help you much.
- You're driving me crazy.
- Right?
And how is morning #3?
So I never want to leave.
Then... why don't we make it official.
Given, let's become "officially" boyfriends.
You're cute.
I don't know if I do
I'm a boyfriend material.
Why don't you let me judge.
I'm older and smarter, remember?
That's what you say.
It was easy for you.
Because I'm a steward?
Maybe this restrains you?
Will you fly to Austin?
No way.
I'm thinking of transferring there
next semester.
It even scares me a little.
You tell me this move
will I be startled and run away?
Why?
Do what you have to do.
We will invent something.
Got it? God, you're great.
- Because of the exams?
- They are today.
Hi, woman
You are forbidden to rejoice,
when I'm so sad.
Then you need a drink, if so.
- I'm sick of listening to you...
- She needs that...
- Hello?! "She" is right here.
- And the weekend is set...
Will you join us?
You have no exclusive rights
this weekend.
He is waiting this weekend,
so come on!
Blowing it... dear.
Yes, I'll blow it!
- Hi, Anthony.
- Hi, Vako.
Vako is wrong because
his boyfriend is not here.
I wanted to call you last night, but that's it
turned into a nightmarish night.
You had to work,
as I understand.
No, but my sister is out of town
and I had to take care of Sam.
- Yes, you've been terribly busy.
- Come on, you love Sam.
But I also love my boyfriend,
which I have not seen in a month.
- Let me explain...
- We'll talk later, okay?
What?
Damn it. It was rough.
Didn't you have to drink beer somewhere?
Do not worry. I'll call you
later.
Well, sure enough
ruin my surprise, huh?
- I'm such an idiot.
- Fortunately, I'm the best boy in the world.
Wait! Does this surprise mean...
- what I want?
- Oh, I'm here, aren't I?
This is technically no surprise, because
you friend always surprise me.
I'm moving to Austin.
Which means I moved to Austin.
I have an apartment in Clarksville.
- And you were going to tell me when?
- Today, before you hang up my phone.
- Yes, I'm sorry.
- And after he apologized...
- I have one last surprised.
- Oh, I don't deserve this...
No, you don't deserve it, but I love you
anyway.
Paris. During Christmas break.
- I was so bad with you...
- Yes, it was.
So you owe me a favor.
Whatever.
I'll choose when. For whatever it is.
- Here we are.
- Here?
Does this "duck" mean?
- Fox.
- Mmmm, go.
- Welcome, gentlemen.
- Thanks.
- This one?
- Yes, especially for us.
Did he say Texas?
I think in French that means
that I want my promise right now.
- What?
- Are you scared?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
One year later
Honestly Tim, you have to move
from Jace, officially.
I have a great roommate,
I only have two months left,
before for a taste of the real world.
Exactly. Jace is your real world.
You are, anyway, constantly
together. I am only...
- interfering roommate.
- Is that important?
- What?
- Yes, the real world. Do not interrupt me...
- What is tight?
- Oh, God, don't turn!
Benjamin!
- I... Are you really?
- Yes...
Are you visiting?
- I study here.
- I thought you were in Chicago.
I have to go.
Benjamin, wait!
- What do you want?
- I don't know, let's talk, I guess.
I can not.
Look, I know you're mad at me.
I'll get out of your way, but...
Here, take this. I'll call you one
in the evening and we can... communicate a little.
- How do you know I'm not going to throw it away?
- I'm leaving now.
Wait.
On one condition.
Your sketchbook. Let me look at it.
He was right, Benjamin.
For which?
For many things.
Give me back the sketch later.
Your standard is standard!
Last year we were in one class
in chemistry. It took him a lot to recognize me.
And then what?
Tim, he asked about you...
where are you, how do you drive her...
And you said...
I told him I'm in Chicago, but I didn't
met a year after that.
What should he do if he calls?
Think of Jace.
Oh my God. Not like having sex on the phone
with him.
What?
- What?
- I... I think...
that he has something, for example
like a little uncle.
No no no. No!
- What exactly do you mean?
- Someone older and flush with money.
Luxury.
Probably bidding money.
Do you think a guy with his ass,
will hang with a rich old man,
just because of his personality?
- Hello?
- How is it?
Okay... uh... thank you.
Thanks for picking me up.
Where are you?
- I... had...
- No.
No, Tim. I mean, where was he?
Lord, five years is a long time, huh?
Yes, something like that.
Look, I'll answer every question,
who you want. With you.
Come on, face to face.
I do not think so.
Why? Aren't you dressed?
You lie in your bed alone
shorts.
Benjamin Bentley, did you train?
God, what the...
What are you doing here? How did you find me?
I found Alison in the phone book.
Come on!
Don't relax.
Come in.
Does that mean I can't
to start getting to know you?
It is not a good idea.
Come with me for dinner.
I'm not going anywhere before I get it
some answers.
Okay.
Five years ago...
I went to Garrose for a year...
to run away from you...
from Bryce...
by all.
And by myself, including.
- Are you heterosexual in Austin?
- Not exactly hetero.
It's easier to be gay here.
Wait. Are you gay now?
Just sleeping with some guys
to navigate, but yes.
And your parents?
They are no longer in my life.
What about you?
Chicago was just... was it a lie?
Keep me away?
No. I was there the first year.
Daddy?
This is Jace. We are together
for a year and a half.
I guess I deserve it.
I was thinking of seducing you tonight.
I told myself I would do anything
to bring you back.
- Now I'm kind of... ashamed.
- Tim... Tim, I...
I'm glad to see you again...
but I'm afraid of you.
This is new territory for me.
So... you want me to drive it slow.
Okay.
We'll drive it slow.
Until recently.
Okay, Ali knew all the time,
that Tim was studying here and she said nothing.
Maybe she just tried
to protect you.
- I'm a big boy.
- How would I know.
I called him to return his sketchbook.
So... so you're planning
should I meet Tim?
I hope so.
I told him you weren't at work today.
Okay. I just think it's important
he should look at the two of us as a couple.
Are you jealous, Jace Holdon?
Speaking of now,
I also had a similar problem.
Lets hear.
Uh... about 6 months ago...
on the flight to Boston, she was nervous
a traveler named Erin.
It was... sweet... a younger boy...
but he was terrible and had to hold
his hand throughout the flight.
I don't think I know him.
Well, when we landed, he invited me
get me a drink.
- And you... you... are gone.
- Almost...
Even when I mentioned you,
he was still trying to kiss me.
And he was really sexy,
I won't lie...
I definitely wanted it, but...
I made my choice,
that I want you
And didn't you?
I didn't.
But part of me wanted it. And you can
to try to understand me.
I'm just old-fashioned.
And I only want you.
And I believe you.
Delivery.
Pizza! You have to be Jace?!
- And you're probably Mister Abercombie.
- I'm Tim. Nice to meet you.
Tim! What a surprise!
Hey, I decided we could all be
friends... with pizza.
Or Thai food?
God! This is Italian!
- Italian!
- Look at this place!
- That's good, isn't it?
He took my crutches and left me
on the beach with those girls.
Who are the girls? Those you flirt with?
Yes, but someone else helped me,
after escaping.
- I don't want to remember that.
- Some welding happened there.
Benjamin! A gay man who doesn't understand
about cars, just hit the jackpot!
I heard you do too.
I understand what you're really asking.
His name is Eric.
He was a friend.
He died last year
and bequeaths everything to me.
I'm sorry.
But it's a little unusual...
to inherit so much money...
by a friend, I mean.
- Right?
- Yes.
Unless he was your uncle
or something like that...
So... Alison told you
all the gossip.
Eric was old, rich and gay and I should
to be his toy boy?
I don't know, Tim.
This is nonsense.
Eric was a good person and also the best
a friend I once had.
- Didn't he try to do something.
- Oh, try.
But I don't, however.
Did he want to?
Sometimes you can't tell a friend,
that you love him.
I want to tell a friend like him.
And like you, Benjamin.
And now I want to be a friend
with both of you.
If you give me a chance.
Sorry, Tim's out of town,
and Benjamin teaches.
And when they're out of town I want...
Tim and Jace get along well.
No, it's not.
Okay, fine, I promise, lunch on Sunday.
I will come. I love you.
I have to close.
I have to close!
Are you Jace's roommate
or something like that?
No, I'm his boyfriend.
Yes, great!
Believe it yourself.
Look to get my note.
Hey, are you ready for dinner?
- They left you a note.
- A note?
Read it!
Benji, is that a joke?
You didn't expect to see me that soon.
My parents reached out for a ticket.
- Where was last week? In Boston?
- Yes and what?
You think it's... No!
This kid didn't write it.
I haven't even seen it since.
Since when?
How about: "What did we do in this
hotel room! It still hurts my ass.".
- "With love, Erin".
- Nothing has happened.
It is...
I don't even know what that is.
I'm not a fool, Jace.
I've never cheated on you.
What is this?
- Tim.
- Oh, tight Jace!
I saw the kid at our door.
I'm damn sure
that it wasn't Tim.
I don't know what's going on, but if anyone is
under suspicion, it's you.
I was completely honest about mine
friendship with Tim
Friendship?
Are you kidding? I see the way
looks at you when I'm right there.
- Asking you to give him a chance...
- I get the whole picture, okay?
I trust you Ben, I don't blame you...
Benjamin!
I think he's cheating on me.
Do you have anything to do with it?
What? No! What happened?
I was hurt, that's what I'm saying.
He was there in front of the apartment and...
leave a note, Jace denies
I do not know either...
I don’t know what is going on...
Everything is fine. I'll get a beer
and you will tell me what happened.
- I'll take off your pants...
- Well dear.
- I don't want you to sleep with your jeans.
- Mmm...
The Japanese used it as a torture.
I'll always be there for you, Benjamin.
You're awesome.
He was faint.
I'm sorry I blamed you.
Are you calm now?
Well well. Hey.
I'm just a friend,
who supports you. Remember?
We'll put you to bed...
Echo?
Tim?
You're not a gay pursuer,
you know this.
Hello.
I was... uh...
I would...
If I want something from you is to
you practice honesty.
You've been busy.
Eric?
Yes.
He is...
beautiful.
Hey what are you doing?
Stop it, stop it, stop it...
I slept with Tim.
I knew it!
As soon as he told me,
that you will pay,
I realized you did something stupid.
- "Stupid" is too much.
- How about: "Have you lost your mind?!".
- Better "stupid".
- I do not understand. What about Jace?
I do not know. He's in Chicago.
Do you still love him?
- Yes of course...
- You have to deal with him.
and put a distance between you
and your past.
Tim is not my past.
Yeah he hurt me before, but...
I love it.
And it's probably stupid...
I can't explain why, but...
I love it.
Yes, but you can't have both.
If Ronnie Adams walks in the door now,
my heart will leap.
But we have a chance, right?
Life went on.
Except for Tim.
It's different for me.
Excuse.
See. You and the rest of the world
you see the spoiled, arrogant athlete.
I see the boy whose parents
they were giving him trouble,
they didn't realize how talented he was,
he is brilliant who showed me
that he needs me.
Yeah, I know Jace loves me and stuff, but...
we are still together...
he was fine when we met,
he will be fine also if we break.
Flat.
Flat. Ben...
Ben.
Everything will be fine, Allison.
- Do you go to school here?
- Leave me alone!
You're not from the countryside.
You study here.
I get out of here.
You guys decide
threesome problem.
- Benjamin, wait?
- Enough lies, Tim.
I was stupid enough to believe you.
And now, I lost the Jays.
I told you I would do anything
to bring you back.
- You wanted to believe.
- No!
You wanted this relation...
No, I had to realize he never did
will not fall for someone like this!
Why would you think that?
Because of you!
What's wrong with us?
My life is so fucked up
when you show up.
- What else is left between us?
- A lot. Trust me.
You're a damn coward.
Congratulations!
It's for your own good. Talk about it.
I'm going to the party.
Congratulations, Ben.
I want you in my life, Ben.
- I can not...
- I need you.
I slept with Tim.
No...
You... sometimes you do things...
You have to hate me.
No...
Look, that would be very easy.
I had enough faith that we would fix it
things between us
before you run to Tim's bed.
I've always admired...
of your courage to go out
in the 9th grade light.
Seriously.
But when it comes to proving,
who are you really...
it turns out that was the last one
a real risk you took.
So much, you were so scared of...
everything.
I'll do it.
Excuse me...
- Ben, what are you doing here?
- I need to talk to you.
Even if I have to travel all the way
to Chicago to do it.
Hi Jace.
Hi Allison, people are waiting
queued up to board.
Choose: Sit or get off the plane.
We'll sit down. Thanks.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome
aboard the United Airways.
Please walk down the aisle and sit down
in your places as fast as you can.
Look, I don't know what
you're doing here, but I...
Now.
♪ Do I have to change my phone
secretary... ♪
♪ now that I'm alone? ♪
♪ Because now he says "we" ♪
♪ we cannot answer the phone. ♪
♪ And I know that doesn't make any sense, ♪
♪ because you went out that door. ♪
♪ but this is the only way
to hear your voice and so on. ♪
♪ - This is ridiculous...
- Yes it is. ♪
♪ For some reason I just... ♪
♪ Maybe you're outplaying ♪
♪ I am a stronger man. ♪
♪ Enough is enough. ♪
♪ without walking over with my head bent, ♪
♪ I'm so tired of being sad ♪
♪ to cry for you. ♪
♪ And I'm so tired of love songs, ♪
♪ I'm so tired of tears. ♪
♪ I'm so tired of wanting
still be here. ♪
♪ And I'm so tired of love songs, ♪
♪ so sad and slow, ♪
♪ that I can't even stop the radio. ♪
Please,
Please come home with me.
Okay.
You really liked last night?
I spend them all.
Again a headache?
Do you want coffee?
You're kidding, would you bring me some aspirin?
- Are you okay?
- Mmm.
Honey.
Jace!
Are you Ben?
Yes, Ben Bentley.
Jace received a brain aneurysm crisis.
He said his grandmother had died
from an aneurysm.
We managed to keep one, but the other can
to appear at any moment.
Too weak for another operation,
If this happens.
He only offered to those
unexpected circumstances,
to donate his organs.
What does this mean?
That other people will live happy lives
because of him.
He is very weak but wants to see you.
Go to him, right?
Hello dear.
Good afternoon, son.
Honey... you're locked in this hotel
from the month. Let's take you home.
There's nothing left for me, Mom
The Lord took it from me.
I hate it for that.
And he hates me.
No, dear, no.
Because I loved him.
I brought you a fruit cupcake.
Did you bring me a fruitcake?
Mom, what am I supposed to do?
with the fruitcake?
Honey, you can do nothing with it.
The fruitcake is no good reason.
Except as an excuse...
to live.
And you have thousands of reasons to live.
Dream boldly, yes!
You just have to hold your head
high up to the sky.
If you spread your wings, you can fly.
Because now is your time
to shine.
So don't give up on this dream,
thinks you can fly.
So never give up.
Supposedly from that
dreams are made.
This is such a fun situation.
Nobody sleeps, some dream,
no one says if it will ever come true.
Dream boldly, yes!
You just have to hold your head
high up to the sky.
Just spread your wings and you can fly.
Hello. This is Ben. Talk!
Ben, please call me.
I want to make sure you're okay.
Ben, it's mom, your dad and I
we really want to see you.
♪ You are so quiet.
Please, honey, please call. ♪
♪ Ben, Dad, look, I'm going to travel
to Austin next week ♪
♪ and I want to invite you to dinner. ♪
♪ No excuses, okay? Miss you. ♪
♪ Hi, I'm Ben, make some noise. ♪
♪ I'm Alison. Listen, thanks
about my birthday flowers. ♪
♪ I think you will be a better gift.
Call me. ♪
♪ Son, I have to hear you,
pick up the phone, please. ♪
♪ Call me, I need you now. ♪
♪ Ben, it's Brian, I haven't heard you
since the wedding. What are you doing now? ♪
♪ How was Christmas? ♪
♪ It was our first Christmas without you. ♪
♪ You mean so much to me,
for her father and Karen. ♪
♪ I love you. ♪
♪ This is Ben Bentley. No guarantee. ♪
♪ You can run, but you can't
to hide Ben. ♪
♪ I keep your promise and I will
they kidnap next Tuesday night. ♪
♪ Dress Up Decently! ♪
- If it's any gay meeting...
- Stop it.
You sound like an elderly uncle.
Get out of my life!
- Oh, shit, Alison told you that...
- The language, sir.
I'm supposed to be your mother.
- Get out of here!
- We're not going anywhere.
- Yes, we're out.
- Do what I tell you.
Listen, Ben, don't give up this time,
because everything is not just perfect.
I love you.
Ben, I loved Jace, but it's been years
and your life is not over.
I... I don't want to go forward.
The last thing Jace would want
is to stay in one place in his memory.
No...
Sorry, I disagree.
Is this something included?
Sorry, it was so high.
Lord, thank you so much
to see you all here tonight.
I'm pretty clumsy in speeches,
so be understanding.
The works on display tonight
are the result of 20 years of work.
I think you've seen "my great"
artwork: Frog floats in a boat.
I painted it when I was 8 years old
and I think they understand why I keep it
something for such a long time.
I owe my creativity
to many people.
Of models, of course,
Executor Eric Canroy,
which meant a lot to me.
He was my father,
idol and just... so much more.
And many people, in fact,
have inspired me, but...
only one kicked me in the ass.
And he did it hard, and...
gave me the courage to earn
his art in light
and put it here.
I want to note that he actually is
is here tonight.
And I would end this weird speech,
thanking him publicly.
Benjamin Bentley.
Honestly, everything is true
very, very complicated.
I know.
Translation, timing and subtitles:
sofiaguy ™, 2018 https://sofiaguy.space