Subtitles by explosiveskull
♪ ♪
♪ Thank you for the music ♪
♪ The songs I'm singing ♪
♪ Thanks for all ♪
♪ The joy they're bringing ♪
♪ Who can live without it? ♪
♪ I ask in all honesty ♪
♪ What would life be? ♪
♪ Without a song or a dance ♪
♪ What are we? ♪
♪ So I say ♪
♪ Thank you for the music ♪
♪ For giving it to me. ♪
It would be amazing
if someone could get these
to the mainland
for the last post.
The pleasure and privilege
will be mine.
Señor, you're the manager.
I need you to stay here
and make sure
this place is ready
for the most incredible
opening party of all time.
Whatever your dream,
Ms. Sophie, we will make real.
SOPHIE:
This was her dream.
I'm just trying
to see it through.
You've done
much more than that.
Yeah, but is it enough?
I wish I could ask her.
I wish she was here.
(HORN HONKING OUTSIDE)
It's collection time.
Let's not be late.
Wait.
She never shows up anyway.
(MAN OUTSIDE SHOUTS IN GREEK)
(HORN HONKING OUTSIDE)
Don't worry.
My mom was late for everything.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
WOMAN:
So, it is nearly time
for the graduating year
to go out into the world.
Supported by their friends
and families,
so many of whom they are
grateful to have in attendance
on this august day.
But first, custom dictates
that I call on
the undergraduate selected
- by his or her peers...
- Sorry, sorry.
...to deliver
the valedictory address.
This year, that undergraduate,
- punctual as ever...
- (SIGHS)
is Donna Sheridan.
(CHEERING)
You're going to do
great things, Donna.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Thank you, Vice-Chancellor,
for everything.
This place
has taught me so much
about friendship,
loyalty, love.
But most importantly,
it's taught me
that the best things in life,
the very best things,
happen unexpectedly.
- Hit it!
- (CHEERING)
("WHEN I KISSED THE TEACHER"
PLAYING)
♪ Everybody screamed ♪
(ALL WHOOP)
♪ When I kissed the teacher ♪
(ALL CHEER)
♪ They must have thought
they dreamed ♪
♪ When I kissed the teacher ♪
♪ All my friends at school ♪
- (WHOOPING)
- ♪ They had never seen ♪
♪ The teacher blush ♪
♪ She looked like a fool ♪
♪ Nearly petrified ♪
♪ 'Cause she was
taken by surprise ♪
♪ When I kissed the teacher ♪
♪ Couldn't quite believe
her eyes ♪
♪ When I kissed the teacher ♪
- ♪ My whole class went wild ♪
- (WHOOPING)
♪ As I held my breath,
the world stood still ♪
♪ But then she just smiled ♪
♪ I was in the seventh heaven ♪
- ♪ When I kissed the teacher ♪
- (WHOOPING)
- ♪ What a mad day ♪
- ♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Now I see everything
in a different light ♪
♪ What a mad day ♪
♪ I was up in the air ♪
♪ And she taught me
a lesson all right ♪
(KISSES)
♪ I was in a trance ♪
- (WHOOPING)
- ♪ When I kissed the teacher ♪
♪ Suddenly I took a chance ♪
♪ When I kissed the teacher ♪
♪ Leaning over me ♪
♪ She was trying to explain ♪
♪ The laws of geometry ♪
♪ And I couldn't help it ♪
♪ I just had to kiss
the teacher ♪
♪ What a mad day ♪
♪ Now I see everything
in a different light ♪
♪ What a mad day ♪
- (GASPING)
- ♪ I was up in the air ♪
♪ And she taught me
a lesson all right ♪
♪ What a crazy day ♪
♪ When I kissed the teacher ♪
♪ All my sense had flown away ♪
♪ My whole class went wild ♪
♪ As I held my breath,
the world stood still ♪
♪ But then she just smiled ♪
♪ I was in the seventh heaven ♪
♪ When I kissed the teacher ♪
♪ I want to hug, hug, hug him ♪
♪ I want to hug, hug him ♪
♪ When I kissed the teacher ♪
♪ I want to hug, hug, hug him ♪
♪ I want to hug, hug him ♪
♪ When I kissed the teacher. ♪
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
She didn't come.
My mother.
Can you believe
she didn't come?
She never comes.
(SIGHS) And every time,
it surprises me.
I have gotta get better
at that.
You give that woman hell
when you get home.
I am not going home.
- Not for a long time.
- Oh.
The old "stay away
as punishment" ploy.
I tried that, but my parents
just rented out my room.
And sold your dog.
No, it's not punishment.
It's the opposite.
It's like a gift to myself.
- Where will you go?
- Anywhere.
Everywhere. (SIGHS)
Life is short,
the world is wide, and...
- I want to make some memories.
- Hmm.
In other words,
- you're leaving us.
- Oh.
I never would.
I was just putting out feelers
for our future.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Come on.
We'll always have each other.
ALL:
Dynamos! Dynamite!
Sleep all day
and whoop all night!
♪ ♪
(LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- Whoa!
- (GASPS)
♪ ♪
Oh, they're so beautiful.
Uh, a little to the left.
Little bit more.
And down just a bit.
Perfect. Good.
Those flowers are beautiful.
- Thank you so much.
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
Sky? What time is it there?
It's early.
I was just thinking about you.
About tomorrow.
- How's it going?
- Oh, you know,
nothing focuses the mind
like the last minute.
- (CHUCKLES)
- But you're ready.
I can't believe
I'm not gonna be there.
Feels weird.
Yeah, but we agreed...
six weeks in New York,
learning the hotel business
from the very best.
It was too big a chance
to pass up.
- Soph.
- What?
- Nothing.
No, it doesn't matter.
Except that it obviously does.
They've offered me
a job permanently.
Oh.
Okay.
- I can say no.
- But you don't want to.
You want to say
the opposite of no.
Yeah, I do.
But you could come with me.
But I'm here.
I'm always gonna be here.
Soph, your mum died a year ago.
And I rebuilt this hotel
in her honor.
She wouldn't want you
to dedicate your life to her.
She dedicated hers to me.
We can't keep
having this fight.
Apparently we can,
until we realize
that there's nothing left
to fight for.
Sky?
Yeah, I know.
I should go.
Yeah.
I'll be thinking of you
tomorrow.
It's gonna be amazing.
Take care, Soph.
Yeah. You, too, Sky.
("ONE OF US" PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
♪ They pass me by ♪
♪ All of those great romances ♪
♪ It's as if
you're robbing me ♪
♪ Of my rightful chances ♪
♪ My picture clear ♪
♪ Everything seemed so easy ♪
♪ And so I dealt you the blow ♪
♪ One of us had to go ♪
♪ Now it's different ♪
♪ I want you to know ♪
♪ One of us is crying ♪
♪ One of us is lying ♪
♪ In her lonely bed ♪
♪ Staring at the ceiling ♪
♪ Wishing she was
somewhere else instead ♪
♪ One of us is lonely ♪
♪ One of us is only ♪
♪ Waiting for a call ♪
♪ Sorry for himself ♪
♪ Feeling stupid,
feeling small ♪
♪ Wishing he had never
left at all ♪
♪ I saw myself ♪
♪ As a concealed attraction ♪
♪ I felt you kept me away ♪
♪ From the heat
and the action ♪
♪ Just like a child ♪
♪ Stubborn and misconceiving ♪
♪ That's how I started
the show ♪
♪ One of us had to go ♪
♪ Now I've changed,
and I want you to know ♪
♪ One of us is crying ♪
♪ One of us is lying ♪
♪ In his lonely bed ♪
♪ Staring at the ceiling ♪
- ♪ Wishing he was ♪
- ♪ Wishing she was ♪
♪ Somewhere else instead ♪
♪ One of us is lonely,
one of us... ♪
♪ One of us is lonely ♪
♪ One of us is only ♪
♪ Waiting for a call ♪
♪ Sorry for herself ♪
♪ Feeling stupid,
feeling small ♪
♪ Wishing he had never
left at all ♪
♪ Never left ♪
♪ At all. ♪
(SIGHS)
(BOAT'S HORN BLARING)
TANYA: The poor girl
is under so much pressure.
The hotel reopening.
We have to be strong for her.
Strong. Absolutely.
- She needs our support.
- Mmm.
She needs bolstering.
Yeah. Well, bolstering's
what she'll get.
What she doesn't need
is you crying
every time someone
mentions Donna.
(ROSIE WHIMPERING)
- (TANYA SIGHS)
- (ROSIE SOBS)
(LAUGHING)
I'm so glad you're here.
Come on.
Let's get this show
on the road.
She's very strong.
ROSIE: I can't wait to see
this hotel you've built.
Well, it wasn't actually me
who built it.
- What's it called?
- (ENGINE STARTS)
The Hotel Bella Donna.
- Oh, God.
- (ROSIE SOBS)
TANYA: So, two of your three
possible fathers can't make it?
SOPHIE: They're all my fathers,
and they have great reasons.
Harry is doing
some huge deal in Tokyo,
and Bill is receiving an award
for being the greatest Swede
of all time.
Maybe it's for the best.
Oh. Oh, I would have been fine.
Absolutely fine.
I'm-I'm very strong.
TANYA: Just tell me you didn't
invite your grandmother.
ROSIE:
Wicked Witch of the West.
She hasn't been seen outside
of Las Vegas for decades.
(HORN HONKING)
You must meet
our hotel manager.
♪ ♪
Buenos días.
Be still, my beating vagina.
SOPHIE:
Señor Cienfuegos,
these are my mother's
greatest friends.
- This is Tanya.
- Doña Tanya.
Hmm.
Your beauty comes not only
from the exquisite structure
of your bones
and the laughter
in your sparkling eyes,
but from the goodness
that flowers within you.
Like a fountain.
Have him washed
and brought to my tent.
Don't think fountains flower,
do they?
Mine does.
SOPHIE:
And this is Rosie.
Madam Rosie.
- Oh.
- (CHUCKLING)
You have the courage of a lion
and the passion of a panther
and the wisdom of a flamingo.
- Are flamingos wise?
- Let the man speak.
We are going to the jetty
to make the welcome
decorations.
Sounds wonderful.
We do our best.
It is all we have.
(ROSIE GASPS)
Señor Cienfuegos.
That means "a hundred fires."
So that's 50 for you
and 50 for me.
- 90-ten.
- 60-40.
80-20.
That's my final offer.
♪ ♪
(BELL DINGS)
(DINGS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
- Uh, excusez-moi.
- (GASPS)
Oh, bonjour, mademoiselle.
Um... uh, je suis
locked out de ma chambre.
- Oh, I don't...
- Uh, je, um...
put my tray out,
uh, dans le corridor,
mais, uh, malheureusement
quand je, um...
turned back, uh,
la porte était fermée.
Et maintenant, j-je need
une, uh, uh...
uh, spare key, uh, uh, pour,
uh, reentrer dans la chambre.
S'il vous plaît, mademoiselle.
Sorry, I didn't understand.
Could you say all that again?
Oui.
Je suis...
Wait a second.
I don't work here.
Well, I should call the police.
I'd rather you didn't.
(SETS PHONE DOWN)
They probably wouldn't
understand my French anyway.
♪ ♪
DONNA:
So, Harry, you work in a bank.
I'm afraid so.
Uh, my father,
more or less, owns it.
I'm fulfilling my destiny.
(DONNA SIGHS)
I'm searching for mine.
I have this feeling
it's in Greece.
Why Greece?
I'll find out when I get there.
Leaving tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
- Yeah.
Right. Better move fast.
Um...
Would you mind carrying your
bag on your other shoulder?
Uh, sure. Why?
Well, 'cause then, you see,
the hand nearest me
would fall straight down,
and mine could sort of
brush against it.
And then I could take
your hand in mine
in a totally natural
and spontaneous way.
Or you could just ask
to hold my hand.
- Of course, that's plan B.
- (LAUGHING)
- (QUIET CHATTER)
- (PIANO PLAYING GENTLE TUNE)
DONNA:
It's not just Greece generally.
It's a specific place.
At the far end,
there's an island, Kalokairi.
And people used to think,
if you sailed on from there,
you'd fall off the edge
of the world.
That sounds like
the place for me.
Of-of course it does.
Absolutely.
Um, but now perhaps we can
change the subject slightly
and talk about the advantages
and disadvantages of us
spending the night together.
(CHUCKLING):
Whoa, okay.
Bold move.
Because,
from where I'm sitting,
I mean, it seems to be
pretty much all upside
with-with very little reason
not to just crack straight on.
Mmm...
My family don't really
react well to foreign romances.
Years ago, my mom
was in Central America,
and she had her heart broken
into a million little pieces.
Right.
Yeah, fair enough.
I mean,
I'm sure you're correct.
DONNA:
Mmm.
♪ ♪
I mean, there is
one more reason, though.
You'd be doing me
a huge favor because...
yeah, this...
this would be my first time.
(LAUGHS, SNORTS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
You're kidding.
No, it's a... a thing
I always say
to make me look cool.
- No, I-I'm not kidding.
- (CLEARS THROAT)
Uh...
(SIGHS) Harry.
We just met today.
Yes, but when you know,
you know.
- When you fall, you fall.
- ("WATERLOO" PLAYING)
And when you're defeated
by love,
you're utterly defeated.
Whoa!
♪ My, my ♪
♪ At Waterloo ♪
♪ Napoleon did surrender ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ And I have met my destiny ♪
♪ In quite a similar way ♪
♪ The history book
on the shelf ♪
- ♪ Is always repeating itself ♪
- (WHOOPING)
♪ Waterloo ♪
♪ I was defeated,
you won the war ♪
Oh, my. (GASPS)
♪ Waterloo ♪
♪ Promise to love you
forevermore ♪
(DONNA WHOOPS)
♪ Waterloo ♪
♪ Couldn't escape
if I wanted to ♪
- Ooh!
- ♪ Waterloo ♪
- (GASPS)
- ♪ Knowing my fate ♪
- ♪ Is to be with you ♪
- (CHUCKLES)
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
Waterloo ♪
♪ Finally facing my Waterloo ♪
♪ ♪
(GRUNTING)
- GROUP: Hey! Hey!
- (GRUNTING CONTINUES)
♪ My, my ♪
♪ I tried to hold you back ♪
♪ But you were stronger ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
- (WHOOPS)
- GROUP: Oh, yeah!
♪ And now it seems
my only chance ♪
- ♪ Is giving up the fight ♪
- (CROWD GASPS)
♪ And how could I
ever refuse? ♪
♪ I feel like I win
when I lose ♪
♪ Waterloo ♪
♪ Couldn't escape
if I wanted to ♪
♪ Waterloo ♪
♪ Knowing my fate
is to be with you ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Waterloo ♪
♪ Finally facing my Waterloo ♪
♪ ♪
(SHOUTING RHYTHMICALLY)
♪ So how could I ever refuse? ♪
♪ I feel like I win
when I lose ♪
♪ Waterloo ♪
♪ Couldn't escape
if I wanted to ♪
♪ Waterloo ♪
♪ Knowing my fate
is to be with you ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Waterloo ♪
♪ Finally facing my Waterloo ♪
(GASPS, LAUGHS)
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Waterloo ♪
♪ Knowing my fate
is to be with you. ♪
Whoa!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(LAUGHING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING,
RAIN PATTERING)
(DONNA SIGHS)
That was the greatest event
of my life.
But it's been a good life,
you know.
Full of happy things, but...
that was the best of them.
Did you enjoy...?
No, don't answer that.
But did you?
It was lovely.
Thank you.
No. Thank you.
♪ ♪
(QUIET SNORING)
(TANYA SNORTS)
- SOPHIE: Hello.
- Hello, darling.
How's it going down there?
(SOPHIE SIGHS)
There's enough moussaka
for millions,
with moussaka to spare.
I hope you'll be proud.
I already am.
And so are Bill and Harry.
I miss them.
They're really sorry
they couldn't make it.
If it had been
any other date...
I know.
But I have you.
To tell you the truth,
I'm not sure I can face it.
I don't know if I can,
either, but... we still will.
Because it's a special night...
not for mourning,
but for celebration.
(SAM CHUCKLING)
That's how Mom
would have wanted it.
She would have wanted
to be there.
To get very drunk indeed
and dance until she dropped.
(CHUCKLES)
Our dancing queen.
Yeah.
It will get better.
Just not quite yet.
- I'll see you later.
- See you later, kiddo.
♪ So when you're near me,
darling ♪
♪ Can't you hear me? ♪
♪ The love you gave me ♪
♪ Nothing else can save me ♪
♪ When you're gone ♪
♪ How can I ♪
♪ Even try to go on? ♪
♪ When you're gone ♪
♪ Though I try ♪
♪ How can I ♪
♪ Carry on? ♪
- (HORN HONKS)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
DONNA:
Hey.
(SIGHS)
You grew your hair.
It's longer now.
It is a bit. Yeah.
I know we could talk
about that,
but, uh, the ferry
leaves any second, and, uh...
I think great things
are waiting for me.
I prefer it shorter.
(STAMPING)
(SIGHS)
(FOOTSTEPS RUNNING)
(CHUCKLES)
Wait! Wait!
- Please!
- (HORN HONKING)
Don't. Oh, God.
Turn around right now!
It's not too late!
This is great.
I'm just going to follow you
everywhere.
By the end of the day,
I'll have a whole new wardrobe.
I don't think that'll suit you.
I say I can make it work.
I really wanted
to catch that ferry.
There'll be another tomorrow.
Thanks.
DONNA:
Right, uh...
but what would be
really great...
today, not tomorrow...
is if, uh,
somewhere in this harbor
there was a guy.
Young, tall,
dashingly handsome?
He's probably
passable-looking, but...
he has a boat.
And a couple of days free
before he takes part
in a sailing race.
So maybe he can take her
where she wants to go.
- He'd love to.
- (CHUCKLES)
But the sad fact is...
this-this isn't my boat;
I just wanted to impress you.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, okay.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
Jump on. I'm Bill.
♪ ♪
I actually have an elderly
relative on the island
who help...
helped me buy this boat.
There are two beds,
but unfortunately,
- one of them is rather full.
- Huh.
Convenient. (CHUCKLES)
You have one of those smiles
that makes
the rest of the world
smile, too.
(LAUGHING)
It's lucky this trip
is not long enough
for my fragile heart
to shatter completely
when you leave my boat.
Ugh. I get it.
You're one of them.
One of who?
There are two kinds of seducer.
First doesn't actually
like women,
so wants to assert
his power over them,
but the second,
and far more dangerous,
is the guy who genuinely
falls in love every evening,
only to fall out of it again
the next morning.
But as you run away,
you tell her
you're the one in pain
and she's just too much
for you to handle.
Like this?
- (GRUNTING)
- Whoa!
("WHEN YOU WERE LONELY"
PLAYING)
♪ When you were lonely,
you needed a man ♪
- (SCOFFS)
- ♪ Someone to lean on ♪
- (LAUGHING)
- ♪ Well, I understand ♪
- ♪ It's only natural ♪
- (SIGHS)
♪ But why did it
have to be me? ♪
Oh, just like that. Yes.
♪ Nights can be empty ♪
♪ And nights can be cold ♪
♪ So you were looking
for someone to hold ♪
- ♪ That's only natural ♪
- (LAUGHING)
♪ But why did it
have to be me? ♪
♪ I was so lonesome ♪
♪ I was blue ♪
♪ I couldn't help it ♪
- ♪ It had to be you and I ♪
- (GRUNTING)
♪ Always thought you knew
the reason why ♪
- Huh?
- (LAUGHING)
(BILL CHUCKLES)
♪ I only wanted
a little love affair ♪
♪ And now I can see
you are beginning to care ♪
(GASPS)
♪ But, baby, believe me ♪
- ♪ It's better ♪
- (BILL CHUCKLES)
- ♪ To forget me ♪
- (DONNA WHOOPS)
(CHUCKLES, WHOOPS)
OFFICIAL:
Your hair.
It's shorter now.
Well, yes,
I had to cut it for work.
I wonder, could you please
hurry up a bit?
Uh, you see, I've followed
a girl all the way from Paris.
She wrote me a note.
A very kind note.
Saying good-bye.
But when you've found
the only girl you think
you're ever gonna love, it's
gotta be worth one more try.
Don't you think?
It's better short.
♪ Men are the toys ♪
♪ In the game that you play ♪
♪ When you get tired,
you throw them away ♪
♪ That's only natural ♪
♪ But why did it
have to be me? ♪
♪ Falling in love
with a woman like you ♪
- ♪ Happens so quickly ♪
- (CHUCKLES)
- ♪ There's nothing to do ♪
- (GRUNTS)
♪ It's only natural ♪
♪ But why did it
have to be me? ♪
We only just met.
And you're not
that kind of girl?
Absolutely not.
Usually.
MAN (IN DISTANCE):
Hey!
What was that?
Nothing. Uh, um, a seagull.
Now, where were we?
♪ It's only natural ♪
♪ But why did it
have to be... ♪
MAN:
Hey!
Come on!
(GRUNTS, SIGHS)
We're coming!
Hi.
Just checking
you're not in danger,
which you're obviously not,
so we'll be off.
- Uh, my engine is not working.
- Oh.
Oh, that is bad luck.
I-I'll radio for someone
to come and help you.
They should be along soon.
- Bill.
- MAN: Please, please.
There is a woman waiting for me
on the mainland.
Her family,
they not want her to marry
a simple fisherman like Alexio.
They want rich man.
Ugly, fat, big mole on face,
but rich.
But she...
she want me.
And I love her
with all my heartness.
Please help, kind sir
and beautiful lady
with head full of curls.
(LAUGHS)
Well, obviously
we're doing this.
BOTH:
Yes.
♪ ♪
There!
BILL:
I see them. Okay, everyone.
- We're nearly...
- Apollonia!
Whoa! (LAUGHS)
What are you doing?
We could get you closer.
If you love someone,
you're willing to die for her!
Yeah, but you don't have to.
- It's an important distinction.
- (CHUCKLES)
Apollonia!
Alexio!
Aah! Apollon...!
He's just swallowed
a big mouthful of water,
but the basic point
he's trying to make
is that he loves you.
What?
He loves you!
ALEXIO:
Apollonia!
Apollonia! No, Apollonia!
- Apollonia!
Apollonia, come back!
(LAUGHS) Yes!
- Apollonia!
- (INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Apollonia!
- Good work.
- You, too.
Apollonia!
- I love you!
- (GASPS)
Oh, God. I don't think
she can swim, either.
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(WHOOPS)
- SOPHIE: Good morning.
- Good morning. - Morning.
SOPHIE: Oh, good morning.
It's so nice. Guys.
- I'm glad you like it.
- (CHUCKLING): I do.
And these are perfect.
- Everything is.
- Thank you.
It's so good.
It's all so amazing.
If you are happy.
I would be even happier
if you were happy.
No happiness for me.
As you say,
that ship sailed
many long years ago.
But ships turn around.
They come back.
Not for me.
She left. Never to return.
But don't you worry.
I have made my peace with pain.
SOPHIE:
You and me both, señor.
What? What is it?
I'm not sure.
Tell me.
I fear a storm is coming.
(BIRDS SCREECHING)
BILL:
You sure you're okay here?
DONNA:
Yeah, I'll be fine.
I'll come right back
after the race.
But that won't be
for three weeks.
Look at this place.
Isn't it beautiful?
It is, yeah.
What? What's wrong?
Storm is coming.
(CHUCKLING):
It's a clear sky.
Trust me.
Actually, don't.
- But I know I'm right.
- I'll still be fine.
I got a very good feeling.
♪ ♪
(EXHALES SOFTLY)
TANYA: And you and Sam
did all of this?
- We had some help.
- From Sky.
Right. Yes, right.
And there is more.
DONNA:
Hello?
TANYA:
Oh, how did she know?
- How did Donna know?
- What?
That that could be this.
I guess she just...
saw the future.
♪ ♪
♪ I have a dream ♪
♪ A song to sing ♪
♪ To help me cope ♪
♪ With anything ♪
♪ If you see the wonder ♪
♪ Of a fairy tale ♪
- (GASPS)
- (CHICKENS CLUCKING)
♪ You can take the future ♪
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
♪ Even if you fail ♪
♪ I believe in angels ♪
♪ Something good
in everything I see ♪
♪ I believe in angels ♪
♪ When I know the time
is right for me ♪
♪ I'll cross the stream ♪
♪ I have a dream ♪
TANYA:
Mmm.
♪ I have a dream ♪
♪ A fantasy ♪
♪ To help me through ♪
- (SCREAMS)
- (CREAKING, CRASHING)
(GASPS, WHIMPERS)
♪ And my destination ♪
- ♪ Makes it worth the while ♪
- (TANYA CHUCKLES)
♪ Pushing through
the darkness ♪
♪ Still another mile. ♪
Do you think she'd like it?
- Oh, Sophie. (SOBS)
- Soph.
(WIND HOWLING,
THUNDER RUMBLING)
Oh, no.
He said this might happen.
(WOMAN SHOUTING IN GREEK)
- (MAN SHOUTING IN GREEK)
- (THUNDER CRASHES)
(LAUGHING)
- (CRASHING)
- (GASPING)
(HORSE NEIGHING)
Hello?
(HORSE NICKERING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(NEIGHING)
Hey.
- Whoa.
- (NEIGHING)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(NEIGHS)
(DONNA SCREAMS, GASPS)
(NEIGHING)
Wait there, okay?
I'll be back, okay?
(WIND WHISTLING)
(THUNDER CRASHES, RUMBLES)
Stop! Stop.
Can I help?
I've got it.
Tie off the ropes.
You got it?
- You got a plan?
- Oh, absolutely.
I'm a trained veterinarian.
- Really?
- No, no. I'm an architect.
- But don't tell this guy that.
- (GRUNTS)
- (NEIGHING)
- Whoa. Okay.
DONNA:
Whoa. I'll distract him.
You grab the halter.
Good plan.
What's the halter?
(DISTRESSED GRUNT)
Just talk calmly.
Oh, easier when I'm calm.
All right, my friend.
Storms are scary.
And I wish I was home
and dry right now, too, but...
believe me,
if it came down to a choice
- between leaving you...
- Whoa!
...and helping you,
- there is no choice at all.
- Whoa, whoa. Whoa.
Good boy. Good boy.
- (SHUSHING QUIETLY)
- (SOFTLY): Good boy. Good boy.
♪ ♪
So, uh, we've walked
the entire island.
I still haven't seen
where you live.
In a shack on a hill.
(DONNA LAUGHS)
And what the hell
are you doing there?
Uh, I don't know.
Running away, I guess.
Back home, everything
was lined up for me.
A great job and just...
you know,
my whole life mapped out.
I wanted to take a break
before I signed up to it.
How about you?
(TAKES DEEP BREATH)
I have absolutely nothing
mapped out.
And no clue
what the future holds.
Enough walking. Let's ride.
(DONNA LAUGHS)
(QUIET, INDISTINCT CHATTER)
So, how come you're here
all alone, saving horses?
Uh, I've been traveling
all my life.
My dad was never
in the picture,
and my mom's always on tour.
Oh, she sings?
Sweet as sugarcane.
You know,
there's some great stuff here.
This dress would look
very pretty on...
You really don't know me
at all, do you?
MAN:
♪ Okay! ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
- (CHUCKLING)
♪ Kisses of fire,
burning, burning ♪
♪ I'm at the point
of no returning ♪
♪ Kisses of fire,
sweet devotion ♪
♪ Caught in a landslide
of emotion ♪
♪ I've had my share
of love affairs ♪
♪ But they were nothing
compared to this ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I'm riding higher
than the sky ♪
♪ And there is fire
in every kiss ♪
Oh, my God.
♪ Kisses of fire... ♪
God! This whole place
is incredible.
I am definitely
staying here forever.
Yeah, your mom
wouldn't miss you?
(CHUCKLING): No, she's not
that kind of a mom.
Oh, I'm-I'm sorry. I didn't...
Oh. Oh, this isn't a sob story.
I'm fine.
And it's not easy
being a mother.
If it was, fathers would do it.
Well, I wish
I could stay here, too.
- Uh, when do you go back?
- Hmm?
To your fully programmed,
good job,
- short haircut life?
- (LAUGHS)
- I have a week. Um...
- (CHUCKLES, CLEARS THROAT)
Listen, about what's
waiting for me back home...
- Wait. Hang on, hang on.
- No, there's something...
(WHOOPS LOUDLY)
(DONNA CONTINUES WHOOPING)
(CHUCKLES)
I'm definitely staying here.
Excuse me.
- Are you the owner?
- My son the owner.
He had to buy bar
because no other place
let his band play.
Hello.
So, how can I help you?
Firstly, you're all awesome.
Oh.
And second,
I'd like to sing here sometime
with my group.
You have good voice?
Oh, sweet as sugarcane.
Then let us hear.
Oh, no.
(CHUCKLES) Not just like that.
Here on island,
everything just like that.
It's the path to happiness.
You think too much,
you get unhappy.
Thinking at all
is pretty much...
- (LAUGHS)
- ...a mistake.
(SAM LAUGHS)
Well, in that case...
Uh...
Okay.
♪ Take it easy ♪
♪ With me, please ♪
♪ Touch me gently ♪
♪ Like a summer
evening breeze ♪
♪ Take your time ♪
♪ Make it slow ♪
♪ Andante, andante ♪
♪ Just let the feeling grow ♪
(BAND JOINS IN)
(CHUCKLES)
♪ Make your fingers ♪
♪ Soft and light ♪
♪ Let your body be the velvet ♪
♪ Of the night ♪
♪ Touch my soul ♪
♪ You know how ♪
♪ Andante, andante ♪
♪ Go slowly with me now ♪
(LAUGHS)
♪ I'm your music ♪
♪ I am your music
and I am your song ♪
- ♪ I'm your song ♪
- ♪ I am your music ♪
♪ And I am your song ♪
♪ Play me time and time again ♪
- ♪ And make me strong ♪
- ♪ Play me again ♪
♪ 'Cause you're
making me strong ♪
♪ Make me sing,
make me sound ♪
♪ You make me sing
and you make me ♪
♪ Andante, andante ♪
♪ Tread lightly on my ground ♪
♪ Oh, please don't
let me down ♪
- (LAUGHING)
- (SAM CHUCKLES)
You are hired.
- Really?
- You are very, very, very hired!
- Yes!
- Mama.
- Come on. Come on.
- (WOMAN SPEAKING GREEK)
DONNA (LAUGHING):
Oh!
- ♪ I'm your music ♪
- ♪ I am your music ♪
- ♪ And I am your song ♪
- ♪ I'm your song... ♪
♪ I am your music
and I am your song ♪
♪ Play me time and time again ♪
♪ And make me strong ♪
♪ Make me sing ♪
♪ Make me sound ♪
♪ Andante, andante ♪
♪ Tread lightly on my ground ♪
♪ Oh, please don't
let me down ♪
♪ Andante, andante ♪
♪ Oh, please ♪
♪ Don't let me down. ♪
- SAM: Okay. Great.
- (DONNA CHUCKLING)
- (SAM GRUNTS)
- (DONNA WHOOPING, LAUGHING)
SAM:
Right.
DONNA (CHUCKLING):
I just don't think you know
- what you're doing.
- Uh...
I'm hoping, if I keep pulling
on these two bits of wood,
we might eventually bump
into land.
Oh, okay.
There's another little island
over there.
I thought we might go
for a picnic.
Where's the food?
Oh, you're going to catch it
- on the way.
- (LAUGHS) Oh.
Uh... (CLEARS THROAT)
So...
we haven't talked
about last night.
- No.
- You should know
that I never do that
that fast.
I mean, hardly ever.
Well, sometimes.
A bit recently, in fact.
But on the whole, not.
I thought it was miraculous.
Um, I'm gonna say
something here,
and you should shut up
as I'm saying it
because you'll think
I'm crazy for a while.
But gradually, you'll...
...you'll realize I'm right,
and then you'll spend
the rest of your life
thanking me
for saving so much time
and just getting
straight to it.
Well, I'm ready.
I wasn't joking yesterday.
I was serious.
I want to stay here.
And I think you should, too.
I think we should make a choice
to do something radical
and wonderful.
To live in this
extraordinary place
with someone...
with someone miraculous.
I told you
you'd think it was crazy.
I just don't think
it's that simple.
Nothing is.
Everything is.
When you break it down.
(LAUGHS)
I don't think it's crazy.
(CHUCKLES)
That'll do.
For now.
(DONNA LAUGHING)
(CAMERA CLICKING)
♪ ♪
(DONNA WHOOPING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
- It's done.
It's done. We're done.
It's over.
Sophie, Sophie, my darling,
everything will be okay.
Apart from the fact that the
welcome decorations are down,
the garden is a swimming pool,
the swimming pool is a marsh.
We can take care
of all of that.
The party's still a day away.
What party?
I just got a call
saying that, because
of the storm last night,
no flights have come
into Athens at all.
So there will be
no millionaire guests
at the not-that-grand opening.
Which is just as well,
because the band
can't get here, either,
because the ferries
aren't running.
So there will be no one
to entertain
all the people
that aren't here anyway.
It really is over,
and I've let everybody down.
No, no, no, that's not true.
Especially Mom.
Nothing you do
could ever let her down.
Trust me, I know.
How-how do you know?
Because I did let her down.
("THE NAME OF THE GAME"
PLAYING)
♪ I've seen your eyes ♪
♪ Tender like mine ♪
♪ Only a week ♪
♪ Since we started ♪
♪ It seems to me ♪
♪ In a short time ♪
♪ I'm getting
more open-hearted ♪
♪ I was an impossible case ♪
♪ No one ever could reach me ♪
♪ But I think I could see
in your face ♪
♪ There's a lot
you can teach me ♪
♪ So I wanna know ♪
♪ What's the name
of the game? ♪
♪ Your smile and the sound
of your voice ♪
♪ Does it mean anything
to you? ♪
♪ Got a feeling,
you give me no choice ♪
♪ But it means a lot ♪
♪ What's the name
of the game? ♪
♪ I was an impossible case ♪
♪ Can you feel it
the way I do? ♪
♪ Tell me, please ♪
♪ 'Cause I have to know ♪
♪ I'm a curious child ♪
♪ Beginning to grow ♪
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
- ♪ And you make me tall ♪
- (GRUNTS, GASPS)
- ♪ And you make me feel ♪
- (GROANS, SIGHS)
♪ And you make me show ♪
♪ What I'm trying to conceal ♪
♪ If I trust in you ♪
- (GRUNTS)
- (BLEATING)
- (GASPS, SCREAMS)
- ♪ Would you let me down? ♪
♪ Would you laugh at me ♪
♪ If I said I care for you? ♪
♪ Could you feel
the same way, too? ♪
♪ I wanna know ♪
♪ Oh, yes, I wanna know ♪
♪ The name of the game. ♪
SAM:
I went after her.
Of course I did.
Chased her all the way back
to the farmhouse.
SAM:
Wait, Donna!
Donna! Donna, please.
- Please just listen to me.
- (GROANS)
- Love to.
- You will?
Yeah, of course.
I'll listen while you answer
three questions.
Are you engaged
to that beautiful woman?
Yes.
And did you tell me about it?
No.
And do you seriously think
- I could ever forgive you?
- Please, Donna.
- Go.
- Donna, please just listen to me.
That is enough listening! Go!
(DOOR SLAMS)
♪ No more ♪
Carefree laughter
Silence
Ever after
♪ Walking through
an empty house ♪
Tears in my eyes
♪ Here is where
the story ends ♪
This is good-bye
♪ ♪
♪ Knowing me, knowing you ♪
- ♪ Uh-huh ♪
- ♪ There is nothing ♪
♪ We can't do ♪
♪ Knowing me, knowing you ♪
- ♪ Uh-huh ♪
- ♪ We just have ♪
- ♪ To face it this time ♪
- ♪ This time we're through ♪
- ♪ We're through ♪
- ♪This time we're really through ♪
♪ This time we're through,
we're really through ♪
♪ Breaking up is never easy,
I know, but I have to go... ♪
♪ I have to go,
this time I have to go ♪
- ♪ This time I know ♪
- ♪ Knowing me, knowing you ♪
♪ Is the best I can do. ♪
♪ ♪
(CRYING SOFTLY)
(QUIET CHATTER)
And now we turn, please,
to clause 47, item 12.
The wording here is unclear,
especially in reference to
"amortization
of accrued assets."
- (MAN SNORING)
- As the assets we discussed
are tangible, I advise
the more legitimate phrase,
"depreciation,"
be used henceforth.
And furthermore...
- MAN: You are bored, Mr. Bright.
- (SNORTS)
On the contrary.
Nothing I like more
than a good...
contract negotiation.
Especially one
that's been going on
for more than 14 hours.
This deal will make
your company
- the number one in Europe.
- (POURING DRINK)
Worth taking time, I think.
Absolutely. 14 more hours.
Bring them on.
That's a nice picture.
Oh, my wife and daughter.
You have family?
I have a daughter.
Best thing in my life.
So, to continue.
Uh, clause 47, item 12.
As we said, the wording
is most unclear...
She really is
the best thing in my life.
This you already said.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I just realized something.
What, Mr. Bright?
What did you realize?
It's no use climbing the ladder
if you're on completely
the wrong wall.
The contract is marvelous,
by the way.
Make any changes you like.
Just sign. Sign, sign, sign.
WOMAN: His skill in writing
is matched only by his charm,
his sailing expertise
only by his charisma.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please join me in welcoming
the wonderful Bill Anderson.
(CROWD MURMURING QUIETLY)
(APPLAUSE CONTINUES)
(APPLAUSE QUIETS)
Oh.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you for the award.
Um, I'd like to thank...
...my mother, Alma.
Thank you. Tack, Mama.
(CHUCKLES)
- And, uh...
- (BUZZING)
I also have a wife.
- She's lovely.
- Hello?
- How's he doing?
- His best.
It's one thing
to get your twin brother
to take your science exams
at school,
but this is a different deal.
It was his idea.
He knows something I forgot:
that family
is all that matters.
Just don't let him tell
the goat story.
There's a very amusing story
that I think you will find
really, really, really amusing.
It's about a goat.
(ROSIE GRUNTS)
ROSIE: So many bags.
I should have known.
- TANYA: It's not that many.
- (ROSIE GASPS)
- ROSIE: Donna?
- TANYA: Donna?
- (SCREAMS)
- Donna!
Donna!
(SCREAMING, LAUGHING)
Oh, my God,
I see what you mean.
(SINGSONGY):
This place is paradise!
I'm so glad you're here.
What's happened?
Where's the hot architect?
Oh, turns out
he was lying to me.
He's not an architect?
He's engaged.
- To someone else.
- (ROSIE GASPS)
(CHUCKLING):
And she looks beautiful, and...
now he's gone back to her.
I hate it when they do that.
- Okay.
- Aw.
DONNA: So I've been sleeping
in this farmhouse.
I don't know who owns it,
but it's the most beautiful
place in the world.
It also has a horse.
TANYA: Yes, very romantic.
We're taking you home.
ROSIE: Uh, not before
a fabulous performance
by the greatest girl band
in the world.
- Yes! Whoo!
- We've got all of the gear.
- Where are we playing?
- Oh, no, no, no.
I can't. I can't.
I'm not in that mood.
Oh, but it will put you
in that mood.
Of course it will.
The floodlights,
the greasepaint.
- (LAUGHING)
- The adrenaline of the crowd.
A thousand descendants
of great Greek warriors
cheering and clapping furiously
as the irresistible beat
transforms their bodies into
pulsating pillars of flesh!
(WHOOPING, LAUGHING)
(SIGHS)
(ROSIE CHUCKLES)
- (MAN SNORING)
- (ROSIE CHUCKLES)
I don't know how
to sing about love
when I'm not feeling it.
Then sing about
what you are feeling.
♪ I was cheated by you ♪
♪ And I think you know when ♪
♪ So I made up my mind ♪
♪ It must come to an end ♪
♪ Look at me now ♪
♪ Will I ever learn? ♪
♪ I don't know how ♪
♪ But I suddenly lose control ♪
♪ There's a fire
within my soul ♪
- (WHOOPS)
- (BAND JOINS IN)
♪ Just one look and I can ♪
- ♪ Hear a bell ring ♪
- Yes, Donna!
♪ One more look
and I forget everything ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Mamma mia, here I go again ♪
♪ My, my,
how can I resist ya? ♪
♪ Mamma mia,
does it show again ♪
♪ My, my, just how much
I missed ya? ♪
- (WHOOPING)
- ♪ Yes, I've been brokenhearted ♪
- Ah!
- That's nice.
♪ Blue since the day
we parted ♪
♪ Why, why did I ever
let you go? ♪
♪ Mamma mia,
now I really know ♪
♪ My, my, I should not
have let you go ♪
- Let's go, girls.
- Okay, okay.
- Excuse me.
- Okay.
(LAUGHTER)
♪ I was angry and sad
about the things that you do ♪
- Mwah.
- (GASPS, LAUGHS)
♪ I can't count all the times ♪
- ♪ That I cried over you ♪
- (GRUNTING)
(LAUGHING)
Yes!
- ♪ And when you go ♪
- (WHISTLES)
- (SHOUTING IN GREEK)
- ♪ When you slam the door ♪
♪ I think you know
that you won't be ♪
- ♪ Away too long ♪
- ROSIE: Donna!
- Donna, look! Let's go!
- ♪ You know ♪
- ♪ That I'm not that strong ♪
- (TANYA SQUEALS)
♪ Just one look
and I can hear a bell ring ♪
♪ One more look
and I forget everything ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Mamma mia, here I go again ♪
♪ My, my,
how can I resist ya? ♪
♪ Mamma mia,
does it show again ♪
♪ My, my, just how much
I missed ya? ♪
♪ Yes, I've been
brokenhearted ♪
♪ Blue since the day
we parted ♪
♪ Why, why did I ever
let you go? ♪
♪ Mamma mia,
now I really know ♪
♪ My, my, I should not
have let you go ♪
(SCREAMS, GASPS)
- Hi, there.
- Bill?
- (CLAPPING)
- MAN: Bravo!
(LAUGHTER)
- BILL: I swear, it's true.
- (LAUGHING)
(LAUGHS)
- My point is...
- I know what your point is.
You don't know
what my point is.
Your point is that
you fancy him.
Mm, you see?
You were wrong.
That's not my point.
It's not that I fancy him.
My point is actually
that I love him
and I want to have his babies
and eventually push him around
in a wheelchair
and scatter his ashes.
I see.
And he likes Donna.
And I don't think
that's very fair.
He can help her feel better.
Do you know
what makes me feel better
when my heart's broken?
Cake.
Why doesn't she
just do that instead?
Just eat humongous amounts
of cake
and leave hot Scandi guy to me?
(QUIET LAUGHTER,
INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I'm going in.
No, you-you're staying out,
sister,
because you love Donna
and you want her happy.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
This is my friend, Bill.
- It's a pleasure to meet you.
- I've heard nothing about you.
- (LAUGHS) Hi.
I brought Donna here
on my boat.
You've got a boat?
He's got a boat?
And then I worried about her,
so I came back.
He worries, he cares,
and he's got a boat.
And now I'm taking her out
to sea again.
Taking her out to sea again...
in a boat.
You don't think I should go?
Are you kidding?
Of course you should.
Tell her she should go.
- You should absolutely go.
- That's what I'm saying.
- ROSIE: I-I'm saying it, too. Go. Go.
- TANYA: Go.
- And do everything I would do.
- Nearly everything. Sorry.
Thanks, guys.
- I'll be back soon.
- TANYA: Bye, darling.
Bye.
(QUIET CHATTER)
Could I get some cake, please?
- Cake over here?
- A lot of cake.
SOPHIE:
He's not picking up.
I can't even tell him
how wrong it's all gone.
Do you think he's just not
hearing the phone?
Or that he's taking it
out of his pocket,
seeing it's you
and deciding not to answer?
It's wonderful that you put
that image in her head.
(WHISPERS):
Bolster. Bolster.
I think his phone's on silent.
I don't even know what
I would say to him anyway.
You would say you love him more
than you love this argument.
- That's really good.
- I know.
I love him more
than any argument.
Ooh.
Just wish he was here
so I could tell him.
Well, I wish Bill was here,
too, so I could hit him.
What did go wrong with you two?
Oh...
Well, there was this
other woman hanging around.
I asked him about her, and...
you know you're in trouble
when the word "just"
comes before the word
"friends."
That's how most
of my marriages ended, too.
♪ One night ♪
♪ I was taking a walk ♪
- ♪ Along the ♪
- ♪ River ♪
♪ When I saw him
together with ♪
♪ A young girl ♪
♪ And the look
that he gave her ♪
♪ Made her shiver ♪
♪ 'Cause he always used to ♪
♪ Look at me that way ♪
- ♪ And I ♪
- ♪ And she thought ♪
- ♪ Maybe ♪
- ♪ Maybe she should ♪
♪ Walk right up to her
and say ♪
♪ Ah-ha-ha ♪
♪ It's a game
he likes to play ♪
♪ Look into his angel eyes ♪
♪ One look
and you're hypnotized ♪
- ♪ He'll take your heart ♪
- (MEN GRUNT)
♪ And you must pay the price ♪
♪ Look into his angel eyes ♪
- ♪ Whoa ♪
- ♪ You'll think ♪
- ♪ You're in paradise ♪
- (MAN GRUNTS)
♪ And one day
you'll find out ♪
♪ He wears a disguise ♪
♪ Don't look too deep ♪
♪ Into those angel eyes ♪
♪ Oh, no, no, no, no ♪
♪ Ah-ha-ha ♪
♪ Ah-ha-ha, ha-ha-ha ♪
It's terribly important
to remember...
♪ Ah-ha-ha, ha-ha-ha ♪
...just what terrible people
all men are.
♪ Ah-ha-ha, keep thinking ♪
♪ About his angel eyes ♪
♪ Keep thinking ♪
♪ Ah-ah ♪
♪ Sometimes when I'm lonely ♪
♪ I sit and think about him ♪
♪ And it hurts to remember
all the good times ♪
♪ When I thought I could never
live without him ♪
♪ And I wonder,
does it have to be the same? ♪
♪ Every time when I see him ♪
♪ Will it bring back
all the pain? ♪
♪ Ah-ha-ha ♪
♪ How can I forget that name? ♪
♪ Look into his angel eyes ♪
♪ One look
and you're hypnotized ♪
♪ He'll take your heart ♪
♪ And you must pay the price ♪
♪ Look into his angel eyes ♪
♪ You'll think
you're in paradise ♪
♪ And one day you'll find out ♪
♪ He wears a disguise ♪
(ROSIE WHIMPERS)
- ♪ Don't look too deep ♪
- (ROSIE GRUNTS)
- ♪ Into those ♪
- (MEN CHUCKLE)
♪ Angel eyes ♪
♪ Oh, no, no, no, no. ♪
BILL: Not a single ferry?
You can't be serious.
I made it all the way
from Stockholm
spending I don't know how much
on a private plane.
You can't tell me now I can't
make it the last few miles.
(SIGHS)
What?
Time has been most cruel
to you, sir.
Your hairline... it disappear.
And your face... it collapse.
I would suggest we swim for it,
but perhaps not.
Men at our time of life?
Sir, in your case,
age becomes you.
As it does the tree,
the wine...
and the cheese.
(LAUGHS)
Thank you very much.
- You're not so bad yourself.
- (CHUCKLES)
I was told you couldn't come.
Why the hell are you here?
I'm a spontaneous person.
(WHISPERS):
No, you're not.
No, I'm not.
♪ ♪
(GASPING)
(LAUGHING)
DONNA:
Oh, that was incredible.
BILL: Do you want to see
what's in there?
Oh, it doesn't matter.
Just getting it
is reward enough.
Really?
(LAUGHING):
No. Are you kidding?
Open it now.
- (TAPPING LEGS)
- Drumroll.
Got it?
(LAUGHS)
- For you.
- (DONNA SIGHS)
You're very kind.
I have at least 18
ulterior motives.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
There is a lovely little
food store back there.
They've got this cake
called baklava,
which is layers of pastry
filled with chopped...
You've had enough.
Somewhere on a boat
on the ocean
with someone that isn't me
is literally the handsomest man
in the world.
Right, except for this guy.
ROSIE:
Jesus Christ.
What kind of island is this?
(WHISPERS):
Take this. Yes, take this.
(TANYA CLEARS THROAT)
Hi.
I just want to be up-front
and say that I
visually enjoy you.
- Oh, that's, uh...
- SOFIA: You.
Man, coming over here.
I'm so sorry. Excuse me.
I'll be waiting.
Hi. I'm looking for...
I know who you looking for,
with your wandering eye
and restless groin.
I should cut it off,
the way you hurt
- that precious angel.
- I know, I know.
But she pick herself up
after you tearing
her heartstrings.
She leave on a boat
with most famous stud
in Europe.
And I would not wait
for return.
Man has so many notch
on his bedpost,
the bed fall down.
It's called karma,
and it's pronounced, "Ha!"
Yeah. I deserve that.
Okay, he's coming back.
Tell me I look good.
You always look good.
You're meant to be
bolstering me.
- I'm sorry.
- So bolster. Bolster.
All right.
You look so beautiful...
Whatever. My point is,
I don't even mind
if you're not rich.
I say...
- Where was that cake, now?
- Just back there.
- Let's go.
- Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
(SIGHS, GROANS)
(SIGHS)
I just wanted to say
it was very nice
when you turned up today.
I'm glad I could help.
Thank you.
(CLEARS THROAT)
- Good night, then.
- Good night.
I was just really sad.
I know.
- Men are pigs.
- All of us.
Which is not to say
I don't like pigs.
I do like 'em.
I mean, I wouldn't want one
as a pet.
Just get over here.
(DONNA LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
BILL: I don't understand
how this gets us to the island.
It's a little trick I learned.
When you're faced
with a problem,
you literally
strap yourself down,
can't get up until it's solved.
Oh.
Well, let's put it to the test.
Too tight?
By no means.
Hey, you remember me?
I'm a man in my 50s.
Most days,
I don't remember my own name.
Perhaps this remind you.
(GURGLING):
Apollonia!
Alexio!
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Listen, everyone.
Many moon ago, this great man
save my life by saving my love.
Ah, it was nothing.
Anybody would have done
the same.
Yeah.
Tough crowd.
These are difficult days
for them.
For all us fishermen.
For many years now,
we do more and more work
for less and less pay.
Now our boats lie idle,
and we drink
in joyless surrender
to our economic fate.
Well, in that case,
maybe all of you
want to come
to a very expensive party.
Totally free.
- A party?
- Yeah.
(SPEAKING GREEK)
(ALL CHEERING)
Yes! And bring your wives
and family!
(ALL GROAN)
Ah, come on.
HARRY:
Uh, just a minute.
I just seem to have, um,
tied this a little tighter.
Excuse me!
Hello? I just...
Anyone? Hello?
(YELLS)
- Need some help?
- (HARRY COUGHING)
ROSIE:
No guests.
Just us and a mountain of food.
I'm beginning to think
my soul mate
may actually be carbs.
Then mine must be wine.
And Sky is mine.
Maybe he's right.
Maybe I should leave
this island.
ROSIE:
Sophie, listen.
Your mother...
was the bravest person
we ever met.
And if she taught you anything,
it's that it's your choice how
to live the rest of your life.
Do what makes your soul shine.
I'll try.
- Nailed it.
- To the wall, baby.
Yay.
SAM:
Mmm.
SOPHIE: It's going to be
a beautiful night.
Mm-hmm.
I wish I had someone
to share it with.
Oh, come on.
- We have each other.
- Yeah.
Oh, I think we've got
more than that.
Take a look.
("DANCING QUEEN" PLAYING)
(CHUCKLING):
It's Bill and Harry.
No!
♪ ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ You can dance ♪
♪ You can jive ♪
♪ Having the time
of your life ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ See that girl ♪
♪ Watch that scene ♪
♪ Dig in the dancing queen ♪
♪ Friday night
and the lights are low ♪
♪ Looking out
for a place to go ♪
♪ Where they play
the right music ♪
♪ Getting in the swing ♪
♪ You come to look for a king ♪
♪ Anybody could be that guy ♪
♪ Night is young
and the music's high ♪
♪ With a bit of rock music ♪
♪ Everything is fine ♪
♪ You're in the mood
for a dance ♪
♪ And when you get the chance ♪
♪ You are the dancing queen ♪
♪ Young and sweet ♪
♪ Only 17 ♪
Whew. (LAUGHS)
♪ Dancing queen ♪
♪ Feel the beat ♪
♪ From the tambourine ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
- ♪ You can dance ♪
- (WHOOPS)
♪ You can jive ♪
♪ Having the time
of your life ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ See that girl ♪
♪ Watch that scene ♪
♪ Dig in the dancing queen ♪
(LAUGHTER, WHOOPING)
(CHEERING, SHOUTING)
(LAUGHTER)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING, CHATTER)
♪ You're a teaser ♪
♪ You turn 'em on ♪
♪ Leave 'em burning ♪
- ♪ And then you're ♪
- (GASPS)
♪ Gone ♪
♪ Looking out for another ♪
♪ Anyone will do ♪
♪ You're in the mood
for a dance ♪
(CHEERING)
♪ And when you get the chance ♪
♪ You are the dancing queen ♪
♪ Young and sweet ♪
♪ Only 17 ♪
ROSIE:
Yeah!
(ALL SHOUT)
♪ Dancing queen ♪
♪ Feel the beat ♪
♪ From the tambourine ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ You can dance ♪
♪ You can jive ♪
♪ Having the time
of your life ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
- ♪ See that girl ♪
- (CHUCKLING)
♪ Watch that scene ♪
- ♪ Dig in the dancing queen ♪
- Ah.
(LAUGHING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Oh, yeah, thank you.
Ah...!
Thank you for coming.
Thank you, thank you.
- Have a look. - Oh!
- ♪ Dig in the dancing queen ♪
SOPHIE:
Hi.
(LAUGHING)
Oh!
Mwah! Yeah!
- ♪ Dig in the dancing queen. ♪
- Look.
Sky!
(CHEERING)
SKY:
Fairly obviously,
- they're not all millionaires.
- I don't care.
And there's no press.
There won't be
- any coverage of the evening.
- I-I don't care.
And I could only book
the worst band in the world.
SOPHIE (LAUGHING):
They're a great band.
And I don't care
about any of it.
- You got here.
- And I'm never leaving again.
I don't care about the job
or New York or anything.
I don't care about anything
that isn't you.
Señor Cienfuegos, uh,
the party is still happening.
I will look after
the fireworks.
Sky is here, and these
are my other two dads.
Of course, it takes
three great men
to create such a woman.
(SOPHIE CHUCKLES)
It's a pleasure
to be of service.
(LIGHT LAUGHTER)
BILL:
Wow.
My God, Sophie.
Look what you've done
with the place.
She wanted
to make her mum proud.
As if she hasn't
done that all her life.
(QUIET CHATTER)
♪ ♪
Excuse me a minute.
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
TANYA:
(CLEARS THROAT) Here's to us.
May the rest of our lives
be the best of our lives.
- Ooh. Cheers.
- Mm-hmm.
You're not drinking.
- She's missing her man.
- Oh.
Which one? (SNICKERS)
Oh, yeah,
that's the big question.
- What?
- Oh, it doesn't matter.
Who want more vine leaves?
Ooh, definitely not.
I'll have some more.
It's the last time.
We leave tomorrow.
- All of you?
- All of us.
Except me.
- Really?
You don't have to.
Really?
That farmhouse on the hill
you're sleeping in,
who you think own it?
I...
I do. Me. (CHUCKLES)
Yeah, I know it's run-down,
but my...
- son is no help.
- (GRUNTS)
He put all his energy
into that horrible band.
They're a great band.
(LAUGHS)
Your ears are cloth.
But, uh, if you live there
and make it beautiful,
you can stay for free.
Donna, seriously, don't.
There is a whole world
out there.
There's one right here.
I'd love to stay.
- I'd love nothing more.
- (CHUCKLING)
And I could do
amazing things with it.
You know, maybe one day,
it could be a hotel.
It could be incredible.
But you hardly know me.
Because I judge
a person's heart
by the way they treat animal.
And you are kind to Hector,
my horse.
And your son.
Who is also an animal.
(LAUGHS)
I'm overwhelmed. I...
I don't...
Excuse me just one second.
Well, I did say
that that mutaka smelled funny.
- "Moussaka."
- Bless you.
(PANTING, RETCHING)
Okay.
Think we know what that means.
(PANTING)
SKY:
Soph. There you are.
I've just been speaking
to this guy.
He's actually a journalist,
and he wants to write
about this place for his blog,
which means
- it could be the start...
- I don't care.
No, I know you keep
saying that,
- but actually it'll...
- Sky. Listen to me.
What?
I have never felt closer
to my mom.
I know.
It's being in this place with
her photos on the walls and...
I'm pregnant.
What?
In exactly the same place
that she was.
Only this time we know
who the father is.
- Soph, you're pregnant?
- Yeah.
I am.
And I have you
and my three dads,
and she had nobody.
She didn't even have
anybody to tell.
She must have been so scared.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
All right. Bye.
- Mwah!
- Bye!
SOPHIE: She wasn't scared.
I know that now.
She knew that she could do it,
- because she wasn't alone.
- (SIGHS)
She had me.
And you have me.
Oh, we can't tell anybody
about the baby.
We have to wait until
at least the 12-week scan.
- Right.
- (DISTANT RUMBLING)
- What is that?
- What?
That noise.
♪ ♪
("HASTA MAÑANA" PLAYING)
♪ Where is the spring
and the summer ♪
♪ That once
was yours and mine? ♪
(LIVELY CHATTER)
♪ Where did it go? ♪
♪ I just don't know... ♪
You're at the party,
but you're not in the party.
I've been dancing.
Just not with you.
Dance with me now.
And never, ever stop.
I gave you your chance, Bill.
I'm asking you for one more.
Well... it's just not
gonna work, is it,
if you haven't learned
from the first time.
Oh, believe me
when I say I have.
I never believe you, Bill.
Your pants
are a raging wildfire
that cannot be contained.
Not anymore. I-I've changed.
(SCOFFS)
For that to ever happen,
something would have to really
break down your barricades,
force you to feel
some real pain and loss
for the first time
in your shallow playboy life.
And that is never gonna happen.
So all we can be now
is friends.
And you're just gonna have
to start getting used to that.
You're very strong, Rosie.
Finally.
(ROSIE SIGHS)
She'd have really loved
all this, wouldn't she?
- Who?
- Donna.
(BILL INHALES DEEPLY)
(BILL SNIFFLING, WHIMPERING)
Oh, my love.
Oh, no. Come. Come here.
(BILL CRYING)
Aw.
♪ Hasta mañana ♪
♪ Say we'll meet again ♪
♪ I can't do ♪
- ♪ Without you... ♪
- ROSIE: Mmm.
♪ ♪
SKY:
Come on, this way.
- Just keep walking.
- SOPHIE: You better not have
some kind of surprise lined up.
(LAUGHING):
No, not at all.
- No. Why?
- I hate surprises.
I thought you loved surprises.
Yeah, but it's already
too much...
the party not happening
and then happening
and then you showing up
and the pregnancy.
- It's all amazing, but...
- Watch out.
I'm so incredibly,
crazy overwhelmed right now
that I don't want anything
remotely shocking
or-or different to happen
in the next decade.
- Yes...
- (SONG ENDS)
- What?
- (CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
Too late.
♪ ♪
Mes enfants, je suis arrivé.
Let the party commence.
(SCATTERED LAUGHTER)
Grandma?
You weren't invited.
That's the best kind of party,
little girl.
SOPHIE:
So, Sky got you here.
No, Sky just helped it happen.
You got me here.
What do you mean?
I've decided to commit
to being...
"a grandmother."
(SHUDDERS)
It's 25 years too late.
I say we move past that.
You know, Soph, being
a grudge holder makes you fat.
So let's just concentrate
on the here and now
and me stepping up
to becoming a good grandmother.
A great grandmother.
Thank you.
No, he's saying that...
Wait. How do you know?
- Sky?
- I didn't say anything.
We agreed. Soph...
I only told Sam
because he's my stepfather,
and also one third
of my real father.
I just told Bill.
He's my best friend.
And I told Harry.
He's father number three.
I told many, many people.
Excuse us,
ladies and gentlemen.
Rosie and I would like
to propose a toast
to the woman
of this and every hour.
- (APPLAUSE)
- Yes.
You're too kind.
- They mean Sophie.
- I know that.
Come on up, Sophie.
- (CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
- Soph!
(ROSIE CHUCKLING)
SOPHIE:
I just want to say,
for a while now,
I have been living
my mother's wishes,
and tonight they've come true.
With this...
and with this.
Great-grandmother.
I'll be leaving that
out of the bio.
And now I can fulfill
one of my greatest wishes.
Ever since I-I was a child,
I've wanted once, just once,
to be a part
of Donna and the Dynamos.
(CHEERING)
You're gonna be so great.
("I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU"
PLAYING)
Do it for your mom, baby.
♪ I ♪
♪ I have known love before ♪
♪ I thought it would no more ♪
♪ Take on a new direction ♪
♪ Still ♪
♪ Strange as it seems to be ♪
♪ It's truly new to me ♪
♪ That affection ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ I don't know what you do ♪
♪ You make me think that you ♪
♪ Will change my life forever ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ I'll always want you near ♪
♪ Give up on you, my dear ♪
♪ I will never ♪
♪ You thrill me,
you delight me ♪
♪ You please me,
you excite me ♪
♪ You're all that I've
been yearning for ♪
♪ I love you, I adore you ♪
♪ I lay my life before you ♪
♪ I only want you
more and more ♪
♪ And finally it seems ♪
♪ My lonely days are through ♪
♪ I've been waiting for you ♪
♪ I'll carry you all the way ♪
♪ And you will choose the day ♪
♪ When you're prepared
to greet me ♪
♪ I'll be a good mom, I swear ♪
♪ You'll see how much I care ♪
♪ When you need me ♪
♪ You thrill me,
you delight me ♪
♪ You please me,
you excite me ♪
♪ You're all that I've
been yearning for ♪
♪ I love you, I adore you ♪
♪ I lay my life before you ♪
♪ I only want you
more and more ♪
♪ And finally it seems
my lonely days are through ♪
♪ I've been waiting for you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I've been waiting ♪
♪ For you. ♪
(CHEERING)
(CROWD WHOOPING AND WHISTLING)
(WHOOPING)
Not bad.
You gotta work
on your breathing,
and you were a little pitchy.
Is what I would say
if I wasn't a loving relative.
Speaking as a grandmother?
- I'm so proud I could combust.
- (CHUCKLES)
You've got glitter
in your veins.
You got it from me.
Now, I need to find Sky,
because he and I
were gonna talk about you.
Where is Señor Cienfuegos?
He'll know where Sky is.
Cienfuegos?
That's an unusual name.
He's an unusual man.
See for yourself.
Ruby!
Fernando?
("FERNANDO" PLAYING)
Mi amor.
México, 1959.
♪ Can you hear the drums,
Fernando? ♪
♪ I remember long ago ♪
♪ Another starry night
like this ♪
♪ In the firelight, Fernando ♪
♪ You were humming
to yourself ♪
♪ And softly strumming
your guitar ♪
♪ I could hear
the distant drums ♪
♪ And sounds of bugle calls
were coming from afar ♪
♪ They were closer now,
Fernando ♪
♪ Every hour, every minute ♪
♪ Seemed to last eternally ♪
♪ I was so afraid, Fernando ♪
♪ We were young
and full of life ♪
♪ And none of us
prepared to die ♪
♪ And I'm not ashamed to say ♪
♪ The roar of guns and cannons
almost made me cry ♪
♪ There was something
in the air that night ♪
♪ The stars were bright,
Fernando ♪
♪ They were shining there
for you and me ♪
♪ For liberty, Fernando ♪
♪ Though we never thought
that we could lose ♪
♪ There's no regret ♪
♪ If I had to do
the same again ♪
♪ I would, my friend,
Fernando ♪
♪ If I had to do
the same again ♪
♪ I would, my friend,
Fernando ♪
♪ Now we're old and gray,
♪ Since many years
I haven't seen ♪
♪ A rifle in your hand ♪
♪ Can you hear the drums,
Fernando? ♪
♪ Do you still recall
the fateful night ♪
♪ We crossed the Rio Grande? ♪
♪ I can see it in your eyes ♪
♪ How proud you were to fight
for freedom in this land ♪
♪ There was something
in the air that night ♪
♪ The stars were bright,
Fernando ♪
♪ They were shining there
for you and me ♪
♪ For liberty, Fernando ♪
♪ Though we never thought
that we could lose ♪
♪ There's no regret ♪
♪ If I had to do
the same again ♪
♪ I would, my friend,
Fernando ♪
♪ Yes, if I had to do
the same again ♪
♪ I would, my friend,
Fernando. ♪
(CHEERING)
HARRY: I'm just saying,
he has my ears.
SAM: And I'm just asking
why you care.
- HARRY: Don't care. Absolutely don't.
- Good.
HARRY: We're all three of us
grandfathers, and that's that.
- It's fine.
- Yes, it's fine.
HARRY:
It's just, over the years,
people have tended to be
extremely complimentary
- about my ears.
- Oh, yeah?
(CHUCKLING): People have
complimented your ears?
To such an extent that I hope
he's inherited them.
- The boy?
- Yes.
- Donny?
- That's right.
Well, he does have lovely ears,
but I've also noticed
that he has rather piercing
blue eyes.
- Really?
- (HARRY LAUGHS) - Yeah.
What about
his beautifully shaped feet?
- Huh?
- You're not taking your shoes off.
- (TANYA GROANS)
- (SAM SIGHS)
- Ah...
- Hey!
That walk gets longer
every time we do it.
Yeah, but it's worth it
for what's at the top.
- (LAUGHING)
- (BILL GROWLS PLAYFULLY)
Fine, rub my tired,
single nose in it.
- Hi. Ciao.
- ROSIE: Ciao.
- SAM: Hey.
- BILL: Hi.
Well, you two look
obscenely happy.
She has turned my frown
upside down.
Eso no es el único
que he levante.
Ah, sí. Yes.
Oh, and I'd like
to introduce you
to the other great love
of my life,
my brother,
Don Raphael Cienfuegos.
Oh, God,
I hope his wife is dead.
Alas, she is,
and I fear I shall
never find happiness again.
Think again, brother.
Come on, everybody.
Let's do this.
You look beautiful, Ruby.
A day to remember, huh?
(VOICE BREAKING):
I wish she was here.
She is.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(EXHALES)
(TAKES DEEP BREATH)
♪ ♪
♪ I've never felt this strong ♪
♪ I'm invincible ♪
♪ How could this go wrong?
♪ No, here ♪
♪ Here's where we belong ♪
♪ I see a road ahead ♪
♪ I never thought ♪
♪ I would dare to tread ♪
♪ Like an image passing by ♪
♪ My love, my life ♪
♪ In the mirror of your eyes ♪
♪ I can see it all so clearly ♪
♪ All I love so dearly ♪
♪ Images passing by ♪
♪ Like reflections
of your mind ♪
♪ My love, my life ♪
♪ Are the words I try to find ♪
♪ But I know
I don't possess you ♪
♪ With all my heart,
God bless you ♪
♪ You will be my love ♪
♪ And my life ♪
♪ You're my one and only ♪
♪ I held you close to me ♪
♪ Felt your heart beat ♪
♪ And I thought, "I am free" ♪
♪ Oh, yes ♪
♪ And as one are we ♪
♪ In the now and beyond ♪
♪ Nothing and no one ♪
♪ Can break ♪
♪ This bond ♪
♪ Like an image passing by ♪
♪ My love, my life ♪
♪ In the mirror of your eyes ♪
♪ I can see it all so clearly ♪
♪ All I love so dearly ♪
♪ Images passing by ♪
♪ Like reflections
of your mind ♪
♪ My love, my life ♪
♪ Are the words I try to find ♪
♪ But I know
I don't possess you ♪
♪ With all my heart,
God bless you ♪
♪ You are still my love ♪
♪ And my life ♪
♪ Yes, I know
I don't possess you ♪
♪ With all my heart,
God bless you ♪
♪ You are still my love ♪
♪ And my life ♪
♪ You're my one ♪
♪ And only. ♪
♪ ♪
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
(RHYTHMIC CLAPPING)
(MUSIC SWELLING)
♪ I was sick and tired
of everything ♪
♪ When I called you
last night from Glasgow ♪
♪ All I do is eat
and sleep and sing ♪
♪ Wishing every show
was the last show ♪
♪ So imagine I was glad
to hear you coming ♪
♪ Suddenly I feel all right ♪
♪ And suddenly
it's gonna be... ♪
♪ And it's gonna be
so different ♪
♪ When I'm on the stage
tonight ♪
♪ Tonight the Super Trouper
lights are gonna find me ♪
- ♪ Shining like the sun ♪
- ♪ Sup-p-per Troup-p-per ♪
- ♪ Smiling, having fun ♪
♪ Feeling like a number one ♪
♪ Tonight the Super Trouper
beams are gonna blind me ♪
- ♪ But I won't feel blue ♪
- ♪ Sup-p-per Troup-p-per ♪
♪ Like I always do ♪
♪ Sup-p-per Troup-p-per ♪
♪ 'Cause somewhere
in the crowd there's you ♪
(CHEERING)
♪ Facing 20,000
of your friends ♪
♪ How can anyone
be so lonely? ♪
♪ Part of a success
that never ends ♪
♪ Still I'm thinking
about you only ♪
♪ There are moments
when I think I'm going crazy ♪
♪ But it's gonna be all right ♪
♪ You'll soon be changing
everything ♪
♪ Everything will be
so different ♪
♪ When I'm on the stage
tonight ♪
♪ Tonight the Super Trouper
lights are gonna find me ♪
- ♪ Shining like the sun ♪
- ♪ Sup-p-per Troup-p-per ♪
- ♪ Smiling, having fun ♪
♪ Feeling like a number one ♪
- ♪ Tonight the Super Trouper ♪
- ♪ Sup-p-per Troup-p-per ♪
♪ Beams are gonna blind me ♪
- ♪ But I won't feel blue ♪
- ♪ Sup-p-per Troup-p-per ♪
♪ Like I always do ♪
♪ Sup-p-per Troup-p-per ♪
♪ 'Cause somewhere
in the crowd there's you ♪
♪ So I'll be there ♪
♪ When you arrive ♪
♪ The sight of you will prove
to me I'm still alive ♪
♪ And when you take me
in your arms ♪
♪ And hold me tight ♪
♪ I know it's gonna mean
so much tonight ♪
♪ Tonight the Super Trouper
lights are gonna find me ♪
- ♪ Shining like the sun ♪
- ♪ Sup-p-per Troup-p-per ♪
♪ Smiling, having fun ♪
♪ Sup-p-per Troup-p-per ♪
♪ Feeling like a number one ♪
- ♪ Tonight the Super Trouper ♪
- ♪ Sup-p-per Troup-p-per ♪
♪ Lights are gonna find me ♪
♪ Shining like the sun ♪
♪ Sup-p-per Troup-p-per ♪
♪ Smiling, having fun ♪
- ♪ Feeling like a number one ♪
- (LAUGHING)
♪ Tonight the Super Trouper
beams are gonna blind me ♪
- ♪ But I won't feel blue ♪
- ♪ Sup-p-per Troup-p-per ♪
♪ Like I always do ♪
♪ Sup-p-per Troup-p-per ♪
♪ 'Cause somewhere
in the crowd ♪
- ♪ There's you... ♪
- ♪ Super Trouper ♪
♪ Lights are gonna find me. ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
♪ ♪