(grand orchestral fanfare
playing)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ ♪
(engine stops)
(gasps, grunts)
♪ ♪
(hisses)
(hissing)
(panting)
♪ ♪
♪ Are you blind
when you're born? ♪
♪ Can you see in the dark? ♪
♪ Can you look at a king? ♪
♪ Would you sit
on his throne? ♪
♪ Can you say of your bite ♪
♪ That it's worse
than your bark? ♪
♪ Are you cock of the walk ♪
♪ When you're walking alone? ♪
- ♪ When you fall on your head ♪
- (whimpers)
♪ Do you land on your feet? ♪
(sniffs)
♪ Are you tense
when you sense ♪
♪ There's a storm in the air? ♪
(chuckles softly)
♪ Can you find your way blind ♪
♪ When you're lost
in the street? ♪
♪ Do you know how to go
to the Heaviside Layer? ♪
♪ Because Jellicles can
and Jellicles do ♪
♪ Jellicles do
and Jellicles can ♪
♪ Jellicles can
and Jellicles do ♪
♪ Jellicles do
and Jellicles can ♪
♪ Jellicles can
and Jellicles do ♪
♪ Can you ride on a broomstick
to places far distant? ♪
- ♪ Familiar with candle ♪
- ♪ With book ♪
- ♪ And with bell? ♪
- (clangs)
♪ Were you
Whittington's friend? ♪
♪ The Pied Piper's assistant? ♪
♪ Have you been an alumnus
of heaven or hell? ♪
- ♪ Are you mean like a minx? ♪
- ♪ Are you lean like a lynx? ♪
♪ Are you keen to be seen ♪
♪ When you're smelling a rat? ♪
♪ Were you there
when the pharaohs ♪
♪ Commissioned the Sphinx? ♪
♪ If you were and you are ♪
♪ You're a Jellicle cat ♪
♪ Jellicle songs
for Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Jellicle songs for
Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Jellicle songs
for Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Jellicle songs for
Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Jellicle songs
for Jellicle cats ♪
♪ We can dive through the air ♪
♪ Like a flying trapeze ♪
♪ We can turn
double somersaults ♪
♪ Bounce on a tire ♪
♪ We can run up a wall ♪
♪ We can swing
through the trees ♪
♪ We can balance on bars,
we can walk on a wire ♪
♪ Jellicles can
and Jellicles do ♪
♪ Jellicles can and
Jellicles do ♪
♪ Jellicles can
and Jellicles do ♪
♪ Jellicles can and
Jellicles do ♪
♪ Jellicle songs
for Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Jellicle songs for
Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Jellicle songs
for Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Jellicle songs for
Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Can you sing at the same time
in more than one key? ♪
- ♪ Duets by Rossini? ♪
- ♪ And waltzes by Strauss? ♪
♪ Ah... ♪
♪ And can you, as cats do,
begin with a "C"? ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ That always triumphantly
brings down the house ♪
♪ Jellicle cats
are queens of the night ♪
♪ Singing at
astronomical heights ♪
♪ Handling pieces
from the Messiah ♪
♪ Hallelujah, angelical choir ♪
♪ ♪
♪ The mystical divinity ♪
♪ Of unashamed felinity ♪
♪ Round the cathedral rang ♪
♪ "Vivat" ♪
♪ Life to the ♪
♪ Everlasting Cat ♪
♪ Feline, fearless ♪
♪ Faithful and true
to others who do ♪
♪ What? ♪
♪ Jellicles do
and Jellicles can ♪
♪ Jellicles can
and Jellicles do ♪
♪ Jellicle cats sing
Jellicle chants ♪
♪ Jellicles old
and Jellicles new ♪
♪ Jellicle song
and Jellicle dance ♪
♪ Jellicle songs
for Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Jellicle songs for
Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Jellicle songs
for Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Jellicle songs for
Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Practical cats ♪
♪ Dramatical cats ♪
♪ Pragmatical cats ♪
♪ Fanatical cats ♪
♪ Oratorical cats ♪
♪ Delphicoracle cats ♪
♪ Skeptical cats ♪
♪ Dyspeptical cats ♪
♪ Romantical cats ♪
♪ Pedantical cats ♪
♪ Critical cats ♪
♪ Parasitical cats ♪
♪ Allegorical cats ♪
♪ Metaphorical cats ♪
♪ Statistical cats ♪
♪ And mystical cats ♪
♪ Political cats ♪
♪ Hypocritical cats ♪
♪ Clerical cats ♪
♪ Hysterical cats ♪
♪ Cynical cats ♪
♪ Rabbinical cats ♪
♪ And magical cats ♪
♪ Jellicle songs
for Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Jellicle songs for
Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Jellicle songs
for Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Jellicle songs for
Jellicle cats, Jellicle ♪
(singing alone):
♪ Songs for Jellicle cats. ♪
(gasps softly)
MACAVITY:
Going to the ball?
I wouldn't if I were you.
Could get dangerous.
You know, they say
Macavity will win this year.
Macavity?
♪ There's no one
like Macavity ♪
(whispers):
A wonderful magician.
♪ But a monster ♪
♪ Of depravity ♪
One moment, you see him...
Come on!
MACAVITY (whispers):
Magic.
- (gasping quietly)
- (Macavity laughing)
So, what's your name?
(hisses)
Cat got your tongue?
- Victoria.
- Victoria?
You must have another.
Another?
The naming of cats
is a difficult matter.
It isn't just
one of your holiday games.
You may think at first
I'm as mad as a hatter
when I tell you a cat must
have three different names.
First of all,
there's the name
that the family use daily,
such as...
- Peter.
- Augustus.
- Alonzo.
- Or James.
But I tell you a cat needs
a name that's particular.
A name that's peculiar
and more dignified.
CHORUS (in unison):
Else how can he keep up
his tail perpendicular?
Or spread out his whiskers?
Or cherish his pride?
But above and beyond,
there's still
one name left over.
And that is the name
that you never will guess.
The name that no human research
can discover,
but the cat herself knows
and will never confess.
When you notice a cat
in profound meditation,
the reason, I tell you,
is always the same.
Her mind is engaged
in a rapt contemplation
of the thought,
of the thought, of the thought
of her name.
Her ineffable,
effable,
effanineffable,
deep and inscrutable,
singular name, name,
name, name, name,
name, name, name, name,
name, name.
♪ ♪
Mr. Mistoffelees
the Magical Cat!
♪ Jellicle cats,
come out tonight ♪
come one, come all ♪
♪ The Jellicle moon
is shining bright ♪
♪ Jellicles,
come to the Jellicle Ball ♪
♪ Jellicle cats,
come out tonight ♪
♪ J... ♪
(yells)
♪ Jellicles, come to the ♪
(grunts)
♪ Jellicle Ball ♪
♪ Jellicle cats
meet once a year ♪
♪ At the Jellicle Ball
where we all rejoice ♪
♪ And the Jellicle leader
will soon appear ♪
♪ And make what is known
as the Jellicle choice ♪
♪ When Old Deuteronomy
just before dawn ♪
♪ Through a silence you feel
you could cut with a knife ♪
♪ Announces the cat
who can now be reborn ♪
♪ And come back to
a different Jellicle life ♪
♪ For waiting up there
is the Heaviside Layer ♪
♪ Full of wonders
one Jellicle only will see ♪
♪ And Jellicles ask
because Jellicles dare ♪
♪ Who will it be? ♪
CHORUS:
The Heaviside Layer?
Far, far up in the sky,
from where
the most deserving cat
will be reborn
into another life.
So they can be who they've
always dreamed of being.
How will they be chosen?
By singing the song
of themselves, of course.
Who they are and what they do.
♪ ♪
Come.
Come and see a cat
who's competing
to be the Jellicle choice
tonight.
♪ I have a Gumbie Cat in mind ♪
- ♪ Her name is Jennyanydots ♪
- (yawns)
♪ Her coat is
of the tabby kind ♪
♪ With tiger stripes
and leopard spots ♪
♪ All day she sits
upon the stair ♪
♪ Or on the step ♪
- (groaning)
- ♪ Or on the mat ♪
♪ She sits and sits and sits ♪
♪ And sits ♪
♪ And that's what makes
a Gumbie Cat ♪
♪ That's what makes
(Jennyanydots grunting)
♪ But... ♪
♪ When the day's
hustle and bustle is done ♪
♪ Then the Gumbie Cat's work
is but hardly begun ♪
♪ And when all the family's
in bed and asleep ♪
♪ I tuck up my skirts
to the basement to creep ♪
♪ I am deeply concerned ♪
♪ With the ways of the mice ♪
♪ Their behavior's not good ♪
♪ And their manners not nice ♪
♪ So when I have got them
lined up on the matting ♪
♪ I teach them music,
crocheting and tatting ♪
♪ Diddly dup, diddly dup,
diddly dup wup boo ♪
♪ Diddy dup, diddly dup ♪
♪ Diddly dup wup boo ♪
♪ Diddy dup, diddly dup,
diddly dup ♪
- ♪ Wah, wah ♪
- ♪ A doo ba doo ba doo ♪
♪ Ba doo ba biddly da doo da ♪
♪ Waddly wah, waddly wah ♪
It's dinner and a show.
♪ Wah wah, waddly wah ♪
♪ Waddly wah,
waddly wah wah wah ♪
JENNYANYDOTS:
♪ A doo ba doo ba doo ♪
(scatting)
(panting)
(screams)
- (mice laughing)
- (hisses)
MUNKUSTRAP:
♪ I have a Gumbie Cat in mind ♪
- ♪ Her name is Jennyanydots ♪
- MICE: ♪ Jennyanydots ♪
♪ The curtain cord
she likes to wind ♪
♪ And tie it into ♪
- ♪ Sailor knots ♪
- (groaning) - Ooh.
♪ She sits upon
the windowsill ♪
♪ Or anything
that's smooth and flat ♪
- ♪ She sits and sits ♪
- (groans)
♪ And sits and sits ♪
(grunts)
♪ And that's what makes
a Gumbie Cat ♪
♪ That's what makes ♪
♪ A Gumbie Cat ♪
♪ But... ♪
♪ When the day's
hustle and bustle is done ♪
♪ Then the Gumbie Cat's work
is but hardly begun ♪
♪ I think that the cockroaches
need employment ♪
♪ To prevent them from idle
and wanton destroyment ♪
♪ So I formed from that lot
of disorderly louts ♪
♪ A troop of well-disciplined,
helpful Boy Scouts ♪
♪ With a purpose in life
and a good deed to do ♪
♪ And I've even created ♪
♪ A beetles tattoo ♪
(rhythmic drumbeat
and footsteps)
♪ ♪
JENNYANYDOTS:
Cockroaches! Faces!
Mm. (grunts)
And now for
the icing on the cake.
Why does she want
another Jellicle life?
I can't keep being
in this kitchen.
Don't get cocky.
(scoffs)
(laughs)
♪ ♪
♪ So for Old Gumbie Cats
let's now give three cheers ♪
♪ On whom well-ordered
households depend, it appears ♪
♪ Three cheers,
three cheers, three cheers ♪
♪ Thank you, my dears. ♪
RUM TUM TUGGER:
Mm. Meow.
- Hmm?
- It's a little old-fashioned, don't you think?
With the cockroaches dancing
and the mice singing.
Well, actually,
the mice were really good.
(giggling)
- But it's all a bit old-school.
- Get out.
I'm just trying to offer you
some feedback here.
Well... well, actually,
I just thought I'd have
a feed at the back.
Get out of this kitchen now!
- Let's dance!
- ♪ ♪
(sighs)
♪ The Rum Tum Tugger ♪
- ♪ Is a curious cat ♪
- ♪ A curious cat ♪
(both grunting rhythmically)
♪ If you offer me pheasant,
I'd rather have grouse ♪
♪ If you put me in a house,
I would much prefer a flat ♪
♪ If you put me in a flat,
then I'd rather have a house ♪
♪ If you set me on a mouse,
then I only want a rat ♪
♪ If you set me on a rat,
then I'd rather chase a mouse ♪
(mouse squeals)
CHORUS: ♪ The Rum Tum Tugger
is a curious cat ♪
♪ And there isn't any call
for me to shout it ♪
CHORUS:
♪ For he will do as he do do ♪
♪ And there's no doing anything
abou-awou-awou-out it ♪
(grunts):
No.
♪ ♪
♪ The Rum Tum Tugger
is a terrible bore ♪
♪ When you let me in,
then I want to go out ♪
♪ I'm always on the wrong side
of every door ♪
♪ As soon as I get home,
then I like to get about ♪
♪ I like to lie
in a bureau drawer ♪
♪ But I make such a fuss
if I can't get out ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
Do you think
he just got neutered?
'Cause those notes are, like...
- (high-pitched): high.
- (chuckles)
You know...
(clicks tongue)
CHORUS: ♪ The Rum Tum Tugger
is a curious cat ♪
(grunts) ♪ And there isn't
any use for you to doubt it ♪
- Lights.
- ♪ For he will do as he do do ♪
♪ And there's no
doing anything ♪
♪ Abou-awou-awou-out it ♪
I can dance how he dances, too.
- Look.
- MUNKUSTRAP: Let me see.
♪ ♪
It's easy.
♪ The Rum Tum Tugger
is a curious beast ♪
♪ My disobliging ways
is a matter of habit ♪
(grunts)
♪ If you offer me fish,
then I always want a feast ♪
♪ When there isn't any fish ♪
♪ Well, darling,
I'm not having rabbit ♪
♪ If you offer me cream,
then I sniff and sneer ♪
♪ For I only like ♪
♪ What I find ♪
♪ For myself ♪
(sighs)
- ♪ Victoria... ♪
- (Jellicles sighing)
Stop milking it.
♪ So you'll catch me in it
right up to my ears ♪
♪ If you put it away
on the larder shelf, whoo! ♪
♪ The Rum Tum Tugger ♪
♪ Is artful and knowing ♪
- ♪ The Rum Tum Tugger ♪
- ♪ Doesn't care for a cuddle ♪
♪ But I'll leap up in your lap
in the middle of your sewing ♪
♪ For there's nothing I enjoy
like a horrible muddle ♪
Yeah!
♪ ♪
♪ The Rum Tum Tugger
is a curious cat ♪
♪ The Rum Tum Tugger ♪
♪ Doesn't care for a cuddle ♪
(grunts)
Nah, nah. No more milk.
Milk!
Whoo!
- (grunts)
- ♪ The Rum Tum Tugger is ♪
♪ A curious cat ♪
♪ And there isn't any need
for me to spout it ♪
♪ For he will do as he do do ♪
♪ And there's no ♪
♪ Doing anything ♪
♪ About ♪
♪ About... ♪
Wow.
♪ There's no doing
anything, yeah ♪
♪ About ♪
(Jellicles squealing)
♪ About it. ♪
(Jellicles squealing, meowing)
(laughs)
(hisses)
♪ ♪
♪ Remark the cat ♪
♪ Who hesitates towards you ♪
♪ In the light of the door ♪
♪ Which opens on her ♪
♪ Like a grin ♪
♪ You see the border
of her coat ♪
♪ Is torn ♪
♪ And stained with sand ♪
♪ And you see ♪
♪ The corner of her eye twist ♪
♪ Like a crooked pin ♪
- ♪ And ♪
- ♪ She haunted ♪
♪ Many a low resort ♪
♪ Near the grimy road ♪
♪ Of Tottenham Court ♪
♪ She flitted about ♪
♪ The no-man's-land ♪
♪ From the Rising Sun ♪
♪ To the Friend At Hand ♪
♪ And the postman sighed ♪
♪ As he scratched his head ♪
♪ You'd really have thought ♪
♪ She'd ought to be dead ♪
♪ And who'd have ever
supposed that that ♪
♪ Was Grizabella ♪
♪ The Glamour Cat ♪
♪ Grizabella the Glamour Cat ♪
♪ Who'd have ever supposed ♪
♪ That that ♪
(hisses)
♪ Was Grizabella ♪
♪ The Glamour Cat. ♪
(breath quivers softly)
VICTORIA:
Who was she?
She used to be
the star of the Windmill.
Then she went with Macavity.
CASSANDRA:
Now she lives on the wasteland.
(footsteps clomping)
BUSTOPHER:
Good evening, all.
Oh, no.
Look what the cat dragged in.
Oh, my.
You look absolutely starving.
You can't attend the ball
on an empty stomach.
So you're hoping to be chosen?
Yeah. He wants to be reborn
as a thin cat
so he can get fat
all over again.
- But he's going to lose.
- How dare you.
- Don't listen to her.
- Don't you listen to him,
because he is
a complete and utter bas...
♪ I'm Bustopher Jones ♪
♪ I'm not skin and bones ♪
♪ In fact, I'm remarkably fat ♪
♪ I don't haunt pubs ♪
♪ I have eight or nine clubs ♪
♪ For I'm the
St. James's Street cat ♪
♪ I'm the cat they all greet ♪
♪ As I walk down the street ♪
♪ In my coat
of fastidious black ♪
♪ No commonplace mousers ♪
♪ Have such well-cut trousers ♪
♪ Or such an impeccable back ♪
Yeah, you've got it.
Here we go.
(laughs)
Ready?
(whoops)
MACAVITY:
Scuse me.
Are you, by any chance,
Jennyanydots?
(chuckles):
Yes.
You know, your work
should be on the world stage.
Yes.
And that face
should be on a poster.
(gasps)
(whoops):
Meow!
♪ In the whole of St. James's,
the smartest of names is ♪
♪ The name of
this Brummell of cats ♪
♪ And we're all of us proud
to be nodded or bowed to ♪
♪ By Bustopher Jones
in white spats ♪
(sighs)
♪ My visits are occasional
to the Senior Educational ♪
♪ And it is against the rules ♪
♪ For any one cat
to belong both to that ♪
♪ And the
Joint Superior Schools ♪
(takes deep breath)
♪ For a similar reason,
when game is in season ♪
- ♪ I'm found not at Fox's but Blimp's ♪
- (grunting)
(gasps)
♪ I am frequently seen ♪
♪ At the gay Stage and Screen ♪
♪ Which is famous
for winkles and shrimps ♪
♪ In the season of venison ♪
♪ I give my benison ♪
♪ To the Pothunter's
succulent bones ♪
(munching loudly)
♪ And just before noon's
not a moment too soon ♪
(music stops abruptly)
Right, well, that's not
going to work, is it?
Okay?
Look at you and look at me,
and you know...
you know that I'm sensitive
about my size.
Okay? And yet
you embarrass me. You...
(hisses) That's what
I say to you. (hisses)
Okay? Now, listen.
You'll never get me
up there on your own,
so let's gather up
a few more of the...
cats, and we'll
try again, shall we?
♪ ♪
Yeah, okay.
Nice and good.
Everybody ready?
And five, six, seven.
♪ And just before noon's ♪
♪ Not a moment too s... ♪
Hey!
(grunts)
(groaning)
♪ To drop in for a drink
at the Dro... ♪
♪ O... o... ♪
♪ O... ones ♪
Thanks, Tugger.
♪ When I'm seen in a hurry ♪
♪ There's probably curry ♪
♪ At the Siamese
or at the Glutton ♪
(gasps)
♪ If I look full of gloom ♪
♪ Then I've lunched
at the Tomb ♪
♪ On cabbage, rice pudding
and mutton ♪
♪ In the whole of St. James's,
the smartest of names is ♪
♪ The name of
this Brummell of cats ♪
♪ And we're all of us proud
to be nodded or bowed to ♪
- ♪ By Bustopher Jones in white ♪
- (gasps)
♪ Bustopher Jones in white ♪
♪ Bustopher Jones
in white spats ♪
(yelling, whooping)
(laughing)
♪ So much in this way
passes Bustopher's day ♪
- ♪ At one club ♪
- ♪ Or another I'm found ♪
♪ It can be no surprise
that under our eyes ♪
♪ He has grown
unmistakably round ♪
♪ I'm a 25-pounder
or I am a bounder ♪
♪ And I'm putting on weight
every day ♪
♪ But I'm so well-preserved
because I've observed ♪
♪ All my life a routine,
and I'd say ♪
♪ I am still in my prime,
I shall last out my time ♪
CHORUS: ♪ That's the word
from the stoutest of cats ♪
♪ It must and it shall
be spring in Pall Mall ♪
♪ While Bustopher Jones
wears white ♪
♪ Bustopher Jones wears white ♪
♪ Bustopher Jones
wears white. ♪
Spats?
Macavity!
(chuckles):
Puss in Spats.
I love it.
Hungry?
Look like you haven't
eaten for days.
Go for it.
Look at it.
Smell it.
Really tasty.
(sniffing)
Well, come on, Puss in Spats.
You can do it.
- (laughs)
- (scream echoes)
Ineffable.
(grunt echoes)
Can we help you?
You really shouldn't
be out alone.
I'm not alone.
I'm with my friends.
Friends?
Looks like they've run away
and left you.
Don't worry.
We'll look after you.
Won't we?
Why don't you come inside?
- ♪ Mungojerrie ♪
- ♪ And Rumpelteazer ♪
♪ We're a notorious
couple of cats ♪
- ♪ As knockabout clowns ♪
- ♪ Quick-change comedians ♪
- ♪ Tightrope walkers ♪
- ♪ And acrobats ♪
♪ We have
an extensive reputation ♪
♪ We make our home
in Victoria Grove ♪
♪ This is merely our center
of operation ♪
♪ For we are incurably
given to rove ♪
♪ We are very well-known ♪
♪ In Cornwall Gardens,
in Launceston Place ♪
♪ And in Kensington Square ♪
♪ We have really
a little more reputation ♪
♪ Than a couple of cats
can very well bear ♪
No photos, right?
♪ If the area window
is found ajar ♪
♪ And the bedroom
looks like a field of war ♪
♪ If a tile or two ♪
- ♪ Comes loose on the roof ♪
- (tile shatters)
♪ Which presently fails ♪
- ♪ To be waterproof ♪
- (tile shatters)
♪ If the drawers are pulled out
from the bedroom chest ♪
♪ And you can't find
one of your winter vests ♪
♪ Or after supper
one of the girls ♪
♪ Suddenly misses
her Woolworth pearls ♪
♪ The family will say ♪
♪ "It's that horrible cat" ♪
♪ It was Mungojerrie ♪
♪ Or Rumpelteazer ♪
♪ And most of the time
they leave it at that ♪
♪ ♪
(laughing)
(laughs)
♪ Mungojerrie
and Rumpelteazer ♪
♪ Have a very unusual
gift of the gab ♪
♪ We're highly efficient
cat burglars as well ♪
♪ And remarkably smart ♪
- ♪ At the smash-and-grab ♪
- (glass shatters)
♪ We make our home
in Victoria Grove ♪
♪ We have no regular
occupation ♪
♪ We are plausible fellows
who like to engage ♪
♪ A friendly policeman
in conversation ♪
Hello, police officer.
I bought these for her myself.
- You did what?
- Wait.
♪ When the family assembles ♪
♪ For Sunday dinner ♪
♪ Their minds made up
that they won't get thinner ♪
♪ On Argentine joint,
potatoes and greens ♪
♪ Then the cook would appear
from behind the scenes ♪
♪ And say in a voice
that is broken with sorrow ♪
♪ "I'm afraid you must wait
and have dinner tomorrow ♪
♪ For the joint is gone
from the oven like that" ♪
♪ Then the family will say ♪
♪ "It's that horrible cat" ♪
♪ It was Mungojerrie ♪
♪ Or Rumpelteazer ♪
♪ And most of the time
they leave it at that ♪
- ♪ Mungojerrie ♪
- ♪ And Rumpelteazer ♪
♪ Have a wonderful way
of working together ♪
♪ And some of the time
you would ♪
- ♪ Say it was luck ♪
- (grunts, gasps)
♪ And some of the time ♪
♪ You would say
it was weather ♪
♪ We go through the house
like a hurricane ♪
♪ And no sober person
could take his oath ♪
♪ Was it Mungojerrie? ♪
♪ Or Rumpelteazer? ♪
♪ Or could you have sworn
that it might have been both? ♪
♪ And when you hear
a dining room smash ♪
♪ Or up from the pantry
there comes a loud crash ♪
♪ Or down from the library
there comes a loud ping ♪
♪ From a vase that was
commonly said to be Ming ♪
♪ Then the family will say ♪
♪ "Now, which was which cat?" ♪
♪ It was Mungojerrie ♪
♪ And ♪
♪ Rumpelteazer ♪
♪ And there's nothing at all
to be done about that. ♪
(vase wobbling)
(dog barking in distance)
(gasps, grunts)
(dog continues barking)
MISTOFFELEES:
I'm coming, Victoria!
(yells, grunts)
(gasping, grunting)
Don't worry. Stay there.
(dog continues barking)
(dog barks, growls)
(grunting)
(gasping)
(dog growling)
(gasps, sighs)
Here, doggy. Fetch!
(dog panting)
(both panting)
I've been looking for you
everywhere.
I-I thought you'd miss
the arrival.
What arrival?
Of Old Deuteronomy.
(dog growling)
♪ ♪
(gasps, pants)
- Where am I?
- (ship horn blowing)
It seems we're on a barge
in the middle of the Thames.
What are you doing here?
I haven't got
the faintest clue.
And I've lost
all of my cockroaches.
I can't be on a barge
in the middle of the Thames.
I'm supposed to be
going to the ball.
Oh, no. You're not going
anywhere, Puss in Spats.
I'm determined to win,
and I prefer
my competition chained up.
Growltiger.
Keep them here.
Meow!
He's called me that twice now...
"Puss in Spats."
Like it's sort of a joke,
and I rather like it,
so the joke's on him.
Who are you?
Growltiger.
♪ I'm a Bravo Cat,
I travel on a barge ♪
♪ In fact, I am
the roughest cat ♪
♪ Who ever roamed at large ♪
♪ From Gravesend up to Oxford ♪
♪ I pursue my evil aims ♪
♪ Rejoicing in my title of ♪
♪ The Terror of the "Taymes" ♪
Right, no, see,
that doesn't rhyme.
You can't just say "Taymes"
'cause it rhymes with "aims."
It's-it's the River Thames.
- (hisses)
- (whimpers in pain)
(Griddlebone giggles)
Ow!
Okay, so it's Growl...
Growltiger, you say?
Yep, I think I've got it.
I think that's it.
(quietly): I-I fully
understand now who it is.
Thank you for telling me.
Where have you been?
Oh, it-it's mine.
Yet another trick
that went wrong. (chuckles)
You're just in time
to see Old Deuteronomy.
Who is Old Deuteronomy?
♪ Old Deuteronomy's ♪
♪ Lived a long time ♪
♪ She's a cat who has lived ♪
♪ Many lives in succession ♪
♪ She was famous in proverb ♪
♪ And famous in rhyme ♪
♪ A long while before
Queen Victoria's accession ♪
♪ Old Deuteronomy's ♪
♪ Lived many lives ♪
♪ You know,
I am tempted to say 99 ♪
♪ And her numerous progeny ♪
♪ Prospers and thrives ♪
♪ And the village
is proud of her ♪
♪ In her decline ♪
♪ At the sight of that placid
and bland physiognomy ♪
♪ When she sits in the sun ♪
♪ On the vicarage wall ♪
♪ Oldest inhabitant croaks ♪
♪ "Well, of all things ♪
♪ "Can it be really? ♪
♪ "Yes, no, ho, hi ♪
♪ "Oh, my eye ♪
♪ "My mind may be wandering,
but I confess ♪
♪ I believe it is
Old Deuteronomy" ♪
♪ "Well, of all things ♪
♪ "Can it be really? ♪
♪ "Yes, no, ho, hi,
oh, my eye ♪
♪ "My mind may be wandering,
but I confess ♪
♪ I believe it is
Old Deuteronomy" ♪
♪ "Well, of all things ♪
♪ "Can it be really? ♪
♪ "Yes, no, ho, hi,
oh, my eye ♪
♪ "My mind may be wandering,
but I confess ♪
♪ I believe it is
Old Deuteronomy" ♪
♪ "Well, of all things ♪
♪ "Can it be really? ♪
♪ Yes, no, ho, hi,
oh, my eye" ♪
♪ My legs may be tottery ♪
♪ I must go slow ♪
♪ And be careful
of Old Deuteronomy ♪
♪ Jellicle cats
meet once a year ♪
♪ On the night we make
the Jellicle choice ♪
♪ And now the Jellicle leader
is here ♪
♪ Jellicle cats
can all rejoice ♪
JELLICLES:
Who will it be?
- Who will it be?
♪ ♪
♪ Jellicle cats,
come out tonight ♪
come one, come all ♪
♪ The Jellicle moon
is shining bright ♪
♪ Jellicles,
come to the Jellicle Ball ♪
♪ Jellicle cats
are black and white ♪
are rather small ♪
♪ Jellicle cats
are merry and bright ♪
♪ And pleasant to hear
when they caterwaul ♪
- (yowls)
- ♪ Jellicle cats ♪
♪ Have cheerful faces ♪
♪ Jellicle cats have
bright black eyes ♪
♪ We like to practice
our airs and graces ♪
♪ And wait for
the Jellicle moon to rise ♪
- ♪ Jellicle cats develop slowly ♪
- (meowing)
♪ Jellicle cats
are not too big ♪
♪ Jellicle cats are roly-poly ♪
♪ We know how to dance
a gavotte and a jig ♪
♪ Until the Jellicle moon
appears ♪
♪ We make our toilette
and take our repose ♪
♪ Jellicles wash
behind their ears ♪
♪ Jellicles dry
between their toes ♪
♪ Jellicle cats
are white and black ♪
are of moderate size ♪
♪ Jellicles jump
like a jumping jack ♪
♪ Jellicle cats
have moonlit eyes ♪
are black and white ♪
♪ Jellicle cats,
as we said, are small ♪
♪ If it happens to be
a stormy night ♪
♪ We'll practice
a caper or two in the hall ♪
♪ If it happens
the sun is shining bright ♪
♪ You would say we had
nothing to do at all ♪
♪ We are resting and saving
ourselves to be right ♪
♪ For the Jellicle moon
and the Jellicle Ball ♪
♪ Jellicle cats,
come out tonight ♪
come one, come all ♪
♪ The Jellicle moon
is shining bright ♪
♪ Jellicles,
come to the Jellicle Ball ♪
♪ Jellicle cats,
come out tonight ♪
come one, come all ♪
♪ The Jellicle moon
is shining bright ♪
♪ Jellicles,
come to the Jellicle Ball. ♪
♪ ♪
- (purring)
- (rhythmic breathing)
♪ ♪
(rhythmic breathing)
(panting softly)
(rhythmic breathing continues)
♪ ♪
It's party time!
With your permission,
of course.
(exhales sharply)
♪ ♪
(hissing)
(breathing rhythmically)
♪ ♪
(rhythmic breathing)
(rhythmic breathing continues)
- (music speeds up)
- (breathing continues faster)
- (music ends)
- (Jellicles panting)
(panting)
♪ ♪
♪ Silence ♪
♪ Not a sound
from the pavement ♪
♪ Has the moon lost
her memory? ♪
♪ She is smiling alone ♪
♪ In the lamplight ♪
♪ The withered leaves
collect at my feet ♪
♪ And the wind ♪
♪ Begins to moan ♪
♪ Every streetlamp ♪
♪ Seems to beat ♪
♪ A fatalistic warning ♪
♪ Someone mutters ♪
♪ And the streetlamp gutters ♪
♪ And soon it will be morning ♪
♪ Memory ♪
♪ All alone in the moonlight ♪
♪ I can smile at the old days ♪
♪ I was beautiful then ♪
♪ I remember ♪
♪ The time I knew
what happiness was ♪
♪ Let the memory live ♪
♪ Again. ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Follow me home ♪
♪ If you dare to ♪
♪ I wouldn't know ♪
♪ Where to lead you ♪
♪ Should I take chances ♪
♪ When no one
took chances on me? ♪
♪ So I watch from the dark,
wait for my life to start ♪
♪ With no beauty in my memory ♪
♪ All that I wanted ♪
♪ Was to be wanted ♪
♪ Too young to wander
London streets ♪
♪ Alone and haunted ♪
♪ Born into nothing ♪
♪ At least you have something ♪
♪ Something to cling to ♪
♪ Visions of dazzling rooms ♪
♪ I'll never get let into ♪
♪ And the memories
were lost long ago ♪
♪ But at least you have
beautiful ghosts ♪
♪ And so maybe my home
isn't what I had known ♪
♪ What I thought it would be ♪
♪ But I feel so alive ♪
♪ With these
phantoms of night ♪
♪ And I know that
this life isn't safe ♪
♪ But it's wild and it's free ♪
♪ All that I wanted ♪
♪ Was to be wanted ♪
♪ I'll never wander
London streets ♪
♪ Alone and haunted ♪
♪ Born into nothing ♪
♪ With them I have something ♪
♪ Something to cling to ♪
♪ I never knew I'd love
this world they let me into ♪
♪ And the memories
were lost long ago ♪
♪ So I'll dance with
these beautiful ghosts ♪
♪ The memories
were lost long ago ♪
♪ So I'll dance with
these beautiful ♪
♪ Ghosts. ♪
♪ The moments of happiness ♪
♪ We had the experience ♪
♪ But missed the meaning ♪
♪ And approach to the meaning ♪
♪ Restores the experience ♪
♪ In a different form ♪
♪ Beyond any meaning ♪
♪ We can assign to happiness ♪
♪ The past experience ♪
♪ Revived in the meaning ♪
♪ Is not the experience ♪
♪ Of one life only ♪
♪ But of many generations ♪
♪ Not forgetting ♪
♪ Something that is
probably quite ♪
♪ Ineffable. ♪
♪ ♪
Are you all right, my dear?
We haven't met before, have we?
No.
I'm not from round here.
I was abandoned.
Oh, poor thing.
Would you like to see me make
the Jellicle choice?
- Am I allowed?
- Why wouldn't you be allowed?
I'm not a Jellicle.
Not yet, perhaps.
Come. We're about to begin.
♪ ♪
(quiet lapping)
Gus.
Gus, it's your call.
(Gus exhales sharply)
I just wanted to wish you...
- jolly good luck.
- Oh.
I'm a tremendous fan
of your work.
(chuckles) Mm.
- What's your name?
- Mr. Mistoffelees.
I'm a Magic Cat, you see.
(chuckles)
Oh.
- Do you ever get nervous?
- No, no.
It's all practice,
practice, practice.
Then nothing can go wrong.
T-Touch wood.
I've never played
The Egyptian before.
OLD DEUTERONOMY:
Gus...
the Theatre Cat.
Cross paws.
♪ ♪
Mm.
♪ Gus is the cat ♪
♪ At the theater door ♪
♪ Uh, my name, as I ought
to have told you before ♪
♪ Is really Asparagus ♪
♪ But that's such a fuss
to pronounce ♪
♪ That they usually
call me just Gus ♪
Mm.
♪ My coat's very shabby ♪
♪ I'm thin as a rake ♪
♪ And I suffer from palsy
which makes my paws shake ♪
♪ Yet I was, in my youth,
quite the smartest of cats ♪
♪ Though no longer a terror
to mice or to rats ♪
♪ For I'm not the cat
that I was in my prime ♪
♪ Though my name was
quite famous ♪
♪ They say, in my time ♪
♪ And whenever I join
my friends at their club ♪
♪ Which takes place at the back
of the neighboring pub ♪
♪ I love to regale them,
if someone else pays ♪
♪ With anecdotes drawn
from my palmiest days ♪
♪ For I once was a star
of the highest degree ♪
♪ I have acted with Irving ♪
(chuckles):
♪ I've acted with Tree ♪
♪ And I like to recall
my success on the halls ♪
♪ When the gallery once gave me
seven catcalls ♪
♪ But my grandest creation ♪
♪ As I love to tell ♪
♪ Was Firefrorefiddle ♪
♪ The Fiend of the Fell ♪
(snarls)
(laughing)
- (Gus grunts)
- (sighs)
♪ Then if someone will give me
a toothful of gin ♪
♪ I will tell how I once played
a part in East Lynne ♪
♪ In a Shakespeare performance
I once walked on pat ♪
♪ When some actor suggested
the need for a cat ♪
♪ And I say now these kittens ♪
♪ They do not get trained ♪
♪ As we did in the days
when Victoria reigned ♪
♪ They do not get drilled
in a regular troupe ♪
♪ And they think it is smart
just to jump through a hoop ♪
♪ And I say as I scratch myself
with my claws ♪
♪ Well, the theater is
certainly not what it was ♪
♪ These modern productions
are all very well ♪
♪ But there's nothing
to equal ♪
♪ From what I hear tell ♪
♪ That moment of mystery ♪
♪ When I made history ♪
♪ As Firefrorefiddle ♪
♪ The Fiend of the Fell... ♪
(thunder crashing)
- (song ends)
- (thunder fades)
(applause, Jellicles yowling)
I could do it again, you know.
(applause, yowling continue)
(sighs, chuckles softly)
(panting)
MACAVITY:
Bravo!
Bravo, Gus.
Could I trouble you for
an au... an autograph, sir?
(Macavity gasps)
To see Firefrorefiddle
come alive tonight
was truly inspirational
and scary.
Macavity! (laughs)
OLD DEUTERONOMY:
The next contestant is
Skimbleshanks the Railway Cat.
♪ ♪
♪ Skimbleshanks
the Railway Cat ♪
♪ The Cat of
the Railway Train ♪
♪ There's a whisper
down the line at 11:39 ♪
♪ When the Night Mail's
ready to depart ♪
♪ Saying, "Skimble,
where is Skimble? ♪
♪ "Has he gone to hunt
the thimble? ♪
♪ We must find him
or the train can't start" ♪
♪ All the guards
and all the porters ♪
♪ And the stationmaster's
daughters ♪
♪ Would be searching
high and low ♪
♪ Saying, "Skimble,
where is Skimble? ♪
♪ "For unless he's
very nimble ♪
♪ Then the Night Mail
just can't go" ♪
♪ At 11:42
with the signal overdue ♪
♪ And the passengers
all frantic to a man ♪
♪ That's when I would appear ♪
♪ And I'd saunter to the rear ♪
♪ I'd been busy
in the luggage van ♪
♪ Then he gives one flash
of his glass-green eyes ♪
♪ And the signal goes
"all clear" ♪
♪ And we're off at last
for the northern part ♪
♪ Of the Northern Hemisphere ♪
(blows whistle)
(rhythmic tapping)
(tapping continues faster)
(drums join in)
♪ Skimbleshanks
the Railway Cat ♪
♪ Skimbleshanks ♪
♪ The Railway Cat ♪
♪ Skimbleshanks,
Skimbleshanks ♪
♪ Skimbleshanks
the Railway Cat ♪
♪ The Cat of
the Railway Train ♪
♪ You could say that
by and large ♪
♪ It was me who was in charge
of the Sleeping Car Express ♪
♪ From the driver
and the guards ♪
♪ To the bagmen playing cards ♪
♪ I would supervise them all,
more or less ♪
♪ I will watch you
without winking ♪
♪ And I'll see
what you are thinking ♪
♪ And it's certain
that I wouldn't approve ♪
♪ Of hilarity and riot ♪
♪ So the folk are very quiet ♪
♪ When Skimble is about
and on the move ♪
♪ You can play no pranks
with Skimbleshanks ♪
♪ I'm a cat that
cannot be ignored ♪
♪ So nothing goes wrong
on the Northern Mail ♪
♪ When Skimbleshanks
is aboard ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Oh, it's very pleasant ♪
♪ When you've found your
little den with your name ♪
- ♪ Written up on the door ♪
- ♪ Whoo-whoo! ♪
♪ And the berth is very neat
with a newly folded sheet ♪
♪ And there's not a speck
of dust on the floor ♪
♪ Then the guard
looks in politely ♪
♪ And will ask you
very brightly ♪
♪ "Do you like
your morning tea ♪
♪ Weak or strong?" ♪
♪ But I was just behind him
and was ready to remind him ♪
♪ For Skimble won't let
anything go wrong ♪
♪ When you creep into
your cozy berths ♪
♪ And pull up the counterpane ♪
♪ You ought to reflect
that it's very nice ♪
♪ To know that you won't be ♪
- ♪ Bothered by mice ♪
- (mouse squeaking)
♪ You can leave all that
to the Railway Cat ♪
♪ The Cat of
the Railway Train ♪
♪ Skimbleshanks
the Railway Cat ♪
♪ The Cat of
the Railway Train ♪
♪ And he gives you a wave
of his long brown tail ♪
♪ Which says
"I'll see you again" ♪
♪ You will meet without fail
on the Midnight Mail ♪
♪ The Cat of the Railway ♪
♪ Train... ♪
(yelps)
♪ ♪
(Macavity laughing)
Macavity.
♪ ♪
♪ Macavity's a Mystery Cat ♪
♪ He's called the Hidden Paw ♪
♪ For he's
the master criminal ♪
♪ Who can defy the law ♪
♪ He's the bafflement
of Scotland Yard ♪
- ♪ The Flying Squad's despair ♪
- (sniffs, huffs)
♪ For when they reach
the scene of crime ♪
♪ Macavity's not there ♪
♪ ♪
(grunts)
♪ Macavity, Macavity ♪
♪ There's no one
like Macavity ♪
♪ He's broken every human law ♪
♪ He breaks the law
of gravity ♪
♪ His powers of levitation ♪
♪ Would make a fakir stare ♪
♪ But when they reach
the scene of crime ♪
♪ Macavity's not there ♪
♪ Macavity's a ginger cat ♪
♪ He's very tall and thin ♪
♪ You would know him
if you saw him ♪
♪ For his eyes are sunken in ♪
♪ His brow is deeply lined
with thought ♪
♪ His head is highly domed ♪
♪ His coat is dusty
from neglect ♪
♪ His whiskers are uncombed ♪
♪ He sways his head
from side to side ♪
♪ With movements like a snake ♪
♪ And when you think
he's half asleep ♪
♪ He's always ♪
♪ Wide awake! ♪
♪ Macavity, Macavity ♪
♪ There's no one
like Macavity ♪
♪ For he's a fiend
in feline shape ♪
♪ A monster of depravity ♪
♪ You may meet him
in a bystreet ♪
♪ You may see him
in the square ♪
♪ But when a crime's
discovered, then ♪
♪ Macavity's not there ♪
♪ He's outwardly respectable ♪
♪ I know he cheats at cards ♪
♪ And his footprints
are not found ♪
♪ In a-any files ♪
♪ Of Scotland Yard's ♪
♪ And when
the larder's looted ♪
♪ And the jewel case
is rifled ♪
♪ Or when the milk is missing ♪
♪ Or another Peke's
been stifled ♪
♪ Or the greenhouse glass
is broken ♪
(glass shatters)
♪ And the trellis past repair ♪
♪ There's the wonder
of the thing ♪
♪ Macavity's not there ♪
♪ Macavity, Macavity ♪
♪ There's no one
like Macavity ♪
♪ There never was
a cat of such ♪
♪ Deceitfulness and suavity ♪
♪ He always has an alibi ♪
♪ And one or two to spare ♪
♪ Whatever time
the deed took place ♪
♪ Macavity wasn't there ♪
♪ And they say that
all the cats ♪
♪ Whose wicked deeds
are widely known ♪
♪ I might mention Mungojerrie ♪
♪ Rumpelteazer, Griddlebone ♪
♪ Are nothing more
than agents ♪
♪ For the cat
who all the time ♪
♪ Just controls
the operations ♪
MACAVITY:
♪ The Napoleon of crime ♪
(laughing)
Mwah!
♪ Macavity, Macavity ♪
♪ There's no one
like Macavity ♪
♪ He's a fiend
in feline shape ♪
♪ A monster of depravity ♪
♪ You may meet him
in a bystreet ♪
♪ You may see him in a square ♪
♪ But when a crime's
discovered, then ♪
♪ Macavity, Macavity ♪
♪ Macavity ♪
♪ ♪
♪ When a crime's
discovered, then ♪
♪ Macavity's not there. ♪
(laughs):
Aha!
Yes!
The time has come to make
the Jellicle choice.
Old Deuteronomy, if you would.
As I am the only
contestant left.
And, quite obviously, the best.
And so...
Never.
(blowing)
I choose the cat
that deserves a new life.
I judge a cat by its soul.
He's got soul.
I've got plenty of soul.
You're a cheat, Macavity.
- (Macavity grunts, laughs)
- (whooshing)
(groaning)
♪ ♪
(Macavity chuckling)
(Old Deuteronomy whimpers)
(grunting)
Mm.
Deuteronomy.
- I am going to the Heaviside Layer.
- (gasps)
I demand that you grant me
another life.
You will never go
to the Heaviside Layer.
Oh? We'll see about that.
Growltiger,
make her walk the plank.
(hisses)
- (Old Deuteronomy whimpers)
- (Macavity chuckles)
(gasps)
♪ ♪
- Say it's me...
- (Old Deuteronomy whimpers)
...or you'll drown
in that river.
OLD DEUTERONOMY: You'll never
be my Jellicle choice.
- This is your last chance.
- (whimpers)
(echoing):
Never!
Where is Old Deuteronomy?
Where is she?
We don't know.
(hisses)
Where is she?
Look, it was only a bit of fun.
We didn't know
he was gonna take Old Deut.
There must be
something we can do.
CASSANDRA:
We can't just magic her back.
VICTORIA:
Yes, we can.
You're a magician.
What?
MUNKUSTRAP:
It's not a bad idea.
Might be worth a try.
Really, I can't.
You could try.
Good luck.
(quiet, shuddering breaths)
You can do it.
Cross paws.
Can we get a spotlight?
Please don't make me do this.
- And a drumroll, please.
- (light clanks)
(drumroll)
♪ The greatest magicians ♪
♪ Have something to learn ♪
♪ From Mr. Mistoffelees'
conjuring turn ♪
♪ And we all say ♪
♪ "Oh, well, I never ♪
♪ "Was there ever
a cat so clever ♪
♪ As magical
Mr. Mistoffelees?" ♪
♪ I'm quiet and small ♪
♪ I am black ♪
♪ From my ears
to the tip of my tail ♪
♪ I can creep through
the tiniest crack ♪
♪ I can walk on
the narrowest rail ♪
♪ I can pick any card from
a pack ♪ (chuckles softly)
♪ I am equally cunning
with dice ♪
♪ I am always deceiving you
into believing ♪
♪ That you're only
hunting for mice ♪
♪ I can play any trick
with a cork ♪
♪ Or a spoon and a bit
of fish paste ♪
♪ If you look for a knife ♪
♪ Or a fork ♪
♪ And you think
it is merely misplaced ♪
♪ You have seen it one moment,
and then it is gone ♪
♪ But you find it next week
lying out on the lawn ♪
♪ And we all say ♪
♪ "Oh, well, I never ♪
♪ "Was there ever
a cat so clever ♪
♪ As magical
Mr. Mistoffelees?" ♪
(grunts)
- You can do this.
- (sighs)
(chuckles nervously)
♪ My manner is vague
and aloof ♪
♪ You would think
there was nobody shyer ♪
♪ But my voice has been heard
on the roof ♪
♪ When I was curled up
by the fire ♪
♪ And I've sometimes
been heard by the fire ♪
♪ When I was about
on the roof ♪
♪ At least they all heard
that somebody purred ♪
♪ Which is
incontestable proof ♪
♪ Of my singular
magical powers ♪
♪ And I've known
the family to call ♪
♪ Me in from the garden
for hours ♪
♪ When I was asleep
in the hall ♪
♪ And not long ago
this phenomenal cat ♪
♪ Produced seven kittens
right out of a hat ♪
(gasping)
MOUSE:
Mr. Mistoffelees?
My hero.
- (chuckles): Oh.
- Don't go.
- Oh, no.
- Falling.
- ♪ And they all say ♪
- Oh, gosh. Run!
♪ "Oh, well, I never ♪
♪ "Was there ever
a cat so clever ♪
♪ As magical
Mr. Mistoffelees?" ♪
(inhales deeply, grunts)
♪ "Oh, well, I never ♪
♪ "Was there ever
a cat so clever ♪
♪ As magical
Mr. Mistoffelees?" ♪
Please.
(grunts)
(whimpers)
VICTORIA:
♪ "Oh, well, I never ♪
♪ "Was there ever
a cat so clever ♪
♪ As magical
Mr. Mistoffelees?" ♪
♪ And we all say ♪
♪ "Oh, well, I never ♪
♪ "Was there ever
a cat so clever ♪
♪ As magical
Mr. Mistoffelees?" ♪
♪ "Oh, well, I never ♪
♪ "Was there ever
a cat so clever ♪
♪ As magical
Mr. Mistoffelees?" ♪
♪ "Oh, well, I never ♪
♪ "Was there ever
a cat so clever ♪
♪ As magical
Mr. Mistoffelees?" ♪
(grunts)
OLD DEUTERONOMY:
♪ "Oh, well, I never ♪
♪ "Was there ever
a cat so clever ♪
♪ As magical
Mr. Mistoffelees?" ♪
♪ And we all say ♪
♪ "Oh, well, I never ♪
♪ "Was there ever
a cat so clever ♪
♪ As magical
Mr. Mistoffelees?" ♪
♪ "Oh, well, I never ♪
♪ "Was there ever
a cat so clever ♪
♪ As magical
Mr. Mistoffelees?" ♪
♪ "Oh, well, I never ♪
♪ "Was there ever
a cat so clever ♪
♪ As magical
Mr. Mistoffelees?" ♪
♪ "Oh, well, I never ♪
♪ "Was there ever a cat
so clever as magical ♪
- ♪ Mr. Mistoffelees?" ♪
- ♪ So clever ♪
♪ As you ♪
- ♪ As me ♪
- ♪ "Oh, well, I never ♪
♪ "Was there ever
a cat so clever ♪
♪ As magical
Mr. Mistoffelees?" ♪
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you the marvelous,
magical Mr. Mistoffelees.
(applause, Jellicles yowling)
MACAVITY:
She's tricked me.
I will get there.
I will get to
the Heaviside Layer.
I will win!
You'll all see.
- (Jennyanydots whimpers)
- (Gus growls)
Come with me!
(echoes):
Meow!
(grunts)
(hisses)
- (grunting)
- (Jennyanydots yells)
(grunts, groans)
(grunting, panting)
Don't mess with
the crazy cat lady.
(screeching)
(groans)
(retching)
(grunts)
- (yells)
- (yowls)
- Firefrorefiddle!
- (screams)
JENNYANYDOTS:
Yes! (panting)
♪ The Fiend of the Fell. ♪
(panting, meowing)
(giggles)
JENNYANYDOTS:
Oh, you fiend.
- (chuckles)
- (purrs)
♪ Daylight ♪
♪ See the dew on a sunflower ♪
♪ And a rose that is fading ♪
♪ Roses wither away ♪
♪ Like the sunflower ♪
♪ I yearn to turn my face
to the dawn ♪
♪ I am waiting ♪
♪ For the day. ♪
♪ ♪
(hisses)
Sing.
♪ ♪
♪ Memory ♪
♪ Turn your face
to the moonlight ♪
♪ Let your memory lead you ♪
♪ Open up, enter in ♪
♪ If you find there ♪
♪ The meaning of
what happiness is ♪
♪ Then a new life ♪
♪ Will begin ♪
♪ Memory ♪
♪ All alone in the moonlight ♪
♪ I can smile at the old days ♪
♪ I was beautiful then ♪
♪ I remember ♪
♪ The time I knew
what happiness was ♪
♪ Let the memory ♪
♪ Live again ♪
♪ Burnt-out ends ♪
♪ Of smoky days ♪
♪ The stale, cold smell ♪
♪ Of morning ♪
♪ The streetlamp dies ♪
♪ Another night is over ♪
♪ Another day is dawning ♪
♪ Daylight ♪
♪ I must wait for the sunrise ♪
♪ I must think of a new life ♪
♪ And I mustn't give in ♪
♪ When the dawn comes ♪
♪ Tonight will be
a memory, too ♪
♪ And a new day ♪
♪ Will begin ♪
♪ ♪
(gasping)
♪ Sunlight through
the trees in summer ♪
♪ Endless masquerading ♪
♪ Like a flower ♪
♪ As the dawn is breaking ♪
♪ The memory ♪
♪ Is fading ♪
♪ Touch me ♪
♪ It's so easy to leave me ♪
♪ All alone with the memory ♪
♪ Of my days in the sun ♪
♪ If you touch me ♪
♪ You'll understand
what happiness is ♪
(deep, shuddering breath)
♪ Look ♪
♪ A new day ♪
♪ Has begun. ♪
♪ ♪
You are the Jellicle choice.
(Jellicles gasp softly)
(breath trembling)
Thank you.
♪ All that you wanted ♪
♪ Was to be wanted ♪
♪ Never to wander
London streets ♪
♪ Alone and haunted ♪
OLD DEUTERONOMY:
♪ All your memories of pain ♪
♪ Let them go ♪
♪ And you'll dance with
these beautiful ghosts. ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Up, up, up ♪
♪ Past the Russell Hotel ♪
♪ Up, up, up, up ♪
♪ To the Heaviside Layer ♪
♪ Up, up, up ♪
♪ Past the Russell Hotel ♪
♪ Up, up, up, up ♪
♪ To the Heaviside Layer ♪
♪ Up, up, up ♪
♪ Past the Russell Hotel ♪
♪ Up, up, up, up ♪
♪ To the Heaviside Layer ♪
♪ Up, up, up ♪
♪ Past the Russell Hotel ♪
♪ Up, up, up, up ♪
♪ To the Heaviside Layer ♪
♪ Up, up, up ♪
♪ Past the Jellicle moon ♪
♪ Up, up, up, up ♪
♪ To the Heaviside Layer ♪
♪ Up, up, up ♪
♪ Past the Jellicle moon ♪
♪ Up, up, up, up ♪
♪ To the Heaviside Layer. ♪
(grunts)
(laughs)
Up, up, up!
Heaviside Layer, here I c...
(grunts)
(grunts, whimpers)
Oh. Oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
(screams)
(grunts)
Ineffable.
(whimpers, yowls)
- (laughing)
- You're alive!
♪ ♪
♪ The mystical divinity ♪
♪ Of unashamed ♪
♪ Felinity ♪
♪ Round the cathedral rang ♪
♪ "Vivat" ♪
♪ Life to the ♪
♪ Everlasting ♪
♪ Cat. ♪
♪ You've heard
of several kinds of cat ♪
♪ And my opinion now is that ♪
♪ You should need
no interpreter ♪
♪ To understand our character ♪
♪ You've learned enough
to take the view ♪
♪ That cats are
very much like you ♪
♪ You've seen us both
at work and games ♪
♪ And learnt about
our proper names ♪
♪ Our habits and our habitat ♪
♪ But how would you
ad-dress a cat? ♪
♪ So first
your memory I'll jog ♪
♪ And say a cat is not ♪
♪ A dog ♪
♪ So first
your memory I'll jog ♪
♪ And say a cat is not ♪
♪ A dog ♪
♪ With cats ♪
♪ Some say one rule is true ♪
♪ Don't speak till you ♪
♪ Are spoken to ♪
♪ Myself, I do not
hold with that ♪
♪ I say you should
ad-dress a cat ♪
♪ But always
bear in mind that he ♪
♪ Resents familiarity ♪
♪ You bow ♪
♪ And taking off your hat ♪
♪ Ad-dress him in this form ♪
♪ O Cat ♪
♪ Before a cat
will condescend ♪
♪ To treat you
as a trusted friend ♪
♪ Some little token of esteem ♪
♪ Is needed,
like a dish of cream ♪
♪ Or you might
now and then supply ♪
♪ Some caviar
or Strasbourg pie ♪
♪ Some potted grouse
or salmon paste ♪
♪ He's sure to have
his personal taste ♪
♪ And so in time
you reach your aim ♪
♪ And call him ♪
♪ By his name ♪
♪ A cat's entitled to expect ♪
♪ These evidences of respect ♪
♪ So this is this ♪
♪ And that is that ♪
♪ And that's how you ad-dress ♪
♪ A cat. ♪
(birds chirping)
I believe you truly are
a Jellicle cat.
A dear little cat.
♪ ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ ♪
("Beautiful Ghosts"
by Taylor Swift playing)
♪ Follow me home ♪
♪ If you dare to ♪
♪ I wouldn't know ♪
♪ Where to lead you ♪
♪ Should I take chances ♪
♪ When no one
took chances on me? ♪
♪ So I watch from the dark,
wait for my life to start ♪
♪ With no beauty in my memory ♪
♪ All that I wanted ♪
♪ Was to be wanted ♪
♪ Too young to wander
London streets ♪
♪ Alone and haunted ♪
♪ Born into nothing ♪
♪ At least you have something ♪
♪ Something to cling to ♪
♪ Visions of dazzling rooms ♪
♪ I'll never get let into ♪
♪ And the memories
were lost long ago ♪
♪ But at least you have
beautiful ghosts ♪
♪ Perilous night ♪
♪ Their voices calling ♪
♪ A flicker of light ♪
♪ Before the dawning ♪
♪ Out here the wild ones ♪
♪ Are taming the fear
within me ♪
♪ Scared to call them
my friends ♪
♪ And be broken again ♪
♪ Is this hope
just a mystical dream? ♪
♪ All that I wanted ♪
♪ Was to be wanted ♪
♪ Too young to wander
London streets ♪
♪ Alone and haunted ♪
♪ Born into nothing ♪
♪ At least you have something ♪
♪ Something to cling to ♪
♪ Visions of dazzling rooms ♪
♪ I'll never get let into ♪
♪ And the memories
were lost long ago ♪
♪ But at least you have
beautiful ghosts ♪
♪ And so maybe my home ♪
♪ Isn't what I had known ♪
♪ What I thought it would be ♪
♪ But I feel so alive ♪
♪ With these
phantoms of night ♪
♪ And I know that
this life isn't safe ♪
♪ But it's wild and it's free ♪
♪ All that I wanted ♪
♪ Was to be wanted ♪
♪ I'll never wander
London streets ♪
♪ Alone and haunted ♪
♪ Born into nothing ♪
♪ With them I have something ♪
♪ Something to cling to ♪
♪ I never knew I'd love ♪
♪ This world
they've let me into ♪
♪ And the memories
were lost long ago ♪
♪ So I'll dance with
these beautiful ghosts ♪
♪ And the memories
were lost long ago ♪
♪ So I'll dance
with these beautiful ♪
♪ Ghosts. ♪
(song ends)
♪ ♪
(music fades)