Fuck, you scared me, man.
"You scared me, man."
What took you so long?
What's with the cousin?
Your sister is freaking out,
she wants to leave.
Relax. We had trouble finding her.
Agustín. Help me!
What a drag.
Relax, bitch...
...and I cum!
No wonder...
...the pussy...
...is in the dick.
No wonder...
...the tits...
...are so milky.
One more...
...and I cum.
Remember when he performed
in his underwear?
I remember.
Paloma.
Good, so anyway...
Yes, we want them.
Are they dangerous?
Any possible complications?
Fuck. I saw this coming....
Sara has to go back for an exam.
Are you crazy?
Barbara, slow down!
Who is Melda?
The caretaker's wife.
We're picking her up.
Why don't you just call her?
Sir? Do you know where I can find Melda?
Maybe at Lorenza's.
- That one?
- Yes.
Thanks.
Are you Mapuche?
Everyone here is Mapuche, right?
But you speak Spanish?
Good...
How are you doing Melda?
Fine, Agustín.
Hello. I'm Brink.
Nice to meet you.
Need help?
Just leave them.
Melda they are going to die!
That's why they were abandoned.
Are you kidding me?
Fucking dog!
Agustín, give me the dog.
Fucking dog... mother fucker.
How are you doing?
Come jump on the boat. Careful.
I'll help you.
- Hi honey.
- Hi love.
Is there a soccer team in this
town Mr. Bernardo?
Yeah!
What happened!?
Relax, Barbara...
Is this the only house around here?
No, there's also my cousin's...
I'm realistic.
You act so eco-friendly and shit...
You knew you'd end up
throwing that fucking dog away.
What was your plan, what was your plan?
In the United States...
Does this shit work?
Is there ammunition?
Shut up!
Good night.
So boring!
C'mon man.
Melda, yeah, one loaf a day is fine.
Slave!
Where is my breakfast!
Breakfast!
Agustín, your dick! Gross!
Sit down, girlfriend.
He doesn't understand a thing.
You failed, my friend.
Mother fucker!
C'mon!
Are we playing or what?
I dare you.
I'm gonna get you!
Get out! Out!
It's fucking freezing out.
Fuck!
I'm that dog.
You know she's shy and weird.
And you know she's alone.
Apologize, man.
Sara is gonna be pissed.
I think she was abused as a child or
she's a lesbian or something.
You're the lesbian, man.
Miss Barbara, miss Barbara, do you copy?
Miss Barbara...
What's going on Bernardo? Over.
Good morning. Miss Sara just arrived,
we are crossing the lake, over.
Nice to meet you.
Hey beautiful!
Thank you.
How do you like my gringa?
Thanks Bernardo.
What's with those rocks you told me about?
Can we just not walk,
and take the boat instead?
So c'mon, tell them!
Muscle relaxers?
C'mon, man.
Put this on.
No offense but she wasn't hypnotized.
No way she was going to suck your dick.
Impossible.
Yeah, but did you notice
when she grabbed the coal?
Did you see her face?
She was in a fucking trance.
Man, you fascinate me.
For real.
No wonder, the fire...
...I don't know what it's made of.
No wonder...
...it burns me...
...I don't comprehend it.
Are you guys on drugs?
I don't know what's wrong with her.
She hasn't been sleeping
and burned her hand.
Is it bad? I know a doctor...
If you need one.
Do you have sleeping pills?
We don't use those.
I have something better...
let's go to the house.
- Now!
- Let's go.
Who did this to you?
It hurts?
I gave her some herbs, she has to
drink them with hot water.
Why are you talking to me in English?
This shit's a mess.
This idiot had another fight with Alicia.
Agustín, where are you? Over.
Barbara, we're messing around
with the walkie-talkies at Bernardo's...
We're having some of Melda's bread.
Over and out.
Take her clothes off.
Bernardo, can we take her to your house?
Please.
Put her on the couch.
What's going on?
Laurita, go to bed!
What's going on Agustín?
She jumped in the lake. She says
she hasn't slept in four days...
I don't know what the
fuck is wrong with her!
Calm down, what's wrong baby?
I have some sleeping pills.
What pills?
- Give her two.
- I'm not giving her those things.
Let me do this.
Easy, easy...
Open your mouth.
Come on, open your mouth.
Open your mouth... there you go.
- Calm down.
- Swallow.
Melda, you said you knew a doctor.
- She is not a doctor!
- Yes she is!
Where you picked me up.
Anything is better than here.
Calm down, OK?
Hey, come, come.
She is your friend, OK? She is
going to take care of you.
Look at her, she's going to take
care of you, OK? I'll be right back.
Calm down!
Bernardo gave her sleeping pills.
She is not doing good.
I think she's a bit crazy, look at her.
She is going to get ready now.
Tell your friends that
everything is going to be OK.
Sit over there.
Spanish.
Speak Spanish!
What's going on!
Can you explain!?
She says it's not what it looks like...
Her soul is being purified...
...it will come back to her body
and she will regain consciousness...
- ...but we have to let her finish.
- That's a lie!
She's not breathing! She's not breathing!
Call a doctor, please, a doctor!
She's fine! Lower your voice,
we are about to finish!
Keep her warm, keep rubbing
these herbs under her nose.
She's going to be OK.
I'm done.
We have to go.
Agustín, we need to go!