Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
WOMAN 1: The global economy continues
to collapse as food prices spike.
MAN: The world population has now
reached its eighth-billion mark.
WOMAN 2: Food has
now replaced oil
in becoming the most
prized commodity.
WOMAN 3: California has now broken its
all-time record for the longest heatwave.
We now have more than eight
billion mouths to feed.
Even the slightest drop
in our world food supply
can mean the total collapse
of our way of life.
WOMAN 4: Indonesia promises to be
the leading food basket of the world,
as Indra Siswadi,
the youngest elected President
in the history
of the country...
No more hunger!
...declared his mission
in aiding
the new World Hunger
Prevention Initiative.
[CROWD CHANTING]
In times like these,
we can't help but ask,
is this the beginning
of the end?
SARI: Hungry?
Starving.
Wake up.
You got that same squirm
the first time we met.
[CHUCKLES] I don't squirm.
All right, maybe a little.
It feels wrong letting you go
this time, I guess.
CAMERAMAN: Yo, Sari!
We got the one-on-one
with Indra. Let's go!
As in the
Presidential-elect, Indra?
He's gonna change
the world, you know.
Save a lot of people.
You should come.
As soon as I get
myself straight.
Listen...
I got something for you.
There's no stone yet,
so, I guess it won't be
official until...
But I will. I mean...
As... As soon as...
Shut the fuck up.
[HORN HONKING]
Can a proposed girl
get a minute here?
I'll take that as a yes?
You'll have to ask for my
parents' blessings first, dummy.
They'd kill you
if they found out about this.
Copy that.
Ask me again
when I get back.
And next time,
don't mumble.
Yes, ma'am.
SARI: Wake up.
WOMAN 2:
Morning, Mr. Congressman.
Thank you for last night.
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
VOICE ASSISTANT: Good morning.
It is 8:00 a.m.
[DISTORTED ELECTRONIC
VOICE SPEAKING]
AUTOMATED FEMALE VOICE:
The future is now.
AUTOMATED MALE VOICE: Puninar.
Your trusted solutions partner
and the logistics
of the future.
- Play on.
- [JAZZY UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEEPING]
[SIGHS]
All right.
What is it this time?
[DRONE WHIRRING]
[CROWD SHOUTING AND CLAMORING]
WOMAN: [OVER PA]
PIRANAS delinquents,
please stay behind the fence
and remain calm.
MAN: Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Attention.
Please stay behind the fence
and remain calm.
SOLDIER: Get back inside!
[SHOUTING AND GRUNTING]
[CRYING] Mama.
Mama!
WOMAN: [OVER PA] Please proceed to the
filtering facility in an orderly manner.
[COINS JINGLING]
All citizens
must stand in line
to secure your
weekly ration quota.
You a Marine girl?
Sergeant Raya, sir.
How'd you figure that, sir?
Well, let's just say you and I
both know how to respect the quiet,
- unlike the Air Force.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Yes, sir.
- [CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
AUTOMATED VOICE: This is
Level One PIRANAS Military.
All personnel must uncover their faces
and heads for facial identification.
[BEEPING]
[ANGGA SIGHING]
Ah, Mr. Secretary.
- How's it hanging, sir?
- Shriveled.
Licked by many,
deformed by all the bullshit.
But I digress.
I regret I asked.
Listen.
It is a gross
understatement to say...
that it's difficult for me
to get this kind of meeting.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Do not embarrass me.
[MAN LAUGHING]
Mr. President.
Congressman Angga.
The man I've been
telling you about.
Mr. President.
As you must already know,
in the cowboy hat,
Mr. Hengky Laksono.
Man in charge
of all things public media.
More handsome in person
than on TV, I'm sure.
SOEGANDA:
General Adnan Atmadja,
Commander of
the GERRAM Paramilitaries.
And the head of
the PIRANAS Party himself,
Mr. Farid Baskoro.
It's a pleasure
to finally meet you, sir.
I like to think of them as
the four pillars of PIRANAS.
More like the four horsemen.
[MEN LAUGHING]
Impressive job
on that Farmer's Bill.
Looks like you wanna be
on the winner's team.
ANGGA: Always, Mr. President.
But...
enough with the ass-kissing.
Truth is, gentlemen...
you suck at PR.
- Angga.
- Let him speak.
You see, our economy...
well, it may be in the lead.
But, the biggest threat...
still lies within.
Gentlemen, the people
are starving.
Their nationalism, morale...
dying.
So, you're saying
we need to cut our profits
and fight
world hunger bullshit?
I'm saying, all they need...
is a dream.
Something that'll take
their minds off the hunger.
A promise of a better future.
A Heroic Act.
You see, gentlemen,
The Reform,
they're secretly gaining
massive followers.
Promising more food for all.
And whether
you like it or not,
the people will side with anyone
who can offer them change.
And these guys,
they're saying exactly
what they want to hear.
You're looking at a ticking
time bomb strapped to your ass.
What are you proposing?
We destroy their idea.
Regains the people's trust.
PIRANAS gets a new face-lift.
Then, we can enjoy
our riches in peace.
I volunteer for the lead.
Black Ops. Off the books.
And in return...
I want 1%
of what PIRANAS makes.
Every year...
for the rest of its days.
GENERAL ADNAN: Holy shit.
[LAUGHTER]
[DOOR OPENS]
[ANGGA EXHALES]
I hate it when you do that.
Tell me I got it.
Don't know how
you pulled that shit off.
But... you got it, kid.
[GROANS IN RELIEF]
What's this?
The catch.
They want you to lead the
operation with The Wolf himself.
Wisnu.
What?
Get me back in there.
You walk in there...
we'll lose
this opportunity forever.
I dislike the guy as much as you
do, you know that.
But they trust his ass
more than yours.
Do not screw this up.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
Finally,
the four old men...
have come to their senses.
The hunger has turned us
against each other.
No. It only shows you
who you really are.
Guess we'll be working
together again.
[CHUCKLES]
People are savages,
don't you think?
We like to believe
we're better than animals.
But the truth is, we kill.
We feed off each other
just the same.
Just the same.
In this jungle,
either you eat...
or be eaten.
Take a look.
Prototype suit.
Shipped this morning.
American.
My God.
An invisibility cloak?
Yes.
They call it "The Hide."
Combine military-grade
LED Kevlar
with nano cameras
within the seams.
First, the UAVs,
the Kodiaks,
and now this.
They're licking our asses clean.
Speaking of tactics,
your so-called Heroic Act is...
no offense, idiotic.
We are here
to preserve order,
not practice democracy.
Well, I'm not here
for your opinion.
You're still the same mutt
I met years ago.
And me?
Still head of this operation.
So, fall in.
You know...
I used to love
dressing up like Rambo.
Thought I'd be
more respected.
It taught me a very,
very valuable lesson.
Oh, yeah?
What's that?
- [GUN COCKS]
- Fear!
Unlike in the movies,
real people, primitives...
have no respect for bravery,
or kindness, or heroes.
Only fear.
You wanna stop
your Reform?
The only way
is to exterminate them.
You've got company.
All units, black quad drone!
North side!
Don't let it get away!
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
MAN: Go!
Hey.
Hey, you!
Somebody...
Shoot!
Hey!
Hey, stop!
Hey, you. Stop!
[GROANS]
Bitch!
Right there!
Stop right there!
Hands. I wanna see them now!
Who do you work for?
Turn around, slowly!
The smart pad,
toss it over!
Hey, do you hear me?
[GUNS COCKING]
I'm a government official,
on duty.
People will be
looking for me.
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
Stay back!
Weapons down, now!
- [MAN PANTING]
- [GRUNTS]
SARI: Stop!
Sari?
Lower your guns.
I know this man.
He's not one of 'em.
I... I thought
you were dead.
What does Wisnu
know about us?
You joined the Reform?
If you can't get me
what I need,
- then you should leave.
- Sari, wait!
Come with me.
I've got everything
we've ever wanted.
I can protect you...
You helped incite
the Revolution.
You really think
I didn't know that?
I covered corruption stories
for breakfast, for God's sake.
I did it for us!
Don't you see
what this world has become?
Hey, do you hear me?
Mom.
Pack your things, honey.
- We're leaving.
- [SCOFFS]
I get it.
And you're blaming me!
She's yours.
What?
Since I found out
you were involved,
Indra was being hunted...
We went underground,
spent years building
this Reform together.
You founded the Reform?
You've been fed
on lies, Angga.
Then I just gave you
the death sentence.
Get out!
Now!
[WARBLING]
- [WARBLING CONTINUES]
- [GROANING]
[GROANING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
- [SCREAMING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
[SCREAMING]
- [SLASHING]
- [GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
[PANTING]
[SCREAMS]
- [SLASHING]
- [BOTH GROANING]
Who's in charge?
Where's the great
Reform's hideout?
- [ALL SCREAMING]
- Guns! Guns!
MEN: Clear!
Alert the Party.
The Congressman is now
an enemy of the state.
[ANIMAL HOWLING]
Of all places,
abandoned shopping mall?
We call it home.
He's with us!
[WHISTLES]
[KEYS JANGLING]
[INDISTINCT WHISPERING]
Sari, Dinda, you all right?
Spec.
Where's everyone?
We're it.
Who's he?
He helped us escape.
He's clean.
ANGGA: If I was a spy, this place
would've been burned to the ground.
Sorry you had to be here.
ANGGA: What are you
trying to achieve?
You want your
presidency back, is that it?
I used to.
I fought so hard for what
this country would be...
could be.
Then, it all just...
faded.
The people,
they need to know
what they're really
suffering for, Congressman.
Greed.
Corruption.
That's why we're here.
Nothing more.
Then what are you
waiting for?
You've got your army with you.
They seem equipped and ready.
Walk with me.
[MAN COUGHING]
INDRA: They were my voters.
Believed in me.
But now they're... here.
But these people,
and the one
that died today...
volunteered.
For me.
You call them army.
I call them family.
If it wasn't for Spec,
we would've never learned
to defend ourselves.
Who is this Spec?
Never knew his real name.
Sari found him
on the streets.
Saved him...
just like she saved me.
Then give me
that one phone call.
I'll guarantee her safety
for the rest of her life.
You have one minute
before they track us down.
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
- Soeganda.
- Ganda, it's me. Listen.
I don't have much time.
Angga, what the hell happened?
They're accusing you
of helping
the separatists,
for God's sake.
I've found her, Ganda.
I've found Sari.
Kid, it's too late.
Your name is on
the GERRAM kill list.
Wisnu has taken your plan and
skewed it into one of his own.
And whatever it is,
it'll be carried out in three days.
In three days?
[STUTTERS] That's impossible.
Ganda, you've gotta help me stop
him, or I'll be dead.
Do you hear me?
Sari will be dead.
Son...
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I love you like my own,
but you cannot
win everything.
I'm sorry.
Good luck out there.
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
I wanna meet him.
SPEC: That takedown...
straight-out military.
Look, I'm putting together
an attack team.
I want you in.
I'm in.
[DOG BARKING]
OGGI: [CHUCKLING] Let me
get this straight.
- You want the five of us...
- Six.
Pardon me, six.
...to go after the adorable
Wisnu and his huggable thugs,
to stop an unknown
PIRANAS conspiracy?
Let's see, they have
a name for that.
What is it? Oh, yeah,
it's treason!
[SCOFFING]
Are you fucking nuts?
We'd... be dead.
D-E-D. Dead!
Besides, look at us.
We've probably forgotten
half the things we used to do.
And who the fuck
is this National Geographic?
Innocent people's lives
- are at stake here.
- Oh, bullshit, LT.
Since when do you care, huh?
Hey, maybe Wisnu is right.
Maybe they are terrorists.
Maybe they all
deserve to die.
I found her, Ogs!
Sari.
And a little girl
that turns out to be mine.
All of us,
we're at the top of the kill list.
Is everything okay in here?
- [SCOFFS]
- I hope you don't mind
- the powder tea.
- Ma! Will you just get out?
Just trying to help.
OGGI: Look...
I feel you.
And PIRANAS, man, I'd shove it up
their bumhole any day of the week.
But I can't.
I...
I just can't.
Then we'll show
ourselves out.
It was nice
seeing you again, Ogs.
[DOOR CLOSES]
You must be
so disappointed in me.
Son,
you've always chosen
your own path.
And you've always
pulled through.
Disappointed?
You're just waiting for an
opportunity to impress...
not just me,
but the whole world.
OGGI: LT!
Could use the exercise.
Come on!
I'll show you
where the guys are.
[CROWD CLAMORING
AND CHEERING]
Which one is he?
The one with his face
on the floor.
[YELLING]
[GASPING]
[GRUNTING]
BARA: Look, it's good
to see you guys and all,
but...
really not into reunions.
Isn't that oil
all over you?
So?
No reason.
Listen, Bara...
[EXHALES]
- We got a job for you.
- Yeah.
It's one of those
won't-make-it-out-alive kind.
So it's a suicide mission?
When do we start?
[TINO EXHALES]
What's in it for me?
I told you the amount.
You'd be worry-free
for the next decade.
Oh, stop. We all know
how it is.
Last cash lasted us,
what, huh,
four, five years tops?
Why do you think
they demoted me?
Bullshit graveyard-shift,
checking every damn door
in the PIRANAS Tower
before they finally fired me?
Oh, come on, Tino.
Where was our beloved LT
when the Corp kicked us out?
He got that shiny brand-new
job passing dirty bills.
With taxpayers' money.
Our money.
All right, leave us.
But...
What do you want, Tino?
Finally.
You might've fooled the herd,
not me.
I want what you have.
[SCOFFS]
You think a fancy watch
will change my mind?
Plus a quarter...
of everything in my stash.
Now, are you in...
or out?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Yeah.
LT!
Actually, I was
in the middle of my vlog.
Um, so if you don't mind...
[UPBEAT DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
- I gotta get outta here.
- Just...
- Yo, freckle dick.
- Yo.
[SCREAMS]
[GROANING]
- ETHAN: You son of a...
- ANGGA: Hey!
- [ETHAN GROANING]
- OGGI: Guys, guys, guys, stop!
Hey, hey. Hey!
[ETHAN GROANING]
Ethan, I need the best tech.
I need you to find some
very classified information
on the PIRANAS VIP server.
The PIRANAS server?
You gotta be shitting me.
Look.
We're not supposed
to tell you this, kid, but...
It's a top-secret...
recruitment test.
What?
Only a lucky few
get selected.
You pass this one,
all eyes will be on you, kid.
You'd be famous.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait.
Uh...
Acting gigs,
red carpet famous?
Sky's the limit.
All right.
Here goes nothing.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
MAN: Move! Move!
Stand back! Get out!
Get out of my face.
- MAN: Get back!
- Heads up.
We've got company.
They tracked us.
Shit!
- We've gotta get outta here.
- Wait.
- Who's "they"?
- How much more time?
- This isn't a test, is it?
- How much?
[MONITOR BEEPS]
Come on, come on,
come on!
MAN: Move! Move!
Done. I'm done. Holy shit!
This can't be right, can it?
Tomorrow's date.
Click on that.
What is this?
Nothing but PIRANAS
Senators' profiles.
No.
These are targets.
Sacrificing their own Senators,
scapegoating the Reform.
Wolves in sheep's clothing.
It's a false-flag attack.
There'll be murders
and riots.
Give something for the people
to be angry about.
A government-sanctioned
genocide.
- MAN 1: Left, clear.
- MAN 2: Right, clear!
MAN 3: All clear!
[CHUCKLES]
Get the cavalry.
[CAROUSEL POWERING UP]
[CAROUSEL STOPS]
ANGGA: Electrical manual?
Hey, do you know when
your mother and I first met?
We were instantly drawn
to each other.
You know, like electricity.
She used to say,
"If you come any nearer,
"I'll tase you in the face."
[CHUCKLES]
Anyway... [EXHALES DEEPLY]
Thought I'd make up
for the lost time.
I found it
in the old bookstore.
A free fox pin included
in the back page, too.
Look, I know
I wasn't there for you...
Wake up.
A children's fable?
She's 12, not five.
She's stubborn.
Wonder where she got it from.
[SARI CLEARS THROAT]
You know...
I never really had the chance
to say thank you, for...
what you and the boys did.
So, thank you.
Is it a good time
to meet your parents now?
Oh, you'll never get a chance
to see them now, slick.
You're the bastard
who knocked me up and left me.
Never again.
What?
Don't mumble.
I'll never leave you again.
Maybe it's too late.
I heard about
the attack plan tomorrow.
There's no turning back
from that.
ANGGA: Hey, guys.
Let's get up on the double.
Moving out.
Tino, you're one of
the smartest people I know.
You're gonna start telling me
it's impossible?
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Fucking hell.
We'll think simple.
Subtract.
What is this?
[KNOCKING ON WINDOW]
WISNU: For the Reform!
- Ganda!
- Angga!
[BULLETS WHIZZING]
No time to explain.
Let's go!
Move, move!
MAN: Go, go, go!
MAN 2: Go, go, go. Go, go!
Move, move, move.
ANGGA: Get in the car!
WISNU: Stick to the plan.
I'll tell you where to go.
Copy that.
- Smoke 'em out!
TINA: Let's go!
Package is secured!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
I'm on it. You go.
Spec, no!
[THUDDING]
Holy shit!
We've got Kodiaks.
We gotta get out of here!
ANGGA: Go, go, go!
Get in!
Let's go! Let's go!
No. Sari!
[MUFFLED] No!
[GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
WISNU: Wasn't easy or cheap!
But whatever you manage
to destroy...
we fix.
- MAN: Oh, my God.
- [GUNS COCKING]
Spent a lifetime searching
for this filthy rabbit hole.
But now that I'm here...
it feels like home.
What did you do to her?
No, put that away.
[CHUCKLES]
She's just pretty beat up from
putting up a mean fight, is all.
Killed three of my men.
Why don't you tell your men
to drop their antique toys...
- before I put a hole in her face.
- [GRUNTS]
[GRUNTS]
[NOOSE TIGHTENING]
Roll, please!
[INDISTINCT GROANING]
Long live the Reform.
- [SWITCH CLICKS]
- [WHIRRING]
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[ALL GROANING]
[MUFFLED] No!
[WHIRRING STOPS]
[EXHALES]
And that's it!
Quick,
simple, graphic.
Just how the people want it.
You fuck!
Well, I got a surprise
for you.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
MAN: Congressman!
Congressman, here!
Dinda!
Dinda, you all right?
- Mama!
- [GRUNTS]
Dinda! Mommy's okay, baby.
Mama's all right.
Look, you win, all right?
The Reform is finished!
What else do you
want from me?
You like making deals, right?
So here's one for you.
[PRISONERS CLAMORING]
You see this remote?
Say, "I see it."
- I see it!
- Good.
It triggers the bomb I planted
on the elevator's cable.
Set it to...
- one minute.
- [BOMB BEEPING]
So you gotta choose
how you spend that minute.
Save your woman,
or your kid.
But if I were you,
I'd use it to haul
my own ass out of here.
[GROANING]
You've shown what you would
do for the ones you love.
Now show them
who you really are.
SARI: Hey, you.
You will die in pieces.
Let him be.
And kill the others.
MAN: Move!
[STRAINING]
[PRISONERS CLAMORING]
[GRUNTING]
[WHIRRING]
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[OBJECT THUDDING]
[YELLING]
[MUFFLED GRUNTING]
- [BONES CRUNCHING]
- [GRUNTING]
[GUNSHOT]
[PANTING AND GRUNTING]
Hold on, honey!
[BEEPING]
[PANTING AND WHIMPERING]
INDRA: Hey, Dinda.
What are you doing?
[COUGHING AND GRUNTING]
- [SARI GRUNTING]
- [PRISONERS CLAMORING]
What are you doing?
She's in there!
Get off me!
Stop! Stop...
Will you stop it?
[YELLS IN FRUSTRATION]
[BEEPING]
[EXPLOSION]
No!
[ALL CLAMORING]
[ELEVATOR STOPS]
You killed my daughter,
you monster!
Get off of me!
[SARI GRUNTING]
ANGGA: Hold on!
[GRUNTING]
- The emergency brakes.
- DINDA: Mama!
- We're okay!
- Do you hear that?
Dinda's fine.
- I'm gonna get you up. [GRUNTS]
- [DINDA YELLING INDISTINCTLY]
Don't you give up...
Ah, shit!
[ANGGA GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
Angga! Listen to me!
You take care of her.
Tell her...
be brave for the new world
to come.
Sari, please.
I can't lose you again.
Wake up.
You never did.
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
Papa!
I'm here!
Listen to my voice, Papa!
[EXHALES]
DINDA: Papa!
Over here!
Just follow my voice!
Papa!
Dinda, honey. I can't.
I don't know what to do.
Listen. We're gonna be okay.
Get to the emergency
staircase!
We need you
to pull us out.
Come on! Focus!
Hold on.
[BREATH TREMBLING]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
DINDA: Papa!
- Dinda!
- We're back here!
[CREAKING]
- [GROANS]
- Angga!
[GRUNTING]
I'll get us help!
[SCREAMING]
[DINDA WHIMPERING]
What are you
waiting for?
[EXPLOSION]
[ANGGA GRUNTS]
Pull!
Hold on!
[COUGHING]
[HELICOPTER HOVERING]
[SIRENS WAILING]
Sergeant.
They know everything.
Never a big fan
of PIRANAS anyway, sir.
We're here to help.
MAN: Who told you?
It has been
eight excruciating hours
since the capital kidnapping
incident this morning.
Seven senators have
been held hostage so far,
with no signs of demand
by the Reform separatists.
That is, until recently,
when an anonymous video
was made public
for the world to see.
Warning.
What you are about to see is
graphic and may disturb you.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[SIGHS]
TINO: Who are we
kidding, huh?
How could six has-beens stop
the government in three days?
We were fucked
from the start.
What are you doing?
Leaving.
Job's done, remember?
Our mugs are registered on the
top of the wanted list, Tino.
No shit.
If we stay here,
we're dead.
Where do you think
you're going?
The PIRANAS Tower.
TINO: Why?
How?
- Never mind.
- Tino.
No, no, no,
it's fucking brilliant.
Even if we do manage
to get inside the gates...
[SCOFFS] The Tower's
like a maze.
We can't make it to the second
floor, let alone the VIP chamber.
Yeah, but you can.
You said it yourself,
you used to work graveyard there.
You know its every
floor plan, inside and out.
Maybe you've forgotten,
but they just butchered us out there!
Including his
precious girlfriend!
I'm going back.
I am going back!
Un-fucking-believable.
You two deserve
each other!
Sir, couldn't help
but hearing.
The presidential address
is only hours away.
Even if you were
able to stop them,
you won't make it
there in time. Sir.
[AIRCRAFT ENGINE WHIRRING]
Not by driving,
anyway, sir.
I'll tell them
you hijacked it.
Thank you, Sergeant.
I'm afraid we can't
join your fight, sir.
- We're still under constant...
- I'm not asking you to.
Help as many people out there
as you can, Sergeant.
Oh, and sir...
I think this
belongs to you.
They were tearing
your place apart,
so I kind of stole it.
Good luck out there, sir.
[HEROIC INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
If, uh...
- If I don't come back...
- You will.
So, shut up.
You're just like
your mother.
Go get them, Pa.
PILOT: Ready engine one.
Ready engine two.
Clear skies.
Ready for take-off.
Hold on.
Someone's coming.
- [SIGHS]
- Two minutes!
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
Gather up.
We got a one-hour window
before the cavalry comes in.
Maybe less.
Remember, you only need one
confession to stop all this.
Tino?
Our best point of entry
is the holding area, here.
But in order to get there, we have to
circle around the construction sites, here,
and the trucking hold, here.
It's our best bet in making
it to the Tower alive.
We'll split into four teams.
Ethan, you're the key.
Go to the main
control room.
Override the system.
Lock down their security gates,
doors, and helipad access.
You open only the ones leading
up to the VIP chambers.
- You got all that?
- Any backup, sir?
You're on your own
this time, kid.
Yes, sir.
Oggi, Tino...
you guys are in charge
of the explosives.
Spec?
South watch tower.
360 kill zone.
Bara, you stay with me.
Millions of lives
are at stake tonight.
They're counting on us.
And me...
I'm counting on you.
[ALL YELL]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go! Go!
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
WOMAN: [OVER PA]
Attention.
The state of martial law
has been issued.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
MAN: [INTO EARPIECE]
In position.
Clear.
- [GRUNTS]
- [BEEPING]
Three, two, one.
Execute.
[GUNSHOT]
MAN: Target neutralized.
Left, clear.
Right, clear.
All clear.
Hold for visual.
We got a confirmed,
VIP vehicle exiting compound.
Positive ID.
Farid Baskoro.
- Shit!
- Let him go.
Remember, we only need one
of the PIRANAS Four anyway.
Let's do this.
[SIREN BLARING]
FEMALE REPORTER: The
national curfew is in effect.
It is chaos here
in the city,
as the nation
is on lockdown,
the borders closed and a curfew
issued, due to the nationwide manhunt.
All citizens must
remain indoors until...
You two, hands up!
Now! Get...
Shit.
I can't believe
I'm doing this.
Get the strike squad.
Check the control room.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[BEEPING]
Last one up.
Hope they all work.
[GRUNTING]
RV's clear.
Ethan, strike squad
is en route.
Main exits compromised.
Ethan, get the hell out
of there now.
Wait. I need more time.
Ethan, do you hear me?
Get out, now!
MAN: Move!
[ETHAN SCREAMING]
Shit, he's compromised.
They're gonna be here
any second.
Kid, if you hear me...
we have to go.
I'm sorry.
Do it.
- [EXPLOSIONS]
- [MEN GASP]
- Sons of bitches!
- [ALARM BLARING]
No!
It's a distraction.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Security breach.
They're here
for the VIPs.
Go to the construction site.
You stop them.
You heard him!
Let's move out!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
[GUNSHOT]
I'll hold them off.
They're gonna catch up on us
and you know it!
Me and this butter face,
we got unfinished business.
Guess I'll see you inside.
Why don't you tell
your friends to come out?
I have no friends.
No weapons.
No vest.
Just me.
If that's how
you want it.
You're gonna shoot
an unarmed man?
Come on.
Put a bruise on me.
Break my arm...
something.
Let's make
this simple, then.
All of you against me.
[LAUGHS]
Holster your weapons.
Let's show this clown
what pain really feels like.
Damn. I don't
have all day.
[MEN GRUNTING AND YELLING]
[YELLING]
Get the fuck up.
[LAUGHS]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS]
Hell...
three out of five.
Ain't bad. [LAUGHS]
[YELLING]
[SCREAMS]
Gotta hand it to you.
You got some spirit.
Still breathing, asshole.
[GRUNTS]
[LAUGHING]
[SCREAMING]
[LAUGHS]
You wanted me
to break your arm.
[LAUGHING]
Wash your mouth.
What did you say?
You should wash
your fucking mouth!
[LAUGHING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[ALARM BLARING]
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Security breach.
- Security breach.
- [BLARING]
We got activity.
[BLARING]
Kodiaks!
Covering fire!
[SCREAMING]
- Frags out!
- ALL: Frags out!
[BEEPING]
[ALL GROANING]
Fuck, I'm hit! I'm hit!
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
Armor's blind
without the camera.
Spec, tell me
you got a visual.
- MAN 1: Sniper, top side.
- MAN 2: Go!
Let's go, let's go.
ANGGA: Spec,
take their camera out.
[BANGING ON DOOR]
Spec, you're breaking up.
Ogs!
Spec, take the shot.
Spec, take
the fucking shot!
[GRUNTING]
OGGI: Hey, fatso!
Ogs!
Ogs.
[COUGHS]
No, no, no.
[STAMMERING]
Left vest pocket.
- What?
- Left vest pocket.
I'm gonna get you
some help, Ogs.
[STUTTERS] You...
are gonna clear up
this whole mess...
right, LT?
You're gonna
save those people.
Right?
Damn right, we are.
I must be
such a disappointment.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Security breach.
TINO: They're coming.
[PANTING]
We gotta go.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Security breach.
We gotta go!
[TINO GROANING]
Security breach.
[GRUNTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [GROANS]
MAN: Congressman!
Commander Adnan.
ADNAN:
This ends now!
- The Four...
- [GRUNTS]
They're gonna get away.
Both of us...
we're gonna finish this.
If you really
believe in this,
then you better
hurry the fuck up.
An elevator...
It'll take you straight
to the VIP chamber.
I'll see you
on the other side.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
He's breaking in!
Split up!
On me!
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[SCREAMING]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[YELLING]
[GROANING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Game over.
[GROANING]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
What?
No, no, no, no.
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS ANGRILY]
MAN: Move, move!
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING HEAVILY]
Come on,
you sons of bitches.
[GUN COCKING]
- [DOOR CREAKING]
- [ANGGA BREATHING HEAVILY]
[WHEEZING]
[WIND HOWLING]
[INHALES]
Every man for himself.
[COCKS GUN]
[CLICKS EMPTY]
[HIGH-PITCHED RINGING]
[MUFFLED PANTING]
[SCREAMS]
- [BONES CRUNCHING]
- [SCREAMING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANING]
WISNU: Unbelievable.
How many lives do
you got, Congressman?
[THUDDING]
[MECHANICAL WHIRRING]
ETHAN: LT, come on.
Ethan?
Get behind me!
Get that hatch opened.
[SCREAMING] Wait.
Don't kill me!
Down on the floor!
Get down on the floor
right now!
Confess PIRANAS'
conspiracy on record.
Authorize your company and
broadcast it live, nationwide.
Are you fucking crazy?
They'll put me in front
of the firing squad.
Authorize it.
Make the call.
- [BEEPS]
- [LINE RINGING]
It's me.
There'll be an incoming
video upload
through the central
PIRANAS server.
Just broadcast it as soon
as you receive it.
Nationwide.
Live.
"Do it, or your ass
is fired."
Do it, or your ass
is fired.
Confess.
[CAMERA BEEPS]
My name
is Hengky Laksono.
I am here tonight...
- to tell...
- [GUNSHOT]
[YELLING]
[CHOKING]
[WISNU GRUNTS]
- Ethan, no!
- WISNU: Stop.
Just stop.
What the hell
happened here?
Relax, Mr. President.
Everything is under control.
Systems back online and
Garuda One is ready to go.
Congressman Angga.
You used to have everything.
But now...
you're just like them.
I never planned
for a genocide!
You and your
PIRANAS flag did that!
But I'm not the one who's
committing genocide, Congressman!
The people are!
You fed them a lie,
for God's sake!
Great things are done
with extreme measures.
You showed us that tonight.
Destroyed the enemy's image,
restored the people's
faith in us.
All in less
than a week.
Brilliant, Congressman.
Brilliant.
Now, if you please
excuse me...
I have a public
to address.
My, uh...
"Heroic Act,"
as you call it.
Goodnight, Congressman.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
And he's gone.
It's over.
Now, tell me.
Was she worth it?
Did you really think
people would stop
just because of some
stupid confession video?
Those primitive
will burn,
steal,
rape and kill
all they want.
You know why?
Because the hungry
cares not for justice.
Only for their
own stomach.
But you're wrong.
What they care for...
is to see you dead!
Get the fuck
out of here!
[PANTING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
[GROANS]
[SCREAMING]
[SCREAMS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GUNSHOT]
[DAGGER CLATTERS]
Will you look at that?
Huh?
Last bullet!
Oh, don't look
at me like that.
You think
I'm the bad guy?
You have no idea what monsters
this world can create!
You chose them!
So, bleed for them!
Pleasure working with
you again, Lieutenant!
CROWD: [CHANTING]
PIRANAS! PIRANAS!
PIRANAS!
[CROWD CHEERING]
My beloved countrymen...
this morning...
the Reform
has committed
their most heinous and
cowardly act of terror.
[CROWD BOOING]
I am angry.
I am furious!
[CROWD CHEERING]
With this law,
every citizen...
is now legally responsible
for all members of the Reform.
Starting tonight,
your hunger will be fulfilled!
[CROWD CHEERING]
We will hunt down those
separatist traitors to the ground!
So, let
the manhunt begin!
CROWD: [CHANTING]
PIRANAS!
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
[GROANING]
Done with it.
So...
done with it.
CROWD: [CHANTING]
PIRANAS! PIRANAS!
PIRANAS!
[CHANTING STOPS]
You used to have everything.
What is this?
Who put this up?
But now...
you're just like them.
ANGGA: I never planned
for a genocide!
- Hey, shut it down.
- You and your PIRANAS flag did that!
- Shut it down, now.
- But I'm not the one
who's committing genocide,
Congressman!
The people are!
MAN: You lied to us!
- Good citizens...
- [CROWD BOOING]
Hear me.
This is a setup.
Just another of those
Reform's plots.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[CROWD SHOUTING]
And, listen...
Get me out
of here, now!
[CROWD SHOUTING]
- [SCOFFS]
- [ALL LAUGH]
Get out of my way.
I said, get the fuck
out of my way.
[CLICKS]
That motherfucker.
[SCREAMS]
[ALL SHOUTING]
It's been a week since the
President's infamous confession leaked
and went viral.
The President
and his administration
are being labeled
as suspects,
and will be put on trial
sometime next week.
The question
still remains,
is the President
a patriot or a traitor?
But recently,
there may be arguably
bigger questions at play.
Who is this man
behind the camera?
WOMAN: Who the people
are now calling,
"the hero of
the new Republic."
We now know that his
name is Ethan Suryadi,
a former Indonesian Marine
officer turned small-time vlogger.
Did Ethan work alone?
Who else was involved?
It seems like
we'll be getting
more questions
than answers.
At least, for now.
Good look on you.
[SCOFFS]
Not so bad yourself.
I guess you found
Spec's body.
No.
It was just blood.
Lots of it.
He couldn't have survived it.
And Tino?
Bailed.
No goodbye, nothing.
[SCOFFS] Who knows
what he's up to.
[SOBBING]
Excuse me.
Permission to return this.
In honor
of your son, ma'am.
[SOBBING]
You were with him.
What was he like?
Best man
I've known, ma'am.
Best man I'll ever know.
That's my son.
Hungry?
No.
No, I'm good.
The book you gave me...
The fox pin and the last
pages were burned in the fire.
Guess I'll never know
the ending.
We'll just have to
make our own, then.
Won't we?
CROWD: [CHANTING]
Food for all! Food for all!
Food for all!
Food for all...
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- Whoa.
- Shit.
When's the last time
you had chocolate?
we could afford it?
[RUSTLING]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org