(explosion)
(chimes)
(machine noises)
(waves crashing)
(traffic sounds)
(people laughing)
(crackling sparklers)
(dance music)
- Yo, man!
- Beaker!
- Elliot, you owe me one.
- Hey what's up?
- Brad, how you doing?
(loud conversation)
Hey.
- Hey.
- So how've you been?
- I'm good. How you been?
- Good; I got a job.
- A real one?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, just a gig at a print
shop; a friend hooked me up.
- How's that going?
- I hate it.
- Figures.
I'm just gonna sit here
as long as you talk to me.
(sighs)
- Can we just not make this weird?
- I'm not making it weird.
- Just wanna stick... to
small conversation, okay?
Just small talk.
- Well I fucking hate small talk.
- Guess what, I fucking hate not knowing
what to say to you, so.
- No one's forcing you
to say anything, so.
- You just want me to sit
here, not talk to you?
- It's an option; we all
have options in life.
- I was gonna talk to you earlier.
Me being me, I didn't know what to say.
(laughs)
I didn't even know you
were gonna be here tonight.
- Liar.
- Boggles
- What?
- Boggles.
Nothing.
I mean, what if the world
doesn't end tonight, you know?
I don't know, I hope it does.
Be a real big inconvenience
just to have to wake up
and face reality again.
To regret all the shit you said.
- There's nothing wrong with regret.
- Yeah there is: it's a waste of time.
- People should be able to regret
whatever the fuck they want.
- You know we can't just start over.
- Yeah.
- Wouldn't want to even if we could.
What happened, happened.
- Yeah.
(sighs)
- What now?
- Fuck if I know.
- You okay with that?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
(lighter sparks)
(traffic sounds)
(deep exhale)
(grocery store muzak)
(vibrating phone)
- Babe, why are you calling?
You know I'm at work.
- I forgot.
- I was just, uh, finishing this up.
- Are you on the phone?
- No.
- [Eddie] It looks like
you're on the phone.
- Eddie, go away.
- I just don't want Hannover
finding out, you know?
- I won't tell if you don't.
- Who are you talking to?
- It's just Eddie.
- [Kurt] Who?
- No one. You should
finish cleaning your room.
- I don't know, I kinda like it.
- [Paul] You going to Amsterdam?
- If I get any calls, then yeah.
Right now I'm just...
Doing some organizing.
- [Paul] Well I still
have a couple more hours
before my (inaudible) leaves,
so can I just call you later?
- Okee-doke, love you.
- Love you more.
Bye.
- We have breaking news for you now.
The body of an unidentified
young male was found last night
near Belmont and Halsted.
This is believed to be another victim
of the Boystown Butcher.
A neighbor, walking their dog,
found the man unresponsive
and face down in an alley.
He had been stabbed in the
upper and lower abdomen.
- Can you believe another
kid died last night?
- No, it's fucked up.
- [Reporter] It is the
fifth unsolved murder
in the Boystown neighborhood.
- That's like, what,
the fourth since June?
- [Reporter] Autopsy results are pending,
- Hey turn that shit off; it's depressing.
- [Reporter] but police
think the stab pattern
is identical to the
string of other murders.
- Later.
- [Kurt] Paul, you are beautiful!
(door closing)
- Found you some goodies,
from the Oasis Grocery Store.
You're welcome.
- Did you steal these?
- Mm-hmm.
- Why do you do that?
You're gonna get fired.
(sigh)
- Where's Brad?
- Um, Alison's, probably.
- Sorry about this, but it's something
we're both gonna have to deal with.
- I got a call, I'm going to Pilsen.
What?
- Nothing, I just hate that
you go out there alone.
- Why don't you come with me?
- Why don't you not be a drug dealer?
- What so I can work 40 hours
a week and barely make rent?
- Didn't another guy get
killed over there last night?
- It's Chicago; people die every day.
(tv weather forecast)
- I wanna come with you tonight.
- I'll be fine.
- Okay, I believe you.
I just wanna get out and stretch my legs.
- Okay, but they're gonna think it's weird
if you don't smoke; it's offensive.
- Okay, well if it's your
image you're worried about,
I'll try my best to make you look good.
- I just don't want you
freaking out like last time.
- That was a one-time thing.
- Yeah, one time?
- Yeah, one time.
- Yeah, we had to call the cops,
and they found you in an attic, naked,
hugging a Christmas tree.
- It was hot in that attic.
- Yeah, I know it was hot in that attic.
(laughter)
- Okay, I'll be good.
- Promise?
- Mm-hmm.
- Pinky swear?
- Pinky swears, kiss it.
(techno music)
(low conversation)
- Hey, I got 20; is that all right?
- Yeah, let's see what we got.
There you go.
- Thank you very much.
- No problem.
- You're fine, you're fine.
We're all good, we're good in here.
Everything's fine, we're
having a good time.
Having a really good...
Good, huh?
- Tasty; what do you call this?
- Solar Flare.
That's what I'm told.
- Catchy.
I used to buy from this
one guy down the street.
He sold Hemp Hash, aka Very Berry.
- So you're telling me he's
a pothead with an alias.
- Yeah, you know, just in
case you didn't like one name,
you could call it the other.
- Sounds like a douche bag to me.
(laughs)
- Where'd your friend go?
- Uh, my boyfriend?
- He's cute.
- Thanks; I think he's in the bathroom.
- Everything's two-dimensional.
- So where're you from?
- Around.
- Around...?
- I don't give out my address to customers
or strangers, sorry.
- I'm not a stranger, I haven't
bought anything yet, so.
- Not yet.
- So can I call you?
- I'm pretty busy.
- Are you turning me down?
(laughing)
- All right, put your number in my phone.
I'll text you later so
that way you get mine.
- Okay, oh, Kevin.
- Kurt.
- There you go.
(phone vibrates)
- Be right back.
- I'll be here.
(rapid knocking)
- Paul?
Paul, I know you're in there.
(sighs)
Paul.
- Hi.
(laughs)
I wasn't sure you were gonna make it here.
I thought, "he's gonna get lost."
But you're here!
I'm good!
- You're freaking out.
(scoffs)
- I hate this.
I don't know why I do this.
- It's all in your head,
babe, don't worry about it.
- I feel like an idiot.
- I think it's cute.
- I want a drink.
- Yeah?
You want a drink?
All right, we'll get some
booze on the way home.
Can you get up?
Ready to go?
- Mmm.
- Yeah?
I have to call 911 again?
Good, come on, let's head out of here.
- I can't go out there like this.
- It's fine.
- They're gonna see me.
- I'm done, it's fine, come on.
We can sneak out the back way, okay?
- I'm high as a motherfucker.
Thanks for taking care of me, baby.
- You're welcome, kiddo.
- Mm!
Asshole.
- Wake up!
- Mm-mm.
- Let's go to the beach.
- Come on.
- Mm, I'm still high.
- Let's go.
- Mm-mm.
- Hey!
- No.
Fucker!
- Little bitch.
(yelling)
- All right, come on, let's go.
(crashing to the floor)
- Little soda?
All right, you're good, you're good.
Can you stop?
Don't do it, don't, don't do it, stop.
(laughing)
- Who're you looking at?
- No one.
- Ah, you're looking at someone.
- Over there, yellow shorts.
- Black?
- Yeah.
(laughs)
What, don't you ever
wonder what it'd be like
to do a black guy?
- Uh, nope, not really,
I'm in love with you.
- You're telling me that you
don't look at other people?
- What is this?
- [Kurt] It's a question.
- Yeah I look at other guys.
- Okay, is there anyone on
this beach you find attractive?
Besides me, of course.
- Is this a test?
- [Kurt] No, Paul, I just
wanna know what you're into.
- I'm into you.
- Okay, so then pretend I'm not
the greatest boyfriend on the planet.
- Done.
- Tell me who you'd
settle for on this beach.
(uncertain noises)
Come on.
- That guy, green shorts.
- Ugh, the guido?
- He is not a guido.
- Paul, he's a guido.
(laughs)
- Okay, if you're just gonna
make fun of me, then he's ugly.
- Is that what you want?
- You're being stupid right now.
- I don't see how I can compete with that.
- [Paul] You don't have to
compete with anyone; I'm yours.
- I mean he's got those
arms, and that tan.
- Oh shit, yeah, you're right.
- Me, I'm just extremely
intelligent, savvy, and personable.
- Yeah, modestly drunk,
yep, you got 'em all, babe.
- Yeah.
- We should go somewhere.
(sighs)
- Where do you wanna go?
- Like Paris.
- I was thinking more along the lines of
that ice cream hut over there, but okay.
- [Paul] I'm serious.
- So was I.
- Just you and me in a foreign country,
I don't know, doing whatever.
- We can do whatever here.
- It's not the same.
Well don't you ever get
tired of the same old thing
over and over?
- No?
- Okay, well I do.
What do we do?
All we ever do is we go to work,
we drink, we smoke, we sleep.
- So what?
I like my job, I like drinking.
- So you're happy?
- I'd say so, yeah, aren't you?
- Yeah, I don't know, I
just think it'd be fun
to do something different, that's all.
- I'm toasty.
(laughs)
- My mom says toasty; you're
turning into my mother.
- Come on, let's go swimming.
- Okay, help me up.
- Let's go!
- My handsome steed.
- Hey.
- You look tired.
- Got a little something.
- Are you drunk?
- No, why?
- You smell like booze.
- I don't smell anything.
- I can smell it.
- Okay, Eddie.
- You're supposed to use
the cone when you do that.
Someone could get hurt.
- Thank you so much for taking me, dude,
this place is so good.
- Love you.
- Try some of this.
- Mm-mm.
- Come on, try.
- No, no, no.
Why do you always do that?
Why do you always try
to feed me your food?
If I wanted shrimp, I
would've order shrimp.
I don't like it.
- Okay, why not?
- Because I don't.
Why don't you like smoking weed?
- Because it's stupid.
- Okay, how about this:
you take a bong hit,
and I'll try some of that.
- That's not a fair trade-off.
- Well I think it is,
so agree to disagree.
- You're so touchy, Touchy.
- [Kurt] You started it.
- [Paul] Did not.
- I guess we both did, then.
- Yeah, but then there was that time
when I didn't do anything, and
then you started everything,
and then you attacked me in
the middle of the restaurant,
and then it was all your fault.
- Oh obviously it was
all my fault, as usual.
- Well it was that time.
- [Kurt] It was, it was
definitely my fault, I'm sorry.
- Well I'm sorry, too, for
being the only guy in here
who wanted to share
all this food with you.
- Shh!
- And now you just don't
wanna take part in it,
well that's fine.
- What are we even arguing about?
- We weren't.
Remember our first kiss?
- Mm-hmm, I had pulled
you away from that party
to watch the sunrise.
- I never saw the sunrise
before that, you know.
Let's pretend it's the first time.
- Okay.
- Slower.
- Hey, how much you make last night?
- 500.
- Jesus, why am I still in school?
- Because it's what normal people do?
- If normal is being 100 grand
in debt, then fuck normal.
(laughs)
- At least that 100 grand
gets us a piece of paper
that says we're good at something.
- You check the mail yet?
- No, I'm afraid there might be bills.
- If you need me to cover you this month,
you know I can do it.
- It's fine, I'm just
waiting for a check to clear.
(phone vibrates)
- Hello.
- [Kevin] Kurt?
- Hey, Kevin.
- [Kevin] How's your day been?
- Busy, man, busy.
- [Kevin] Oh, busy's good.
You got time to make another delivery?
- Ooh, I don't know; I'm pretty winded.
- [Kevin] Awe, I'll
make it worth your time.
I'll pay you 20 over your asking price.
- I'm not a whore.
- [Kevin] Apparently not a
good business man, either.
- All right, all right,
let's not get personal.
- [Kevin] Never; just business.
- Um, how about I head
over in about an hour?
I'm gonna make a sandwich first.
- [Kevin] All right,
I'll text you my address.
- Sounds good, I'll see you then.
- [Kevin] Bye, Kurt.
- Bye, Kevin.
(soda can fizzes over)
Shit.
- Just take a seat anywhere.
(loud sex upstairs)
(laughs)
Neighbors.
- Nice.
(scoffs)
I really like your place, it's nice.
- It's okay, my parents pay for it, so.
- Must be nice.
- Not really; they've
got my balls on a leash.
(laughs)
(increasingly louder sex)
So you make house calls?
- Yeah, I - sorry - I
know it's not the usual,
but I promised my roommate
I wouldn't be selling drugs
inside the apartment, so here I am.
- You should be careful;
it's only a matter of time
before you get caught or worse.
- Hey, I'm pretty careful.
Oh, um, how much did you want?
- What's your best deal?
- I can do an eighth for 50?
- Sounds good; same stuff as before?
- [Kurt] Yep, Solar Flare.
- Shweet.
For your efforts.
- No, don't worry about it.
- Consider it incentive
for future business.
Wanna burn?
(opening package, plastic crinkling)
- I should go.
- You should stay, just one hit?
- I gotta go, I promised I'd be somewhere.
But I'll take a
rain-check, how about that?
- I'm gonna hold you to that.
- All right.
- All right, I'll show you out.
So that was fun.
- Yeah.
- We should hang out again soon.
- I don't know, I'm pretty--
- Busy.
- Yeah, and--
- You've got a boyfriend.
- Um.
- I'm sorry, that was bad.
- Why did you do that?
- I don't know, I thought you...
- That never happened.
(sex noises)
Did you cum?
Like a 16 year old.
(laughs)
- You're like a 60 year old man.
Wanna keep going?
- No.
- You hungry?
Let's order some food,
stay in, and watch tv.
- Sounds good.
Stop.
- What?
- Stop it!
(laughs)
Stop!
Stop it, stop.
- What?
Fuck off, Eddie.
(rock music)
(peeing)
(knocking)
- Shit. Just a second.
(persistent knocking)
Just a second!
(zipper)
(door opens)
Hey what the f--
Suddenly need to go, or...?
- Guess not.
- Yeah I was just uh... Want some?
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, it's just weed.
(door shuts)
- How are things?
- Pretty good.
- Is your boyfriend here?
- Not yet; he's on his way though.
- Oh, I did this all
the time freshman year.
It gets you higher.
- Does it?
- It does.
(shower running)
- All right, spark up, let's do it.
There you are.
(phone vibrates)
- Hey, guys.
Is she okay.
(laughs)
- She's a trooper.
Looking for Kurt?
- Yeah, I tried to call him,
but he didn't answer his phone.
- Yeah I haven't seen
him since he got here.
- All right.
(laughing)
- Oh man.
(phone vibrating)
Oh shit.
- Who is it?
- Paul, you made it.
- Yeah, I tried calling you.
- Oh, we were just...
Sorry, it was on silent, you know.
- Yeah.
- Um, this is Kevin.
- Nice to meet you.
We were just trying some of his new shit.
(laughing)
- Yeah it's nice to meet you, too.
All right, okay, all right.
(lighter sparking)
- Hey.
- How was work?
- Same as usual.
- That's good.
Look, nothing happened back there.
- I believe you.
- Do you?
- Why wouldn't I?
- I don't know, Paul,
you seem pretty upset.
- Should I be?
- No, nothing happened.
- I can see that.
Who is he?
- He's just some kid I sell weed to.
- I've seen him before.
- Probably.
- You guys looked like you
were having a lot of fun.
- Yeah he's a fun guy.
Am I not allowed to have fun?
- Just be smart, okay?
- Okay.
- I trust you, I just
don't trust other people;
I know how they are.
- I do, too.
(frustrated sigh)
- I just need to hear it,
just tell me it's not gonna
be an issue, I'm sorry, I know
this is like me freaking out,
just tell me it's not gonna be an issue,
and I'll believe it.
- It's not going to be an issue, okay?
Okay?
- I'm just tired, all right?
I'm sorry, I'm just really tired.
- Come on, do you wanna go home?
- No, I don't.
Know what, I just wanna drink.
- You want a drink?
- I wanna drink; I want a lot to drink.
- Well there's booze back inside.
Come on.
(laughs)
Come on, come on, let's go.
(soft music)
(phone dialing)
- [Kevin] Hey, dude, where you at?
(people partying loudly)
- Are you into me?
- [Kevin] What?!
- [Kevin] No, why?
- Then why did you kiss
me the other night?
- [Kevin] Because I wanted to?
- What does that mean?
- [Kevin] I like you, I don't know.
Man, why don't you come back to the party?
- I can't.
- [Kevin] What?
- No, I can't.
- [Kevin] You can do whatever you want.
I'll see you soon, then?
- Later, not tonight.
- [Kevin] Hey, Kurt?
- What?
- [Kevin] Relax.
- Goodbye, Kevin.
(beep)
(traffic sounds)
(bubbles)
Shit.
- You gotta bubble up.
- I bubbled!
(crash)
- You can't bubble up on
Bubble Up, how bout that?
- Well how the fuck was
I supposed to know that?
- Here we go.
- This game sucks.
(explosion)
I hate it.
- Well don't quit.
I thought you said you were
gonna go a day without smoking.
- Yeah, well you're pissing
me off, so leave me alone.
- I wanna smoke.
- Seriously?
- [Paul] Mm-hmm, yeah.
- Are you sure?
- Mm-hmm, yeah, dude, I want to.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
(soft music)
- What are you doing?
Shit, I don't know, I think I'm too high.
- You're never too high.
- Sorry.
- Is it me?
- No, it's not you, I think
I'm just too fucking high.
Look, let's just be chill.
- All right.
- Babe. Paul.
- What?
- Can't we just lay down
here and not do anything?
- Yeah, but where's the fun in that?
- I'm being serious.
- [Paul] Okay.
- Look, I'm just, I'm not
in the mood, I'm sorry.
- Okay.
I can feel your heartbeat through my back.
(traffic)
- Can I help you? Excuse me?
(stabbing and sounds of struggle)
(sirens)
(retreating footsteps)
- With the investigation
of a Boystown murder
still underway, authorities
continue to pursue all leads.
The entire city's force is on watch
and enforcing strict curfew.
They're asking anyone who
sees anything suspicious
to report it, and reminding people
not to travel alone at night.
("True Grit" by Joywave)
(phone vibrating)
(sizzling)
(music stops)
- We're gonna get another noise complaint.
What are you doing?
- I tried to cook spaghetti,
but I burned the meat.
- It's the thought that counts.
You okay?
- No.
- What happened.
- Paul wants to go to Paris.
But when I think about it...
When I think about the future, I see...
I don't know what I see.
Last night, I dreamt that
I shot him in the head,
then watched him die right in my arms.
When I woke up, I felt
horrible, completely horrible.
But I can't remember if it
was because I'd shot him,
or if I really wanted him dead.
What does that mean.
- I don't know man, it was just a dream.
(coughs)
- You know I don't want to hurt him, Brad.
I couldn't, I wouldn't.
- I don't think you would.
- I'm selfish.
- How?
- It just doesn't make any sense.
He's beautiful, he's kind, he's caring.
And I'd throw it all away right now,
and if it was that easy, I would.
I just wish I could go back
to the beginning, you know?
Back to when things were new and exciting.
Back to when I'd get butterflies
from a fucking text message, you know?
Just waiting for the response.
Everything about them gives you a hard-on.
You always wanna know
exactly what they're doing.
Nothing else matters.
- Yeah.
- [Kurt] It's that spark.
(ethereal music)
It's that spark that fades.
You get to know someone, you
let them under your skin,
and you feel like you're suffocating.
- [Brad] Listen, Kurt.
Are you happy?
Does he make you happy?
- [Kurt] What if there's
someone else out there?
Someone who could make me happier?
- [Brad] There's always someone else.
There's always someone else who's smarter
and cuter, funnier, that's life, Kurt.
- [Kurt] I don't know if I
could be happy knowing that.
(phone vibrating)
(laughter from tv)
(flushing toilet)
- You got a text when
you were in the bathroom.
- Oh.
- It's from Kevin.
- You looked?
- It was right on your screen, Kurt.
- [Kurt] It can wait.
- Seemed pretty urgent.
- It's just weed, babe, it can wait.
- That's not what the
conversation looked like.
- What?
- You guys chill a lot?
Plan on chilling some more?
- What are you talking about?
- [Paul] Don't sit there
and act like I'm an idiot.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- Your text, Kurt.
- Oh, so you're going through my texts?
- No, I-- It was open and I saw something
and I think you need to explain.
- There's nothing to explain.
(scoffs)
You don't do that; you don't go through
people's shit like that.
He buys weed from me, sometimes
we hang out afterward,
it's not a big deal.
- Then why are you getting so upset?
- Because you're making me
upset by blowing this up.
- I'm calm, you're freaking out.
- Can't believe you're
doing this right now.
- [Paul] Me doing this- what is this?
- This is bullshit.
- Yeah, I think so, too.
- You wanna go through my
texts, go ahead, do it.
Do it, I'll stand right
here and watch you.
- I saw enough.
- Okay then.
- I just want you to be honest with me.
- Then don't go through
my phone behind my back,
and make me out to be the bad guy.
You know this whole fucking
thing is completely out
of context, and you had no right.
- Where are you going?
- Home.
- Why?
- Because I don't feel like
fighting with you all night.
- We're not fighting, I'm
trying to get you to tell me
what the fuck is going on.
- Look, nothing is going on, okay?
- So what, you're really just
gonna walk away from this?
Babe, wait!
- What?!
- Kurt?
Kurt.
What the hell happened back there?
- I don't know, you tell me.
- Just tell me the truth;
you can tell me anything.
- I don't think I can do this anymore.
- Okay, so stop.
- That's not what I mean.
I mean this, us.
- Wait, Kurt, what?
- I mean I don't think this is working.
- Kurt, this is about
a text message, right?
- I think we should break up.
- Why?
I mean, it's a little dramatic.
What, we were fine, we
were arguing, it happens.
Kurt, I'm not connecting
the dots here, what...?
- Just, I need to be alone, all right?
- [Paul] You need space?
- Yeah.
- Kurt, I can give you space, I can--
- No, that's not what I mean.
I'm sorry.
- What did I do?
- You didn't do anything.
- It's that kid.
- It's not.
- [Paul] I saw you two,
all right, I'm not stupid.
- You're wrong.
- Was he your safety net? Your rebound?
- [Kurt] No, hey!
- Fuck you, you're a piece of shit.
- It's not like that, it's not.
It's me, it's us, it's everything.
It just doesn't feel right anymore.
It's not perfect.
- You want perfect?
Kurt, I fucking love you.
What more is there?
- I don't know, I don't know.
- Look at me, you love me.
Kurt, look at me.
Look at me, Kurt.
I'm yours, all right, I
don't want anyone else.
You mean to tell me I
don't make you happy?
Tell me you don't love me.
- I don't love you.
- I don't believe you.
- I'm sorry.
- Come on, Kurt, this is a mistake.
- Sorry, Paul.
- So, what, that's it?
This is how it ends?
- Guess so.
- This is what'll make you happy?
Okay.
(shattering glass)
- Fuck!
(sobbing)
("Pulling Feathers" by Joywave)
- What are you doing?
- I gotta go.
- Your breath stinks.
(door closing)
- You're an hour late.
Did you realize that you were that late?
- Yeah, I looked at the wrong schedule.
- Oh, that happens sometimes.
Uh, Paul?
What is uh...
- What?
- I don't mean to be, um, intrusive or--
- But you can't help it.
- I noticed that your,
um, relationship status,
um, changed this morning.
- Yeah; I didn't realize we were friends.
- Oh, you added me a while back.
So anyway, um, it's my
birthday today, and, um,
I don't know, I'm having a
little get together tonight,
and it could be cool stuff.
So, I don't know, if you wanted to come,
you're more than welcome to.
Or whatever, you know. It's whatever.
I don't know, it...
If you don't wanna go, it's totally cool.
No sweat off my back
or anything, your back.
Um. It's just...
I don't have that many friends...
- I'll come.
- Oh, okay, well, um...
Cool.
- So how much do you guys want?
- Can I get a half-eighth?
- Me, too.
- I don't do half-eighths,
they're annoying.
I can do an eighth for $60?
You and Little Chickpea
over here can split it.
- Sure.
- All right.
Thank you.
- Hey, where you going?
- Gotta head back north.
- But what about Excalibur?
- What about Excalibur?
- You should hit one.
- Yeah, man.
All right, you ready for this, man?
- Uh, yeah.
- Okay, here we go.
- Suck it.
- Go, go, go.
- Come on.
- All right, clear it.
(coughs)
(laughter)
- You guys are assholes.
- [Jack] Paul, do you have any Queens?
- Go ballistic.
- Ballistic I shall go.
It's to you.
- Oh, um...
Hey, Eddie, do you have any
(farts)
(laughs)
- Weak, dude. Weak.
- I know, I thought it
was gonna be a bigger one.
- It wasn't.
- Hey, Eddie, do you have any
(farts)
(laughter)
That one was kinda silent.
- Redeeming quality.
- It's better to let it
out and bear the shame,
than it is to hold it
in and bear the pain.
- Yeah, said it again.
- Ben Franklin said that.
- Might've been Gandhi.
- Eddie, you remember that time
that fat hooker tried to rape you?
You were telling us that
story the other day.
- No, she did, no, Crystal.
- Crystal was her name!
- She pushed you up against
that car and just like,
tried to you know, into ya.
- Tried to stick you in her.
- Yeah up in it.
Hey, Eddie, where'd you
get that alligator head?
- I dunno, Louisiana maybe?
- You don't know where
you got an alligator head?
- That must've been a seven footer.
- I don't know.
- Adolescent; killed it at
its adolescent age, monster.
- Do you have any sevens?
- Ay-yo, now we're talking,
check this out, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Do it, do it, toot the horn.
(loud whistle)
All aboard drunk train, here we go.
Put it, all right, dude,
who're you trying to impress?
Bunch of dudes here, so.
(coughs)
Good?
- Yes!
(applause)
- Thanks, Justin, you drank
half my fucking birthday present.
- Bro, relax, I drank like a third of it.
You got plenty more.
- This one time, I shit
my pants at a restaurant.
(laughs)
- I'm sorry about my friends.
- No, why?
- They're assholes.
- I think they're nice.
- You like them?
- Yeah, they're fun.
- Yeah, they're pretty cool.
- Happy birthday.
- Oh, yeah.
- Right.
- Cheers.
- [Paul] Cheers.
- If you were gay, I mean, if I were gay,
do you ever look at me?
Sexually?
Ever?
- Eddie, I think we should--
- Oh, right, right, just, it's
stupid, yeah, we don't have
to talk about that.
Cuz I wouldn't mind.
I mean, I'm not gay or anything, I just...
Just open to new stuff, and
trying new things, I don't know.
- Eddie, I think we should--
- You guys were perfect.
I mean, that's what it looked like.
You guys had the best
pictures and statuses.
I was always jealous of that.
Of you two.
With him.
- [Paul] Eddie...
- You don't have to say
anything, if you don't want to.
I mean, sometimes words
ruin the best emotions.
- Eddie, I think we should
go back to the party.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- [Paul] All right.
- Yeah, okay.
(intense, ominous music)
(intercom buzzer)
(buzz, buzz, buzz, buzzzz)
- [Paul] Hello?
- Look, it's me, don't hang up.
- [Paul] What do you want, Kurt?
- Listen, I just, I just got mugged.
- [Paul] Are you okay?
- I'm just, I'm a little dazed.
Just some blood.
I'm okay though.
Look, my phone got stolen,
my money, my train pass.
I woulda called Brad, but I didn't,
I don't even know his fucking number,
I don't even know your number.
Your place was the closest,
I didn't know what else to do, I'm sorry.
(door buzzes open)
You know I really
appreciate you doing this.
- I'm not gonna leave you in
the street like this alone.
Even if you do deserve it.
You know you're lucky; it
could've been a serial killer.
- Wish it was, now I'm just broke.
- Okay, you should probably
get stitches, honestly.
- I'll be fine.
- Well, I'd hate to say I told you so.
- Got it.
- Well, okay, look, I've gotta go to bed,
I've gotta work in the morning, so...
I mean, you can stay over if you want.
- Is that okay?
- Gonna have to be, right?
- Thanks, anyways.
- You can use this.
Also, I'm pretty sure this is yours, too.
Good night.
(knocking)
(persistent knocking)
- I'm fine.
- You know, it's a good
thing Paul texted me,
I thought you were fucking dead.
- Well I appreciate the
concern, but I'm fine,
I just lost my fucking
phone, and my money--
- Yeah, well, I mean are you
and Paul working it out or?
- Brad.
- What?
Okay.
You can talk to me if you want, you know.
- [Kurt] I said I'm fine.
Okay.
- This is Chip.
- Hey.
- How's it going?
- Jerry.
- Kurt.
- Christine.
- Nice to meet you.
- Santos.
- Kurt.
- And Peter.
- Nice to meet you.
- This guy has the best weed.
- [Voiceover] Can I get you a beer, man?
- Yeah, sure, let's do it.
(conversation)
("Golden State" by Joywave)
(laughter)
Oh yeah, I'm getting there.
(crosstalk)
All right.
(snorts coke)
Oh my God.
(laughter)
(cheering and yelling)
- Your boyfriend.
- He's not my boyfriend.
I should say hi.
- Why?
- I'm gonna go say hi.
Hey.
- Hey, Kurt.
- What are you doing here?
- Not allowed to be at the same party?
- Yeah, no, I mean.
Thank you so much for last night.
Thank you.
- You're welcome; just
happy you're all right.
- Oh, no, no, dude, I got mugged.
- [Paul] You here long?
- No, no, yeah, no, I'm.
(laughs)
Well, I just wanted to say hi.
- Hi.
- Okay.
(louder rave music)
(muttering)
(heavy breathing)
- Doing all right?
Doesn't look like it.
Can I sit down?
Yeah?
- [Kurt] Yeah.
- I was looking for you inside.
- Just came out here
to get some fresh air.
Who are those people you were with?
- Just people.
- Friends?
- Yeah.
- I want us to be friends.
- Friends like you're friends with Kevin?
That kind of friends?
- That's different.
- No it's not.
Do you like him?
- What?
- Seemed like you were having fun.
- It's nothing serious.
- Just someone to fool around with, right?
- You think you know
me so well, don't you?
- I don't.
It looks better.
- Yeah it doesn't hurt anymore.
- That's good, that's really good.
What are you doing?
You can't do that.
- Why not?
- Because you don't mean it.
Tell me you love me.
Tell me.
That's what I thought.
- Wait!
- This whole thing's just gonna sink.
I don't wanna see you anymore.
(phone vibrating)
(News broadcast talking
about disabled children)
- Hey, it's me.
I don't know why I'm calling.
I feel like I just need to clear the air,
and we should talk.
You're probably at work.
Try to give me a call
when you get out, okay?
Thanks, bye.
(soft, intensifying music)
Did you get my voice mail?
- No.
- Look, I know you probably
don't wanna do this right now,
- You're right.
- But I think we should
talk while we're both sober.
- I was sober last night.
- I just need you to hear me out.
- Look, I've heard enough, all right?
You can't just show up here
and corner me like this;
it's not fair.
I didn't call you back for a reason.
- I just need to explain myself.
- No, you don't.
- Look, I don't want it to end like this.
- Kurt, you did this.
All right, this is you.
We're done.
- I know I fucked you over, but
I don't want you to hate me.
- You looked me in the eyes,
and you told me you didn't love me.
Do you remember that?
- I'm just trying to make things
easier, I just wanna talk.
- Why do you do this?
Why do you, can't you just leave me alone?
- I don't know, is that what you want?
- Yes, that's exactly what I want.
I want you just to stop, all right?
I wanna move on.
Fuck, you moved on.
I wanna do that, I wanna move on.
- It's just, you kept
going through my head,
and I wanna talk and you're ignoring me--
- Shut up, just shut up!
You just talk and you talk, and you just,
you have no idea what you're saying;
you sound like an asshole.
Now listen though, I'm not
your boyfriend anymore.
All right, I'm not your fucktoy.
I'm not even your friend.
- Why not?
- They say what doesn't
kill us makes us stronger.
Well I'm pretty sure some
things just cripple us.
- Look, I just can't
cut you out of my life.
Okay?
- You already did.
I could've been with you forever, Kurt.
(ominous music)
(traffic)
- Jesus Christ.
- You can't help, it's over.
- Look, everything's gonna be okay, okay?
Just, you're gonna be fine.
- (muttering)
- Yeah, hello, this is an emergency.
Yeah, yeah, someone's been stabbed.
Yeah, he's awake.
Yeah, yeah, he's talking.
I'm at the corner of
Wellington and Sacramento,
Wellington and Sacramento.
Yeah, please hurry, please hurry.
Shit, all right, they're on
their way, just hang on, okay?
- I know you.
- I don't think so, buddy.
- Did you--
- Don't talk, okay, they're coming.
- I'm gonna be famous.
- You're gonna be fine.
- I'm gonna be on tv.
- I can hear them, man, you hear that?
You hear that?
They're coming, all right, they're coming.
No no no no, don't go to
sleep, don't go to sleep!
No, come on, man, stay with me.
- I know you.
He loves you.
- The fuck?
(sirens)
("Appearances" by Joywave)
- [Paul] Remember our first kiss?
- [Kurt] Mm-hmm. I had pulled
you away from that party
to watch the sunrise.
- [Paul] I never saw
the sunrise before that.