[OH, DARLING PLAYING]
* Oh, Darling
Will you marry me?
* I'll love you
Till my dying day
* Oh, Darling
Will you marry me?
* I'll love you
Till I die, baby *
Mmm. Where you going?
Work. Sunday brunch.
I'm already late.
Neil's going to kill me.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah,
last night was fun.
You're not feeling
weird about...
No.
No, he was hot, right?
Very.
But not as hot as you.
Meet me at the cafe.
I'll be done at six.
* We'll go on down
To London town
* Or maybe even Rome
* No, we'll never know
* A place called home
* Until we're old and grown
Hello.
How's your day?
Good. Good. Yeah.
Um...
Okay, so I want
to talk to you...
Wait,
before you say anything...
I saw you looking at it
last time you were over.
It's the artwork
I did for the florists.
I thought that print would,
you know, look good
in your bedroom.
That's really sweet.
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
Um...
Okay, I...
I wanna take a break.
What?
Yeah, just...
Just a break
for a little while.
We're not breaking up. I...
Why?
I mean, I just need some time
to just figure things out.
For myself. And so I think
we should take a break.
What's going on?
Nothing's going on. I...
I just... [SIGHS]
It has nothing
to do with you.
Neil, I'm sorry.
The subway was crazy
but I'm here now.
It's brunch, Aaron.
Are you crazy?
I know, I know.
Look, I'll take one of
your shifts next week.
Table four, okay?
Okay, thank you. Thank you!
You seem angry.
Are you angry?
I'm not angry, Annie.
I'm hurt.
'Cause I love you.
Is there someone else?
No.
We always said we'd be
honest with each other.
I know.
That's why I'm here.
So we can talk.
These six months
have been great.
I know they have.
That's why I don't understand.
How you guys doing?
I'm Aaron, I'm gonna be
your server today.
Thank you.
You guys have
any questions?
We need more time.
I'll be right back.
[SIGHS]
Is there someone else?
It isn't serious.
It's...
What's his name?
It doesn't matter.
Just tell me his name.
Mandy.
"Mandy?"
Yeah.
You're seeing Mandy?
Uh... [CHUCKLES]
Mandy is nice.
Mandy is great.
Wait, you never mentioned
before that you...
Well, that's because
it's a recent development.
Me and Mandy is...
Have you ever had feelings?
You know, feelings for...
women?
Well, yeah. Yeah. Um...
She's just...
It's different.
Yeah, I have.
I just... I need some time
to figure things out,
that's all.
Please don't be upset.
Okay?
Are you...
You guys ready?
I can't see you anymore.
Stan...
[SIGHS]
* Oh, Darling
Will you marry me?
* I'll love you
Till my dying day
* Oh, Darling
Will you marry me?
* I'll love you
Till I die, baby *
How'd your
skaterboy thing go?
Oh, disastrous.
I mean, he was so immature.
I met him.
He seemed really sweet.
He was really young
and he didn't have
his shit together.
Hold on, he was like 23.
Yeah.
Yeah, so am I.
And he didn't understand
that I had auditions.
Yes, but I'm sorry.
You don't give yourself
an opportunity to be
in a relationship.
I give a lot of opportunity.
No, you don't.
Yes, I... How much
money did you make?
Uh, 240.
You did not.
Yeah, it's brunch.
Ah, it's because you're flirty
and you put your hands
on their...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
vile customers' shoulders.
No, I do not.
That's true.
Whatever. 240?
You didn't even...
You're buying drinks
on Wednesday, period.
See you later.
Tell Marcus I said "Hi."
Yeah.
AARON:
I feel really bad for him.
Well, here's the thing, though.
He doesn't make
himself available.
So it's not like
he's gonna find someone.
Wait, wait, wait.
What about that skinny,
white skater boy?
Which one?
[LAUGHING]
That's true.
Goes through 'em
like left and right, man.
And never settles down with
any of them.
He just wants
to take him out
for a spin on...
the Neil train.
The Neil train.
Oh.
I smell like hash browns.
Mmm.
[LAUGHS]
I woke up the other day
before the alarm went off.
Just sitting there,
watching you.
Really?
Yeah.
Your head on that pillow.
Looked like a little nut.
[CHUCKLES] Yeah.
Aww.
Like a big ol' almond
or something.
[CHUCKLES]
I just wanted to take my jaw...
unhinge it...
Mmm-hmm.
and swallow your head whole.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
You know,
there's no distance
between us.
I love you.
Last night was fun. Yeah?
It was hot
to see you with him.
Really?
Working your thing, yeah.
You serious?
Yeah.
I was thinking,
do you...
Do you maybe wanna like
try an open relationship?
We could try.
Yeah?
Maybe.
Maybe?
You know.
But we need some rules.
We definitely need rules.
Yeah.
What if...
Okay, no repeats.
We only have fun
with a guy once
and we always,
always tell each other.
Come on.
Let's not make rules
we know we're gonna break.
Please don't ever
lie to me, Marcus.
I can't promise that.
Neither can you.
Well, I've never lied to you.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
What about whatshisname?
No, don't even
bring him up.
I was working on play,
playing his boyfriend.
I got confused, all right?
And P.S.that was once
in six years, so...
Fair enough.
Okay, well,
what about our place,
like, are we allowed
to have people over, or we...
All right, listen.
The rules.
We don't fall in love.
That's it, that's the rule.
* A million dark nights
* You feel that you have
No hope *
[HUMMING]
So in the 60s,
they talked a lot about
changing the world,
and ending the war,
the truth is, kids,
they didn't really do much
except take a lot of drugs
and get herpes.
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
Okay, uh, sorry.
Teacher's feeling
a little out today.
Let's just open
the textbooks to...
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
Um, okay, don't forget,
your Watergate assignment
is due tomorrow.
You can put anything you want
in them, but make them
about Nixon.
Oh, shit.
Hey, Mandy.
Hey.
Do you ever look
at internet porn?
Yeah, everybody does.
I guess cause things
are over with Stan.
Yeah, I still don't
understand why.
He's 20, he's in a band.
Uh, so?
Last night, I looked at
this site for two hours.
Just all these pictures
of stuff.
I think it's done
something to my brain.
Huh?
Like, when I woke up
this morning
I somehow felt like my brain
was somehow different.
You know,
because of the porn,
like it
changed the chemistry
of my brain.
I don't think
porn changes your brain.
What would you
like to look at?
I mean, when you look.
Oh, um...
I'm on Zoloft.
Huh?
So I'm not much
in the mood for...
Oh.
all of that...
Oof, bummer.
You want to hang out
after work?
Yeah.
Cool.
No kissing.
Okay.
[PANTS UNZIPPING]
I don't know.
There's no way it can work,
right? I mean, he's...
He's in a band.
Are you trying to
convince me or you?
Wait, you think that...
Well, I don't know.
What about the guy before,
Patrick?
I mean, how long were
you guys dating before you...
No, about six months,
but I mean, it's not
a pattern, okay?
I just... I need to find
somebody that's stable.
Stan isn't?
I mean, I don't know.
I guess he kind of is.
I mean, he's definitely
always there.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
I don't know, Mandy.
Come on, I mean,
like, he's 20 years old.
And you know, he's like
a struggling musician.
You know, like I'm enough
of a mess as it is.
I don't need, like,
more mess in my life.
Uh, when Stan and I
had our talk
I, uh, I told him
I was seeing you.
Wait, what?
Yeah. [LAUGHS]
I don't know.
He was convinced that
there was someone else.
And he kept asking,
"What's his name?"
So finally
I was like, "Mandy".
Wait, why did you tell Stan
that you were seeing me?
I don't know,
it just came out.
It seemed easier, you know.
It was him that I was leaving,
I was changing lifestyles.
Have you ever been
with a woman before?
No. Have you?
Not since college.
Mandy, you did?
I went to Vassar.
[LAUGHING]
Did you like it?
I did.
It was fun.
She was very forceful.
Mmm-hmm.
Surprising.
She had this...
What?
It was fun.
Did you ever think about
becoming one full time?
Although the sex was fun,
but at the time
I wasn't interested,
and everything that
went along with it,
but now...
Maybe.
Thanks.
No, thank you.
Are those my, uh...
[SIGHS]
Sorry.
[LAUGHS] Sorry.
Here.
So obviously,
this was your first time.
Yeah.
You're very good.
Thanks.
You're very cute.
You, too.
Want to hang out again?
Sometime,
maybe tomorrow or...
I don't know.
Ah, sorry.
You have a girlfriend?
No. I mean, we...
broke up.
Well, I'm honored
to be your first.
[CHUCKLES]
You really think I was good?
Yes, Tom.
Listen,
my name isn't Tom.
It's not Tom.
It's Stan.
Stan.
I'd love to do this again.
I'll leave it up to you.
You know, just email me or...
Okay.
Marcus.
Would you, uh...
Would you hold me?
Yeah.
Hey, Mandy, it's Annie.
I'm just calling to say hi.
It was fun
hanging out today.
Anyways, no need
to call me back.
Or... Yeah.
Okay, so I'll...
I'll see you at school.
Bye.
[SIGHS]
We should move
to Middle America.
Raise a bunch of adopted kids
from the Phillipines.
Are you drunk?
[CHUCKLES]
No, I'm serious.
Okay.
How many?
Mmm.
Probably no more than five.
That would be really nice.
Mmm-hmm?
Yeah.
Kids, backyard, fence.
Dogs, cat.
Kitchen table, dishwasher.
Maybe a garbage
disposal unit.
A llama.
[CHUCKLES] You're crazy.
So have... Have you...
Have you, you know...
Taken advantage of
our new situation yet?
Why do you ask?
No reason.
Well, have you?
Maybe.
"Maybe"?
Well, I don't know.
Yeah, well, I do.
You left the sex towels
in the hamper
for me to wash.
I'm sorry. Shit!
[CHUCKLES] Not a big deal.
No. I thought he was stupid.
And?
Yeah. I guess so.
So have you...
fooled around?
No.
* Thousand rainy days
* You worry
He'll be gone
* Gone, gone...
What?
It's nothing.
It's just, on your demo
It's "She'll".
* You worry she'll be gone
Okay.
Why don't we just do it again?
[STRUMMING]
* Thousand rainy days
* You worry
She'll be gone *
Hey.
Hi.
I'm sorry I didn't
call you back last night.
Oh, don't be silly.
I was at the hospital late.
The hospital?
My dad.
It's nothing.
Well, is he all right?
Um...
He had an infection
and it spread into his arms.
But... Yeah, it's fine.
He'll be fine.
Okay, well,
if you ever need to talk...
Yeah, thank you.
I don't know.
I know that it's Friday
but maybe tonight?
Yeah!
Yeah?
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, wait. Shit.
Blind date.
Ah.
I'll cancel though.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't be silly.
E-Harmony. Is that sad?
He's a stand-up comic.
He sounds normal.
I don't think
stand-up comics are normal.
Yeah, you're right.
Well, we'll see.
It'll be funny.
I hope.
What if he's awful?
He's probably actually
not gonna be funny at all.
[CHUCKLING]
That's cool. I know
lots of couple who do that.
Oh, yeah.
You two been together
how long?
Six years.
So does he play?
I know you do.
I think he lied.
What?
I asked him last night.
He lied.
Maybe he hasn't.
Not everyone is
a slut bucket like you.
And you, okay?
True.
[CHUCKLING]
The other night, I...
kinda read his emails.
Oh, shit.
You've gotta trust him.
But I saw the email, and it
said from curiousmusician82
meeting at our place.
Who does he go to bed
with every night, huh?
Who's he spent
the last five years with?
Oh, shit.
Wretchd indie-rock girl
wants another refill.
Go for it.
[GROANS]
How you doing, Miss K?
Hey, Jamal, how are you?
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
All right.
[GROANS]
[RINGING CONTINUES]
[MANDY GRUNTS]
Where's my fucking phone?
Oh, I'm sorry, Jamal
that I used that word.
Your phone is right there.
What?
Hello?
Hello, Mom?
What's going on?
Calm down.
I can't hear you.
Mom?
Fuck! Shit! Fuck!
Fuck! Shit!
Mandy.
Annie.
Mandy?
I'm gonna let you two talk.
Is everything okay?
It's my dad.
What happened?
Um, they're gonna amputate
both of his arms.
They tried everything.
It was the only way
that they can stop
the infection from spreading.
Oh, my God.
He told me a turkey joke.
A what?
[CHUCKLES]
A joke about...
About a turkey
my mom handed...
Okay.
Okay, Mandy,
we'll get somebody
to cover for you, okay?
You should get to the hospital.
Okay.
Oh, wait, actually,
before you go, maybe...
Maybe we should say
a prayer to God or...
I don't know any prayers.
Me neither,
but I'm pretty sure
you just talk to him.
I don't know,
I guess you...
Okay. Yeah.
Oh, I just...
All right, I'm sorry.
I just don't think
I can do this right now.
No, of course.
I just thought... I don't know,
I thought maybe it would...
...help.
Can I kiss you?
Yeah.
It's getting late, man,
and my partner
will be home soon.
Okay.
Sorry, I just...
No, I'm sorry. I thought
he knew that you were...
Yeah, but...
Right.
Yeah, I'll go.
Stan.
Oh. Oh, sorry.
I'm interupting.
Yeah,
this is my partner, Aaron.
I served you
at the cafe last week.
I thought that girl
you were with was...
I'm really sorry.
I'm just gonna get going.
No, no, no.
Stay. Stay.
Look, I just got some pot
on my way home.
We could smoke up, you know.
Order some takeout.
We could watch a game.
Right?
There's the game, right?
There's gotta be a game on.
We have DVDs if...
You know what?
Let's just listen
to some music.
Um, Stan, stay.
Marcus, tell him.
It'll be fun.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay!
Okay, cool. Okay.
I'll, um... I'll just put
this in the fridge and I'll
get the takeout menus.
Cool.
You okay?
Yeah.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Where'd he go?
I need something.
Something that's mine
sometimes.
I'm yours.
That's now what I mean.
You don't love me anymore?
Oh, stop it.
Sorry.
Let's watch a movie.
Sean Penn as Harvey Milk
and Mystic Riv mash-up.
I know you're angry.
Is that my daughter in there?
[PEOPLE LAUGHING]
Life in New York just...
It gets you down sometimes.
I find that
it's just tough.
And it's like
the little things,
you know, it's like...
Diners are weird.
There's never enough napkins,
And those really
thin napkins that come
out of those dispensers?
And you always have to...
I always use 50 of them.
And it's like,
"Just make...
Just make...
Just make one napkin
that's thicker.
It would save you money
and it would save me time."
And those half
and half containers?
You know? Man!
I think open-heart
surgery would be easier
first thing in the morning.
Try to open those things.
What did you think?
Your act is kind of
like observations.
Yeah.
You know, about life.
Mundane shit,
but with a twist.
But you know,
they do make easy-to-open
half and half containers
with the screw-top.
So... [LAUGHS]
You didn't think it was funny.
Oh, no, David.
No, it was very funny.
I mean...
The way you deliver it,
it's full of irony.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Yeah.
But you know what's
actually really funny?
Mmm.
Is when you...
When you like
implicate the audience.
You know?
Implicate?
Yeah, like, um...
Instead of talking about
everyday stuff, what if
you talk about...
I don't know, Darfur.
I don't know
anything about Darfur.
Exactly. Exactly,
that's the point.
You're holding up
a mirror to the audience.
So you're pointing out the fact
that there's this horrible
genocide going on
and no-one knows
anything about it.
Now that's funny.
Uh, I want people to laugh.
Darfur isn't funny.
It's like a tragedy.
No, I know. I know.
But comedy
comes from tragedy.
So...
Yum, this pirogi
is really good.
WOMAN: What sort of therapy
or counseling did you get?
MAN: Well, this repairative
therapy comes in
a number of flavors.
I attended two types of
conversion therapy sessions.
One was free.
It was held on the basement
of a Christian church
with a lot of praying.
[DOORBELL BUZZES]
[TV SHUTS OFF]
Hi.
Hey, hi!
Listen, I'm sorry.
No, come in.
I don't want to bother you.
Bother me, please.
I'm eating froyo and watching
TiVo of Rachel Maddow.
It's fine.
Oh, how are you?
How's your dad?
Uh, my dad. Uh...
Shit. I don't know.
He's, um...
He's alive, right?
I mean, he doesn't
have any arms.
But he's alive.
So the doctor says that
he is recovering.
But my mom, she is...
I don't know,
I think it's the stress.
We're in the waiting room
and she started singing.
Singing?
Yeah, like, uh...
* Life changes
Love lasts forever
* Happy 33rd birthday, son
What song is that?
I don't know.
I think it's like a message
from a greeting card.
My mom, she just sings messages
from greeting cards now.
Yikes.
Yeah.
I know.
My brother took her home
so she'd get some sleep.
But I just...
I couldn't go home right now.
No, no, stay.
Do you want some of this?
It's actually really good.
Oh. I'm sorry. I just...
I'm sorry.
[GASPS]
Oh, my God!
* I'm seeing things
That aren't real
* There's no water in the pool
* But I am still swimming
* I'm hearing sounds
That aren't here
* There's a voice downstairs
* And I am still lonely
* I'm feeling
I've fallen asleep
* Awake in a dream
* But I am still searching
I don't even see
where it is.
How could I not know
he was gonna be a freak?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
That's like, seriously.
Darfur?
That was really harsh.
He wasn't funny.
Ugh, worst date ever.
I mean...
Hey, I'm hungry.
Yeah, me too.
This was a nice surprise.
How are you?
Are you feeling okay?
I mean, after...
Yeah, okay.
I'm better than okay.
Hey, I have an idea.
Let's go into Manhattan
and do something.
Like museum or a movie.
I have to go to the hospital.
You should take the day off.
You're so stressed.
You brother can handle things
for the day.
You're a bad influence.
You have a little...
Here, I got that.
I made it worse. Okay.
Thanks.
[LAUGHS]
You're welcome.
That is yummy.
That train
is taking forever.
Oh, I'm sorry. Is that...
It's new.
You like?
Mandy, are... Are we...
I just... I didn't think
it was more than...
Oh, I'm sorry.
We can take that one, right?
Oh, shit.
This train's stopping.
We've to wait for the F.
ANNOUNCER: This is the last
stop on this train.
Everyone please
leave the train.
Thank you for riding with
FTA New York City Trains.
Hi.
Hey, Annie.
How are ya?
I'm good. Uh...
You remember...
Hi.
Mandy.
Mandy, right. Hi.
Hi.
It's great to see you again.
It's good to see you, too.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
So I know
it's none of my business,
but are you two still, uh...
Well, you're right.
It's none of your business.
Sorry.
I mean, it's not
like a big deal.
Very cool. She's...
Very pretty.
I'm sorry. I thought
that day...
Hey, Annie.
Um, Annie. I'm just gonna
go down, it's my brother.
Oh, hey, yeah.
No rush, I'll wait.
You thought what?
I just thought
you were lying.
That day at the cafe.
We're...
We're not together.
Hey.
Hey, you remember me?
Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, I got you this.
No, I don't understand.
Mom's in the hospital?
What...
What happened, Evan?
Is mom all right?
Stan you need to
talk to these guys.
No, no, no, Annie.
It's fine. Don't go.
Wait a minute.
You were our waiter
at the cafe, right?
Yeah, right.
And it's funny.
Marcus here
is a client of mine.
Yeah, right.
We should be at
the back of the car for this.
Yeah.
Okay.
We'll see you guys later.
See you soon.
Bye.
Hey. Everything okay?
Any news?
[SIGHS]
* Today is the first day
* For all mankind
* And step-dad
May there be no limit
To the happiness you find
* Wanna wish you
Happy Kwanzaa
* Happy Kwanzaa
What's happening?
Are you all right?
Is everything okay?
Mandy, are you...
What are you doing?
[SIGHS]
Why is everybody
looking at me?
Okay, just take it easy,
all right?
I'll be OK.
I'm just... I'm just gonna go.
Wait, Mandy. No.
Let me walk you.
No, don't be silly.
I'm just fine.
I'll walk you home.
No. No, Annie.
It's okay, okay?
I'm okay.
I'm... I'm sorry, Stan.
That' fine.
I have no idea
what just happened.
Do... I...
Stan, I gotta...
Go, go.
Okay.
You're gorgeous,
you know that?
Stop.
It's true.
I missed you.
You missed me?
You just spent
the last four nights here.
Too much?
No.
Sorry I was so stupid.
Not as stupid as me.
You see it?
This patch of red
on your inner thigh?
Yeah.
Before we continue, tell me,
Aaron, how many new partners
in the past six months?
You're not playing Doctor.
Surely someone as
handsome, and
endowed as you...
Marcus, please.
I'm on my knees,
and look, no response.
It might be herpes.
It was that NYU kid.
Fungus.
Fungus?
Shit!
[CHUCKLES] Stop.
Where you going?
You got jock itch.
What?
Fungus, aka the jock itch.
Ew!
[GROANING]
Um, you left your
laptop on last night.
What?
Sorry.
That's...
That's not cool.
I, uh, I saw some of
the sites that you go to.
It's for work.
It's porn, Stan.
So I look at porn sometimes.
Well,
I like gay porn, too.
And you have
a profile on that site
"Manhunters" or something,
and it's...
It's you, I mean,
it's a picture of your...
Annie! Annie,
you have no right!
Okay, okay.
Listen, you're right.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry for snooping.
It isn't cool.
But I want you to know
I think it's...
It's cool.
I mean, it's sexy
you're exploring.
I haven't since
we've gotten back together.
Oh, so...
You fooled around
with a guy?
Oh.
Oh, it's one of those guys
from the subway the other day,
wasn't it?
I can't have this conversation.
Stan.
Look, Aaron,
you don't have
herpes with the clap.
You got jock itch.
You need to go to Walgreens
and get some medicine.
Might even have some
in the medicine chest.
Don't look like that.
Means you're a jock.
Mmm?
You should be happy.
Jock.
You don't get it.
I've been
freaking out all week.
[SCOFFS]
I live here, too, remember?
I went online
and saw these pictures of...
Last week it was
oral gonorrhea.
You wanna tell me
what this is really all about.
What would you do
if I was positive?
Are you positive?
No.
[CHUCKLES] What is this,
let's play "I have HIV?"
No...
Just tell me.
What would you do?
First I'd kiss you.
Then I might cry.
We'd look at each other
for a long, long time.
Then I'd kiss you again.
Kiss you some more.
Then I'd undo your pants...
Take 'em down real slow.
Then your briefs.
And I'd suck your cock.
Take you to the bedroom,
and we'd have very hot,
very safe sex.
And I'd hold you tight.
Then I'd leave you.
[CHUCKLING]
People have all have needs,
eventually.
And I just... I don't want
to be one of those women,
you know?
One of those women
that's like
"Oh, he did what?
I had no idea men did
stuff like that
because I am
a complete moron."
I don't wanna be that woman.
I just...
I wanna be smart about
the way things are
with sex and needs.
I mean,
look at our parents.
My parents are divorced.
Exactly.
Dad boned his assistant,
Mom blew the plumber,
and everybody's
gotta suffer.
It's the same god damn
story every time.
But we can be different.
You know?
Try something new.
Open things up,
like an arrangement.
Like if I found
a man attractive
and you did, too, then...
No, we could.
Or maybe a woman.
I can't talk
about this right now.
Stan, you're, um...
You're hard.
I've been reading the emails
you write to Stan.
[SIGHS]
Oh, I get it now.
So you...
read my emails,
then you go screw
some NYU boy.
No. No, it is not like that.
Why do you do this?
Do you have feelings for him?
No.
Tell me.
I mean, is that why you didn't
want me here the night that
I walked in on you two?
Tell me.
Here's the deal.
If we do this,
we do it together.
Okay? If we wanna
explore our bi side...
I'm not bi.
Curious, whatever
you wanna call it.
We do it,
we do it together.
And it's only about sex.
I'm ashamed.
You in a church?
No.
Then can the shame shit.
I don't know,
between men and women
there's just usually
all of this, like...
This grrrr, you know?
It's never equal.
It's just always all this ick.
But with you, there's not.
It's like your my boyfriend
and my gay best friend
all rolled in one.
I'm not gay! I'm not...
Give me your hand.
See? I like this.
We don't do it often?
No, and we can talk about it.
Like, tell me about...
about your time with Marcus.
What?
That's his name, right?
Readyforever25, Marcus?
[GROANS] Yeah.
Yeah.
He what?
Yeah. He fucked...
You fucked him?
He fucked me.
Oh, I...
I just assumed
that you, uh...
Oh.
Do you want me to go?
[BOTH GROANING]
[GROANING LOUDLY]
[PANTING]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
What are you doing
on my phone?
answering mine?
Well, this is gay.
You're in the other room.
We've got unlimited minutes.
Listen...
The other night
I couldn't sleep.
I looked over at you.
You were so silent,
and I thought,
"What if...
I'm scared, Aaron,
one day
I'll come home
and you won't be here?"
Crane accident,
brain tumor,
stray bullet,
dirty bomb, cancer.
The hole you'll leave behind,
I'll never fill.
It's been six years.
I'm forgetting life before.
How could I live without you?
I'll live till
I'm 1000 years old
and never leave you.
[TREMBLING]
I feel something for him.
I don't know what.
I'm confused.
I won't call him again.
Hey.
We don't have any stuff here
for your fungus.
Better go to the corner
drugstore before they close.
Yeah.
Yeah, cool. Great.
Look for Tinactin.
Tough acting...?
What?
Aaron.
Yeah?
Hurry back.
Hi.
Hey.
Missed you at school.
I took some time off
because...
Right. How are things?
Not good.
You never returned
my calls.
You called once.
Things got busy.
Stan?
Yeah.
Yeah, we're back together.
Things got confusing.
I...didn't mean to hurt you.
There are
consequences, Annie.
I was hurting,
and that night...
[SIGHS] Never mind.
I'm sorry.
He died, Annie.
My dad, and I never
went to see him.
I didn't go and see him.
[SOBS]
I'm a fucking horrible person.
No, you're not.
And after my mom went nuts,
after you,
it's just so much.
It's just too much.
You should go.
But Mandy, I...
I will be at school
in a few weeks.
Okay.
You should go on YouTube
and check out the David guy
you went on a blind date with.
The comic?
Seems you left
quite an impression.
Hey. Are you okay?
Hey... [CHUCKLES]
Slow down, Speedracer.
I don't have
a lot of time.
How are things?
With Annie.
Can we not
talk about that?
Sure.
Bedroom?
Maybe we should
hang out sometime.
We're hanging out now.
Uh, I don't know, coffee.
See a band.
Maybe.
It's gonna be
my birthday in a week.
Happy birthday.
Turning 26, right?
Your Manhunt profile...
I'm gonna be 30.
Okay.
Cool.
You ever wonder what
it'd be like if we all live
to be a thousand years old?
Like, if there was no death.
Then we could all get happy.
Or maybe not.
We don't have
1000 years, do we?
Should we take a chance?
Marcus, what's going on?
I love you.
Uh...
No, you don't.
I think about you
all the time.
I have a girlfriend.
I love Annie.
And you've said
you were just looking...
I know what I feel.
I... I came here
to get off.
You feel something, too.
I know.
I'm gonna get going.
Stan, I know you're confused.
Confused?
You don't know
anything about me.
You're the confused one,
fucking bringing me here,
you say shit like that.
"You love me?"
What is that?
We hooked up a few times.
That was it.
Don't call me again.
Stan, wait...
[SCREAMS]
[SOBS]
Shit!
[GARGLING]
Sorry, I had
this taste in my mouth.
You know,
they say you shouldn't
swim on an empty stomach.
See, comedy comes
from tragedy, motherfucker.
You guys like Darfur?
You guys said
you wanted dark.
MAN: You suck!
You suck!
You think I'm a mess?
I'll show you, Annie.
Annie!
Oh!
Oh, my God.
MAN: Is that guy dead?
WOMAN: Who's Annie?
Shit. What happened?
Did you get mugged?
I don't wanna talk about it.
Did you call the cops?
I mean, are there
any witnesses?
It's taken care of.
Did you call the cops
or not?
No.
Oh, God,
I'm gonna call them.
I wasn't mugged.
Then what happened?
I'm gonna move out.
Aaron.
Just need some space
to figure this all out.
Aaron, please.
You lied to me.
For weeks, about him.
Then you tell me
you love him.
I didn't mean
for it to happen.
I'll start looking
tomorrow.
Aaron...
No, just...
I want to be alone.
I don't know, he's just...
He's knda quiet,
but I feel like he's really
taking everything in.
You know, like he hears me.
I don't know.
And he's my best student.
Here.
How is it? Is it too hot?
I mean,
I don't mean temperature.
Bit spicy, is it?
I tried not to make it
so spicy this time.
It's good.
We could have gone out,
you know.
But I love cooking.
I mean, I know
I'm not that good at it,
but I should do more of it.
Cooking, cleaning.
I don't know,
that's what people do, right?
Anyway, there's more rice
in the kitchen if you want it.
I'm fine.
Hey, look at me.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I told you I'm fine.
Okay. I just...
I tried calling you earlier,
and you weren't there.
Were you working at home, or...
What's with the third degree?
Sorry, I just...
I though you had
a big design project.
What are you wearing?
What?
Christ, you're not 18 anymore.
Okay, Stan,
you're hurting my feelings.
You're not
acting like yourself.
Did something happen today?
No.
We said we'd be honest.
It's nothing.
Did you meet a guy today?
I mean, online,
is that what happened?
Is that why you didn't
answer your phone?
Was it that guy, Marcus?
You're reading
my fucking emails again?
No, Stan, but I know you,
and we said we'd be honest.
We said we wouldn't
do anything
without talking about it.
I'm going.
Just tell me what happened.
Hey, do you know
when Miss K's coming back?
Jamal, Miss K will be back
very soon.
Okay.
Did you...?
Yeah. Sublet.
Are we gonna talk about this?
We talked.
And I said
I just need some time.
I apologized.
Can we not do this?
Sorry.
I don't understand.
Are we breaking up?
I don't know.
I just need some time
to figure things out.
Well, figure 'em out with me.
We've been through this.
Okay.
Look, I, um...
I invited Alice
and her girlfriend.
I think it's her girlfriend,
over for dinner.
I asked Neil from work, too.
I already invited them
here for your birthday.
I thought since
it was my birthday...
You should come.
Yeah.
Maybe, I've got to
take care of some things.
Okay.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SOBBING]
Another round.
Hey.
You're...
Yeah.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Join me.
How's it going?
Long day.
Yeah.
I hear ya.
This is on the house, guys.
How can people
have it all figured out?
I don't know.
I'm not one of those people.
I hate those people
who know what they want.
Cheers to that.
I mean, I have no idea
what I want.
And everything I touch
turns to shit.
See, I'm worried,
like It's not that
I don't know what I want,
but that I actually do know,
but I'm scared to go for it.
Well, it seems like
you went for it with Stan.
I think he made it clear
he's not interested.
Why didn't he just tell me?
He was scared.
I mean, shit, if Mandy
wanted to fuck me again,
I would do it.
Doesn't mean
I don't love Stan.
Just having my fingers
inside of her...
[LAUGHING]
I don't know.
That's a lot of information.
How about that whisky?
You guys want another one?
Yes, please!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Do you think he's gay?
Be honest.
A part of what makes him
so attractive to...
Wait, wait,
can I say this?
I just told you
I fingered Mandy.
Say it.
He's such an open guy.
Trusting.
I never felt like it was
about me being a guy.
It was amazing.
What was I thinking?
Stan told me you suggested
the whole arrangement.
I did, but I mean,
think about it.
At some point I'm gonna have to
get married and have a kid.
Or cook.
Or something. I mean,
don't I want that?
Do you want that?
No.
Then don't do it.
Easy for you to say, homo.
Straight people have it tough.
All that fucking pressure
to conform.
That's why you all hate us.
Jealous.
You got it all figure out?
I broke all our rules.
And we didn't have many.
Now he's moving out.
You gonna let him go?
I want things back
the way they were.
But you can't.
So it's either
a life with him,
with all its complications
and flaws,
or life without.
Shit.
Let's drink.
[BOTH GROANING]
[CHUCKLING]
I'm gonna be a mess.
That'll put hair on your chin.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Just what I need.
[LAUGHING]
I totally... I deep-throated
that ketchup bottle
for like five minutes.
The teacher's were stunned.
It was...
Oh, my God.
It was our
senior acting project
and he gives head
to a Heinz bottle.
What grade did you get?
Uh, I think I got an A.
Nice.
You did not!
Do you remember...
"The Red Room"?
Yes, it was about a squirrel
who built a nest
in my vagina.
Oh, my God, yes,
it was hilarious!
[LAUGHING]
And... And what, we did...
We did that thing together
where I had the little elf
who lived off Hi Tek.
Yes, and he looked
like Michael Landon.
Yes!
Michael Landon?
Yeah.
Oh, Michael Landon!
Can you believe
I was into Michael Landon?
You were into Michael Landon?
I was!
Wow.
I think that was
my last boy crush.
Hmm. Let me clear this.
It was delicious.
Should I help you?
Sure.
I like her.
Yes?
Yes.
She's great.
How did you meet her?
You really wanna know?
Yeah.
It's kinda gay.
[CHUCKLES]
Let's hear it.
Sauna, steam room, gym.
Are you kidding me?
That's nice. It's kinda hot.
It's not the first time
I've gone trolling.
Not mine either.
She talked to me
and she convinced me to
go to my dad's funeral
'cause I wasn't gonna go,
because my family is
just ,like, a little insane.
And I felt like, um,
I have a lot
of insanity already,
and I didn't need
to go to the funeral
and absorb some more.
But, um...
I get it.
But she was really nice
and she came with me,
and I wouldn't have
been able to go
if I wasn't with her.
You went with her, actually?
Yeah.
I can't believe that.
That was the exact day?
That was... Okay,
right, so this is like...
I mean, she was just
sitting there, catatonic, so...
That's heavy, dude.
I know.
She must be in
a really rough place.
I can't believe she's...
...here.
Yeah.
I'm there for her.
I am sorry
to hear about your dad.
I told him jokes.
I told...
those headstone jokes.
The jokes that I never
told him before I died.
He liked jokes.
Tell me one.
Okay.
"Hey, Dad, give me five.
Okay, I'll settle for a toe."
He didn't have arms.
They cut them off.
Oh.
Enough about me and Mandy.
What about you?
Me?
Where's Marcus?
You dodged the question
all through dinner.
Isn't it his birthday?
Yeah.
And don't get mad
but I saw...
the moving boxes
in your bedroom.
Hey, Marcus, Happy Birthday!
Hi, Neil.
Good to see you, man.
Come, meet Mandy.
Mandy?
Yeah.
Hi, Mandy.
Hi.
Welcome.
Howdy, stranger!
Alice.
Hey!
Hi.
Hey.
Um, we just finished
cleaning up, but there
might be some leftovers.
Oh, no, that's okay.
I'm fine.
Uh, all right,
I'm gonna get
something in the kitchen.
I'll be right back.
So Marcus,
how's it going?
Uh, pretty well, pretty well.
New client.
Ooh, exciting.
Yeah.
I wish I had a regular job.
Somebody bring Marcus a glass!
Oh, thanks.
It's kinda boring, actually,
but you know, you make do.
I got to pay the bills somehow.
Wanna talk?
Sorry.
I didn't mean to startle you.
He really hurt me, Alice.
Six years.
It's bound to happen.
You think you can forgive him?
And I went away for three weeks
to do another play.
But it's been amazing,
and also
like, it's scheduled so that
if I have an audition
in the afternoon
I just work morning shifts.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHING]
Oh, you do.
Yay! Happy birthday!
Happy birthday! Whoo!
Yay!
[WHISTLING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hey.
Hi.
Before you say anything,
just let me explain.
I know it's late,
and I know...
I messed things up
and I know you
messed things up, too,
but none of that matters, okay?
Because I've been thinking,
and I know there's
no road map for this,
but maybe there's a way
that we can make things work.
You know, your needs,
my needs, we can, I know.
I saw this special on couples
out West...
Out in Oregon or something.
And there were three
or four of them sharing.
And yes, yes, they were fat
and there was lots of
facial hair going on.
But we can forgo beards, right?
Beards aren't a requirement.
Maybe we could
meet another couple?
Like us, you know,
somebody already in love
and they could
love us both, maybe.
I don't know,
but I'm willing to
try whatever it takes.
Because I wanna be with you.
I love you, Stan.
I don't love him.
I love you.
Let's make a wish.
How about that,
each of us, okay?
* A million dark nights
* Reveal that you have lost
* Lost, lost
Lost, lost
* But then comes the sun
* You feel you might have won
* Come on, come on
Come on, come on
* Yeah
* Let there be times
* That's all there is
* Dont' let there be times
[ALL CLAPPING]
* Thousand rainy days
* You worried
He'll be gone
* Long gone, long gone
* Gone along
* But then comes the sun
My man
* You feel you might have fun
* Come on, come on
Come on, come on
* Yeah
* Let there be times
* That's all there is
* Let there be time
* A hundred dotted day
You worry he'll be gone
* Gone, gone, gone, gone
Gone, gone
* But then comes the sun
* You feel you might have fun
* Come on, come on
Yeah, yeah, yeah
* Let there be time
* That's all there is
[ALL CHEERING LOUDLY]
Thank you.
[ACOUSTIC MUSIC PLAYING]