TIME.
8.8.
IT'S NOT DARK YET.
LET'S RUN A COUPLE MORE.
HOW'S THAT
KNEE HOLDING UP?
UH, IT'S PRETTY GOOD.
IT'S A YOUNG MAN'S GAME.
GEORGE, I'M LOOKING
FOR A SPONSOR...
SOMEONE WHO WILL PAY
MY DUES AND ENTRY FEES
AND SOME OF MY EXPENSES.
IF YOU DO, I'LL WEAR
YOUR NAME ON MY SHIRT.
I'LL MAKE APPEARANCES
AT THE CAR DEALERSHIPS
AND, UH, IN YOUR RESTAURANTS.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YOU LOOK REAL GOOD WITH
THAT ROPE OUT THERE, MAC
BUT THIS HERE'S
YOUR BACKYARD.
IT AIN'T NO
P.R.C.A. RODEO.
I KNOW.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT--
YOU GET YOURSELF
INTO THE PACHECO AT
THE END OF THE SUMMER--
RANCH HANDS' RODEO--
YOU DO WELL THERE
AND WE'LL TALK BUSINESS.
DEAL?
DEAL.
THANKS, GEORGE.
THAT A BOY.
MOM, HOW ABOUT THIS ONE?
LET'S SEE.
"THIS FILM
CONTAINS SCENES
OF VIOLENCE, NUDITY
AND STRONG LANGUAGE."
NOT FOR CHILDREN UNDER 18,
ESPECIALLY CHRIS McCLAIN.
GOOD-BYE, BRAD PITT.
MOM,SPECIES.
ISN'T THAT WHERE SHE
TURNS INTO THAT...?
YEAH.
AND KILLS THOSE...?
MOM.
OH, HERE WE ARE,SOUND OF MUSIC.
DON'T YOU LIKE US ANYMORE?
YOU HAVE A STRANGE
SENSE OF HUMOR, MOM.
VERY STRANGE.
I WAS KIDDING.
(dog barking)
SOMEONE FORGOT
TO LET LEO OUT.
I LET HIM OUT BEFORE WE LEFT.
YOU MUST HAVE DREAMED YOU DID.
CAN YOU GET HIM, KEL?
I GOT HIM
BEFORE WE LEFT.
YOU KNOW, I SWEAR
I CHANGED THAT LIGHT...
SATURDAY OR SUNDAY.
I KNOW I CHANGED IT.
I'M SURE I DID.
Woman:
CHRIS, READ IT
IN THE HOUSE.
(gunshots)
DON'T MOVE.
MOM?!
HELP!
Man 1:
YOU HEAR
FROM THE HOSPITAL?
Man 2:
MOTHER DIED IN FRONT
OF THE HOUSE.
FIANCE'S STILL ALIVE.
THEY TOOK TWO BULLETS OUT.
WITNESSES?
JUST THE GIRL.
IS THERE A MOTIVE HERE?
CASH, CREDIT
CARDS, JEWELRY--
SHOOTER LEFT IT ALL.
THE GIRLS KNOW
ABOUT THEIR MOTHER?
THEY KNOW.
C.P.S. IS ON THE WAY.
THE SHOOTER
SPOKE TO HER.
SHE TOLD ME
AFTER IT HAPPENED.
WE WERE WAITING
FOR THE POLICE.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
HE SAID, "DON'T MOVE."
CHRIS.
WE WANT TO CATCH
WHOEVER DID THIS.
SO IF THERE'S ANYTHING
YOU CAN TELL US.
IF HE WAS WHITE OR BLACK.
HOW TALL HE WAS.
WHAT HE
WAS WEARING.
IT WOULD REALLY HELP.
THAT'S OKAY.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO ANSWER RIGHT NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
FOR NOW, YOU'RE
GOING TO STAY
WITH CHILD
PROTECTIVE SERVICES
BUT WE CONTACTED
YOUR FAMILY IN CHICAGO.
UH, MILLER.
GAYLE MILLER?
AUNT GAYLE.
AND YOUR FATHER
IN BECKETT.
WE'RE TRACKING
HIM DOWN.
HE DOESN'T HAVE A PHONE.
YEAH.
HE MOVES AROUND A LOT.
WHAT'S HE DO?
HE'S A COWBOY.
(country rock music playing)
ANY TIME YOU WANT
TO HAVE ANOTHER GO
JUST CALL ME.
YEAH, OKAY.
NOW, I'D BE INTERESTED
IN MAYBE SOME OTHER PLAYERS.
(music continues)
THAT'S GOT TO BE HIM.
CHARLIE McCLAIN?
DETECTIVE ROSS.
THIS IS DETECTIVE CORTEZ.
THANKS FOR COMING DOWN.
GLAD YOU FOUND IT OKAY.
WHERE ARE THE CHILDREN?
THEY'RE WITH
CHILD PROTECTIVE SERVICES--
PROBABLY ON THEIR WAY
TO COURT BY NOW.
YOU CAN'T JUST
HAVE THEM, CHARLIE.
THEY'RE
IN PROTECTIVE CUSTODY.
YOU HAVE TO GO
BEFORE THE JUDGE.
Charlie:
WHO DID THIS?
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE
TRYING TO FIND OUT.
HOW'D YOU GET ALONG
WITH THE EX-WIFE?
WE DIDN'T TALK
THE LAST COUPLE OF YEARS.
DID YOU KNOW SHE WAS
GETTING
MARRIED AGAIN?
YEAH, I HEARD.
YOU DIDN'T GET TO SEE
YOUR KIDS MUCH, DID YOU?
I MEAN, EVEN BEFORE SHE
GOT HOOKED UP WITH KALLEN.
NO.
ONLY GOING TO GET WORSE
AFTER SHE
MARRIED HIM.
I WAS 400 MILES FROM HERE
WHEN THIS HAPPENED...
SHOOTING POOL IN A BAR
WITH SOME FRIENDS.
NOW, I KNOW YOU BOYS ARE
JUST DOING YOUR JOB...
BUT DO IT ON SOMEONE ELSE,
WILL YOU?
OKAY, I KNOW
HE'S PRINTING
THE FRONT DOOR.
ALL RIGHT.
I GOT EVERYTHING
ON THE SECOND FLOOR.
I'LL HEAD OUT.
OKAY.
YOU'RE CHARLIE?
I'M ANNA--
MR. KALLEN'S HOUSEKEEPER.
I'M VERY SORRY.
JESSE WAS SO KIND--
SUCH A GOOD MOTHER.
YOU RECOGNIZE THAT NECKLACE?
I GAVE IT TO HER.
TAKE IT.
NO, I DON'T THINK I SHOULD.
OH, SHE WOULD'VE WANTED YOU
TO HAVE IT.
PLEASE.
I WON'T TELL ANYONE.
CHARLIE McCLAIN.
I'M THEIR FATHER.
LISA EVERSON.
CHILD PROTECTIVE SERVICES.
I'LL SEE IF
WE'RE ON SCHEDULE.
HEY.
HI.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW MUCH YOU'VE GROWN.
I'M SO SORRY
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED.
AUNT GAYLE'S COMING, TOO.
ALL RIGHT, MS. EVERSON.
THERE'S BEEN NO
ARREST, YOUR HONOR
AND IT'S IMPORTANT
TO GET THE GIRLS
OUT OF TOWN
FOR THEIR OWN SAFETY.
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
GIRLS...
LISTEN UP,
PLEASE.
THIS COURT LOOKS
AFTER YOUR SAFETY
AND WELFARE.
IF WE CAN
WE TRY TO KEEP THE
FAMILY TOGETHER
BECAUSE WE BELIEVE IT'S
IN YOUR BEST INTEREST.
SO, MR. McCLAIN
I AM GOING TO GIVE
YOU YOUR GIRLS
BUT IN LIGHT OF
MRS. MILLER'S PETITION
I'M GRANTING YOU
TEMPORARY CUSTODY.
NOW, YOU'LL BE ASSIGNED
A COUNSELOR FROM THE DEPARTMENT
OF FAMILY SERVICES IN BECKETT.
AND IN THREE MONTHS'
TIME, YOU'LL APPEAR
BEFORE THE BECKETT
COUNTY SUPERIOR COURT.
NOW, IF THE COUNSELOR'S
REPORTS ARE POSITIVE
AND, OF COURSE, IF THE GIRLS
WANTTO STAY WITH
YOU, THEY WILL.
IF NOT...
THE COURT WILL MAKE
OTHER ARRANGEMENTS.
NOW, IS THAT CLEAR, SIR?
UH, YES, MA'AM.
ALL RIGHT. NEXT CASE, PLEASE.
OKAY.
THIS IS YOUR TRUCK?
YEP.
SHE'S GOT 400,000 MILES ON HER.
OKAY.
COME ON.
(horn honks)
WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
CHARLIE?
YOU NEVER WANTED
TO BE A FATHER
TO THOSE KIDS.
YOU WOULDN'T EVEN KNOW
HOW TO GO ABOUT IT.
IT'S JUST NOT FAIR
TO THE GIRLS.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET YOU
HAVE THEM.
(limousine engine starting)
SECOND-HAND SMOKE KILLS,
YOU KNOW.
(coughing)
YEAH, WELL, I'M
TRYING TO QUIT.
HEY, GIRLS,
THIS IS IT.
COME ON OUT.
HEY, CARL.
GOOD-LOOKING GIRLS, MAC.
THANKS.
Carl:
RECKON IT'S GOING TO TAKE
SOME GETTING USED TO.
RECKON SO.
STILL THINK YOU SHOULD
STAY AT MY PLACE
TILL WE KNOW
IT'S SAFE HERE.
YEAH, WELL...
WE BEEN ALL OVER THE RANCH;
I'LL LEAVE ONE OF MY BOYS
HERE FOR A WHILE.
CARL, NOW, I DON'T...
THAT'S JUST THE WAY
IT'S GOING TO BE.
(cows mooing)
COME ON...
GIRLS, THIS IS
SHERIFF DEWITT.
THIS IS KELLY,
AND THIS IS CHRIS.
NICE TO MEET YOU BOTH.
I'LL COME BY LATER
AND CHECK ON YOU.
OKAY, THANKS A LOT.
(whistling)
(dogs barking)
COME ON!
THAT'S IT!
THIS IS DENVER
AND THAT'S DALLAS.
COME ON IN.
LET'S GET YOU
SETTLED.
(car engine starts)
(cows mooing)
THIS IS IT?
YEP.
IT'S SO SMALL.
YEAH, WELL...
YOU GET USED TO IT.
THERE'S NO TV?
NOPE.
(scoffs):
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
YOU TAKE THE BED.
I'LL TAKE THE COUCH.
STAY OFF THE BED.
NO,YOUTAKE THE BED.
WE'LL SLEEP IN CHICAGO.
(sighs)
MR. McCLAIN?
I'M SUSAN SHAW.
I'M A COUNSELOR WITH THE
DEPARTMENT OF FAMILY SERVICES.
WHERE ARE THE GIRLS?
(sighs)
INSIDE.
HOW ARE THEY?
ALL RIGHT, CONSIDERING.
THE YOUNGEST, CHRIS,
IS STILL PRETTY SHOOK UP.
SHE SAW IT HAPPEN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE'S DEAD.
I'M SORRY.
I CAN ONLY IMAGINE HOW
HARD THIS IS FOR YOU.
THAT'S MY CARD.
COUNSELING IS
A CONDITION OF
YOUR CUSTODY
SO YOU NEED TO COME INTO MY
OFFICE AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
I'VE SCHEDULED 10:00
TOMORROW MORNING.
WE'LL MEET
TWICE A WEEK.
CALL ME ANYTIME IF
YOU HAVE QUESTIONS.
OTHER THAN THAT,
GOOD LUCK.
NOW THAT THEY'RE HERE
YOU HAVE TO START BEING
THEIR FATHER AGAIN.
YEAH, WELL...
HOW THE HELL DO I DO THAT?
(birds chirping)
(Chris whimpering)
(screaming)
Kelly:
IT'S OKAY,
IT'S OKAY, CHRIS.
(Chris sobbing)
KELLY?
Kelly:
DON'T CRY.
(Chris sobbing)
Kelly:
IT'S OKAY.
DON'T CRY.
DON'T WORRY.
YOU'RE SAFE.
IS SHE OKAY?
SHE'LL BE FINE.
COME ON.
YOU WANT ME TO GET
A GLASS OF WATER OR SOMETHING?
NO.
IT'S OKAY.
COME ON.
Charlie:FROM NOW ON
I GOT TO GET THE FIRST SHOWER
IN THE MORNING.
Kelly:
I CAN'T HEAR YOU!
Charlie:
IT ONLY TAKES ME
FIVE MINUTES.
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
I GOT TO GET TO WORK
IN THE MORNING.
IT ONLY TAKES ME FIVE...
WHAT IS THIS?
LAUNDRY.
DIRTY LAUNDRY DOES NOT GO
ON MY ALLMAN BROTHERS
RECORDS.
IT HAS TO BE WASHED.
AND WHO IS SUPPOSED TO WASH IT?
DON'T KNOW HOW.
YOU PUT IT IN THE SINK
YOU PUT IT IN SOME WATER
AND SOAP, WASH IT
AND HANG IT UP TO DRY, OKAY?
(frustrated sigh)
OKAY, THIS IS DRIVING ME CRAZY.
MOM BRAIDS IT.
OKAY...
WE'LL BRAID IT.
THAT'S A PONYTAIL
NOT A BRAID.
(dog barking)
Woman:
WHERE'S MY COWBOY?
I'M OVER HERE.
CHARLIE McCLAIN.
YOU BACK TO WORK ALREADY?
YES, MA'AM.
I'M GOING TO OWE YOU
FOR THE WEEK?
CASH MONEY.
WHERE'S YOUR GIRLS?
INSIDE.
KELLY!
CHRIS!
COME ON OUT!
THERE'S SOMEONE
I WANT YOU TO MEET.
HELLO.
I'M DOTTY CLAYTON...
AND THIS IS MY RANCH.
WHICH ONE OF YOU
IS KELLY?
I AM.
I KNOW YOUR FATHER
DON'T HAVE NO SODA OR JUNK FOOD
IN THE HOUSE
BUT I'VE GOT A FRIDGE
FULL OF ROOT BEER
AND BOXES
OF CANDY BARS
AND YOU JUST COME AROUND
WHENEVER YOU LIKE
AND HELP YOURSELVES.
OH, DOTTY'S GOING TO TAKE
REAL GOOD CARE OF YOU.
ALL RIGHT?
TAKE IT EASY, GIRLS.
THINGS AIN'T NEVER AS BAD
AS THEY SEEM RIGHT OFF.
COME ON, GET UP THERE.
GET UP.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
MOM LIVED LIKE THIS.
I CAN'T BELIEVEWE'RELIVING LIKE THIS.
HEY, COW. HEY, COW.
HEY, HEY.
IT'S GOING TO
BE A LONG DAY.
I'VE HAD WORSE.
WELL, THAT WAS
JUST THE FIRST TRUCK.
OH, NO. MORE TRUCKS?
OH, YOU'RE TALKING NOW.
WHEN THE LAST
COW IS DONE
AND IT'S, OH, SOMEWHERE
WAY AFTER DARK
YOU'RE GOING TO WANT
TO FALL DOWN ON A BED
AND SLEEP
FOR THREE DAYS.
SINCE YOU BROUGHT THAT UP...
THAT PART ABOUT
FALLING DOWN IN A BED.
OH, HERE IT COMES--
ANYTIME A COWBOY
STARTS A SENTENCE
WITH, "SINCE YOU
BROUGHT THAT UP"
YOU KNOW YOU'RE
IN FOR A WORLD
OF TROUBLE.
I NEED TO BUILD
A NEW BEDROOM FOR THE GIRLS.
THE BUNKHOUSE HAS A BEDROOM.
YEP, THAT'S RIGHT,
AND I WANT IT BACK.
THE GIRLS NEED
TO HAVE THEIR OWN ROOM.
WE'RE OPPOSITE SEXES.
WE CAN'T BE BARGING IN
ON EACH OTHER.
OH, AND WHO'S SUPPOSED
TO PAY FOR ALL THIS
NEW CONSTRUCTION?
WELL, I DON'T HAVE ANY MONEY.
AND, LOU, HE DOESN'T
EVEN KNOW WHAT MONEY IS.
HE'S RIGHT
ABOUT THAT, BOSS.
I GUESS THAT MEANS YOU.
ARE THEY INSIDE?
YEAH.
THEY DIDN'T WANT
TO COME OUT.
HOW'S MY LITTLE ONE?
UH, SHE'S STILL
PRETTY SHOOK UP.
I DON'T KNOW
IF IT'S BECAUSE, UH...
SHE'S SCARED THE GUY WHO SHOT
JESSE'S GOING TO COME AFTER HER
OR BECAUSE SHE SAW
THE WHOLE THING.
OR BOTH.
OH, HELL, MAN
GO ON, BUILD IT.
JUST GET IT RIGHT.
MAKE IT PRETTY, HUH?
PRETTY.
OKAY?
YEP.
HEY! COME ON, COW!
HEY, HEY!
Kelly:I DON'T WANT TO TALK
ABOUT MY FEELINGS AGAIN.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT?
WE HAVE
TO GO SHOPPING.
WE'VE ALREADY
BEEN THROUGH THIS.
NO, WE HAVEN'T.
YOU SAID THAT WE CAN'T LEAVE
THE RANCH AND THAT WAS IT.
CARL DOESN'T WANT
YOU GIRLS WALKING
AROUND TOWN.
IT'S NOT FAIR.
WELL, NOT
EVERYTHING IS.
WE NEED TO GO TO A DRUG STORE.
FOR WHAT?
TAMPAX
SOAP, SHAMPOO
TOOTHPASTE.
I DON'T WANT TO USE
YOUR CRUDDY STUFF
AND NEITHER DOES CHRIS.
AND BESIDES, WE HAVE
NOTHING TO WEAR.
OKAY.
I KNOW YOU AND YOUR SISTER
ARE TRYING
TO GET USED
TO THE WAY THINGS...
THE WAY THINGS ARE SUCK...
DAD.
"THE WAY THINGS ARE SUCK, DAD."
THEY'RE NOT COWBOYS.
THEY'RE GIRLS
FROM LOS ANGELES.
WELL, THEY'RE PART
OF MY LIFE NOW.
WELL, THEN, YOUR LIFE
HAS TO CHANGE PERHAPS.
DID CARL REACH YOU?
ABOUT WHAT?
ROSS AND CORTEZ.
THEY PICKED UP A GUY
FOR QUESTIONING
AND HELD HIM
FOR A FEW DAYS.
BUT IT WASN'T HIM.
ALSO, KALLEN'S
GOING TO LIVE.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
HE SENDS HIS CONDOLENCES
AND WISHES THE GIRLS GOOD LUCK.
HE SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT THEIR THINGS?
HE SAID HE'D HAVE THEM PACKED UP
AND SHIPPED IN THE FALL.
HE'S SENDING THEM
TO ME OR TO GAYLE?
WHERE DO YOU WANT IT SENT?
OH, GIVE ME A BREAK.
WE HAVE TO BUY OUR
CLOTHES IN THERE?
I DO.
THERE SHE IS.
OKAY.
HELLO.
GAYLE MILLER CALLED
MY OFFICE.
SHE CALLED
JUDGE MORGAN, TOO.
SHE'S LOOKING FOR
A LOCAL ATTORNEY
WHO DOES CUSTODY CASES.
SHE'S DETERMINED
TO GET THE GIRLS.
IF I'M GOING TO HELP,
I NEED HISTORY ON THIS.
GAYLE, UH...
SHE WAS ALWAYS TRYING
TO BREAK US UP
RIGHT FROM THE START.
BUT, JESS, SHE DIDN'T CARE.
SHE WAS ALWAYS
BUCKING THE FAMILY.
SO YOU MARRIED ANYWAY?
WE WERE IN LOVE.
NOBODY WAS GOING TO BREAK US
APART, NOT EVEN GAYLE.
MAC, THAT...
LET ME SEE THAT.
YOU CAN'T WEAR THIS;
I CAN SEE THROUGH IT.
NO.
UM, JESSE AND GAYLE--
HOW'D THEY GROW UP?
WHAT WAS THEIR UPBRINGING?
THEY GREW UP IN PASADENA.
THERE WAS A LOT OF MONEY.
THEIR FATHER WAS A BANKER.
AND I WAS, UH,
I WAS A REAL STEP DOWN
FOR THE FAMILY AS FAR
GAYLE WAS CONCERNED.
BUT SHE MARRIED WISELY?
OH, YEAH.
SOME BIG SURGEON IN CHICAGO.
HE RUNS A HOSPITAL THERE.
THEY HAVE TWO KIDS,
BIG HOUSE IN THE SUBURBS--
ANOTHER ONE IN FLORIDA.
NOW SHE WANTS THE GIRLS.
YEAH. I GUESS SHE DOESN'T THINK
I'LL MAKE
MUCH OF A FATHER EITHER.
WHERE'S CHRIS?
I DON'T KNOW.
CHRIS?
(door opening)
WHERE THE HELL...?
IS THIS OKAY?
YEAH.
LOOKS REAL NICE, DARLING.
Charlie:NOW, THIS PRETTY GIRL
IS NAMED GEORGIA.
WE'VE ROPED A LOT
OF CALVES TOGETHER.
IN FACT, SHE'S THE MOTHER OF
THE COLT I'M RIDING RIGHT NOW.
SHE'S PREGNANT.
SHE'S HAVING A
ROUGH GO OF IT.
WE'VE GOT THE VET
WATCHING HER.
WE'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE
TO KEEP OUR FINGERS CROSSED.
COME ON-- LET'S GET HER
CLEANED UP AND FED.
THEN I'M TEACHING YOU TWO
HOW TO RIDE.
DID MOM RIDE?
ALL THE TIME.
SHE NEVER RODE WITH US...
NEVER EVEN
TALKED ABOUT IT.
HOW'D YOU MEET?
YOUR MOTHER NEVER TOLD YOU?
WE NEVER ASKED.
HOW DID WE MEET?
WELL...
I'D JUST FINISHED
THIS RODEO UP IN TUCSON AND...
I DECIDED TO KICK BACK FOR A FEW
DAYS BEFORE HEADING UP NORTH.
YOUR MOTHER, SHE'D, UH,
SHE'D LEFT HOME.
SHE HAD TO WORK
AS A WAITRESS
IN THIS BURGER JOINT
I JUST HAPPENED TO WALK INTO.
CAN YOU IMAGINE YOUR MOTHER
AS A WAITRESS?
OH...
SHE WAS A BRIGHT LIGHT
IN A DARK ROOM.
AND WE FELL
HEAD-OVER-HEELS IN LOVE.
AND IN THE BEGINNING,
SHE LOVED THIS LIFE--
THE RODEOS
AND THE TRAVELING AND...
AND THEN WE
GOT MARRIED
AND THEN
YOU WERE BORN.
IT GOT HARDER
FOR YOUR MOTHER
LIVING ON THE ROAD
TEN MONTHS OF THE YEAR
AND WHEN CHRIS CAME ALONG
IT SEEMED TOUGH
TO STAY TOGETHER.
SHE WANTED MORE FOR YOU GIRLS.
HELL, I WANTED
MORE FOR YOU, TOO.
WE JUST SEEMED
TO DRIFT FURTHER
AND FURTHER APART.
WE ENDED UP GOING
OUR SEPARATE WAYS.
YOU LET US GO.
I JUST DID
THE BEST I THOUGHT I COULD.
IT WASN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
WE'RE WORKING AS
HARD AS WE CAN
TO FIND THE MAN
WHO KILLED
YOUR MOTHER...
BUT WE NEED
YOUR HELP NOW.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO SAW IT HAPPEN.
TRY TO REMEMBER.
IT WAS DARK.
THE DOG WAS BARKING
IN THE BACKYARD.
(barking)
THE LIGHT BY THE FRONT
OF THE HOUSE WAS OUT.
YOUR SISTER WENT
TO GET THE DOG.
YOUR MOTHER
AND MR. KALLEN
WERE WALKING
TOWARDS THE HOUSE.
A MAN JUMPED OUT
OF THE SHADOWS.
HE HAD A GUN; HE
SHOT YOUR MOTHER
AND MR. KALLEN.
YOU SAW HIM
SHOOT HER.
HE TURNED
TO YOU.
NO.
HE SAID,
"DON'T MOVE."
DON'T MOVE.
Kelly:MOM?!
HELP!
HE LOOKED AT YOU,
DIDN'T HE, CHRIS?
YOU WERE GETTING OUT OF THE CAR
AND HE LOOKED
RIGHT AT YOU.
EASY.
(crying )
HELP US, CHRIS.
TELL US WHAT
HE LOOKED LIKE.
COME ON. YOU SAW HIM, CHRIS.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH.
WHAT DID HE LOOK LIKE?
I SAID THAT'S ENOUGH.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE WEREN'T TRYING
TO UPSET HER.
WELL, YOU DID.
LISTEN, KALLEN DIDN'T
SEE THE SHOOTER.
HE DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING.
HE CAN'T HELP US.
AS FAR AS I.D.ing THE KILLER,
IT'S UP TO CHRIS.
YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY OTHER LEADS, DO YOU?
WE'RE WORKING ON IT.
WE'VE BEEN ASKING
AROUND ABOUT KALLEN.
HE DOESN'T HAVE
A WHOLE LOT OF FRIENDS
IN THE CONCRETE BUSINESS.
HE BACKED OUT OF
A BIG CONTRACT--
COST THE UNION A
COUPLE HUNDRED JOBS.
LOTS OF BAD BLOOD
ON BOTH SIDES.
LOOKS LIKE YOUR EX-WIFE
WAS JUST IN THE WRONG PLACE
AT THE WRONG TIME.
COME ON.
OKAY, KEEP ONE LEG
ON EACH SIDE
AND YOUR MIND
IN THE MIDDLE.
THAT'S ALL
THERE IS TO IT.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
I JUST WANT TO GET THINGS
BACK TO NORMAL.
NOTHING IS
NORMAL ANYMORE.
YOU LIVE ON A RANCH,
YOU OUGHT TO KNOW HOW TO RIDE.
NOW PUT YOUR FOOT IN THE STIRRUP
AND SWING YOUR LEG OVER.
I DIDN'T SEE ANYONE.
WHAT?
BY THE TIME I GOT THERE,
HE WAS GONE.
NOT NOW, KEL.
WHY CAN'T SHE TELL THEM
ANYTHING?
SHE JUST CAN'T.
HE LOOKED
RIGHT AT HER.
GET ON THE HORSE.
SHE SAW HIM!
GET ON THE DAMN HORSE.
WHY CAN'T SHE GO FIRST?!
SHE'S BEEN THROUGH
A HELL OF A LOT.
IT DIDN'T JUST
HAPPEN TO HER!
KELLY...
SHE WAS MY MOTHER, TOO!
COME BACK HERE.
WHERE THE HELL ARE YOU GOING?
I HATE THIS!
I HATE YOU!
OH, YOU HATE THIS?
YOU THINK I LIKE
SEEING SOME DAMN
SHRINK TWO TIMES A WEEK?
YOU HATE THIS.
I WASH YOUR CLOTHES;
I CLEAN UP AFTER YOU.
I HAVE TO LISTEN TO YOU COMPLAIN
EVERY DAMN DAY!
HUH?
I GOTTA LISTEN TO YOU COMPLAIN
EVERY DAMN DAY!
"I HATE YOU."
OH, THAT'S GREAT.
Chris:THERE'S NO SHERIFF TONIGHT.
WHERE'S DAD?
WHO CARES?
WHAT IF HE NEVER COMES BACK?
HE'LL COME BACK.
HE HAS TO.
WHAT IF HE DOESN'T?
WHERE ARE WE GOING TO GO?
WHO CARES?
ANYWHERE.
I WANT TO GO HOME.
(up-tempo country music
playing)
I BEEN, UH,
WATCHING YOU ALL NIGHT.
YOU'RE CHARLIE McCLAIN,
AIN'T YOU?
I ROPED AGAINST YOU ONCE
UP IN OKLAHOMA CITY.
NAME'S MACEY.
KYLE MACEY.
REMEMBER ME?
YOU KICKED MY ASS.
TOLD YOU IT WAS HIM.
GOT OFF RODES
A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO.
COULDN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
HEARD HE WAS GOING TO TRY
SOME KIND OF COMEBACK
BUT DON'T LOOK LIKE IT TO ME.
HE'S JUST A SORRY-ASS, HAS-BEEN.
HE AIN'T NEVER COMING BACK.
LET IT GO, MAC.
NOT TODAY.
Macey:
COME ON, MAC.
I SAID, NOT TODAY.
HEY, SUE.
HEY!
LET'S GO.
NO, NO.
I GOT TO GO HOME.
CHARLIE, YOU'RE
NOT GOING HOME.
YOU'RE GOING
TO JAIL.
NO. NO!
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND;
I GOT TO GO HOME.
(door closes)
I GOT TO TAKE A SHOWER.
Kelly:
WE HAVE A MEETING WITH SUSAN
IN HALF AN HOUR.
DO YOU WANT
TO TELL THE GIRLS
WHERE YOU WERE
LAST NIGHT?
MAC?
I WENT TO A BAR.
I GOT INTO A FIGHT, AND, UH...
I SPENT THE NIGHT IN JAIL.
KELLY?
I WANT TO GO BACK TO L.A.
I WANT TO TALK
TO MY FRIENDS.
WE DON'T EVEN HAVE A PHONE.
I DON'T WANT TO LIVE HERE
WITH HIM.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
AT THE END OF THE SUMMER
HE WON'T BE OUR FATHER
ANYWAY.
HEY.
I WILL ALWAYS BE YOUR FATHER.
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT BEING A FATHER.
CHRIS, DO YOU FEEL
THE SAME WAY AS KELLY?
OUR MOTHER IS DEAD
AND WE HAVE TO LIVE
WITH HIM.
HOW DO YOU THINK
WE'RE FEELING?
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU ISN'T FAIR
AND IT'S VERY,
VERY COMPLICATED.
YOU HAVE TO GRIEVE
YOUR MOTHER'S DEATH
WHILE TRYING TO BUILD
A LIFE WITH YOUR FATHER.
FORGET IT.
MY LIFE IS GONE.
YEAH, WELL, SO IS MINE.
I NEED A SMOKE.
(scoffs)
OKAY.
YOU GOT INTO A FIGHT.
YOU SPENT THE
NIGHT IN JAIL.
THE GIRLS HAD NO
IDEA WHERE YOU WERE
AND NO WAY TO REACH YOU.
HOW DID YOU THINK
THEY'D REACT?
THE GUY HAD IT COMING
AND THERE WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
A COP WATCHING THEM.
CARL HAD TO
PULL HIM AWAY
AND BESIDES, THAT'S
NOT THE POINT.
IT'S NOT CARL'S
RESPONSIBILITY
TO TAKE CARE
OF YOUR DAUGHTERS.
IT'S YOURS.
YOU HAVE TO DO
BETTER THAN THIS.
THAT'S WHAT TEMPORARY
CUSTODY IS ALL ABOUT.
WELL, MAYBE IT'S TOO HARD,
AND I CAN'T DO IT.
YOU WERE THE ONE
WHO TOLD ME
THAT THE GIRLS NEEDED SOMEBODY
THEY COULD TALK TO ABOUT THINGS
SOMEBODY THEY'D BE COMFORTABLE
TALKING TO.
WELL, IT'S NOT ME,
AND IT'S NOT EVER GOING TO BE.
PUT DOWN IN YOUR REPORT
THAT AT THE END OF THE SUMMER,
THOSE GIRLS GO BACK TO CHICAGO.
THAT'S SAD.
DO YOU KNOW WHY?
YOU'RE NOT JUST LOSING
THE GIRLS TO GAYLE.
YOU'RE LOSING THE CHANCE
TO BE THEIR FATHER.
YOU ARE GIVING
UP A LIFE
YOU CAN NEVER
HAVE WITHOUT THEM.
JESSE IS DEAD.
YOU'RE ALL THEY HAVE
AND THEY NEED YOU.
PLEASE DO NOT
GIVE UP ON THIS.
YOU'VE NEVER BEEN
TO A RODEO, HAVE YOU?
NO.
CALF'S IN THE SHOOT.
YOU'RE ON THE HORSE
IN THE BOX...
AND THEN...
THE GATE OPENS AND...
BANG.
OF COURSE,
IN A RODEO,
THE DAMN CALF'S
JUMPING AROUND
LIKE A RABBIT.
Chris:
HEY!
IT'S SOMETHING TO SEE.
(panting)
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
IT'S GEORGIA.
COME ON!
KELLY, COME ON!
(dogs barking)
(grunting)
(Georgia whinnying)
(whinnying continues)
OKAY, GIRL.
IT'S OKAY.
I'M GOING TO HELP YOU.
YEAH, THAT'S A GOOD GIRL.
I'M GOING TO
HELP YOU NOW.
IT'S OKAY, GIRL.
ALL RIGHT, GIRLS, COME ON.
I NEED YOUR HELP.
OKAY.
OKAY, GIRL.
JUST GO UP THERE BY HER HEAD.
OKAY.
THAT'S IT, GEORGIA.
WE'RE GOING TO HELP YOU.
IT'S OKAY. IT'S OKAY. WHOA.
THAT'S A GIRL.
IT'S OKAY, GIRL.
(whinnying)
SHE'S GETTING WEAKER.
COME ON, GIRL.
DON'T YOU GIVE
UP ON ME NOW.
OKAY.
COME ON, GEORGIA.
YOU GOT TO PUSH.
(whinnies)
OKAY, GIRL.
COME ON.
YOU GOT TO PUSH.
OKAY, COME ON, GEORGIA.
COME ON, GEORGIA!
(Charlie grunting)
COME ON!
COME ON, GEORGIA!
COME ON.
THAT A GIRL.
COME ON, GEORGIA,
ONE MORE!
(grunting)
COME ON, THAT A GIRL.
THAT A GIRL.
COME ON, GEORGIA,
ONE MORE.
(foal whinnying)
THAT A GIRL.
OKAY, COME ON.
COME ON.
COME ON. COME ON.
COME ON, THAT A GIRL.
THAT A GIRL.
THAT A GIRL. OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, GIRLS,
COME OVER HERE AND HELP ME NOW.
GO OVER THERE
AND GET SOME HAY.
WE GOT TO CLEAN HER UP.
THAT'S IT.
(foal whinnying)
(dogs whining)
(dogs barking)
OKAY, NOW, I WANT YOU
TO RUB HER ALL OVER.
COME ON,
CLEAN HER UP.
IT'S NOT GOING TO BITE YOU.
THAT'S IT, THAT'S IT, COME ON.
CLEAN HER UP.
RUB HER ALL OVER.
THAT'S IT.
LET HER FEEL YOU.
LET HER SMELL YOU.
THEN SHE'LL BE GOOD.
SHE'LL LET PEOPLE TOUCH HER.
OKAY, NOW, SHE'S GOING TO NEED
SOMEONE SPECIAL TO FEED HER.
ALMOST EVERY HOUR, SOMEONE'S
GOING TO HAVE TO LOOK AFTER HER.
OKAY, YOU THINK
YOU CAN DO THAT, CHRIS?
OKAY.
YOU WANT THAT JOB?
YEAH.
OKAY. SHE'S GOING TO BE
YOUR RESPONSIBILITY.
OKAY, THAT'S IT.
ISN'T SHE BEAUTIFUL?
(whistling)
HI, SUSAN.
HI, DEB.
CHARLIE McCLAIN STOPPED BY
THIS MORNING.
YEAH, I HAVE A SESSION
WITH HIM TODAY.
HE WANTS
TO RESCHEDULE IT.
HE'S, UM, PUTTING IN A PHONE
FOR THE GIRLS.
OH. UH, DID HE SAY WHEN?
HE SAID HE'D CALL YOU.
HE WAS COVERED WITH DIRT,
RIGHT OFF THE RANCH.
WELL, YOU KNOW, A LOT OF GUYS
SAY THAT THEY'RE COWBOYS
BUT HE'S THE REAL THING.
THE FIRST TIME I SAW HIM
AT HIS HOUSE
I THOUGHT HE WAS GARY COOPER.
GARY COOPER.
VERY INTERESTING.
DEB... PLEASE.
HE'S A CLIENT.
I'M NOT GETTING PERSONALLY
INVOLVED WITH HIM.
I'M NOT SAYING THAT YOU ARE.
NO, BUT YOU WERE THINKING IT.
REALLY, SUSAN.
AREN'T YOU?
(laughs)
OKAY.
OKAY, EVERYTHING FOUR
FOOT AND DOWN IS CHRIS.
EVERYTHING FOUR FOOT
AND UP IS YOU, KELLY.
I'LL GET THE CEILING
WHEN I'M DONE
WITH THE PHONE.
IS IT GOING TO WORK?
IT SHOULD.
DOTTY PUT IN A LINE
A LONG TIME AGO.
I JUST NEVER USED IT.
WHERE'D YOU LEARN
HOW TO DO ALL THIS?
IN THE ARMY.
DID SOME CARPENTRY,
PLUMBING, ELECTRIC
A LITTLE BIT
OF EVERYTHING.
GIRLS, THE ROOM'S
NOT GOING TO PAINT ITSELF.
UM, WE'VE NEVER PAINTED
A ROOM BEFORE.
OKAY.
IT'S NOT THAT HARD.
PUT A LITTLE PAINT
ON THE BRUSH
AND THEN YOU PUT
THE PAINT ON THE WALL.
THAT'S ALL
THERE IS TO IT.
LET'S GO...
OH, NOT SO MUCH.
UH, TRY TO GET
JUST THE TIP, OKAY?
LIKE THAT.
WE'LL COAT THE CORNERS
FIRST, THEN THE EDGES
AND THEN WE'LL COME
BACK AND DO THE MIDDLE.
JUST LIKE THIS.
OKAY?
YOU KNOW, WHEN
I WAS A LITTLE BOY
MY MOTHER HIRED
SOME LOCAL KIDS
TO PAINT THE HOUSE
DURING THE SUMMER.
SHE TOLD ME I
HAD TO HELP THEM.
I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT I WAS DOING.
BUT BY THE END
OF THE SUMMER
I COULD PAINT
A WHOLE ROOM BY MYSELF.
HERE, YOU TRY.
OH, THAT'S GOOD, KELLY.
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
SO HOW MUCH
DID YOUR MOM PAY YOU?
NOTHING.
IT WAS ONE OF THOSE,
UH, PAINT-THE-HOUSE-
AND-I'LL-LET-
YOU-LIVE DEALS.
SORT OF LIKE THIS?
SORT OF.
IS THE PHONE DONE YET?
OH, THE PHONE.
LET'S SEE.
JUST PUT THE JACK IN.
YOU TRY IT.
(dial tone drones)
NOW YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY BOYFRIENDS
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT,
DO YOU?
ONLY IN HAWAII.
OH, GREAT.
(dogs barking)
OH, HELL.
I WAS GOING
TO CALL YOU.
I KNOW.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WE BROUGHT PICTURES.
MAYBE IT'LL HELP HER REMEMBER.
WE'LL TRY TO DO
A SKETCH THIS TIME.
WHAT?
I SAID, NO.
THE SHOOTER'S
STILL OUT THERE, MAC.
I KNOW.
WHAT IF HE
COMES LOOKING?
HE CAN'T FIND HER HERE.
WE DON'T KNOW THAT
FOR SURE.
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
THEY'RE DOING EVERYTHING
THEY POSSIBLY CAN.
WE GOT SIX GUYS
ON IT EVERYDAY.
WE RUN ANYTHING THAT
SMELLS LIKE A LEAD.
WE CANVASSED
THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
THEN CANVASSED IT AGAIN
AND THEN AGAIN.
WE QUESTIONED EVERYONE
WHO KNEW YOUR EX-WIFE
WHOEVER KNEW KALLEN.
AND YOU'RE STILL
STUCK IN THE CHUTE.
WHOEVER IT WAS
COULD HAVE SHOT HER
RIGHT THERE
AT THE HOUSE
IF HE'D WANTED TO.
I'M NOT GOING TO PUT HER
THROUGH THIS AGAIN.
SHE'S HAD A HARD ENOUGH TIME
DEALING WITH IT AS IT IS.
SHE HAS TO PUT THIS
BEHIND HER AND MOVE ON.
I WILL KEEP MY EYES OUT.
GOD HELP THE SON OF A BITCH
IF HE EVER SHOWS UP HERE.
MR. McCLAIN,
YOU'RE INTERFERING
WITH A MURDER INVESTIGATION.
ANDYOU'REINTERFERING
WITH OUR LIVES.
CARL, I WANT YOU
AND THE DEPUTIES OFF THE RANCH.
HEY, MAC...
I APPRECIATE WHAT YOU'VE DONE,
BUT YOU CAN GO BACK TO L.A. NOW.
WE'RE DONE HERE.
IT'S OVER.
8.2 SECONDS.
THIS IS REALLY
SOMETHING, CHARLIE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
VISITING.
TALKING WITH MY NIECES.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I JUST WANTED
TO SEE THE GIRLS
MAKE SURE
THEY'RE ALL RIGHT.
THEY'RE FINE.
I WANT YOU TO LEAVE.
I AM SO SORRY, GIRLS.
IF I'D HAD ANY IDEA
OF THE CIRCUMSTANCES
THAT YOU...
I'M ASKING YOU TO LEAVE.
I'LL BE IN TOUCH.
THIS IS DAVID WINSTON
A LOCAL ATTORNEY
I HAVE ON RETAINER.
I THOUGHT WE SHOULD
SEE FOR OURSELVES
WHAT KIND OF LIFE YOU'VE MADE
FOR KELLY AND CHRIS
BEFORE WE SPEAK
TO THE JUDGE.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
WE'VE PETITIONED
THE BECKETT SUPERIOR COURT
AND THE JUDGE HAS AGREED TO SEE
US IN HIS CHAMBERS NEXT WEEK.
WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS, GAYLE?
BECAUSE I HAVE TO.
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO CHANGE.
YOU NEVER CHANGED FOR JESSE.
ALL THOSE PROMISES...
AND YOU DIDN'T CHANGE.
YOU'RE GOING TO END UP
HURTING THOSE GIRLS
JUST LIKE
YOU DID MY SISTER.
AND I WILL NOT ALLOW THAT
TO HAPPEN AGAIN.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT THE GIRLS.
YOU JUST HATE ME.
LOOK AT THIS.
LOOK HOW THEY'RE LIVING.
I CAN GIVE THEM
EVERYTHING, CHARLIE.
WHAT CAN YOU GIVE THEM?
WAS IT GOOD TO SEE
YOUR AUNT GAYLE?
LIKE OLD TIMES.
I WAS ASKING THE GIRLS.
KELLY?
YEAH, I GUESS.
DO YOU EVER GO TO VISIT HER
IN CHICAGO AND SEE
YOUR COUSINS, CHRIS?
YEAH.
THEY CAME TO L.A. A FEW TIMES...
AND WE'D GO OUT FOR DINNER.
COME ON, CHRIS.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND
WHY SHE'S HERE, CHRIS?
DO YOU?
SHE DOESN'T WANT US
TO LIVE HERE ANYMORE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
SHE DOESN'T WANT YOU
TO STAY AT THE RANCH
FOR THE REST
OF THE SUMMER.
SHE WANTS TO TAKE YOU
TO CHICAGO RIGHT AWAY
AND THEN THAT'S
WHERE YOU'LL LIVE.
FOR GOOD?
FOR GOOD.
SHE CAN'T EVEN WAIT
UNTIL THE SUMMER'S OVER.
I DON'T THINK
IT'S IN HER NATURE
TO WAIT FOR ANYTHING
SHE WANTS.
THIS ISN'T GOOD FOR THEM.
AND IT'S WORSE FOR CHRIS.
IT'S HARD ENOUGH FOR HER
TO DEAL WITH HER MOTHER'S DEATH
WITHOUT BEING MOVED HALFWAY
ACROSS THE DAMN COUNTRY.
IS SHE GOING
TO COME OUT OF THIS?
YES.
WHEN?
WHEN SHE'S READY.
IF SHE DOESN'T
TALK ABOUT IT
THEN SHE FEELS
SHE'S PROTECTED
FROM IT SOMEHOW.
IT'LL LAST UNTIL
SOMETHING TRIGGERS
AN EMOTIONAL CATHARSIS
AND THEN EVERYTHING
WILL COME OUT.
IN THE MEANTIME...
IT WOULD HELP HER
IF YOU WERE
ABLE TO EXPRESS
YOUR OWN FEELINGS
A BIT BETTER.
FEELINGS ABOUT WHAT?
ABOUT JESSE...
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
WITH YOU AND THE GIRLS.
I'M NOT VERY
GOOD AT THAT.
I TRY, I GET ALL...
IT TAKES PRACTICE.
ARE THEY
STILL OUT THERE?
YEP.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
YOU EVER TALK
TO HIM ANYMORE?
NOT FOR YEARS.
I DON'T THINK
WE EVER TALKED.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHY WE GOT MARRIED.
I WAS YOUNG.
IT DIDN'T LAST LONG.
IT ENDED BADLY,
AND THAT'S THAT.
YOU SEEING ANYBODY NOW?
NO, NOT AT ALL.
SO WHY AREN'T YOU
SEEING ANYBODY?
YOU MEAN, WHY
AREN'T I DATING
OR WHY AREN'T I
IN A RELATIONSHIP?
BOTH.
I'M NOT DATING 'CAUSE
I DON'T HAVE THE TIME.
I CAN'T LEAVE MY JOB
AT THE OFFICE.
PEOPLE DON'T SUFFER
BETWEEN 9:00 AND 5:00.
NO, THEY DON'T.
AND I'M NOT IN A
RELATIONSHIP BECAUSE...
THE RELATIONSHIPS
I'VE BEEN IN
HAVEN'T WORKED FOR ME.
YOU HAVEN'T MET THE RIGHT MAN.
NO...
NOT YET.
AND IF YOU DID?
THEN I'D GO OUT
WITH HIM.
ON A DATE...
OR A RELATIONSHIP?
BOTH.
ANYMORE QUESTIONS?
YEAH.
DO YOU KNOW HOW TO DO
A FRENCH BRAID?
YEAH.
IT'S EASY. I'LL SHOW YOU.
TAKE THIS HAIR.
OKAY?
MAKE IT
THREE PIECES HERE.
WERE YOU ANY GOOD?
OH, I HAD A FEW GOOD YEARS.
YOUR DADDY WON RODEOS
IN HOUSTON AND CHEYENNE
AND PLENTY OF OTHER PLACES.
HE WAS A P.R.C.A. CHAMP
THREE YEARS IN A ROW.
WHAT'S P.R.C.A.?
PROFESSIONAL RODEO
COWBOY ASSOCIATION.
WHAT'S THAT FOR?
THIS IS A SCORE LINE--
GIVES THE CALF
A HEAD START.
I CAN'T LEAVE THE BOX
TILL THE CALVES CROSS THIS LINE.
IF I DO, I BREAK THAT BARRIER,
AND THAT'S A TEN-SECOND PENALTY.
THEN I MIGHT AS WELL PACK UP
AND HEAD HOME.
NOW THE CLOCK IS GOING TO START
WHEN I CROSS THAT BARRIER
AND IT STOPS
WHEN I THROW UP MY HANDS.
NOW...
EVER SEE A MAN GO FROM ZERO
TO 30 MILES PER HOUR
IN ONE SECOND?
HANG ON.
Charlie:
WHAT'S THE TIME?
8.2 SECONDS.
WELL, PACHECO'S A SMALL ARENA...
KIND OF LIKE POWAY.
I DID A 7.9 AT POWAY ONCE.
GOT TO DO A LOT BETTER
AT PACHECO.
WHAT'S PACHECO?
A RANCH HANDS' RODEO,
LOCAL COWBOYS.
YOUR DADDY DOES
WELL THERE
WE'RE GOING TO SIT DOWN
AND TALK BUSINESS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOUR DADDY'S
LOOKING FOR A SPONSOR.
A SPONSOR FOR WHAT?
GET BACK INTO
THE RODEO.
COSTS A LOT OF MONEY
TO LIVE ON THE ROAD THESE DAYS--
MOTELS,
RESTAURANTS.
GOT TO DRIVE YOUR
HORSE ACROSS COUNTRY
KEEP HIM FED
AND HEALTHY.
AND THE P.R.C.A. FEES
WELL, THEY
AIN'T CHEAP.
MUST BE $450 BY NOW.
AND THAT'SPERRODEO.
THEN THEY GOT DUES
ON TOP OF THAT.
YOU NEVER SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT GOING BACK TO THE RODEO.
KELLY!
THAT WAS
BEFORE YOU CAME HERE.
SO NOW WHAT?
WE GO ON THE ROAD?
WE LIVE IN MOTELS ALL YEAR LONG?
THIS IS MY LIFE.
IT'S WHAT I DO.
IT'S NOT JUST YOU ANYMORE!
WHAT IFIDON'T WANT
TO LIVE LIKE THAT?!
(frustrated scream)
MOM SURE DIDN'T.
Judge:
THERE ARE THREE WEEKS
UNTIL THE FINAL
CUSTODY HEARING.
YES, YOUR HONOR
BUT MRS. MILLER'S NIECES
ARE IN IMMEDIATE JEOPARDY
LIVING WITH MR. McCLAIN.
HOW SO?
HE WAS DRUNK IN A BAR,
STARTED A FIGHT
AND SPENT THE NIGHT IN JAIL,
YOUR HONOR.
Winston:
THE SCHOOL YEAR
STARTS IN A MONTH.
MR. McCLAIN HAS MADE
NO ARRANGEMENTS
WHATSOEVER
FOR THE GIRLS' EDUCATION.
HE HASN'T SPOKEN
TO A SINGLE TEACHER
HASN'T EVEN SHOWN
THE GIRLS
THE SCHOOL THEY'D
BE ATTENDING.
WHAT SCHOOL WOULD THEY
BE ATTENDING, MR. McCLAIN?
Miller:
I HAVE PREREGISTERED
THE GIRLS
IN THE FINEST PREP SCHOOL
IN ILLINOIS.
ORIENTATION IS THE FIRST WEEK
IN SEPTEMBER, YOUR HONOR.
THERE'S STILL PLENTY OF TIME
TO GET THE GIRLS
INTO THE BECKETT PUBLIC
SCHOOL SYSTEM, YOUR HONOR.
WHAT IS IT YOU AND MRS. MILLER
WANT, MR. WINSTON?
WELL, WE'D LIKE YOU
TO MAKE A RULING
ON THE CUSTODY ISSUE
NOW, YOUR HONOR.
THE RULING'S
ALREADY BEEN MADE.
OH, WE DON'T THINK IT'S WISE
TO WAIT THREE
MORE WEEKS.
MS. SHAW?
ALL MY REPORTS RECOMMEND
THAT MR. McCLAIN BE ALLOWED
TO FINISH THE SUMMER
WITH HIS DAUGHTERS.
THE GIRLS NEED A SECURE
AND STABLE HOME
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
MR. McCLAIN
HAS ALREADY SHOWN
HE'S NOT ABLE
TO PROVIDE THAT FOR THEM.
Susan:
HE IS A FIRST-TIME
SINGLE PARENT,
YOUR HONOR.
Winston:
MRS. MILLER IS READY, WILLING
AND ABLE TO STEP IN.
NO ONE HAS YET DETERMINED
THAT THAT WILL BE NECESSARY,
MR. WINSTON.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH.
I'LL GIVE YOU AN ANSWER
BY THE END OF THE DAY.
(mooing)
MORGAN SAID YOU CAN KEEP
THE GIRLS FOR THE SUMMER.
HE FELT IT WAS
TOO SHORT A TIME
TO WARRANT PULLING THEM AND
TO OVERRULE THE L.A. COURT.
BUT HE HAS SOME SERIOUS
CONSIDERATIONS
ABOUT THE GIRLS
AND ABOUT YOU.
YEAH, WELL...
JOIN THE CLUB.
IT'S NOT GOOD, MAC.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN TO YOU IN SEPTEMBER.
HE COULD GIVE THE GIRLS
TO GAYLE.
SO, UH, WHAT YOU'RE SAYING IS
IS THAT I REALLY ONLY HAVE
THREE WEEKS LEFT WITH THEM.
I'M SORRY.
THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE SORRY ABOUT.
I WOULDN'T HAVE GOTTEN
THIS FAR WITHOUT YOU.
YOU'RE UP EARLY
THIS MORNING.
YEAH.
THE COLT'S LOOKING
REAL GOOD.
YOU'VE DONE A GOOD JOB.
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK YOUR MAMA
WOULD BE PROUD OF YOU, TOO.
YOU KNOW, WHEN I ASKED
YOUR MOM TO MARRY ME...
I DIDN'T HAVE
A WHOLE LOT OF MONEY.
I COULDN'T BUY HER
ONE OF THOSE BIG DIAMONDS
OR ANYTHING.
BUT THERE WAS THIS INDIAN
AND HE HAD A LITTLE STORE
OVER IN MERCED.
IN THE WINDOW, HE HAD THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL TURQUOISE NECKLACE
YOU'VE EVER SEEN.
AND YOUR MOM
SAW IT ONE DAY.
SHE TOLD ME
HOW MUCH SHE LIKED IT.
SHE ASKED ME TO GET IT.
AND I DID.
SO I WENT BACK
AND I GOT IT FOR HER
AND I GAVE IT TO HER...
THE DAY I ASKED HER TO MARRY ME.
AND I WAS THINKING...
I THINK THIS NECKLACE
WOULD LOOK AS
BEAUTIFUL ON YOU
AS IT DID ON HER.
I WANT YOU TO HAVE IT.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
HONEY?
IT WAS SO DARK.
HE WAS IN THE SHADOWS.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I COULDN'T SEE HIS FACE.
I KNOW.
AND I KEEP LOOKING
TO SEE HIS FACE
BUT I NEVER CAN.
I-I NEVER CAN.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
I-I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT!
NO, IT'S NOT.
THERE WAS NOTHING
YOU COULD DO.
I DIDN'T SCREAM.
I DIDN'T RUN FOR HELP.
I JUST STOOD THERE.
OH, IT'S OKAY.
NO, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY.
DO YOU THINK HE'LL WIN?
IF HE DOES, I'M
GOING TO HAVE
TO FIND MYSELF
A NEW COWBOY.
I DON'T LIKE
WHEN THINGS CHANGE.
NOBODY DOES, HONEY.
BUT THEY CHANGE ANYWAY.
MM-HMM.
YOU GOT ALL THE PHONE NUMBERS
YOU NEED
RIGHT THERE ON THE COUNTER.
YOU SHOULDN'T GO.
DOTTY SAID
SHE'D MAKE YOU DINNER
BUT YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN
FOR BREAKFAST AND LUNCH.
CHRIS NEEDS YOU HERE.
SHE'LL BE FINE.
JUST MAKE SURE
THAT SHE FEEDS THE DOGS
AND LOOKS AFTER
THE COLT.
SHE'S ONLY TEN.
AND DON'T LET THE DISHES
PILE UP.
IT'S BEST IF YOU DO THEM
AS YOU GO ALONG.
WHAT IF SHE'S NOT FINE?
WELL, THEN YOU TAKE CARE OF HER.
I DON'T WANT
TO TAKE CARE OF HER.
I DON'T WANT TO BE HER MOTHER.
I'M A KID.
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE A KID!
KELLY, CALM DOWN, ALL RIGHT?
CALM DOWN.
YOU DON'T CARE ABOUT ME.
YOU ACT LIKE YOU CARE
BECAUSE YOUHAVETO.
YOU NEVER CARED.
YOU... NEVER....
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YES. YES, ITISTRUE.
DO YOU THINK
I'D BE LIVING HERE
IF MOM WAS STILL ALIVE?
YOU NEVER EVEN THOUGHT
ABOUT US AT ALL.
WHAT'S THAT?
LETTERS-- FOR YOU AND CHRIS.
"KELLY...
"I JUST SAW
YOUR THANKSGIVING PLAY
"AND WANTED TO TELL YOU
THAT YOU WERE
THE PRETTIEST PILGRIM
ON THE STAGE."
YOU WERE ABOUT EIGHT YEARS OLD.
I SAW THE SHOW;
I WATCHED THE WHOLE THING
FROM THE BACK.
YOU WORE A BLUE DRESS.
AND YOU SANG
"GOD BLESS AMERICA."
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE THERE.
YEAH, WELL...
THERE'S A LOT OF THINGS
YOU DON'T KNOW ABOUT.
WHY DIDN'T YOU EVER MAIL THESE?
I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D READ THEM.
NOW, YOU CAN SAY
WHATEVER YOU WANT ABOUT ME.
IT'S PROBABLY ALL TRUE.
BUT DON'T YOU SAY
I DIDN'T THINK ABOUT YOU.
There's little Davy Johnson.
Look at this guy.
Five years of age
and look at this clown--
He's got him.
And what a ride. There's Davy.
He completed his ride
in the opening
of the Mutton Busting.
Way to go, Davy!
The crowd loves you. You betcha.
GERALD SMITH.
WELL-KNOWN COWBOY
AROUND THESE PARTS.
HE'S DRAWN THUNDERBOLT.
Here he comes.
The chute's open,
and Thunderbolt comes up high.
Look at that.
Just keep hanging on, Gerald.
Eight seconds into the ride.
Hold on.
Here comes the side door.
I think he made it--
eight seconds.
There's the steer
and here comes Frankie.
Look at this. He's got him down.
Yes, and under five seconds.
And he's up next,
and here he comes.
The long rope is up.
He's got that little doggie.
Down he goes.
Now comes the roping...
Look at that.
He's under ten seconds.
That's official, folks.
Defending Champion Carl Collins
in 9.4.
OKAY, MAC, YOU'RE UP.
THE TIME TO BEAT IS 9.4.
TIME TO BEAT'S AN EIGHT.
Now, as you well know,
this is a big return
for Charlie.
He's fighting his way back
from injuries
for the past few years.
It's sure good
to see Mac's back.
This roping event
is usually the domain
of those young bucks.
READY, MAC?
Go get them, Charlie.
Hey, you've got him, cowboy.
Grab him up... looking good!
Yay!
Man:
7.9.
Charlie McClain's
comeback time, folks--
an amazing 7.9 seconds.
MAC IS BACK.
MAC IS BACK--
I LIKE THAT,
IT'S CATCHY.
HERE YOU GO.
HOW'S YOUR KNEE?
PRETTY GOOD.
THAT WAS A GOOD RUN, MAC.
IT WAS A DAMN GOOD RUN.
I'LL DROP BY
DOTTY'S THIS WEEK.
WE GOT BUSINESS
TO DISCUSS.
THAT A BOY.
CONGRATULATIONS.
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE HERE.
I DIDN'T WANT
TO MAKE YOU NERVOUS.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
MY SPONSOR WANTS ME TO
SIGN A CONTRACT THIS WEEK.
TELL ME SOMETHING.
WHAT KIND OF A FATHER
DO YOU THINK I AM?
I THINK YOU'RE A FATHER
WHO LOVES HIS DAUGHTERS
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
IS THAT ENOUGH?
WASN'T IT ENOUGH FOR YOU
WITH YOUR FATHER?
MY FATHER DIED
WHEN I WAS THREE.
I NEVER KNEW HIM.
I NEVER HAD A CHANCE
TO LEARN FROM HIM.
THEY WERE JUST BABIES.
I WAS AFRAID
I'D LET THEM DOWN.
I STILL FEEL THAT WAY.
I WOULD IMAGINE
IT'S THE MOST INTIMIDATING
THING THAT YOU'LL EVER DO
BUT...ITHINK...
YOU'VE GOT WHAT IT TAKES.
YOU THINK THERE'S ANY
CHANCE I'LL GET THEM?
I THINK IT'S A LONG SHOT.
I TALKED TO
MY ACCOUNTANT
AND WE'RE GETTING
THINGS ALL SET UP.
AFTER SALINAS, WE'RE GOING
TO SWING THROUGH NEVADA
THEN DOWN TO ARIZONA...
CROSS OVER
THROUGH NEW MEXICO
UP COLORADO
AND INTO WYOMING
AND THAT SHOULD BRING
US INTO THE FALL.
THEN WE'LL HAVE
A FEW WEEKS TO
DO SOME PROMOTION.
WE'LL START AT MY
PLACE IN MODESTO.
WE'LL MAKE IT A BIG DEAL, UH...
SIGN SOME AUTOGRAPHS.
WE'LL GIVE AWAY
SOME RODEO TICKETS AND...
MAC, ARE YOU WITH ME HERE?
I'VE CHANGED MY MIND, GEORGE.
YOU SAID IT WAS
A YOUNG MAN'S GAME ANYWAY.
I RECKON IT IS.
MAC...
THANKS.
THANK YOU.
GOOD LUCK.
SO WHEN DO YOU LEAVE?
I'M NOT.
I TURNED HIM DOWN.
BUT YOU WANTED
TO BE IN THE RODEO.
I THOUGHT I DID.
BUT THEN I REMEMBERED
HOW LONELY IT
GETS ON THE ROAD.
I'D BE COMING BACK
TO THAT HOUSE
AND IT'D BE DARK AND QUIET.
OF COURSE, IT'D BE CLEAN.
AND THERE WOULDN'T BE ANY
LAUNDRY LYING ON MY RECORDS.
BUT I'D ALWAYS BE WONDERING
WHERE MY GIRLS WERE AT.
I'D ALWAYS BE WONDERING.
YOU WANT TO BE WITH US?
WHAT'S THE MATTER, KELLY?
WHAT IF WE HAVE
TO GO WITH GAYLE?
(crying)
DADDY...
I-I PROMISE I WON'T
COMPLAIN ANYMORE.
(crying):
I'M S-SORRY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
IT'S OKAY.
I GOT IT FOR YOU, FOLKS.
THANK YOU.
THERE YOU GO.
HEY.
HOW YOU DOING?
WELL, I THINK
WE'VE BEEN BETTER, HUH?
YEAH.
FEEL READY?
KELLY.
CHRIS.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
CHARLIE.
HELLO.
LET'S GO.
YOUR HONOR, MY SISTER AND I
WERE VERY CLOSE.
I'VE KNOW KELLY
AND CHRIS SINCE
THEY WERE BORN.
IN MY CUSTODY,
THEY WOULD LIVE IN A STABLE
FINANCIALLY SECURE
FAMILY ENVIRONMENT.
MR. McCLAIN'S HISTORY
AS AN ABSENTEE FATHER
IS WELL-DOCUMENTED.
THAT'S NOT
THE QUESTION HERE.
THE QUESTION IS, WHAT IS
AT STAKE FOR THE GIRLS?
AND, YOUR HONOR
THEIR BEST INTEREST
IS HAVING THEM LIVE WITH ME.
THANK YOU.
I HAVE SERIOUS CONCERNS
ABOUT YOU, MR. McCLAIN.
YOU'VE BEING UNWILLING
TO CHANGE YOUR LIFE
FOR SO MANY YEARS,
HOW CAN I BE CERTAIN
THAT YOU'RE READY
TO CHANGE IT NOW?
GIRLS, DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING
YOU'D LIKE
TO SAY?
UM...
IT'S BEEN REALLY HARD FOR US
SINCE OUR MOM DIED...
AND...
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE WE KNEW OUR DAD.
AND IF WE GO BACK NOW...
I JUST THINK IT'D BE REALLY SAD.
THAT'S ALL.
DO YOU FEEL THE SAME WAY
AS YOUR SISTER?
MY FATHER LOVED THE RODEO
HIS ENTIRE LIFE.
HE HAD A CHANCE TO DO IT AGAIN.
UH, YOU DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
AND... HE TURNED IT DOWN.
HE DECIDED
THAT HE LOVED US MORE.
I WANT TO STAY WITH HIM
YOUR HONOR.
I REALLY WANT TO LIVE
WITH MY DAD.
MR. McCLAIN
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO SAY ANYTHING?
I'VE, UH, I'VE MADE
SOME MISTAKES, YOUR HONOR.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
BUT I KNOW WHAT I WANT NOW.
DO YOU?
YES, SIR.
THESE ARE MY GIRLS.
I'M THEIR FATHER.
WE'RE A FAMILY.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
AND I HAVE NEVER FELT THAT
MORE THAN I FEEL IT RIGHT NOW.
NOW, I'VE BEEN TOLD THAT, UH...
THEY NEED ME.
AND, UH...
I'LL BE THERE FOR THEM.
IT'S ALSO
THE OTHER WAY AROUND, TOO.
I NEED THEM.
SO, UH...
PLEASE...
PLEASE, YOUR HONOR...
LET ME BE THEIR FATHER.
MS. SHAW.
(clears throat)
YOUR OFFICE STAYS
IN CLOSE CONTACT WITH THESE
FAMILIES FOLLOWING DECISION?
YES, YOUR HONOR,
WE CERTAINLY DO.
OKAY.
MR. McCLAIN...
I HEREBY GRANT YOU
FULL AND FINAL CUSTODY
OF YOUR DAUGHTERS.
(laughs)
Kelly:
YES.
THANK YOU, SIR.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
THANK YOU.
(laughing)
YOU'RE WELCOME.
THANK YOU, SUSAN.
OH, YOU'RE
WELCOME.
THANK YOU, MS. SHAW.
THANK YOU.
I MAY NEED SOME HELP WITH
THESE TWO FROM TIME TO TIME
SOMEONE TO TALK TO.
I'D LIKE THAT.
OKAY.
COME ON.
LET'S GO HOME.
HOW ABOUT SATURDAY NIGHT?
SURE.
LET'S GO!
I'M GOING TO HAVE YOU TWO
RIDING AND ROPING BETTER THAN ME
WITHIN TWO WEEKS.
OH, YOU GOT IT!
YES!
(shrieking)
ARE YOU OKAY?