[music playing]
19.
Seen Joe?
Is he on tonight?
Supposed to be.
If he's on anotherbender, that's it for him.
Um, place your bets.
[knocking]
Joe?
It's me, Paula.
Come on, I need to talk to you.
[knocking]
You're being a real
jerk, you know that?
What is it about
this girl anyway?
Just forget about it.
Do us all a favor, OK?
Joe?
[phone beeps]
[ringing]
MAN: Evening, Joe.
Where am I?
Table eight.
PAULA: Eight's unlucky.
JOE: Table nine.
You know, I almost feel
sorry for him sometimes.
The world never runs
out of suckers, does it?
Hope not.
Them suckers are
making my car payments.
Mine too.
Joe's on the web.
What a shocker.
This Brazilian chick
wants to jump my bones.
How do you say, bring
it on, in Spanish.
It's Portuguese.
Sheldon's looking for you.
You were due back on the
floor 20 minutes ago.
Right, OK.
[computer beeps]
[non-english speech]
WOMAN: You know what?
David almost didn't let mecome out with you tonight
because he says you're
a bad influence.
That's because I
don't take any crap.
No.
Actually, it's because thelast time I went out with you,
I got like, totally trashed.
And then I was hung
over for almost a week.
[giggles]
You had fun
though, didn't you?
I want you.
Nobody cares, freak.
ANNOUNCER: There are 62
laps to go in this race
here at [inaudible] Speedwaywith the front runner, 27
car [inaudible] has
about a two second lead
over Wallace in number four.
You owe me a drink.
Go, pay up.
I know where you live.
NASCAR-- it's on
all the TVs in hell.
All they do is go round andround in circles, every day.
[laughs]
Did I ever tell youabout my Jeff Gordon dream?
Mm-mm.
[gasps]
It's the day
before our wedding.
He's in this really bad
crash-- car flips over,
pieces go flying off, everybodyis like, oh my god, is he dead?
But just then,
through the smoke,
I see somebody climbing
out, and it's him.
Takes his helmet off, and he isfine, just a little banged up.
It was so sexy.
Honey, you need help.
Tell me about it.
[SINGING] I just
want you to know--
[inaudible] he's gone, baby.
Let him go.
[chuckles]
Come on, you and me.
I might need
another drink first.
[MUSIC - JOAN JETT
& THE BLACKHEARTS,
"DO YOU WANT TO TOUCH ME"]
[SINGING] We've
been here too long
trying to get along, pretendingthat you're oh so shy.
Shy, shy.
I'm a natural man,
doing what I can.
My temperature is running high.
Running high.
Friday night, no one in sight,and we got so much to share.
WOMAN: Share, share.
Talking's fine if
you got the time,
but I ain't got
the time to spare.
Yeah, do you want to touch--
ALL: Yeah.
- Do you want to touch--
We should go to Las
Vegas this summer,
rent a fancy hotel room, goout gambling every night.
Wouldn't that be awesome?
Well, there's one problem.
What's that?
I'm married, Tanya,and so are you, remember?
Yeah, I remember.
Thank you.
Good night.
Mama?
You're supposed to be asleep.
I have a big test tomorrow.
Mr. Gillis always putsin these trick questions.
I hate him.
You'll do fine.
Where do you go with Cindy?
No place special.
Basically, we just go outand make fools of ourselves
in front of total strangers.
Why?
[sighs]
Because being an adult
is boring sometimes.
How come Dad never goes?
Because he has his
friends and I have mine.
Sleep.
[crickets chirping]
[ominous music playing]
[door creaking]
[snoring]
[door creaks]
[typing]
[interposing voices whispering]
MAN: Want to talk sex?
WOMAN: Tanya, did
you get my message?
WOMAN: Anyone in Boston wantto have a threesome tonight?
WOMAN: You slut.
What time?
MAN: Hey, sexy mama.
You want some?
WOMAN: I don't know
if I trust my husband.
What should I do?
TANYA [VOICEOVER]: Have agirlfriend make a pass at him
sometime when you're not there.
If he turns her down, youknow you can trust him.
[computer beeps]
PAULA: I reached a personalmilestone the other day.
Huh?
Twelve month, no sex.
Yeah, calendar year.
I register my car more oftenthan I sleep with a guy.
What you need is a computer.
What I need is a man beastwith a cabin on a lake and time
to burn.
[inaudible] get acomputer, get a man beast--
plug in, baby.
Singles bar, the newMillennium, the internet--
Where'd you read that?
Eh, some magazine.
[chuckles]
Watch your fingers.
I don't even want to knowwhat you're up to online.
No, you don't.
Believe me.
[indistinct whispering voices]
WOMAN: Should I go to Vegasor Atlantic City for vacation?
Atlantic City, definitely.
WOMAN: Do you know any
good places to stay?
Golden Treasure Casino.
You'll like it.
WOMAN: You've been there?
I am part owner.
WOMAN: Wow, you must be rich.
I do OK.
WOMAN: Thanks for the help.
Wow, you're
welcome, sexy kitten.
What are you doing?
Nothing, just--
you're up early.
Dallas won.
What was the score?
20-14.
Well, we're $50 richer.
That's not bad, is it?
Can we move back
to Rhode Island?
Danny--
It's better there.
I can't.
Why not?
Danny, we've been over this.
My job's here.
I'm stuck.
You can go back and
live with your mom,
if you want to, if that'swhat you want to do.
You're not stuck,
you just like it here.
Sexy kitten.
Where are you from?
WOMAN: Pittsburgh.
JOE: What do you look like?
Describe yourself.
WOMAN: Blonde,
petite, nice body.
[keyboard clattering]
You?
JOE: 6 feet, athletic, handsome.
And hung like a
workhorse, right?
How old are you?
TANYA: 27.
27, blonde, petite--
mm, come to papa.
TANYA [VOICEOVER]:
How old are you?
Hmm--
40.
TANYA [VOICEOVER]:
Maybe I'll look you up
when I come to Atlantic City.
JOE [VOICEOVER]:
Maybe you should.
Are you as hot as you sound?
TANYA [VOICEOVER]:
Hot and horny.
JOE [VOICEOVER]: Picture please.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
[VOICEOVER] Are you a pervert?
[laughs]
Definitely.
Mom, will you dry my hairlike Christina Aguilera?
Uh, plug in the dryer.
I'll be there in a minute.
What's your real name?
Joe.
TANYA: Good talking to you, Joe.
I'm Tanya.
Email me sometime.
You seem nice.
That's it?
What happened to hot and horny?
You email me, I'll reply.
OK, I just did.
[notification dinging]
Ha-ya-ya.
Yeah--
[drill whirring]
[computer beeps]
JOE: I got your
picture last night.
Is that really you?
[computer dings]
You were on that damncomputer again, weren't you?
[singing]
Hey, Mark.
Hey, Joe.
Your numbers come up onlucky seven or something?
What is it?
I met someone.
PAULA: That's great, Joe.
Good for you.
Where'd you meet her?
Online.
Oh, say strip club.
Please say strip club.
Online-- Joe, come on.
I know, I know.
But this is different.
Been e-mailing back andforth a couple of weeks now.
You know how when youjust click with somebody?
She's smart.
She's funny-- looks
like a supermodel,
not that that matters.
Before you go all in on thisgirl, will you do me a favor?
Meet her in person first.
I'm not stupid.
JOE: I can't keep doing this.
I need to meet you.
I need to know you're real.
TANYA: Soon, Joe.
Be patient.
JOE [VOICEOVER]: You
keep saying that.
I'm tired of being patient.
I'm not waiting anymore.
TANYA: What's that
supposed to mean?
JOE [VOICEOVER]: It
means no more email
until I meet you face to face.
[beeps]
[plane engine roaring]
[slot machines chirping]
Excuse me, Joe Donnelly?
One in the gold tie.
Looks fun.
It is.
Jump on in there.
Don't know how.
21 wins.
You want it as close asyou can without going over.
House hits anything under 17.
That includes a soft seven--
Oh my god.
Hi.
And I'm standing hereexplaining the damn rules.
I know.
I'm thinking, um, Joe, it's me.
What are you doing here?
You said you needed to see me.
See?
I'm real, Joe.
Are you ever.
How do you do?
Don't know what to say.
I didn't think you'd come.
[sighs]
I'm married.
OK.
Are you happy?
I'm sitting in a coffee
shop in Atlantic City
with a man I met online.
Take a wild guess.
And I have a daughter, Molly.
She's cute.
Thanks.
If this changes things
for you, I understand.
And I won't think any
less of you, I swear.
I just didn't want to
start this out on a lie.
I wanted you to knowwhat you're getting into.
OK.
Tell me.
Did I scare you away?
I'm still sitting
here, aren't I?
Turn your head to the side.
I want to see.
Do you know who
you remind me of?
Don't laugh-- Steve McQueen.
[chuckles]
Yeah, if your hair were shorter.
Who do I look like?
Let me see--
you look like a cross
between Michelle
Pfeiffer and Melanie Griffith.
[giggles]
Wow.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking you're verybrave for coming here.
I hope you're not disappointed.
Not in the least.
Now what?
You tell me.
Take me upstairs.
You all right?
I've never cheated
on anybody before--
makes me feel weird.
Do you think I'm a slut?
Hell no.
If he was taking care of yourheart, you wouldn't be here.
[sighs]
Look at you.
You are an angel.
Oh, I'm not an angel.
I'm a brat.
So how long have you
owned the casino?
Oh, casino--
Mm-hm.
Well, I don't
actually own the place.
I'm a pit boss.
I work here.
But you said--
I was building myself
up for fun, you know?
I never really thought
we'd meet, especially--
You're not rich?
Oh no, ma'am.
Let's say this is bankruptcy.
Well, that's me right there,teetering on the brink.
[scoffs]
Guess this changes
things for you, huh?
What the hell do you think?
I just made the worst
mistake of my life.
I never want to hear
from you again, ever.
Understand?
OK.
I never came here.
Whatever you say.
[giggles]
Gotcha.
JOE: So I don't know whatyou want to see first.
There's a bar over thereplays pretty good country
Western, if you like country.
TANYA: Were you a cop?
How'd you know that?
The way you carry yourself.
Most guys are all slouchedover when they walk.
Not you-- you--
shoulders back, chin
up, in control--
definitely law enforcement.
Yeah.
Something happened?
Could say that.
You want to talk about it?
Not really.
[horn blaring]
It's a crosswalk,
you frigging idiot.
What?
He almost hit us.
It's not that.
It's just-- it's exactly likesomething I would have said.
I was a detective, theCounty Sheriff's Department
outside of Providence.
There is a high profilemurder they couldn't solve.
Sheriff tried to
pin it on some guy.
I wouldn't go along
with it, so I got fired.
Case went to grand jury.
Sheriff was a crook,
just like I said.
They threw his
ass out of office.
Did you get your job back?
No.
But you were right.
I testified against thedepartment-- cardinal sin.
Nobody would hire me after that.
Hell, you must think I'm a fool.
My fool.
Molly-- that's my main
job, taking care of her.
And I do wholesale
cosmetics on the side.
Somebody needs to graze
this guy with a bullet.
Wholesale cosmetics--
how's that work?
Is that one of those
pyramid schemes?
I just do house parties.
It's pretty basic.
Whatever you sell, you get yourshare, the company gets theirs.
[crowd booing]
I'm going to do one for you.
You sing?
[MUSIC - JOAN JETT & THE
BLACKHEARTS, "DO
YOU WANNA TOUCH ME"]
[SINGING] We've been heretoo long trying to get along,
pretending that
you're oh-so shy.
I'm a natural man,
doing what I can.
My temperature is running high.
Friday night, no one in sightand we got so much to share.
Talking's fine if
you got the time,
but I ain't got the
time to spare, yeah.
Do you wanna touch--
CROWD: Yeah.
TANYA: Do you wanna touch--
Do you wanna touch me there?
CROWD: Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
[cheering]
[car alarm blaring]
[slot machines whirring]
Thank you.
And have a good night.
Paula, I want to meet someone.
This is Tanya, the
love of my life.
Nice to meet you.
Joe's bee on cloud
nine since he met you.
So what are you two up to?
Joe's been showing me around.
Well, make sure he
takes you to the beach.
It's really nice.
Add that to the list.
As much as I love thisplace, we have to move on.
Oh, will you tellSheldon I'm going to want
a personal day tomorrow?
- Sure.
Thanks.
Hey, Teddy.
It's Daddy.
Everything all right?
TEDDY: Where are you?
I thought you had tonight off.
I'm not drinking,
I promise, OK?
I'm just out with someone?
Who is she?
Listen, I just called to sayif I'm late, do not worry, OK?
You're already late.
Look, I'll see
you in the morning.
He's good.
[phone dial tone]
You know, sometimes I
look around the casino--
all these people, theycouldn't have less in common.
But for some reason, they
end up in the same place
on the same night doing
the exact same thing.
Sounds like my honeymoon.
[chuckles]
I'm an alcoholic.
You don't seem like it.
You seem so in control.
I am, now.
That's after I got blackballedfrom the department.
I hit a bad batch--
alcohol, pills.
Took me right down.
Thank you for telling me.
You're welcome.
It feels so good, mm.
So how long have
you been divorced,
and why didn't you tell me?
You don't miss much, do you?
You had a song.
He had to come from somewhere.
I've been divorced
about five months,
but it was over way
before it started.
Susan, my ex, you'd like her.
She got me through
some really hard times.
And you thanked
her by leaving?
I didn't love her anymore.
I am not a good liar.
How is he handling
it, your son?
The divorce?
Mm-hm.
OK, I guess.
He misses his mom.
He doesn't want me
living by myself.
He sounds sweet.
He is.
I want you to meet him.
I was thinking maybe we couldhave breakfast together.
That's not going to work.
Why?
My flight leaves in an hour.
OK.
Can't you call and
say your flight
got canceled or something?
I can't, Joe.
I told Molly.
Please, one more day.
One more day, for me.
Joe, don't ever
ask me to choose
between you and my daughter.
You'll lose.
OK.
[clears throat]
So when am I going
to see you again?
Soon as I can get away.
Don't worry, I'm
coming back, I promise.
I know this hasn't
been easy for you.
You know what happened
to mom and me.
We're going to be all right.
You are the best thingthat ever happened to me.
I know I don't alwaysact like it, but you are.
And that was a hell of
a catch [inaudible]..
Who taught you that?
My little man, my little man--
PAULA: She seems nice.
She's married.
Kids?
A daughter.
Internet romance
with a married woman--
what could go wrong?
JOE [VOICEOVER]: I try and tryto stop thinking about you,
but it's hopeless.
I adore you like
no one before you.
I will never let
you go, I swear.
Your fool, Joe.
TANYA: There you are in
the early light of day.
There you are in the
quiet words, I pray.
I've been blessed by the simplehappiness of the perfect love
we have made.
Every time I turn around, whenI am lost and when I am found,
like an angel standing
guard, there you are.
There you are standing
in a crowded room.
There you are, theEarth, and I am the moon.
My desire is to stand by thefire that burns inside you.
Your fool, Tanya.
[slot machines whirring]
What do you think?
I don't know.
I'm going to watch
a few more hands.
Call for you.
Not now.
Someone named Tanya.
Is this Joe
Donnelly, the man I
keep having dirty dreams about?
I don't know.
Can you describe those dreams?
So what did you think?
JOE: Think about what?
You forgot already?
The video, you fool.
Let me tell you something,I will never, long as I live,
forget that video.
Blew my mind.
I'm not even going to tell youhow many times I watched it.
Well, how about the realthing again next Saturday night.
JOE: You coming back?
TANYA: Told you I would.
Oh, man.
I can't wait.
[knocking]
WOMAN: Hey, Tanya.
Listen, I gotta go.
My flight gets in at
2:15 in [inaudible]..
There's something we need totalk about when I get there.
Sounds serious.
Kind of.
I love you, hun.
Love you too.
[phone beeps]
Hey, Molly.
Hi.
Hey, I'm a little freaked out.
David wants me to
get a Wonderbra.
[chuckles]
What did you do?
What?
Nothing.
Don't what nothing me.
I know that look.
Either you've done somethingyou shouldn't have,
or you're going to.
I think I'm having an affairwith a guy I met online.
You think?
I am.
He lives in Atlantic City.
That's why I went there.
[laughs]
Uh, you slept with him?
Don't lie.
I knew I should
have gone with you.
I'm going back next weekend.
Can you take care
of Molly for me?
Tanny, what if Mark
finds out about this?
I just have to
make sure he doesn't.
ANNOUNCER: Flight
109 from Pittsburgh
arriving now on concourse 5.
Passengers arriving fromPittsburgh on concourse 5.
Passengers with connectingflights to Georgetown, please
go immediately to gate four.
Don't screw this up.
ANNOUNCER: Flight 234 toLondon now boarding gate 17.
Flight 234 to London
now boarding gate 17.
I missed you.
Let me look.
[scoffs]
Lord, am I in trouble.
[giggles]
I almost didn't make it.
I got to the airport
and chickened out.
What are we doing, Joe?
[shuts engine off]
Promise you won't be mad?
I won't.
What is it?
It's mine, isn't it?
Are you mad?
Well, this is probablythe happiest day of my life.
I'm not joking around
this time, Tanny.
Let's get married.
Joe--
This is big.
We're having a baby.
I know it's big.
Why not?
You know why not.
So divorce him.
It's not that simple.
Sure it is.
- No, it's not.
- Sure it is.
- It's not.
- Hun--
It's not.
[thunder bellowing]
You don't understand.
Explain it to me then.
The guy I'm married
to, he's not--
I don't even know his name.
What's his name.
Mark.
He's not like you, OK?
I don't trust what he woulddo to me if he found out.
I don't trust what
he would do to you.
What do you mean?
What's he going to do?
Never mind.
What's he going to do, Tanya?
I don't want to
talk about this.
- I do.
- I don't.
I just think about himthe whole time I'm there.
When I'm here, all I want to dois think about you, you and me.
If we can't do that, I mightas well be back in Pittsburgh.
It's just temporary until Ican find something, you know,
better.
Hold on a second.
I'll see if he's here.
Teddy?
Oh, I love thinkingabout you sitting here, sun
coming in right [inaudible].
Teddy?
This is Teddy.
This is Tanya, friend of mine.
What a handsome
young man you are.
Catch.
[laughs]
So what's he do for a living?
Come on, I'm just asking.
I don't know.
All I know about is BDNH.
BDNH.
BDNH Auto, the
salvage yard he owns.
That's how I met him.
They needed someone
to handle their books.
The rest of his life-- yourguess is as good as mine.
These guys come over
to the house sometimes,
these creepy lookingguys in expensive suits--
he won't even talk
to them in the house.
Or he'll get a
phone call, say he's
going to some NASCAR race--disappear for a few days.
When he comes
home, I find clumps
of money in his coat pocket.
I counted it once--
$10,000, Joe, in two days.
He didn't make it doingbrake jobs, I know that much.
He could be
involved in some kind
of organized crime, you know?
Drugs, racketeering,
something like that.
Pass himself off as thisregular guy, you know?
I had no idea who
I was marrying.
Sometimes I think the
only reason he married
me is because he worried when Ilooked at the website, figured
out something was going on.
Can I use your phone?
- What?
I have to book a
room for the night.
You're staying here.
I'm not having you in a hotel.
It's too soon.
Think about him.
What do you think he's
going to feel, seeing
another woman in his mom's bed?
Susan never slept here.
You know what I mean.
That's OK.
You can stay, if you want.
Are you sure, hun?
Because I don't mind a hotel.
Yeah, you make my dad happy.
Oh--
Oh.
[laughing]
Oh, was I too loud?
I don't think so,
but it's all right.
It's all right.
[laughing]
God.
Oh, baby.
Oh my god, what--
what-- what happened?
Oh, oh-- it's OK.
It's not real.
It just-- it clips in.
Oh, does that gross you out?
No, it freaked me out.
It's OK.
[sighs]
So what'd you say toMark to let you get away?
Oh, I told him that wehad some sales conference
to go to that uh, we werecoming out with a new line
of smudge free lip gloss.
Not the brightest
bulb on the tree, is he?
Oh, don't be jealous.
You're the one I love.
Besides, you're
bigger than he is.
Oh, you mean George.
- George?
- George.
Why George?
- Because he's curious.
- Oh.
[giggles]
Do you want it to
be a boy or a girl.
I don't care.
Either way, it makes me happy.
Here's what we do
after the divorce.
We bring Molly out.
We have a baby.
We buy a house.
You put in a pool.
We'll be a family.
How does that sound?
Before we make
any more plans, I
have to tell you what happened.
What?
I was six or seven
when it started,
13 when it finally stopped.
Whole time it was happening,you know what I thought?
I thought it was love.
I thought he loved me.
He kept telling me
how special I was.
That's why I told
on him, because he
started um, paying attention tosomebody else, some other girl.
I felt like I wasn't
special no more.
Like I was nothing.
I'm damaged.
Do you still want me?
[slot machines whirring]
Paula, I'm having Joe's baby.
Is this a congratulationsmoment, or an oh dear?
Well, both, I guess.
You know I'm married.
Yeah, Joe told me.
Divorce court, here I come.
You know, there's
not a lot of pretense.
But Joe, he's pretty wide open.
It just wouldn't take muchto hurt him, you know?
Oh, you have feelings
for him, don't you?
Who said that?
Don't worry.
I'll be careful with him.
What are they doing in there?
Beautification.
I've never had aprofessional makeup job before.
I usually just slap it on.
Oh my god.
Know what I'm thinking about?
What?
All the hearts
you're going to break.
Ta-da.
TEDDY: Woah.
It's a bit over the top?
No, no, you look great.
Yeah?
Uh, hello, over here.
Come on.
TEDDY: Looking good, Paula.
How's the pizza?
TEDDY: It's good.
[sniffling]
What's wrong, baby?
I'm lying to myself,
and I'm lying to you.
[inaudible]
Mark isn't going to let me go.
He'll put-- he'll put
me in the hospital
again if I ask
him for a divorce.
He beat you up?
Why didn't you tell me?
[inaudible]
something I'm proud of.
I saw my mother stuck in
an abusive relationship.
I swore it would never be me.
I thought she was weak
for staying with him.
How often does he hit you?
Oh, as often as
I make him mad.
I don't argue with him anymore.
I just give him what he
wants when he wants it.
Anything he wants?
Are you still sleeping with him?
Do you have any
idea what would happen
if I started denying him sex?
How do you know it's my baby?
Because Mark got fixed
after we had Molly.
When's the last time
you slept with him.
When?
Two days before I left.
Two days.
Straight sex or kinky stuff?
Oh, what?
Oh, now you're mad at me too?
Well, that's just what
I need, another man
who thinks he owns me.
Go to hell, both of you.
[car door opens]
Boy, I tell you,
when that Tanya leaves,
that girl is gone.
Come here, baby.
Oh, baby, I'm sorry.
It's OK.
I get jealous, OK.
I'm a jerk.
I lay in bed with
him some nights and--
if his heart would
stop beating--
I wish he'd die.
I even had a dream
about it once.
It was awful.
It was just a dream.
It doesn't mean anything.
I know.
But then in the
morning when I woke up,
I wanted it to be real.
Honey, killing
never solved anything.
Talking is always
the better way.
There are some people
you can't talk to.
I know.
He ever lays a hand on youagain, you take pictures, OK?
OK?
Come on, you're shivering.
Come on.
Let's get you home.
[heartbeat]
[clears throat]
[computer beeps]
[sighs]
MARK: You've been
having sex with my wife.
Now she's growing fat
with a bastard in her--
not for long.
I have heard that the loss ofa baby can make people crazy.
[laughing]
You think maybe she mightneed some help afterwards?
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Um, just a sec.
Mom?
Phone.
Who is it?
Hello?
JOE: It's me.
Just a sec.
Take this downstairs.
Thanks, hun.
Joe, I told you, you
can't call me here.
Look, I just got an
email from your husband.
He knows about the baby.
TANYA: What?
That's impossible.
Yeah, well, he knows.
And he says you're
going to lose it.
He said that?
Wha-- what should I do?
Put him on the phone.
Let me talk to him.
TANYA: Are you crazy?
Put him on the phone, Tanya.
No.
Then I'm coming to Pittsburgh.
Joe, stop.
If you come here, you'regoing to make things worse.
Let me handle this, please.
I'll call you later, OK?
OK?
- You can't.
I'm working tonight.
I'll call you at the
casino, 10 o'clock.
[phone beeps]
[slot machines whirring]
Any calls for me?
No calls.
You sure?
[phone dialing]
MARK: Hello?
Who is this?
I said who is this?
Bring it on.
Somebody just stole $100 worthof chips from [inaudible]
from that table.
- Busy night, sorry.
- Busy night?
- Hey, it happens.
It's a casino.
You should be more careful.
Roll the tape back
and see who it was.
There's a camera
over every table.
Back off, guy, all right?
I know how this works, man.
It will only take
you two minutes.
I want to know [inaudible].
[coughs]
No.
[grunting]
MAN: Come on, get
his arm [inaudible]..
[police radio chatter]
JOE: Thanks for
taking care of Teddy.
- You want to talk about it?- Not really.
Then I'll talk
and you can listen.
I don't want a lecture, Paula.
You know, I just shelledout $1,500 so you could
sleep in your own bed tonight?
Think that entitles me to acouple of minutes of your time?
What are you now, my sponsor?
You know, maybe a
sponsor's what you need.
Look at me, Joe.
At least show me that courtesy.
Look, friend to friend,
I got to tell you.
This thing you've got
going on with Tanya--
- Tanya.
It doesn't take a genius toquestion the wisdom of it.
She's there.
You're here.
She's married with a kid.
You just got divorced.
Look what it's
doing to you, Joe.
I love her.
Love someone else.
I mean, she's a sweet
girl, I admit it.
But there are other
women out there.
Like who?
Like anyone, like me.
I'll pay you back the money.
Get it-- right-- uh-huh.
It's cool.
When there's a theft, they'resupposed to check the tapes.
That's policy.
Check on the tapes.
Nothing's ever your fault.
[computer chimes]
MARK: It was you that calledthe other night, wasn't it?
You were too scared
to say anything.
You're a damn coward.
[laughing]
You know, I can't believe mywife slept with such a loser.
Thank you for making myrelationship with my wife
better.
We're on the mends,
and it's thanks to you.
Mark.
[phone dialing]
[ringing]
TANYA: There's nobody
here right now.
Leave your name and numberand we'll call you back.
[voicemail beeps]
[computer chimes]
[computer beeps]
JOE [VOICEOVER]:
Where have you been?
TANYA: The hospital.
JOE [VOICEOVER]: What did he do?
TANYA: I told you the
kind of man he was.
JOE [VOICEOVER]: He beat you up?
TANYA: Yes.
JOE [VOICEOVER]: Did you takepictures like I told you?
TANYA: Yes, Joe.
JOE [VOICEOVER]:
Send them to me.
TANYA [VOICEOVER]: No, Idon't want you to see them.
JOE [VOICEOVER]:
Send them to me.
Do it now.
[computer chimes]
Tell me what happened.
TANYA [VOICEOVER]: I
was in the kitchen.
I didn't hear them come in.
[screaming]
They took me out
back by the pool.
[screaming]
They raped me, Joe.
Mark just stood
there and watched.
Where's your
damn boyfriend now?
Where's your damn boyfriend now?
[screaming]
I lost the baby.
No.
[screaming]
[inaudible] what
do I-- what do--
what-- what-- what am I doing?
What am I doing?
God--
I'm coming there.
Don't say no.
I'm coming.
I'll take care of him.
He's never going
to touch you again.
[gun cocking]
TANYA: I'm sorry.
I swear, he will pay for this.
Just give me time.
He will pay.
WOMAN: No, I never should havegotten you into this mess.
Just let me go, please.
JOE [VOICEOVER]: I can't.
He's going to get
what he deserves.
You're right.
He needs to be in hell.
TANYA: Are you sure?
JOE [VOICEOVER]: I have neverbeen so sure about anything.
What's the fastest way to thejunkyard from interstate 76?
TANYA: Take route 76 tothe [inaudible] Road exit.
Take it down to Shannon Street.
JOE [VOICEOVER]: Not
the Holton road exit?
It's closer to the yard.
TANYA: Holton's lit up-- alot of cops out at night.
Take Shannon DeGrant, go left,and then bear left at the fork.
And you'll see BDNH up ahead.
Joe, I'm scared.
JOE: Me too.
TANYA: If this doesn'twork, he's going to kill me.
JOE: It'll work.
When you leave here tomorrow,you will never see him again.
TANYA: Don't look at him.
Don't talk to him.
Just do it and get
the hell out of there.
JOE [VOICEOVER]: Oh, I'llhave to speak to him.
TANYA: Why?
JOE [VOICEOVER]: I want
him to know who I am.
[ominous music playing]
[indistinct voice]
MARK: [inaudible].
That's what confused me.
Called over here the
day before yesterday.
Said he was looking for anengine block for an Impala.
I said to him, at least
[inaudible] in crisis.
The hell's going on with
the Chevy [inaudible]..
[chuckle] I knew
it wasn't right.
Yeah, OK, man.
Sounds good.
All right, take care.
[phone beeps]
Mark?
I'm Joe.
[gun fires]
[ominous piano music plays]
[music on radio playing]
[inaudible] another one.
Where's Mark at tonight?
Out with the guys, I guess.
How is your friend?
Oh, didn't I tell you?
We decided to stop?
Yeah, a few weeks ago.
What happened?
I woke up.
Took me a while.
But when it came
right down to it,
I realized Mark
is the one I love.
I mean, every relationshiphas its problems
you got to work through them.
So the answer is you
run away every time,
you're going to be runningaway the rest of your life.
You are so smart
about relationships.
You should write a book.
Yeah, maybe I will.
I'm serious.
[sharp knocking at the door]
Could you get that?
Yeah.
MAN: Tanya Sullivan?
CINDY: Yes?
No, I mean, I'm--
I'm her friend.
This is her house.
Come in.
Tanya?
Who is it?
CINDY: The police.
Mrs. Sullivan?
Yes?
Is there somewhere
we can talk in private?
TANYA: It's my best friend.She can hear.
What is it?
What's--
There was an
incident this evening,
ma'am, involving your husband.
What incident?
What ha-- is he all right?
A shooting, ma'am.
I'm afraid he's been killed.
[gasps]
Why don't we all sit down.
This is a difficult situation.
Who did it?
Do you know who did it?
We don't know anything yet.
Um, it looks like
a botched robbery.
There's been a few break
ins out in that area.
What am I going to do?
[sobbing]
What am-- what am I--
going to tell my baby?
[sobbing]
[phone ringing]
He was always
very [inaudible]..
[phone ringing]
WOMAN: Doing OK?
Hello?
JOE: Hey.
Joe, you-- you can't
be calling me here.
My god, you said so yourself.
I know, but I
wanted to talk to you.
TANYA: Not now.
People are here.
God, if you had any idea.
JOE: When?
Everything's
died down a little.
I'll call you.
Let me call.
I love you.
I love you too.
[phone beeps]
[keys clatter]
JOE [VOICEOVER]: Are you OK?
It's been two weeks.
I haven't heard from you.
I'm starting to worry.
Are you there?
[computer beeps]
I love you.
Tell me you're OK.
[computer beeps]
[keys clatter]
Where are you?
Why aren't you answering me?
[computer beeps]
Right here?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Um, sorry to
intrude, Mrs. Sullivan.
Do you have a minute?
So much for doing this.
I know it's a difficult time.
I want to say, first
of all, that um, again,
how sorry we are for your loss.
Oh.
There's just a
couple of questions.
Um, did Mark have anyenemies that you're aware of?
Anyone who might wish him harm?
I thought you said
it was a robbery?
Well, that's what
it looks like, yes.
But we don't want
to miss anything.
Well, I--
I can't think of no one who'd--
Ma'am?
I don't want to accuse
nobody of nothing.
Mark deserves the most
thorough investigation
we can give him.
Well, there was this guy whoused to work out at the yard.
He was messing with
the VINs or something.
Mark fired him.
This was when?
Six, seven months ago.
But I don't think he
would've done nothing.
Do you remember a name?
Sam.
Sam Pooler.
OK.
Thank you for your help.
Um, you take care, OK?
If uh, if you need anything, youjust give us a call, all right?
[soft guitar music playing]
WOMAN: [SINGING] If
you see him, would
you kiss him for this queen?
I always was in love
with him, though I
never said a single thing.
Step out of the vehicle, sir.
PAULA: Susan called.
She asked me to put
Teddy on a plate.
That's not going to happen.
Well, I already dropped
him off on the way over.
What?
Where?
The airport.
Paula, give me your car keys.
His flight leaves
in 20 minutes.
Give me your car keys now.
Paula--
[engine turns over]
Excuse me.
ANNOUNCER: Last call
to flight [inaudible]..
Teddy?
What the hell is this?
Let's go home?
No.
What's going on?
I'm going to Rhode
Island to live with Mom.
You don't have to do that.
I want to.
[somber music playing]
I love you.
I love you too.
You going to be OK?
Just eat.
Be right back.
[lock clicks]
What are you doing?
Would you believe
quail hunting?
Look, I'm worried
about you, all right?
You think I'm going touse one of those on myself?
[inaudible].
Just that you put somebodyin a desperate situation,
you take away their
support system,
you add alcohol to the mix, anotherwise sensible person could
end up doing something stupid.
Those aren't going anywhere.
Yes, they are.
I'm taking them.
[door closes]
And you're all set.
Singles by the new
Millennium, huh?
Another sex starved
female coming at you?
Do's and don'ts?
Don't believe a
word anyone says.
Paula, if anything
happens to me,
I put all my things in order.
They're in a briefcase
under my bed.
[VOICEOVER] My worst
fears came true.
I gave you my life, putall I have in your hands.
I asked you to marry
me and you said yes.
And now you ignore me.
So I'm taking control of
my life one last time.
I will arrive in Pittsburghtomorrow morning at 8:30 AM.
I saw a park coming out of town.
I will wait for you there.
I'm asking you to meet meso we can talk face to face
and come to a
decision as to what
we're going to do from thispoint on, together or separate.
So I guess we'll see nowwhere I rate in your life
and in your heart.
I am still and foreverwill be your fool for life.
Hey.
How you doing?
Good.
Hey, a girl named TanyaSullivan ever come in here?
Tanya?
Yeah, all the time.
You a cop?
- Me?
No.
Nice girl?
Nice ain't the first
word comes to mind.
What is?
Willing.
[knocking]
Hi.
My girlfriend and I lostour baby a few weeks ago.
I wondered if I could speak withthe doctor that treated her.
What's the patient's name?
Tanya Sullivan.
[phone ringing]
Are you sure this
is her hospital?
Well, I have the
sonogram from here.
That's us-- hmm, weird.
[computer beeps]
Sir, this is 10 years old.
Excuse me?
10 years ago.
See?
Can I, uh--
can um-- can I have that back?
Thank you.
TANYA: They raped me, Joe.
They took me out
back by the pool.
[knocking]
Who are you?
Who is he?
You know this guy?
You bet your ass she knows me.
Tell him, Tanya.
Tell him who I am.
Go upstairs.
I'll be there in a minute.
Who is he?
Will you calm down?
My boyfriend, OK?
Happy now?
And what am I?
Go home, Joe.
This is 10 years old.
10 years.
Was there ever a baby, Tanya?
Tell me, was there?
And the pool-- there is no pool.
You said they raped you
out back by the pool,
but there isn't one, Tanya.
He never laid a
finger on you, did he?
The bruises, how-- the bruisesin the photo-- how'd you
do that?
It was makeup.
You painted them on.
Who was he, Tanya?
Who did I kill?
He sure as hell
wasn't some mobster.
You didn't kill anybody.
Far as I know, it was a
robbery that went bad.
The emails, BDA
junk-- you sent those.
You push all the right
buttons, didn't you?
Go home, Joe.
Why'd you do this?
Why'd you do this to me?
Go home.
You're going to hell for this.
[scoffs]
[sighs]
TANYA: I ordered it all online--
except for the rug,
that's from Sears.
Do you like it?
It's OK if you don't.
I've got 30 days to return.
I'm just not sure
that maybe you should
be buying so much new stuff.
Why not?
It looks bad.
I don't care how it looks.
People might think that--
I don't care
what people think.
Well, maybe you ought to.
Tanya, this is real life.
Mark is dead.
Someone killed him.
He's dead.
[slot machines whirring]
[inaudible].
Seen Joe?
Is he on tonight?
He's supposed to be.
Hell, if he's on anotherbender, that's it for him.
Uh, place your bets.
[phone ringing]
[hangs up]
Joe?
Sheldon's going
to kick your butt.
No--
JOE [VOICEOVER]:
Anything happens to me,
I put all my things in order.
They're in a briefcase
under my bed.
Dear Paula, a man named
Mark Sullivan was killed
in Pittsburgh a few weeks ago.
It was me.
I drove there and killed him.
Tanya was involved.
She helped set it up.
I have all the proof.
Take it to the police.
DETECTIVE: Please
make sure Teddy is OK.
I love him so much.
He's all I have left.
I know that doing this
is the coward's way out,
but I am at my end.
I was so blind and so
stupid, and so in love.
Little did I know she
never meant any of it.
Joe.
Mark's insurance policy--bit of money there--
bored of their life, who knows.
Most people don't really
need a reason to lie.
For some, it's the
lie itself they
get a charge out of, seeinghow far they can push things,
you know?
Getting lost in
the make believe--
it's still murder, though.
Let me them.
They look bad.
I bought them.
Let me see them.
[laughing]
I can't believe I'm
even sleeping with you.
Yeah, yeah.
[laughs]
[knocking]
DETECTIVE: Did you evermeet a man in Atlantic City
by the name of Joe Donnelly?
I met a lot of people
in Atlantic City.
There was a Joe I met, butI talked to a lot of people.
DETECTIVE: Did you developa relationship with him?
It isn't true that you werehaving a physical relationship
with Joe?
Maybe online.
No, I'm talking
about in person.
No.
DETECTIVE: Did you eversend Joe films of you naked?
No films of me naked, no.
I didn't.
OK.
I'll tell you this.
We do know that Joe
took his own life.
OK, Tanya, things get
difficult in life.
Sometimes things get difficultand you get into situations.
You get married to somebodyand then you meet someone else.
OK, let me ask you this.
What's your online name?
Tanya1013, I have SexyKitten--
I've had 100 different names.
But you had a
relationship with Joe.
Yes.
Yes, you did.
[sighs]
Hm?
You know what?
Online is a game, OK?
There is nothing wrong withtalking to somebody online.
There is nothing wrong with it.
I have a list of
people that I talk to.
I have probably 50
I-- I talk to a
guy named Dennis.
I talked to a guy named Tom.
Everyone I have a differentrelationship with.
There is nothing
wrong with that.
There is nothing wrong withsitting and talking back
and forth to someone online.
Sometimes you say stuff.
Come on, everybody does it.
Nobody can see.
They don't know you.
Sometimes you say stuff.
DETECTIVE: It's
all there, Tanya.
All of it.
Been a lot of things toa lot of different people.
[keyboard clattering]
What do you want
me to be to you?
[MUSIC - KEATON SIMMONS,
"CURRENTLY"]
KEATON SIMMONS: [SINGING]My love is a storm.
She doesn't wait for me.
And now that she's
gone, I fear that she'll
never be back in my arms,oh, where she held me tight.
And I just might
be losing, uh-oh.
When the rain comes down,the clouds will roll, lord,
and the wind will blow.
You on my undertow
caught in a riptide.
And I am currently
in love with you.