[ Birds Singing ]
[ Rooster Crows ]
We were a big family and, uh,
we was too many children.
Uh, it was very
difficult to manage
all the families,
mm, for my father
and mother,
and, uh, you know,
they had to do--
they had to do
very hard work...
every day, you know,
and life was very difficult
at that moment.
We liked, uh--
W-W-W-We liked...
our mother better
than our father.
It, you know,
it's very difficult to say.
You know,
I'm sorry to say this...
because, uh,
when we compare
with our father,
and our father, you know--
Our mother, she was,
uh, very nice, uh, for us.
Yeah, he was very tough.
Always he beatin' us.
Then, sometimes
twice a day...
[ Chuckles ]
or three times
he beatin' us,
and, uh,
it was very, uh, hard.
[ Laughs ]
Yeah, this is the--
This is very, you know--
I remember it always,
this tree.
When we--
When I was young--
This tree is, uh, uh,
something special...
for me.
[ Laughs ]
[ Crowd Cheering,
Radio Announcer Speaking
Indistinctly ]
[ Radio Announcer ]
...of Ethiopia, really
pouring it on right now.
[ Cheering Continues ]
Always, I pray, uh--
That is very important.
You know, uh--
Uh, just,
you hard work,
and the God help you.
If, uh--
If the God not help you,
your work is, uh,
nothing.
[ Man Panting ]
[ Running Footsteps ]
* [ Drums Beating ]
* [ Upbeat African ]
* [ Man Vocalizing ]
* [ Man Singing
In African Language ]
* [ Chorus Repeats ]
* [ Continues ]
[ Crowd Clapping In Time ]
[ Announcer ]
I declare open...
the games of Atlanta.
[ Crowd Cheering,
Whistling ]
The athletes of the Centennial
Olympic Games.
[ Cheering Continues ]
Ten thousand meters,
men, final.
[ Announcer #2 Speaking French
Over Loudspeaker ]
[ Announcer #1 ]
And the field includes...
the bronze medalist
of the 1993--
1995 World Championships,
Paul Tergat of Kenya,
1995 African Games
Gold medalist,
Joseph Amachuga of Kenya.
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
[ Man ]
On your mark.
Get set.
[ Crowd Roars ]
[ Men Panting ]
[ Panting ]
[ Speaking
African Language ]
[ Man Shouting
In African Language ]
[ Clucking Tongue ]
[ Man On Radio Speaking
African Language ]
Hey!
[ Man On Radio
Continues ]
"Moscow."
[ Rooster Crows ]
[ Mother Speaking
African Language ]
[ Donkeys Braying ]
[ Running Footsteps ]
[ Haile Panting ]
[ Speaking Softly ]
[ Rooster Crows ]
* [ Boys Singing
In African Language ]
[ Man ] Good morning, class.
[ Together ]
Good morning, sir.
Sit down.
Thank you, sir.
[ Man ]
Oh, Haile.
You are late.
You are late again.
Okay, sit down.
Here, I mentioned that
we have seven continents
were formed.
Seven continents
were formed...
because Gondwanaland
was splitted into seven.
We have Russia,
we have Australia,
North America, South America,
North America,
South America,
Africa, Europe and Antarctica.
Africa, Europe
and Antarctica.
[ Panting ]
* [ Men Singing ]
* [ Singing ]
[ Haile's Father
Shouting ]
[ Shouting ]
* [ Singing, Shouting
Continue ]
[ Speaking Softly ]
[ Speaking
African Language ]
[ Metal Rattling ]
[ Empty Cans Rattling ]
[ River Running ]
[ Water Sloshing
In Cans ]
[ Man Speaking
On Radio ]
[ Crowd Cheering ]
[ Announcer Speaking Over P.A.,
Indistinct ]
[ Man Continues ]
[ Crowd Cheering ]
[ Whistle Blowing ]
[ Whistle Blowing
Continues ]
[ Man Speaking ]
[ Cries Out ]
[ Speaking
African Language ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Haile Speaking
In African Language ]
[ Man Chanting ]
[ Congregation Chanting ]
[ Chanting Continues ]
[ Baby Squalling ]
[ Squalling ]
[ Man Chanting ]
[ Babies Continue
Squalling ]
[ Speaking Softly ]
[ Congregation Murmuring ]
[ Man ]
Hey.
Hut.
Hey!
[ Crowd Chattering ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Shouts ]
[ Groans ]
[ Speaking
African Language ]
[ Crowd Whistling,
Cheering ]
* [ Singing In
African Language ]
[ Crowd Clapping,
Cheering ]
[ Woman Ululating ]
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
* [ Man Singing ]
[ Shouting In
African Language ]
[ Haile's Father Speaking
In African Language ]
[ Woman Chanting ]
[ Women Ululating ]
[ Children Shouting
Playfully ]
[ People Chattering ]
[ Call-And-Response
In African Language ]
[ Laughing, Chattering ]
[ Scraping ]
[ Women Ululating ]
[ Man Chanting ]
[ People ]
Amen!
[ Call-And-Response
Continues ]
* [ Singing, Clapping ]
[ Rooster Crowing ]
* [ Man Singing ]
[ Shouting, Chattering ]
[ Labored Breathing ]
[ Labored Breathing
Continues ]
[ Haile Shouts In
African Language ]
[ Shouting ]
[ Haile Speaking Softly ]
[ Speaking African Language ]
* [ Woman Singing
In African Language ]
* [ Continues ]
[ Arguing ]
[ Laughing, Chattering ]
* [ Ends ]
[ People Murmuring ]
* [ Man Singing ]
[ Wailing ]
[ Sobbing ]
* [ People Singing,
Clapping ]
[ Haile Sobbing ]
[ Sobbing ]
* [ Singing ]
[ Weeping ]
* [ Singing, Wailing
Continue ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Panting ]
[ Man Shouts ]
[ Speaking
African Language ]
[ Whistle Blows ]
Haile!
[ Shouting ]
[ Both Speaking
African Language ]
[ Chickens Clucking ]
[ Rooster Crowing ]
[ Speaking
In African Language ]
[ Father Speaking ]
[ Bleating ]
* [ African ]
[ Horn Honking ]
* [ Man Singing
In African Language ]
[ Horns Honking ]
* [ Continues ]
[ Honking Continues ]
[ Chattering
In African Language ]
* [ Continues ]
[ Bus Horn Honks ]
* [ Ends ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Brother Speaking
In African Language ]
[ Chopping ]
[ Brother Speaking ]
Good.
[ Mutters ]
[ Chattering
In African Language ]
[ Woman Ululating ]
[ Ululating Continues ]
[ Chattering Continues ]
[ Man Whistles ]
[ Scattered Shouting
In African Language ]
[ Children Shouting ]
[ Rooster Crows ]
[ Exhaling Forcefully ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ People Chattering
In African Language ]
[ Exhaling Forcefully ]
[ Panting ]
[ Panting Continues ]
[ Breathing Heavily ]
[ Blowing ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Chattering
In African Language ]
* [ Man Chanting ]
* [ Chanting Continues ]
[ Speaking
In African Language ]
[ Haile Continues,
Whispering ]
[ Speaking
In African Language ]
[ Haile Continues ]
[ Speaking
In African Language ]
[ Woman ]
Mmm.
[ Coins Dropping ]
Hello?
[ Speaking
In African Language ]
[ Horns Honking ]
[ Speaking
In African Language ]
[ Conversing In
African Language ]
[ Chuckles ]
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
[ Lieutenant Tizazu
Shouting ]
[ Speaking
In African Language ]
[ Panting ]
[ Bleating ]
[ Herder Shouts ]
[ Haile Shouting ]
[ Bleating Continues ]
[ Panting Continues ]
[ Man Announcing ]
Abebe Bekila is running
without track shoes.
For the first time
in Olympic history,
the Ethiopian national anthem.
[ Panting Continues ]
[ Two Men Announcing
In Foreign Languages,
Overlapping ]
[ Panting Continues ]
[ Announcing Continues ]
[ Crowd Cheering ]
[ Panting Continues ]
[ Cheering Continues ]
[ Haile's Panting Intensifies ]
[ Crowd Cheering
On Television ]
[ Panting Continues ]
[ Cheering Continues ]
[ Scattered Whistles ]
[ Woman Ululating ]
[ Panting Continues ]
[ Cheering Continues ]
[ Scattered Whistles Continue ]
[ Man Shouting
In Foreign Language ]
[ Crowd Clapping Rhythmically ]
[ Cheering Intensifies ]
[ Man Announcing
Over Loudspeaker,
Indistinct ]
* [ Men Singing
In African Language ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Speaking
In African Language ]
[ Haile Thinking ]
[ Cheering Continues ]
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
[ Panting Continues ]
[ Coughs, Spits ]
[ Haile, Indistinct ]
[ Father, Indistinct ]
[ Cheering Continues ]
[ Haile Thinking ]
[ Ringing ]
[ Panting Continues ]
[ Crowd Applauding ]
[ Family Members Applauding ]
[ Alem Shouting ]
[ Chuckles ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Woman Ululating ]
[ Cheering ]
* [ Chorus Singing ]
[ Excited Chattering ]
[ Cheering, Whistling ]
[ Women Ululating ]
[ Cheering Continues ]
* [ Ends ]
* [ Woman Singing
In African Language ]
* [ Ends ]
* [ Drums ]
* [ Upbeat African ]
* [ Man Singing
In African Language ]
* [ Chorus Repeats ]
* [ Man Continues ]
* [ Man, Chorus Continue ]
* [ Chorus Singing ]
[ Clapping Rhythmically ]
* [ Man Resumes ]
* [ Chorus Repeats ]
* [ Man, Chorus Continue ]
* [ Singing Stops ]
* [ Orchestral Version ]
* [ Ends ]