Have a drink.
I know that we haven't been
seeing each other lately.
I hope you won't be upset at me...
for calling only when I need a favor.
Sorry to bother you.
Actually, I should be the one doing this.
But I just got transferred to a new section
at work, and things have been hectic.
You know my wedding will be held in Hawaii.
I need someone who can secure
a good venue for the post-reception party.
Your company published
guide books for Hawaii, right?
Were you in charge of those?
On occasion, yes.
Awesome! You must have been there
several times then, haven't you?
Well...
Will you help?
I'd be so grateful.
Well then. Please give it some thought.
– See you.
Turn her down, Minori.
None of our old classmates wound go to
Hawaii just for a post-reception party.
It'll just be Aiko's fellow cabin attendants
and her fiance’s clients.
It doesn't matter.
Her fiancé is rich and
has big-name clients, right?
No one will pay any attention to us.
This party is just an excuse to let
his clients hook up with her colleagues.
Aiko just wants ordinary girls
like us there as hired help.
You don't know that.
I'm sure of it.
Okay.
If you accept the task,
she'll ask you for a written proposal.
A proposal?
Outlining the venue, the program as well as
details from concierge to cloak service.
"I get so confused if it's not all written down."
She'd say in that sweet voice of hers.
And after you've written it
all out like she said...
You've actually done this for her?
She would pick your work to pieces,
pointing out typo and grammar errors.
After you finally fixed all these errors,
she starts vetoing the contents.
I have a full-time job.
Why should I take so much crap
from her helping her out?
So Aiko's dad runs a very established restaurant frequented by politicians.
Since she moves in more rarefied circles than us commoners...
her go-between were always hugely popular.
Kayoko would suck up to her
in hopes of getting invited to one.
Then Aiko became a cabin attendant
and stopped answering Kayoko's calls.
So Kayoko started badmouthing her.
Nevertheless, when Aiko suddenly asked her
to help with her post-reception party...
Kayoko was like "Anything for you."
Hilarious, isn't it?
Kayoko is a woman who spends
her downtime in beer bars.
How would she possibly know
anything about entertaining in Hawaii?
I guess so.
Although Aiko has her flaws,
she doesn't mean to be a pain in the neck.
She just can't help saying
"Maybe there's a better place."
She's a terror to work for.
Sure sounds that way.
Congratulations, Tajima!
For me? Thanks!
– Tajima, congratulations!
Congratulations...
Way to go, Tajima.
Thank you.
Is it a boy or a girl?
– It's a boy.
– It's a boy!
– Congratulations.
– You are too kind.
Congratulations!
The manuscripts are ready.
"Work Your Brain and Raise Your Pay."
"Walking Tour of 300 Famous Eateries."
And "Live Longer by Laughing."
Please go through them.
Efficient as ever.
Shall we do something on astrology next?
No.
Let's create a guide book to Hawaii.
We've already done a bunch of those.
I know.
"Hawaii Now!"
"My Personal Hawaii."
"Shopping in Hawaii."
"Hooray Hawaii."
"Feeling Hawaii."
"Hawaiian Ocean."
Enough. You're giving me a headache.
We published all these books
without making any trip to Hawaii.
Surprising, but clearly possible.
Hawaii is a hugely popular
travel destination now.
If we were to compile a guide to
the places only locals go...
it will definitely be a hit.
And to be safe, we can throw in
a guide for Hawaiian weddings.
Weddings and local hangouts are totally
unrelated. Rethink your strategy.
We can even include a top ten ranking
of Spam Musubi at the back.
I'm not convinced.
Boss.
I saw something the other day.
That's a pretty nice car you bought.
It's secondhand.
Every one else here
is struggling to pay their rent.
Owning a Porsche has always been my dream.
If word gets out...
everyone might start
clamoring for a pay rise.
– Aiko? I'll plan your party for you.
– Really?
I'd like to go there right away.
Can you get me a ticket?
– Right away.
– Thanks. That'd be great.
– Bye.
I'm terribly sorry.
That's...
Aloha. Welcome to the Moana Surfrider.
Thank you.
I'd like another.
It goes down so easily, it's like juice.
Sure thing, ma'am.
You sure can drink.
Are you alone, miss?
She ignored me!
This is so typical of lonely women.
Thank you.
Imagine coming all this way
just to snub people.
It's always the lonely ones, I tell you.
It's written all over their faces.
Hey, waiter. A crazy guy just came in.
Hey...!
You...
You there!
You're not a guest here, are you?
You look like a bum.
What are you doing here?
Hey!
Are you collecting bottles for money?
I happen to have some money with me.
I'll buy some bottles from you.
How much are you charging?
Hey, mister. He's a friend of mine.
Is that right?
Are you hoping I'd be grateful or something?
Excuse me?
You wanted to feel good
helping a poor guy out?
What do you mean?
Well. I don't appreciate the gesture.
Even if you don't, there's no need to
highlight that fact, is there?
I just wanted to shut that annoying
old man up, that's all.
It worked, I feel better now.
We're not friend, you're free to go.
But if you plan to hang around,
stop flinging accusations...
and join me for a drink,
so we can talk trash about him.
You're pretty all right, I guess.
I get that all the time.
Listen...
there's a full-moon party tonight
at Haleiwa Beach. Come if you'd like.
Sorry. Looks like
I've been invited to another party.
You can come anytime.
The party will last all night.
The chairman will be attending the party,
so dress appropriately, okay?
Okay.
Now, face each other.
Very nice. Stand a little closer.
Excuse me.
Let's try that again. Sorry.
Minori.
What's with the outfit?
You're really overdressed.
You told me to dress appropriately.
Allow me to introduce.
Akane...!
Go that way!
Get off the horse.
Meet up again.
I guess as much. Thanks.
You're welcome.
That's the Hawaii Polo Club chairman.
He said he'd teach me how to ride.
This is my friend. Yoshimura Akane.
She lives here.
She'll help you plan the post-reception party.
So you're the party planner.
The desire to serve others reflects
mankind's most noble sentiment.
I'm not in the habit of
saying "Thanks" to dripping sarcasm.
Great. You'll get along just fine.
I'll leave the rest to you.
No... wait.
Shall we ditch the party?
It's the same old crowd.
You looked like you were
having a ball though.
No, I was just making it fun for them.
But I haven't even met the groom yet.
Oh, he's hard at work
selling condominiums over there.
Better not bother him.
Are you new to this kind of parties?
Yes.
Friends of Alan?
Amazing guy.
His products are sold in all big countries.
Alan?
The "horse."
He's the host.
This is his product.
Moisturizer that you wouldn't believe
you can find them in the toilet.
But you're here to have fun, so bottoms up.
What is this?
Pineapple wine.
I'll pass.
Well...
before you speak, the president of
the winery is right over there.
– It's delicious!
– Thanks.
Hi.
I think the flavor satisfies Japanese taste.
Actually, she loves it.
Thank you very much.
That guy just used me to
talk to that president, didn't he?
He wore a suit to the party in Hawaii.
His kinds are like anteaters,
scavenging for money.
Don't you mean hyenas?
Let's hit a real party.
Is drink driving legal here?
I haven't had a drop.
So you aren't really drunk then?
You've got slam it shut really hard.
We'll drink at my place.
Stealing food from a party
is pretty cheap, don't you think?
Well, you took the champagne, didn't you?
Yes, but I wouldn't bring along
a Tupperware to such a function.
– Don't you find it embarrassing?
– Speak for yourself...
– Akane!
– I'll never bring a Tupperware.
Harassing the rich again?
Hey, Emi. Heading to work?
Yeah, but do you mind if I have some?
Sure.
This is Aiko's friend.
I'm Minori.
– I'm Emiko.
– And I'm Akane. Cheers.
Cheers!
Wearing Emi's clothes again?
– Hey Mako.
– She's a painter.
No sugar daddies today?
I knew everyone there.
Is there anyone you don't know?
Sorry to drag you from that party.
We'll go somewhere better.
There's a place called Loa Ridge.
That's where the rich men gather.
Just for the record,
I didn't come here to find a rich man.
So are you saying you'd rather
scrape by than be rich.
I'm saying I'm not looking
for a man in the first place.
You prefer women?
How do I say "Lesbian" in Japanese?
You're already speaking in Japanese.
We won't discriminate. It's fine.
Again for the record,
I am only attracted to men.
So Minori, what type of guys do you go for.
Well, let's see...
someone who'd tell me
when I've had enough to drink.
Of course, I wouldn't listen
and continue to drink.
He'll say, "Enough!" and take away my glass.
But I'll probably hide
some whiskey under my bed.
So you aspire to be an alcoholic?
Get serious if you want your life to work out.
Who asked you?
A Japanese guy won't cut it for me.
I want to stay here, so I need a green card.
When's your visa expiring, Akane?
In three months.
You've got to try harder
and hit the party more.
So you'll settle for any American?
No way. If I have to settle for
some low-income housing over here...
I'd rather go back to my hometown
in Akita and grow rice.
You're from Akita?
Akane!
Oh no. It's Honma.
He's Akane's stalker.
Are you so fond of rich men?
I've got clients from the polo club too.
Take it easy, Honma.
Honma sells insurance.
Do you know how I feel when I hear
my client talking about you.
Okay... I know it's hard.
I know I'm way too old for you...
but I can't control my feelings for you!
You need to find a way to.
Listen, Honma.
If you really love this girl...
you've got to be willing
to help her find her Mr. Right.
Now that's true love.
Who's this chick?
That's right, Honma.
You've got access to lots of
private information at your firm.
Can't you just divulge some?
I'll get fired for that.
Akane, have you got any idea
what people say about you?
What do they say?
Are they calling me a Japanese idol?
They say you're a desperate picnic ant!
They are going to start turning you away.
That's not very nice.
So stop this silly daydreaming
and marry me.
Okay? Will you please marry me?
Will you?
No!
That's wrong.
Guys who take advantage of women
when they are down are the worst.
Jerks who resort to
such manipulative tricks...
are either the sort who borrow small change
without intending to pay it back...
or the sort who makes things difficult for
the staff at convenience stores.
Which type are you?
Or are you both?
Who the heck are you?
Go home.
Here...
bottoms up.
Good morning, Mako.
Good morning
Here.
This is from Akane.
Thanks.
Yes.
"Morning shift. Join me for lunch.
Bring the key and come before noon."
Would you like to try on this color?
Here you go...
You look amazing!
These colors are so slimming.
It fits you so well that
it seems tailor-made for you.
I almost hate to charge you for it,
but that would be twenty dollars.
Oh!
Such energy.
Are you hungry?
Wow! this looks delicious.
This is really awesome.
What do you think?
It's fantastic.
What did I tell you?
Hold on.
Okay.
Don't tell me you tweet about your food?
I have to write a Hawaii travel guide.
Can you show me more places like this
where the local hang out?
Is that why you are here?
To be perfectly honest...
I'm using company money and
Aiko's connections...
to have fun in Hawaii.
My company is covering all my expenses.
I can pay you to be my local
coordinator. Are you in?
I'm in.
Here we are.
– Here?
– This is the place.
– It's lovely!
– Right?
Here we are.
Wait. I want a photo.
– Should I pose like this?
– Shift a little to that side.
Okay.
Why did we park so far away?
I can't help it, there weren't any
parking space available.
So how do you attract a white guy?
Do you serve him food or something?
That won't cut it.
Americans like strong women.
Watch and learn.
I think you're good at arm wrestling...
but you can't beat me with muscles like these.
I won't challenge you because
I don't want to embarrass you.
You should stay outside, sweetie.
He didn't want to deal with you.
I'm going back in.
I think you're good at arm wrestling...
but you can't beat me with muscles like these.
It looks like you're having fun.
Oh!
Want a drink.
Am I supposed to talk this up too?
There isn't anybody to impress today.
May I?
Be my guest.
So did the boss of that pineapple winery
agree to make an investment?
Thanks to you, he agree to
peruse my business plan.
I'm thinking of inviting him to my shop.
Your shop?
Well, a restaurant.
Would you like to come over?
I could use with another's opinion.
Food's on the house.
Well...
but what about my friend?
Should we help her?
She'll be fine.
You have any liquor there?
Just name it.
Thanks.
Thank you.
This is it.
I want to launch my shop in the mainland.
Hawaii is just my testing ground.
"Japanese Tea Rice"?
It's an Ochazuke restaurant.
Coming Through.
What do you think?
– It's quite ordinary.
– That's the point.
Perhaps you should add
more variety to your menu?
No, that's won't work. My plan is
to launch my stores across the country.
The States is teeming with
Japanese restaurant as it is.
I need to set my brand apart from
the others. It's tougher on the mainland.
I see.
Why the States? Why not Europe?
No, I want it to be in America.
Russia's cold. This will go over well.
No way.
So it's either the States or nothing?
I wouldn't say that.
– What about Thailand?
– That's out of the question.
Smashed presidents' faces,
smashed pumpkins for Halloween.
Designs, you know, I think
there were like twenty kinds or so.
Drugs are an easy audience,
so we sold a lot to bars.
You are the head of a coaster company then.
Not only coasters,
but we also made place mats.
Okay.
After trying to make several designs,
our company was sold
to a larger kitchenware company.
So now, I'm just investing the money
we made from there.
You're living on dividends.
I'd very much like to hear any good
financial advice you might have for me.
How about investment trust?
How about talking at my place?
Or exchange-traded funds?
Come on,
let's go.
Listen, I'm living with a couple of girls
that I'm dating right now, but...
I don't think you'd mind, do you?
"Dating"?
To put it simply, it's a trial period.
He has several girls from among which
he'll choose on to be his girlfriend.
So he can officially sleep
with several girls at the sane time.
But I've never heard of anyone
living with all his dates.
Sound efficient.
It's a joke.
So what happened?
I'm not living in a harem.
I see.
What about you, Minori?
You left with a Japanese businessman.
Nothing happened.
We had Ochazuke and Japanese wine.
You're in Hawaii, you know.
Then I went over to his place...
You went to his place?
Well...
sort of.
Is this a warehouse?
Yes, I rented it as a warehouse,
but it doubles as my house now.
Disappointed?
Not really.
I wear an expensive suit just to
look presentable for business dealings.
But actually, I'm struggling financially.
I've had my share of setbacks.
When I first took the plunge into
business, I sold toe socks.
They rakes in enough profits
to fund my next venture.
That's dry cleaning service.
But that was a disaster.
So next, I tried selling Konjac diet foods.
That did all right.
After that, it was charcoal-infused shampoo.
I guess the advertising didn't work.
It was a major flop.
I made a comeback
with those green tea cookies.
That did pretty well until sales flattened out.
I used the profit to start
my current restaurant.
Don't you think you're being
way too adventurous?
That's what I need. I don't want
to lose the entrepreneurial spirit.
Perhaps you should take
into consideration local tastes.
No, that won't work.
The cookie business taught me a lesson.
To be well received in the States,
you need a unique Japanese touch.
For example, the Japanese dedication
to meticulous service.
Or an "oriental" vibe.
All these may seem normal to us,
but they really make an impact overseas.
It's hard to see that in Japan.
Want a drink?
And you left?
That guy did not impress me.
What's wrong with that?
Back in Japan, my boss kept telling me
to publish anything that would sell.
Travel guides, diet cookbooks,
pelvis correction exercise manuals...
B-list restaurant guides,
shocking apocalyptic prophecies...
lymphatic massage for a slimmer face
and guides to the best spas in town.
That is...
I saw myself in him. It irked me.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
So you prefer a man who doesn’t work?
No, a man should at least work
to support his loved ones.
I see. So love begets money?
Even if he's rich, he still needs to work
to maintain his fortune, right?
That's not true.
It's not about how hard you work.
The reality is that the rich get richer
and the poor remain poor, Minori.
That's warped logic.
There's more to life than that.
Emi got married in a hurry
to secure a green card...
only to get abused and now,
she's divorced.
You have to choose wisely, you know?
I don't want a green card and
I'm not in a hurry to get married.
So you're all right with staying single?
I can't marry the guy I'm dating anyway.
You're seeing someone?
Why can't you marry him?
– You mean he's already married?
– Drop it already.
There's nothing worse than cheating.
Okay, I'm so sorry.
I'm only saying this in your best
interest. You better listen up.
I hear you, Sis.
But I don’t need you
pointing out all my faults.
I'm not looking to settle down
and I don't intend to marry for money.
Neither do I. But you've got to
start looking somewhere, don't you?
I'm just starting with the rich.
Why the rich?
Minori, you think all rich people
are jerks, don't you?
That's discrimination.
Yeah. While you don't discriminate,
you'll sleep with anyone.
What's that supposed to mean?
You're the one crashing parties
to mount rich tycoons.
That was just innocent fun.
What about Honma?
I did sleep with Honma.
See? You did.
Who else?
Nobody.
What?
I've only slept with Honma.
In fact, he's my first.
That's why he's always on my back.
I think he feels responsible.
Eh?
Why are you so surprised?
What kind of person did you think I was?
Well... I mean...
What about all those men?
I didn't sleep with any of them!
I don't have affairs with married men or
go to their place on the first date!
"Boss, here are the pictures taken
in Hawaii. Fieldwork is progressing well."
"But please send me more money...
"as I'm running low on funds
Regards Minori."
"Minori, I hope you're enjoying
your trip in Hawaii."
"We need to talk after you get back.
Regards, Tajima."
Hello?
How's everything? Found a good spot
for the post-reception party?
That's...
I'm spoilt for choice.
I'm thinking out on the sea...
or maybe on a rooftop.
Or how about a garden party?
Like in Kailua.
That's a great idea.
I'm sure Satoshi will love it.
Let's get together to discuss it.
Welcome.
This way, please.
Are you alone today?
I've been thinking about
what your friend said the other day.
If I really care about you...
I should find someone suitable for you.
That's what true love is about.
Have you been drinking?
I'm not drunk.
I've chosen a few clients of mine
who might be suitable for you.
Please don't show this to anyone.
I'll be fired if I get found out.
You didn't have to do this.
If things don't go well with
any of these men...
I hope you'll choose me.
There's going to be an Epicurean Club party
tomorrow afternoon at Loa Ridge.
Let's go together.
Regarding your garden party idea...
Yes.
I think it's great.
You do?
But I'm concerned about bathroom
facilities for female guests.
You see, my friends and clients
tend to attract women wherever they go.
Hey, Tsutomu.
I heard you're going to
Loa Ridge today. May I tag along?
I don't think so.
The pineapple wine venture fell through.
But a guy I met at Alan's party
showed interest in Japanese food.
I would like to meet him again.
Please do me a favor.
All right then.
Why don't you join us, Minori?
It's a party at Loa Ridge.
Sure.
Shall we?
Thank you.
I see you prefer successful guys.
What?
– This house looks really nice.
– Wait...
Come here...
The event is still going on.
Isn't that why we are here?
No, we have to wait for it to end...
before we join the cocktail party.
So we're commoners after all.
Being here is a big deal in itself.
Here, as in hanging around the periphery?
Go home if you hate it so much.
Why are you dressed like that?
This is my strategy.
She works for me.
What's going on?
So, Minori.
Finally interested in the rich?
I'm just here for the drinks.
I'll see how it's going inside.
I wonder when they will
start throwing us table scraps?
This is serious. Shut up.
Get off your high horse.
You're just waiting to pounce on change
that falls from their pockets.
You don't understand because you've never
put your best foot forward, Minori.
I'm sorry, but what are you trying to say?
You've never taken anything seriously
enough to understand our feelings.
Are you talking about yourself?
A person looking to marry rich
for a good life shouldn't talk.
If you want money, why don't you
just get a job? Seriously.
Okay. I think we're good.
Let's go.
It's better to look plain than tacky.
If you can't marry a rich man,
you can always be his mistress.
Is that a joke?
I think your son will be so thrilled to have
a yacht for his junior high school graduation.
Oh, that is fantastic.
You know now the Japanese food
is widely accepted in the States?
And my restaurant
is specialized in tea rice.
Thank you.
Hi.
We met at Alan’s party the other day.
I’m running a Japanese restaurant.
You know now the Japanese food
is widely accepted in the States?
And my restaurant is specialized in tea...
Thank you.
Do I act like a professional?
No, be the flustered rookie.
Maybe you'll win their sympathy.
In that case, shall I rip my sleeve as well?
Those people love doing charity work.
Hon!
Listen, don't forget to take my advice.
Hey!
Hey, Hon.
How's the night fishing the last time?
No good.
You're still the record holder.
Of course.
Hon and I train hard against
each other in trawling.
He's really good at it.
May I introduce my new assistant, Akane?
I feel so c-c-c-cold.
You need something to put on?
Yes.
Don't you have a bigger glass?
Hi, nice to meet you.
Can I show you my business?
Thank you.
Finding this funny?
No, it's boring actually.
The world sure is run in a tedious way.
Go ahead and sneer.
That boring shop of yours
is never going to make it big.
No, I'm sure it will be a hit.
Japanese food is all the rage on the mainland.
And yet you branded
your product as "tea rice"?
If you're promoting Japanese cuisine,
you should call it "Ochazuke."
That would be setting the bar too high.
What a lame excuse.
Everyone calls "Sushi" by its name today.
You're never going to strike big
with and attitude like that.
Are you content to play second fiddle
or trendsetter all the time...
and earning enough just to survive.
What are you talking about?
What I mean is...
you should follow your heart.
People can tell when you're half-hearted
about your own business. You fool!
Go home.
– Don't tell me what to do.
– Come on.
– Let's go.
– Let's go of me!
Ouch, that hurts.
If you really believe in what you're doing...
you'll continue selling your product,
even if it's from the side of a truck.
Listen.
Instead of poking your nose into my business...
you should worry about yourself.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Let me introduce our new friend.
Hello.
My name is Tomoya Abe.
Nice to see all of you.
I'm the grandson of Kiotaka Abe.
I grew up in Japan,
but when I was very young...
I spent long vacations
here in my grandfather's house.
My grandfather has already passed away...
but those moments are
very precious memories to me.
I'm sure that all of you have
unforgettable memories as well.
So I'm not disappoint you.
And, will honor your traditions...
and I will rise to your expectations...
now that I'm accepted
as one of your members.
I know you!
Oyamada, where's your draft?
Sorry, It's almost done.
We'll publish a book on pelvis correction exercise.
Yes, Boss.
What should we do about the binding?
I'm so sorry, Miss Oyamada.
Could you do these too?
Is the book on Jumbo Meals done?
What about the facial slimming?
The World's Ending in 2012 in a hurry!
Yes.
I know. I'm so sorry.
I'll contact them immediately. I'm so sorry.
Well...
let's call it a night.
No way!
You think by getting drunk,
we can just forget everything by tomorrow?
No, I don't.
But we're going in circles.
– Why doesn't anybody understand?
– I understand. I really do.
I work the hardest in the company.
Yes, you do.
Don't you think it's ridiculous
that I don't get a pay rise?
It's ridiculous.
I can't believe it.
I'll resign tomorrow.
Now, hold on a second.
I'll do something about the money.
I'll talk to accounting
or just claim more expenses.
It's not about nickels and dimes.
Yes...
I'm asking, is this all I'm worth to them?
But you know, Minori...
without you, the company would fall apart.
The company would go bust immediately.
I mean it.
Do you really think so?
Of course! That's obvious.
That's... those ungrateful brats...
– Well said, Tajima.
– No...
Please give me a break.
I can't drink anymore.
Wait... wait a minute.
Stop drinking.
That's enough for this night.
Oh, man.
That sucks.
It sure does for me.
Hold on... that hurts.
What do you want?
– I don't know.
– Why...
No... stop. That's enough.
I'll take that.
Are we done here?
You were pretty smashed.
Who are you?
To put it simply, my family owns
a bunch of natural gas plants...
as well as chemical and oil companies.
In other words, you're very rich.
Akane would be delighted.
The gold diggers are always after me.
Is that why you collect bottles
and make palm syrup.
What a luxury that is.
Are you a modern-day Robin Hood?
I should be thinking about the business,
but I lack my father's talent.
Is that so?
What do I know?
And, why do you drink so much?
Well... it's my hobby.
Like you collecting bottles.
You don't want to talk about it?
Is it a guy?
Correct?
I think it's a boy.
Or was it a girl already?
Hell. I'll just tell you.
A lot of stuff happened at work,
and I was really down.
So I slept with a junior co-worker.
But he's married.
Since we're colleagues,
I still have to see him everyday.
And...
I started bringing him home
with me after drinks.
This went on for about four months.
And then...
I found out his wife was pregnant.
It's really messed up.
That's why you came to Hawaii?
I don't know what I'm doing.
I really ought to think it through.
What is it?
Nothing.
When I first met you...
at the hotel the other day,
you tried to help me, didn't  you?
Not that you needed any help.
Still...
I think that you helped me a lot
even when you're already feeling down.
Oh, stop.
Is it really okay for me to join you?
Yeah. It's like a celebration.
(Hawaiian language)
Auntie, I'd like to introduce Minori.
Nice to meet you.
(Hawaiian language)
She says you're as pretty as a flower.
Thank you.
(Hawaiian language)
It's her husband who passed away.
I just saw him surfing the other day.
(Hawaiian language)
Let's go.
Loa Ridge was a disaster,
but today will be different.
Our target today is...
to jog along this course.
When he comes, run alongside him.
Make conversation so that
he'll remember you...
then we see him again
at the party this weekend.
What do you think?
That's a good plan...
right?
It's okay, Honma.
No.
We only have three
potential candidates left.
It's enough.
No.
I got it.
No, you don't.
You still don't get how I care for you.
Yes, I do.
No, you don't.
Do you have any idea
how valuable this information is?
I said, that's enough!
I've made up my mind
the moment you showed me this.
You've made up your mind?
I've made up my mind to marry you.
Akane... no!
You don't have to shout.
I can hear you fine.
You should find a man
who will give you happiness!
That's why I've chosen you!
I only played along since
you went to the trouble to do this.
So it's enough.
A-A-Akane!
That's why I don't need this anymore.
My papers!
Oh well.
Akane.
You're dating that rich guy from
Loa Ridge? Are you crazy?
Who are you calling crazy?
I can just hear Emi now.
"Minori's boyfriend is a Loa Ridge guy
while you've settled for Honma."
– You're dating Honma?
– Never mind that.
Why...?
Forget about Honma.
Are you going to be living at Loa Ridge?
Akane!
Our table's over here.
Yes, I can see that.
You know what? Honma's kind of cute.
Don't make fun of my boyfriend.
Can you not be paranoid?
Akane!
Shall I place the order for you?
Yeah, by all means.
So come on, tell me.
Akane...!
What is it now?
– There's no Caesar salad.
– Any salad will do.
Hey, they've got mushroom salad.
That's great. Get that.
– So...
– What?
you agree a rich guy is still the best?
Akane, you think all rich people
are jerks, don't you?
That's discrimination.
You've finally awoken to love.
Will love really beget money?
That was what you said.
Forget what I said.
How did you hook up with him?
Can you tell me?
It's nothing worth mentioning.
Don't be coy.
You told him your sob story about dating
a married man and he consoled you?
Well...
That's pretty close to the mark.
That goes against what you told Honma.
Remember what you said?
Guy who take advantage of women
when they are down are the worst.
Jerks who resort to
such manipulative tricks...
are either the sort who borrow small change
without intending to pay it back...
or the sort who makes things difficult for
the staff at convenience stores.
Which type are you?
Or are you both?
Wow, you've got a good memory.
That's because I intend to marry him.
Really? Congratulations!
Like I said, this is not about me.
Everything all right?
They are getting married!
What?
Congratulations.
That's wonderful.
Now comes the hard part.
Forget about Honma.
What is it?
Akane...
You've got something
precious going on there.
So stop talking about me already!
You're so annoying!
Hey, whatever happened
to the pipeline in Azerbaijan?
Since that conflict in Georgia,
we had to abandon the project
right, Tomoya?
Yeah.
It seems.
It seems?
Why aren't you more cooperative?
He wants me to be more serious.
Tomoya.
Do whatever you like.
How is it going with the guide book?
Hey.
– Tajima.
– Yes.
Has she called you?
No.
She contacted you though.
She checked out of her hotel
and I can't reach her on her phone.
She should be there for two weeks,
but it's been twenty days.
You don't suppose
she will stay for good, do you?
She's on a tourist visa, though.
How long is her visa valid for?
I believe it's three months.
We can't wait that long.
– Tajima.
– Yes.
Go to Hawaii and find her.
Eh?
Saki...?
Look. According to this,
they will let you fly a Cessna.
A Cessna?  Really?
Is that awesome or what?
– That rocks...!
– A Cessna, no less!
– Awesome!
Yes..!
– I know! We'll be pilots.
– Awesome!
Wait.
Excuse me.
– Look at this.
– What? We can play with dolphins.
Really? Dolphins are so cute!
Pardon me. Excuse me.
– Dolphins are the cutest!
– This is so exciting!
Really want to go to Hawaii!
You've got to take the night cruise.
That's where I met my ex.
– Really?
– Sure.
– You want to meet guys, don't you?
– Excuse me.
Yes, I do.
I swear to God this will change your life.
All right! This is so exciting!
So exciting!
Excuse me. Please excuse me.
It's going to be great.
There's an amazing place...
just beyond the next mountain.
I found it with Ryan.
There's a hidden river deep in the jungle.
You'll be amazed when you see it.
It will blow you away.
What are you doing?
See for yourself.
I'll be parking the truck ahead.
Come and have some.
Your friend?
What?
Oh... yes.
All right.
I take one large
Lomi Lomi Chazuke...
Lomi Lomi. Okay
and one large Salmon Chazuke.
I have a medium Poke Dashi Chazuke...
and one medium Ume Chazuke.
Just a moment, please.
What's up, Tomoya?
How are you doing?
Here you are.
– Thanks.
– Thank you.
Pick anything you like.
Thank you. Please come again.
Thanks.
What do you think?
It's delicious!
It goes great with Hawaiian food.
I infused Japanese flavors
into local cuisine.
This way, the locals can get
a taste of Japanese food...
and the Japanese can also
draw closer to Hawaiians.
It feels like...
I'm erasing borders.
It sounds interesting.
Do you always set up shop here?
No.
I go downtown in the mornings,
and come here in the evenings.
At night, I target the tourists
in Waikiki after they hit the pubs.
Sounds busy.
Well, you told me to sell my products from
a truck if my store didn't work out.
Are you going out with him?
Yeah... you can say that.
He's from a rich family, right?
Apparently.
Good for you.
Excuse me!
A commoner's got to work.
I'm better off working anyway.
It's a lot of fun.
Did it sound like sour grapes?
No, I know what you mean.
I'm a commoner too.
Give me one large Poke Chazuke.
Hi! I come over.
See you then.
Are you off to work?
I have to get approval for merger plans.
I don't know much about
the workings of the company...
but I'm a board member after all.
Aren't you a hard worker then.
All I do is nod.
Where shall we meet for dinner?
Sorry, I promised to meet Aiko tonight.
I'll call you when I'm done.
– Sorry.
– Thank you.
Excuse me,
have you seen this lady?
No.
Excuse me,
have you seen this lady?
No...?
Are you close to Mr. Abe's son?
Yes... just recently.
I guess word travels.
The four of us should
get together sometime.
Good idea!
My friend's having a gallery opening.
Do come with him.
Have you heard when the next
Epicurean Club party will be held?
No, I haven't.
I need to use the washroom.
I set up a mobile Ochazuke
food truck in the parking lots...
so that I can sell at different locations.
I like the mobility idea. That's smart.
I'm a little unsure about the menu,
mixing local dishes with Ochazuke.
Do you think that would work?
Well, I'm already selling Poke Chazuke
and Spam Chazuke.
They're quite popular.
I see. Okay.
Well...
aren't you Mr Abe's...?
I am like Ohana(family) to Mr Abe.
Mr Kamada?
Tomoya wants to order
your Ochazuke takeout again.
So you're friends with Mr Abe as well?
Yes, of course!
Now, I see why you get
such awesome ideas.
Okay.
I'm interested.
See you.
It's nice to see you.
Can you show me some more of this?
Another one...
is...
Tonkatsu.
Loco Moco.
Loco Moco? I like Loco Moco.
Lau Lau Chazuke.
That's a good idea.
What can I do for you?
Well, Akane...
do you know that Ochazuke hawker?
"Ochazuke hawker"?
He was at the Loa Ridge party
trying to find backers for his business.
Are you interested in that?
Of course not!
Anyway.
He doesn't need my money and...
he has no lack of interested investors.
What's the big deal about it anyway?
So you don't like Ochazuke that much.
– Thank you.
Minori, will you be at your
boyfriend's place today as well?
Why don't you join us for drinks?
Minori!
Thanks for your help back there.
How did it go?
He's going to invest.
Really? That's wonderful.
It's all thanks to you, Minori.
This calls for a celebration, right?
– Did he agree to it all?
– I can't thank you enough.
Everything went so smoothly.
I see.
I'm so relieved.
What did he say?
He took the initiative to discuss details.
– I see. So he was into it?
– Totally.
Excuse me...
Have you seen this lady?
No?
We don't know her.
Sorry to bother you.
Thank you.
Where on earth are you, Minori?
Excuse me...
have you seen this lady?
No. Sorry.
Thank you.
I see.
So you'll be expanding to the mainland.
Up until now. I've been
so concerned with just staying afloat.
I had to come up with new ideas
if the previous one didn't work out.
There was constant pressure and,
I think I lost myself for a while.
I know what you mean.
Really?
I did a lot of thinking
after I closed down my restaurant.
I still remember the first time
I came to the States.
When my dad was posted to the States...
Mom and I visited him once.
At the Arizona countryside.
My father and I borrowed bicycles
and rode around in the neighborhood.
We had burgers at a diner.
That memory stuck in my mind.
Remember what you said to me?
You said I've got to know
what I want to do in life.
Can I get your advice again when I start
scouting for shops in the mainland?
Sure.
But wouldn't it be better if
you consult an expert instead?
I'd prefer someone who knows me
over an any business expert.
Sure.
They are probably just good friends.
I can tell from their eyes
there's something going on.
What are you going to do?
Crush that Ochazuke hawker
with your wealth and influence?
I thought I've found a woman
who can accept who I am.
Any girl would say "yes" to you.
But it's not for her!
You've lost me.
It doesn't matter to her who I am.
You mean she'll dump you
in spite of your social status.
What's so great about that Ochazuke guy?
You're upsetting yourself
by letting your imagination run wild.
So silly.
I thought I've found a woman
who can accept who I am.
We're just going in circles now.
May I go already?
Hold on...
– You're just repeating yourself.
– Just one more drink.
One more drink.
Check out this marlin!
I break the new record.
– Get your hands off.
– Just one more drink...
Akane!
Are you still trying to
land yourself a rich guy?
What's with you?
Answer me!
Of course not! Why would I?
Then what are you doing?
Honma, come and join us.
How dare you!
Honma.
Where did you get that huge tuna?
I made it. I did it!
Minori, can you believe this?
What's this?
Honma doesn't trust me!
That's totally understandable.
I won't marry someone who doesn't trust me!
Minori.
Do you really think he's good enough?
Me?
Minori, you should apologize him?
Yeah, you're going to regret it
if he dumps you.
Tomoya, this is my new record, bro!
My battle...
I hate trawling!
It's stupid!
Shut the f*ck up!
Tomoya, you never know the high of it.
Do you really think that Ochazuke
dude is good enough for you?
You're mistaken. We just ran into
each other at the restaurant.
He's better than someone collecting bottles.
Is that how you judge people?
Look who's talking!
I gave up a lot of opportunities
just to be with you, Honma!
I knew it!
So you do regret choosing me!
No, I don't!
You will definitely regret it.
You'd better kiss and make up.
What's wrong with me?
Seriously, who are you?
What do you want to be?
Minori, Mr Abe runs a major
international company...
You...!
will do anything to land a rich husband!
How dare you!
Yeah, I'll do anything!
Darn you!
Bring it on!
Come on!
We need to talk.
Mr Abe!
It's all a misunderstanding.
Minori only has eyes for you.
That's what I think.
Who is this guy?
Oh, pardon me.
I run a condominium
and yacht resale company.
– Here's my another name card.
– Get out of my way!
No... stop it!
We'll let them work it out.
Akane!
We're nothing but
convenient tools to guys like him.
We're not human to them.
Don't you understand?
Just let go of him.
Wait...!
The problems lies with yourself!
Do something about it!
What did I do?
So you're nice to everyone?
For being so nice to me...
Thank you!
Are you okay?
Calm down!
You'll kill him!
He's killing Honma!
Just calm down!
Well...
You all carry on then.
We shall make a move.
Goodbye.
I'm really sorry.
I'm okay now.
Really?
I'm so sorry.
I had a drop too much.
It's okay.
Is your business doing well?
Well...
I'm just starting out.
I see.
If you need any help,
you can come to me.
Thanks.
I'm sorry I went ballistic.
That's what keeps you...
from getting ahead.
I'm sorry.
So when's the weddings?
I don't know if I'll go through with it.
I mean the wedding ceremony.
Thank god.
You worry too much.
What is it?
Do you know him?
No.
Just a stranger.
Sorry about today.
No worries.
We'll celebrate another day.
But...
won't he get angry again?
I'll be busy planning my trip
to scout for shops anyway.
See you then.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
What happened to the
natural gas plant in the Caspian sea?
Well, nothing much has happened.
Well, who is the principal company,
The UK again?
No way.
Azerbaijan will have thirty percent...
the two Japanese will take ten percent...
and we have fifteen percent.
You'll still have to stick with the
Russian pipeline. We can't live without it.
I don't think Europe wants Russia
to have any control of the business anymore.
Absolutely true.
Even if you extend it to
the black sea through Georgia...
There's a problem in South Ossetia.
You don't know when Russia will be involved.
Thus you cannot pass Armenia.
You lay it from Turkey to
the Adriatic Sea out to Italy.
What if we let that joint venture company
from Switzerland handle it?
I don't think even they
could remedy the situation.
It's a fool's errand.
Hey, you want to give it a try?
Sure.
I'll do it.
I'll be flying over there next month
and be in charge there.
I won't be back until I accomplish the project.
I see.
I give you credit.
– Thank you.
– That's impressive.
Aiko, Satoshi.
Congratulations!
I've been asked to make a speech.
My name is Endo Kayoko.
Because they're holding their wedding
here in Hawaii,
I did a little research.
Is she going to quote from a travel guide?
You've got to admire her style.
Let's see...
In Hawaii, people greet
each other with the word "Aloha."
This word...
"Aloha" means...
Love.
Pride.
Wisdom.
Welcome.
Trust.
Hello.
Goodbye.
Thank you...
and I love you.
It is a beautiful word...
with a wealth of meaning.
But when translated literally...
"Alo" from Aloha means "to share."
And "ha" from Aloha means "breathing"
Put together, it means "shared breathing."
In Japanese, we have a similar phrase...
that means a perfect match.
In a marriage...
it's not wealth or looks that matters,
but compatibility and finding whether
someone who is your perfect match.
It sure is.
It really is.
With that meaning in mind,
I think Aiko and Satoshi...
can be said to be
a perfect match made in heaven.
Aloha!
You're next, Akane.
We'll just be having a party at the shop.
– Really?
– Yes.
Will you stop that?
What's wrong?
I'm just getting my money's worth.
Have you found a job yet?
I'm thinking of becoming an editor
for a free town paper...
or a waitress.
The editor sounds good.
I don't know.
But what a shame...
you could have been living up at Loa Ridge.
That's true.
How was the States?
I forgot, this is the States too.
Are you waiting for someone?
I see.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
So where will you be setting up
your first shop on the mainland?
I think I'll start at Washington D.C..
Because it's the capital?
That's funny.
I visited Texas too. Great place.
As I expected...
a nation-wide chain store
should start from the capital.
Sounds exciting.
How was the wedding?
It was beautiful.
Were you envious?
I can imagine.
Is he well?
The successor to Abe corporation.
I haven't seen him in a while.
Really?
Why not?
Because I'm a commoner.
Actually, I...
I...
When do you suppose
I'll be able to get married?
Soon, I suppose.
Really?
Yeah.
I'm sure of it.
You think so?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Do you mean it?
Of course.
I guess...
I'll take your word for it.
Excuse me.
Here's the manuscript from Minori.
Is it done?
Here you go.