♪ [Multicom Entertainment
Group jingle] ♪
♪ [country music]
[Metal voice] I
done told you once.
A 100 times.
Every man has got a price.
[Priest] Not every
man they don't.
[Metal voice] Hah,
you want to know mine?
Hell no.
[Metal voice] Well it
is a hell of a lot cheaper
than it should be I
can tell you that.
Hah, no one to
blame but yourself.
[Metal voice] I
ain't making excuses.
You know, if ifs
and buts were candy
and nuts we'd all have a
merry Christmas, right?
And if I hand it over,
I'd probably wouldn't
change nothing, truth be known.
See a man can want bad.
You ever hear the
one about the grave?
The grave?
Yeah, about that old
grave up in Hoke county.
[snickers] No, never
heard of that one.
[Metal voice] Hell man,
that's the first one they tell.
It's guaranteed to
chill your shit.
I don't care if you're
John D. Rockefeller
or Jed fucking Clampett,
it ain't never enough.
Now I don't know
about them big cities
but down here, were
nobody got nothing,
you get your ass whooped
over a fistful of dirt.
Now this here is the
story of a bunch of folks.
Starts off with two youngins,
no-count upbringing.
One of 'ems name was King and
the other they called Tyn.
Hmm.
[Metal voice] And these
boys, they had ripped off some
old goat and caught him
joyriding in his fancy Cadillac.
A buddy of theirs
squeaked on 'em
and before you knew
it, they was busted
and sitting in the hot
seat in front of the judge.
Damn if both of them
didn't get maxed out,
20 years a piece.
Which they would've
done if they hadn't
been approached one morning
with a business proposition.
-Wex--
-This is the real
deal, you know.
I'm listening,
go on and say it.
Alright, I can give you a tip
on the crime of the century.
Crime of the century?
[Wex] That's right bitch,
crime of the century.
What's that, bumping
off Quick E Stops?
Look, you want
to hear or not man,
I mean, you know, fuck no.
Yeah well I do.
Alright, you know that
old bastard Matheson Hoke?
What about him?
That old coot buried
himself with the key
to the family jewels
man, all of it,
took it all with him.
He buried it?
Honest to God
Almighty man, millions,
billions, maybe more
man, there ain't no way
of tellin' for certain man.
Shit.
Yeah I mean this is the
chance of a goddamn lifetime,
it's a fucking lottery in
the goddamn ground, you know.
Matheson didn't have no
heirs, didn't leave a will,
man and to this day nobody knows
what he did with
all that stash man.
Except you right?
Except me man.
[King] Alright Wex
what's the catch?
Don't cost all I want done
is to take care of Limonjillo.
Goddamn rump ranger.
I'm telling you man the guy is
on my ass all day, every day.
He's fucking everywhere man.
I piss, he's in the fucking
yard right next to me man.
Sounds to me like the
boy has got a crush on you.
Yeah sounds like
puppy love to me.
Shit I don't care
what it is man,
I can't take it much more man.
I don't get no sleep!
I ain't telling you
what I dream about,
you know what I'm saying?
Hey Wex, you like apples?
What's that got
to do with anything?
Well maybe old Limonjillo
will come over tonight
and fuck you up the ass.
How do you like them apples?
Ah shit man, that
ain't funny man.
You know I hate that shit.
Fucking assholes, dicks.
Cool up, cool up, cool
up, Cole's watching.
[Wex] No man fuck
that silly little bitch,
now look, this tip is
cash money man, I mean,
if you don't want it I got
others to deal you know.
I mean I'll take my
business elsewhere man.
So where is it?
Big shit we got a deal.
[shouting] Hey you ought
to get back to work boy!
[Prisoner] Fuck that man.
So how much you
say is in that vault?
Buttloads man, take your
wildest and multiply it by 10.
Crime of the century, huh?
You're the dumbass
of the century.
[Metal voice] Now a
load of folks might cast
a cold eye on wild ass
stories of buried treasure.
But King wasn't one of them.
It's easy to get bit
by the gold bug when
the only distraction you got
is counting ceiling tiles.
And King, he got
swallowed whole.
[background shouting]
[Tyn] Mmm,
gullible, shit ought
to be stamped on your forehead.
Don't cost nothing to
talk about it, do it.
Wait, wait, wait,
hold on a minute.
I remember that one,
yeah, it's usually what
you say about 30
minutes before I end up
flat on my ass with a
blue light in my face,
legs spread, licking
pavement, right?
What are you going to live
on when you get out huh?
Food stamps?
Cool down dick boy.
Step at a time.
[Officer] [shouting] Hey
wipe-ass this ain't no disco,
get back to work!
Yeah well how you ever
got laid is a mystery to me.
Not a mystery, right,
it's why I listen
to your shit in the first place.
And I'll be giving your
ass the walking papers.
Well let me tell
you something boy.
We're going to make it.
We got it all worked out, I even
took care of old Limonjillo.
What the fuck kind
of name is that anyway?
Boy's mama love jelly.
Got a sister named Oranjillo.
- And you got him to back down?
- [King] Uh-huh.
Told him old Wex had dick rot.
[snickering]
How did he take it?
Cried like a baby.
So what do you say?
Well...
I'll hold off on
them walking papers.
Yeah!
Just don't go get to
shooting off about that grave.
♪ [country music]
[Metal voice] Now you might as
well tell a dog not to bark.
See King is young, full
of piss and vinegar.
So of course he ran his mouth,
bragging to his friends.
...stash in the
grave somewhere.
[Metal voice] But he
kept prepping to bust out.
'Cause him and Tyn both
knew there ain't nothing
you can't get in the
joint, long as you
got the patience and the cash.
♪ [country music]
[cell door slamming]
[flushing]
Come on now, come on little
baby, come here baby.
[cell door closes]
[flushing]
Oh yeah.
[Metal voice] So
he took out a little
insurance policy
for the trip ahead.
Thank you.
[Metal voice] And next
he'd done the obvious thing.
Like I told you, every
man has got a price.
Only question is,
in what currency?
♪ [ominous music]
Come on.
Hmmm.
Get the scripts?
Yeah.
But uh, these here you
don't get 'till after.
There might not be an after.
Oh there's going to be
an after, a happily ever.
Well when you hit that
yard, you're on your own.
Guards will be shooting to kill.
Yeah, just as
long as you ain't.
I ain't decide yet.
Well I know
they're 10 for one.
But I will appreciate
you holding off.
Well...
Hold your hand out.
Why?
You want out or not?
Son of a bitch, what
the hell you doing?
What the hell is this for?
Rabbit's foot, it's for luck.
♪ [ominous music]
♪ ["That New Jerusalem" by
Doyle Lawson & Quicksilver] ♪
[breathes heavy]
[breathing heavy]
Come on!
[heavy breath from running]
[King] Been a long time since
I've been out in
the open like this.
[Tyn] What are
you talking about,
we work these fields everyday.
[King] What? Now it ain't
the same though is it?
[Tyn] No, you're
right, bigger.
[King] You're damn right it is.
Hell I wonder what old
Travis is going to think.
[Tyn] I couldn't give a rats.
[King] Ain't going to
like it, us out, is he?
[Tyn] Would you?
Knowing what he done.
Probably thinks we're
going to lynch his ass.
They say no one ever
escaped from Rutledge before.
-[King] Yeah is
that what they say?
-[Tyn] Yeah.
[Metal voice]
Now them boys knew,
that when things
got going too good,
the smart money
was on the blowup.
Tyn in particular
was tighter than
a hawk's ass in a nosedive.
Fortunately King still
had an ace in the hole.
[gunshots and ♪ country music ]
[Tyn shouting] Got
two coming our way dammit.
[Cop shouting]
There's no way to run boy!
[Tyn] Look if I go down
it's going to be standing up.
You better stop running!
Because I'm going to
beat the living shit
out of you for dragging
my ass out here.
[sarcastic whining] Hey
look man we can do it man,
I'm the fucking King
right, I'm the King...
I'll drop them.
Where the hell did
you get that? [gunshot]
Shit give me that thing.
[gunshot and glass shattering]
-Aah!
[gunshot]
[Metal voice] So
King's little surprise
got them out of a jam
and into the swamp.
Even a blind hog can find
an acorn every now and then.
You ever run?
Thought about running?
Ain't nobody not
thought about it.
[Priest] No I suppose not.
Problem with running
is, you don't ever stop.
Once you get up in
the ears of it,
you realize you don't
have anywhere to run to.
[King] Which way you
think we ought to head?
[Tyn] South, Mexico.
[King] Mexico, ain't no
one go to Mexico no more.
[Tyn] What they close
Mexico or something?
[King] Atlanta maybe?
[Tyn] Count of
two seconds there.
[King] Well what the hell
are we going to do in Mexico?
[Tyn] What they
always do in Mexico.
[King] Drink beer and tequila.
[Tyn] Yup.
[King] Speak any Spanish?
[Tyn] Not a word.
[King] Well I
guess we could learn.
[Tyn] Yep, learned
English, damned if we didn't.
[King] Man, I mean shit.
[Tyn] What?
[King] Goddamn jailbreak.
[Tyn] It was pretty
good wasn't it?
You son of a bitch.
What?
How the hell did you get that?
Don't you worry about it.
Well give me a bite.
What you didn't bring
your own vittles?
Okay, okay.
Here you go.
You greedy bastard.
There you go.
♪ [country music]
[King] So what are you
going to do with yours?
You know what?
We ain't even out the swamp yet.
You know you ought to
spend some time thinking
about that instead of
spending money you ain't got.
What in the hell
crawled up your butt?
Not a goddamn thing.
I think you'd be a
little more pleasant
since you got your ass rescued.
All I'm saying
peckerhead, is that I ain't
going go around blowing sunshine
when I got two days
swamp in every direction.
Plus being wanted.
So don't be getting
satisfied on me.
Because life will drop a rock on
your head when
you ain't looking.
Guaranteed.
[snickers]
You want to know what
I'd do with mine?
Car, piece of land maybe.
Piece of land?
[Tyn] You heard me.
What about a piece of ass?
Now you know, I ain't never
been a shit talker like you.
[King] A shit talker?
- [Tyn] Uh-uh.
- What just because I
appreciate the finer
- things, the romance life?
- King, shut up.
[laughing]
[King] Come on!
[King] You want to hear
something funny?
[Tyn] Mhmm.
It's about Jordan.
Please, girl is about as
funny as a cavity search.
You know her and I, we
used to go at it some.
Damned if every time we done it,
she didn't hoist her legs
up over my shoulders.
Her feet would be about
six or seven inches
from my face every
time we had done it.
And I would just turn
my head a little bit
and her toes would be
staring me right in the face.
And I could always tell
when I hit her sweet spot,
'cause her toes would
kind of crinkle up
and double over one
another and shit, you know,
like, like, she just
couldn't stand it?
You're obsessing
a girl's toes.
[snickers] You
believe that one?
Why don't you just
stick your little dick
in a fire and call it even huh?
[laughs]
One of these days, you're
going to figure it out that
a good woman, she
ain't easy to find.
And when you find
'em, you keep 'em.
You know what my idea
of a good woman is?
[King] What?
Be about three feet tall,
toothless with a
six inch tongue.
Flat head to put beer on.
Yeah I can see why
that might draw you in.
Oh Tyn...
I've seen her.
Hell we must've
been away a long time
because that sure
do look good to me.
[Tyn] Damn straight.
They got all the
fucking women's clothes.
No I see some unisex.
Come on.
Hey King, check it out.
[laughing]
Lord have mercy.
Hey, you remember
Steph Dean Maybank?
Oh yeah she was
a lot of woman.
She was kind of sweet
on you, wasn't she?
I never understood that.
Woman like her.
Well she was rode
hard and put up wet.
No wonder she liked you.
[gun clicking]
-Tyn!
-[gunshot, Tyn gasps]
[sheet tearing]
Oh.
[Tyn screams and murmurs]
[Tyn] Fuck I've been shot!
[shouting] Help, aah!
[Tyn moans in background]
Die shithead, aah!
[Tyn murmurs]
You are one stupid
motherfucker man.
You should've had
your balls blown off.
Yeah well thinking never
was my strong suit, was it?
[groans]
Is it bad?
-Don't freak out on me man,
that shit makes me laugh.
-I ain't freaking out.
-It hurts to laugh man.
-Alright man I ain't
going to make you laugh.
How does it look?
Looks like you've been shot.
Fuck man, don't
make it with me man!
Come on, just don't be a butt
hole, it's going to be fine.
[Metal voice] Now when
Tyn woke up that morning,
there's no way he could've
figured he'd be out
three pints of blood by lunch.
Sure he might have
had a premonition,
dreamed himself
naked and singing the
Star Spangled Banner at
the Elk's Lodge fish fry.
I doubt it, like most
of these in this world,
both good and bad,
he came from
nowhere and went
back the same way.
♪ ["Little White Church"
by Little Big Town] ♪
[Driver] So I picked
her damn yap dog up
off of floor, I
figured she wouldn't shoot
me if I was holding
her shih tzu.
But the goddamn dog can
tell I'm scared to shit,
because I mean this
girl was certifiable.
And I knew it wouldn't take much
for her to squeeze one off.
So I said: "Marlene,
ain't no sense in this!".
And she says: "You put
down my Licky!", she says.
I said: "I'll put
down your Licky
if you put down
that goddamn gun.".
Standoff.
But the dog is going
crazy, yapping,
tinkling all down my leg.
And the phone rings.
Ring, ring, and the dog
starts barking louder.
Yip-pip-pip-pip-pip.
So the bitch shoots the phone.
Across the room hits the thing
like dead center on the five.
So I take the dog and I hold him
over my crotch,
which was a mistake.
I think I got the
damn thing aroused.
So now I'm getting
nervous, so I say:
"Alright Marlene,
somebody is going to get
hurt here, I'm walking, you'll
thank me for this later!".
So I got to put the dog
down real nice, you know,
and Licky starts to hump my leg.
I ain't kidding man,
the dog is going nuts.
Jesus.
[Driver] So there I
am, heading for the door,
this thing flapping off my
trousers, you know I'm kind of
high-stepping it because I
figure that's the only way
it will let it go, you know.
Well about three
steps from my door,
my foot comes down
right on Licky's head.
Cracked his skull like
a damn pecan.
- Fuck me.
- And BANG that's
when she shoots me.
Hit me in the hip,
shattered the goddamn bone.
I got a plate in there
the size of your head.
I can't pass a metal
detector for shit.
So don't let getting
shot get you down kid.
You'll be alright.
At least you didn't kill no dog.
Yeah, yeah I'm back here
counting my blessings.
Ain't that a funny
thing, everybody
thinks they got it the hardest.
I ain't said that.
You didn't have to, it's
written all over your damn face.
Mm hmm. You boys got to play the
hand that was dealt to you.
Now those cops might
get you, they might not.
You just got to
resist that temptation
to get back on the wrong side.
Now I didn't learn that
until it was too late
but you all got plenty of time.
♪ [music plays out]
[King] You alright?
Alright you boys take my car.
You got to be kidding me?
Go ahead you need
it more than I do.
The insurance will
pay out so don't think
I'm doing you no big
favor or nothing.
I'll wait a couple of days
before I report it to give
you boys some lead time.
Well I don't know
what in the hell to say.
Ain't nothing to say, just,
help a fugitive if you ever
get the chance, alright?
We uh, we ain't never
going to forget this.
Alright.
Son of Licky.
Cass, you better get
your ass in this house,
them fish sticks are
going to be cold as ice.
Hang on Marlene,
I'll be there directly.
Something about a woman
who shoots to kill,
I can't just seem to quit her.
You all drive careful.
[knocks] Get on.
[Metal voice] Now you
might wonder where King
could take an escaped con
for medical attention.
Well, truth is,
they didn't have any
doctors in their
personal acquaintance.
They didn't know
anyone who could
tend to a living,
breathing person.
They did know someone however,
who could tend to a dead one.
♪ [country music]
Alright ladies, five card gut.
Deuces are suicide, kings
are wild. [background shout]
[Man #1] Boo, Boo
you ain't ante.
I didn't get me cards yet.
[Man #2] You hear about
Boo, the fucking Arab
aerial terrorist man?
-You know that my uncle
is a crop duster?
-[Man #1] The one from Henners?
[Man #2] Yeah the
Para Quad Express.
-[Man #1] Uh-huh.
-[Man #2] He took us
up one afternoon man
and me and Boo were just
fucking hanging out the doors,
brought my 12 gauge, you
know, and we were just
looking for movement.
Took us right over the trees,
like 200 feet up tops man.
So we come over this
clearing and I see
a fucking bunch of
whitetails, you know,
about six or seven
three-point bucks.
You know what I thought,
I had fucking died and
gone to heaven man.
[Boo] Hey!
Am I telling a
fucking story or what?
Fucking terrorist.
Listen.
So I fucking dive on
them all crosshaired man.
The buck went off clean.
Looking at Boo I scoot
over and let him, give
him the 12 gauge
and I'm like, okay man I'll
give him a shot right?
So he gets it ready to go,
he's ready to squeeze one off
and we hit this
fucking turbulence.
Fucking, just as like
as he fires, like the
plane goes like that.
So I'm looking down on the
ground for like a wounded deer
or something like
that and I notice
the fucking tire
underneath the plane man,
Boo shut fucking landing craft.
[Boo] He had
shot out the tire,
I didn't shoot out the tire.
[Man #2] I fucking hit the
deer man. [knocking]
-[Man #2] Huh
-What the hell?
I didn't hit the fucking tire.
Boo get that.
[knocking]
[Man #1 in baby voice]
I didn't hit the fucking tire.
This fucking Polack ass dick
motherfucking tire shooter.
Alright let's see 'em.
[Man #2] We got
three of a kind.
Ah, full.
[Man #2] Where?
I said one eyes are wild son.
That's a goddamn bold face
Travis, you said suicide.
Easy man, easy.
Purcell.
Well, if it ain't
the Bobbsey Twins.
Fresh from the joint.
Yeah, well, got us into a
little scrape as you can see.
Tyn here took one.
What the hell you want
from me? You know where
the hospital is at.
Yeah but the
hospitals don't exactly
roll out the welcome
mat for folks
like us now do they Travis?
Well King y'all is wanted.
And I can't be
violating probation
to be harboring no fugitives.
Let me tell you
something, my boy here,
he done time for
you and so did I.
Look King I got
legit business here,
this ain't no rest stop
for petty criminals.
Now you listen here faggot.
Now I already got a low
opinion of your ass,
don't make me act on it.
Well it wasn't a hollow-point
I'll tell you that much,
because you would be dead son.
Lot of people don't know
that, look at the entry
wound, got a lot of blood.
Hollowpoint blood comes
from the exit wound.
Don't touch the damn thing,
you'll get him infected.
Well goddamn he's bleeding
on the velvet Deluxe.
Bring him in here.
[King] Come on I got you.
[Tyn groaning]
Lot of people don't know that.
[Boo] What?
The hollow-point.
Aaah!
[Travis] They were looking
for you, on the news.
Said y'all might be heading
south, Mexico maybe.
You see that, we made the TV.
They have stickers
and everything,
said you guys were dangerous,
armed and dangerous.
[Tyn] Oh shit, King couldn't
hit the ground laying down.
[Travis] Cops were
around the other day.
Thought that y'all might
be heading back up here.
Shit son you got lit up.
Now don't just stand there,
you stitch him up or whatever.
Well I think we should
stop the bleeding,
if he got one of the vitals,
we're shit out of luck.
I ain't a fucking surgeon.
Well ain't you got
nothing for the pain?
Aah, goddammit!
Here you go boy.
Hows that?
Oh boy, I'm going to need
the bottle, give me the bottle.
[King] Now just slow
down, slow down son.
One step at a time like
you always tell me.
Take it easy kid,
just let the pain flow.
Get the hell out
of here with that.
Excuse me.
The police man, they're
going to come back here.
And Travis might be able to
hold them off for a while but,
it don't make sense for
them to get both of us.
Now don't you worry
about the police okay?
We're going to be just fine,
long as we ain't got
us no rats in here.
We need to tell them
about the hit for God sakes.
Well you just shush ok?
You're talking to pain.
Now you listen
to me goddammit.
I always watched your back,
even when I knew you
were being an idiot.
This ain't got nothing
to do with hanging in.
So I ain't asking, I ain't
suggesting, I'm telling.
You get in that goddamn car and
you get the hell out of here.
Come on, I want
to take care of that
little piece of business
we talked about.
I'm going to set us both up
and then I'm going to come
back here with ill-gotten.
You can bank on that okay?
You boys you take good
care of him you hear?
I'm going to be back in
about two days and...
it'll be in your benefit
to keep him breathing.
I'll do my best, but this
ain't
Marcus Welby.
Yeah this ain't Marcus
Welby, he ain't
Marcus Welby
.
Hey King...
Adios.
[heavy breathing]
[Priest] He shouldn't
have split.
[Metal voice] You'd a
done the same I guarantee.
[Priest] When chips go down,
you don't leave your man.
[Metal voice] Ain't but
one reason to leave your man.
That's for a woman.
♪ [country violin music]
[knocking]
[King] Hi.
Did you miss me?
Like a cramp.
You ain't see me in
three years and...
here I am in the
black of night.
What do you want me to say?
Well, how about uh,
"hello you handsome devil."
That'd be just fine.
It's over King, a while back.
Tyn got shot.
Is he dead?
No, I don't think so.
This ain't none
of my business.
Jordan, I got
nowhere else to go.
I know you still got
it for me somewhere.
Don't you?
Don't you?!
I'm a dog without a home.
[loud moaning]
♪ [ominous music]
[a man hums]
[Tyn] Tell me something.
About what?
[Tyn] Well say something
for God's sakes.
Tell me about your job.
[Travis] Ain't
nothing to it much.
Embalming.
You just drain the blood.
You drain it?
Just stick a big old metal
thing in a carotid artery and
just like a keg pump,
[plops], out it comes.
Ain't you uh,
ain't you feel weird?
Messing with dead
folks all the time.
Ahh, it's like anything Tyn.
You get used to it.
-It's interesting, I
take pictures sometimes.
-[Tyn] Tsk.
Of dead folks?
Yeah.
You're a sick bastard.
Ain't nobody to say
what's sick and what ain't.
[Tyn] Why would you want
to photograph all them
people you embalm?
Now that shit's
goddamn degrading.
You know you could tell a
lot about someone from
the way they died.
[Tyn] Like what?
[Travis] Like what
kind of folks they was.
[Tyn] Well what
kind of folks was he?
[Travis] That's a tricky one.
He does look a little flushed.
Neck end ain't right.
Boy got his chain yanked.
Jumped into the shower and
broke his neck and drowned.
I'll be damned.
[Travis] Well the kid
was careless.
Wasn't that way it
would've been another.
You're a keeper,
you know that?
Don't even try King.
This show is one night only.
Well, you are.
I ain't saying I've been
all that good to you but--
Good, because you'd be lying.
[King] I don't know why I
did all them things I did.
But then with Tyn getting
shot and seeing you again,
see now I realize what
a shithead I've been.
I do.
Keep on, I
ain't stopping you.
[King] I'm going
to make it up to you.
Because I got me a plan that's
going to change everything.
Tomorrow at this time, I'm
going to come back here
and I'm going to put
us on easy street.
You going to rob a bank?
Well you wouldn't
believe me if I told you.
But I'm headed for the
bigger and the better
and I'm taking you along.
That's a promise.
I ain't never got
what I've been promised.
You get me fixed up,
I'm gone at first light.
You need a hospital Tyn.
You ain't got long.
I ain't going back.
Well you're going to die.
[huffing and puffing]
Travis man, give
me something else.
Tyn what was King
saying about that money?
Tell me.
Travis, please man.
Come on man, I'm
sobering up man.
Well, you lost a lot of blood.
Don't, don't leave me man.
Ain't much I can do.
Man I shouldn't
go alone, you know.
Yeah well you come in alone,
I reckon thats how
you're going out.
Wait...
For what?
The grave.
What grave?
Ma- Matheson Hoke.
Supposed to be some... some loot
buried in his grave.
I just... I just ain't ready to
leave yet.
That's all, I ain't
ready to leave yet.
I wish you could
see what it's like.
What's like?
[Tyn stops breathing]
[swamp atmospherics]
[whistling]
Man you call this easy money,
I ain't used to no menial labor.
Cletus you lazy
son of a bitch.
Well I don't see you
on nobody's payroll.
Just shut the hell up.
Y'all be thanking
me when you sip
on one of them liquor
drinks on one of them
islands you seen on the cable.
[Cletus] I ain't thanking
you for shit if we get caught.
[Travis] We ain't
going to get caught.
[Cletus] Yeah that's
easy for you to say,
you ain't still on probation.
[Travis] Who ain't?
[Cletus] Boo.
[Travis] That's because
Boo didn't get caught
lighting a joint
at a damn Stuckey's.
[Cletus] Man how the fuck
was I supposed to know
that dick was a cop?
[Travis] Just
shut the hell up.
[Boo] That was a sheriff.
[Cletus] Same diff.
Good friend for
Jesus sake forbear,
to dig the dust enclosed here.
Blessed be the man that
spares these stones,
and cursed be him
that moves my bones.
William Shakespeare.
Shakespeare?
Hey, check it out, how come
Ophelia got a smaller one?
[Travis] That's what they
do when there wasn't no body.
Boo you're on guard duty.
I don't know man I got
the heebie-jeebies.
[Travis] Well it's just meat.
It ain't just meat.
It is too Clete.
That's Matheson damn Hoke man,
he owned the whole fucking town,
he is a crazy son of a
bitch, wasn't just meat.
Well it don't
matter what you was.
It do matter what you was.
Yeah well dead
is dead is dead.
That's the stupidest
fucking thing I've ever heard.
Well don't go getting mental
on me now Clete, okay?
Now he may have been
something when he was living,
now just tell that to the
maggots that's lapping up
his innards, okay?
Them worms eating his eyes.
[burp] You're going
to make me sick.
Okay when you
eat a burger Clete,
you thinking about
the cattle, huh? Huh?
Hell no right, you're
thinking about dinner.
In a similar fashion
that's how we
gotta think about our
friend, Matheson Hoke.
Dinner, okay?
So save yourself a heap of guilt
and get on the right of
mind perspective son, okay?
Perception.
I swear you're going to
make me barf if you keep
talking like that.
Yeah well it's just meat
and bone Clete, like you.
Burger.
[swamp atmospherics
and coughing]
[Cletus] I got to quit smoking
man.
Hey Trav, that curse on
the gravestone about the
dude who moves his bones?
You think that stuff
is serious man?
I mean you think that baby
Jesus is looking down on
us and judging?
I mean Hoke was a sinner right?
I mean it's alright.
[Travis] Come on now Clete,
come here on down here,
won't be long now boy.
Forgive us Lord we
know naught what we do.
[whistling]
[cracking tree branches]
Crowbar, crowbar.
Hey careful man
don't wreck it.
Who gives a duke?
I want the truth son.
♪ [ominous music]
Thar she blows.
[whistling and cracking
tree branches]
♪ [sneaky music]
Jesus Christ.
I don't see no goddamn gold.
[barfing]
[Travis]
The fuck are you doing?
I don't see no jewelry neither.
Check the pockets.
[footsteps]
[Travis] That's a weekend
at Myrtle Beach right there.
[branch snapping and footsteps]
We got damn company, Cletus,
get down here quick. Come on.
Damn what the fuck was
Boo doing up there?
-We got to fucking make a run
for it man, wait for my mark.
-Shhh.
[footsteps]
[loud thump]
Oooh.
Boo.
Cletus!
That boy is smarter
than he looks.
What?
[Boo yelling]
He smacked that boy
upside his head, come on.
[Cletus makes kung fu sounds]
[Travis whispering]
Oh shit it is King.
Oh no man!
Oh holy Jesus.
What the hell did you
hit him so damn for Boo?
Thought he was a cop.
A cop? Tell that
to the hanging judge.
How the hell was I supposed
to know that he was a--
Oh shut up Boo, you idiot.
Hey look feel
his pulse, come on.
-Oh nothing.
-[Cletus] Man you
ain't doing it right.
Well you do it.
Look you got to slap his
face around a little bit okay?
Put some pressure on his
head, stop the bleeding
[slap]
Oh shit, hell
of an idea Travis.
And good job Boo.
Goddamn grave robbing fuck.
Hey I don't force
y'all to do nothing.
Travis you said nothing
funny was going to...
-You know.
-[Boo] Oh Jesus Christ man,
he's bleeding pretty bad.
I'm going go get the car.
[Travis] Hey, what the hell for?
-Take him to the hospital.
-[Travis] Hospital?
Yeah man you can't just
leave him lying like that.
[Boo] The car is
two miles from here.
Two miles you hear that?
Well do something to him man!
Bang on him and plug his
nose up or something!
[Boo] Well if you
know so goddamn much
why the hell don't you do it?
Well I don't know how to do
it neither but I know that's
how you're supposed to do it.
[Travis] Well he
ain't got no pulse man.
[Cletus] Check his neck!
[Travis] Nothing,
like a lolly.
He ain't no pulse, you sure?
Yeah I'm sure, I'm sure
Boo fucking killed him.
I beat my dog harder
than I beat him.
I didn't kill him!
Goddamn this Travis,
this ain't no yodelayheehoo.
Just pipe down, okay?
Now look this ain't
the end of the world.
What the fuck you
talking about Travis?
Man, we are fucked!
We're going up the river!
We don't have a snowball's
chance in hell! We're going
to fry like bananas--
[Travis] Cletus
shut the fuck up.
Okay, you ain't helping
nothing for Christ's sake.
Now listen we got a jam here.
It ain't a little jam, okay.
It's a major fucking
pickle, right?
And we got to think
through this thing.
We can't get excited, right?
That's how people
always fuck up.
They get excited and then they
do something stupid, right?
Now here's the facts,
A, King is dead.
Two, we're fucked to shit.
And C, we got to get out
of here before someone
else comes, right?
Goddamn man I knew
I shouldn't have come
because I ain't never
getting off probation.
Cletus stop crying okay?
Now we got to take the
body, there ain't no choice.
Where you going to take
him, it's almost dawn,
you're going to drag
a body for two miles?
No Boo I ain't, okay.
But no body, there's no crime.
Alright homeslice.
So what's the idea man,
because I just don't see it.
Look someone
finds a body Clete,
you, me and Boo
are gone for good.
We got to put him somewhere.
Wait a minute
man, Travis, nah-ah.
No, no chance man, nah-ah.
Look, look Clete, we
didn't do nothing wrong okay?
It's just goddamn
bad luck, right?
[Travis]
You want to get put
away for this shit, huh?
Be my fucking guest.
Now where's the
last place anybody
would look for a dead
body, huh? Huh?
A fucking grave, right?
[swamp atmospherics]
You're a cracker.
[Travis] Goddammit, Jesus.
Son of a bitch,
teefed some wheels.
You're going to
take King's wheels?
You damn right.
Fuck fuck fuck me!
Be gentle, be gentle man.
[Travis] He's dead Clete.
[Boo] Whatever you
do, just hurry up.
Look Trav man, I'm not
sure if this shit is me.
Yeah Travis I'm not sure
this shit is me either.
Don't give me that
cold feet bullshit okay?
Now y'all dropped the tab,
y'all gonna to
take the trip.
You should stomp on that.
Oh really Boo, come on down
here.
[huffing]
Wait wait wait,
hold on a second man.
Wait, hey, shouldn't
someone say something?
[Travis] Let's
just get it done.
[Cletus] You
reckon he was solo?
[Travis] Can't
take any chances.
[Boo] Who the hell is
going to know him up here.
Oh you're going to risk it?
This ain't happening,
[shouting], this
ain't happening!--
Shut up!
Boo, take the keys.
Lose the car and no
BS, no screwing around.
I don't want you stopping
for a corn fritter and a
milkshake, you hear me?
[Boo] I ain't hungry.
[Cletus] Where are
we going to meet?
[Travis] You know my
old lady's land?
[Boo] Um...
[Travis] Huh?
[Boo] Yeah.
[Travis] A Barn,
southwest corner,
get back there as
soon as you can.
[Cletus] Mind you Boo, don't
mess up like you always do.
[Travis] Hey that ain't his
nature.
You need to be more
supportive of that boy.
♪ ["I Always Get What I Don't
Want" by Jimmy Murphy] ♪
[engine starts and choking]
[Travis] What the hell
could be keeping him?
[Cletus] I had me a great
uncle once, shot a man.
[Travis] Maybe he's lost,
had a girlfriend, got drunk.
That boy could fuck
up a wet dream.
[Cletus] He went a-running,
back into the swamp.
Didn't think anyone
would come after him
because it's hard to track
in the bogs, but they did.
They come after him
and they got him too.
Spent the rest of
his life in jail. [snifs]
They always get you,
don't they Trav always?
[spitting]
No they don't, not always.
Didn't get Jesse James.
He wasn't real, because if
he was, they'd gotten him too.
[Metal voice] Now Clete...
Was an expert at worrying.
Boy could out-worry a cat in
room full of rocking chairs.
But for once he was justified.
They had a man
bearing down on them
that was meaner than
a redheaded stepchild.
[Priest] No one
is past saving.
[Metal voice] This
one went past saving
and went straight to hopeless.
Because there is
devil dogs born,
and devil dogs bred
and when they die,
they'll be devil dogs dead.
[grumbling]
[whistling and chain rattling]
[Man] You are a tough
cookie, you are.
[coughing]
[Man] Get in there you, now.
Okay, alley-oop,
alley-oop here...
[Man making noises as he lifts]
Here ya go.
Ooh, stand up there now.
-Yea, how are you doing?
-Uhhh
[Man] You alright?
Lean up on that just
for a second here.
There we go. Come here.
Listen, thick noggin,
you know that?
Ooh.
[splash]
[Travis] As long as
we hide the spoils,
we'll be in the short rows.
[Cletus] Don't you feel even
a pang of guilt after all
you've done to that boy?
[Travis] Guilt is for
little people Clete.
I ain't done it, Boo is
the one that whacked him.
Yeah, but you crossed him.
Him and Tyn, it's
like I'm meant to go
do time at the joint and
you stole that goddamn car.
I can't change that.
They had my papers.
You'd a told him too.
[Cletus] Damn, you
cut the finger off?
[Travis] Hell yeah.
[splashing and Boo panicing]
Yeah, yeah, take it easy kid.
[gasping for breath]
Now, choice number one.
You hold on to what you
got, you keep lying.
[Boo coughs]
Upside is, you
don't betray anyone.
They'll remember you fondly.
Downside is, it's a quick tide.
[Boo coughs]
Th-t hey say drowning is a
particularly cruel way to die.
At- at first you can hold your
breath, it's a glimmer of hope.
But it starts to hurt, your
CO2 is backing up the pipes,
so you wait and you wait,
eventually those lungs
they hit that panic
button and start
sucking wind regardless
or air quality.
[coughing]
It's the water in the lungs
that sets off the terror.
Look at me.
Terror.
♪ [ominous music]
And this makes for
a final desperate
attempt to reach the surface.
Which of course you realize
is going to be useless.
It's just a finger Clete.
[Cletus] Ain't
nothing past you Trev.
Let me see.
Damn it's old.
It's got some of
that code writing.
Give me it,
give me that thing.
Man, just wanted to
look at it faggot.
It's foreign.
Well it ain't English because
I would've done recognized that.
Choice number two.
You roll.
[pissing]
Lose a few friends, aah.
[Boo coughing]
But you live.
[Boo splashing in water]
Mixed reviews
on that one.
[Boo coughs]
And now the third choice,
that's a tough one.
But there's no death, no
dishonor, just to live.
[Boo coughing and struggling]
You know a wolf
caught in a trap,
he don't think twice about
chewing off his foot.
You know that?
[Cole] Wolf wants to live.
You lob it off, I'll let you go.
Some things I'm
going to pay to see!
Here you go!
♪ [ominous music]
What guarantee I got?
Well you're to die if you
don't, I guarantee that.
I ain't tell you nothing.
Well it is your choice.
It- it's the critical
moments that make the man
[Boo coughs]
Here you go.
[Boo screams]
Smarts I reckon, huh?
Nothing, not a word.
Just the police doing
their usual bullshit.
They ain't on to us.
[Travis] How the
hell you know that?
'Cause Boo is loyal,
he ain't no rat,
he never ratted out in all
the years we've known him.
It was Cletus, Cletus,
[shouting] Cletus!
They was the ones that got broke
out of jail to, get that gold.
[Boo struggling and
gasping for air]
[Cole] Ah shit, my knife.
[Metal voice] Yeah well Boo
got the hang-tit on that one.
Back at the farm,
Travis and Clete waited
long enough to get
discussing it.
Then figured Boo
went on a bender.
But the truth is, they
was more interested
in what was on that
ring that wondering
if Boo would show up at the
trailer park in a day or three.
♪ ["Drunkard's Dream"
by Dave Evans] ♪
[Jordan] What were you
doing getting this Travis?
[Travis] I found it
in my old man's closet.
[Jordan] Ain't no
need to lie sugar.
[Travis] Or to pester.
[Jordan] Well its liable
to have been stolen?
As liable as it plopped
out a monkey's ass,
but I don't reckon
it matters does it?
Nothing against you Travis,
I just don't want whoever
owns it to come looking
for it and blame me.
Is it valuable?
Yeah.
It's an engagement ring,
see the stone settings?
There's a monogram.
There's a Hoke monogram.
Is that right?
Killed his wife.
Wife turned to itty bitty
pieces, didn't find 'em neither.
Think she was like a second
cousin or something like that.
Ophelia was just
a gold digger.
She married Matheson at
16, with him being over 70.
[Cletus]
So she couldn't satisfy
her youthful urges huh?
The old man was
firing blanks huh?
No that ain't it.
Story goes that Matheson
demanded that she give
him an heir,
or he's going to cut
her out of the will.
Ophelia found out
was she was barren,
couldn't have a child,
so she bought one.
Wow, she bought one?
Pretty much anything for sale.
And Matheson never
knew the kid wasn't his?
Kept it a secret, wouldn't
see him until she can return.
Rumor is he found out.
Son of a bitch
iced her, goddamn.
Nobody knows for sure.
Now these rings, they
usually come in pairs.
[Cletus] Oh that's right yeah,
they usually come in pairs.
[Travis] Yeah we ain't
got the other one.
Oh not even in your
old man's closet?
I could check but uh...
Well, by itself, it
ain't worth so much.
Not with just one.
Now with two then
you'd have something.
Oh?
Yeah we did seen that.
Do you speak foreign?
Oh those figures,
it's Spanish, maybe.
It's Latin, but
I can't read it.
Not with just one.
Well what's the fee
for translating, I mean,
if I was, you know,
to get the other one.
[sigh] Life ain't
all about money, sugar.
Can you get them both?
[Cletus] Man I thought
we fleeced old Hoke.
[Travis] I must've
missed the other ring
in all the excitement.
[Cletus] Come on Trav
it's shark week man.
Let's forget them rings.
[Travis] Them rings, brainiac,
is the key to Matheson's stash.
[digging]
You watchin'?
[Cletus] Ain't
nobody up here but us.
This is going to be
it Clete, the big one.
Bet you he is rotten.
Probably.
If he's half gone, I don't
believe I can stomach it.
Well dead is dead,
we've been over this.
Black gold.
It's his teeth.
[scratching from the
inside of the coffin]
Do you hear that?
♪ [ominous music]
That sound, that damn sound.
The damn scratching sound.
It's impossible, been
there more than a day.
[King groans]
Oh Jesus Christ,
Lord have mercy.
What the fuck Travis?
Shut up Clete, I got
to think for a minute.
But it's a
fucking miracle man!
It ain't a miracle!
Boo just didn't kill him.
We can't just let
him die, are you crazy?
Do I look crazy?
Now take a second to
buy a vowel!
Man you ain't in
your right mind.
Oh God King come here man.
[King] Anybody
got any aspirins?
Just take a few deep breaths
that's it buddy, you're alright.
Come on buddy, you just
throw up your hands.
[grumbling and stumbling]
You got swelled
up big like melon.
Water, can somebody
give me some water?
You hear that, the poor
bastard is thirsty and needs
some fucking water man.
He needs more than water.
Boy cashed his last check.
He ain't cash nothing.
Oh wouldn't know his ass
from a hole in the ground.
Travis what in
the hell happened?
Oh, King, we was
wondering the same thing.
Well I feel like
I've been mule kicked.
All I remember is, I was
walking along and then BANG!
Stars went out.
Uh-huh, that is bushwacked.
[King] Bushwacked?
Uh-huh.
By- by- by who?
Well, that is a good question
that's a damn good question.
Well what are you
boys doing out here?
Well Tyn had a hunch
that something was up
and- and when you didn't show.
Oh T- Tyn, is he alright?
Oh yeah yeah, well I
guess you could say he's
in a stable condition.
[laughter]
Yeah boys, he's tough
as a goat, Tyn.
[laughter]
Two go to Tyn's!
♪ ["One Way Track"
by Boone Creek] ♪
Look man why don't
we just tell him?
What that by accident
we shoveled six feet
of dirt on his ass?
Man it's going to be
worse if he figures...
-Clete?
-What?
Why ain't we headed back
to the funeral parlor?
Uh the fuzz son, we
got more cops up here
than a damn gun show.
Mmm-hmm.
We're going to see Tyn?
Yeah, yeah, just
sit tight Weevo.
-Yeah just sit tight Weevo,
that's a very good doggy.
-Ain't just a, oh!
Now look, look here.
Best case scenario he
doesn't figure shit okay,
he thinks we saved him and his
thrived to share the booty.
Man he ain't
going to find that.
Look Clete, just
imagine you spent 36 hours
in six square feet of room okay?
You ain't going to pop
out whistling Dixie.
And he ain't going to look too
kindly on the sick motherfuckers
that done it to him.
And I know King, he will
kill whoever done it.
So just go on and
plait your long hair.
Or meditate, whatever
the hell you got to do.
Man it ain't going to work.
Look Clete if you tell
him you might as well
blow your own damn
nuts off okay?
But I'll tell you one damn
thing, I ain't in the
nut-blowing business.
Woah, woah, woah, woah, Trav.
-You ain't going to
whack him right?
-Well we killed him one time.
It'd be a cinch next time.
[Metal voice] Now I respect
a man that's willing
to finish what he
starts, whether
it's a killing or
Sunday crosswords.
With bloodletting you got to
strike while the iron is hot.
[Priest] In the
heat of the moment?
[Metal voice] Yeah, if
the man stands on the end of
a diving board too long he's
going to lose the will to jump.
Can't let the sound of your
own wheels drive you crazy.
You get a man to start thinking,
most likely he'll back off.
But when it come to
Travis and Clete,
thinking in general was
a risky proposition.
So let me get
one thing straight.
Now Tyn told you all that
I might need some backup?
Yep.
So y'all went
out to the grave,
and you didn't find me so
by process of elimination
you just figured I
was in with old Hoke?
Yeah well, some folks might put
that in the miracle category.
Yeah we're just glad to
see you back, brother.
Yeah I bet you are.
What if I was to tell you boys,
I thought were a couple
of lying sons of bitches?
[Travis] I'd say prove
it you damn ingrate.
We didn't have to pull your
ass up out of that shit.
Ooh, look at you
getting all squirrelly.
[Travis] Nah I just don't
like them to bite the
hand that feeds.
Well I just got a feeling
that you wasn't out there
out of kindness
for your fellow man.
Well I just got a feeling
you ought to stick your
head stone up your ass.
Yeah you wouldn't piss on
your own momma was she on fire,
and the only reason you
ever let go of any nickel
was to get a better grip.
You was after the
loot, wasn't you?
Yeah fuck you bitch.
Then why don't you just track
down the truth for a change?
What happened to Tyn?
Tyn?
You heard me.
That's a negative.
That son of a bitch
took a dirt nap.
[loud thump]
[Cletus] Hey hey!
[scuffling]
Now you guys just
stop that right now!
Stop!
[muffled] Son of a bitch!
[Cletus] Oh, oh, oh,
oh King Jesus fuck!
[muffled] Goddamn.
Man I done told you we
should've told him the truth.
You killed him didn't you?
We didn't kill nothing.
Wasn't even us who whomped
you, it was fucking Boo-Boo.
-Boo done it.
-Boo wouldn't even whack
a spider off his own dick.
I swear to you, he didn't
mean to, it was an accident.
Oh shit.
You know Boo can get a little
squeawompish about things.
Oh and he put
me in the ground?
Okay, alright
well not exactly.
I guess we all done that but,
you know man Boo
whacked you pretty good.
At that point we pretty
much figured you was G O N.
You didn't have no pulse.
Jesus man we'd never
put you in the ground
if we thought you
wasn't already dead.
Goddammit brother I swear.
If the situation was reversed,
I'd hope you'd do
the same for me.
Hell I'm just glad
everything worked out.
Ain't shit worked out.
I ought to kill
you motherfuckers.
[Travis] Oh motherfuckers huh?
You're the one that
brought Tyn to us, okay?
Shot and half dead.
It ain't our fault
he kicked it okay?
Fuck listening to you
is what killed his ass.
Yeah it's true King.
I mean that boy was bad off.
Wasn't much we could do.
And then he told
you about the grave?
So where is it?
Don't know, we're
on the hunt though.
We?
I don't see no we.
Yeah maybe you should have
your fucking vision checked.
♪ ["My Little Woman, You're So
Sweet" by Doc Watson Family] ♪
There ain't no
need to get yourself
on the water, it
wasn't all the late.
I don't want to hear it.
Look, I got a
good excuse okay?
Well I'm sure you do,
from the looks of y'all.
[Cletus]
No shit Jordan I mean it's
a pretty fucking good one.
Honey I told that I was
going to come back here
and I was going to
buy you your own
corner lot in
Margaritaville, didn't I?
Well here I am.
Back off King, I
need to finish this.
Oh y'all can keep
the lovers quarrels
to yourselves if you don't
mind, we got business to do.
Yeah well something you
boys need to understand,
being businessman and
all, supply and demand.
Now you all got the demand
to know what's on these rings
and I got the supply
to give you the answer.
So then your question is price.
Why don't you give us
an invoice or something?
Yeah we ain't exactly
liquid at the moment.
I don't give credit.
Look honey, I got
you covered okay?
You got me covered?
Oh chill miss Dow
fucking Jones okay?
Now your boy here is trying
to give you a kickback.
Why don't you try
trust for a change?
I'm just going to keep these
rings until you get back.
Downpayment.
Only if you got
something to tell us.
You want to back it
up in here padre, huh?
As thy dinst love,
but only covet,
all the gold to
thee, my beloved.
Shit brain teaser.
[Jordan] Think again,
it's plain as day.
Looks like Ophelia
should've been
more careful about
what she wished for.
[Metal voice] You wish on a
star long enough you're bound
to feel the world owes you a
few twinkles for the trouble.
Just like old Ophelia.
Them boys thought they
had something coming.
I'll be damned if
they weren't right.
♪ ["King, Travis &
Cletus Breakdown" by
Antoine Silverman] ♪
[Travis] You don't think
she's yanking us on this one?
[King] Well I don't know,
it makes perfect sense to me.
I say we get the booty and
give her the shaft.
I say you better shut up
before I beat your ass again.
Hey hey hey, here
you got the crowbars,
you got burlaps, I got the
lantern, we ready to go?
We're locked and loaded man.
Then nothing to
it but to do it.
[Travis] Home
again, home again.
Let's pop the hood.
[King] All right. On three
let's put a hurting on it.
One, two, three!
[grumbling and moaning]
[Cletus] Damnation!
[grumbling]
[King] Holy
shit, there's stairs.
[Cletus] Yea! I'd like
Travis to go first.
[Travis] Shit
it's dark as fuck.
[King] Like the inside of a
dog give me that damn thing.
Move out of the way pussies,
only one way to find out.
[Travis] Only one
way to find out.
[Cletus] Shit.
♪ [ominous music]
You look a little spooked.
You don't look
too good neither.
Neither of y'all are going
to win any beauty contest.
-[Cletus] Hey!
-[Travis] What?
[Cletus] Remember that
story about that psycho
with the hook for a hand?
[Travis] You mean the
one that gigged folks
in the eyeball?
[Cletus] Yeah yeah remember
there was this young couple
out smooching in
the woods one night.
And the girl heard a
scratching sound and she
was like: "What's that?"
And the guy is like: "Don't
worry about it", went back
to smooching on her.
And then she heard the
scratching sound again.
And then they went home, next
morning when they woke up,
there was a hook caught
in their car door.
-Cletus?
-Yeah?
Shut up.
[Cletus] True story man.
♪ [ominous music]
Oh shit looks deep.
[Travis] Yeah was
this in the message?
Cletus why you crying to
me like a goddamn dingle
berry back there?
[King] You two ought to
get married you know that?
[Cletus] What damn
good is gold and whatnot
doing for anybody down here?
If it is here.
Well if ain't it's missing
one hell of a chance.
Well all I know is there
better be a damn stack of Ben
Franklins as high as my ass.
[whisper] Easy man.
[King] Let's see.
Holy Shit, wooo!
Hold these.
[Travis] Open her
up, open her up.
[King] Oh it's show time boys.
[clang of crowbar hitting metal]
That was easy.
[Travis] Well open
her up open her up.
[Cletus] [hissing]
Come on man!
Okay listen no bullshit okay.
The past is the past, right?
From here on in,
we're on the level.
- All for it.
- All right? Deal?
Got a deal?
Deal! Stake home!
[laughing]
You hippies. Okay,
let's get it, boys.
Can't see a damn thing.
Holy shit.
[Travis] Killed his wife.
[Cletus] Chopped her up
into itty bitty pieces.
Ophelia.
[choking and barfing]
Easy.
Guys!
Is it real?
[King mumbles]
[shouting]
We're rich as bitches.
Shit boys, haul in the
dogs and piss on the fire.
♪ [country music]
[shouting]
Woo, Mardi Gras!
We're rich!
[shouting]
Beautiful!
We got more money than you
could spend in a lifetime.
More than 50 lifetimes!
I knew it, I fucking knew it!
[shouting]
[door slams shut]
Damn thing is locked.
Son of a bitch!
[pushing at the door]
[mumbling and stumbling]
[shouting] We're
trapped, we're trapped
like rats in a death cage--
Cletus, get the fuck
out of my way.
[Cletus] Back off man!
Somebody!
[Cletus] Help, help!
["Help!" distantly echoes]
♪ [ominous music]
[Jordan voiceover] As thy
dinst love, but only covet,
all the gold to
thee, my beloved.
I never got what
I've been promised.
Ophelia found out
was she was barren,
couldn't have a child,
so she bought one.
The daughter, the daughter...
[gun being primed]
[Cole] Hi Jordan.
Those will kill you, you know.
Got to die of something.
That's true.
Sounded like, quite
a soirée down there?
I don't hear nothing.
Really?
Sounded like your boy King.
He ain't my boy.
Oh that's too bad.
I thought y'all cut such
a fine figure together.
I ain't taking you
aim to grave digging.
[laughs] Yeah.
I want to give it to
you this way sugar.
This is the real skinny.
You're circling the drain.
Fixing to meet your reward.
[gunshot]
[gargling]
I hate to tell you I told
you so, but I told you so.
[choking]
No no no no, don't try to talk.
Yeah.
This is where the road forks.
Me to live and you to die.
Only time will tell though
who got the goldmine
and who got the shaft.
[gasping] Fuck you.
[gunshot]
[moaning]
[choking]
[Metal voice] Last cigarette.
It's almost dawn.
[Metal voice] Dawn already?
Yes.
[Metal voice] Well,
we're getting towards done.
Like it says, good friend
for Jesus sake forbear,
to dig the dust enclosed here.
Blessed be the man that
spares these stones,
and cursed be he
that moves my bones.
And old Travis, Cletus and King,
hell, nobody ever found them.
That's how they went out,
buried alive in gold.
Just missing persons like
old Ophelia Hoke, a mystery.
Of course they found her and
Cole laid out by the grave.
He was already gone
her lying there with
the gun in her hand.
All the jury see was a dead cop
and didn't nobody give a flying
fuck that he was crooked.
Jury deliberated 22
minutes, that's all it took.
Now I'm going to give you
a little pearl of wisdom.
Don't matter how
you squirm or fight,
spend yourself trying
to get upstream.
At the end of the day every
man gets what he deserves.
Me, you, every man.
I have one
question, the child.
What happened to Matheson
and Ophelia's child?
[Metal voice] Their daughter?
Ain't no telling.
[door opens]
I will pray for you.
Don't wait up.
♪ [music]
[swamp atmospherics]
♪ ["I Heard The Angels Singing"
by Doyle Lawson & Quicksilver] ♪
♪ ["The Grave End" by
Antoine Silverman] ♪
♪ [Multicom Entertainment
Group jingle] ♪