Subtitles by explosiveskull
(SLOW SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(CAMERA FLASH WHINES)
(SUPPRESSED SCREAMING)
(CAMERA CLICKS)
(SIREN WAILING)
(CAMERA CLICKING)
Nice, Jameson,
let them hands go!
(GRUNTING)
There we go.
Come on!
Uh-huh, there you go, nice work.
There you go Jameson,
nice, baby, nice!
(DOOR SQUEAKS)
Hey, check it out.
Pete!
That's Marco Reign, man!
TY: Yeah, like that.
Hey, Pete, good to see ya!
How you doin'?
Are you still trainin'
the riff-raff I see, huh?
You haven't
changed much, Green.
(LAUGHS)
Welcome to the mat!
Well thanks, I'd like to
introduce you to Marco Reign.
It's an honor.
What can I do for you?
What's he doing here?
I don't know.
Uh well, you know, I
just wanted to show him
the old stompin' grounds,
we got a match coming up.
That big fight whether
Del Toro coming up, right?
I got a lotta
money on that match.
Oh yeah, who you got?
What do you think?
BENJAMIN: And
well, we were looking
for a sparring partner.
I'm just saying man.
I'd make a better champion
than that fool any day.
MARCO: How 'bout
that guy back there?
PETE: Which one?
The one hittin' the pad?
That's Jameson.
Hey, he's pointin' at you!
You might get that
shot after all.
(SCOFFS) 'Bout time!
Think the other guy holding
the bag would be perfect.
He's about the same
size as Del Toro.
A little older, but seasoned.
My favorite fighter in the gym.
Come on, come on!
Let's go!
He just wants
somebody to dance around
for a few rounds, you know.
I'm sorry to make it
such short notice,
but, if you can give him a try?
Sure.
Yeah, yeah, Jameson!
PETE: Come on.
Rip through 'em!
Rip through 'em,
baby, rip through 'em!
There you go!
PETE: Hey, Ty!
Come!
Come here!
Seriously, man?
Seriously.
Okay, we got a
photo shoot at three,
so I'm thinking you
shouldn't change,
you should just go dressed
as you are, alright?
How are you feelin'?
Alright?
Okay, let's make
this short and sweet.
Just, show this kid
who ya are, right?
They want someone
to warm Reign up
before his fight this week.
You know Marco?
I know his manager, Green.
Long story short, Ben
and I work together.
He poached my fighters.
That was a long time ago.
Listen, don't hurt him too bad.
Keep it simple.
Remember, this is
good for business.
I'll make you look good.
I promise.
You always do.
(SLOW BROODING MUSIC)
Careful.
Watch your face, we
got that photo shoot.
Do your thing, Marco.
Let's make this quick, now.
That kid's built
like a freight train.
Work that!
COACH: Alright,
do your thing.
Nice feint.
Stay in his face, Marco.
Hey, your work on
looking for, Marco.
(MEN MUTTERING)
PETE: Down, down!
Yes, yeah!
Get him down!
(CROWD GROANING)
(SLAMS)
(CROWD GROANS)
Round one is over.
How you holding up?
Nice throw.
I got him right
where I want him.
Just another day
in the office, man.
Do what you do.
Do it out there, man.
PETE: Okay.
MAN: Let's go, Marco.
Let's go, baby!
PETE: Four minutes,
left, hold on, now.
Take it, take it, hold
in there, for four.
- Come on, Marco.
- Relax.
Focus.
MAN: That's right, that's it.
PETE: Yeah, focus.
MAN: Go Marco!
(MARCO BREATHING HEAVILY)
Tap out,
motherfucker, tap out.
Yeah, tap out.
MAN: Tapped out!
Fuck, man!
Bullshit!
SHAUN: Easy!
Marco, it's over!
That's it, that's it!
That's over!
Hey, Marco,
- it's over!
- Punk!
- Punk ass shit, boy!
- It's okay.
It's practice,
practice, it's practice.
Shaun get our stuff,
meet us in the car.
Bullshit, man!
Yeah, come on, come
on, come on, let's go.
I'm sorry, Green!
Holy!
I thought it was just practice!
(LAUGHS)
You are something!
You are (LAUGHS).
That might not have
been good for business,
but it sure was fun to watch.
(LAUGHS)
Can't believe you
pulled that off.
I learned from the best.
Here you go.
You earned it.
Thanks.
You should head home
and get some rest.
Hey, Pete.
You think I could've
pulled that off
in front of a thousand
screaming fans
and a bunch of TV cameras?
I don't know, Ty.
I mean, to him it
was just practice.
Plus there is something to
be said for home advantage.
You're probably right.
Hey, Ty.
I think you'd beat him
if it really counted.
I really do.
See you tomorrow, Pete.
See you.
(PEOPLE IN GYM GRUNTING)
Oh, Ty.
Dude, that was incredible.
It was just a good work out.
No, no, no, no.
That was fire, bro.
I mean pure fire.
Watch, check it out.
I got it right here, watch.
(PEOPLE YELLING FROM VIDEO)
Being all that.
Come on.
You know, this is something
you could show your kids.
Whatever, man.
You know, let's get a drink.
I'm buying, come on, celebrate.
Look, I'm tired, alright?
I'm headed home.
Rain check on that drink.
Yeah.
Alright, whatever
you say, champ.
Hey.
Send me that video.
You liked it.
Trying to be all cool,
but you liked it.
Alright, you got it.
(FAINT AMBIENT MUSIC)
Whitney!
Whitney, come here.
You never guessed what happened.
I can see what happened.
Jesus, Ty.
Look at your face.
You should see
what I did to him.
Come here.
I wanna show you something.
Is that, what's his name?
Yes it is.
Look at me.
Damn, baby.
Look, I made
Marco Reign tap out.
I went toe to toe with the best.
I could tell my kids
that I beat the best.
Tell whose kids?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I say my kids?
I heard my kids.
I meant to say our kids.
I gotta go.
Kim called in sick today
so I gotta work tonight.
You're not gonna be
working that job as longer.
Well look, I'm
telling you Whitney,
things are really
about to change for us.
You know I love you baby.
And I'm so proud of you.
I just.
I wish you would think
about getting a real job.
Ty.
Come on, here we go.
Here we go with that
real job stuff again.
Can we not have that
conversation right now?
Hey.
You smile for me?
Stop.
Come here.
Smile for me.
- Stop.
- Yes.
See, that's what
I'm talking about.
That smile right there.
I hate you.
I know.
I just want us to
think about our future.
That's all.
This is our future.
I gotta close tonight so,
don't wake up.
(SLOW MELLOW MUSIC)
(KEYBOARD TAPPING)
(PHONE VIBRATING)
Hello.
Hello, Ty Matthews.
This is Ben Green.
We didn't get a chance to be
properly introduced early today
but I manage Marco Reign.
Yeah, I know who you are.
Thanks for recommending
Jameson to our gym.
Yes, but I have
a proposal for you.
If you could come by my
house tomorrow morning.
I'll text you my address.
Yeah.
Yeah, what time?
First thing in the morning.
And by the way, it
goes without saying,
no mention of what
happened earlier
to anyone today, alright?
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Bye bye.
Alright, well, I
see you tomorrow.
(FAINT AMBIENT MUSIC)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Hi, may I help you?
Hey, my name is Ty Matthews.
I'm here to see Benjamin Green.
Great, come here.
Please wait for Mr.
Green in the office.
TY: Thank you.
Yes, ready?
Okay, thank you, dear.
Ty Matthews!
Have a seat, take a load off.
This is a really,
really nice place
you have here, Mr. Green.
Thank you.
You got a little butterfly there
when he did a
little work on you.
Yeah, it's just
part of the game.
It is, yeah.
Have you given any
thought to your future?
I haven't yet.
Well, I think you're
hell of a fighter.
You got a lot to learn but
you got great potential.
What are you saying?
I'm saying I
like to manage you.
Wow.
I'm honored, Mr. Green.
I think I'm gonna have
to stick with Pete.
You know, I mean he's been
like a father figure to me
and I think I'm gonna have
to roll with him on this.
You sure about that?
Yeah, I mean I'm
very appreciative
but just feel like I
need to be loyal to Pete.
No, I get that.
Alright that just, so
there's no misunderstanding,
here's $10,000 and there you go.
What's that?
Well, if you're
not on my team,
you're against me.
So, that's a
non-disclosure agreement.
No lawsuits, no bullshit.
That's it, you keep your
mouth shut about yesterday.
Alright?
Alright, what if I don't?
Now.
Then I'll say you got kicked
in the head once too often.
What are you gonna benefit by
saying you got a sucker move
that you used to get
Marco in a headlock?
Rear naked choke
is a sucker move?
I mean Marco used that in his
last title fight against Lake.
Now listen to me, son.
This is a billion
dollar industry.
This is a business model.
Now, Marco is up here
and you, Ty, are way down here.
And I can't have you
me meddling in things
that are way, way beyond
your comprehension.
Now, I don't care how
good a fighter you are.
I can't have you
hemorrhage in my business
over a stupid sparring match.
Now, just sign that
and I don't wanna hear
about yesterday ever again.
How old are you?
Hm?
34.
34, well I understand, I
see you're almost at the,
the end of your prime.
And you got something to prove
and you haven't had a chance.
But this can be your chance now.
See, you just that.
And I never wanna
hear about this again.
Now, take the money, enjoy it.
There are two copies.
One for you, one for me.
There you go.
I'll take that one.
Sign the other.
Okay.
(FAINT AMBIENT MUSIC)
Aisha!
TY: Who is this?
VICTORIA: You emailed
me about a story.
TY: Victoria?
VICTORIA: Are
we meeting or not?
How about at Maly's, 10 o'clock?
I can do that.
VICTORIA: Better
not be bullshitting me.
TY: I made Marco
Reign tap out.
VICTORIA: I'll see you
at Maly's, 10 o'clock sharp.
I wish you would think
about getting a real job.
(FAINT AMBIENT MUSIC)
Now, Marco is up here
and you, Ty, are way down here.
TY: You think I
could've pulled that off
in front of a thousand
screaming fans
and a bunch TV cameras?
I don't know, Ty.
I mean, to him it
was just practice.
I think you'd beat him
if it really counted.
♪ Just too late ♪
♪ For tears ♪
♪ Our dance too late ♪
♪ Too late to cry ♪
♪ Oh but it's too late ♪
Ty.
- Victoria.
- Yes.
I didn't think
you gonna show up.
I know, I am so
sorry that I'm late.
Here, let's get a table.
You wanna drink?
Yeah, sure.
Hi, what can I get you?
Hi.
I'll have a Scotch, neat
and whatever he wants.
Buck on the rocks.
Got it.
Thank you.
(SIGHS)
Thank you for waiting.
No problem.
I'm gonna be really honest.
I know there are
a lot of fighters
that are better
than the big names
but they don't have
managers like Ben Green
giving kickbacks to the league.
He and I had a very
interesting conversation today.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I think this story
is the first step
to change the entire game.
For the record.
Cool.
Here you go.
VICTORIA: Thank you.
Thanks.
So, Ty Matthews.
Now that was a sparring
session, not a real fight?
No, I'd beat him
in a real fight.
Oh yeah, what
makes you think so?
Look, there are guys
that don't even wanna
lose in practice.
He's one of them.
Got a little too cocky.
I saw an opportunity
and I took it.
That must've felt good.
Better than sex.
Could you describe that?
The fight or sex?
Whatever you prefer.
(LAUGHS)
Well, I prefer not
to talk about sex.
Why not?
I don't think my girlfriend
would like it too much.
Ah, so you've a girlfriend.
Yeah.
You don't seem too
happy about that.
No, I love her.
It just we're not on the
best terms right now.
Okay.
So, we have to talk
about something else.
Let's talk about how I think
you need another drink.
♪ I love you ♪
♪ You love me ♪
(GIGGLES)
Yeah, I don't know
where I'd be without him.
How did you two meet?
Have you known him
most of your life?
My mom died when I was 13.
Pete took me when I ran
away from a foster care.
Well, he sounds more like
a father than a trainer.
Yeah.
When I had nowhere
to go, he took me in.
Gave me job at the gym.
And he taught me how to fight.
I'll probably in jail
if wasn't for him.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I think you should show
me how you beat Marco.
I can't show
people that video.
But I can have my guy
from the gym show you.
Well, I don't
wanna see the video
and I don't want your friend
at the gym to show me either.
I want you to show me.
Right here?
Yeah, right here.
No.
Yeah.
I want you to show me.
You know you gonna
get me thrown in jail
for doing it
especially like this?
You know I'll keep
your ass out of jail.
Don't be a pussy, you can do it.
Don't be a pussy?
Mm-hm.
I knew that would do to you.
So, I slid my arm
around his neck like this.
This is called a
rear naked choke.
Well, I like the name of it.
Then I grab my own bicep.
Uh-huh.
And lock my hand behind
his head like this.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Just like this?
TY: Just like this.
So, is this as
hard as you can go?
I can go harder.
♪ When will this pain be gone ♪
♪ When will this
life be through ♪
♪ Must I go on and on ♪
♪ Wanting the touch of you ♪
♪ Why am I torn apart ♪
♪ Breaking my heart in two ♪
♪ Why did I have to start ♪
♪ Wanting the touch of you ♪
♪ You've not come back ♪
♪ Yet I can't believe ♪
♪ We're through somehow ♪
♪ I never heard ♪
♪ You say the bait of words ♪
♪ That it's over now ♪
♪ I jumped my heart ♪
(MOANING)
I want you to choke me.
- Yeah.
- Here.
Harder.
TY: Harder.
(MOANING)
(SLOW DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(PHONE VIBRATING)
(ELECTRONIC AMBIENT MUSIC)
You're home.
What time is it?
12:30, something.
Come here.
Ugh.
Baby, you stink like booze.
Where were you?
I went out with
Pete for a drink.
And he got wasted and
spilled vodka all over me.
I mean how you that old
and you still can't
hold your liquor?
That's crazy, right?
Crazy.
I don't even recognize
this face anymore
without cuts and bruises.
I love you.
I know.
I'm gonna take a shower.
WHITNEY: Yeah.
(FAINT AMBIENT MUSIC)
(MOANING)
TY: Beneath your
head from like that.
Yeah.
I can still smell it.
Hey.
Where can I find Peter Mack?
You could find him
in the back somewhere.
JOHN: Alright,
what's he look like?
GUY: Black guy, red jacket.
What happened to your ear?
Man, I was getting down
with this chick, right.
She's hot too she used
to being grab my ear
and scratch my shit.
Maybe you shouldn't been
put in on her like that.
Come on now, you know
how I gotta rip with zip
for the team, right?
Come on.
Who's that?
I don't know.
Probably that's your boyfriend.
JOHN: Your Peter Mack?
Yeah, why?
You own this place?
How can I help you?
I'm looking for Ty Matthews.
He working out here today?
What did he do?
Oh, I can't say
but off the record,
I think it has to
do with a lady.
I think a lady has a gripe
and I gotta follow through.
So Ty, my goodness.
Ty and the ladies.
Yeah, well.
Come on, I'll introduce you.
Don't tell me don't
miss those days.
Yeah.
Hey Ty, this mas has a
few questions for you.
Ty Matthews, how are you?
Yeah, who are you?
I'm Detective John Beckett.
I just got a couple
of questions.
If you don't mind.
Pete, what's this all about?
You tell me.
No, it's alright.
I'd rather not talk here.
I'd rather go to somewhere
a little more private
like down in my office.
I'll be back inside an hour.
If you wanna come
talk to me, 'right.
You don't have to.
It's unofficial.
But you'll help me out.
Fucking asshole.
Not you, me.
You can't have this up here.
I was supposed to
check it in downstairs.
Have your permission
to look inside?
Otherwise, I gotta go
downstairs and check it up.
Sure.
Are there scissors
here or anything sharp?
Knife or razor blade
and where you cut?
No.
You know.
I got this ex-partner, Jimmy.
He's obsessed with
Asian culture, you know.
Like tai chi, martial arts,
married an Asian girl.
Anyway, he's got me drinking
32 ounces of warm water
everyday when I wake up.
I've been doing it for
like four weeks now.
The philosophy or the
ideology behind it
is that your body
has been sleeping
for four, six, eight,
10 hours a night, right?
You're completely
dehydrated when you wake up.
So, this, when you
drink the water,
it kick starts your
system and reboots it
and I'm telling you,
it flushes your whole system
because nothing in your body,
nothing there, it's like a
plunger, the water goes down,
everything out,
everything clean.
Hey, what is this
have to do with me?
Nothing.
I figured since you
were an athlete,
maybe you heard of that.
You're a boxer, right?
No, I practice MMA.
Practice MMA.
You hit people
for a living, yeah?
You could say that.
Would you say that
you're a violent person?
But man, what's
this all about?
Do I need a attorney
or something?
I don't know.
Do you?
(RECORDER BEEPS)
VICTORIA: So, Ty Matthews.
So that was just a sparring
session, not a real fight?
TY: I would beat
him in a real fight.
VICTORIA: Oh yeah,
what makes you think so?
TY: Look, there's some guys
that don't even wanna
lose in practice.
He's one of them.
He got a little too cocky.
I saw an opportunity
and I took it.
VICTORIA: That
must've felt good.
TY: Better than sex.
That's Victoria Mata,
was voice you heard on the tape.
You know her right?
Yeah.
What time was the interview?
10 p.m.
What did you do
after the interview?
I went home.
What time was that?
Fuck, man.
I don't know.
JOHN: Think.
I go home at 12:30.
You can ask my girl,
she'll vouch for me.
But the meeting with
Victoria start was at 10 p.m.
She was a little late.
Tell me.
The tape's only 30 minutes long,
what did you do in
the rest of the time?
She's a good looking girl.
Have a predilection
for fighters.
Maybe she added you up.
Flirted with you a little
bit, touched your leg.
You guys got a little
liquored up, maybe.
And she takes ya home
back home to her place
and things get out of hand.
One thing leads to another and.
What are you talking about?
Well, a predilection
for fighters
means that she liked you.
She had a thing for...
No, no man.
What do you mean things
things got out of hand?
(SIGHS)
JOHN: She was
strangled to death.
She's dead?
(YELLS)
(CHUCKLES)
Do you think I killed her?
I don't know.
Why would I kill her?
What was that thing
you said on the tape?
You said winning a fight
is better than sex.
Is that true?
Speaking of hydration,
I gotta take a piss.
Can I get you anything?
No.
Emmy set time of death
somewhere around 3 a.m.
Cause of death?
She was strangled.
The guy's an MMA fighter.
CHIEF: Anything
else like DNA,
tissues, semen in the victim?
We'll have it later tonight.
Forensics is working on it.
CHIEF: How about
the girlfriend?
She works at a nail salon,
I'm gonna go talk to her now.
You know it just works.
Get to it.
I know what you did.
You know what you did
so let's just cut the shit.
I didn't do anything.
You at least fucked her.
That much is for sure.
What do you mean?
Are you gonna sit
here and tell me
that nothing happened
between you two?
I mean she interviewed me.
That's about it.
How'd you do it?
Huh?
You get to do things to her
that your girlfriend
won't let you?
That's how it
happened, isn't it?
I'm not saying
another word to you.
And where's my phone call?
I wanna call my trainer.
You can call whoever you want.
But just so you know, Ty,
I will find out exactly
what happened eventually.
Enjoy your phone call.
Yeah?
Hanged up.
ANGELA: Whitney?
Yeah.
I need to speak with you?
I'm on my break, actually
but one of the other
girls can help you out.
This is regarding your
boyfriend, Ty Matthews.
So you said he was home
right around 12:30.
So, would you say
definitely before 1 a.m.?
Yeah, he was definitely home.
Okay.
Is he in trouble?
He might be.
Is that blood?
What?
On your shirt.
Oh, yeah.
I always get blood on
me from patching up Ty.
It's old.
Does Ty have any
new cuts on his face
or anywhere on him last night?
Ty has new cuts every night.
Have you told in there
what you just told me?
What, that I slept
with the reporter?
No.
Not yet.
But Whitney's my girl.
And I love her.
But it felt good to
have somebody care
'bout what I do for a change.
Do you want me to drive
you home or somewhere else?
Not home.
Listen, you have to
open up to Whitney.
Well, thank you very much,
Whitney, for your time.
Give me a call if you think
you have anything else.
(THUDS)
3:36.
3:36?
You got home
last night at 3:36.
Some detective came
to my job today.
Want to know what
time you got home.
What did you say?
I lied, Ty.
To the police.
Trying to protect your ass.
So won't you tell me
where you really where?
Oh, just sit down.
I think I'm gonna
stand right here
and let you tell me what
the fuck is going on.
I met with a reporter
that wanted to do
a story on me beating Marco.
You beating Marco in practice?
Yeah.
Then Ben Green gave me $10,000
not to post the video
of me beating Marco.
Who the hell is Ben Green?
He's Marco's manager.
Check the dresser.
Go on, bottom drawer.
(GLOOMY AMBIENT MUSIC)
Why didn't you just tell me?
Well, Green paid
me to shut my mouth.
Okay, I even had
to sign this thing.
This does not change the fact
that I had to lie to
the police for you.
And what is this
thing you signed?
We can't take this
guy suing us, Ty.
She was murdered.
Alright baby, the reporter
I talked to, she's dead.
God.
Police think I killed her.
Come on, Whitney.
I've done a lot of
fucked up shit in my life
but I'm not a killer.
But something happened
between you two.
Right?
I gotta go.
Alright, I gotta
go clear my head.
Look, when I come
back, we can talk more.
Just know I love you.
Very much.
I will never do anything
to hurt our relationship.
Okay?
ANNOUNCER: And here we are.
Here we are, the final fight.
The final round, round five.
Del Toro and Marco Reign.
Fighters, they're at it again.
They're at it again.
BOOMER: Where
are you from, baby?
MAN: Yeah she worked hard
for that much, she worked hard.
Yeah baby.
Give her that teaser.
Whoa, whoa.
Oh, we got it.
Alright boys, shots?
More rounds?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'll get that.
Be right back, boys.
Let me get out three
shots of whiskey
for that losers over there.
MAN: Get the fuck outta here!
Of course.
Just a minute.
Can you believe this fight?
Those guys over there,
they bet for the other guy.
Nobody beats Marco Reign.
It's my guy right there.
I did.
What did you say?
Did you say somethin'?
Speak up, boy.
That's what I thought.
I said I did.
Hold up, boys, hold up.
I got this.
Take your fucking drink,
get the fuck outta here.
Talking shit talkers, boys.
Think they can hit the gym,
think they can fight.
I would whoop up his ass.
MAN: Talk smart, Boomer.
Trying to mess up
our festivities here.
MAN: Nah, not
tonight, Boomer.
Doesn't he know
this is what we do?
He sustained wounds,
his first puck.
Come on, now get the
fuck outta here, man.
Let me ask you something,
you work on Tuesdays?
Yeah, I work here
almost every night.
You have to see her before?
Yeah, she was here
the other night,
sitting over there
with some guy.
This guy?
(HIGH INTENSITY DEEP MUSIC)
Boy, huh?
Fucking cocksucker!
(THUDS)
Fuck you boy.
Motherfucker-doo.
(THUDS)
I'm not giving this
gym rat a fight on TV.
Five million
dollars said you will.
You think?
You'll make more on this fight
than the last three
fights combined.
Where are you gonna
make that kind of money?
I got an idea.
Oh shit!
I couldn't help but the
notice the kinky shud.
A kinky shud?
Kinky how?
Like at one point,
he came from behind her
and like had his
arm around her neck.
It's a little weird but
didn't make anything other,
and it looked she like it.
They leave together?
Yeah.
(PANTING)
If you hear anything else,
if you remember something,
please call me.
Ugh.
(POLICE SIREN WAILING)
(PHONE BEEPS)
(PHONE RINGING)
Hey Jameson,
what are you doing?
JAMESON: Look
at you superstar.
Almost a million views.
Yeah, I sign
something that's saying
I couldn't post that video.
JAMESON: Oh man, my bad.
Just want people to know
who the real champ is.
You ain't mad, are you?
I woke you up?
I'm sorry.
Kit came back.
Yeah, Ty's DNA matches
the semen found in Mata.
What time did they
leave the bar that night?
The server said late.
So they flirted pretty heavily.
He's our guy, I know it.
His woman is lying to us.
Let me go talk to her.
You know, girl to girl.
Okay.
(THUDS)
Hey.
Hey Ty, Ty Matthews?
Can I help you?
Sure and you certainly can.
I am doing a piece on you
for the National Tribune.
I was wondering if I could
ask you a few questions.
May take a few
minutes of your time?
Hey Ty!
TY: Yeah?
Please forget about the woman.
Come, come with me!
Comin' now, Pete.
Hey, you know, maybe we
should this another time.
Okay, well here's my contact.
Just call me, stay in touch.
TY: Okay.
REPORTER: Promise?
PETE: Ty!
Close the door
behind you, would you?
Liked the video.
Well, I guess you
want your money back.
No, not necessarily.
Marco liked it.
So the two million other people.
Thank you for meeting me.
Have a seat.
Can I get you
something to drink?
Are you trying to tell
me that I'll need one?
Maybe.
So how does a hundred
thousand dollars sound to you?
Sounds like a lot of money.
Well, congratulations.
This is your lucky day, Ty.
They want you to fight
Marco for the title.
Finally get your
fight with Marco.
When?
Two weeks.
Our event, our rules.
You know that's not
enough time for anyone
to be ready for a
fight like this.
Yes, it is.
You think Ty
killed that reporter?
I don't know if he did.
He maybe has a legitimate alibi.
I will beat him anytime, any
rules, any place, whenever.
I was hoping you'd day that.
Do we have a deal?
Whitney.
I know this isn't easy for you.
But you know why I
brought you here?
I brought you to this bar
because this is the last place
Victoria was seen alive with Ty.
Right here.
This seat in particular.
This is where Ty sat the
night she died and you,
Whitney, you were seating
where Victoria sat.
I'll have to send
the details over later.
Pete, I assume
you're his manager.
Well, I have to discuss...
Yeah.
He's my manager.
Well, good.
I will leave you.
You guys have a
lot of work to do.
Got a title fight, Pete.
And then he reached over.
Kinda like this.
And he brushed the
hair off of her face.
He had sex with her.
His DNA matches the semen
we found inside of her.
This man, he isn't
who you think he is.
He's dangerous.
The man that you sleep next to,
that man is a killer.
So let me help you.
Are you sure that Ty
was home by 12:30?
(CHUCKLES SILENTLY)
(MELLOW AMBIENT MUSIC)
WHITNEY: What's
the matter, baby?
I'm getting a hundred
thousand dollars to fight Marco.
You serious?
I can't leave it, babe.
Yeah.
I've been waiting
my whole life,
for a title fight.
It's crazy.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MOANING)
Are you scared?
Ty.
(MOANING)
This is what you want?
Yeah, harder.
Harder.
Choke me.
Choke me like you
choked that white girl.
What did you say?
(WHITNEY SOBBING)
Whitney.
What was that?
You know I love you.
More than anything
in this world.
I love you too, baby.
Then why would you fuck her?
Jesus, Ty.
They found your
semen inside her.
And now she's dead.
I messed up.
Okay, I just wanted
her to do a story on me
and she kept comin' on to me.
Right, it's poor fucking Ty!
Right?
It's always somebody
else's fault.
I wish you had killed her.
Come on, Whitney.
No.
Funny, no!
Don't.
Good luck on your fight,
and just stay the
fuck away from me.
Just.
(GRUNTING)
How do you get in here?
Pete, I've been breaking in
this place since I was a kid.
Take a rest.
I'ma beat Reign.
(GRUNTS)
I already beat him once.
Green tried to scare
me but I don't care.
I'm gonna beat that fool again,
but this time, the whole
world's gonna see it.
(PANTING)
But I need your help.
You know I will help you.
I really do.
But I have to know
something first.
Did you do it?
Not you.
Are you serious?
Not you too.
I have to know, Ty.
How can you ask me
something like that?
I mean do you really
think I killed this girl?
You got to see
this from my side.
I have the cops comin' in
here telling me one thing,
Green, telling me another.
What the fuck did Green say?
I just have to hear from you.
What happened?
What do you think happened?
Just can't imagine
you would kill that girl
but I don't know.
This is crazy!
So fucking thing is crazy!
Listen, Ty.
You've been like
a son to me but...
Go fuck yourself, Pete.
Go fuck yourself.
Ty!
(FAINT MELLOW AMBIENT MUSIC)
(THUDS)
Unless she ask me
what I had on him.
I had it hard on him.
And I know you can smell it.
(LAUGHS)
Crazy bitches these days, huh.
MAN: Yeah, Joey.
TY: Joey!
Hey, what's up, Ty.
What are you doing here?
I wanna fight.
Sure.
Alright guys, we
got a fight tonight.
Place your bets.
Who wants to fight this
monster right here, huh?
What do you got?
Place your bets or go home.
Joey, let me have him.
I want to fight.
JOEY: You wanna
fight this guy, huh?
Yeah, why not?
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Alright, place your bets guys.
What do you got on him?
Bets guys, come on!
We got a fight to start.
We got a fight.
What do you got?
Come on.
Alright, alright, we got
a fight tonight guys.
Hey, let's keep it
real nasty tonight.
Dirty.
We fight till we drop.
Nobody call the cops,
nobody calls an ambulance.
Let's get this fight
going right, guys.
Let's go, let's
see what you got!
Let's see what you got, player.
Come on.
Get in, get in.
Who wants to get paid?
Ooh!
MAN: Get up,
- get up.
- It's alright, it's alright.
Get back in it, get back in it.
(GRUNTING)
JOEY: Come on, that
don't hurt, that don't hurt.
(GRUNTING)
(THUDS)
There you go, whiz ball, baby.
(YELLING AND GRUNTING)
(GROANING LOUDLY)
(YELLING)
Come on, man.
You wanna go home?
You wanna quit?
(CROWD CHEERING)
Come on, man.
(THUDS)
That hurt, huh?
What you got, man?
What you got?
(GRUNTS)
(THUDS)
Stay down!
Come on!
(CROWD CHEERING)
BETTOR: Get my cash in here.
MAN: I wanna see your fight.
(THUDS)
(GRUNTING AND GROANING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(YELLS)
(THUDS)
Okay, that's enough man.
That's enough, hey!
That's enough, man.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
What are you fucking thinking?
Take a rest.
Hey.
Ty!
He alright?
Still breathing.
Alright, so you got my money?
You nearly kill a man and
now you care about his money?
It's all there.
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait.
This is it?
What do you mean?
This is it.
Everybody saw the video.
Everybody knew
you was gonna win.
We're you talking about me?
You're a celebrity now!
Enjoy that shit.
Good fight.
Ty?
Ty, I never back heard from you.
All you said that
you will call me.
Yeah, I've been busy, okay?
Yeah, well I'll have
this just one question.
I was really good friends
with Victoria Mata.
And I was wondering if you
knew what happened to her.
I don't know what
happened to Victoria.
Alright, I'm sorry
for your loss.
Get him out of here.
Yo, my man.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I wanna buy a ring.
Now, do I know you?
You look really familiar.
Nah, you don't know me.
Hey, well, I'm sorry but,
I gotta ask you to take
your business elsewhere.
Why?
I just gotta ask you to leave.
I told you I'm
tryna buy a ring.
(LAUGHS)
No man, wait a minute.
That's why you look familiar.
You're the dude from
the fight video.
Yeah, yeah that's me.
And I'm fighting him again
but this time it's
gonna be on TV.
Yeah, man.
Hey, I'm rooting for you.
Oh sir, we have an
excellent selection
of gold chains over here.
I don't want a gold chain.
Okay.
I wanna buy my girlfriend
an engagement ring.
Oh, of course.
Right this way.
We just got these in.
Like to take a look?
I want that one.
It's a beautiful choice.
It is a very expensive ring.
Okay.
I'll wrap it up for you.
Where are you going?
Jesus Christ, you scared me.
I just need some time away.
Gonna stay with my
mom for a while.
(SIGHS)
You are not doing
this right now.
Marry me.
I can't.
Please marry me.
I've waited almost my
whole life for this moment.
But I can't even enjoy it.
Out of all the times
in my life I needed you,
you gonna leave me now?
Whitney!
No, Ty.
Let me go!
- Listen to me!
- I'm not fucking Marco.
Don't you ever touch me!
That look in your eyes.
You did kill her.
(MELLOW AMBIENT MUSIC)
(FRAME SHATTERS)
(SOBBING)
Turn the back
foot all the way.
All the way.
'Cause really the whole
body working, right?
Show me.
TRAINEE: Alright, okay.
- I got you.
- Hey, what's up man?
I really wished you
would've check on me
before you posted that video.
I'm sorry, dude.
Look, everything's
not a game, Jameson.
I wasn't tryna make it a game.
You know, you're right.
I should've asked your
permission first, right?
You know, I gotta
take a piss right now.
You good with that?
Hey, don't do that.
You're my boy, I'm just
trying to look out for you, bro.
Nice watch.
I gotta thank
you for that too.
Put some money in
the Marco fight.
They offer well.
Nice.
Where's Pete.
In the office.
Tryna get some work in late?
Yeah, man.
I know a great way you can
take care some of those bills.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
I know a fighter who's
looking for a manager.
Heard he's got a big
payday coming too.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Fight's comin' up soon.
I know you didn't
kill that girl.
I'm sorry for even asking.
Whitney's gone.
This fight's all I have left.
Well, let's get to it then.
We got a lot of work to do and
not a lot of time to do it.
Yes, sir.
(MELLOW AMBIENT
ELECTRONIC MUSIC)
(SUDDEN FAST PACED MUSIC)
ANNOUNCER: Marco
Undefeatable Reign.
Ty The Tiger Matthews.
The fighter whose
video went viral.
In an unknown location.
The battle the
internet demanded.
No crowds.
No rules.
No nonsense.
This time, it's official.
Exclusively tonight at 10 p.m.
Can you lose the glasses, sir?
So take me through
what happened.
I have witnesses.
Why would he do this to you?
He was angry over
some fight on TV.
He was upset that Marco won.
How was I suppose to know
the guy was a fighter?
What do you say to him?
Nothing.
He was upset I was
rooting for Marco
and he savagely attacked me.
The man is a danger to society.
You guys need to do something.
Were you hitting on him?
Hitting on him?
No.
We're at a strip club.
I was hitting on a woman.
Okay.
I thought you.
Uh-huh.
BOOMER: That's ridiculous.
Okay, we'll be back
in just a second.
There's no smoking here.
Either he's a bullshit artist
or Matthews' attacked him.
Kick him up.
Take his name.
Do you guys see
- what he did to my face?
- Yes.
- Alright.
- Would be known
I'd like to press charges.
I was thinking of that
would be the next thing
outta your mouth.
To the fullest extent.
Fill this out.
I'm sorry, can you
help me fill it out?
I have a splint on
my hand right here.
What's your name?
Boomer Craveli.
Two Os.
Seriously?
(DEEP SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(THUDS)
(DEEP EXCITING MUSIC)
Come on, babe.
(SUSPENSEFUL AMBIENT MUSIC)
(BELL RINGS)
Center up.
ANNOUNCER: To
millions have joined us.
Tonight, you're watching
these two go head to head.
Alright gentlemen,
obey all the rules,
protect yourself at all
times, follow my instructions.
Let's have a clean fight.
Touch gloves and let's do this.
JAMESON: Come on, Ty!
WHITNEY: Hey, baby.
You got him, Ty.
Come on, baby.
You ready to fight?
Are you ready?
Do it!
WHITNEY: Come on, baby.
Come on, Ty.
Watch out!
Come on, baby.
(THUDS)
Get up, get up.
(YELLS)
(THUDS)
Get him off you,
get him off you!
Come on baby!
You got it, let's go!
(THUDS)
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Get him, baby!
Come on!
(BELL RINGS)
(DEEP FAST PACED MUSIC)
(THUDS)
Hold him, hold him!
Come on, Ty!
Come on, baby!
(THUDS)
That's it, Marco!
(CRUNCHES)
Back to your corner.
To your corner!
(DEEP SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
Come on, babe.
(BELL RINGS)
(CAMERA CLICKS)
(THUDS)
Get him, Ty!
SHAUN: Hang onto his feet!
Nice feet, Marco!
(THUDS)
BENJAMIN: Come on, Marco!
(GRUNTING)
WHITNEY: Hold
him, hold him tight.
Get on him!
WHITNEY: Ty, that's it, yes!
Yeah!
Come on, boy, go!
ANNOUNCER: He's going
for the rear naked choke!
WHITNEY: Get him, hold it!
Yeah.
(THUDS)
WHITNEY: Hold him, Ty!
Hold him, Ty, you got him!
(CROWD CHEERING)
Yes!
PETE AND WHITNEY: Ty!
(CROWD CHEERING)
TY: Yes!
ANNOUNCER: I can't
believe my eyes!
Ty Matthews has choked
out the champion!
The champion is down!
(FAINT AMBIENT MUSIC)
(CROWD CHEERING)
JOHN: Ty Matthews,
you're under arrest
for the assault
on Boomer Carveli.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and
will be held against you
in the court of law.
You have the right
to an attorney.
If you cannot
afford an attorney,
one will be provided to you by...
What are you doing?
Back up.
What's this all about?
You'll be arrested for
obstruction of justice.
(SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Do you understand them rights
that I just sentenced to you?
- Ty?
- You have the right if might
you wish to waive these rights.
Ty?
Ty, what's happening?
What did he do?
What the hell happened?
This man at a bar.
He started a fight with me.
You're gotta be kidding me.
With everything that's
going on right now,
you couldn't just ignore
some asshole at a bar?
I know, baby.
You're right.
There's always
an excuse with you.
Always some reason why the
whole world is against you.
This time, you really
did it to yourself.
Got the money for your fight.
It's all going to the lawyer.
Who you gonna blame for that?
Whitney.
I love you, baby.
I love you too.
It's just not enough, sometimes.
I gotta go.
I'll try to come
and visit you soon.
I just need some time
to clear my head.
You're a trained killer
who brutally assaulted a man
outside a bar.
And now you're going
to jail for it.
And while you're
doing time for that,
I'm gonna get you
for Victoria Mata.
WARDEN: You have a visitor.
You're making
yourself comfortable.
What are you doing here?
I came here to see the
fighter that turned me down.
You should've
honored our contract.
But like I said before,
if you're not on our team,
you're against us.
But I wanna thank you for
a great show (CHUCKLES).
You're a hell of a fighter.
I won that fight.
Yeah, I know you won the
fight and lost the war.
Hey, if you wanna be a winner,
you gotta know the game,
your plan and the rules.
Like your buddy.
Jameson?
Ah, he's a winner.
And young and strong.
He knows the game.
(FAINT BROODING MUSIC)
Oh, he would do anything
the be a champion.
You know, there's a lot of money
to be made in this business.
And I make my money by
any means necessary.
(BROODING AMBIENT MUSIC)
You killed her, didn't
you, you motherfucker.
Some have a shelf life
just longer than others.
(BROODING AMBIENT MUSIC)
Like I told you.
Don't fuck with things
that are way beyond
your comprehension.
I'm gonna get outta here.
(SCOFFS)
And when I do, I'm
gonna kill you.
I don't think
you're taking this in.
See, this is your home now.
This cage is the only place
you're gonna be
fighting for a while.
Why'd you do this to me?
I hate to lose.
I take it personally.
You take care, champ.
We have here this
evening, Marco Reign.
Of course, I'm still champ.
That punk got lucky.
I'll fight that guy
again anytime, any place.
That's including prison.
(SORROWFUL AMBIENT MUSIC)
TY: What happened
to your ear?
Man, I was getting down
with this chick, right.
She's hot too she used
to being grab my ear
and scratch my shit.
TY: I really wished
you would've check on me
before you posted that video.
JAMESON: You're my boy,
I'm just trying to
look out for you, bro.
TY: Nice watch.
I gotta thank
you for that too.
Put some money in
the Marco fight.
They offer well.
(BROODING AMBIENT MUSIC)
Subtitles by explosiveskull