That's her, all right.
Captain...
Why don't we
just go in there
and pull her out?
It's the mayor's
daughter, Harris.
One false move
and the whole thing
crumbles.
The ransom note said
the place was booby-trapped.
We go waltzing in there,
house goes boom,
dead mayor's daughter.
Not on my watch.
I guess it's up
to Garrett now.
Unfortunately.
You don't think he's up to it?
It's a simple money exchange.
He takes the money
to the warehouse.
The kidnappers
tell us the safe way in.
Yeah, he's up to it.
The problem is,
he'll do it his way.
Sam Garrett always
has to do it his way.
Man:
we should keep
all the money,
let that little bitch
stew inside the house.
No way.
We don't fuck
the boss.
We follow the plan,
or it's our asses.
How are you doing?
I wasn't supposed to hear
that little interchange,
was I?
Well, you know,
actually...
What the fuck
was that?
Come on.
Let's check it.
( engine starts )
Go, go!
Is this Compton or East LA?
Gotta be Compton.
( gunfire continues )
( hissing )
Aaah!
Something's wrong.
I can feel it.
( horn honking )
( honking )
( gunfire )
This is not good.
That's it!
I'm moving to Lauderdale!
- Something's happening.
- What is it?
I don't know.
I can't see her anymore.
( helicopter overhead )
You didn't make the exchange.
I don't have time to explain.
- You're ad-libbing again,
Sam.
- Yeah, I know.
- Is the girl still in there?
- We don't know.
I would like to know why
you've chosen once again
to directly disobey...
Where the hell do you think
you're going?!
Son of a...
( helicopter whirrs )
( muffled noise )
( ringing )
Oh, you bastards.
Fuck the boss.
Sam:
My, my, my.
What language
you young people use.
You learn
to talk like that
in private school?
Or just how
to shake down
your old man?
- A phony kidnap scheme.
- Do you know who I am?
I'm the fucking
mayor's daughter.
You have the right
to remain silent,
which I suggest
you do.
- You can't do this to me!
- Well, I'm doing it.
What is it?
You get the call
after the money drop,
disappear,
and then it's "missing
and presumed dead"?
Is that it?
There's a bomb
on that table.
I know it's a bomb.
I've seen millions
of these.
Look... Start, stop.
Stop.
No stop?
Get down!
Here they come.
Sam:
get down!
( people yelling )
What the fuck
is going on?
Get the cuffs
off of her.
Captain, she staged
this whole thing.
- They're hurting me.
- Shut up.
That's the mayor's daughter.
The kidnap victim.
You got proof?
You got witnesses? Anything?
- Where's my father?
- I said, shut up.
Captain...
Captain, listen.
I'm going through
a transitional period
in my life right now.
I need to know that both
emotionally and financially,
I'm going to have
the continued
and unwavering
support of the LAPD.
- You're full of shit.
- I know.
I've got no options.
I've got to investigate.
It's political.
She's the mayor's daughter.
That's what she said
when she blew up the house.
Take unpaid suspension,
collect unemployment.
That's the best I can do
until I sort this out.
Let me take the case
and I can sort it out.
- I can't do that!
- There's perps out there
with submachine guns!
She wasn't
in this thing alone.
Sam, you'd be a hell of a cop
except for one thing...
You do not know
when to quit.
Where's my dad?
Both:
Shut up!
( ringing )
Yeah.
Female voice:
this is Ready Credit
calling for Sam Garrett.
( fake Chinese accent )
Oh... Mr. Garrett,
he no here!
He go very far away!
Long, long trip!
Two, maybe
three month! Yeah.
Call back two,
maybe three month.
Thank you. Bye bye.
Female voice:
I need to leave him
a message, sir.
( wrapper crinkling )
Go away!
Nobody's home.
Breaking and entering
is against the law,
you know.
Want a beer?
You need to upgrade
your lifestyle a bit.
I can't
afford a lifestyle,
thanks to you.
What's the story
on the mayor's daughter?
Nothing.
She's in therapy.
We can't get at
the case files.
So basically,
I'm screwed.
Be patient, son.
In the meantime,
I've got
a proposition
for you.
How would you
like to become
a big TV star?
"The world's drunkest
out-of-work cops"?
Captain:
I'm serious, Sam.
I've got a friend
who's producing
one of these new
reality TV shows.
You know, a bunch of idiots
stuck on an island together.
I know.
The winner gets to be
on "Celebrity Checkers"
and the loser goes
on the Shopping Channel.
I don't think so,
Ellis.
Look.
His cast is not playing well
with the test audiences.
They're not heroic enough.
He thought if he could add
a real live, red-blooded,
all-American cop into
the mix, he could improve
his demographics.
He asked me
if I could spare one.
You I can spare.
What's the pay?
The grand prize
is 10 million bucks...
If you win.
Plus, you get 30 grand
to spend one week
in a tropical
Pacific paradise.
Why me?
What's the catch?
There's no catch.
The producer is
a friend of mine.
That's very nice, Captain.
I appreciate your generosity.
But what's in it
for you?
All right.
The same producer has
made me a tentative offer.
You've got to keep this
to yourself.
My landlord
and I aren't speaking.
Who am I going to tell?
I am going to be
the new host
of "The World's Biggest
Police Busts."
It's a great salary,
it's a nice nest egg.
Do me this favor,
and I will find a way
to get you back on the force,
with full back pay.
Let me think
about it.
( phone rings )
Recording:
This is Garrett,
leave a message.
Female voice:
This is the Acme Finance
Company, Mr. Garrett.
We would appreciate it
if you'd call us...
( machine stops )
What's the show called?
"Treasure Hunt."
Host:
A tropical island...
Beautiful sandy beaches,
fabulous Pacific sunsets,
waves lapping upon
silky untrodden shores.
And hidden somewhere
among it all...
$10 million in cash.
Now, let's meet
our contestants:
here comes Mindi Rain,
professional fashion model
from Chicago;
John Turner,
a security guard from Texas.
The lovely Tina Mason
works in a Los Angeles
used record store
and rescues stray dogs
in her spare time.
Phillip Edwards,
retired Navy SEAL
with three tours
of duty in Vietnam,
and the beautiful Kim Nelson,
a teacher from New York
who owns her own school.
How about that Steven Chaney?
A newspaper reporter
with a degree in English
Literature.
Susan Billings,
a stockbroker
and marathon runner,
and a genuine American hero,
detective Sam Garrett,
on special leave
from the LAPD.
Modern day pirates,
stranded on a deserted island.
One week to stay alive,
or maybe die trying.
And they're all here
for... A "Treasure Hunt"!
That's right.
I like that.
God, we look great.
Speak for yourself.
I don't know, I thought
you looked stunning.
Yeah, really hot.
Why don't you boys
put your brains
back in your pants,
where they belong,
and we'll all
get along just fine.
- Thanks for the help, pal.
- What did I say?
( glass clinking )
You people...
The most famous people
on network television.
In less than 24 hours,
you're gonna be marooned
on a beautiful
island paradise.
And here's
executive producer,
Stuart McMahon,
to tell you why.
- Thanks, Jack.
- You bet.
And thank all of you
for joining our treasure hunt.
I'm very glad you're here.
And I think
we all know why we've come.
For $10 million,
in cash,
buried somewhere
on Palm Key Island.
You will all be given
treasure maps
with certain
key clues missing,
and a piece of parchment,
with a pirate's poem.
These final clues,
they might be the ones
that help you land
the treasure.
It's all in
your travel bags.
Good hunting,
and try to stay alive.
What do they mean,
"try to stay alive"?
I wasn't aware of anything
in our contract
that would allow you to put us
in any kind of danger.
No, no. It's all
in good fun, Ms. Mason.
- Jack, explain.
- Certainly, Stu.
We have hired our own...
"Pirates."
They're ex-Navy SEALs,
and their job
is to take you all
out of the hunt.
They're silent and deadly.
You will not hear a sound
until they take you down.
You sure this isn't cable?
Oh, no.
It's perfectly harmless.
They carry paintball guns.
The paintballs
just sting a little bit.
Besides,
we can't really
let them kill you,
because this show airs
during the family hour.
That's it folks.
Eat, drink, enjoy...
This is the last good meal
you're gonna have in days.
Congratulations.
Can I talk to you
for a minute, Stuart?
Yeah, sure.
If this is about
another cash advance...
- No, no, Stu.
- Forget it.
I'm not helping you out
of any more financial messes.
I got you this job,
that's enough.
I'm not going to ask you
for more money, Stu.
I've got everything
taken care of now.
I want to thank you...
For your generosity.
Okay. That's fine.
I'm glad to do it.
Anyway, get to bed,
all right?
You've got a busy day
tomorrow.
Everything's
taken care of, Stu.
Thank you.
Thanks.
I'm sorry
about that exchange
at the table.
I got a little annoyed
at that Turner guy.
That's all right.
He just had too much to drink.
As a matter of fact,
so have I.
You meant well
and it was a nice
thing to say.
I shouldn't have
overreacted.
It's the world we live in.
If I had done that
in the workplace,
you could have me fired
for sexual harassment.
For the next week,
this is the workplace.
And in my office you can
say anything you'd like.
It just better be good.
I'll do my best.
So, why are you doing this?
I was running low
on beer and hot dogs.
How about you?
Looking for your 15 minutes?
Maybe.
This is gonna be
a boatload of fun.
You folks ready
to get it on?
Turner:
this isn't exactly
what I expected.
This isn't
what we saw last night.
Can't we wait
until it's nice?
You want nice?
Go on vacation.
This is
national television.
We got six days.
That helicopter is heading
to the other side
of the island,
where the showers,
the wet bar,
and the hot food are located.
The first to find the treasure
gets to enjoy that side,
until the chopper
takes you back
to civilization.
Some of us have jet lag
and a little hangover.
What's to keep us from hiking
to the other side
and taking a nap
and a shower?
We do have you outnumbered.
And we sign the paychecks.
Remember that. Play along.
Enjoy yourselves.
The crew and I will stay
with you at base camp,
through the trees.
And I can promise you
that our huts,
well, at least mine,
is just a little bit nicer
than yours.
How nice?
We have to maintain climate
control in my hut.
That's where
the satellite uplink
is located
for the day's tape.
We're going to be shooting
videotape of all of you
as you get used
to your surroundings
and start the treasure hunt.
I promise you.
You're gonna forget
we're even there.
All right?
Let's make some TV!
Come on!
Watch it up ahead.
It's narrow, okay?
I don't want to lose
any of you right off the bat.
Let's go!
- Come on! Move it!
- We're coming!
How are you gonna survive
a week like this?
What's with all these huts?
Why so many?
There must be 50 of them.
Ladies and gentleman,
these huts were built for
last year's
multimillion dollar
blockbuster hit...
"Monkey See, Monkey Do."
- I hated that movie.
- At least they're
still standing.
All right, it's time for you
to split into teams.
Start strategizing.
Let's find some treasure!
Strategizing?
That's probably
the longest word he knows.
All right, teams,
come on.
This is going to be
a piece of cake.
I've seen guys like this
in the service.
They're wimps.
Since you've made me
the team leader,
I think we should
come up with a plan.
If we're going to play,
we might as well play hard.
This is war.
Let's huddle up.
No touching.
Only my dogs
get to do that.
It's just instinct.
I'm a herding animal.
Relax.
He's being cute.
Gender traitor.
Oh, God!
I think she digs me.
It's a good start.
Julie?
- What satellite are we
bouncing off of?
- Westar 3.
I'm rolling
the show open now
for levels.
Give me
a schedule rundown.
7:00 p.m.... Jack sends
the unedited video
from today's tape to us
via satellite uplink.
We'll start cutting
into the first episode
for airing on Friday.
Jack does a live stand-up
Friday with the cast to close
the show.
And what about
tonight's show?
Tonight's episode
is a bio piece,
scheduled to promote
the Friday premiere.
So we've got
edited interviews,
B-rolls on contestants,
profiles, etcetera.
That's all tape.
I want something live tonight.
Already taken care of.
We'll cut to a live shot
of the island, followed
by some of today's tape.
Don't give away
any secrets.
No, no, it's video
of the contestants
on the beach,
moving into their huts,
stuff like that.
Call Jack. See if he can do
a live stand-up intro
to tonight's show.
More immediacy.
That's what we need.
I don't know if he can.
The island's got bars up.
I'm getting a little noise.
I can't guarantee a clean
signal.
- It must be the weather.
- I didn't know we were
expecting any.
All right, I'll go see Bill
at the forecast center.
All right.
Summer of 1968...
That was the last one?
All right.
Thanks, Danny.
All right, Bill.
Tell me some good news.
I've got my eye
on a system.
A big weather system
just east of Midway.
Is it a storm?
It will be as soon as
this small air mass
from the south hits
the main front... Then boom.
- But it's not a storm.
- No. Not yet.
Just give it time.
You just tell me when
it is a storm, will you?
The ratings
for the pre-show special
were through the roof.
I'll be damned
if I'm going to blow that
on a few drops of rain.
Hell, a typhoon will be good
for the ratings.
Big waves mean big numbers.
I'm not sure we can justify
risking people's lives
over ratings.
It ain't "we," it's me.
Our audience wants to see
these people in jeopardy.
They want to see the cast
picked off one by one.
And I always give
my audience what they want.
If you're not careful,
they're all gonna get
picked off that island,
at once.
Hey.
Drinking?
It gets me
through the day.
Day's over.
You see?
It works.
- What are you reading?
- It's Bloody Morgan's
biography.
He wrote it himself
in an English prison.
All these pirates
fancied themselves poets.
I guess on-board ship
there was nothing better
to do.
Except each other.
What's it got to do with us?
They like
to sprinkle clues
into the verses.
Like, "A place for
stout ship and sail,
where the four winds
never find.
Due west
from Kingston jail,
golden bounty
in kind."
It's a description of
a lagoon,
surrounded by palm trees,
off the coast
of Jamaica.
It's where Bloody Morgan's
treasure was buried.
The same kind of clues
in this parchment.
You think understanding
this pirate stuff
is gonna help you find
the treasure?
It could.
I don't know.
It's a theory.
But if I work
this out properly,
we could get to that treasure
before anyone else.
If I were you,
I'd keep it to myself.
You've got to be careful
what you say around here.
There's a lot of money
at stake.
As a cop you develop
an instinct about people?
Sort of a feeling
in your gut?
Sometimes.
Usually it just turns out
to be gas.
But I think it's still safe
to be suspicious of everybody.
As a matter
of fact,
for the next
couple of weeks,
I think
a little paranoia
is justifiable.
You know
what I mean?
Gotcha.
You really lord this police
stuff over all of us,
don't you?
Just because you're
team leader? I hate cops.
Everybody hates cops.
I hate cops.
I saw what you
did to that man.
You scared him to death.
Am I forgetting something?
Aren't you and I supposed
to be on the same team?
You saw everybody
listening to us.
Your cash split would be
better if you slimmed down
the team.
Get that poor man
so paranoid,
one of those
ex-Navy SEALs gets him.
I suppose you've made
your alliance
with your favorite
cast members...
Like that
Susan bitch.
You know, Tina,
you've been watching
way too much reality TV.
Whatever.
- Just a second.
- Sure.
Do you think there's
a storm coming?
I don't know.
Clouds are coming in.
It's getting windy.
I can hear
the breakers building.
Could be.
So, what was that
all about?
I don't know.
Either she's in
a real bad mood today,
or she doesn't like me
very much.
Tina? Nah.
She's young,
but she's harmless.
Really?
She just called you
"that Susan bitch."
She did?
Accused me of spreading
dissension and anger
among the contestants.
Maybe we should form
an alliance.
Susan!
You like me!
You really like me!
Not particularly.
But as team leader,
you have your uses.
If you go down,
I'll shed a tear.
But just one.
Think about it.
Bill:
Right here.
Just west
of Lisianski Island.
These two systems
will probably hit
near Midway.
Form the biggest
hurricane to hit
the Pacific in years.
And head
in what direction?
North by northwest.
Straight for Palm Key.
So the cast and crew
are definitely in danger.
- Have you told Stuart?
- Didn't do any good.
His attitude was,
"So what if they're
stranded?"
I know.
"Death is temporary.
TV is forever."
This is chopper 1138.
We're approximately
two clicks away
from the insertion zone.
Jared, we're coming up
on the drop zone.
- You ready to hit it, Rance?
- Locked and loaded.
Locked and loaded.
Those folks won't know
what hit them.
( helicopters whirring )
You're up early,
Detective.
What's going on?
Could you go back
and come out again?
Try to show a little more
surprise for the camera.
I thought this was supposed
to be reality.
Yeah, TV reality.
Asshole.
- Sam, sticks and stones...
- Oh, shut up.
( alarm buzzing )
All right, boys.
Let's move out!
Let's go!
( siren blasting )
Rise and shine, folks!
- What's happening?
- What is that noise?
Sam:
Just keep repeating,
"It's only TV."
Are those
helicopters?
It's pandemonium
and panic here on Palm Key,
as the island is apparently
under armed invasion!
We're down.
Head for the extraction point,
and wait for us.
Pilot:
Copy that. Roger.
Let's go.
What is this bullshit?
Yeah.
How's anybody supposed
to get some sleep?
- I need my eight hours.
- Don't count on it.
The first challenge
of the island...
The first lesson
of the jungle...
Be alert,
be watchful,
and maybe
you'll survive.
Was that
the Navy SEALs?
You never know,
my young friend...
Until you feel
their hot breath
and their
cold steel
take you down.
- ( phone rings )
- Excuse me.
It's his boyfriend.
( ringing )
Yeah.
How did we do?
Absolutely fantastic,
gentlemen.
You scared them like sheep
to the slaughter.
Good. I'll see you
in the morning.
Sleep well.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
Great.
Get some rest, guys.
- Good morning, Sam.
- Good morning.
Just packing
our gear.
- Hey, Sam.
- Good morning.
Ready to find
that treasure?
I'm all a-twitter.
You think
I'm a real worrier,
don't you?
To be honest,
I don't think
about you much.
Here's the deal.
Somebody's gonna win
a lot of money
and the rest of us
are going to go home.
Maybe, maybe not.
Get a look
at that shoreline.
It's a lousy day.
I used to cover hurricanes
for the "Herald" in Miami.
See how choppy
those waves are?
Sam:
What's it mean?
Take a guess.
All right, team one,
let's go.
I think
it's this way.
Susan:
Detective?
Team leader?
Sorry, Sam.
If we're supposed
to follow this map
in order,
then where's
the competition?
The maps are all different.
And all the clues.
They just lead
to the same place.
Turner:
Yep, this way.
I think we're right
on the money.
Turner. He must have
overheard me last night.
So let's follow Turner.
Won't do us any good.
Like Steve said, all the maps
are different.
What's that first stanza
of the pirate's poem?
"A pint of grog
is nearly game,
by pool that's cool
on nearby plain."
That's a stupid poem.
- I know it is.
- What's "grog"?
It's rum. And game means
"old or spoiled."
"Old and spoiled."
That would be like
our team leader.
I prefer "vintage."
Tina:
This poem doesn't
make any sense.
Sometimes you can't go
with the literal meaning
of the words.
Tina:
whatever.
Sometimes you can.
You are the bomb.
Bomb? Aren't you a little old
to be talking like that?
Ooh... A little
grouchy today?
Curmudgeonly.
It's more dignified.
Okay, guys.
New heading.
North.
If those guys get
picked off,
maybe you and I
can form a loyalty
alliance.
You know,
when we get
the treasure?
Like sisters
against the world?
A "Thelma & Louise" thing?
Yeah, I loved
that movie.
Do you remember that cop
that followed them around?
- Uh-huh.
- I'm following him
right to the cash,
and you can try
and compete...
If you think
you can handle
this "Susan bitch."
Well, la-de-da.
So...
How do we start?
- Start what?
- You know, a little trust.
We get in bed together
and get the treasure first.
That's great.
But who's to say
you won't betray me?
It's $10 million.
I totally intend to.
Now I'm starting
to like you.
I feel the same way.
Hey.
"In bed together"?
I think this is
the place to look.
Look right there.
Turner:
Let's spread out
and start looking.
Where?
It could be
anywhere.
Turner:
This looks like
a likely spot over here.
What's your story, mate?
What are you
talking about?
The GI Joe-Rambo deal?
I just wanna be ready
for anything, okay?
You remind me
of a captain I had
in Vietnam.
I think he saw "Patton"
once too often.
Maybe you guys have
the same tailor, huh?
Okay, Mr. Edwards...
Not that it's any
of your business...
Five years ago I was working
for Great Eastern Armor.
Every night,
we made a little milk run
to the local bank.
One night we got hit...
Hard.
Three of my friends
were taken down.
I spent a year
in recovery.
I swore no one would ever
take me down again.
Nobody.
Take a break in place.
I'm just talking shit.
Yeah, quiet's nice, too.
Check this out.
I found something.
I'll take that,
Mr. Edwards.
Go to hell.
- I'm the team leader.
- I didn't vote for you.
Find your own damn clues.
Those aren't the rules.
We're supposed to share
in the discovery.
- A team effort, remember?
- Exactly. So let's have it.
You are looking like assholes
on national television.
- Exactly.
- Okay, you win.
Pick it up, old man.
- "Old man"?
- You heard me.
Get your hands
off him!
I thought you said
you were a teacher.
- I am.
- What kind of school?
Martial arts.
That's right, boys.
A new pecking order.
Bitch.
Goddamn it.
You and I got to talk.
Damn it... A woman.
Yeah, could you hold
for a minute?
This better be important.
I got the network affiliates
on a conference link-up.
You wanted to know
when it's a storm?
Well, it's a storm.
Sam, wait a second.
I just got an idea.
Listen to this line...
"Davy Jones' locker
is as shallow
as low tide."
What's that sound like
to you?
- It's a tidal pool.
- Exactly.
That's where
the treasure is buried.
I'd stake your life on it.
That's comforting.
We're still gonna need
the exact coordinates.
There must a hundred
tidal pools on this island.
But only one on this map.
They're not gonna let us
find the money that quickly.
It's worth a shot.
Anything better to do?
I'll be brave.
She's got a point.
That was a little
obvious, wasn't it?
I had
a good teacher.
Stuart:
What? Talk to me!
It's getting bad.
Hurricane warnings.
Gale force.
I suppose you better
contact the island.
I did, nobody's listening.
You need to get a chopper in.
Get those people
out of there!
I can't blow a 13-week
network commitment
for a little rain
and wind. Come on!
These people
are being paid
to be on that island
and survive,
so damn it,
let 'em survive.
You are such
a bastard.
Really?
And what part of "currently
seeking new employment"
don't you understand?
What is happening
down there?
What kept you guys?
Shut up and dig.
Not me.
I am strictly white collar.
Just do it, Rance.
- Did you bring my stuff?
- Yeah.
A check for one million,
fresh passport...
You're gonna
be fine, Jack.
If this passport isn't fine,
I'll be dead.
How much you owe, Jack?
You mean, just to the IRS,
or to Vegas and Miami?
Oh, I don't know.
Just pick a number
out of the air.
Enough to get me killed.
Enough to get you
killed.
That's what I can't
figure out, Jack.
If you're such
a big a celebrity,
how's a fake passport
going to help you
once you get off
the island?
This show hasn't been
picked up by the foreign
TV buyers yet.
After this week,
I'm sure it won't be.
All right, I give up.
What kind of car are
you going to buy?
- Ooh, a Cadillac. No!
- This way.
No, no.
A beemer.
Tina:
This is gonna be fun!
Oh, yes!
Let's go.
Whoo!
What was that?
Get ready, guys.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
There wasn't
supposed to be
any killing.
I didn't get
into it for that.
Stop your whining.
You got in for the money,
the same as the rest of us.
Rance:
Got it!
( laughs )
- Whoo-hoo-hoo!
- We hit a Jackpot.
Yee-hah!
( men laughing )
- Fantastic.
- I thought it was
gonna be a check.
( muffled male voices )
Hey, are they supposed to be
hunting for treasure?
I thought they were
supposed to be hunting us.
Those aren't
paintball guns.
The easiest money
you ever made.
We got company.
- Jack: Oh, my god.
- Take them out.
- What do you mean...?
- Take 'em out!
( gunfire )
Move, move, move!
No! Stop it,
goddamn it! Stop them!
I hear guns.
I'm sure it's just
the paintball guns.
I carry a gun
for a living.
Real weapons don't
sound like that.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
Where did
the cameraman go?
He said something about
getting some batteries.
Is the weather getting
really bad, or is it me?
It ain't you,
sister.
Susan:
Oh, my God!
There they go!
Man:
Split!
Right, right!
Two!
Stay with me.
Move it, move it!
Let's go!
Oww!
Got one! Move it, move!
Come on!
Go, go, go, go!
Come on, move it!
Let's go!
She's went down here.
Man:
spread out!
Find her!
Keep looking!
Let's go!
Check there!
Damn it.
- Oh-hh!
- Shh.
- Man: Wait! Whoa!
- Don't make a sound.
- I can't breathe.
- Shh! Shh-shh.
- Nothing, nobody.
- I ain't got time
for this shit. Let's go.
Okay.
This is gonna hurt,
but it's a free ride.
- ( groans )
- Come on.
( thunderclap )
So, how did we do, Jack?
Think we're ready
for prime time?
( retching )
I'm gonna go check
on the guys.
Go ahead.
- ( Jack retches )
- ( laughs )
Hey!
Come on!
I think we should go back!
- I think we should go back!
- Don't stop!
He's a cop.
He knows what he's doing!
Get to camp!
( wind gusting )
Which way?
I don't know,
I think it's this way.
Ow.
( gasps )
( yelps )
Come on!
( screams )
Just go!
Go on!
No! I'm not leaving
without you!
I can't!
Come on!
I'm bigger and I'm older.
Let's go!
Come on!
This is getting
really bad.
Treasure or no treasure,
I'm going back to those huts
- until this blows over.
- I'm with you, lady.
Hey, wait a minute.
I think I'm onto something!
Edwards:
Get over here.
This wasn't supposed
to be like this!
You're telling me!
I thought it was supposed
to be sunshine and bikinis.
That's not
what I mean!
( thunderclap )
Kim:
What's going on?
She's hurt.
- One of the paintballs
get her?
- No, she's been shot!
- Shot?!
- They're using live ammo!
Real bullets!
We've got to get back
to camp! Come on!
Let's get out
of here!
I wounded one
of the contestants!
I didn't know how much time
you wanted us to waste,
so we came back here!
There's another team
out there!
What do you
want me to do,
kill everybody?
Fuck them!
Let's take the money
and get out of here!
They can implicate us!
You kind of dropped
that ball, didn't you, Jack?
The way I see it,
it's your worry, not ours.
We're all anonymous.
You? You're on the cover
of those TV mags.
At least in this country.
And with all those
bodies all over the island,
I don't think you'll ever
be able to use that passport.
Oh, my God...
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
- Now what happens?
- Bad news, Jack!
Your ratings are in,
and we're your
mid-season replacement.
No! No, no, no!
Give me the radio!
I'm going to higher ground
to call a chopper in
for extraction.
Let's go!
Okay, move out.
Make sure this
goes out right away.
It's got a name...
Hurricane James.
Named after
the great sea explorer,
captain James Cook.
He died on an island
in the Pacific.
Yeah, right.
So when does it blow over?
It doesn't.
The hurricane is
nature's great
slate cleaner.
It goes where it wants,
destroys everything
in its path,
and moves on.
So, what happens next?
The fun begins.
We have to go back!
We have to go find them!
No, we stay here.
Look!
They're coming!
Hey!
Kim:
I'll take Susan
and look for bandages.
- Good!
- Listen,
we need a hired gun
on this deal.
It's down to you or me!
Or me!
I'm a licensed
security guard
it the state of Texas,
you know.
Great, a Texas security guard.
God help us.
Mr. Chaney, I work
in a dangerous business!
I carry a gun
for a living, okay?
Yeah, yeah, I know.
In the state of Texas
they require
a thousand hours of training
to carry a hair dryer,
and only 40
to carry a gun.
Let's just let Phil do it!
He's ex-military!
No, I'm too old and tired
to lead! You do it!
Yeah!
- Is that okay with you?
- Yeah, I'm okay with that.
All right, look...
We know they're
coming after us,
So here's what we do:
Steve, you and Turner
go and check the hut
for food or weapons,
or anything you can dig up!
- Okay!
- I'll take
the first watch.
- No, I'll do it!
- No, I got it.
- Be careful!
Bad news...
The chopper pilot
refuses to fly.
What do you mean,
"refuses"?
We paid him enough money.
I'll cut his...
- Why?
- He says a storm system's
tearing up the whole Pacific.
He doesn't want to risk
an ocean flyover.
How are we supposed to get
to the fucking pickup ship?
There's a chopper
on the other side of
the island.
- We can take that.
- All right. Let's move!
If that pilot won't fly,
I'll put a gun to
his fucking head!
You don't think
they're gonna try
the same damn thing?
Our number one priority
as of this moment,
is to eliminate
these people.
Yes, sir!
No witnesses,
no crime.
Let's go.
Dumb shit!
What...
What is that line?
Tsunami.
Tidal wave.
Stirred up
by the hurricane.
It should make landfall
on those folks in six hours.
All right. That's it.
I'll call in the choppers
and get those people
out of there.
It's too late.
Choppers are grounded.
You're going to go down
in TV history
as the first producer
to kill off his entire
first season cast.
Should make a hell
of a bargaining tool
next time you negotiate
actors' contracts.
They're not
going to die!
I won't let them.
You won't?
That island
may not survive.
That's not even
the best part.
See that tail section
of the wave?
That may hit us.
If it does...
We're driftwood.
Hello?
- Hello?
- Recording: Hello.
This is
your carnival princess
coming to you...
This is Palm Key Island.
Somebody help!
Help. Hello?
We're under attack!
- Help!
- ( buzzes )
( thunderclap )
How's she doing?
Kim's a good nurse.
I got a merit badge
in this in Girl Scouts.
I think I stopped
the bleeding,
but she's gonna
need antibiotics.
- Anything in the huts?
- Nothing but bandages.
We found some
satellite gear.
We might be able to use it
to call for help.
Yeah, maybe Steve
can help you figure it out.
If there's time.
Well, we better
get going.
Susan, you ready
for some aerobics?
Sure.
You may feel like hell,
but you look great.
Hey.
Thanks for pulling me out
back there.
Don't mention it.
I found all
the canned goods,
cheese and crackers
and stuff I could.
Water, too,
but no weapons.
Only my knife.
I got a couple
of radios.
Steve, you think you can get
that satellite uplink working?
I don't know, maybe.
You were right.
They're coming from the north.
- They're five minutes away.
- Satellite uplink?
No time! Here's what
we're gonna do.
We're gonna head south,
then we're gonna
double back.
Get the other women,
and let's move out!
There they are!
Do 'em!
( distant whistling )
Incoming!
Go, go, go!
( yells )
Steve, help!
Come on!
( rocket whistling )
Let's go!
Come on!
Steve:
Wait, wait!
I think the explosions
have stopped.
Who do we have to fuck
to get off this island?
My money's on
the helicopter pilot.
These guys aren't finished
with us yet, goddamn it!
- Let's get to the chopper!
- Let's go!
Okay, gentlemen...
No more witnesses.
Let's go get us
a chopper.
( constant thunder )
Sailor:
This is the U.S.S. Intrepid.
We are tracking the storm
on all primary
and secondary grids.
The latest coordinates
indicate
a north by northwest track
at approximately five knots.
We have two reports
of foundering vessels.
The first, 70 clicks
southeast of Palm Straits,
bearing 1-5-0.
The second, 55 clicks north
of our current position,
bearing 1-7-9.
We will advise
as to weather conditions
as you approach the vessel,
chopper commander.
Please state current position
and estimated ETA
Woman:
This is chopper command.
We are approximately 20 clicks
from distress coordinates.
ETA, 1400 hours, over.
- Prepare the secondary
rescue team.
- Aye, sir.
Secondary rescue team,
prepare to launch.
Repeat, secondary rescue team,
Load all necessary
personnel aboard chopper
bravo tango zero.
Soldier:
Go, go, go!
Move it, move it!
Chopper Command:
Chopper bravo tango zero...
I want you
out of there ASAP,
before the winds pick up
any further.
Roger that.
Get us something,
anything.
Okay, call me back.
Can the Coast Guard help?
They've only got
three, four hours
flying weather left
and they have too many
other grids to cover.
Downed planes.
Sinking boats.
Shouldn't they have warned us?
They couldn't. Nobody could.
This storm appeared
out of nowhere.
I hope to god
it leaves the same way.
- I haven't got time to hope.
- ( phone rings )
Station?
Yes.
Whoa.
Island team to pick-up.
What's your position? Over.
I'm 200 nautical miles
southwest of the island.
These conditions are
impossible. I'm taking an
alternate course.
If the weather gets
much worse than this,
we won't be able to fly.
You cannot alter
our pickup time!
I don't have any choice.
If I continue to plow
through this, I'm gonna sink!
- How much time?
- I don't know!
Well, give me a guess!
Bryant!
Oh, my God...
( people screaming )
( static )
Shit!
Fuck 'em.
( rapid thunder )
Kim:
Jesus, it looks like
where I grew up on the farm.
- Hey, Garrett.
- There's a cot over there.
That lamp is new.
Sam:
Yeah, it is.
And these matches.
- Okay, okay.
- ( Susan groans )
This is all just
a little too convenient.
Maybe it was something
we were meant to
stumble across
for a scene
in the show.
Or maybe a hideout
for the Navy SEALs.
Navy SEALs don't
kill innocent people.
That's bullshit.
Whatever.
If this is their cabin,
won't they
come back soon?
I hope we won't
be here that long.
- You're gonna be fine.
- Thanks.
- Let's talk outside.
- Come on.
How is she?
I'm not really sure.
Her body temperature
is dropping
and she's lost
a lot of blood
with all the exertion
and the trauma.
Sam:
Think she'll go
into shock?
It's a possibility.
I don't know
what I can do about it.
- Hey.
She's not giving you
very good odds, is she?
You heard that?
I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter.
I wanted an adventure
and I got one.
Yeah.
How come?
I guess I realized
that stocks and bonds
were all I knew.
I mean,
my entire world
was this office
in Oklahoma City,
and the gym.
I wanted to live.
- I wanted to have some fun.
- So, that's it?
Just running around naked,
communing with nature?
I've always been
an optimist.
I also thought I might
win the big prize.
And if you did,
what then?
Back to your office
in Oklahoma City?
No, I was...
I was going to open
a homeless shelter
for runaway kids.
Have I been flirting
with Mother Teresa?
I had a kid sister
who went out to Hollywood
with big dreams,
and she lost
all of them.
And then we lost her.
It happens to kids
like her every day.
Yep, I see it a lot.
I can't imagine
being a cop.
I like it.
You get to carve out
your little piece of
the world.
Try to make a difference.
I guess I've been
flirting with a saint, too.
By no means.
No, my motivations
are purely selfish.
If I have a good day,
I sleep better.
So, Sam...
What would you
have spent the money on...
If you won?
Hot dogs and beer.
You think I'm kidding?
Rance:
How are we supposed
to get out of here
- with no rendezvous ship?
- Don't worry about it.
We'll take the chopper
and fly to Hawaii.
There's a guy in Maui
that will give us
fresh passports.
Suppose he takes
only cash?
That won't be
a problem.
Think the storm
has passed?
I don't know.
I'm just glad
the rain has let up.
Steve, you've
covered hurricanes,
what do you think?
No... This is just
the calm
before it all
hits the fan.
Little pockets
of easy weather
are all over these
storm systems.
We better enjoy it
while we can.
How far do you think
we are from the beach?
It's not
that big of an island.
Maybe a couple of hours.
We're ready
to go.
Okay,
let's move out.
Watch your step.
( screams )
Turner:
What happened?
What the hell was that?!
Okay, check it out!
You guys go that way!
Split up!
Shit!
What are you looking at?
Okay, let's move.
Oh, my God!
They fell!
Kim:
I can't believe
I did this!
How can I be
so fucking clumsy?
Hey.
Are you okay?
- I think so.
- Son of a fucking bitch!
- How bad is it?
- It's a sprain.
We'll just walk
a little slower.
We can't. They'll find us
on this road.
They blew up the camp.
They think we're dead.
Not for long.
We're walking the same path.
It's a matter of time before
we knock heads with them.
Wait a minute.
If a couple of us
could double-time
back to that chopper,
we could fly our asses
out of here.
If that chopper
is still there.
If Sam and Phil could
take the shortcut
along that path,
they'd hit the beach
in half an hour.
- It's a tough climb.
- We can make it.
- You can't leave us here!
- Turner: She's right!
The rest of us will have
no chance on this road.
There's no protection.
There's no place to hide!
We won't have a chance.
- You will, if we
lower the odds a little.
- What are you thinking?
If we double back
and take them by surprise,
they won't expect it.
- You okay with that?
- Good to go.
Sam...
If you wait any longer you're
not gonna be able to fly.
- You've got to go now.
- We're gonna need one
of your radios.
Steve, you and Turner
keep an eye on the jungle
in case they come after you.
- Let's go.
- Stay on channel 2.
- Right.
- We can't fight those guys!
- They're professionals.
- So are you, and so am I!
You're the big
bad-ass security guard!
You've been wanting
to lead this group,
now's your chance.
What do we do
if they come back?
Use your head...
And keep moving.
- Okay, let's go up here.
- Let's go.
We never should
have split up!
It's our
only chance.
( moaning )
( groans )
( cracks )
Aaah!
You have the right
to remain silent!
Anything you say
will be used against you!
( chuckles )
- ( rifle cocks )
- Hey, brother...
- Time to die.
- ( whirring )
Ooh!
( sighs )
I'm getting too old-time
for this shit!
So am I!
Let's go find
that chopper.
Hold it!
What's that?
Shit.
It's Logan!
The contestants
are still alive.
That's bullshit.
It can't be them.
We torched the bastards.
Who else?
Did you see any burning bodies
in the village?
I didn't think so.
It looks like we've
got a fight on our hands.
From who?
These TV pricks?
One man dead,
one man missing...
Maybe we underestimated
these "pricks."
These "pricks" now
have weapons.
So do we.
Rance:
Fuck 'em.
Let's get off this island.
Let's go.
Leave the transmitter on.
What?
Why?
I'm sending reports
to the local TV station
trying to warn residents
on the island.
My last few
live reports.
I've routed
the rooftop camera,
satellite maps,
barometer...
Anything I can send.
Not tonight.
Come on, come on.
I've seen enough.
Let's go.
No one's going
anywhere now, Stu.
No boats, no helicopters
are gonna fly in this.
For good or bad,
we're here for the duration.
Oh, and Stu...
Yellow's not
your color.
You know what?
You're fired, too.
You wanted
reality TV?
You got it.
Bill:
How would you like to do
some real work for a change?
Put something useful
on the airwaves.
Do what we got
in this business to do,
before it became
all about the money.
Maybe save some lives.
All right...
All right,
show me what to do.
We have to get out
in the open.
This road's about to flood!
- No, no!
- We'll get electrocuted!
We have to keep moving!
It's the fastest way!
I'm stiff!
Why am I stiff?
Runner's high.
There it is,
we made it.
Not yet.
Hey! Great to see somebody.
Anybody.
- Where you people been?
- Did they send help?
I haven't heard
from anybody
since I dropped you people
on the beach.
I'm having
a hurricane party.
Have a drink.
Get this thing started!
No, I'm not
flying up in this shit.
That's how you get killed.
( cocks gun )
So's this.
( screams )
Mindi!
Help!
Help me!
( screaming )
We have to help them!
No! No, there's
nothing we can do.
We have
to keep moving!
Come on!
Hold up!
Sam?
Sam, come in!
It's me, Steve!
Yeah, Steve,
I hear you.
Give me your position.
Where are you?
About a mile south
from where you left us.
We lost two.
Mindi and Turner.
- Mercs do it?
- No, lightning.
Okay, I got you.
We're right above you now.
Stand by.
- Take us down.
- Where?
Steve, is there any kind
of a clearing nearby you?
Yes!
Right in front of us!
It's a little plateau.
It looks like it might
be drier.
Okay, I see it!
( gun cocks )
Steve, you copy?
Steve, come in!
Looks like
our ride's here, guys.
What the hell's
going on down there?
I don't watch your show,
Sammy, so I haven't
seen your bio.
You're good.
Real good.
How's this grab you?
( screaming )
Put it down
in that clearing.
If I take it down
I might not be able
to get it
back up again.
I'm just bouncing
around in the wind!
I said,
take us down, now!
I can't wait
to meet you, Sammy.
I hope you brought
the guns,
or I start picking
your friends off,
one by one.
You ever done
any sniper work?
- A little bit.
- One more thing...
I'm gonna need
your knife!
All right.
Jeffries.
Watch them.
Rance!
Follow me.
Put the money in the bags!
Let's go.
What are you thinking,
little girl?
I'm not staying
on this island.
Put your hands
behind your head.
Sammy!
Where's the old man...
The vet?
I heard he was
with you.
He's dead!
Dead?
How?
Heart attack.
On the trail.
I'll check it out.
Sammy, how many of my men
did you kill?
How many you
got left?
Is this the way it's gonna
go down, Sammy?
Huh?
Jeffries:
Thank you, ladies...
But it's time
to call it a night.
( gunshot )
- Are you okay, baby?
- Yeah! Are you okay?
Wait!
Here's your money.
I just need a ride!
Please?
Yeah...
I could use
a hostage.
There goes
a real piece of work.
Get in there!
Take us up, now!
All right!
No guarantees.
Just do it!
Do it!
I've got the map.
- Let's get the hell
out of here!
- Okay.
- You okay?
- Yeah. Yeah. Go.
It's gonna be
a bad one!
But we'll be safe
up in this tree.
With the surf coming in here
we could be hit by
a tidal wave
and wipe out
these fucking trees!
Guys, look at this.
There's a cave on the side
of this cliff.
It's high enough
above the beach
to keep us safe.
The cave is on
the south side
of the island!
It could give us
just enough shelter,
but we've got
to move fast!
No, we can't!
Susan's in bad shape!
- Susan isn't dead yet.
- All right, let's go!
And we're up in three,
two, one... Now.
Eastern edge of the storm
is approximately
six miles west of Waimea
Point, at last reading.
Maximum sustained winds,
140 miles per hour.
We expect landfall
on the outer island
in less than 20 minutes.
- We're clear.
- All right.
Let's go again
in five minutes.
You think they'll
make it on the island?
I don't know
if the island
will make it.
God help them.
God help us all.
We're gonna crash!
Get us up above this thing!
There's a million in it
for you.
I don't know where "up" is!
It's all black outside.
- Sweet Jesus.
- I don't think you're
on his A-list.
Bastard!
You're gonna kill us!
Go!
Will we be safe
in here?
Safest place
on the island,
I guess.
That's not saying much.
Hey, how's she doing?
I think
she's in shock.
- ( alarm sounds )
- Here it comes.
Holy shit!
Hang on! I'm trying
to get above it!
( screams )
Kim:
Oh, my God, guys.
It's the money.
You know, that rescue team
will probably be here
any minute.
Let's get to work.
- Command: Any sign of them?
- Not yet.
Keep looking.
Pilot:
Wait a minute...
We have visual confirmation.
The island is still intact.
Send in the airlift
rescue choppers on the double.
I guess you aren't
coming back, huh?
What do you care?
You've got
a big new TV career.
It didn't work out.
They said I'm
not camera friendly.
Tough town.
Tell me about it.
I hear you're signed
for "Treasure Hunt 2."
I guess that makes you
the big TV star now.
Doesn't he look
like one?
You must be
"Mother Teresa."
You can
call me Susan.
- Susan?
- Yeah.
- Sam's a good cop.
- Yes, ma'am, he is.
If he ever wants
to come back on the force,
I'd love to have him.
I took care of his little
political problem.
Page one.
Well, thank you, Captain.
I will be back...
Right after the hiatus.
And after you help me
build my homeless shelters.
That's right.
- Cheers.
- No, ma'am.
You drink one for me.
I'm still on duty.
Susan:
He seems like
a nice guy.
Sam:
He's kind of an asshole,
but he's okay.
Would you mind getting us
another round of drinks?
- I'm not your wife.
- Not yet.
Is that a proposal?
Well, call it
a proposition.
The first of many.
That'll cost you more.
Now, isn't that nice?