[MUSIC - GENITORTURERS,
"ASPHYXIATE"]
WOMAN: (SINGING)
Your first encounter
with the ones who
make you feel a chance
to taste their disease.
Invite you in to lick
their skin, press open
and to feel all is real.
Your senses low,
your pleasures grow
White hands sew up the deed.
Another limb to lift
your skin, press open.
Had to dream it was real.
With your hands wide open.
Lick your wounds
and come inside.
With your hands wide open.
Lick your wounds
and come inside.
With your hands wide open.
[Chorus]
As the cord pulls tighter.
Come inside.
[Crickets chirping]
[KICK ME KATE, "BOYFRIEND IN A
BOX" ON RADIO]
MAN: (SINGING)
Boyfriend in a box.
He's out about again--
I got to go.
I'm going to be late.
No you're not.
Shit.
I'm already late, Tony.
We've got time.
No, I really don't.
This will only take a sec.
As romantic as that
sounds, I think I'll pass.
Sorry.
It's your loss.
Do you know what a tease is?
I do.
And I'm not one.
My parents think I'm at work.
Don't be mad.
This weekend.
I'm not mad.
Yes you are.
Don't be.
This weekend.
Ow.
Aww.
[Laughs]
I got to go.
[Engine starts]
[belt buckle rattles]
[tv static in background]
[object clatters]
[eerie tone playing]
[music playing]
[buttons beeping]
Tony, it's Jen.
Yeah, I'm home.
No.
I'm calling on my cell.
I don't know.
My phone line is cut.
I think my mom and my
sister are fighting
about collect calls again.
No.
My dad was asleep.
He'll never know.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
OK.
All right.
I just wanted to tell
you I got home, OK?
And Tony?
Don't be discouraged.
This weekend.
Love you.
Bye.
I'm starving.
[Whispering sound playing]
[eerie tone playing]
[screaming sound playing]
Dad, wake up!
[Monstrous sound playing]
[music playing]
[buttons beeping]
DISPATCHER (PHONE): 911.
I need an ambulance.
It's my parents.
DISPATCHER (PHONE): Calm down.
I think they're dead.
DISPATCHER (PHONE): Are
they still breathing?
No!
They're my-- I can't
get that close.
It's my parents.
[Whimpers]
DISPATCHER (PHONE):
Did somebody do this?
Are they still in the house?
[Thud]
[tense music playing]
Hello?
Ma'am?
Ma'am, are you still there?
[Sobs]
[mirror shatters]
[door creaks]
[knob clicking]
[SCREAMING SOUND AND SHARP
NOISE]
[helicopter hovering]
[cruiser siren]
[backgrund radio chatter]
[camera snapping]
Upstairs bedroom.
Come on.
Get up there.
Whew.
OFFICER: You ain't
seen her all night?
No, sir.
She wasn't here when I got here.
I haven't heard from her.
You got it there?
Much obliged.
You just drink this, Jeni.
Warm yourself up.
Everything's going
to be all right.
[Distant siren]
Turns out that
there's a younger
sister, name of Heather.
Ain't been seen all night.
I think we might have been
kidnapping on our hands.
We're going to find her
little sister, Jeni.
Need a bit of your help.
Yes, sir.
Sheriff Dane?
Not now, Reynolds.
All due respect, sir, I
think now is the right time.
She wasn't kidnapped.
She ran away with them.
[Music playing]
[OFFICE PHONE RINGING AND
CHATTER]
SHERIFF DANE: Who'd
she run away with?
Rod Farrell and
some of his friends.
Scott something or the other
and two girls from Kentucky.
SHERIFF DANE: Long
way from home.
Even farther now.
Why would they do
something like this, Jeanine?
You wouldn't believe me.
SHERIFF DANE: Try me.
Because they're vampires.
[Eerie tone playing]
[music playing]
[helicopter flying by]
Whoa, whoa.
Hold on, sister.
Right this way.
This is the mother.
Second victim?
You don't need to
run some more tests?
You know, check her out--
- In due time, deputy.
Second victim, please.
You know, for what it's
worth, I put time of death
about two hours ago,
but that's just me.
Yeah.
Do me a favor, Deputy Johnson.
- Yeah.
Just show me the
second victim, would you?
Sure thing, doc.
Meet your second victim.
That's the second one.
Yeah.
Thank you
See, he ain't got
much of a face there.
Yeah.
I can see that.
Mr. Wendor suffered 22 wounds
to the skull and brain.
That was the cause of death.
Ruth?
DR. HAIR: Mrs. Wendor put up
a bit of a fight, it seems.
Is that a fact?
Not good enough,
unfortunately.
The brain stem was
almost completely
lacerated all the way through.
Come again?
DR. HAIR: She was
practically decapitated.
Sheriff, these people
weren't murdered
for the sake of stealing a car.
- No?
- No.
It was more than that.
It had to be, for this
degree of brutality.
I mean, whoever it is had
some kind of bloodlust.
Definitely.
Oh, there's an officer.
SHERIFF DANE: What's
it look like out there?
Oh, typical circus.
Do we have any idea where
the daughter is at this time?
Do we have any idea--
Care to join me
Mm-mm.
Not if my life depended on it.
[REPORTERS TALKING OVER EACH
OTHER]
I have a statement I'd
like to make, please.
Can I please make a statement.
Please, y'all settle down.
As of right now, arrest warrants
are being issued for Roderick
Justin Farrell,
Howard Scott Anderson,
Charity Lynn Keesee,
Dana Lynn Cooper,
and Heather Ann Wendorf.
What caused you to make
the daughter a suspect?
Rumor has it that
this was a kidnapping.
I have no comment on
those details at this time.
Is it true that
the killers were
vampires, that they killed the
Wendorfs to drink their blood?
Sheriff Dane, are
the killers vampires?
Whatever they are,
we're going to get them.
Do we have any ideas where
the daughter is at this time?
Do we have any idea what
happened to the parents?
[Music playing]
WOMAN (PHONE): Howard Johnson.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll give you the number.
It's 555-9847.
Got it.
Hey, Bill?
We got them.
[Music playing]
You got it?
Yeah.
This one right here.
All right.
Yeah, Mickey.
You can bring them in now.
Don't come in too hot, OK?
Follow our lead.
All right.
Everybody down.
Everybody on their knees right
now with your hands in the air.
All right, everybody,
don't move.
Put your hands on your head.
Happy Thanksgiving.
All right, everybody.
Don't move.
Stop.
Stop moving there.
You stop.
Put your hands in
the air right now.
Don't move, young man.
You are asking for it.
OFFICER: You little shit.
Please, kill me now.
Get down.
Don't you understand?
I cannot be stopped.
Yeah?
There are no earthly means
by which you guys can bind me.
I'm sure you think so.
Well, you've got
the police now, OK?
Oh.
You know what?
You are in a great deal
of trouble, my friend.
Come on.
We have you now, all right?
[Grunt]
Will you relax now, please?
So that we can talk?
OK, everybody?
Come on.
Take him out.
[MUSIC - GENITORTURERS, "ONE WHO
FEEDS"]
WOMEN: (SINGING) Shake
until your master calls you.
Shake until your mother bleeds.
Until you suckle from
the one who feeds.
Would you like to be famous?
What's that?
I like you, Officer Dewey.
OFFICER DEWEY: So
what is it exactly
that you're getting that?
Do you have any
idea what I've done?
Do you have any clue who I am?
I suggest you sit back
and keep your mouth shut.
I need to see my girlfriend.
Maybe.
She's pregnant with my baby.
I said maybe.
You let me see her, I give
you guys full confession.
Full confession, right now.
Full fucking confession.
Come here.
Full confession.
- We'll see about that.
World famous Officer Dewey.
[Laughs]
Little ring to it, doesn't it?
Huh?
Mwah.
[Sirens]
[office phone ringing]
Looking for Ben Odom.
Well, you found him.
- Mike Dane.
- Sheriff Dane.
Good to see you.
Glad you could make it.
Follow me.
You offer an audience, I see.
SGT. ODOM: Hey,
Rod, this here is
Sheriff Dane from Lake County.
He's a might interested
in what you've got to say.
I always did
enjoy an audience.
Well, I, uh--
I think an audience deserves a
good story, wouldn't you say?
Where do you want me to start?
Well, why don't
you start by telling
us about the Vampire Hotel?
[Scoffs]
[eerie tone playing]
Vampire Hotel.
It was at a place called
the Land Between the Lakes
up in Kentucky-- a place
where we could be ourselves.
That's where our coven
first came together.
It was a spiritual place.
It was our place, man.
[MUSIC - GENITORTURERS, "STITCH
IN TIME"]
WOMEN: (SINGING)
Wearing me down.
Oh how low, just to waste
my time thinking of you.
ROD (VOICEOVER): Nobody
could touch us there.
WOMEN: (SINGING)
You're tearing me down.
Down and low--
ROD (VOICEOVER): It was place
we could really be ourselves,
you know?
You had to go
somewhere to be yourself?
We weren't exactly prom
king and queen, you know?
SGT. ODOM: No?
ROD: I'm sure you
already knew that.
Well, I had a
sneaking suspicion.
But what I'm wondering,
Rod, is this.
Why-- why were you
so much different
than everybody else, hmm?
[Lighter clicks]
What made you so different?
I guess it all goes
back to the beginning--
the very beginning.
Tell me, officers.
Have you ever heard
of a black mass, hmm?
Educate us, Rod.
It's how I came
into this world.
I mean, it's bloody
sacrifice and physical abuse.
You talking about
your mother, right?
She's been accused of some very
ugly things, isn't that right?
Like that incident with
Jayden's little brother?
Is that what you're
talking about?
SGT. ODOM: Well, who's,
uh-- who's this Jayden?
[Scoffs] He's this rival
vampire, or so he believes.
Personally, I
question his reality.
But, you know, my
mom, she thought
by being crossed over by
Jayden's little brother
would get her what she wanted.
She's embarrassing.
I mean, clearly-- clearly,
you can understand
why I had to get away from her.
SGT. ODOM: Oh, of course.
You were trying to
run away from her.
Of course.
I understand that.
Is that you were, uh--
is that why you were
down in Florida?
Me, Scott Anderson,
Dana, and Charity
all fucking hopped in Scott's
dad's car and fucking took off.
So we went down to Florida to
pick up my girlfriend Heather.
You know, that place
can't hold us anymore.
[MUSIC - GENITORTURERS,
"TERRORVISION"]
SCOTT: (SINGING) Gotta
make the bells still
when we get to New Orleans.
WOMAN: (SINGING) You're
turning on your terrorvision.
You OK, Charity?
WOMAN: (SINGING)
Channel 1, 2, 3.
Do you think he loves her?
SCOTT: Rod loves many women
and many women love Rod.
That's just the cross he bears.
DANA: Shut up, Scott.
Charity, talk to me.
Are you OK?
That's all right.
You don't have to
talk right now.
Everything's a little bit weird.
Yeah.
This is a mystical
journey we're on.
And things are strange
on a spiritual plane.
Didn't I tell you
to shut up, Scott?
WOMEN: (SINGING) We got
a freak show coming.
Hey, Rod, do you
want a cigarette?
ROD (VOICEOVER): I'll
be honest with you, man.
Charity was less
than thrilled to see
my ex-girlfriend, Heather.
But honestly, who gives a fuck?
I didn't.
It's a laugh.
[Snickering]
What's so funny, Scott?
Hey, Rod, can we talk?
When we stop, can we talk?
It's important.
Hey.
Make a right up
ahead, all right?
WOMEN: (SINGING) While I
plant a seed of violence
into every little head.
Hail to the freaks!
We got a freak show coming.
ROD (VOICEOVER): I
remember the sun.
Yeah.
The sun was coming up.
What about, uh-- what
about Heather Wendorf?
What about Heather Wendorf?
Called her up, told her to cut
class and meet me in the woods.
She didn't mind cutting class?
As far as I can tell,
cutting class is the number one
pastime in Eustis.
Is that right?
Huh.
JENI: Hey.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Are you cutting class?
No.
[Bell rings]
JENI: Yes you are.
You're totally cutting class.
Yeah.
Well, so are you.
You better not tell mom.
I think I'd resist the urge.
You want a ride or something?
No.
All right, then.
Later, gator.
[Music playing]
I've been waiting for you.
How long have you been here?
Not long.
5,000 years.
OK, that's long.
[Laughs]
Not to me, it's not.
It's been a speck in time.
A moment's passed.
Jeez.
I thought it was a
long walk over here.
And to a mortal,
I'm sure it was.
In fact, it must be Thursday.
[Music playing]
Drink in my blood, Heather,
and soon, you will cross over.
Cross over?
Into the realm of the vampire.
You will be immortal,
just like me.
You know, Rod,
I don't know if I
believe in that kind of stuff.
It just doesn't seem real.
Really?
[Whip sound]
[whip sound]
Did that feel real?
No.
It will.
Soon, it will feel
more real than anything
you've ever felt before.
You know, Rod, I'm not sure
how this is all going to work.
How what will work?
Running away.
Getting out of here.
I mean, my parents would
never let me leave.
We'd have to kill them first.
Would you like me to
kill your parents for you?
No.
God, no.
Of course not.
I could do it.
Rod, I was just saying--
(WHISPERS) I know
what you were saying.
Where are you going?
Rod?
Are you going to call later?
Rod, where are you going?
Diet Coke makes you hungry?
So is that-- that's
your secret, huh?
[Laughter]
Mmm.
It does.
I'm sure it does.
Where you folks from?
Here.
There.
Rod.
Yeah?
Can we-- can we go
outside and talk?
There's nothing you can say
to me that they can't hear.
We're all family here.
That's kind of want I
wanted to talk to you about.
I wanted to tell
you sooner, but I--
ROD: Pregnant?
This is coming at the worst
possible time, Charity.
Do you know that?
Huh?
[Thud]
God.
Fuck.
What are you doing?
[Music playing]
[heart beating]
We are one.
(ECHO) We are one.
[Sighs]
We are one.
One soul, one life force, one.
One.
[Sharp noise]
Heather, I'm Sheriff Dane.
I know.
My parents voted for you.
I wish I could
thank them for that.
I truly do.
Now, suppose you tell
me what happened.
I'll tell you what I know.
Good enough.
Rod told us we had a week,
but suddenly that changed.
[Music playing]
Rod was the only one
who really understood,
who really knew what
I was going through.
Everything all right, honey?
(SLOWED DOWN) Everything OK?
Honey?
Heather, answer your mother.
What?
Sorry.
I just want to know if
everything's all right.
I guess.
The reason that
I ask, honey, is
that I know that you were not
in Mrs. Albrandt's class today.
Whoa.
You skipped class?
I just want to know why.
Had female problems.
OK.
Oh, jeez.
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
Yes she is.
Hold on.
It's for you.
I'll take it in my room.
Female problems?
You going to let her
get away with that?
[Sighs]
Hello?
Dad, I got it!
No, honey.
Well, who's she talking to?
It's going to be OK.
She's not Jeni.
I know.
Is everything OK, Rod?
Something wrong?
No.
Nothing.
Things have simply just
become a little bit more--
[music playing]
--urgent, that's all.
We leave tonight.
Tonight?
But you told me we had a week.
ROD (PHONE): The spirit
world has beckoned us.
Their timetable
does not coincide
with that of the mortal world.
We must-- we must--
obey their wishes.
I need you.
Well, have you
spoken to Jeanine?
Of course.
I need time.
For what?
I need time to
say my goodbyes.
Say them quickly.
And remember, time waits
for no transient souls.
RICK: What's this?
Where's the remote?
I've got a job.
Hmm.
The estrogen in this
house is overwhelming.
Fine.
Watch what you want.
[Radio chatter from tv]
[police siren from tv]
You don't have to go.
[Crickets chirping]
[music playing]
[music from tv]
Hey.
What are you looking at?
My own high school yearbook.
Is that you?
[Chuckles] Sure is.
You look--
Eh, well, I get better
with age, don't you think?
Wouldn't argue.
Where's mom?
Upstairs.
[Yawns]
Mom, I'm sorry
about skipping school.
[Music playing]
HEATHER (VOICEOVER):
"Dear mom, dad, and Jeni,
I don't have very much
time, but I must say
that I love you all very much.
I'm leaving for good, but
I don't want you to worry
about me because I'll be fine.
I had to go with Jeanine
because she needs
someone to look after her.
Please don't try to find us.
Just know that I'll miss you
and I'll always love you.
Heather."
ROD (VOICEOVER):
The plan was simple.
Wait till Heather leaves, then
we go steal her parents' car.
(SINGING) When I
get to New Orleans,
I will prey upon the fallen.
You can find me--
[growling]
There she goes.
SCOTT: (SINGING) Dark
master, open the gates.
Open the gates.
Come on, Heather.
Don't back out on us now.
[Scott singing]
Scott.
Hey, man, I need you
to fucking focus.
Can you do that for me?
I'm focused, man.
[Animal noises]
I have a gift for you, Scott.
No shit?
What is it?
By communing with me now, we
will transcend this reality.
We will cross to a
spiritual realm--
the realm of vampires.
[Deep voiced echo]
And we'll be more powerful than
any mortal we shall encounter.
Now we drink freely
of each other's soul--
each other's blood.
[Bizarre noises]
[music playing]
The challenge is ahead of us.
It looks us deep in the eyes.
Are you strong enough
to take that challenge?
I'm strong enough.
OK.
Now follow me to our destiny.
[Dog barking in distance]
No way.
How we going to get in?
Shut the fuck up for a second.
- How we going to get in?
- All right.
All right.
ROD: There it is.
Nice.
This is our ride.
This is our ride, man.
It's unlocked.
Let's go.
Rod.
You ready?
Should we back it out
and try and be quiet?
We should just go.
Uh, Rod?
[Sighs]
Are you done?
Looks like we're just going
to go inside and get the key.
Stop.
Let's not be foolish.
What are you doing?
What we're doing is we're
walking into that house
and taking exactly what we need.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
I'm going to take the father.
You take the mom, all right?
Beat her in the head.
[Quiet laugh] That's
not going to do.
What happens if the
old man has a gun, huh?
You ever think of that?
I didn't think so.
No.
We need something metal.
[Eerie tone playing]
Yeah.
This is it.
[Harsh tone playing]
[laughs] Let's go.
[Crickets chirping]
DANA: Come on, Heather.
Get in.
Where's Jeanine?
DANA: Get in the car, Heather.
Where's Johnny
Rod and Scott went
ahead to get her.
They're picking her up?
Yeah.
They just thought
it'd be best if they
went ahead and helped Jeanine.
We'll all be meeting up soon.
I just wanted to go with them.
Yeah.
Well, we got to hurry
because Rod, you know,
and Jeanine, they're
waiting for us.
Let's go.
Nice bear.
SHERIFF DANE: So you
went ahead and got in?
I didn't think--
I didn't know that--
SHERIFF DANE: You thought
that Rod and Scott
were out picking up Jeanine.
Nothing about that
struck you as odd?
It all struck me
as odd, Sheriff.
It freaked me out.
Why didn't you get out, then?
Tried to.
I tried.
It's just, with Rod, you can
never really just say no.
I know it sounds crazy,
but I trusted him.
I really did.
[Music on radio]
HEATHER: Hey, guys, I think I
forgot something in my room.
Easy.
There's nothing you
could have forgotten
that Rod can't provide.
[Charity laughing]
DANA: What?
You brought seven suitcases.
Shh.
Shut up.
[Snoring]
[music playing]
[sighs]
[snow globe playing music]
[water trickling faintly]
Do you hear that?
- Hear what?
Shh.
Listen.
[Music playing]
I need you to go
check that noise out.
Scott, focus.
I need you to go
check out that noise.
This is taking too long.
She must have changed her mind.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
The guys went to go get
Jeanine, remember, Dana?
There they are, so chill.
It's my folks.
[Eerie tone playing]
[music playing]
What's going on?
Why are they in my parents' car?
Relax.
Just needed a better car.
It's all part of the plan.
Plan?
What plan?
Charity, stop the car.
We're not stopping.
No.
Stop the Explorer.
Flash your lights or something.
Just relax, all right?
Yeah.
Mmm!
[Laughs]
Let's see what you got.
Boring.
This-- this, however,
will be very useful.
That's why I grabbed
that stuff, man.
Those pearls.
I knew that other
stuff was junk.
Something really bad
must have happened.
Nothing bad has happened.
Charity, flash your light.
We have to go back.
Make them stop.
Honk your horn or something.
Little piss, just
freaking relax, OK?
We'll stop later.
No.
Make them stop now!
Shit!
Cops.
It's just the girls, man.
They're flashing their lights.
I think-- I think they
want us to pull over.
[Quiet laugh] Relax.
Is she telling them?
Dana, we have to go back.
I have to tell him.
Hey, hey, hey.
Charity will handle it.
Just sit back and relax.
Charity, what's going on?
Are we going back?
Did you tell Rod that my
parents are going to freak out
when they find their car gone?
CHARITY: Yeah.
ROD: And what did he say?
CHARITY: Nothing.
What's Scott doing?
Why is he switching the
license plates on our car?
DANA: So the cops can't run our
plates if we get pulled over.
HEATHER: The police?
Are you serious?
[Engine starts]
ROD: Hey, look at me.
We have taken a
bold step forwards.
You know that?
Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah?
I know that.
All right.
Remember this.
Our coven in New Orleans,
they're going to be grateful.
Grateful to you for your
contribution to them.
Make her chill out, will you?
I'm trying.
Heather, listen.
You got to relax, OK?
We just needed a better
to get us to New Orleans.
It's going to be just fine.
- No.
I can't do this.
We have to go back.
What the hell is she doing?
How the hell am
I supposed to know?
She wants us to
pull over again?
Pull over.
I said pull over.
I want to put an end
to this shit right now.
God.
What the hell is going on here?
HEATHER: What's he saying?
You know Rod.
The usual.
HEATHER: Well, what's
he telling her?
You don't think
you're the only one.
Come on.
We're all family now, right?
It's not about you anymore.
It's about what's
best for the family.
Get out of the car.
We're ditching it.
- Good.
Let's just go back and
forget this whole night.
I don't think
you understand me.
What do you mean, then.
We're ditching the car.
This shitty rust bucket
is just slowing us down.
Grab your stuff.
We're all riding
in the Explorer.
Rod, this is a bad idea.
- What is?
- This.
Taking my parents' car.
They're going to kill
me when they find out.
They're not going to find out.
They'll find out.
Trust me.
They'll find out
and they'll kill--
Shh, shh, shh.
Trust me, all right?
Your parents are
never going to know.
All right?
OK?
All right.
Whoa.
What the fuck are you doing?
What?
This is my stuff?
It's too much shit.
You can't take all that.
I need it all.
All of it?
Yes.
Here.
Let me help you.
All right, gimme.
All right, hold on.
Rod.
What are you--
Rod!
Give me the fucking bags.
Forget it.
Fuck you!
Fuck it.
[Door slams]
Ah, yeah!
Well, if you all
your stuff, we can
wait until you go and get it.
No?
[Music playing]
I want to go back.
It's too late for that, OK?
We can't go back.
No.
There's-- there's
still a chance.
We can go back.
My parents might not even find
out about us stealing their car
if we just turn back now.
We can't go back, all right?
Even if we wanted to.
- Do you want to?
- Heather.
Do you want to go back?
I mean, if we just went
over to Jeanine's, she
could talk him into stopping.
We're not going
to Jeanine's, OK?
I don't even want to
do this without her.
Don't you understand that my
parents are going to kill me?
Your parents aren't
going to find out.
What's that supposed to mean?
Look, to put it bluntly,
Heather, your parents are dead.
Charity, that's not funny.
[Music playing]
HEATHER (VOICEOVER):
I don't know where
we are when I woke up the
next day, but something in Rod
had changed.
It was like I didn't even
know who he was anymore.
Aww, fuck.
Fuck.
What the fuck!
What's up?
Something's wrong with
this fucking Explorer.
That's what's up.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
It's driving fine,
then it's slowing down,
and driving fine,
slowing down, sputtering.
ROD: It's because it's
out of gas, moron!
God.
That was so fucking stupid.
Don't start with me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey.
Hey, shut the fuck up.
- Idiot.
Hey.
Shut the fuck up, all right?
I'm so sorry, man.
I wasn't paying attention.
Hey.
Momentary lapse of senses.
Don't let it happen
again, all right?
Don't fucking let
it happen again.
Jeez.
What are we going to do?
What?
We're going to go get gas now.
It's going to be
a hell of a walk.
Hey.
Where are you going?
I'm going to get gas.
No, no, no, no.
No, no.
You stay here.
You watch the girls.
Dana and I are going
to go get the gas.
Let's go.
- What?
There's nothing here for miles.
(MOCKING VOICE) There's
nothing here for miles.
Let's go.
Don't let anything
fucking happen to them.
Do you understand me?
- I got you.
- Huh?
- Do you understand me?
Yeah.
All right.
Let's go.
That's Rod's seat.
I don't see him
sitting in it, do you?
Just don't be sitting in it
when he gets back, that's all.
You really are scared
of him, aren't you?
I'm not scared of him.
You're scared to death of him.
God, you're scared
of everything.
I am not.
You're scared of me.
I am not scared of you.
I've got powers.
Rod's given me powers
as a vampire and stuff.
And-- and I am not
scared of anything.
I can feel your
powers weakening.
My powers aren't weakening.
I am draining you--
your powers.
Whatever.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
And another thing-- what
the fuck are you doing!
The fuck does it look like.
I'm going home.
[Quiet laughing]
What's so funny?
It's just funny.
It's just funny, that's all.
How do you like it!
How does that feel!
Is that funny?
I'm-- I'm sorry.
It's a strange new world.
If you've begun to cross
over, soon you'll understand.
What do you mean?
You need to drink.
See, you have to
be strong when you
cross over to become a vampire.
[Music playing]
Drink.
You need your strength.
[Police siren]
Shit.
The cops.
SCOTT: Man.
I knew it.
Fucking dead, man.
Shit.
CHARITY: Relax, Scott.
Just be cool, OK?
Don't blow it.
How you doing, officer?
[Radio chatter]
Everything all right here?
No, sir, it's not.
No.
If it was, wouldn't
need this, right?
SCOTT: Charity, what
are we going to do?
We're so busted.
We are screwed.
We're going to to get arrested.
You know, these things
are real gas guzzlers.
You wouldn't believe it.
I believe it.
Yeah?
This one time, I used to
have this Buick, right?
And it was old just like this.
Eh, you expect a car like that
to do you wrong, you know?
But a car like this--
You into automobiles, son?
Yes, sir, I am.
- You are?
- Yeah.
Got a V8 on that?
[Scoffs] I wish.
Six, but gets the job done.
OFFICER: Ah, six.
Yeah.
OFFICER: All righty.
All righty.
Have a Happy Thanksgiving.
Hey, you too.
It is so funny how they
go through all this effort
of wearing their uniforms
and carrying their weapons,
when clearly--
I mean, fucking clearly, they
are no match for my powers.
I mean, come on.
It is so clear to me now that
our family cannot be stopped.
When we go to New
Orleans, our coven--
we form and we mutate.
And perhaps, we might
even be able to forge
a coexistence with
the lupine lures
of New Orleans' eastern side.
What's a lupine?
It's a werewolf, dumbass.
Fuck off.
I wasn't talking to you.
Fuck you.
Can werewolves and
vampires really do that?
Today, I am absolutely
sure anything--
anything-- can happen.
I have a present
for you, Heather.
HEATHER: What the fuck
are you doing with those?
Those are my mother's.
Huh?
Were your mom's.
A symbol of your past life.
(HIGH PITCHED VOICE) Help me.
Help me.
[Laughs]
Let me stop you right there.
Just let me get some
things straight here.
Were you trying to
get away or not?
Of course I was.
SHERIFF DANE: But
you're in the car,
you're drinking blood off
these other girls' arms.
I just don't understand.
I wouldn't expect you to.
God, has anything like
this ever happened to you?
Can't say as it has.
HEATHER: Well, it's not
exactly easy to tell
a car full of vampires that
you're just walking away.
I was scared.
I was-- I was scared of
what they would do to me.
[Music playing]
Drink.
The three of us need strength.
I can't wait to
have your baby.
Rod, I need to talk to you.
Can't it wait?
It already has long enough.
[Sighs]
OK.
Talk.
In private.
So what's so important?
I just need to
know if it's true.
Everything's true.
No.
No, I mean somewhere inside
of me, I know it's true.
You didn't do the
things you said you did.
And my parents are still alive.
I assure you--
Rod, I know how you
like to talk, all right?
And I understand that.
I'm mad.
I just-- please tell
me it's not true.
Do you know how many
souls one must consume
to open the gates of hell?
It's a number far greater
than you can count.
Rod.
Would you deny me entrance
to the gates of hell?
I just need to know.
[Clock ticking]
[grunts]
[thud]
[grunting]
[laughs]
Wake up.
Help me get his
wallet, all right?
[Panting]
[breathless laugh]
Hmm.
[Humming]
Who are you?
What do you want?
Shut the fuck up, lady.
[Gasps]
Shit.
You fucking bitch.
[Music playing]
[groans]
[quiet sobbing]
Get away from me.
Please.
(WHISPERS) You taste
just like your daughter.
Go to hell!
I intend to.
[Thudding]
I beat your father's
head in with a crowbar.
The one that's in the car.
And your fucking
bitch of a mother
threw coffee on me, so I
bashed her head in too.
That's it.
[Music playing]
Help me!
[Screams]
Get off of me!
[Crying]
Hey.
You'll get through it.
Be strong.
It's OK.
ROD (VOICEOVER): I don't
know what to tell you, man.
I snapped and I liked it.
You know, to tell you
the truth, I felt a lot
better when it was all over.
[Eerie tone playing]
All right.
It's time to make
yourself useful again.
Hey, go upstairs.
Find some money.
Scott.
Don't forget my jacket.
[Music playing]
[quiet sobbing]
[distressed growling]
It's a shame, don't you think?
I don't know.
We've left our mark without
leaving our mark, you know?
What do you mean?
[Cigarette sizzling]
Rod.
We should get out here.
Yeah?
SGT. ODOM: And you left?
We left.
At this point, both
Ruth and Rick Wendorf were
already dead, is that right?
Are you not listening
to what I just said?
Did you not just hear me, huh?
Yes.
I beat their faces
in, all right?
I murdered them.
I'm admitting to murder.
God.
Rod, there's just
one thing that I'm
not real clear on right now.
Listen to me.
Look.
Will you look at me?
You went there to steal a car.
That is all.
Why so much bloodshed?
I don't know.
OFFICER: Get up.
Get up.
[Phone buttons beeping]
HEATHER (VOICEOVER):
I don't remember much
of what happened after that.
I was in a daze.
Mom?
It's Dana.
I don't know if you've
heard-- you have heard.
CNN?
Yeah.
We're-- we're in-- we're
in big trouble here.
We're running out of money.
Mom, I need you to wire me
some money in Louisiana, OK?
Where, exactly?
Howard Johnson's.
Yeah.
I'll give you the number.
It's, uh, 555-9847.
OK.
Thanks, mom.
I knew I could trust you.
So what's up?
She's sending the money.
OFFICER: Hey, Bill, we got them.
That's great news.
How much is she sending?
I don't know.
You didn't ask.
Just be glad we're
getting something, OK?
Maybe we can eat some real food.
Hey, come here.
Heather, come here.
All right.
Tonight, our coven is complete.
Our journey is complete.
Every single roadblock
has been erased.
Do you realize that?
Every single one.
We are here.
We are now.
We're forever.
We are now family.
[Eerie tone playing]
DANA: Hey.
I'm expecting a wire
to come through.
I'm, uh-- I'm Dana Cooper.
Where is it coming from?
From South Dakota.
[Phone ringing]
And the signer's name?
Oh, Jodi Remington.
Nope.
No.
We haven't received it yet.
So if you have a seat over
there with your buddies,
we can let you know
when it comes through.
Thanks.
He's going to let us
know when it gets here.
They tell you how much it is?
Don't be stupid.
What?
How is that stupid?
It just is.
[Cruiser engine running]
I'm going to go
check on it again.
Ask how much it is.
Yeah, Mick, we got a UN589.
Looking at it right now.
Has that wire
come through yet?
Let me check.
What was the name again?
Dana Cooper.
And the sender's name, please.
Jodi Remington.
No.
But if you have to sit over
there with your buddies,
I'll be able to help
whenever it comes in.
You let me know as
soon as it gets here.
[Music playing]
All right.
Everybody freeze.
Get down on your knees.
All right, everybody,
don't move.
Don't move an inch.
Get up.
Hands on your head.
Put your hands in the air.
Officers--
On your knees right now.
- Get your hands on your head.
- Happy Thanksgiving.
- And stop moving.
- I was wondering if you guys--
- Stop.
- Get down on your knees.
Stop moving!
Well, you know the rest.
Heather, um, we, uh--
I know this has been a long
couple of days for you.
And we realize that.
[Quiet crying]
Here, Heather.
[Music playing]
I'm so sorry.
Are you OK?
I'm sorry.
[Music playing]
[birds singing]
[music playing]
[MUSIC - GENITORTURERS,
"CRUCIFIED"]
WOMEN: Behold, all the
eyes shall see them.
All the wounds that pierce them.
WOMAN: (SINGING) Take
pleasure in his sins.
Take pleasure in her suffering.
When you lie with the beast,
you shall die with the beast.