Who are you?
I am your Guardian. As long as I live
the Horned Demon cannot come.
Where does this quote come from?
- From hell.
Any idea, Jamie?
I don't know any dead languages.
- He who understands can learn a lot from it.
It's Vergilius.
-Well done.
Mucus.
-Knowledge is power.
Blessed are the poor in spirit.
So this is your paper about Plato.
You can give better assignments.
- Give an example.
Macbeth.
-Nice for the Easter holidays.
A ten-page paper
about Macbeth.
Good is evil and evil is good
we rushed through fog and rain.
Macbeth, first company, first scene.
Monday I had breakfast with 4 slices
bacon. And bacon is fat in the canteen.
I had lunch with a puff
potato with sour cream and butter.
Just a little butter.
Tuesday I got it
a box of fudge from my grandmother.
I intended to hand them out.
But I ate them myself in the evening.
You also have to confess sins
who are not talking about food?
As a penance you have to
five minutes on psalm 39.
Go and say your deed of repentance.
Five.
If I succeed, I want a liposuction.
Just like models from lingerie
advertisements.
What do you think?
Why am I actually asking?
What are they doing in the church?
They repair the damage
of the earthquake.
Will those boys stay the entire vacation?
Maybe I'll just stay here.
-Really? I stay too.
There are not enough places to sleep.
Maybe we should share a room.
Imagine.
Bless me, I have sinned.
I did a week ago
last confessed.
Since...
I doubted.
All pain leads to redemption.
-Why did God take my father?
He was fantastic,
he was always there for me.
God teaches us his lessons
in many different ways.
It's not fair.
Mama is always so busy.
She hardly has any time for me.
I don't know where I belong.
Do you understand that God?
has a plan for you.
Do you go during the Silent Week
to your mother?
It is a good week
to improve the relationship.
I want you to be throughout
seven minutes ...
reflect on the infinity of God.
Think about why Christ ...
hung on the cross.
Seven?
-That's very easy.
I've been a bad girl.
-How so?
I've been to a man.
In the carnal sense?
I don't know for sure. I think so.
Do you believe so?
I met him on the beach.
We swam together.
We didn't go far into the water.
Everyone on the beach could still see us.
He kissed me.
I wanted to stop him.
But it was so delicious.
He pulled my top off ...
It was wrong
but I allowed it.
I didn't know what to do.
I closed my eyes
and prayed for advice ...
and when I opened them again,
he had taken off his swimsuit.
You have to think of another way
deal with your family problems.
Without all these impressions.
Your lack of respect
leads you to darkness.
I have another question.
Is oral sex a pickle sin
or a capital sin?
As a penance
you stay here in church ...
to reflect on you for twenty minutes
on the infinity of God.
Twenty?
What has she done?
-What not?
Telephone for you in the office.
Your mom.
What's your name?
-Daniel.
That is a big tool.
-Yeah, nothing for little girls.
Do I look like a little girl then?
Funny.
-Do you think he is beautiful?
Yes, my 12 year old sister also has one.
Watch out with that jetty.
What is it, mama?
-I can't come for you.
I'll go by bus and train.
-No. I have little time now.
I'm going to Australia with Russel.
He writes something about Aborigines or something.
It's getting serious.
You can stay in school this week.
You are kidding me.
-You'll be out for a weekend soon.
You can still do something about your schoolwork.
-I want to go home.
Don't start this way.
Oh, there is the taxi.
I'll still call.
I love you too.
Are you okay?
Yes, it's fine.
It's fine. I will stay here.
Fortunately the library is open.
Someone who stays here.
Nice. Then the problem is
with the rooms also solved.
Jamie can sleep with Faith.
- Why isn't Jamie going home?
Last time she was bright and blue.
Her father had done that.
I tried to help her ...
but sometimes it is hopeless.
Just watch.
Her hair and her nails are
grew after her death.
She was in the outside wall,
as if it was a warning.
I send her to the laboratory.
Come on, let's go.
I am turning this area off.
You will hear from me again.
Please come with me. Remember your head.
Do you think the stories are correct?
This must be an Illuminati.
-What is that?
It used to be here at school
a poetry group.
They were called after the Illuminatis
in England.
They disappeared a hundred years ago.
- They never heard from them again.
Until today.
This wall is from after the fire.
The entrance from the church
is bricked up.
They have put a lot of effort into it
to close this space.
Decent work.
Did you know this was here?
Take a look here.
What happened here?
- I hoped you knew that.
What is this?
-It's a baptistery.
It's hard to see
with all those skeletons ...
but i think its here
five or six people burned.
What a boring room.
Let's hang up some things.
It's my room.
-This week is mine too.
Do not touch it.
-University of Stanford. Waiting list.
Poor study head. Not accepted.
-Not yet.
Nice view.
Shall we get their attention?
Put it a little harder.
The show is over.
At work, boys.
Come on, work.
That you dare. Suppose they see you.
-That was the intention.
A teacher or something. This is not
allowed anyway.
Do you never do something that is not allowed?
With a boy or something?
I do not have a boyfriend.
Then we have to find one for you.
A passionate twink.
Have you never done it before?
I can give you a few tips.
Not necessary, I have to study.
-I too, but you know ...
Working alone makes you boring.
We can do you
help with a new hairstyle.
And makeup.
Sexy clothes.
Do you like to see me?
You do have options.
If you do your best.
Do you really think so?
-Yeah, you just gotta get loose.
Then they can't keep away from you.
How is it that the hair grew through?
-Egg whites?
In a stone wall?
-It's a well-known phenomenon.
Under the right conditions
can it happen.
Her skin has remained less beautiful.
It's enough like this. The food is
getting cold.
What shall we do?
I'm going to remove my legs.
-There will be a nice movie again.
Don't like the diet menu?
Someone wants this
bring to Mother Clodah?
What is it late?
-We have to leave.
Can I use your computer for a moment?
Mother Clodah is not very popular.
She's weird.
What do you think of me?
-You are nice. But why are you ...
Have you become a nun?
That is a logical question.
What about then?
- I'm from an orphanage.
An orphanage.
Because of the sisters I have my calling
discovered and found the power of God.
I sometimes feel like an orphan.
If you want to talk to someone
you come.
Excuse me.
I should have listened to you.
- You're looking for a plaster.
I cannot find the first-aid kit.
We do have one. Wait a second.
Do you have him?
-Almost.
Found it. Come on.
Stanford?
Yes, when I got engineering
went to study.
I want that too.
How do you end up here?
I am an intern here. I learn everything about it
the restoration of historic buildings.
How strange, no one ever
had discovered that that space was there?
Yes, as if it had to remain hidden.
I want to investigate.
We have a library.
I'm sure you can do that.
Do you have Internet?
-Yes, but you must have a password.
I want to help you.
Monday, at noon?
Nice, see you on Monday.
Good night, Faith.
Careful with your arm.
- All right, doctor.
dorms
How does such a seance go?
You talk to the dead.
It's just like a long-distance call.
Just lie still.
Where were you?
I don't do it anyway.
Welcome to the pleasure garden.
How was the living dead?
-With whom?
Mother Clodah.
Did she let you pray?
Or have you succeeded?
- She didn't open.
Do you have her collection
seen crucifixes?
No vampire approaching her.
- How old would she be?
She is timeless. It never dies.
- We are not disturbing, are we?
We will cheer you up a bit.
After all, we are fellow sufferers.
Something like that never really works?
Let's try the Illuminati
to recall.
How?
-With a seance in the chapel.
Their aura is still floating around.
-It's completely dropped off there.
We will soon be thundering.
-What would really have happened?
Good idea.
And Sister Sherilyn?
No problem.
Our buoy queen takes care of that.
Come on, we gotta be quick.
You get wine and a few candles.
What is it?
Do I have to go steal those things?
Everyone must do something.
You belong now.
Then it's going to be crazy. Forward.
All right then.
Why did you do that?
-For fun.
That was not fun.
- Don't be so serious.
Here are the candles and here is the wine.
Come on, Faith.
-I'm not going.
It was a joke. Do you find that so bad?
Do you really think you're going to hell
if you steal candles?
Are you not ashamed?
-Pious aunt.
Dark say.
This is  cool .
I want to get out of here.
Let's have a drink at Father Michael.
What now?
Grab each other's hands.
We greet our Illuminatis sisters.
Tell us your secrets.
Tell us how you died.
-Take us into contact with Kurt Cobain.
Seriously.
Eyes closed.
We greet our Illuminatis sisters.
Get up and contact us.
Come alive. Go walk again.
Go breathe again.
Greetings to you.
It does not work.
Come out, wherever you are.
-It does not work.
We are definitely doing something wrong.
They probably don't hear us.
I'm starting to get hungry.
We cannot reach the other side,
because ...
What are you going to do?
All modern stuff out.
They hamper things.
Maybe we should
to the other side.
Hurry up.
Doesn't everything have to go out?
-You want it to work?
I call on the spirits of the past.
Get up from your silent grave.
We greet you. Stand up.
Are you there?
You can't go in there.
I just looked.
What is happening?
What lies there?
A book.
What does it say?
It is Latin. I can not read that.
I know who does.
Hey. Let me out.
I'm coming.
What a silly joke, say.
Where's the rest of it?
They are...
Go to bed.
I'll come back to this tomorrow.
That lying must have ended.
I know where you have been.
I found this in the church.
And this one was under the scaffolding.
Listen carefully. You are only allowed in it
part where the altar stands.
The rest is forbidden territory.
It is not safe there.
Is that clear?
I understand you well.
I was just like you.
I never let myself say anything.
You can appreciate good advice later.
My teacher warned
always against temptation.
It seems innocent,
but don't give in.
Have I been clear?
You know that cleanliness
leads to heaven.
You don't mean this.
Do we have to clean the kitchen?
-That's necessary.
Is this to strengthen our character?
- Child labor is forbidden?
Go ahead.
I'll finish this.
You can do the fridge.
There she goes.
I wouldn't eat that.
-What is it?
My bait.
Is someone going to fish?
-No, thank you.
Women belong in the kitchen.
We are attacking the bacteria here.
Have a nice afternoon then.
We found something last night.
A moldy skeleton?
-No, an old book.
And all in Latin.
And let me read Latin.
You are the only one who can help us.
I think it has something
to do with the Illuminatis.
These notes were in the book.
They are from one Gertrude.
She writes that the book is her heart
ignites desire.
Sounds good, right?
We're going back tonight.
-After what happened?
Then you don't want to know
what happened in the past?
Don't you like us?
Knowledge is power.
You are quite curious.
Come on.
Do you really think that Sherilyn
kicks in here?
Of course.
And we have a secret weapon.
Crazy.
-He is on.
Come with me.
Mysterious.
It is mainly Latin.
The rest is in Gaelic, I think.
-What does it say?
Who read aloud from this book,
becomes mistress of the devil.
That is not a cat piss.
-It's a book about magic.
This is the book of the Horned
Demon, the Master of the Elements ...
the Lord of the Fertile Earth.
The long-awaited one.
Nice name
for a fertility god.
Does he have a flat stomach?
This book brings you great power.
The reader is required
to open the Forgotten Gate ...
making the long-awaited
will enter.
If you execute this command, the
Long awaited rising from the ocean ...
on the darkest day
of the year.
Good Friday.
That's next week.
-Crazy.
What must we do?
-To be severely punished ...
the Guardian, the Bearer of the Mark.
Woe to them. Their head is cut off.
What is a Guardian?
- Someone at the court?
It is a story.
Something that happened a long time ago.
De Wachter has prevented that
the long-awaited could enter the world.
I think some pages are missing.
We do not have all the information.
Gertrude says that ...
We must first open the gates.
-Who is Gertrude?
Miss Illuminatis 1896.
I had only taken this with me.
We need the Mirror Conspiracy
to carry out.
On Good Friday.
Read the spell over the Noordpoort.
We turn our face
to the north.
The beach is there.
-Then the north is there.
There is the north.
Give it some water.
Water.
Guard of the Noordpoort.
Send your water.
Raise your voice, o Demon.
The water
will flow through the Noordpoort.
Accept this pure sacrifice.
Let us witness your power.
Was that it?
-Yes. Come with me.
Has anything happened?
We will notice that.
It did not work.
Foxglove.
A poisonous wild plant.
You may.
- I'll do it soon.
This is the church, isn't it?
What is so special about that?
-The baptistery is older than the rest.
Is that bad?
-No, but strange.
How can sea water be there?
end up?
In the rest of the church
there is no trace of it.
That's strange.
-On top of a hill. I don't get it.
I quit. I go back to work.
I still have to do something
for Sister Sherilyn.
Wait a moment.
-I want to test my translation program.
Not now.
Guardian of the Zuidpoort,
show the way.
Raise your voice, o Demon.
Earth from the Zuidpoort leads us to you.
Accept this sacrifice so that we witness
may be of your strength.
What is it?
I think we have the South Gate
have opened.
Let's hurry up.
It is almost Good Friday.
What now?
-We have to go to the beach.
Then my hair will frizz.
No, it says it's at noon
afternoon must.
But we still need something.
Search for the spell
of the water 's up.
This is it, I believe.
You must know for sure.
Does this not go a bit far?
Do you prefer to do something else?
With this or that?
Well, say.
Courage is the most important virtue,
says Gertrude.
We just want to see what happens.
Good.
This will be fun.
Bergamot oil purifies the sea water.
And we need candles to
to awaken our hidden powers.
White clothing, as old as possible,
so that our aura can go through.
Mirrors, those are the most important
for the last spell.
He needs us
bring the long-awaited.
Now we are going to clean the ocean water,
just like a century ago.
If you go fishing, you must first
three orphan greetings pray ...
and only then eject the line.
Manifest you, o Demon.
The water from the Zuidpoort is now
burning.
Accept this pure offering.
You have it.
What would it be like if it worked out?
At least I let myself be
never prescribe the law again.
What is a pure girl?
-A virgin.
We need that.
I know.
And who can that be?
Slut.
The Long-awaited is vain.
Hence those mirrors.
But more important than mirrors ...
Is blood. Blood from a virgin.
Bye, Faith.
You don't have to drink it.
Come on in.
I'll see you there.
We'll wait.
Daniel, do you want it again?
with me on the computer?
Yes Nice.
At eight o'clock tonight?
Which is good.
Until then.
How's Daniel doing?
- I'll see him tonight.
In the library. I have asked him.
I'm going to the library tonight.
-Stay out of this.
I just check if it's not out of control
runs. I know what type it is.
I don't need any help.
Do not.
That is foxglove.
Very toxic.
I'm Erica.
Faith sent me.
She wants you to come to her room.
It's number 24.
Do not be afraid.
There are no sisters.
Kelsey, hurry up.
I have to leave.
Where is she?
She is taking a shower.
She asked if you wanted to wait. Sit down.
What are you going to do?
We'll see.
Here I have them.
What the hell?
Have you never seen a girl
dress up? You have a sister, right?
You know, Faith is ...
very sweet, but you're just not ...
What is it? You want well.
Not with you.
- Nobody needs to know?
I don't want to be with you.
- You are still a virgin.
I know what it looked like ...
-Never mind.
I just sat there.
-I do not give a hoot.
I don't want to talk about it.
I warned you.
-So that is why you went ahead.
He just dragged me on the bed.
I do not believe you.
- You think he really wants you.
There are so many other girls.
With those talks about Stanford
he just wants to seduce you.
Take a look outside.
What do you have? Come with me.
It is salty.
What does it say?
"The Guardian of the Lord
warns everyone.
It will happen again. "
Is there really a Guardian?
From meat and blood?
Yes, and it's serious to him.
- But what does he mean by this?
He wants us to stop.
-Why did we get the Book then?
He sets us to the test.
To see if we are wise.
I'm sick of everyone
always wants to test us.
De Wachter wants to protect us.
I'm talking about adults.
They always know everything better.
They can go to hell.
Who would be the Guardian?
-The Book was talking about the Sign.
The Sign Carrier.
Of course.
I already know who the Guardian is.
Mother Clodah?
What are we afraid of then?
An old person with some crucifixes?
-What are you going to do?
We're going to stop her.
Let's go.
We still have a lot to do.
This school costs my father gold money.
- My parents are getting mad.
Forget it.
I can see you tomorrow
use your computer?
Of course. For what?
Nothing special.
What's wrong with you?
How do you mean?
- You are not yourself.
There is nothing.
Would you like to help me?
-Of course.
What are your plans?
I want to go to Stanford.
Just like my dad.
You were crazy about him, right?
You are very mature.
You can almost fly out.
You just have to trust in God.
I have a lot of trouble with that.
I understand that. I also suffered.
But you have to learn to forgive.
You have to forgive your mother for them
you left. And your father too.
Then you have peace with it.
Trust in the Lord.
I've come to bring your food.
-Do you want to put it in?
You have many crucifixes, say.
Kelsey, come with us.
What's your name?
-Faith.
That means 'trust'.
Do you have that too?
Whether I trust in God?
I'm trying my best.
I didn't have it at your age.
I wanted it
and I hoped so too.
But it only happened
when I looked into Jesus' eyes.
So sad and so beautiful.
Who are those girls?
The Illuminatis.
Faith, come join us.
Erica, come with us.
Gina, come with us.
Nicole, come join us.
The Lord is my light and my salvation.
Who would I fear?
When culprits approach me
to eat my meat ...
they will stumble themselves.
We remain confident.
Do you believe?
Help me.
The food is up.
De Wachter is dead.
The girls are ours.
It seems like a heart attack.
She was already walking
to struggle for a while.
The boys from the lab have a sign
found on the corpse from the church.
They had no idea what it was.
Do you want to view the photo once?
Of course.
Come to us, o Long-awaited.
We call You, Master of Spirits.
You move forward with Latin.
- I did my homework.
Blessed are the poor in spirit, right?
-Knowledge is power. I got that from you.
Welcome, come join our circle.
- Here you are among friends.
You are very popular here.
What did you do with them?
- You look like a saint.
You play with fire.
This is a serious matter.
That has always been it, scared.
I'm not scared anymore.
Then come to us.
Then take a look.
Are you not afraid of your soul?
Look here.
You are not devil servants,
but ordinary girls.
Go to bed, girl. And think about it
that you pray. Tomorrow is Good Friday.
We start again.
Hurry up.
Long awaited ...
we call you.
Let us know if we are worthy of you.
It does not work.
The Book is missing its path .
The Book illuminates its path.
I just figured this out.
What are you doing here?
-This is really insane.
I know how it works, I think.
I have been thinking here all day.
This is the way out.
After a long thought I realized.
Take the book.
-Come on, down here.
The Illuminatis knew this way out
apparently not.
How do you mean?
-During that fire.
Where is it?
We have to get the Book back.
We have to find Faith.
I give up. What is it?
This is a diabolical book.
A translation of a book about
black magic. And it really works.
Okay, you wanna get rid of it?
Just give.
So disappeared.
You will not see that book again.
Fish don't do black magic.
It's dry.
I have thought about the power of God.
And I have the answer.
Jamie, what are you doing here?
The power of God does not fall
at that of the long-awaited.
Stop the blasphemy.
You are not a devil's servant.
Then I will serve you.
I pray for your soul rest.
No need.
I would have liked to be with de Wachter
want to talk.
But I want to know one more thing.
How are you planning to stop me?
I'm sending you home.
Look into my eyes.
Tell me all your secrets.
De Wachter is still alive.
We're going to Father Michael.
Get out.
Alarm center.
Send the police to Santa Carlita.
Calm down. I can not do anything
if I don't understand you.
My friend is in danger and I ...
Stay there. We send help.
Wait ...
Thanks for calling.
The book.
-Sorry.
We need it for
the Mirror Conspiracy. Come on.
The Book is ours.
We need some stuff.
First some salt.
And we make it
the consecrated host.
First find Daniel.
Blessed be the soul
of your fairy tale prince.
He will experience a lot,
just before his death.
Can I have the Book?
-The Book is ours.
You do not know what you are doing.
-The power of God is mine.
The Book is lying.
The text was changed 1000 years ago.
How do you know that?
Finally.
Nice dagger.
Stop immediately. I want you
don't hurt. None of you.
The Apocalypse is approaching.
Woe to the earth and the sea.
Because the devil is coming to get you.
He strikes quickly and relentlessly.
With the Mirror Cladding
you don't provoke the Long-awaited.
Lucifer comes to steal your soul.
Just look in the mirror.
Then you can see for yourself.
-Sorry, I just don't believe you.
My order has been trying for a thousand years
to submit the devil to God.
Jamie, come live in the light.
I'm in charge of you.
Let me go.
De Wachter is dead.
Long live the long-awaited one.
What do we do with Faith?
-Let her.
It's Good Friday.
Behold the long-awaited one.
He who knows no equal.
Show us Your dark forces.
Let us see you.
Ancient, enter again
the black earth.
Great pleasures await You.
The rule is yours.
Submit
to the power of the true God.
I brought you back.
I get the power.
The police and the church claimed
that Jamie had gone mad.
That she had Sherilyn and Father Michael
killed and then committed suicide.
They were silent about the devastation
to the font and the room.
So maybe other girls have it
indeed called the devil.
That was my confession, Reverend.