Here bird, here bird bird bird!
Here Birdy!
Here ya go little fella!
Want some bread little guy?
A little bread for you, a
little for you, a bit for you
a little bit for you
oh no!
Aww, looks like a broken wing...
Let's get you inside little
guy, I'll fix ya up!
- Sweetie, Breakfest is almost
ready!
Corning dear!
Look Norma! I found another
hurt bird!
Oh Daryl, not again!
What? Nothing should be in pain!
Ok sweetie but hurry up, your
breakfast is going to get cold!
Ok dear!
Hey Daryl...
Yes dear?
When do you think we'll get
approved for the birthing?
Oh very soon I'm sure!
We filled out all the
paperwork,
went through all the
necessary steps,
These things just take time...
Yeah I know, I just...
Oh how great it would be to
have a child daryl!
How I would love to
raise achild in Heaven!
There ya go little guy, now
you just sit tight,
it'll take a couple
days for you to heal
ha-ha-ha, Can we have a boy?
I would really love a boy!
Oh a boy would be wonderful!
I'll get m
Good morning! Is this the home of
Citizen Daryl, and Citizen Norma?
Yes Siry!
The two of you have been
living in heaven for...
2O years now, correct?
Yes sir
Well congratulations sir!
Today is your lucky day!
Your application for one child
soul has been approved!
So if you and your wife would
like to join me
We have perpared a vehicle to go
to the birthing center right now!
It's the messenger, he's come for us! Norma,
today's the day vve get to give birth!
Oh my god Daryl! We're
getting Our child!
Our child! our child! This is great!
This is wonderful!
Oh daryl I love you so much!
I love you too, and you're
going to be a great mother!
It is now the time to start
the birthing process!
Are you ready Citizen Norma?
I am!
Have you chosen a name for
him yet?
Yes! We wish to call him...
Marius! Little Marius!
Do you two solemnly swear to
raise Marius in accordance
with the texts that Caine
has provided us?
Yes sir!
Do you promise to keep marius
away from the wall
and the evil one that dwells
behind it?
Yes sir!
It is your job to raise your
child up right here in heaven
So that when God gets back,
which should be any day now,
He can look in the eyes of our
newest citizen and know that
they are ready to love
him unconditionally!
Let us all thank Caine together!
(crowd chanting)
Hail Caine! Hail Caine!
This is where we keep
the worms babies
We care for them until they're
ready to be harvested
do you accept that
responsibility?
We do, we do! We surely,
surely do!
Yes! I'm so happy to be given
this honor! I've wanted this
for as long as I can remember!
Then look over at our inventory
and pick the one that looks
the most beautiful to you
take your time,
and choose wisely!
Aaawww this one has
your mothers eyes!
Eeww, this one's too messy!
He-he, ooh, that one has too
much energy!
- Eehhh, it's a little
bit too fat
- That one's too bumpy
-that one has too many veins
- That one's too big!
Aawaww, what's wrong with
that one?
He's just tired, he's
been here for a long time
Nobody has ever wanted him
aaawww, Gary“.!
aaww, poor fella!
In a few days we will have
no choice but to put him down
We want this one!
Sweetie are you sure?
What about this one over here?
You of all people should
understand, you're always trying
to save those birds! I want to
save him, please daryl?
Then lift little Marius into your
arms and present him to your peers!
The process has successfully
completed!
This is your home now
you live here, with us!
We're what's called, "Parents"
We'll care for you, and love
you
and teach you all about heaven until
you become a man of your ovvn
and-and meet a woman!
and fall in love!
And then, when you're
married for a while
you'll get put on a list for
a child soul of your own!
Look sweetie, he's taking a
liking to Caine already!
That's our savior, Caine!
He watches over us and keeps
us safe from the fiends that
want to come back into heaven
but aren't allowed
if it wasn't for him, none of us
would be able to exist right now
He deserves all our love, all
our praise, and all our thanks.
Come now don't overwhelm the boy
he's going to learn all that
in the education center
tomorrow!
I bet you're hungry little guy!
You see Marius, you just put the
fork into the food, like so
and then lift it up into your
mouth and chew, then swallow
Do you understand?
No, no dear, you have
to speak to him louder!
MARIUS! PUT THE FORK...
NO! THE FORK!
INTO YOUR HAND!
HHAAANNNDDD! YOUR HAND SEE!
YOU HAVE TWO OF THEM!
LOOK!
This is your bedroom. This is where
you'll sleep when it gets dark
Sleeping is a time when we close
our eyes and rest for a while
Caine says we need to rest our
eyes for a few hours a night
Because too much exposure to
God's love can wear on the brain
It needs time to rest...
We love your Marius, and we're
so happy you're here!
Ok son this is it! this is
where you'll be spending a
great deal of time until you get
used to things
You'll learn everything you need
to know to become a functioning
member of our society
It may seem a little
overwhelming at first
but it will help everything make
more sense, I promise
Alright class, please take
your seats
My name is Mr Apple
I'll be your teacher for the
next few yea rs
Now if you turn your
information packets to page 3
We will begin our lesson for
today!
Hi, my name's Marius,
what's yours?
Eden“.
Well...Whatcha' looking at?
The wall...
Don't ya wonder what's behind it?
The evil one and all her lies
dwell behind that wall...
Our lord Caine built the wall to
keep her out forever
You see... Caine and the Evil
One were once a team
They built and founded
heaven together
But our humble lord Cainejust couldn't
tolerate her deceitful ways any more...
She wanted to use and
exploit us!
So Caine did what he had to do!
He did it for us!
He cast her out that filth!
So that we may live
here in peace!
Let us all thank Caine!
Look at you little guy!
You look like you've made a full
recovery
Marius! Come here son!
Ok son, put him down
Look at him fly!
You see son, all life in heaven
is equal
One creature is not more
important than the other
we're all alive, and therefore,
we're all loved by God!
And God's love is unconditional!
So if you see one of God's creatures
in danger, it's your duty to help it!
Then, some day, it
might help you back!
Do you understand
what I mean Marius?
Well Gee-wilkers Mr. Dentine
Are you sure it's safe to be carrying
this child so close to the wall while
holding a sign that says
"I Don't Love You Caine"?
Sometimes you just gotta walk
on the wild side lil'johnny
Caine ain't the boss of me!
I'm my own man...
In fact, I'm thinking of maybe
even eating meat on fridays
and slappin' my wife in the mouth!
WOOOOOOOOOW!
No Mr. Dentine, say it ain't so!
Don't denounce Caine! don't do
it! Please don't do it!
Oh no Mr. Dentine
it's the evil one!
RRAAWWWRRR! I am The Evil One!
I want to come into your homes
and corrupt your youth!
And there's nothing any of you
can do about it! HAHAHAHA!
Oh my god what have I done!
If only I could turn back time! If only I could accept and
love Caine for the perfect, non-flawed individual that he is
Stop right there you fiend!
Holy fucking shit it's Caine!
NO! I'm here to destroy
this place!
I will have my way with all
the children!
You will do no such thing!
I cast you Back to the
place from which you came!
No Caine, No! I love you! and
everything is my fault!
You're so much better at everything,
and better looking than me too...
Please take me back Cainey-pie!
PLEASE!
GOODBYE! BITCH!
Wow thank you ever so kindly Mr. Caine!
I will hereby love you forever!
And do whatever you say!
Ladies and gentlemen, don't take
pitty on her
You will find that once the evil one's minions
have all been purged from our society
that heaven will be a much
brighter, and better place
Caine.. I love you like a father
loves his son...
like a dog loves his master...
like a man loves his lover...
I know that sounds wierd but
I also know that you understand
You see but you're blind without his light!
Where will you go?
Who else will turn to in your
darkest hour?
There is no choice!
Accept the only way!
Accept Caine into your heart and
you will understand the truth!
For there is no love without Caine,
there is no life with out caine
There is nothing without Caine!
Hail Caine! Hail Caine! Hail Caine!
Hail Caine!
Please little boy, I need
your help!
I'm hurt badly!
It hurts so bad...
I was trying to peak over the wall
and accidentally fell over...
I think I broke my leg...
Please help!
Marius, Marius, what's
the matter?
The wall, over there, there's a
hole, and I-i peaked through it
I know I shouldn't have but I
did and I saw a hurt kitten
and it looked so desperate!
it's leg was broken!
And it was bleeding
and it was crying!
And I couldn't just
ignore the cries!
I couldn't!
You know me Eden!
Marius you have to take
me there right now!
That's it, look right there
right there eden, see it?
Go see for your self!
I'm gonna wait here
I don't see anything...
Who's There?
Somebody?
Hey! Hey there, my name's
Eden, are you alright?
Please! I'm in a lot of pain!
I fell off the wall and broke
my leg please come and
save me before the evil
one gets me please!
We need to help her!
No-no-no-what? what? no! we
can't, we can't She'll get us!
We just have to be quick...
Hey you kids! get away
from there!
Oh no! Run!!
No Marius no! we can't leave her!
Marius no! let go of me! Let go of me!
After them! Don't
let them escape!
Search the area, make sure
nothing came through...
Shit boss! where did
this hole come from?
Get this hole sealed up
before anyone sees it
Kill anything that
tries to come through
You got it boss!
They say when you go into it you
fall directly into her hand!
And then she carries back to your home,
where she makes you murder all your pets!
One... by... one!
Well Marius and Eden,
how nice of you to join us!
Sorry Mr Apple I'm not as good
as you are and I never will be.
Mr Apple, I was just wondering
can animals... talk?
Just take your seat now!
Does that mean yes or no?
You already know the answer
Marius
Whoa! Oh man.. Eden!
Whoa did you see that?
He was a big guy!
Whoa! Oh man.. Eden!
You know we have to go back
for that kitty, right?
Are you sure it's such a good idea to
go on the other side of the wall Eden?
All I know is that since I've
been here, nothing has felt right
But when the kitty spoke to me I don't
know, I felt something different.
Didn't you feel it?
Whoa! Eden did you see that!
We have to go back Marius!
We have to help that kitten!
Hail Caine! Hail Caine!
Oh! you came back for me!
Yeah just stay still we're going
to rescue you!
Get back in here you little shit stain! or
we're gonna be forced to come and get you!
You don't want that s0n!o the bushes!
- Get back in here right now!
- Hunt them down and kill them! Don't
come back unless you have their heads!
- Here kitty, kitty, kitty here kitty,
kitty, kitty here kitty, come to papa!
You see the fruit on the bush? eat some!
it will make you invisible!
What? No way!
They're special! watch
I'll eat some first!
- They went this way!
- Where ever you are, we
won't hurt you!
- I think I heard them over there!
Hurry eat the fruit!
What? NO!
- Come on fuck heads, this way!
I bet you thought you got away didn't youl?
didn't you, you little shit stainl?
No one escapes us!
NOBODY!
We just want to take
you back to Caine!
What the fuck is this? what the
fuck is this? Get them out of here!
What happened?
We got away, that's all
that matters!
So tired... maybe we
should go back inside...
Where did the hole go? it
was just right there...
It closed to you, well for now
anyway
Once the fruit wears off
you'll be allowed back inside
What do we do until then?
Let's go for a walk! Let me
show you around the world!
What's in there?
Come on, I'll introduce you!
Hello...
What are you doing out here?
I'm trying to find my way back
into the garden...
How did you end up getting
here?
Along time ago...
God was a misfit...
He chose to keep to himself and
he lived alone in the universe
he created beautiful,
radiant stars, circled
by tiny rocks made of
twigs and water...
But they were all vacant, and
without any life...
He was lonely, he wanted
to create something new
He played with them non-stop having
every kind of adventure you can imagine
Then when he exhausted all
possible outcomes
He came to the conclusion that the
creatures he created were less than him...
He could never learn from
them only teach them
and for that reason, he could
never fully love them
God wanted something new
He wanted to create pure beauty
and find, love...
She had curves... and an
opening instead of protrusion
She was delicate and sweet
all you hate to do was gaze
upon her once
and for the rest of your life she would
be the one that emerges from the darkness
Whenever you closed your eyes...
Oh she was more beautiful than God, and now
he knew what it felt like to fall in love.
But he wasn't the only one
who fell in love..
And they loved me more than
they loved him..
God learned something he
never knew about before...
HEARTBREAK!
And from heartbreak grew
jealousy...
and from jealousy came anger...
and finally to hatred!
When god learned how to hate, he saw that the
very fabric of love could easily be broken...
He didn't like the way
it made him feel...
He began to destroy things!
And I lost sight of
where he was...
I was alone and scared...
I loved god...
but in order to be together
everything else must be
destroyed
I am without him...
and now...
I AM NOTHING
I wandered the universe alone
Searching, and searching...
and never finding anything...
(painful screaming) What am I doing wrong?
No! What am I doing wrong?
I didn't look at the creature
the way that god looked at me
I wasn't upset that it wasn't
as smart as me
I felt honored to teach it
a companion that will be with
me forever
and always looked up to me
because I came before it
I discovered love
I became infatuated
with them
The way they moved... the way they
looked... the things they did...
The noises they made...
But... I made some...
mistakes...
and after each mistake... they
became more terrified of me...
until all of sudden.
They forgot who I was...
and they wanted nothing
more to do with me...
God doesn't love me...
he doesn't love me...
and they don't understand me...
lam alone again...
Do you know what make you
kids more comfortable?
Peeling that synthetic misrepresentation
of flesh off of your soul...
Watch, and do what I do!
Oohhh! that feels so
much better!
I can feel the pulsating sound of every
single solitary beam of light...
penetrating every dripping
opening on my soul...
sending shivering shivering bits of life
up and down the jelly in my back...
Don't struggle little guy, you'll
get it stuck in the zipper...
You don't want to get your
soul stuck in a zipper! OUCH!
What the fuck are you doing out
of your house after curfew?
I'm very disappointed in you
son!
How many times have I told you not to
accidentally fall out of your window
in the middle of the night and get into
some late night romantic adventure
with the girl down the street that involves you
outrunning the OSWA evil prevention squad!
There was an attack by the Evil
One's minions a little while ago!
Don't you know we're at an evil alert level
magenta blue green circle square star?
Thank you boys so much for
bringing our pride and joy home!
You could have woke the neighbors up!
his lawn is already greener than mine!
This is all I need!
He was the runt of the litter the Messanger
warned us he'd be little bit off,
would you like a cookie dear?
It's ok ma'am, he's a good boy
just keep him away from the windows until
he learns how to sleep a little bit better
Oh you bet we will! Son, no
windows for a month!
No, that's not fair, alright how
about a week?
We can board them up together
like father and son!
We better get going, keep that
little shit under control!
If I ever catch him near the wall again, I
will be forced to use excessive brutal force
ya hear me?
Of course, thanks again
officers, here I'll see you out
Oh Marius I'm so happy you're
home! I love you so much!
Are you.. ok mom?
Just fine dear! Now let's
get you ready for bed...
Are you sure?
I'm sure that it's the middle of the night
and it's way past your bedtime mister!
No, no, no I mean about...
Hey! You're not disobeying your
mother are you?
Get to bed young man! You have a long day
of nailing your windows shut tomorrow!
But dad!
Move it buster!
Remind him that you love him...
I love you son!
Tell him that he's special...
You're a special boy Marius!
You think I was too hard on him?
No you're a great father!
Where am
Awww, hush now my
little baby sit still.
It will
all be over soon...
What happened?
You've fallen out of the graces
of your superiors my dear
Who are you?
Whoever you want me to be...
He'll? me!
Don't be afraid of them!
They are refilling your
veins with new blood!
Mmmmm, do you hear
that sound?
That's how you know it's
still alive...
mmmm it tastes like dreams!!
Your life is meaningless
You'rejust a slave race to a creature that
had it's back turned during your birth
This pretty little face you're
wearing, it's just a fancy bag
To hold all the liquids in...
Once you're ego is disassembled you simply
find a new bag to wrap your liquids in
you must decide your next form go deep
inside and summon the beast within
you're nothing more than an
animal with a broken leg
limping your way through life
one pathetic step at a time
Your friend escaped here
with hidden knowledge
You must find him
and you must kill him...
The others won't see
you as you really are
Now you'rejust like
me an animal...
Well howdy there strangers, welcome to
Caine's worship kiddie round up ranch!
Say I don't know about ya'll but
I feel like singing a song!
How 'bout it lolipop? Would you
like to sing a song for the kids?
Lolipop? Lolipop where are ya?
I'm over here Uncle T!
Overwhere?
I'm right over here!
Well what in Caine's name are
you doing over there?
Oh! Uncle T it's wonderful! You've got to
come over here! Caine is speaking to me!
Caine is doing what?
Oh Uncle T! Caine is speaking to me right
now, and you can't interupt Caine!
Look! Come sit down with me and you can
hear him speak too it's wonderful!
Oh no! UncleT look!
What is it? ls Caine gonna
tell us something again?
Aw, I think so Uncle T, it's a
dead baby bird EW!!
Oh that's terrible! But you know something,
I think Caine can speak to us through
that little dead bird, you wanna know why?
-vvwhhhyyy?
Because Caine knows every time a little
tiny baby bird dies and falls to the ground
But he leaves it there to show
us how much he loves us
and how much the Evil One
hates us!
Oh I hate that Evil One Uncle T!
You see Marius? You see what
happens when you leave the house?
- We all do Iolipop! hey
watch out!
Don't let those ants bite! Caine provided
us with those ants so they can eat the dead
things and we won't have to look at
their ugly corpses all over the place!
- Oh I would have to trip over my dead
sinning grandpa on the way to church!
Exactly Lolipop! So you see
Caine thought of everything!
What happened? Norma?
NORMA!
Norma what are you doing?
Marius don't look!
Why, What's going on dad??
Don't look cover your eyes! -Please Daryll!
Please help me!
Dad why aren't we helping Mom?
What's going on??
You don't understand Marius... couples... they
don't see each other without their clothes on
What? Why? it's one of the rules, GEEZ! What are they
teaching you in those schools..
But we can't just let her suffer
in there dad!
It's Heaven son, there's
no suffering in Heaven!
Dad that's Mom we
have to do something!
How about some ice cream?
How is it? Marius, is it
good?
I don't know dad! I'm not exactly in
the mood for ice cream right now...
Ah sure you are! It's always
a good time for ice cream!
Ice scream, you scream, we all
scream for ice cream! ha ha ha!
Seriously though don't ever scream
unless you're really in danger
Otherwise people are not
going to believe you!
Can we at least check on mom?
Hun, do you have any
clothes on yet??
- Ooww! Daryl please! Daryl!!
Daryl help me!
We better wait a little while she
sounds like shes in a mood right now!
- Please! Please Stop!
Ha! well look at you,
all better?
Good sir, could you possibly spare some
bread for a bird down on his luck?
Marius, that wasn't funny!
Hey! Hey! hey! Down here! -What the ff...
Take a look down good man
You can talk??Of course I can! Didn't
they teach you anything in school sir
No! Well I mean.. maybe..
Hey relax, no big deal! maybe they just
forgot, I mean they forgot to teach
your son about the thing with the naked
ladies!
Your wife is in the other room giving
birth to something rather fierce
You should really get
in there and help her.
But bird... I can't get in there
while her... squidlypie is out!
I'm sure that under the circumstances
you'd be forgiven for your trespasses
Can you just maybe go in there and
make sure the Evil One isn't in there?
You have my word good sir there is
no one of evil descent currently
occupying your living room! just the
beauty and magic of child birth
do go inside and see, go on!
Please? Fine then, I'll
play along wait here!
Hhmmm yes sir, everything
seems to be in order here!
Son, I want you to get
out of here and get help
but, but dad they're gonna..
I know, it doesn't matter, we
have to help your mother, so go
Alright, I love you dad!
I love you too son...
So clearly Caine is telling us that as long as
you stay here with him, you'll never ever die!
Help me please! Please I need
somebodies help!
My Morn is naked and my
Dad is talking to birds!
Help me please! Help! Help! Please anybody!
Somebody help me!
Caine I want to thank you for being
there for me, when nobody else was!
You helped me go on!
You save me from the darkness!
You saved me from drowning
in the darkness!
He's like the slug that's going over
the razors blade with his slime
but he's doing it with angel bite bro! Oh man
dude! He's got it figured out! I see him once
Well not really but, you know what? He comes
to me at night and he gives me good ideas
He tells me, "go preach my word
brotha and I'll look at fiarya"
oowvv! ooww! Daryl! Please! there's
something coming out of me!
Please do something!
Please it hurts!
Hey sweetie... -Ow! Daryl!!
Owl! You doing ok?
Daryl! Daryl Please! get it out of me!
get it out of me!
Can I get you a drink,
or a cool towel or something?
Daryl! Daryl I spoke to God!
Oh yeah?
He's not coming back...
What?! Did he say why? It
wasn't something I said was it?
He's not coming back because
this isn't heaven...
And now I have demon inside
of me...
A demon?
Daryl... Daryl please get it
out of me! Get it out of me!
Oh heavens me!
Help me! Help me! Help me! My
daddy's talking to birdys!
My mommy's running
around naked!
Stop right there! Put down the
weapon or prepare to be slaughtered!
Ow fuck! Ow fuck! Somebody help me!
Somebody help me!
Code dark gray! code dark gray! Deploy
plan X! Outbreak extermination!
Daryl! Daryl! Ha ha ha! d-d-d-daryl!
Wake up Daryl! Daryl wake up!
Wakey Wakey Daryl! Daryl...
I need you to do something for me,
your wife is a very special lady
and she is carrying something
of great value!
But it's too heavy to carry on my own,
can you bring it somewhere for me?
What are you talking about?
- Please good sir, you've always
helped us birds in the past!
What is it?
It's a surprise!
What do I do?
Go into the kitchen, get
yourself a knife!
A great big sharp shiney one! How
about one of those new ones you
ordered the other day
from that magazine?
Oh yes, the one that had that really neat
video where they cut the tin cans in half!
Well now what do I do?
Aw yeah, take it into the living
room, take off all your clothes
You don't want to get her sticky juices on them,
now do you? After all, cleanliness is next
to godliness, you want to look back
when God comes back, don't you? Eh?
Lay down next to her and hold
her in your arms, yes!
Don't worry sweetie, the talking
bird says it's going to be ok!
Comfy isn't it? Go on now, don't be bashful! Rub
against her a little, at least a bit until you
feel the tingling, that's God's way of
rewarding you for a life well lived!
That's love Daryl! That's love!
yes!
This feels... kinda nice...
Oh yes I bet it does! Why My good sir it
even looks as though you are glowing!
Not a shy one I see! She's like putty in
your hands! Now you've got her wrapped
around your little finger! She trusts you
completely! You can raise that knife up
and make an opening for that abomination
to rip it's way into this world!
Oh yes! rip it out!
Rip it out!
Quick don't let it escape, chase
after it!
I love you Norma! I'll be
back soon I promise!
Quick! Go now, chasey
chasey!
Cut them all in half! Gut
them like pigs! ha ha ha!
Kill them! Kill them!
Butcher these damn cunts!
Wanna fuck with me? I'll show
you who you're fucking with!
Eat my fucking steel you
fat fuck!
Slaughter them all! Slaughter
the flesh bags! Fuck em up!
Kill them! kill them all!
You again? Where are
your parents boy?
Please lord! Please descend from the
sky on your diamond studded chariot
Pulled by four white horses that can
fly with angel wings of their own!
Please lord! Please come down from
the sky and take me back with you!
Oh my lord, is that you? Have you
come for me? Have come back?
Is the waiting over?
Ma'am we found your son wandering the streets
muttering something about his mother
walking around with no cloths on
in the privacy of her own home
which is an offense punishable
by exile, is this true?
I met god tonight...
Fucking hell... -!Sir the boy's mother has an exit
wound between her legs, how should we proceed?
Right, citizen Norma, due to high treason your
right to exist in this world has been revoked
prepare to be evacuated!
You are my sunshine, my only sunshine,
you make me happy when skies are gray
You never know dear, how much I love
you, please don't take my sunshine away
Didn't I tell ya? I told ya! yeah
who is the motherfucking man?
I'm the motherfucking man! oh yeah!
who's the man? Who is the man?
The man, is Caine! It's Caine! Go Caine!
It's Caine! Go Caine!
Uummm h-hello?
How could you? This world I
provided for you isn't enough?
You still had to go crawling
back to her
I-I don't understand...
No matter what I do...
No matter what I give you
You all still end up loving her
more, I just don't understand
I just wanted to help the hurt kitty,
I was trying to do the right thing...
You have brought lies into
heaven!
But I understand Marius, more than you
think. I understand the allure she can have
But do you know what? She
will turn on you Marius
She will guide you down the wrong
path, and then she will turn on you
You know since you have come in
here you haven't praised me once
How am I supposed to know
that you love me?
Didn't mean for any of
this to happen, I'm sorry!
Aaannnnnddd?
And, I uh, think you're.. much...
you're much...uhh
Prettier...
P-p-rettier... than-
You must never speak her
name outloud!
Saying her name is like admitting
she exists, it feeds into her ego!
Show me, how you pray!
Are you going to stop fucking lying to me?
Are you? Tell me the Truth!
What do you want to know? I'll
tell you anything!
Tell me what her voice sounds like... Did
she comfort you? What did she say about me?
I don't know dude! Something about
worms, and these lights Bitch was crazy!
You actually spoke to her? You actually
spoke to her? You ate her fucking fruit?
That doesn't surprise me!
You know there was once a time when she loved
me, and as hard as I try to keep her out
a part of me always wishes she would
try to break back the fuck in
She's like the ghost of girl
that's still alive
I am haunted by her, and I love
her, as much as I hate her
...and there she was... The most
beautiful creature I had ever seen
a tall slender girl with long
strawberry blonde hair
and lips that only knew
how to speak my name.
I knew that every moment of my time
here, must be spent only with her...
Hey there...
I never felt anyone
who feels like you do
Your skin, your lips
You my dear, are perfect
oohhh! I love the sounds
that come out of your mouth!
I could just lay here and talk
to you all night long
I feel so safe with you! Like
nothing bad could everhappen!
Why are the others afraid
of me?
Well that's because you're different, they don't
understand you the way that I do.
The fruit, maybe that's the
-answer!
Can you help me get the others
to eat it?
How can you say no to
those eyes?
Oh your beauty! Nothing compares to your
beauty, in anything in the universe!
Thank you! Yes! You're too kind! Thank you!
I don't like it when the
other ones eat your fruit...
What do you mean?
It just doesn't make me
feel very good
That's no fair to every one else,
it would be selfish not to share!
And suddenly I don't
feel so special anymore
I don't mean to cause alarm, but
I can't stop thinking about you
I'm glad I finally got you alone I need you. I
can't get your very image from inside my brain
Such wonderess curves, those luscious lips with
your forests of long
tangly orange hair and that piercing
way that you look deep inside my eyes!
It's as if you can see all the way into
my soul! You just drive me insane!
You bring something out of me! You
give me this weird tickling itch
but no matter how hard I
scratch I just can't sooth it!
It's becoming swollen, please
just touch it for me! Please!
What? Get off of me!
I'll do anything for you! I would
slice apart the tallest mountain
behead the beast of your choosing! I would even
walk on water if it prevented you from drowning
Now how about we get to know
each other a little better!
Stop! Stop it! Oh!
Please! Stop it!
What's that?
One by one they all found their way to the top of
the hill that day
Partaking in every pleasure
that this place had to offer.
Binging and purging all at once
She just opens up her legs and she
radiates a brand new set of colors
that nobodies ever known before
Then you fall in love with her when you realize
that the others only project the colors
that you have already seen!
God?! is that you? Is it really you?
And that was the day the sky
opened up and God created death
It rained down from the heavens in
a fiery load of passion and filth!
Those who chose to sacrifice their virginal beauty to
their whore Goddess
were stripped of their identities and forced to
remain on their scorched
planet as carcoal stained doves
She claimed that she was
more beautiful than God
But death was more beautiful than her
and as his last piece of revenge, god decided that
she would never be-allowed to die
No! What have you done? Damn you! DAMN YOU!
I hope you enjoy living in this pit
alone for the rest of eternity.
I am going to erase you
From this moment on you do not exist to me
Now leave me alone!
But I wasn't the only one left alive
A lot of us had survived and we had all seen that
thing in the sky together
We knew who it was, and that someday it would be
back for us
Until then we must worship, respect, and most of all
we must fear it
But we didn't all see eye to eye
Some believed that her! Fruit had a lot of good to
offer
That much could be
learned from it
We reached an agreement. Those that wanted to
live a pure god loving life came with me
The rest chose to remain in the forest like animals,
constantly blinded by the color of her lies
Caine? Caine? Caine? Are you There? Caine? Can you
hear me? Hello?
What for fucks sake?! I am trying to tell a story down
here!
Sorry sir, but we found the
boys father
He was just seen scaling the wall and
he was.. naked.. and carrying something
Well fan-fucking-tastic! Just what I need! And on
top of it all I lost my fucking place
in the fucking story!
-Sorry sir!
Go over the wall and get him!
Uh... are you.. are you sure?
You heard me! Put on your little helmet and climb
into the big boy seat of that
great big fucking tank I got you and
wipe him off the face of this planet!
You got that you dumb fuck?
-Sir, yes sir!
Where am I?
You're waking up out of your dream
Where's that breathing coming from?
Your lungs Daryl
Where's Marius? Where's Norma?
Don't worry about them! They're both fine!
Probably gathered around the telly watching their
loolo on the evening news helping out his bird friends!
Wonderful human interest story, don't ya think?
There seem to be a lot of animals out here tonight,
don't you think?
Just ignore them and keep moving!
Why are they watching me?
Because they hate you and they want to taste your
stringy flesh!
I don't like the way it's
eyes are looking at me!
Just shut up will ya, you're too stupid for this
conversation!
Just keep moving!
-!I want to be it's friend!
But I don't know how to communicate with it
Why did he do this?
Why would he put all of us in the same
place and not let us talk to each other?
Look you disgustings waste of flesh the only way
I can get out of here is through God's door
but I need him to open it first. Now you're either
going to help me do that
or my friends are going to hold you down and I'm going
to peck the fucking eyes out of your big stupid skull
Do you understand what I'm saying or should I
cleverly word it into a sitcom script
so that your feeble little
brain can process it easier?
I don't feel so good...
everything looks so weird!
Do you think you're the first man to travel down this
path ofelightenment?
Do you think you're something special
If you were rotting on the side of the road
I wouldn't even stop to eat your face meat
Shut up! shut up! Stop talking to me! Shut up! shut
up! Stop it! Leave me alone!
Why don't you just kill them Daryl? Kill them!
Draw a weapon fromyour side
and slaughter them one by one
Kill them daryl! KILL THEM DARYL!
Kill them, and eat them! Chew the meat off their
boned
Taste their souls!
Stop it! Get out of here! Just leave me alone! Leave
me alone!!
Daryl stop crying! Daryl, Daryl stop crying! Calm
down. Don't cry Daryl!
I just want to talk to the animals...
like we're equal!
Come on Daryl, we're here! Come on Daryl, get up,
we're here!
Now you can talk to any animal you want I promise,
just open your eyes!
Ok, Ok...
What are you?
Place that beast on the altar
What?!
I said place the creature on the altar!
Tell me who you are
We are the remains on an ancient people who
chose the path of the life giver
instead of the sky monster
what do you want from me??
You hold in your hands the only creature
to ever be born from a virgin skin
In her eyes it's the most
beautiful thing ever created
That's why I want you to rip its guts out and
dangle them in front of her fucking face!
NEVER!
She must be punished,
for what she's done!
Every second must be lived
in agony, just like us!
There's no way out! It's best you just do what she
says
Just be happy you met her before the other one!
Otherwise you might have ended up like me
I said kill itl!
Come on Daryl do it! Plunge that blade straight
through its heart!
It killed your wife, remember? What do
you care, it's not of your seed anyway
Look at it's eyes! They're so bright...
full of life
There's a soul in there!
Shut your fucking mouth and do what I say!!
Almighty Caine, please open the sky so that I may
receive your light...
Please open your heart so that I may receive your
love!
What are you doing??
Please open your home that
I will never be alone!
You shut up right now!
For I love you the almighty Caine!
Stop saying that!
And should I ever find myself
lost in the shadow of the beast
then grant me the ability to see through the
darkness and find your path again!
I said shut up!
SHUTTHE FUCK UP!
Almighty Caine, please open the sky
so that I may receive your light...
Please open your heart so that I
may receive your love!
STOP SAYING THAT! Please open your home that -I
will never be alone!
For I love you the almighty
Caine!
And should I ever find myself lost in the
shadow of the beast I SAID KILL FOR ME!
Then grant me the ability to see through the
darkness and find your path again!!
What the fuck are you doing??
Sir, you told us to go after the boys father!
I didn't say knock down the fucking
wall while you were doing it!
Are you out of your fucking mind??
No sir, sorry sir, you're
right sir, I am scum sir!
Come on now you stupid bunny fuck! YOU!
FUCKING! BUNNY! RABBIT! FUCK!
What kind of bunny has blue eyes you fucking
aryan piece of shit!
FUCK YOU BUNNY! FUCK YOU BUNNY!
BUNNNNNYYYY!
Give me your hand! COME ON!
COME ON!
I'll pull you up! Don't be afraid!
Caine is here!
I warned you not to go behind that wall!
Hail Caine! Hail Caine! Hail Caine!
It always happens the same way
I create them, they forget me, rediscover me, and
fall in love
Then they destroy each other
That's the problem with pure beauty. No two
people will ever see it the same.
They will fight over the color of your eyes, ignoring
your words completely.
Every now and then one of them
will wonder back into the cave
usually by accident or through
a series of misguided dreams
As soon as they discover me they try to worm their
way back inside of me
but I won't let them! and it drives them crazy
and that's how I learned the truth... He wasn't
waiting for me up there with opened arms
he didn't want me back. He wanted me to stay
bound
so I couldn't float towards him ever again
I will lay here with my eyes closed tightly
drifting in and out of consciousness
Where I will dream of laying beside him,
as he whispers forgiveness in my ear
praying that this world he created for me, will still
be here, when I wake up...