♪ ♪
(music continues playing
through phone)
♪ ♪
MAN (recorded voice):
The Department
of Veterans Affairs
is committed
to outstanding care.
Please continue to hold,
and we will return--
OPERATOR: Hi, Ms. Morisseau.
Thanks for holding.
I'm looking at Walter's
file here.
You said the program
is called "Homecoming"?
-Yes. "Homecoming."
-Okay, yes...
I haven't heard from my son
in two weeks,
and I've been trying to reach
him, but there's no listed...
Yeah, so, ma'am,
that's not a V.A. program.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, I'm seeing here, uh,
it's administered by
a private contractor--
Geist Emergent Group.
Geist?
Yeah. It's not here at the V.A.
That's all we have.
Is there anything else
I can help you with?
No.
(sighs)
♪ ♪
Glory? You ready?
We're gonna be late.
-What's this?
-Geist.
EVITA:
So? What about them?
-They made all of that?
-No.
But they make
household products,
like shampoo, drain cleaner,
-laundry detergent...
-So?
And they just want him to talk
about his feelings? No.
Him who?
What are you talking about?
Walter. The place
that they sent him to.
It doesn't make sense.
I know you're upset,
doudou mwen.
I know you miss him.
That's not what
I'm talking about.
Why would a company
that makes shampoo
and drain cleaner...
Glory, you are my sister
and I love you.
But when you get like this...
I don't need to convince you.
-Where are you going?
-Tampa.
Now? Eske l konnen w ap vini?
Tanpri!
I'm his mother.
I don't need to announce when...
He ran halfway around the world
to get away from your nonsense.
Evita!
It's true.
He'll be home in four weeks,
Glory.
What do you have to say that
you can't say on the phone?
I'm not saying anything.
-What do you mean?
-I'm bringing him home.
(door shuts)
(instrumental of Air Supply's
"All Out of Love" playing)
♪ ♪
(coins dispense)
Hey, I owe you.
I'm sorry?
I-- You waited on me
at that fish place,
and I-I owe you a tip, so...
Oh, it's okay.
Here, please.
I insist.
You'd be doing me a favor.
I-I could tell myself
what a good guy I am.
Sure. Thank you.
Thank you.
-So, anyone strike it rich yet?
-Hmm?
Uh, black gold?
From the jar?
Oh, no. Not yet.
(chuckles)
Oh. Well, there was only
a couple cards in there
anyway, right?
I mean, who are these people?
Do you ever notice?
Uh, no.
It's just funny, 'cause...
Jesus, man.
Oh...
-What?
-Look, I'm sorry.
I just got back from
Afghanistan, like,
72 hours ago,
and clearly I've forgotten
how to have a normal
conversation... sorry.
You were in the military?
I was. Not anymore.
I'm more of a contractor now.
Well, welcome home.
Thanks.
I'm Hunter.
-It's nice to meet you.
-Heidi.
WALTER:
Can I ask you a question?
I was just wondering if
I took things too far
the other day.
Too far?
With the bird? I...
Oh, no, it was... it wasn't--
I mean, it's fine.
Okay, 'cause you seemed like you
were a little upset about...
I wasn't.
(phone rings)
Yes, it's Heidi.
(thunder rumbles)
Okay.
I'll be right there.
Um, can you just
stay right here?
I need to check on something.
Yeah.
(sighs)
(door opens, closes)
REINA:
Ma'am, this is protocol.
I didn't write these policies.
You need to fill out a form...
Seems to me like
you don't have any idea.
Heidi, hi. Um, we're having
a little bit of an issue here.
What issue?
Explain it to me.
This is Walter's mom.
(thunder rumbles)
Wow. Yes. Hi.
I'm Heidi Bergman.
REINA: I told her that we can't
have unscheduled visitors,
but she doesn't seem to think
that I know what I'm doing.
You're in charge?
You work for Geist?
They're the ones that
run this place, right?
Is everything all right?
If there's been some kind
of emergency, we can...
Oh, there's no emergency.
He's my son.
I want to see him.
You're telling me
that's not allowed?
Why would that be?
Well, the purpose
of this facility is
to ease Walter's transition,
and he's been doing great.
It's just that visitors,
especially family, can be...
I drove here from Georgia.
I have 28 papers to grade
and nowhere to be.
Should I call security?
No, no, let's, um...
REINA:
Heidi,
all visitor requests have to be
approved ahead of time.
Well, she's here now,
and she's not going anywhere.
It's fine.
Mrs. Morisseau, why don't you
come with me, please?
(whispering):
It's fine.
Right this way.
What was that all about?
You live in Valdosta, right?
How long was the drive?
It should've been three hours.
Traffic?
No. I didn't have the address.
How did you find us?
Walter said an office park
outside Tampa,
near a swamp and
a retirement community.
-Must be a dozen of those.
-Only eight.
-So you just...
-This was number six.
Mom?
Mom, what did you...
what are you doing here?
I just wanted to see you.
Why don't we all
sit down and talk?
Walter...
Tanpri, fè fanm sa ale.
Got it. Mmm.
Heidi, I'm sorry.
I haven't seen my mom
in a while,
so do you mind
giving us a second?
Sure. Of course.
(muffled rain continues
falling outside)
So, a month ago,
I'm about a hundred miles
outside of Kandahar,
in the middle of nowhere,
and she calls,
says she wants a divorce.
-Wow.
-Right?
Said the whole thing
was too hard on her.
Too hard on her.
-That's pretty rough.
-(laughs)
Well, look, I-I didn't
even get mad, really.
I-I... it was more like...
Fuck this?
Yes, exactly. Fuck this.
Well, look,
I-I-I'd be gone so much
I-I couldn't even remember how
to talk to her anymore,
you know,
or even how to be, really.
Maybe she... maybe she just did
what I was afraid to do.
I'm having, like,
a breakthrough here.
-(chuckles)
-Sure you're not
a couples counselor on the side?
Only on weekends.
Oh.
(Colin sighs)
It's after 1:00. I'm starving.
HEIDI: There's a Chinese place
next door.
Well, how about you? You hungry?
I'm sorry.
You know, it feels really good
to talk about this stuff.
I don't, I don't really get
that many chances.
I-I'm sorry.
Sure. I could eat.
So, you know, I...
after my last tour,
I came home, you know,
tried to get back into things,
relationships, work, but it
just... I didn't fit, you know?
So I went back.
There's a lot of us over there,
ex-soldiers working
as contractors.
We know our way around.
You like it?
It's all right.
-Kind of lonely.
-I bet.
Way out there.
Country's beautiful.
It's not that.
(stammers)
You know, I'm surrounded
by these government people
and you just have to watch
everything you say.
The truth is the last thing
you want to tell them.
Why?
Because they'll use it
against you.
Oh, they act like they're
just doing their job,
but their job is
to find someone to blame.
I'm making it sound like...
No. I know what you mean.
You do?
Yeah.
Someone using you like that?
What?
You know, hassling you, trying
to get something from you?
No.
Because you were just saying...
(chuckles)
I was just being polite.
-Doing it again.
-What?
-Interrogation mode.
-What is that?
Mm, nothing.
Just my work, you know.
Getting information from people.
I just slip into it sometimes
without realizing. Sorry.
Well, I got nothing for you.
Whining about my divorce
and now I'm grilling you.
Jesus, man,
it's a first fucking date.
A first what?
And on that note, I think it's
time to order my first drink.
I should probably...
What? What do you mean?
It's... (stammers)
That's bad luck, you know.
What is?
-Folding laundry while sober.
-(chuckles)
-That is one thing
my mother taught me.
-Oh, really?
It's the only thing, really.
Look at me.
(laughs)
♪ So very much in love ♪
♪ With you. ♪
You gonna tell me
what this is about?
(sighs) She doesn't have
any pictures.
No family, no nothing.
You need to be smarter.
You need to think.
-Think about what?
-Sa w ap fè la?
E fanm sa, Heidi Bergman?
What does she want?
She wants to help.
That's her job.
She supposed to be
some kind of doctor?
Where did she go to school?
What does that have
to do with anything?
Ou pa konn anyen.
You just believe.
But this government doesn't
give away nothing for free.
There's a reason you are here.
Yes, there's a reason.
It's for treatment.
Treatment? Pou kisa?
There's nothing wrong with you.
Nothing's wrong.
I just need to be here.
They want you to think
that there's something wrong,
that you need them,
but you don't need some
therapist making you talk
about what you saw,
what you did.
Look, no one's making me
do anything.
You don't know that, Walter.
Kisa w te wè lot bo a?
If you made a mistake,
-if they tricked you somehow...
-Tricked?
I know the terrible things
that go on over there.
But you think the generals
and their sons
are going to take the blame? No.
Mom, where do you get this shit?
Watch your mouth, Walter.
So what? What's the point
of all this?
They just bring us here
to work on our problems?
That's all part
of their evil plan, huh?
Yes. They bring you here and you
say, "I'm crazy, I'm violent,"
and you show them your weakness
and then they take
advantage of it.
This is exactly how it was
when I enlisted.
-I'm not talking about that.
-Yeah, well, I am.
You said you wanted to serve,
ou te fè.
You're not serving anybody here.
You're being used.
And you're just afraid.
Ou gen rezon,
I am afraid.
I just want you to come home.
♪ ♪
(quietly):
He's packing.
Craig, just go back
to your desk.
We should call security.
No, it's not necessary.
He's had a week four dosage,
Heidi.
If he quits his meds
at this point,
-he's going to go
into withdrawal.
-I know. I know.
Okay, I need to inform Colin.
-I'm sorry.
-No.
What do you mean, "no"?
Heidi...
Have you lost your grip
on what it is we're...
Craig, I haven't lost
a fucking thing.
Now shut your wet little mouth,
turn around
and go back to your toys.
(knocks on door)
Hey.
Walter, what's going on?
I gotta go back with her.
She's having a tough time,
basically, so...
All right.
Look, I'm sorry I have to leave
in the middle of all this.
I'll get back as soon as I can.
Well, if it's what you feel
you need to do, I...
of course I understand.
Just, is it what
you really want?
She's my mom.
She's upset.
It's simpler this way.
Okay.
Can you answer my question,
though?
What do I want?
Yes. You talk about
what you owe
the people in your life
or how you failed them,
like Shrier or Lesky,
but... what do you want?
I don't think that's
a good way of deciding.
Why?
Because if I stayed,
it might be so I can focus
on getting better.
I think that's really important.
But it might be
so I can be with you.
You ever think about that?
I just...
think for you to leave treatment
at this time could be dangerous.
-Dangerous?
-I...
Not... No, not dangerous,
just a little risky to...
To what?
I just don't think
you should leave
if you're not sure you're ready.
Right.
But can you answer my question?
I do.
What?
Think about that.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Please leave a message for...
COLIN:
Colin Belfast.
-(message beeps)
-Hi, Colin, it's Heidi.
I just wanted to let you know
we had an unexpected visitor
here today.
But I... managed the situation
and everything is... is fine.
Okay.
-(door closes)
-WALTER: Heidi?
Walter, I just...
Mrs. Morisseau.
You got what you wanted,
didn't you?
Gloria.
I'm sorry, I just...
It's important to me.
Maybe if I explained more
about our approach...
I understand that,
dealing with the government
and the military,
you don't always feel like
your son's best interests
are a priority.
-They're not.
-(exhales)
I understand
why you feel that way,
but my only intention here
is to help Walter.
-If you could just trust me...
-Trust?
I shouldn't worry about what the
military is doing with my son
because you, Heidi Bergman,
feel that your intentions
are good.
Well, Walter chose to stay.
It's what he wants.
I think you should
try to respect that.
What he wants?
That hasn't mattered
since the day he enlisted.
Well, he's done with that.
It's different here.
It's no different, this place.
Maybe you know that, or maybe
you've convinced yourself
you're serving a greater good.
Maybe you care
about Walter's treatment.
Or maybe you just care
about him.
It doesn't matter.
If you think
that you can protect him,
or anyone else,
in a place like this,
then you're a fool.
(car door opens, closes)
(engine starts)
(insects trilling)
(laughing)
So we have, um, one drink...
-Yeah.
-...after four years
and he calls me the next day.
Unbelievable.
-Thank you.
-(both chuckle)
Uh, he said, uh...
God, what did he say?
He said, "Oh,
it's the weirdest coincidence"
and, uh, he's in my town
and wants to know if he could
stay at my place.
-No.
-But just for a couple of days.
-No, no.
-(laughs)
What did he mean?
What did you do?
Um, I said, uh,
"Anthony, I'm-I'm really sorry,
but my mom won't let me
have sleepovers."
(laughs)
Which is true.
-(phone buzzing)
-But wasn't very nice.
Yeah.
Anthony deserved it.
-Yeah.
-(chuckles)
(exhales)
Is everything all right?
Yeah, it's my wife.
My ex, sorry, my ex-wife.
Wants me to sign
the divorce papers.
Every time we talk,
I make up another excuse.
(chuckles)
She thinks I'm still
in Afghanistan.
(Colin chuckles)
Do you ever get sick of it?
What?
Just... lying like that?
Well, no. I mean, uh...
-I...
-I mean, d...
Don't worry, I'm...
I'm a liar, too.
-You?
-Mm.
What... what do you lie about?
Just every day, I...
I go to work,
I pretend to be this...
this person, this waitress.
I serve people and I smile,
and then I go home,
and it's the same thing.
I pretend to be a...
a good daughter,
and sometimes
I convince myself...
this is me, this is real.
I know what you mean.
Oh, but then I...
like, I'll be in my car,
or right when I wake up,
and it's like I just appeared
out of nowhere.
I can just see my whole life.
It's phony and fake.
And every word that I say,
every second...
I don't know, but if it's...
that is a lie,
then where's the other one,
the real one?
The real what?
Me.
The--
The one I won't let myself see.
Hmm.
But then I start to think,
what difference does it make?
If we lie?
If we lie or tell the truth,
or if it's real or fake
or just...
I just want to take it all
and just...
put it in one place
and just say...
Fuck this?
Yes. Exactly.
Fuck this.
Um...
That's not what you meant,
is it?
HEIDI:
No, it isn't.
Okay.
♪ ♪
MAN (recording):
Hello.
You have reached
the Department of Defense
complaint hotline.
Please begin after the beep.
(beeps)
GLORIA:
Hello, yes,
I do have a complaint.
This is--
I was just now
at the Homecoming building.
In fact, I can say this.
I work there at the facility.
I am on the staff.
And I have seen something.
One of the soldiers,
Walter Cruz,
he wants to leave,
he wants to go home,
but they won't let him.
It's against--
He's being held here,
and so he needs to be
sent home right away.
Or... or I don't know
what will happen.
(traffic passing outside)
(Colin inhales deeply)
-Hi.
I'm tired of it.
Of what?
Lying.
Okay.
I think I did something...
something wrong,
and I don't know what it is.
Okay.
Let's figure it out.
(wind whooshing)
(televisions droning)
(indistinct chatter)
(car doors open, shut)
(televisions droning)