Subtitles by explosiveskull
Libby.
You did amazing work.
I knew I could count on you.
Peace or terror!
What a morning.
Students, welcome to
Course number 422, cap 23
Understanding
Contemporary Warfare.
I apologize for the hullabaloo
you may have encountered
entering the building
but it was a one-off,
I can assure you.
As you may or may not be aware
Professor Shimka, who was
scheduled to teach this course
suffered a heart attack
some weeks back.
In his stead, we are honored
to have secured
the services and talents
of one of the most brilliant
and innovative minds
in American foreign policy
today, Elizabeth Lamm.
Elizabeth received her BA
from Princeton
and her Ph.D.
from the University of Chicago.
Fluent in French,
Japanese, Pashtu..
Winter break, I'm getting
the left hip replaced.
End of the school year,
the right one.
Already, I've had
both knees worked on.
I have the best orthopedic guy,
if you're ever in need.
- Not yet, anyway.
- Willa?
Oh, how did it go?
How crazy was it?
Were arrests made?
Campus cops handled it
with aplomb
a very pleasant surprise.
Wouldn't you agree, Elizabeth?
Yes, security was excellent.
Gracious, my manners.
Everything's moved so fast
I forget you've only
just arrived.
Elizabeth, this is Dee.
Elizabeth.
Without Dee, the office would come
to a grinding and very messy halt.
Whatever you need,
just let us know.
Thank you. I will.
Martin!
There he is,
my phantom roommate
the international
man of mystery.
- Jordan.
- Where you've been?
Like, I know we've
only known each other
a short time, but I worry.
It's my nature, right?
I'm like my Jewish
grandmother that way.
Just, uh, just shoot me
a text, or something.
"Great seeing you too, Jordan."
Thanks for givin' a shit.
You're right, I could've
fallen in a lake and drowned.
- No one would ever have known.
- Thank you.
Hey, any time, roomie.
And this is you.
I'm afraid it's rather Spartan
in terms of creature comforts.
It's perfect, actually.
Well, it may not
be Foggy Bottom
but welcome to academia.
Once everyone gets
to know you, Elizabeth
I think you'll find we have
a good bunch of folks here.
Hearts are in the right place.
It's fine.
I'm used to it. Really.
October 21st, 1805
Napoleon's Navy,
under the command
of Admiral
Pierre de Villenueve
is wiped out
by the British Fleet
under the command
of Admiral Horatio Nelson.
This engagement, known as
the Battle of Trafalgar
establishes Britain's dominance
of the high seas
for the century to come.
Surprisingly,
such a stinging defeat
does little to deter Napoleon.
If anything, his obsession
with crossing the Channel
only grows after Trafalgar.
- Am I interrupting?
- Not at all.
Couple of housekeeping matters.
Would you prefer using your
own email for correspondence?
Or I can set you up
with a department address?
Neither.
I'm old school that way.
- Really?
- Really.
- I prefer hard copies.
- Okay.
Can I have your cell number
for the office?
Don't have one.
You don't have a cell phone?
No, I don't.
Home phone number.
Sorry.
Well, how do you communicate
with the world?
Slowly.
It's all so close, isn't it?
The pieces, the stars
they are aligning.
What a view you have here.
Majestic.
The entire compound
is just breathtaking.
Thank you. It's been
in my family for generations.
I don't really like the lake.
Too many bugs, water's too cold,
no sand.
I know, right? Poor me.
You're having doubts.
By that definition, the US
military uses WMDs every day
and theoretically could be
prosecuted by foreign governments
if they were to adopt
a similar law.
For example,
the N67 hand grenade
is a fragmentation device with an
explosive charge of 6.5 ounces.
So, it qualifies as a WMD
on two counts.
Dannisha?
When you say "Prosecuted
by foreign governments"
you mean prosecuted
as war criminals.
That exact definition,
that wording
I believe, is a matter
for the courts to decide.
Does a figure this polarizing
earn the right
to be given a platform like
this just for her notoriety?
Some will say yes,
uh, some will say no.
Some will say she shouldn't
even be walking free.
But you have to look
to the GU administration
for the real reason
behind this.
Money.
- Oh, fuck.
- What the fuck?
Now, Martin, you show up now?
Just leavin'.
What, hold, we can go
in my room. You don't have to...
No, I'm out of here. Thanks.
What was he doing
in the dark like that?
This is what I've been saying.
I am concerned much of
the analysis is unsubstantiated.
Some will say
it's all circumstantial.
But that's nonsense. Do you
think it's circumstantial?
No, I do not. But wanting
to believe something...
Do you realize that Pearl Harbor
to V-J Day was less than
four years?
A world at war,
and we ended it..
...just that quickly?
This thing has been going on
since the turn of the century.
We have turned a side show
into the main event.
But the response
has to be specific, surgical.
I do think we need to take into account
the reactions, both at home and abroad.
Doesn't it bother you
that the idea
of American exceptionalism
is an anachronism?
Of course.
We're a rudderless ship
where just getting by
is enough.
And Los Angeles certainly showed
how tenuous even that is.
If Maleki's tire
does not blow out
if the CHP does not pull over
if Maleki does not panic.
If, if, if!
An if prevented a catastrophe
that would've made 9/11
look like a footnote.
Now, I don't sleep well at night
knowing that.
We have to win this war.
Total victory.
Thanks for coming
on such short notice.
So you want
all of these changed?
Plus the mudroom and back door.
I wanna add
more locks there, too.
A different key for each.
Okay.
You have a robbery?
No.
Not happy
with your alarm system?
No, it's fine.
If you want cameras,
I have a guy.
No cameras.
Thanks.
I'll get to it.
Sorry if I, uh, spooked you guys
last night.
- Is he...
- No, Neal is gone.
Hey, uh, if we want
this roommate thing to work out
we need to communicate
a little bit better.
- You know what I mean?
- Uh, yeah.
So if you have a problem with
my bringing Neil back here...
Uh, I don't, I don't have
a problem with that.
- Okay, so what is your problem?
- I don't have a fucking..
I don't have a fucking problem.
Look, Martin, we don't really
know each other.
I've got the sense you're one of those
extremely gifted, self-motivated types.
Your test scores, the Ivy
League pedigree, the awards.
Frankly a little intimidating,
but I applaud all that, seriously.
It's just the sneaking around
that weirds me out a bit.
Sneaking around?
What the fuck does that mean?
You just seem really unhappy.
Maybe you should
talk to someone.
You know, if you want
a new roommate
you just go ahead and say it.
That's not what I'm saying.
Well, fuck it.
Opt room for a single
next semester.
That's not what I'm saying.
Hey, I get it, Jordan.
It's what I'm saying.
And the paper..
Is it good?
Our circulation
continues to dwindle.
Last time I checked,
uh, we had a grand total
of 43,000 subscribers.
The entire newsroom is comprised
of an ever-dwindling 25,
myself included.
Dwindling being key word here.
Can I help you?
At least they didn't
try to take a picture.
So sorry, Mr. Lamm,
just a couple of minutes
and your table will be ready.
Thank you very much.
You were saying about the paper?
Oh, th... tha... that's it,
really.
You know, sometimes I think
that leaving the Post
was the biggest mistake
of my professional career.
And then I remember
I wasn't even given a choice
in the matter.
Daddy, I am so sorry
if I had anything to do
with you losing...
That was not your fault.
You know that.
Even your mother has..
Does she know how I feel?
She read your letters, yes.
And she still refuses to see me.
We were so proud of you.
So proud
of your accomplishments.
Were.
And now you're ashamed.
We have to win this war.
Total victory.
Now, more than anyone
you... have done more
to prepare this country
for this moment.
So connect the dots
that need to be connected.
And if the stars
need help aligning, do so.
Talk to Adrian.
The DI is with us on this.
People wanna believe
what you say.
Use that gift.
And if you see this through
to its logical end
your future, your legacy
will be assured.
You will have served
your country honorably.
Do you see it?
Uh, found it.
It's quite beautiful.
Built in 1900
by the legendary J.D. McCarthy
Safe and Lock Company
out of Cincinnati.
It's in excellent condition.
The lock still works?
You look awfully familiar.
Have we met?
No, I'm afraid not.
Of course. Excuse me.
I just wanna say thank you
for your service to the country.
You did what had to be done,
and we're safer for it.
Well, thank you.
I'm glad you feel safe.
Well, let's open this bad boy.
Uh, a little help, please?
Continuing our discussion
of Clausewitz and war
in 1832, he wrote
"Kind-hearted people
might, of course, think
"there was some ingenious way
to disarm or defeat the enemy
"without too much bloodshed.
"It might imagine this as the
true goal of the art of war.
"Pleasant as it sounds
"it is a fallacy
that must be exposed.
"War is such
a dangerous business
"that mistakes
that come from kindness
are the very worst."
Hey, Libby.
It's good to see you.
Adrian.
- How late?
- About three.
Waiting for Amman to check in.
I missed waking up to you
this morning.
Me, too.
I guess I've become
kind of used to it.
Me, too.
The Amman call.
What you wanted to hear?
No.
What, the stars aren't aligning?
Not funny.
Did you tell Rachel?
Nope.
Are you waiting
for the right moment?
I don't think
there is a right moment.
She would like to see you.
Thanks. As if on cue.
Tonight.
The paper trail has to be...
Airtight. Commission-proof.
This is not just any op, Adrian.
I get it.
We are way past
cherry-picking evidence.
Understood.
Just think,
we can end this thing
once and for all.
Hey, your boss wants it done,
my boss wants it done.
That's good enough for me.
The intel has to be credible and
actionable, especially on Vahdat.
He is the key.
I'll get you visas,
travel itineraries,
whatever we can provide.
Now, put that pad away
and get back over here.
Can we talk... inside?
No, not inside.
Where, then? 'Cause I'm
not leaving till we do.
Follow me.
Yeah?
Hey, Martin, can I come in?
Yeah.
Hey.
Yeah?
Did you hear about Sunday?
No, what about Sunday?
Dr. Sipe is having
a get-together at her house
for faculty
and department grad students.
No, I didn't hear about that
but, um, thanks
for the heads-up.
Do you think you'll go?
Yeah, I do.
I hate going
to these things... alone.
Would it be okay
if we went together?
Sure.
Thank you.
So what's with the no phone,
no email
kind of, but not really
off the grid nonsense?
Keeps it all very simple.
I guess I should
congratulate you
on your appointment.
Chief of staff to the
President of the United States.
How does it feel?
It feels right.
Well, I'm glad
it all worked out for you.
We're concerned about you,
Libby.
We've reached out several times.
Reaching out in regard
to the President's intent
to run for re-election?
And the silence is deafening.
We need to make sure
you're still part of our team.
Are you, Libby,
still part of our team?
You flew all this way to hear me
answer that question.
I flew all this way to see you
I served faithfully.
I did everything
I was asked to do, everything.
Back then.
You don't..
- Does it ever give you...
- No.
A decision was made,
an order was given.
Period.
Easy as that.
Just the one thing.
What happened to you and me,
that did hurt.
But, Libby,
the understanding was
you'd resign and we'd all say
nice things about one another.
Presidential medals of freedom
and all that.
I'm not asking you to be
the centerpiece of the campaign.
I'm just looking
for a unified front.
You may have detractors, but your overall
favorable rating within the party is 70%.
So when I do reach out
and I hear nothing
I take that as a "Fuck you."
And being the trusting guy
that I am
I begin to think that maybe
Libby's having second thoughts
maybe Libby's thinking of airing
the family's dirty laundry.
I cannot overemphasize what a
colossally dangerous idea that would be.
Stop following me.
I know you have people watching.
I can assure you
it's not coming from my office.
How about your old buddies
at Langley?
Is that what's happening, Libby?
Are you suspicious of everyone now?
Like I said, tell your people
to leave me alone.
You're a very attractive woman,
Libby.
Sometimes the answer
to a problem
is a very simple explanation
an obvious one.
I'm here in good faith
because of your service
to the President
and the country.
Because Rachel still
considers you a friend.
I wouldn't be speaking here now
if it was otherwise.
So, I've been warned.
Counseled.
This memoir you threaten
to write has Rachel worried.
You're either with us
or against us.
It's as simple as that.
Let's talk again... soon, okay?
What now?
- Mingle.
- Beer first.
And I'll join you
if, uh, if that is okay.
Jordan, I know
I can be a first-class jerk.
I don't want
a single next semester
you're a great roommate, and I
think I can be a good one soon
if that works for you.
Does that mean
I can join you for that beer?
We're bonding.
Then they removed the damaged
cartilage and bone from the..
Now, here's my new word
of the day, acetabulum.
There's our new celebrity
and resident.
Elizabeth, so glad you made it.
Let me make some introductions.
I apologize for sounding
like my parents
but kids these days.
No matter how incoherent,
no matter how many typos
they still expect an A.
I'm talking about,
about basic grammar
middle school stuff.
I don't know how the hell
they expect an A
when they can't even put
a sentence together.
For that matter,
how the hell did they
get into this university?
I'm asking you.
Washington in the summer?
You can have it.
The humidity, the mosquitos.
Yuck.
Oh, you get used to it.
Enjoying the show?
Ah, the glamorous
Elizabeth Lamm.
The architect of Total Victory
and the Burke doctrine.
Kill one of ours,
we kill a thousand of yours.
Ain't that the gist of it?
Something like that, yeah.
Hmm. Have you met her?
Not yet.
Introduce yourself.
When the time's right.
So how long are you here for?
- The semester.
- Hmm.
And we'll see how it goes
after that.
Are you staying near campus
or in the city with the action?
Near campus.
- Thank you.
How about you? You doing
the old meet-and-greet?
Oh, yeah, a couple of
"Hi, I'm Jordan Ritt.
That's Ritt with two Ts. So
thrilled to be taking your class."
Excellent conversation,
if I do say so myself.
Congratulations on that.
Yes, it is a fine art.
Big homes in that area, though.
It's a lot of house
for one person.
I like it. I like the space.
Really? You don't find it
too quiet, too lonely?
Uh, no.
Did you buy?
- Rent.
- Furnished?
Almost.
So what are you sleeping on?
Did they,
did they leave you a bed?
Elizabeth, how often do you
encounter protests these days?
I mean, was Tuesday an anomaly
or i... is it typical?
Now, I promised Elizabeth
there would be no grilling.
No inquisition, not tonight.
Willa, I'm just asking
Elizabeth if every time
she walks out into the world
she has to deal
with those haters.
It's okay, Willa, really.
I see it on campuses still.
That's about it.
I resigned my post
four years ago.
After that, I was a figure
of controversy.
Protests were common.
People were upset.
But as time went by, it receded
and it was replaced
by new controversies.
Toynbee was right.
History's just one damn thing
after another.
But some things
are more damnable
than... than others,
aren't they, hm?
What you did was unconscionable.
Larry, not here.
Willa, you should be ashamed.
You bring this woman in?
All you guys.
Do you realize
what we're legitimizing here?
Larry, please.
We are all aware that liquor
brings out
your unfulfilled penchant
for theatrics.
What the fuck
does that even mean?
It means you're stupid drunk.
The only way
I can stand to be around her.
How many?
Come on.
You know the number.
How many people?
Based on the information that
was available at the time...
How many?
There's always the unknown,
the unkn...
Say it!!
Larry, drop this. Now.
The Amman intel changes
nothing.
Two, maybe three of our guys,
won't be there
at least not during the window.
Vahdat, what about Vahdat?
Not confirmed.
It changes nothing.
But we stress
that you're refutable.
I mean, in and of itself, the
evidence at hand is overwhelming.
When we include the DI
from intel, yes. But...
But it's commission-proof,
correct?
Yes.
Alright, good enough for me.
I just want a moment alone
with Elizabeth, please.
There's one more thing.
I've changed my mind.
I'm recommending we now go
with Directive 7-12.
You were in agreement with the
more conventional approach...
It's a message
that has to be sent.
Libby, it's become clear to me
that this is much bigger
than Homs.
We are sending a message
to the world
"Don't fuck with us anymore."
The discussions with the DOD,
they've all been about this...
I, look, I've wrestled with it.
I'm convinced
the stars have aligned.
I'm urging you to reconsider
7-10. The multiple drones...
These people are like needles
in a haystack.
But to burn down
the entire barn..
When the moment comes,
you will know what to do.
Good evening.
Hey.
The rabid release of energy
in such an explosion
creates a shockwave equivalent
to several thousands pounds
of pressure per square inch,
enough to crush
uh, brick houses and human lungs
and most objects on earth.
Thus, we see the increased
incidents of leukemia
and thyroid, lung, breast,
and bone cancer...
Excuse me, Luis, class,
give me a minute, please.
I'll be right back.
What are you doing here?
I told you, we were gonna finish
our conversation.
Now you're threatening me.
I just want the answer
to the question.
Leave me alone.
- Libby...
- No!
- No what?
- No.
I'm no longer
on your fucking team!
So we can't count on you.
Count on me to tell the truth.
What, then?
Your memoir goes public
and you're at peace?
Why are you making this so hard
on yourself?
If you think
you're in the wilderness now..
Sorry, everyone. I have to go.
Class dismissed.
We'll, we'll make it up.
You say nothing
and nothing changes.
Put that down..
...and move slowly
away from the safe.
Sit on the bed.
Hands to your side,
palms on the covers.
You were following me.
Can you not point the gun
in my face?
You are just a mother-fuckin'
stalker.
I would be within my right
to shoot you dead here and now.
No, I'm not that kind
of stalker.
Bullshit.
I'm not, Dr. Lamm.
You were in my class
and at Dr. Sipe's.
Yes, I'm a graduate student.
Were you sent here?
Is someone paying you?
Nope.
Then you have one chance
to answer
this question correctly.
If I don't like what I hear
I'm either gonna kill you
or call the cops.
You don't have a phone.
Why are you here?
I'll put it this way.
Say I'm a Jew.
I'm not. Say I am.
Now, as a child
I learned my grandparents
they were murdered
in Auschwitz.
What do I do?
I immerse myself in the subject.
All the camps,
attending horrors.
I study hard, I... I excel.
Full tuition, scholarships.
Getting into, you know,
prestigious universities
both graduate and undergraduate.
Now, at said
graduate university..
...my first class,
on my first day..
...I look up and see Dr. Mengele
standing at the lectern.
For Dr. Mengele's been given
an honorary chair
in the political science
department
and will be lecturing me.
You have family there?
What you committed
was an atrocity..
...a crime against humanity.
I..
We believed we were making
the world a safer place.
- Shut up. Shut up. Shut up.
- We believed we were protecti...
Shut up!
You're a fuckin' war criminal
and you should be hung as such.
What's your name?
My what?
Martin. Martin Salhi.
Okay, Martin Salhi.
You have your Mengele.
You're staring into the abyss.
Now what?
Do you wanna kill me?
Nah.
No.
I, um..
...I just wanna understand
how evil works.
Evil?
Yeah.
I wanna know everything. I wa..
Does it wear silk
or... or eat off fine china?
Does it drink latte?
How does it take the unthinkable
and... and make it real,
you know?
Does it have remorse? You know,
how... how does it keep going?
I wanna know the big questions
I wanna... I wanna know
the details.
I wanna know everything.
I wanna, I just wanna understand
everything.
Sit back down.
Please... Martin.
Read it.
You wanna understand?
All of it.
Start there.
Mr. President,
because time is of the essence
I've asked my National Security
Affairs advisor
Elizabeth Lamm,
to address the group.
Elizabeth has taken
all the intel.
Phone intercept,
satellite, imagery,
signals intelligence,
and human assets.
And I think you will agree
that her findings
are definitive and convincing
necessitating immediate
and total action..
...if she may.
Smartest person in the room.
You bet.
Elizabeth, please.
Mr. President,
ladies and gentlemen.
We are currently presented with
a moment in time
in which a single, decisive act
could literally change
the course of history.
The evidence and opportunity
is undeniable.
Omar al-Abadi, ISIL.
Kamal Lateef, Al Qaeda
in the Arabian Peninsula.
Sajad al Jubeir,
Jabhat al-Nusra.
Mohdar al-Hazmi, Hezbollah.
Khalid Saadu, Jaysh al-Sham.
And Dr. S.Q. Vahdat
former head of the Atomic
Energy Organization of Iran.
And quite possibly, the most
dangerous man in the world.
Unbeknownst to one another,
these six men
five leaders of terrorist
organizations and Dr. Vahdat
a rogue agent dedicated
to the proliferation
of nuclear weapons technology
will all be in the same city
Homs, Syria, at the same time
this very evening.
Excuse me, Elizabeth.
Where is Homs, exactly?
Approximately 162 kilometers
north of Damascus.
- And that's...
- That's about 100 miles.
Got it. Thank you.
Never did get
the damn metric system.
Our best estimate is a four-hour
overlap
between 10:00 p.m.
and 2:00 a.m. local time
in which these known enemies
will be within the city of Homs,
all targets of opportunity.
A strike to the heart of Homs
at this moment would cripple
if not terminate
the threat of terrorism
this country has faced
for nearly three decades
at the cost of thousands of
lives and trillions of dollars.
It is approximately
7:05 p.m. local time
giving us just under five hours
to approve
and execute the action.
And what type of strike
are you proposing?
Well, we prepared three
scenarios, in which...
Um, Elizabeth? Excuse me.
I'm... I'm gonna interrupt.
Ladies and gentlemen..
...if we act now
we can defeat these primeval
bastards once and for all.
Now, Elizabeth is gonna walk us
through some scenarios
but I am convinced..
...that our response should be
total and absolute.
Elizabeth, if you would
continue, please.
Thank you,
Madam Vice President.
What the vice president
and her staff
are advocating is unprecedented.
Whatever short-term gain
this action might achieve
we would be opening
Pandora's Box.
We become the pariah.
May I remind the Admiral that
the 7-12 calls
for a tactical weapon.
Tactical nuclear weapon.
It has been the stated policy
of this nation
never to be the first to use a
nuclear device in any conflict.
That has been a doctrine since
the end of the World War II.
He has a point, Rachel.
If you were president
at this moment
would you be willing to
personally authorize
a nuclear strike that would kill
countless innocent men,
women and children?
Yes.
The whole point of a deterrent
is that our enemies need to know
we are prepared to use it.
They need to understand,
we will punish
their fathers and mothers,
husbands and wives and children.
Everyone... they love and cherish
will be held accountable.
Now, it's a different century.
It's a different world.
This war on terror is unique
in terms of who the enemy is..
...and how to combat that enemy.
And if there is any doubt
about the stakes
need I remind everyone
at this table about Los Angeles?
Madam Vice President, there is
no credible evidence
that Maleki had any connection
to Vahdat's group.
That's your opinion.
Mine, that Vahdat
and these gangsters
are committed to detonating
a nuclear device
in an American city
in the next 24 months.
They don't have that capability.
Not yet!
Mr. President, our window
of opportunity
is under three hours
and there is nothing that I have
heard at this table
that refutes Elizabeth's
analysis and evidence.
In one fell swoop
we can win this war
and end this worldwide scourge.
Elizabeth?
Yes, Mr. President?
Do you agree
with the vice president's
recommendation regarding
the 7-12?
Of course I do, Mr. President.
And you're confident
these six men
will be at this place
at this time?
I am.
Especially Dr. Vahdat?
Yes, Mr. President.
You know..
...after I won my third
championship at Texas..
...people just kept asking me
"Coach, what's the secret
to winning?"
And I would always tell them,
"Commitment."
Total commitment.
So... let's go win this thing.
Whiplash in one-zero.
Roger, Tango-45.
Whiplash
Once the initial reports are in
I'll address the nation.
- Thank you, everyone.
- Thank you, Mr. President.
Yep.
Libby.
I knew I could count on you.
"Nuclear bombs dropped in the
base of falsified intelligence?"
These have to be published
immediately.
These go to one person first.
They read it, they publish.
No, no, no, why wait?
It's very important to me
this person is the one
who publishes my story.
Who else knows?
On the outside?
Just you, Martin.
Does it make you feel safe?
No.
We should go out the back.
There are elements
within the White House
an intelligence committee
who will use every resource
at their disposal
to make sure these never see
the light of day.
What? So you're saying
that's who's outside right now?
The basement.
I've got a way out.
Hold up here for a minute.
I have nothing on me.
Um..
I've got a student ID
about 65 bucks, a credit card,
and about 4.50 in change.
Your phone.
- Oh, shit.
- Leave it here.
Let's go.
Should we go to the cops or,
or FBI?
I mean, everyone
can't be involved, right?
This way.
Why?
The trees complicate
satellite and drone
surveillance.
Low-tech can beat high-tech.
Looking at it from their end,
this needs to be a limited op.
Surgical.
Exposure can't be risked.
Questions can't be asked.
A snatch-and-grab
on these streets in this town
would be a last resort.
So, hide in plain sight?
As best as we can.
We'll need money.
This trouble you're in, you
can't tell me any more about it?
No.
What, for, like, my protection
or something?
Really?
I'm trying to right a wrong.
If it wasn't important, really
important, I wouldn't be here.
Shit, Martin.
You realize how bizarre this is?
Please?
How much do you need?
Four hundred dollars.
Um, yes, I can get that.
Thank you, Jordan, okay?
T... thank you.
Uh, could you also swing
by the room and get my laptop?
Yeah.
Maybe grab a sweater?
Yeah. Anything else
while we're at it?
That's it. Promise.
I take it you need all this
as soon as...
Right now works best, actually.
Whatever it is
you're doing here..
...I hope it works out okay.
Be safe.
How do you know to get in
and out like this?
I make it my business to know
every exit
of every building
I step foot in.
You never know
when some dickhead
with a gun might open up.
I used to think
I was just being paranoid.
I gotta show you something.
What we're seeing..
...is it now?
No, yesterday.
This is this morning.
We leave, they enter.
Oh, shit.
No, don't.
Door's open.
Hey, are you guys finished
in here
'cause we reserved the room,
so..
Yep.
Can you give us a minute?
Uh, yeah, absolutely.
Take your time. Thanks.
Any ideas?
- Regarding?
- Where to go.
Where to hide until morning.
Uh, yeah, I've got one.
We're taking the story
to your father, right?
Yes.
He runs a newspaper downstate.
He's the editor, yes.
- What if he won't print it?
- He'll print it, Martin.
Okay, but, like,
what if he can't?
Honestly, I've..
I've been thinking about just
grabbing the backpack
and running.
Dumping the story.
Just getting it out.
You've had opportunity.
What's been stopping you?
Because it's your story
and I respect that.
Your father, what's he like?
He's a good man.
Honest... and caring.
It's what you want a dad to be.
Yours?
He was all that.
He was there the 19th of June..
...visiting his mother
and father.
Dutiful son.
This never ends.
Do you believe
in the hereafter?
Heaven? No.
I do.
And I know I'm gonna have to
answer for what I've done.
Martin... maybe you should go.
Either I get to Springfield
tomorrow or I don't.
But I have a chance,
thanks to you.
My father's dead.
Well, my mother
she may as well be.
She never recovered.
These pages
are important to you?
Well, they're important
to me too.
Dr. Lamm?
Hello, Libby.
Madam President.
I apologize.
I think the team
got a little overzealous.
And, gentlemen,
if you will excuse me
I'd like a moment alone
with Elizabeth.
Oh, come on, Adrian,
it'll be fine.
Gentlemen, please. Go.
Libby, I hope my just being here
will convince you
that what I'm about to say
is the truth
and it comes from my heart.
Despite all that's happened
and all that's been said
I still consider you a friend,
a dear friend.
You served me and this country
brilliantly.
A service
that I believe deserves
to be recognized and honored.
I was at a party recently
and somebody reminded me
of the number.
Do you remember the number,
Madam President?
Of course I do.
A hundred and fifty.
One hundred and fifty thousand
people
died in Homs that night.
I will always remember
that number.
You know the story, Libby.
General Sherman
in the Civil War.
Mayor of Atlanta pleads
with him to save his city.
And the general
says to the mayor
just before he torches it,
"War is cruel."
War is cruelty.
We were at war and we did
what needed to be done
and our country is safer for it.
The stars aligned.
We slayed the dragon and we won.
If there is any victory here
it has fallen on us.
Libby, I offered you
the position
of Secretary of State
four years ago
and I am offering it
to you again.
Madam President, respectfully..
...we ginned up the evidence
and 150,000 innocent people
were vaporized.
Okay, so help me understand it.
You were fine
with drone strikes.
Five innocents here,
ten innocents there.
What's the humane number?
A hundred?
A thousand?
Ten thousand?
Where do you draw the line?
That bomb was dropped
on a lie.
I just can't
live with that anymore.
Tell me about your manuscript.
And the young man.
He's a good-looking boy.
How's he involved?
He's not.
Leave him be.
And the cameras in your house.
- What's that about?
- None of your business.
I think I'm beginning
to understand your dilemma.
My dilemma?
Libby, you're this close
to being charged
with sedition and treason.
You don't know if
there's a copy.
And the obvious move would be to
grab Martin when you grabbed me.
He might be on the other side
of that wall this very moment.
That's the obvious move.
That's not the Rachel Burke
I know.
No? So, what's
the other response, then?
Follow the money.
Follow the boy to see
if he leads you to that copy.
The obvious downside
to that approach
is the more time allowed
the greater the opportunity
for unfortunate mischief.
I'm sure Adrian voiced
that concern.
You are a unique talent,
Libby.
Unfortunately..
...I don't see a very
happy ending
for Martin Salhi
in either scenario
unless you tell me right now
if there's a copy
and where I can find it.
And then, you and I
can come to an understanding
and you can just fade away.
All I can tell you is
what I know.
There's the original.
A dozen notepads of material
written in longhand.
There is not a single copy.
No hard copy,
nor electronic.
Leave Martin be.
He is an innocent.
Please, Rachel.
Do with me what you will..
...but let him be.
How could you do this?
You had regret.
You wanted out.
I agreed to everything.
Everything!
But for you to go
and write this betrayal?
'Cause that's exactly what
it is. It is a betrayal.
A betrayal for you.
A reckoning for me.
Madam President, you are needed.
What is it?
There is a problem,
we should go.
I had to try.
I mean, I owe her that much.
Alright.
So, tell me about Salhi.
Well, they lost him
in Union Station.
Thirty seconds of confusion
is about all it took.
- How is that even possible?
- He's a smart kid.
He found the tracker and stashed
it along with his laptop
in a bag on a bus
headed to Des Moines.
I know we thought the boy
would lead us to other copies
but leaving the backpack
was a mistake.
We did go back and check
the security videos.
Salhi purchased a bus ticket
to Springfield
and we have him boarding
that bus.
- Pull your team.
- That would be a mistake.
The operation is blown.
The pads are in a backpack,
which can be easily
taken when the bus arrives.
It'll look like
a simple mugging.
No. It's already light
in the Midwest.
No. It's too risky. No.
Madam President,
there are people that don't
want that document
made public, ever.
Like yourself.
There will be no second term.
You will be disgraced.
I will take my chances
with the American people.
They remember
what it was like before Homs.
They remember the fear.
Impeachment,
followed by conviction.
- Oh, it's not gonna happen.
- I don't think...
Look, Adrian,
you work for me now.
- Is that clear?
- Yes, ma'am.
The agency can more than handle
its own affairs.
Commission-proof intel
is the phrase I remember.
- This is dangerous.
- Oh, we'll weather it. Stop it.
What should we do with the boy?
Let him go.
I mean, he's the messenger.
And Libby?
Take her home.
It'll be her word against ours.
The American people won't
want to refight a war
that's already won.
Did Adrian fly in
with you guys?
No. He stayed in California.
Dr. Lamm, when your feet
touch that ground
start walking and count to 20.
Only then remove the hood.
Understood?
Yes.
I'm... I'm Martin Salhi.
I'm here to see Phillip Lamm.
You can say it's regarding
his daughter, Elizabeth.
Let me try him.
Hey, Blair, would you
let Phil know that Martin..
Salhi.
There's a Martin Salhi here
to see him.
He's on his way down.
Martin!
- What the fuck happened to you?
- You have to leave.
What? Hey, what..
Daddy.
Oh, no.
- Where is she?
- On the phone with the FBI.
Okay, Fred.
Yes, she was.
Thanks.
Just keep me posted.
You know, about everything.
Okay, thanks.
Get out.
Just putting the period
on the sentence.
I said, get out.
Of course,
she was a dear friend.
I'll make that clear
in the statement.
As of now, there are
23 confirmed dead.
Among those,
Elizabeth Lamm
former National Security
Affairs Advisor
to then,
Vice President Burke
and her father,
Phillip Lamm
executive editor of
the Springfield Register
the site of the attack.
We are learning the FBI
now believes
that the primary suspect,
Martin Salhi
acted alone and specifically
targeted Dr. Lamm
for her role in
the controversial strike
on Homs, Syria,
four years ago.
Mr. Salhi had family in Homs.
Dr. Lamm, known as
the architect of recent
US policy in the war
on terror
advocated what came to be known
as Total Victory.
President Burke has been
on the West Coast this week
attending various
fundraising events.
She is in San Francisco
this afternoon
...Adrian Little,
the President's chief of staff
issued this statement
concerning the attack.
Good afternoon, everyone.
President Burke is both
saddened and stunned
as we all are,
by this vicious act of terror
and the death of our colleague
and good friend, Elizabeth Lamm.
Jordan Ritt?
FBI.
Look, Martin wasn't
the easiest person in the world
to get along with, for sure
but this just makes no sense.
If what you're asking is,
do I think Martin was capable of
blowing himself up,
murdering dozens of people
my answer is no.
I don't believe that.
This is my apartment.
Nobody told you?
Excellent conversation,
if I do say so myself.
- Congratulations on that.
- Yes, it is a fine art.
Subtitles by explosiveskull