[ Beethoven's 9th Symphony ]
My spoon is too big.
My spoon is too big!
I am a banana.
[ happy uptempo music ]
Tuesday's coming.
Did you bring your coat?
I live in a giant bucket.
[ grunting, screaming ]
[ strange, unintelligible sounds ]
[ censored ]
[ jazz swing ]
[ happy, uptempo music ]
[ announcer ] You're watching
The Family Learning Channel
And now...
"Angry Ticks Fire Out Of My Nipples"
[ mooing sound ]
[ bees buzzing - screaming ]
Say - do you want to go see a movie?
I'm feeling fat and sassy.
[ shouting ]
[ Beethoven ]
[ unintelligible ]
[ mommy's voice ] Oh, honey - come quick
Pooby's taking his first steps!
[ crowd cheers ]
[ applause ]
Dance!
Everybody dance!
[ cheering ]
Yay!
[ more cheering ]
Life is good!
This is fun!
My anus is bleeding!
[ more cheering ]
For the love of God
and all that is holy!
My anus is bleeding!
[ screaming ]
[ Beethoven ]
[ unintelligible ]
[ silence ]
[ Beethoven ]