Hey.
Hey, Andy, will you
look at my back?
Actually, Byron, the phrase
is "watch your back"
and yes, no matter
what happens...
No. I mean actually
look at my back.
See, I took a nap this weekend
with the shades open
and the sun focused
through my ant colony
like a magnifying glass
and burned a hole
through my shirt.
Wow, that is weird.
Although it is kind
of funny, you know...
Ants burning a person
with a magnifying glass.
Yeah, well, I got back
at them pretty good,
but the worst part is
I have to change the dressing
every three hours.
Would you help me?
I can't reach.
Sure.
This is what it's all about.
Helping your friend
in a time of...
Oh, my God! It's hideous!
How's it look?
Fine.
Hey, Jessica.
Here's the thing from the place.
My ant colony set
my back on fire.
No, I'm fine.
Is something wrong?
Okay, Tommy and I broke up.
Who's Tommy?
That cute doctor I met
a couple of weeks ago.
He said it bothered him
that I didn't like his cat.
I thought you...
Let me finish.
His cat, which he
kept in his freezer
and apologized to every
time we made love.
Jessica hasn't always
had the best luck
when it comes to men.
Hey, honey, I'm ready to go.
Jessica, I'm in a meeting.
But you're...
Sweetie, this isn't
going to work
if we don't trust each other.
Alex, I really respect
that you want to wait,
but we've been going
out for two months.
I'm sorry, honey.
I'm just feeling a little
fat right now, okay?
You know, maybe I don't need
to be in a relationship.
Lots of things
don't have relationships.
Trees, shrimp,
ketchup, wallpaper.
What is this list I'm making?
Poor Jessica.
I really wanted to help.
Luckily, later that day,
I found the perfect man for her.
Ah, I don't want
to meet anybody.
Maybe I should just take
a break for a while.
Come on, this guy has
a lot going for him
particularly the fact that
you didn't choose him.
Well... that does sound good.
Is he cute?
He's one of the cutest
guys I've ever seen.
He's tall and he's rugged.
Oh, and his butt.
Imagine the finest ass
you've ever seen.
Now double it.
What are you doing?
I don't know. This
is all very new.
♪ You never know just
what's around the bend ♪
♪ Where to go and
where you've been ♪
♪ Just see the world
through my eyes ♪
♪ And I think you'd
be surprised. ♪
So the burn on my back
started to fester,
but getting a private
nurse for the night
was way too expensive,
so I hired a prostitute
to change the dressing
every three hours.
She did it once and left.
She said it was the ninth
most disgusting thing
she had ever been asked to do.
And how was your weekend?
We played tennis.
Oh.
Morning. What's that smell?
Does it smell like a
crab died in yogurt?
Because that might be my back.
Nevermind.
Ow.
What are you saying "ow" for?
I kissed you.
Hard.
You okay, man?
Well, I was just
trying to thank you
for setting me up with Ben.
He is fantastic.
So, is he cute?
Is he cute? He's one
of the cutest guys...
Dude.
The only strange thing is...
sometimes he's
fascinating and witty,
and other times it's like
trying to make conversation
with a really stupid hammer.
It's the same with sex.
Sometimes he's... spectacular,
and then
other times, it's like
he just kind of forgets
how things work.
That's not so strange.
Once, I forgot how to use pants.
Of course, I might
have been depressed.
Show me!
What kind of monster are you?!
Anyway, Ben is great,
and I owe it all to Andy.
You know, I wasn't going to say
anything in front of Jessica,
but I don't like that Ben.
He and his twin brother
are always hanging
out at the bar,
trying to get me to join them
in making fun of
the less handsome.
I won't play.
Wait, Ben has a twin?
Are they identical?
To each other? Absolutely.
To other sets of twins?
Doubt it.
No. Didn't you hear
what Jessica said?
About how sometimes Ben
seems like he's one person
and then sometimes he seems
like he's another person.
I think Ben and his twin
are sharing Jessica.
Hey, Andy, how's that going crazy
thing working out for you?
Yeah, you do sound
a little paranoid.
Sounds like the time you thought
you figured out
the true identity
of the sandwich guy.
Hitler!
That was so embarrassing.
What? You think
when Hitler comes,
he's just going to
goose-step in in uniform?
I'm sorry. "When" Hitler comes?
Byron hired a prostitute
to clean his wound.
"Clean his wound"?
That is the worst euphemism
for sex I've ever heard.
No, she literally cleans
the wound on his back.
Oh...
Then why'd you say it
all sexy like that?
You think everything
I say is sexy.
Here, try this.
Byron has a big, pussy
burn on his back,
and I'm going to ask him to stay
at my place for a while
so that I can change
his rancid bandages.
You still sound hot.
Listen, why don't
I stay with you
for a while and we can take care
of the little guy together?
Really? You'd do that?
We took care of your
neighbor's cactus for a week.
That wasn't anywhere near as
hard as I thought it would be.
Yeah, but we did kill it.
Remember, you gave
it that milkshake?
Oh, yeah, but Byron
likes milkshakes.
Got everything you need, cowboy?
Oh... My grandfather used
to call me "cowboy,"
but he was crazy.
The year before he died,
he just called me, "Gaah."
"Gaah"?
Yes, Bumpa?
Okay, so your painkillers
are starting to kick in.
Wendy!
Keith!
Keith, it's 2:00.
It's your turn to
change Byron's bandage.
I need changing.
Keith.
And some juice.
Wendy.
Hmm?
What is he doing here?
He said he had a bad dream.
Can't he go back to his own bed?
You can try.
No!
The next day, I was still
worried about Jessica.
I was sure she was being dated
by two separate but
identical men,
but how can I prove it?
My plan was simple.
I would inject Ben with
a radioactive isotope.
The next time this "Ben"
came to pick up Jessica,
I would surreptitiously
take a small blood sample.
Unfortunately, there was a lot
of running and
stabbing in this plan,
so I came up with another idea.
When Ben came to
pick up Jessica,
I made a point of mentioning
my grandmother's age.
Then, the next time Ben took
Jessica out, I would see
if he remembered how old
Granny Richter was.
Hey, Ben.
Or, as my 84-year-old
grandmother would say,
"Hey, Ben, I'm 84."
Hey, Andy.
Did I say my grandmother was 84?
Because I meant 84.
Hey, Ben. I'm ready to go.
84? Ben and I were just laughing
about how old my 84-year-old
grandmother is.
She can't even walk
'cause she's 84.
The trap had been laid.
The next night I arranged
to run into Jessica
and her precious boy-toy
so I could bring my plan
to its wickedly
delicious conclusion.
Now I just sound gay.
Hey, Keith.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I should be at Wendy's helping
to take care of Byron.
Listen, have Jessica and
that so-called "Ben"
showed up yet?
I don't know.
Why don't I check the
bottom of this glass?
No, not there.
Pst.
Jessica's coming.
Act like we're talking.
Actually, we are. Hurry!
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la...
Sardines... they're lucky
to even be a fish.
Oh, hey, Jessica, Ben.
Hi, you guys.
I'll get us some drinks.
Okay.
So, how's it going?
Great. Fine.
And now I will expose
this alleged Ben
by showing that he
doesn't know the age
of a certain grandmother.
So, Ben, uh,
you remember the other day
when you and I were talking
about my 84-year-old grand...
Damn it!
So much for my dream of
ever becoming a spy.
Go on. Get your drinks.
I'm done with you.
Oh, I almost got those guys.
Yeah, Chicago, please connect
me to Ben Hoffensteader.
You really need to know
Jessica's okay, huh?
Well, of course. It's Jessica.
And I just know
they're doing this.
It's so obvious.
Hello.
Ben Hoffensteader?
Yes.
Yeah, the twins are
switching off.
So I said, "You take
her, you brought her."
Oh!
What is going on?!
I have something
awful to tell you.
Something so awful you
won't want to believe it.
Oh, Andy, Hitler would be 113.
Ben has a twin, and
the two of them
have been sharing
you like a bike.
Yeah, I know. They're
switching off.
Maybe I left something out.
Sometimes two babies
come out of a lady...
Andy, I know.
Last week I became suspicious,
so I bit one of
them on the thigh.
The next night when the
bite wasn't there,
I knew they'd pulled a switch.
It was so simple.
I had toyed with a
thigh-biting plan briefly,
but I could never crack it.
Together, they are
the perfect guy.
Ben is one of the most smartest,
most interesting people
I have ever talked to,
but he's lousy in bed.
His brother Peter,
a complete maroon, but in bed,
he's like a laser-guided
smart bomb.
Right down the ventilator shaft
and kaboom!
There's a ventilator shaft?
When we meet for a date,
if the smart one shows up,
we have a fascinating
conversation over dinner
and then I tell him
I have a headache
and go home alone.
If it's the one that can't
put a sentence together,
I feed him a power bar and
get him straight into bed.
As long as they don't know
that I know, I am happy
and so are Talky and Humpy.
You're not like the other girls.
Hey, Jessica, I was
just thinking,
you know how on Earth
people walk around and
birds fly in the air?
Yeah.
Did you ever wonder
if on other planets people fly
and the birds walk around, hmm?
Okay.
Here, eat this, and let's
get back to my place.
Ooh.
Hey, honey.
Hey, slugger.
Nice of you to come home.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
"Slugger" needs to
be changed again.
I'll do it.
You're drunk. You'll hurt him.
I'm not going to hurt him.
Come here, little fella.
Keith, you're scaring him.
Why don't we ever
have sex anymore?
We had sex this morning.
It was like you
weren't even there.
I was.
The next morning I
was feeling uneasy
about Jessica's situation.
In my day,
we had names for a
woman like Jessica...
Trollop, harlot,
whore, Mommy...
This is Mr. Pickering.
He's the horrible man
who founded this
company 120 years ago.
Now he's dead.
Come on, she's into one guy's
mind and one guy's body.
You're just threatened
by a woman having power.
Nonsense.
I love the fairer sex.
But science tells us it
degrades their femininity
if they're allowed
to read or own money
or leave the house
or call for help.
You know, there are
pills I could take
that would make you
stop talking to me.
Admit it.
We'd be a lot better off
if we had kept that rib in
and just buggered each other.
Oh.
What was I thinking?
Nobody would be hard on a man
for doing what
Jessica was doing.
She didn't need me
to protect her.
So you don't mind
taking my seconds?
Not when they're so fine.
I'd never mind sharing a
piece with my brother.
Hey, you like it your way,
I like it mine.
I got to tell you...
that sweet pie
tastes even sweeter
knowing my bro's
getting some, too.
Oh, yeah.
You feel pretty smart.
You think you're pulling
one over on the pie?
Well, the pie's pulling
one over on you.
Because the pie
knows everything.
You're talking about
an actual pie?
Of course.
We kept referring to it as pie.
I don't see how there could
have been any confusion.
Were you talking about Jessica?
What?!
No, of course not.
I just get a little
overprotective sometimes.
Of pie?
Yes.
You get away from this.
Okay, I screwed up.
But you heard them.
How could anyone get so
crazily enthusiastic
about a piece of pie?
Oh, sweet crusted son of God!
You told Ben and
Peter that I know.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't going to say anything
but they were having
this insane conversation
about pie, and...
Everything was great
when they thought
they were fooling me,
and you almost ruined it.
Luckily, I convinced them
that the three of us
could still make it as a couple.
Don't you think this whole
thing is kind of unhealthy?
You know what I
think is unhealthy?
You butting in to
my relationships.
Stay out of my love life! Boy,
Jessica's really mad at me.
I've got to do something.
Let me decide who I want
to be involved with.
Here, taste this pie.
It will explain everything.
I don't want any of
your stupid pie.
I'm really mad at you, Andy...
Oh, my God.
I'm not upset with you anymore.
All I can think
about is this pie.
All hail Andy,
bringer of great pie!
What are you doing?
Get away from me!
Hey, Champ.
Hey, guys.
You got a second?
Okay.
Keith and I have been talking.
We know that we've been
fighting a lot lately.
That's probably been
pretty hard on you, huh, sport?
Kinda.
Yeah, we thought so.
And I bet you feel like
all this fighting's
your fault, huh?
Yeah.
Well, it is.
What?
Hey, let's get your
suitcase, cowboy.
You guys are right.
My back has been
feeling a lot better,
so I don't want you
to worry about me
because I'm going to be just...
Does this mean we're
not nurturing people?
We did okay at first.
I just think we tried
to do too much.
Yeah.
Maybe we should start smaller, like...
get a fish.
Mm. Maybe we could
just have fish.
You mean like make fish?
I don't think we're
ready for that.
Yeah. Let's just go out.
And, you know, you're
not supposed to kayak
in the Venice canals, but...
that starry night, the
lady of the Adriatic
was so enchanting I just
couldn't help myself.
You have a beautiful soul.
Ooh, gosh, look at the time.
I've got to get home and
sleep with your brother.
Uh... Jessica, you
know, I've been having
second thoughts about
this arrangement.
Really? Yes.
Well, maybe you could write
a poem or something.
You liked that, huh?
Oh, boy!
You know, I've been working
on some theories about politics.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, I picked up this
book about the Kennedys...
Jack and Jackie...
Peter, I had a lovely conversation
with your brother earlier
and I just had a lot
of sex with you.
Now I'm really tired.
Jessica...
I can't live like this.
When we agreed to
this arrangement,
I thought I could win you over
so that one day I would
have all of you.
Hey, I want all of you, too.
And if you would just
listen to my theories
about stuff and things...
Peter, she is not going
to leave me for you.
Well, she's not going
A woman needs more than
just talk, Mr. Talk.
Guys...
That's the best you can do, huh?
Mr. Talk?
Talk, talk, talk, talk, talk,
Talk, talk, talk, talk,
talk, talk, talk, talk...
Look, Jessica,
I've been practicing
how to kiss.
Let me show you.
Talk, talk, talk.
Hey. Hi.
Can I come in?
Of course.
Is something wrong?
We broke up.
All three of you?
No, they're still together,
but I'm alone again.
Just me and this pie.
Well, in about five seconds,
you're going to be
totally alone again.
I'm sorry I got so mad at you.
I know you were just trying
to watch out for me.
No, it's okay.
I get a little
overprotective sometimes.
I like that you look out for me.
I think it's really sweet.
Well, people should
be sweet to you.
You have a whistling booger.
I thought it was you.
I'm pretty sure it's you.
Be quiet a second.
Oh, yeah, you're right. It's me.
Yeah, see? Yeah.
Let's have some pie. All right.
It was really Jessica with
the whistling booger,
but I let her think it was me
because she was the one who
was emotionally vulnerable.
And sometimes, that's what
friends do for each other.