- [Voiceover] The way I
see it, you can write your
congressman, sign a
petition, get on a bus,
and million man
march in Washington.
Or stuff envelopes, volunteer,
register swing voters
in swing states.
Shit, you can quit your
corporate job and sign up
to teach poor kids on a bus.
Do relief work in some war
torn country, get on some
back to nation trip
and live off the grid
in Vermont, eating bark
and wiping your ass
with oak leaves.
Whatever it is, you'll
probably convince yourself
it's all good, drift
off to sleep at night,
thinking, "I'm doing my part."
See, that's what the
myth's built on, the one
we all got spoon
fed in grade school.
Idea that the little man
can make a difference,
pull himself up by the
bootstraps, you know,
do something positive.
That shit's been hardwired
into every one of our
little American hard drives.
Except, maybe, I picked
up a virus along the way.
Got some worm in me that's
just been digging and digging
and erasing and organizing
because that myth just
wasn't working out.
I started asking myself,
I started thinking that
maybe the only way to
really get at the truth,
the only way to really
shake things up,
is to have the establishment
come face to face
with the barrel of a gun.
(ominous music)
- I'm waiting on
something, Senator.
- Can we at least
cover my privates?
Can we do that at least?
- Why don't we try answering
the question first, Senator?
- Christ.
I'm losing circulation here.
- Would you keep
your voice down?
- Voice down, I'm naked, I'm
tied to a goddamned chair.
How much longer you gonna...
I get it, OK, you got me,
I'm quiet as a church mouse.
- Now you can continue
when you're ready.
(chatter)
- Was it a face to face
meeting and how did
you actually meet him?
- Well, as mentioned, I've
been conducting research
on the hacker community.
And I made contact through
some of my connections.
And no, it's not a
face to face situation.
(chatter)
Miss.
- But is it really viable?
Does this individual
believe that he can actually
undermine the system in
some fundamental way,
that criminal activity
like this might actually
evolve into a legitimate
political platform?
(typing)
(beeps)
- I was asked to read
a prepared statement.
Before I do, I'd like to
direct everyone's attention
to the confess website.
Which apparently
was just updated.
(ominous music)
(beeps)
- I support jobs in South
Carolina over sending
aid to some Arab who's gonna
blow us all to kingdom come.
- OK, fair enough, but that's
not what I asked you, Senator.
- No, you listen to me.
Why should we care, huh?
I'll ask you that.
As a US senator from
South Carolina, why should
I give a shit about sending
aid to Mexico or somewheres
else when I've got some
tobacco farmer lost his job,
he can't make his truck
payments, he's losing his house,
his wife is gonna leave
him, so why the hell should
I care?
Huh?
I mean, if they're starving
in them other places,
let 'em starve.
If they hump monkeys in
the jungles of Africa
and get AIDs, then that's
their cross to bear.
Look, could we cover up
my goddamned genitals?
(chatter)
- Thank you.
So, here we go.
The confess project is about
giving a voice to truths
that are rarely heard.
(hip hop music)
- This is the normal
verse, you understand that?
We all ride this.
- They are going to
treat you, so how can you
say that 40,000,000
people are uninsured?
Come back here and talk.
- Keep it real means keep
it real fucking broke.
- You think this is power?
- There are a few things I'd
like to go over with you.
- Vinny, he's not with me,
get him out of the car.
- Come on guys, I look
like a goddamned computer
department to you?
(sirens blaring)
(hip hop music)
♪ When all your
dreams are shot down
♪ I know that Martin
hunting Hampton
♪ We saw what happened on TV
♪ The pot billion we
knew the government
♪ Did it, even if
they wasn't convicted
♪ The hoods convinced
they committed the murders
♪ So just admit it, goddamn
♪ It ain't hard for me to see
♪ There's a new form of
slavery in this country
♪ We ain't free,
they got us trapped
♪ Alcohol and drugs
♪ Athletes and thugs
♪ That ain't the
only option for us
♪ But we trapped
♪ Ghettos and projects
♪ Police don't serve and protect
♪ They only search and arrest
♪ They got us trapped
♪ Alcohol and drugs
♪ Athletes and thugs
♪ That ain't the
only option for us ♪
- The administration firmly
believes that we have
an obligation to do everything
in our power to bring
open markets and
democracy to those who are
less fortunate.
- [Voiceover] So, would
you characterize this as
an exercise in nation building?
- [Woman On TV] No, I
would characterize this
as a national security priority,
and just as important,
a moral obligation to
give a helping hand...
- [Voiceover] No, we're good,
I got a whole lot of it.
Shit, coming out of
high school, I basically
swept the academic awards.
All the prizes.
Excellence in science
and technology,
national merit scholar,
future leaders award,
engineer, promise prize.
It was basically like
the crowning moment.
The end result of my mamma
enrolling me in every
after school program
out there, give me that
computer early, always
deferring gratification shit.
You know, play by the rules.
Bring an apple to your teacher.
Double check, triple
check that homework.
Don't get caught up in
stupid teenage shit.
It was all about keeping my
eyes on the future payout.
The full ride to a top college.
The high paying job.
A house and a mortgage.
Doing better than my dad had.
I got championed by teachers.
By boosters who wanted
to be part of a story
about at risk kid with smarts.
(jazzy music)
- [Voiceover] Some employee's
gonna pay some high school
drop out to hack into a
company server and bring down
a whole business, and
that's where we fit in.
Safe circle...
- Hello?
Someone up there?
- Fuck.
(gasping)
- Oh come here, come down here.
(laughs)
How come you didn't
call me and tell me you
were coming back?
I would have picked
you up at the airport.
- Well, I know, but I
just took a bus, and,
you know, I didn't have
the exact time I was
coming home.
- A bus, from Mexico?
- Yeah, part time.
- What, you run out of money?
Look at you.
You look so different.
You're older, with
your dreads all long.
Oh, sweetie.
- Mom, Mom, Mom.
- OK, OK, OK.
I can't help myself.
So, you gonna be here
for a while though, huh?
- Well, in the city, you
know, just here to take
care of some stuff, just
to work some things out.
- You gonna stay
here though, right?
- No, I'm gonna be
staying in the city.
But you know, I'll come
through, I'll come see you.
- OK, OK.
- Are you OK?
- I'm good.
I'm fine.
- All right.
- You're not gonna
stay right now?
- I can't, Mom.
- [Mom] Well can't
we just go get
something to eat or something?
- Look, I just got to
go meet this guy later
and I'll be back later
on in the week, OK?
- [Voiceover] First
mover advantage is key.
Gotta stress that,
remember that, Terrell,
I gotta stress that, now
first mover advantage
and its impact on market share.
Now, you gotta mention Gato,
Amazon, Mission Import,
the big boys, that's
what we're gonna be.
(hip hop music)
- So, we start you off at
eight and a half beans an hour,
and that's policy, but
you listen, all right now,
you do good work, OK, I
get positive feedback,
we'll see about throwing
you a little more
in a month or so.
(sirens blaring)
- You promised to
e-mail me everyday,
once it's up and running.
Of course, there's a four
hour time difference,
isn't there?
Or is it three?
Three.
- [Voiceover] Look, we all
know the girl has no talent,
so why don't we just
package her on her looks,
the lifestyle...?
- Exactly, the evolution
from down and out,
reconnecting with the
millionaire father.
- That's it, right?
You're finished?
I can get on it now?
- He's at Stanford,
full scholarship.
Did I already mention that?
- I started out here
three years ago.
All right, I worked
installation.
But I busted my balls
and I proved myself
and now, I'm in management.
- So, that's it, right?
You're finished, I
can get on it now?
What?
- How many times you gonna
ask me that question, man?
- [Kid] Yeah, yeah, yeah, but...
- Did you bring it
to them on time?
All right.
Tomorrow, 8:00 AM, I got
you on around six calls,
a richie rich uptown,
that PR firm and a couple
of geriatrics in Queens.
- I guess we should go with
the eating disorder thing,
yeah, I think that'll
play really nicely,
her getting it under control,
finding herself, whatever.
- [Voiceover] Very
human, touching.
- I can connect it,
it's easy, I know how.
Yeah, yeah, you just have
to do it, I'll show you.
- OK, OK, listen, kid, you
really need to chill out, OK?
- You listen to
me, he fixates, OK?
He has a disorder,
he's special needs, OK?
Now you gonna answer
his questions?
Are you gonna tell him
how long, you gonna tell
me how long?
Because I'm late for my trainer.
- OK, look, all
right, it's my bad,
you know, I was almost
finished anyway.
Look, all I was doing was
installing this webcam,
which I'm throwing in for
free because I made you late
and I messed up your schedule.
As a matter of fact,
let me show you this.
Now, with this webcam,
you're gonna be able
to shoot pictures and
short video clips.
(typing)
Stuff like this.
Enjoy.
- Are you gonna tell him
how long, you gonna tell
me how long?
It's a disorder, he's
special needs, OK?
Now you gonna answer
his questions?
Turn it off.
You know what, I'm
calling your boss.
- You humiliated her,
you humiliated her son,
you were late.
I'm gonna have to fire
you, hey, you can't leave
with the shirt and the hat, hey.
- Excuse me.
There seems to be something
wrong with my door.
- Credit card number
you left got canceled.
Was it even yours?
- Here you go.
- It's a good start,
but you owe 83.25.
- Come on, man, I don't
get paid until the end
of the week, man.
- Yeah, me too.
- OK.
- Hey, you can't come in here.
- Get the fuck out of my way.
- What you gonna do?
- [Voiceover] OK, so,
when they're telling you
the classic stock of
the company you start
is gonna be worth 1.75
million the minute
the company goes
public, you're 19,
you're the fucking man,
the geek turned celebrity,
the quiet kid in the corner
who's gonna be rolling
up in a fucking Benz next week.
You start turning down the
full ride scholarships,
you're feeling good about it.
MIT, well thanks, but no thanks.
Carnegie Melon, maybe next time.
Stanford, I'll take that
honorary doctorate in a couple
years and get that
shit ready for you.
You start promising
your mom a new house,
new car, telling her
she'll be able to quit
that shitty ass job
and take that trip
to the Bahamas she always
used to talk about.
(melancholy music)
(chatter)
- OK, die, yeah,
yeah, die, yeah.
OK.
Yeah, yes, yes, yes.
Never saw that coming, did ya?
- I mean, stuff was changing.
They sold the
division, I don't know,
basically it was the
same routine, pretty much
the same as ever.
- So what happened next?
- Out of the blue,
two weeks notice.
Just like that.
- Hold up.
Explain it, what happened?
- Yeah, can you believe it?
No severance, nothing,
just letters in our boxes
one morning.
I mean, is that right?
Two weeks notice after 14 years?
This is where we're
headed with this new
economy or whatever
they're calling it.
And after we've been
through all that with
the retirement accounts.
- What about 'em?
- Basically they forced
us to keep our retirement
in company stock.
- So what happened, did
the company went under
or what?
- No, after they laid
people off, I heard
they did fine, had
a profitable year.
So, you got something lined up?
You should have no
problem, at least you have
marketable skills.
Hey, maybe you could
call Greg Batenbelle,
whatever it is you
call him now, huh?
- Worry about your
own problems, OK?
- My own problems, huh?
I'm behind in everything, OK?
I had to sell the car.
The house is falling apart.
Temp work is two, three
days a week at best.
I don't know, Terrell, when
I was 20 years younger,
had big breasts...
- What are you talking about?
- It wasn't just downsizing.
He's a pig, you should see
them, these vulnerable,
desperate types.
- Who, I mean you're
talking about your boss?
- Yes.
Everyone knows what's going on.
(phone ringing)
- Can I help you?
- Yes, I was just
doing routine upgrades.
- Sarah let you in here?
- Yeah, she did.
- Well, I'm expecting a
conference call, she should
know that, reschedule.
So sort it out with her, OK?
- Yeah, OK.
(phone ringing)
- Do you understand?
- Right, I understand, but I...
- [Mom] Is that right?
Two weeks notice after 14 years.
- We might possibly be
able to work something out.
(moaning)
(laughs)
- Mr. Connors, I was
wondering about that phone.
- We might be able to
work something out.
After hours occasionally.
Oh, yes.
You like that?
Working late tonight.
You're gonna get a nice big one.
Big Christmas bonus.
Christmas.
- I've been working
really hard, really hard.
- She does what she's
told, doesn't she?
(moaning)
Sugar bonus.
You can go now, Sarah.
Go now, Sarah.
That's fine.
- [Voiceover] Every action has
an equal and opposite reaction.
Newton's third law.
You know, I liked that
shit the day I first
read about it in grade school.
I was convinced it could
be like some guiding
principle of my life.
But as I got older,
it just, it got less
and less true.
'Cause it just
doesn't tell you shit
about dealing with people.
No equation or code
could ever factor in all
the jealousies,
fears, guilt, the ego.
That shit's more
like rolling dice.
(beeping)
- What is this?
- Titties.
(beeping)
- Damn.
Been a while, right?
- Yeah, it's definitely
been a while.
- Hey, it's good
to see you, man.
- Man, you, too.
- How you doing, hey.
Let me show you around.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, cool.
- Just picked up a new server.
- Oh, shit.
- I got it about a month ago.
You remember all that?
It's obsolete shit now.
Come on.
I don't even know
where to begin.
- Me neither.
- History.
- So, do you really want
to talk about history?
- Yeah, OK, go ahead.
- You ain't got anything to say?
- If it's an apology
you're looking for, no.
No, I don't.
So, since then, since
then, where you been?
- Doing my own thing, travel.
Looks like you're
doing all right.
- Surviving.
- Look, man.
Do you think it's possible
that you could slide
me in on something?
- You serious?
- Yeah.
I need to help my mom out.
- It's ugly out there, right?
- Tell me if you got part
time or whatever you got.
You know I can do it.
- They're all nervous,
anxious, trying to protect
their proprietary
applications, they've been
hacked three or four
times in the last year.
Typical financial
service company.
Colombian grad student
fishing around for a sexy
topic for a thesis, she
comes in and interviews
all the time.
Check this out, she's
the daughter of some
congressman from Connecticut.
Come on, I'll introduce you.
Everybody, this is Terrell.
A dinosaur you may have heard
him, he used to go by Blaze.
- You serious?
- Seriously, you should
interview this guy,
get that historical perspective.
- I'd love to.
Hi, I'm Olivia.
- Hey.
- Yeah, I'm doing my
dissertation on hacker culture.
The ethics, motivations.
- Hey, what's this
you guys are watching?
- It's this clip that
was posted this morning.
It's a video of a CEO getting
on with his secretary.
- Yo, this shit is fucked up.
- They just gave a press
conference, I guess
the board forced him to resign.
- Check this shit out.
- She's a good girl, she
does what she's told.
- It definitely has a to it.
- I see it right
here on the website.
Yes, that's the one
I want, the scarf.
The angora scarf.
Yes, that's the one I want,
the scarf, the angora scarf.
Why is this so difficult?
I have informed you that
yes, that's what I want,
the scarf, the angora scarf.
(hip hop music)
- Hey, you're up early.
- Yeah, working.
- That's great, what is it?
- Wall Street Hornton.
- No, come on,
seriously, what is it?
- System security,
I'm working for your
power grade depend.
- You see, you see
that, didn't I tell...
Well.
Sounds good.
- Yeah, well, should be
able to help you out now.
- I don't want to
be some kind of...
- Oh, come on, Mom, stop that.
- Get you some breakfast.
- No, no, I'm fine.
OK?
Just relax.
- I know, but listen,
when you do have a moment,
I'd love to catch up,
hear about your travels,
what you're up to.
- OK, I will.
For now I gotta go.
- Go on, then.
Good luck.
- [Voiceover] See, if you
ain't wearing the right
Works Brother tie, or
you don't got the right
Uncle Tom MBA from
Harvard, then you're
just another bike
messenger delivering shit.
But see, if you flip it,
hold the mirror up to them,
then see who perceives what.
See how they come across when
they ain't focus grouped,
Photoshop isn't in their
most flattering light.
(hip hop music)
- You stop pussy footing
around and pull the
goddamn trigger?
Guy's a fucking retard.
Yeah, yeah, what
can I do for you?
- System security,
Terrell Lussen.
- And?
- And I'm not sure
what you mean.
- Come on, guy, do I look
like a goddamn computer
department to you?
- Well, I thought because
the receptionist just
told me that you were the
person I was supposed to see.
- Down the hall, all the way
down the hall on the right.
On the right side, you'll
see Tim Bellweather's office.
He's the head egghead.
- Thanks.
- Fucking morons.
- Excuse me, did you
just say something?
- What?
- I could have sworn
you just said something.
- God, what are
you talking about?
- Did you say something?
- What, you want me too?
You're a frigging nutjob,
OK, and by the way,
nice frigging outfit, what
is this, dress down Tuesday
or something?
You know what, have a
little self respect, son.
(hip hop music)
- What the fuck are you doing?
- I'm working.
- They're threatening
to drop the contract.
They're one of my
biggest clients.
- The guy's an asshole, man.
- Look, undermine
you're own shit, OK?
But I did you a favor.
- Oh, come on, man,
don't act all innocent.
Don't act like I
don't know how you get
your clients in the first place.
- You don't know shit, OK?
- You're right, I
don't know shit.
- Look, I know you're
still upset about
Safe Circle, OK?
I was upset, too.
But you have got to get over it.
- Oh, man, come on,
man, are you done?
- No, I'm not.
My clients don't have shit
to do with what happened, OK?
You can't fucking
lash out at people.
Why don't you take it up
with Heston if you're so
pissed off?
(hip hop music)
- No, evaluation's off, way off.
Check last year's numbers
again, yeah, hold on a second.
Yeah.
- 'Sup, man, how's it going?
- Do I know you?
- I don't know, do you?
- Look, buddy, what do you want?
I'm on the phone.
- So, you haven't a good one?
- What?
- Are you having a good day?
A successful day.
- Charles, let me
call you right back.
Do I know you?
You worked at the club, right?
- Yeah, the club.
Maybe that's it.
So, what's up, man,
did you fuck anybody
out of their idea today?
- What?
Who the hell are you?
- I'm just interested
in whether you made bank
off of someone else's sweat?
- Bank.
- Yeah, bank.
You know, I'm just
interested, I mean,
did you out contract
anybody today?
(laughs)
- No, no, actually I didn't.
But if I had, I certainly
wouldn't discuss it
with someone like you.
- Yeah, how come?
I mean, do you like keeping
the common man in the dark?
- The common man, is
that what you are?
- Well, I guess you got me
pegged there, buddy, right?
Well, I got to be going,
man, I got to get back
to the club.
- [Voiceover] No, see, when
it's in their best interests,
they'll play like they're
you're best buddy for press.
They told me I was God's
gift, acting like I be playing
golf with them every
Sunday at the country club,
going on dates with
their society daughters.
But see, there's a fine
print in those contracts.
That's the shit you're
blind to when they're
wining and dining you,
talking stock options.
And while you're blinded
by the glitz and glamour,
they keeping their
eyes on the end game.
Which basically involves
sucking you dry of
all the tech know how
you got, and then kicking
you to the curb.
- They were the
size of watermelons.
- Yo, homie.
- Fake.
- Yo, yo.
I got a couple more
questions for you.
How much is it that
you make, anyway?
- Hold on a second.
Are you following me?
- I mean, you make a
good living, right?
- I'm comfortable, yes.
Now get the hell out of my face.
Steve, I'm gonna have
to call you back.
- I'm sorry, man,
what's your name again?
- Cindy, it's Richard,
where's the fucking car?
There's no one down here.
- Richard, Richard, OK,
OK, and what is it that
you do again?
Oh, come on, man, look.
I work at the club, I moonlight
as a messenger sometimes,
so what is it that you do?
Are you like a bond
trader or something?
- I'm a VC, a
venture capitalist.
- That's right, you are.
It's coming back,
it's coming back.
- OK, listen, asshole.
I don't know what the
fuck you're talking about.
And I don't have the time.
So fucking leave me alone.
- All right, it's
cool man, I hear you.
Oh, oh, except for
one thing, man.
You say comfortable.
What exactly does that
mean, because I mean,
how much is that, is
that like a million,
a million five, 2,000,000,
I mean, say when when
I get there.
3,000,000?
Oh, come on, man, what,
you're embarrassed
to say it out loud?
If you want, you could
write it down, you know?
Send me a little note.
So.
- What the fuck are you doing?
Vinny, get him out of the
car, he's not with me.
- Sir, can you please
step out of the car?
- Hold on, I got a
few more questions.
Do you think it's fair
that you make all this cash
all from other people's ideas?
- All I know is I work
hard for the money I make.
Now leave me alone.
- OK, OK, God chill, chill man.
I just wanted to chat.
You know?
You could have asked me
questions, too, made this
sort of a two way sort of thing.
'Cause you just might be
interested in my background.
And in what we have in common.
You have a good day.
- I'm comfortable, yeah.
The common man.
Is that what you are?
- I guess you got me
pegged there buddy, right?
Well, I got to be going, man,
I got to get back to the club.
- [Richard] I'm
comfortable, I work hard
for the money I make.
A venture capitalist.
- Good morning.
You know what, man, I'm
not totally satisfied.
- The hell's the
matter with you? Fuck.
- I don't know, I guess
I'm just still fixated
on what someone like you makes.
You know, your salary.
So, come on, Rich,
how do you feel?
- Don't you fucking touch me.
If I fucking see you
again, I will kick your
fucking ass, do
you understand me?
Do you understand me?
- Yes, I do understand you.
Shit, man, you don't need
to get violent with me.
I was just asking questions.
- Shut up.
Where do I know you from?
- See, I thought you'd
know, but I guess we all
look kind of similar, don't we?
So, you grew up
with cash, right?
- No, no.
I grew up middle class,
now get the fuck out
of here before I call security.
- You grew up middle
class, like Donald Trump
grew up middle class,
is that what you're
trying to say man?
Shit.
- I see you again,
you're fucking dead.
2,000,000, OK?
I made $2,000,000 last
year, that satisfy
your twisted little
fucked up mind?
More than you'll ever make
in a lifetime, all right?
- So, you give to
charity, right?
- Charity.
As a matter of fact we
do, we give to charity.
Benefits, we go to
benefits all the time.
So little black kids
don't end up becoming real
fucking freaks like you.
- Fuck 'em if we do, right?
Just like that Safe Circle deal.
- Cindy, it's Richard, where's
the fucking car?
It's the car, OK?
As a matter of fact we
do, we give to charity.
I'm comfortable, yes.
I'm a VC, a venture capitalist.
I made $2,000,000 last year.
You understand me?
A bonus of three
and a half million.
I grew up middle class.
You work at the club, right?
Is that who you
are, the common man?
As a matter of fact, we
do, we give to charity.
Benefits, we go to
benefits all the time.
(yelling)
So little black kids don't
end up becoming little
fucking freaks.
Are you following me?
I'm a VC.
You understand me?
I'm comfortable, comfortable
venture capitalist.
I make more than your
sorry ass will ever make
in a lifetime.
- Do you see what I'm saying?
- Well, it's captured something.
Some genuine sentiment
but it certainly doesn't
constitute a model yet.
- OK, right.
But think of the implications
for environmental activism,
anti globalism efforts.
- Now.
- Professor, WTO protests.
- Wait a second.
If you want to construct
your thesis around internet
activism or even hacker
culture, that's good,
that's fine, it fits well
within the department's perview.
But this is, it's scattershot.
You need to be patient.
You know, see how it plays out.
See if the media gets behind it.
Propagates with the more
radical communities, right?
- Right.
Thank you so much for your time.
- Look, Olivia,
here's the real issue.
These people, this
person, whomever it is,
what they're doing is
only relevant if you
or somebody else
makes it relevant.
Otherwise, it's just
fleeting digital chatter.
Random noise, right?
- Right.
(tense music)
- OK, so you did know him.
- Right, but didn't
figure it out 'til later.
His hair is different.
Turns out he was a minor
player in a deal my friend
structured a number
of years back.
- Structured, meaning what?
- We provided seed
capital, eventually assumed
the managerial oversight.
- And the deal went sour.
- Depends, depends
who you talk to.
- You forced him out.
- No, look.
They developed this
surveillance technology.
Very sophisticated,
but had no clue,
absolutely no idea
how to grow a company.
Horrible people skills.
He was 19, maybe 20, tops.
- Mr. Heston, please,
was he asked to leave or
did he go voluntarily?
- Asked.
He was asked to leave.
But he was compensated, he
was paid for the programming
work he did.
- There we go.
Have you seen this?
- Yeah, just not this
particular article.
- What do you think?
- I'm not sure yet, you?
- It's not as tight as
it could be, the concept,
but I think that
it's got potential.
- Tight.
- Yeah, it could be
stronger thematically.
I think that it could be
a real mode of critique.
- So, what do you want to know?
- I guess let's start with
some background information.
Tell me about growing
up, being a part of the
hacker community, how
you got involved in it.
- Well, I was your
classic latchkey kid.
My mother really wanted me
to do better for myself,
so she got me a computer.
And then, why are you so
interested in all this?
- Let's stick with you.
- I thought this
was a conversation.
- OK, so, when did you first
start accessing systems?
Accessing information
that wasn't yours?
And what did it feel
like that first time?
What?
- Greg tells me I can trust you.
- Yeah, you can.
- Why?
- Because you can.
It's just a fact.
- Stop.
You want to know something?
I know this guy.
- Don't even joke.
- I'm not joking.
I grew up with him.
It's a small community.
- Do you think you can
set me up with him?
You think you can
get me an interview?
- Maybe, why?
- One more of these,
if it's done right,
and it's front page,
this is prime time news.
- Excuse me, what do
you mean done right?
- OK.
One thing that I've
been thinking about.
Can you imagine if you
were to reconfigure
the sites that had a more
decentralized structure.
Like, a structure that
lets others submit their
confessions, too.
Stuff that they've
forced from people.
Seriously, I need
to talk to this guy.
- OK.
Why don't you let me
borrow that camera for like
a day or two?
- OK.
- Maybe I can get him to video
himself talking or something.
- Yeah, take it.
(contemplative music)
- Get your shit and get out.
- Man, what are
you talking about?
- I don't know you.
I haven't seen you in years.
- Where'd you get this?
- I downloaded it.
It's everywhere.
- What, you felt the
need to Google me first
thing in the morning?
- What did you do?
- [Terrell] Nothing.
- Well, I hope you can
understand why I can't
have you here because
I can't jeopardize my
whole shit.
- OK, man, you know,
it's not the first time
this shit has happened.
- Oh, man, don't
fucking go there again.
Man.
Come on, look, I know
when Safe Circle imploded
that I did not respond properly.
- Respond properly,
are you kidding me?
You just sat back and
watched me get pushed out.
You didn't do anything,
you didn't respond at all.
- Yeah, and then I got pushed
out the door two months later.
You should be happy that
you got out when you did.
- Because you built this
place up by yourself, right?
From nothing.
Yeah, I should be happy.
- Look.
Look.
- Get out of my way, Greg.
- I just want you to know
that if it starts to look
really bad and you really
need something, I don't know.
Money or something, I'll
do what I can to help you.
- Excuse me.
(chatter)
(doorbell ringing)
- Hi, Miss Lessor?
- Yes.
- Agents David and
McAllistor, FBI.
We'd like to speak with
you about, is it your son?
Terrell Lessor?
- Yes, is he OK?
- That's what we need
to speak to you about,
Miss Lessor, it seems
he's in a bit of trouble.
- We're gonna have to ask
you to come with us, ma'am.
Apologies for that.
I also have a warrant here
to search your premises.
- Come on, you bitch.
That's right, look at me.
Yeah.
All right.
- Come on, come on, yeah.
- That's the one I want.
That's the one I want.
- Fuck.
- [Kid] OK, die.
- [Woman] Yes.
Yes, that's the one I want.
- OK, yeah, OK.
- Yes.
(laughs)
Why is this so difficult?
- OK, die.
- I see it right here,
that's the one I want.
- OK, yeah, yeah.
- Yes.
Scarf, the angora scarf.
Item 4122, yes,
that's the one I want.
- Never saw that
coming, did you?
- Mexico.
Maybe it's Mexico.
I remember him saying
he'd been traveling.
I think he blames me
for always pushing.
I pushed him too
hard all the time.
- It's obvious that
he had options.
It seems clear.
- You know they forced them out?
Literally came into work
one morning and they
escorted him out
of the building.
- We're aware of this, Miss
Lessor, it's documented.
- It's what happened after
that, where we need your help.
Now, maybe Mexico isn't
quite the level of detail
that we're looking for.
- No, uh uh, unless you
tell me what you know.
What happened to him?
Get a lawyer.
I walk out.
- Actually, you won't,
Miss Lessor, the things is,
as a material witness,
under the anti-terrorism
legislation, we're at
liberty to keep you...
- Jim.
Why don't you get us
a round of coffee?
I'll take a bran muffin.
Miss Lessor, is there
something we can get you?
Apologies, ma'am.
As you can imagine, the
agency's overworked these days.
It impacts some of
us more than others.
- Let him know we
have a file on him
as a juvenile, remind
her that we know about
the bank hacks and
the DOD of '93.
- Here's my read
on the situation.
Terrell's gonna end up
in prison sometime soon.
Now, I'd wager, based on not
that many years of experience,
but I'd wager, that computer
skills won't do much for him
in maximum security.
Day to day.
Survival wise.
- Look, Miss Lessor,
the bottom line is
if we can get to Terrell
before someone gets hurt,
gets killed, there's a
chance we might be able
to work something out.
But in order for that
to happen, you're gonna
have to help us.
We're gonna need you
to give us a name.
Anything to help
us find your son.
Now we're gonna step
out for a minute.
You think about it.
Write something down.
Anything.
Something for us to go on.
At this point, it's in
Terrell's best interest.
(melancholy music)
- Can you believe these people?
- Yeah, except they're
more like victims.
It's not like the
businessman on the bus
fucking his secretary.
People are going to think
that this is depressing.
- What?
What makes these people victims?
- What did they do?
- Come on, man, look
at this guy, come on.
- He makes a stronger
case when they come across
as crass or arrogant.
He shows that they've
manipulated people's lives
for their own benefit.
- OK, hold on.
All right.
Got something for you.
I got him to answer
your questions.
- You said that you
hadn't seen him.
- Yeah, no, but then I
saw him after we talked.
Now look, don't get too excited.
He had to run, so
it's kind of short.
- Wait.
I can't hear what
you're asking him.
- I'm asking him your questions.
- I have targets in mind,
people, dates, places.
Political figures.
- What, what are you
doing, what are you doing?
- That's so fucked up.
What, I mean, do you really
think that I wouldn't
recognize you?
You have the same voice,
you're wearing the
same fucking necklace.
Get your shit and get out.
- OK, wait, wait, wait, hold up.
- This isn't some
fucking joke to me.
- It's not a joke
to me, neither.
OK, I'm serious,
this is actually me.
- You know what, just get
the fuck out of my house.
- OK.
All right, I can show
you the site, I can show
you the footage, I got it
all on top of my laptop,
all right?
Now look, you know what I
was working on earlier today?
I was working on this
whole idea where others can
submit their own
footage to the site,
you know, kind of like
a whole submit section.
Your idea.
- So, the dread thing?
- Yeah, that hurt.
- She did say you did look good.
(ethereal music)
Come on, I just fucked you.
God, at least give me a hint.
Well.
I have some ideas, too.
I think that we should
generate a list.
Target individuals that
represent larger themes.
Sort of like societal
archetypes, you know?
- That's good, good.
- You just saying that?
- No, no, I mean, you
know, hey, it's basically
going in that direction, anyway.
- Yeah.
Hey, do you need
money for anything?
- What?
- Because you were saying
something about not
wanting to work
for Greg anymore.
- Yeah, I'm definitely not
working for Greg anymore.
Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- OK, well, I could use
some extra equipment for
the next one, but
I'm gonna need,
maybe a thousand man, that's
only if you can spare that.
- Done.
(hip hop music)
- Let's go.
- This is a story
about a sell out.
The cracker, Glenace Bennett.
Fits all their expectations.
Policy advisor to the president
of the United States of America.
Let me tell you
something, I have a voice
on the national stage.
This is jut another
story that the media
is gonna love feeding
white America.
They're gonna love it.
How can you feel so
disenfranchised that you cannot
voice your complaints
through legal channels,
democratic channels, I'm
talking about voting booths,
I'm talking about
the free press.
The administration
firmly believes...
This is a story about
a sell out right now.
Right now, right now.
- This coward, wherever
he is, will be rooted out
and prosecuted to the
full extent of the law.
♪ What you say, what you say?
♪ I missed that
- It's exactly what
you get when you cross
a cyber geek with a
rabidly misguided liberal.
He's bottom dwelling
scum and just the reason
we should bring back public
flogging and public execution,
and he's welcome to come
to my show any time,
I will straighten him out.
♪ Take the votes away
♪ I can political
on election day ♪
- Tell me what you think
about Terrell Lessor.
- Oh, I think he's got balls.
He goes out there and says
everything that I wish
I could say.
♪ Be no flip
♪ Shout and scream revolt,
we wanted to live ♪
- I think he's inspiring,
I look up to him.
I'm behind him all the way.
♪ Town click click,
TV, change the channel
♪ Back, more TV
♪ It's not
- Objectivity in
reporting is something
that we all aspire to.
Our high profile
corporate backers,
they don't report the news in
a fair and balanced manner.
♪ Africa 7,000 daily HIV
- HMOs return profit
to our stockholders.
If you go to the emergency room.
Profit to our stockholders.
Suppose you have a heart
attack in the middle
of the street.
Profit to our stockholders.
♪ Say, say, I missed that
♪ What you say, what you say?
♪ I missed that
♪ What would it take for
us to shake the shit down
us to break the shit down
♪ What would it take
- Give back to the community?
What the fuck are you
talking about, bitch?
Give back to the community?
I fuck all the bitches I
want, all the time, any time.
I don't give.
You know I don't
even write that,
this is entertainment, man.
- I think he's twisted,
he's a criminal, he should
definitely be locked up.
(hip hop music
with fast rapping)
- What, what happened?
- Nothing happened, baby.
It's OK.
- Come here, girl.
- Come on, it's time to get up.
It's time to get up.
(calm music)
Hey, I need to
show you something.
- What?
- The submit section.
Terrell, people are
starting to post their own.
Come on.
- Go, go, go, go.
- Fuck, get the fuck out.
What are you doing, man?
What?
(yelling)
Eight or nine, maybe
11 on the highway,
I don't know.
- [Voiceover] You like the
outdoors, you like nature?
- Yeah, yeah, I hunt, I fish.
- [Voiceover] But you
don't see a connection
between driving one of
these and environmental
degradation, global warming.
You don't think
driving a fucking tank
compared to this
country's foreign policy?
Oil?
- Yeah, I do.
- [Voiceover] Get
out of the car.
- You're not gonna believe
this shit, watch this.
- [Voiceover] Go.
(explosion)
- God, do you see
how we're expanding?
Making linkages.
God, all one shot,
notice that, unedited.
We do it like that
and we avoid criticism
that we got with Bennett about
manipulating the footage.
- I don't think I should
have opened up like this.
- What are you talking about?
The site becomes a place
where people invent,
they form alliances,
they congregate,
they expose all the...
- Oh, God, give it a rest.
- What's your fucking problem?
- You sound like a
chapter from your thesis.
I'm just saying,
this whole thing is
a bit out of control, OK?
- OK.
OK.
So, we regain focus at
the press conference.
I sent out the releases.
It's happening.
You're still going
tonight, right?
- Me?
- Yeah, I told you that I
wanted to be there this time.
I wrote up some questions.
- No, there is no we tonight.
- Why, I am involved.
You know, if you get
caught at this point,
we're both fucked.
I'm backing you on this
shit and you're gonna
keep me out of the most
crucial fucking part?
Are you listening to me?
Fuck.
I can just do it myself
and submit my own material.
OK.
OK, well, are you at least
gonna write the statement?
- It's a bad idea.
- What?
- This press conference.
This shit is just
not necessary, man.
- God, yes it is.
We need the press
conference because we need
to regain focus.
We need to work
it into our terms.
Listen.
Every successful activist
revolutionary group.
The IRA, the Panthers, the
Satisas, the Earth Liberation
Group, they're all alone.
They all have a public face.
A spokesperson.
Are you hearing me?
- Yeah.
- OK.
OK.
So, we'll draft something.
But you need to read it
and make sure it's true
to your vision, all right?
(honking)
(tense music)
- OK.
So, we set it up so the host
bounces like I thought...
- No, no, no, look, this is a
simple if not then equation.
If you and your pals don't
figure out how to shut
this fucking thing down,
then you'll find yourself
in lock down for the
next three years,
because we know what the
fuck you've been doing.
- Sir, sir, do you understand...
- So, look, it's a
simple fucking equation.
- No, look, he's smart.
He's set it up so the
service provider bounces.
It changes locations
like every 20 minutes.
And they're foreign
hosts, so unless you take
whole regions, like
whole countries offline,
I don't know how to do it.
- Well, we view
it as a continuum.
This is not unrelated
to hacker theft of
Wall Street assets, cyber
attacks on the Pentagon,
defacement of government
websites, but it's more
malevolent and far
more dangerous.
This is a form of terrorism,
there's no question
about that, a new and
very troubling breed
of terrorism.
- [Voiceover] Any indication
where the website host
is located?
- [Olivia] You've seen
this guy before, right?
- Not really, no that one.
- [Allan] Say on this time
that we will apprehend...
- I read that he's taking
some leadership position
at Homeland Security.
We should go after him.
Like a fucking coo, right?
- That was Allan Keller,
lead prosecutor from
the attorney general's
office, here in New York.
- Seriously.
You take it to the
next level with him.
It's going there.
It's got to go there.
- No, it doesn't
have to do shit.
- You think that no
one's gonna get hurt?
That violence doesn't enter
the game plan at some point?
- No.
We make the decisions.
And we don't have to follow
any model, precedent,
or whatever the hell else
you want to call it, OK?
Shit ain't predetermined.
- Where are you going?
(tense music)
- Oh, God.
- OK, OK, OK, Mom, stop,
stop, you can't make a scene.
OK?
- I understand.
- I'm fine, really.
- You sure?
- Yeah, really.
- You know they're on to you.
You know that, right, the FBI?
- Yes, yes.
- Came to the house, Terrell.
They took all your stuff.
They held me overnight.
- I'm sorry.
- It's just a question of
time, that's the situation.
Not if, Terrell, when.
- What did you tell them?
- I already lost your
father, I'm not going to lose
you, too, OK?
- I got to get out of here.
- No, no, you listen to me.
- What?
- After your father
died, I swore I would do
everything I could to
give you what you needed
to survive, the skills to
get ahead in this life.
- I don't have time to
listen to this right now.
- Terrell, and you have
them, you have them
and you are wasting them.
What are you even doing?
You've never been
a political person.
- What I'm doing
is having impact.
I'm exposing these assholes
for who they really are.
The media's all
over this story now.
- The media.
Terrell, it's a freak show.
An abduction, a batting,
anything to fill the pages,
the airwaves.
- OK, what about the
articles I sent you?
Your boss, your boss resigned
because of what I did.
- He had two months
before retirement.
They gave him a full
benefits package.
Somebody even told me
that he bought a big house
down in Florida.
His wife didn't even leave him.
You can work out a deal.
That's what the agents
I talked to said.
- I just came to see if
you're OK, all right?
You can take this.
- No, no, no, I don't want that.
I want to know that
you're not gonna end up
in jail or dead.
Do you even hear
a word I'm saying?
Sweet boy.
- I got to go.
(crying)
- I'm waiting on
something, Senator.
- I guess it's
like I said before.
- You didn't say
anything before,
you were evasive before.
- Well, ultimately, if
a constituency does not
support foreign aid or
peacekeeping efforts,
then I, as a US senator,
really don't have...
- Yeah, assuming they're
getting the facts.
Is that what you're saying?
Your constituency, is
that what they're getting?
- People want the facts bad
enough, they can get 'em.
In the United States of
America, they can get 'em.
Could we at least
cover my privates?
Could we do that at least?
- [Terrell] Why don't we try
answering the question first,
Senator?
- [Senator] Christ.
Now, of course, if you
got yourself killed, say,
if you got martyred, well
that would be the best.
That's better than even
going to jail because then
some little elementary school
in the ghetto somewhere
will get named after you.
(grunting)
- Son of a bitch.
- [Voiceover] Maybe
I picked up a virus.
The only way to really
shake things up is to have
the establishment come
face to face with the
barrel of a gun.
Because technology's easy.
It has rules.
Discernible patterns.
'Cause once you get people
impassioned is where
shits starts to blur.
- I mean, if they're starving
in them other places,
let 'em starve.
If they hump monkeys in
the jungles of Africa
to get AIDs, then that's
their cross to bear.
Look, could we cover
up my goddamn genitals?
(chatter)
- I'm going to read
my statement now.
Thank you.
So here we go.
The confess project is
about giving a voice to
truths that are rarely heard.
It's about learning the
behind the scenes reality
from those who own the
means of production,
manipulate the flow
of information,
those who possess the
power to indiscriminately
alter the course of our lives.
(beeping)
- I worked for the UN
for eight years and now
I work for the World
Trade Organization.
- [Voiceover] Into the camera.
- OK, OK, just please, OK.
I work as a chief
intermediary between
governments and
multinational firms.
- [Voiceover] Tell
me about the money.
- WTO believes that
democracy functions best,
actually flourishes...
- [Voiceover] What?
- Flourishes in an
open market environment
and that capitalism...
(gunshot)
(sirens blaring)
(intense music)
- In keeping the
radical social justice
movements of the past,
because it's high time
to harness the frustration
out there and put
principle and
theory into action.
Thank you.
- Miss Alvero.
(beeping)
(tense music)
- What?
- Hurry up, let me in.
Hey.
(beeping)
Greg.
- There was quite a turnout
at your press conference.
- You know who my
father is, right?
- OK.
All right, I'll see.
Olivia, I'm Miss Bradford,
one of your father's
attorneys, we met at
the trust disbursement.
He asked that I meet you here.
(tense music)
- Shit.
(applause)
(melancholy music)
(tense music)
OK.
I'm...
I'm talking now because
shit's happening that has
nothing to do with me.
I'm being blamed for
actions that I'm not even
involved with.
Here's the deal.
If charges are dropped against
me, if I'm granted immunity,
then I will stop the abductions.
So, what's in it for you?
- Conditional immunity
based upon my client's
success in hacking other
sites deemed a dangerous,
indefinite assistance
in targeting suspected
activists, terrorists,
et cetera, and some
as yet unspecified
public service type work.
- A minimum of 1,000,000
for the film rights,
plus a piece of the back
end profits, that's minimum.
That doesn't include tie-ins,
music, merchandising.
- In branding our clients,
it's all about figuring out
who they really are.
Who you really are.
- You have a very fortunate
case in that you've done
a lot of the branding already.
- Exactly, I mean, all
that's left for us to do
is to help you shape
your more mature persona.
How's all of this sound, huh?
Do you have any questions?
- You got a pen?
Thanks.
(ethereal music)
(chatter)
- Go to your house
without saying anything.
Step back, come on, give
him room, give him room,
step back, everybody, step back.
Step back, everybody, come on.
(chatter)
Step back.
Ladies and gentlemen,
ladies and gentlemen,
Mr. Lessor will have a
statement for you very shortly,
in about five or 10 minutes,
please bare with us.
- So, we just worked out a deal.
(chatter)
(hip hop music)
I've always been
deeply concerned with
social justice issues.
It's just at a certain
point, I realized that
the potential for violence
and harm was just too great.
- In our ongoing
reporting on Mr. Lessor,
we recently unearthed
exclusive home video footage
of more innocent times,
which we'd like to share
with you now.
- Terrell Lessor today
signed on as spokesperson for
proactive floating line
campaign in a deal rumored
to be in excess of $2,000,000.
- We all feel frustrated,
you know, sometimes, right?
Powerless.
- [Voiceover] This, in addition
to the book and movie deal
already negotiated...
- Oh, yeah, man, definitely
was trying to make a statement.
I wanted to make people
question, I wanted to make
people think differently
about things.
- His managers indicate
that one of his first
expenditures was paying
off his mother's mortgage
and for a complete
redesign of her home.
- Well, now I'm just really
just trying to keep it real.
I'm trying to speak out
against the people who
took what I was doing
the wrong way and took it
to an extreme.
(club music)
- Hey, you're that guy, right?
- No, probably not.
- Yeah, you are,
the confess project.
I just wanted to say I
really respected what you
were doing, you totally had
something important to say.
- Yeah, thank you.
- Oh, hey, wait.
Can I get an autograph?
I think I still
have it, yeah, here.
(hip hop music, sirens blaring)
- I do not live the life of a
happy fucking celebrity, OK?
It was my choice.
10 years minimum with
no computer, nothing?
What I was trying to do,
which was turn this into
something else,
something positive.
You played me.
- Investigators have yet to
issue a statement as to what
exactly happened several
nights ago, outside this
Brooklyn motel.
Apparently, the locale
where celebrity and
counter culture icon
Terrell Lessor was staying.
At present, investigators
are indicating Mr. Lessor
may, himself, have been
abducted, but are unwilling
to disclose whether
they have any leads.
- I am not living the life of
a happy fucking celebrity, OK?
10 years.
It was just at a certain
point, I realized the potential
for violence and
harm was too great.
I was your classic latchkey kid.
If you can flip, flip.
You're the fucking man,
the geek turned celebrity.
(tense music)
OK, so what do you want to know?
Platform, yeah.
I can, it was my choice.
10 years minimum
with no computer?
Nothing?
What I was trying to do, was
turn this into something else,
something positive.
Yeah, I've always
been interested in
- [Voiceover] If you got
yourself killed, say,
if you got yourself martyred...
- I've talked, I've
talked about...
Consider truth.
Happy fucking
celebrity high life.
- [Voiceover] This
is a story right now.
- I'm just trying to keep
it real, keep it real.
The only way to get to the
truth is to, is to force
the establishment to
come face to face with
the barrel of gun, the
barrel of, the barrel of...
(gunshot)
(upbeat music)