( metal rasping )
( footsteps )
( dance music playing )
Let's go.
Come on.
( moaning )
Oh, my God. Oh.
Oh, yeah.
( laughs, screams )
( grunting, coughing )
( gasps )
( sighs )
Did I tell you about this babe Lucinda,
does the lunch shift with me?
No.
Oh man, she is something else.
I tell you, Costello, the minute I saw her,
I knew I had to bag her.
Look, Nick,
we're here to get a liberal arts education.
That means absorbing the collective wisdom
of centuries of Western civilization.
There's a lot more to life than
just bagging babes, you know?
Yeah, anyway, like I was saying,
yesterday I came close... I mean real close.
But unfortunately close
doesn't count in this league,
so that's why I was wondering if,
you know, you'd help me out.
Forget it.
Come on, Costello.
No. N-O means no. I'm sorry.
This is hers, okay?
She uses it to wipe tables.
It'll take 30 seconds of your time.
- ( TV playing )
- Come on, Costello, what do you say?
The body was found this morning.
The city coroner reports
that the murder took place...
- Are you even listening to me?
- Shh, I wanna hear this.
...and it was preceded by sexual assault.
In response to a News 12 reporter's question,
police spokesman Lieutenant Adam Markowitz
has denied that this is in any way related
to the recent killings which
have plagued the West Side.
Police have positively identified the body
as 20-year-old Suzanne Smyth.
And now to the nation's capital.
The Senate Appropriations Committee will be...
( imitates radio static )
Earth to Costello, come in.
- Do you read me?
- Shit, I'm gonna be late.
( sighs )
( thunder rumbles )
( horn honking )
So for those of you who didn't get one,
you can pick up a list of term
paper topics in my office.
( class laughs )
Are you all right, Mister...
Costello. Yeah, thanks. I'm fine.
Term papers in your office. I heard.
So as promised,
- we have a distinguished guest lecturer today.
- ( pen clatters )
He's a research fellow here on campus
and a leading authority in the field
of abnormal psychology.
His latest book is Rage and Redemption.
You can pick this up at the campus bookstore.
I'm speaking, of course, of Dr. Theodore Steering.
( applause, cheering )
Thank you.
The other day I came across
a widely-accepted definition of
"psychosis" as being, and I quote,
"a mental disorder affecting
the entire personality
with certain characteristics
common to all psychotic conditions,
namely the inability to perform daily activities,
delusion, stupor and/or incoherence
and ultimately,
in worst-case scenarios,
self-destructive behavior."
Well, what struck me about this definition
is that it applies to most of the
students and faculty that I know.
( laughter )
Uh, excuse me, Miss Young?
- Mr. Costello.
- That's right. Patrick Costello.
And your first name's Laurel, isn't it?
Can I help you with something, Mr. Costello?
Well, actually I just had a couple
of questions I wanted to ask you.
- About your term paper?
- Not exactly.
- As a matter of fact, not at all.
- About your lecture notes?
Those are some very comprehensive lecture notes.
Well, I used to be an art major.
Is that what you wanted to ask me about... art?
No. Actually I wanted to know if
you wanted to grab some lunch.
- Uh, I don't think so.
- How about dinner then?
- Say 8:00-ish.
- I'm afraid that's impossible.
Why? Are you married? I mean we're both creative.
I'm sure we can come up
with some kind of solution.
You may not be aware, Mr. Costello,
but the University has very strict guidelines
governing the social relations
between faculty and students.
Oh no, I'm aware, all right.
You're probably wondering, since I am aware
of these antiquated and mostly likely
unconstitutional guidelines and rules,
you're probably wondering why I persist.
I mean, what's the point really?
I'm sorry, Mr. Costello, but I meant what I said.
They may be antiquated. They may be outmoded,
- but I play by the rules.
- Wait a second.
You're really serious, right?
You're not just pulling my leg?
I mean you really mean this?
I'm really serious about a lot of
things, Mr. Costello.
( police radio chatter )
( sirens blaring in distance )
Right over there.
( indistinct chatter )
( camera clicking )
Hmm.
- ( phone ringing )
- Adam: Looks like he's killing them with a belt
and the buckle leaves an impression on the neck.
Yeah, no kidding.
It's... it's a bug.
That's a weird-looking bug.
Sure is.
White Oldsmobile.
( sighs )
Gray Mazda.
Pontiac. Shit.
- Well, it was gray anyway.
- ( imitating car engine )
Whew hoo, boy.
Drinking beers and guessing cars.
Man, you know how to live.
( laughs ) So what did the
teaching assistant have to say?
University guidelines don’t
allow faculty to date students.
Oh, you know,
I've heard some turn-downs in my time,
and in fact I consider myself
somewhat of an expert on the subject,
but I've never heard one that stupid.
Wait.
Dusty blue Van.
Not bad. How are you doing so far?
I'm getting about three-quarters right.
The boy's on a roll. When you're hot, you're hot.
So what are you gonna do?
What do you mean, what am I gonna do?
Well, a guy with your, uh,
extracurricular abilities
isn't exactly helpless in these matters.
Mm, no.
No, this girl's different, you know.
Yeah, well, so are you.
I mean you can read her freakin' mind.
( burps loudly )
You know, have I ever told you that you are one...
hopelessly pathetic,
immature excuse for a human being?
( burps )
Yep.
( imitates engine, crash )
( metal rasping )
- ( woman screams )
- Stop it! Stop it!
Come on, wake up, Costello!
( panting )
- Jesus.
- What am I doing out here?
Hey, beats me.
I'm lying in bed. I hear this yelling.
I thought someone’s being killed out here.
I come in. You're standing
in the corner screaming.
I was standing up?
- How did I get out here?
- I guess you walked.
In my sleep?
Must have been a hell of a dream.
( exhales )
Yeah, it was.
Yeah well, look, I'd...
I'd love to hear all about it,
but it's the middle of the
night and I'm kind of bagged.
So if you don't mind,
let me hear about it in the morning, okay?
( honking horn )
Hello?
( flute sonata playing )
Mr. Costello.
Oh, I... I'm sorry.
The door was open, so I just...
Is there something I can do for you today?
Yeah, I just have a drop form I need you to sign.
- A drop form?
- Yeah.
- Don't you like the class?
- I like the class a lot.
Well then, I don't understand.
Could you just sign the form, please?
There, now I'm officially out of your class,
which means that I'm no longer your student
and you're no longer my teacher, so...
I don't believe this.
You dropped my class just so you can take me out?
Well, I know this is going to sound
a little old-fashioned, Miss Young,
but I guess I’m the kind of guy
who likes to play by the rules.
And what makes you think
that I want to go out with you?
I like Dostoevsky. I like Bach.
And I'm completely addicted to Chinese food.
- ( plate shatters )
- ( whistling, cheering )
- Hey, Nick, listen, you gotta help me out.
- Yeah? What?
Well, you see, I need to borrow your car.
I also need some money, yeah, say around 40 bucks.
You think you can help me out?
I got a date with Laurel.
( laughs ) You sneaky son of a bitch.
Come on, man, can you help me out?
This is serious.
So you get my car and my money,
- and what do I get?
- I don't know.
I'll make it up to you later.
Yeah well, I'll make it really easy for you.
Come here, Costello.
Check that out. That's Lucinda.
- She is quite something, eh?
- Yeah, she's not bad.
- What's this?
- That's hers.
You are such an unscrupulous sack of
shit, you know that?
Yeah, I know.
Okay, she likes green or maybe blue.
- That's her favorite color.
- Blue.
- Um, she loves the Beatles.
- Mm-hmm.
She has a kid sister named Stacy.
- Her favorite movie was The Lost Boys.
- The Lost Boys?
Yeah, she thinks vampires are very sexy.
- You got all that?
- Yeah.
- All right, there you go.
- Thank you.
40 bucks. There you go.
- I love you like a brother.
- I know.
Oh, one thing...
She kind of thinks you’re a bit of a geek.
Good luck.
( chuckles )
Lucinda.
( bottles clink )
- Can I help you?
- It's no problem.
It's a delivery for Miss Young, 1406.
- Go ahead.
- Thanks.
( elevator dings )
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry?
I asked you a question. What are you doing here?
- Well, what's it to you?
- I happen to live here.
This is a security building. How did you get in?
Well, I'm visiting a friend.
- Who?
- Laurel Young.
- Are you a student of hers?
- I was.
You're on the wrong floor.
- I know that.
- Mm.
Well, have a nice evening.
Thanks.
( knocking )
- Hi.
- Wow, you look great.
- Oh, thanks.
- You look pretty good yourself.
- Thanks.
- So, um, I'm starving.
- Yeah, me too.
I know this great Chinese restaurant.
Well, actually...
Here, let me help you with this.
Actually I kind of had something else in mind.
I... I think you're going to like it though.
Oh, okay.
It's really a beautiful place you got here.
Oh thanks. It was my grandmother's.
She left it to me.
I couldn't afford this on my own.
- Wait.
- What are you doing?
I'm gonna take you someplace
you’ve never been before.
Uh, thanks.
Oh my.
This is an unpretentious and intimate little place
that I like to call cafe Ming Costello.
- ( laughs )
- Would you like to sit down?
Oh yes, please. Thank you.
This is lovely.
It's a bit cold, but it's very picturesque.
- A little mood music for us.
- ( flute sonata playing )
Actually the owner is a friend of mine.
This place is usually jammed,
but I slipped him a Franklin
and the place is ours.
It certainly is.
Oh, I hope you like Szechuan food.
I took the liberty of buying everything.
- I love Szechuan.
- ( siren blaring )
- For you.
- Thank you.
So tell me, Mr. Costello,
what made you want to go out with me so badly
that you dropped my class?
Well, I think it was the combination
of your fabulous teaching technique,
your leadership, insightful criticism,
sparkling smile,
- incredible legs...
- Please.
( helicopter whirring )
( laughing )
- Oh, let me take this from you.
- Oh thanks.
So can I see you tomorrow night?
Patrick, I like you. I really do.
I sense a "but" coming.
Well, I've been seeing someone.
You've been seeing someone?
Or you've sort of been seeing someone,
or you're unbelievably,
incredibly involved with someone, what?
I don't know. It's new.
I mean he's older. He's mature.
He's very stable.
- Incredibly boring?
- Definitely not boring.
So, um, I get the picture.
I guess tomorrow night’s out then.
I didn't say that.
No, you didn't.
Can we talk about it tomorrow?
I don't see why not.
Good night.
- I'll call you tomorrow.
- Okay.
woman: Get your hands off me!
No! Help me!
Hold up your gun, Frank.
Bill, help me!
( snoring )
Pfft.
( metal rasping )
Don't you know it’s impolite to stare?
Don't you know it's impolite to stare?
Hmm.
( screams )
Somebody please! Help me!
( choking, coughing )
( banging on door )
( gasps )
Nick: Yeah, yeah, I'm coming.
I'm coming. Jesus.
- Costello.
- ( banging )
What? yeah, just a minute.
Costello, I thought you were in bed, man.
Aw, Jesus.
Come on, man, wake up.
( panting )
- Nick, what's going on?
- "What's going on"?
Are you serious?
You're sleepwalking again, for Christ's sake.
You're even dressing for it.
- You're dangerous, man.
- I'm sorry, man.
Yeah well, do me a favor
and do yourself a favor...
Go see someone.
Get a prescription.
( honks )
- Patrick.
- Hi, Laurel.
Can I speak to you for a sec?
Um, this isn’t a good time.
It's kind of important.
Well, actually, Patrick,
I'm in the middle of a meeting.
- That's okay. I'll just take a second.
- No, it's not okay.
I'm busy. There's someone here.
Okay, okay.
I'll just tell you out here then.
Uh, it's kind of hard to explain,
but there's this man
and he lives in this building.
And I just get a really weird feeling about him.
- I think you should stay away from him.
- What man?
- Professor Steering.
- What?
Laurel, is that for me?
No, Ted, it's for me.
If you don't mind, this'll just take a minute.
What the hell’s going on here, Patrick?
So that's Ted, huh?
That's the guy you’ve been seeing?
Yes, that's right.
Now if you don't mind...
- Laurel.
- What?
Forget it.
( phones ringing, chatter )
I need some information on the homicide case
of the guy who’s strangling women.
Do you know who’s handling that?
Excuse me, are you Detective Markowitz?
Yeah yeah, can I do something for you?
- Hi, I'm Patrick Costello.
- Uh-huh.
- I have some information for you.
- That's great.
- Look, just sit down right over here, okay?
- Okay, thanks.
So what kind of information?
It's about this case that you guys are
working on... the guy who kills women.
What kind of information, Mr. Costello?
I think I saw the killer.
How do you know he’s the killer?
He was in a car and he was strangling a woman.
- Where was the car?
- I'm not exactly sure.
- I think on the waterfront maybe.
- Where on the Waterfront?
I just told you I’m not exactly sure.
You're telling me you saw
some guy killing some lady
and you don't know where it was?
I can give you a description of the man.
How come you don't know where it was?
Well, how is it you don't know where it was?
( sighs )
- I'm a psychic.
- A psychic?
Got some clippings here,
articles that were written about me.
Oh yeah, Patrick Costello.
Oh, Child Psychic, yes.
This is fascinating.
Maybe you can give us a practical demonstration.
What am I thinking?
Well, it doesn't exactly work that way.
Come on, Costello,
you gotta give us something to go on.
How does it work, Costello?
Well, you see, I see things.
Sometimes it happens when I touch something,
other times... I don't know, it just happens.
You know, it just comes to me.
All right, look, here's my lighter.
Now you tell me what kind of car I drive.
A red Camaro?
Look, you're just wasting my time, kid.
Hey, come on, he was half right. It is red.
Look, it doesn’t always happen
when I want it to, okay?
It's kind of hard to do it under pressure.
Well, thanks very much for dropping
by, Mr. Costello.
And you... you stay in touch, okay?
Look, I'm not some kind of crackpot, okay?
I saw this guy.
I also saw the victim. I can describe her to you.
She was in her early 20s.
She had long, wavy reddish hair.
She was Caucasian.
She also... she had this tattoo.
It was like roses on her chest and...
none of the victims had a tattoo.
Maybe he just killed her.
Maybe you guys haven’t found the body yet.
Maybe you'd just better get out of here
before I throw you out, okay?
I think you hurt his feelings.
Aw, poor baby.
Yo, Costello.
Listen, I'm curious about something.
This crime scene that you think you saw,
is there anything about it? Anything that might...
help you identify it?
Listen, I've been over it so many times.
I've told you everything.
Any buildings?
- Actually, yeah, I think so.
- Any distinctive features?
I'm sorry, I just can't remember.
Okay, all right.
Well listen, if you do, give me a holler, huh?
- Yeah sure.
- All right.
I'm telling you, Nick, I know what I saw.
Yeah okay, but how do you know it's for real?
I mean you were dreaming, for Christ's sake.
Look, this guy Steering, eh?
He's the guy she’s going out with, right?
- Yeah, so?
- So it's natural. You're bummed.
You can't stand the guy,
so you start dreaming that he's a killer.
No, you see, the night I dreamed about Steering...
that was before I met him at Laurel's apartment.
Yeah, but you said you saw him
- in the building once before.
- Yeah, so? But...
Look, Nick, I'm telling you I know he's the guy.
- He's the one.
- Come on, admit it. You don't like the guy.
But murder? Jesus.
- Have you seen a doctor yet?
- A doctor?
Yeah, a doctor, about that sleepwalking problem.
No. Don't worry, I will.
Yeah. Come on.
It's very nice of you, but I don't do it.
- I'm closed.
- Sorry.
( needle buzzing )
Hi, is there somebody who could... Thanks.
Hello?
Greetings.
Hi, I was wondering,
have you given this tattoo to anyone
like a young lady, say, in the last six months?
A tattoo cannot be given. It is transferred.
I'm only the medium.
Of course, I understand.
Do you think you could help me out though?
I think I knew this woman before...
In a previous life.
Just a minute.
April, April Harris.
I transferred such a tattoo to April Harris
on the Autumn equinox,
a very propitious day.
Perhaps I have a design that you would enjoy.
( baby crying )
- Yeah?
- Hi, is April Harris here?
- No.
- Well... excuse me. Excuse me.
- Do you know where she is?
- No.
Look, I'm sorry to bother you,
but it's really important.
When was the last time you saw her?
I'm not sure. A couple of days anyway.
You see her, you tell her rent's due.
( ringing )
- Hi.
- Hello, Patrick. It's Laurel.
This is Patrick. Nick and I aren't in now.
If you wanna leave a message, you know what to do.
( door opens )
( closes )
( doorknob rattling )
( dog barking )
( thuds )
- ( glass shatters )
- Shit!
( metal rasping )
( screams )
Who the hell are you
and what are you doing in my room?
April Harris?
Yeah, that's right.
Who the hell are you?
What happened to your hair?
- Okay, I'm calling the cops.
- No, no, no, no, wait.
Um... you're okay.
Yeah, of course I’m all right.
- Listen, I'm really... Get your hands off me!
- Woman: April?
- Okay, okay.
April, what's going on?
This guy broke in. I'm calling the cops.
Wait, let me just ask you one question.
Do you ever go ice skating?
Look, now are you gonna leave
or do I have to call the cops?
Okay, I'm going. I'm going right now.
Sorry. big mistake.
April, I'm sorry.
He said he was a friend of yours.
- I thought... Oh.
It's all right.
- This color sucks, doesn't it?
- I like it.
It sucks. I'm changing it.
- To what?
- Red.
Red? April, not again.
I think I'm gonna be a redhead.
- Hi.
Long time no see.
I... I know what you’re thinking.
You're thinking that I acted like an immature,
jealous, possessive,
foolish, childish jerk this morning, right?
- Yeah.
You're probably also thinking
that I've got a lot of nerve
to come back here without apologizing, so...
These are for you.
( ship's horn blaring in distance )
- Hey.
- Where the hell have you been?
- I ran out of gas.
- Yeah, sure.
Over here.
- Same M.O.?
- Yeah, looks like it.
The same belt marks on her neck.
It's the same killer all right.
The only guy who knew about her
tattoo was that kid Costello.
Yeah, well, maybe the guy is for real, huh? Okay.
Maybe the guy really could see something else.
What, in a dream? Get real, Ricky.
He saw something, all right.
He saw something because he did it.
( clock ticking )
( gasps )
( Ted's voice )
What's the matter?
( normal voice )
Are you alright?
Yeah, um, I'm okay.
I've gotta go.
I don't wanna go.
Get outta here. Come on, scram.
- Bye.
( music playing on TV )
♪ Fighting back
♪ I look at you with emotion... ♪
Man: Crack cocaine:
The real story you won't see anywhere else.
Straighten the legs if you can.
We now take you to Grant Park where Julie Richard
is standing by with an update.
- Over to you.
- Thanks, Bill.
We have just learned the
identity of the young woman.
Her name is April Harris.
She was in her third year at the University
and she was majoring in communications.
- Back to you, Bill.
- Thank you, Julie.
We'll take a commercial break
and then we'll be back with...
( dings )
- Hey, I've been looking all over for you.
- Hi.
Look, I was right.
You can't see him anymore. He's dangerous.
- What?
- I just saw on the TV. They found the body.
- What are you talking about?
- April Harris's body...
They found it down by the waterfront.
Wait a minute.
Are you saying someone was
killed and you know who did it?
Yes, your friend Theodore Steering, that's who.
What could possibly make you say that?
What are you talking about? I saw him do it.
- What did you see?
- Listen, Laurel,
there's something I haven't
told you about me, okay?
Ever since I can remember I’ve
been capable of seeing things.
- Do you understand what I'm saying?
- No. What are you saying?
I'm psychic.
Look, remember that time in your office...
You remember when I knew about Dostoevsky and Bach
and Chinese food and all that stuff?
How do you think I knew about that?
- Do you think that was just a lucky guess?
- I don't believe this.
- Are you saying that everything...
- Shh, shh!
...between us...
are you saying that you were
spying on me or something?
- No no, that's not what I'm saying at all.
- Do you know what I think?
I think that you just don't like
the fact that I'm seeing Ted.
- You haven't even heard a word that I've said...
- I've had enough of this!
If you don't like the fact that I'm seeing Ted,
then you can talk to me about it.
Be up front to me about it,
but don’t start making up stories.
- You're not even listening.
- Yes, I'm listening to you.
Fine, you can believe what you
want, but let me tell you one thing:
Ted Steering is a very very sick man,
and I'm telling you he’s killing people.
Well, then stop wasting your time talking to me.
Go out and get him before he kills again.
( classical music playing )
Thank you.
Thanks.
I have to go to New Hampshire
for a seminar this weekend.
Do you want to come with me?
( sighs )
Why don't you tell me what’s bothering you?
Do you remember my friend Patrick
who came over to my apartment the other day?
Yes.
Well, first of all I should tell you
that I've sort of been seeing him.
I knew that.
- Is there a problem?
- No.
But I told him that I had been seeing you too.
And then he tells me he’s been having
these dreams and you're in them.
What kind of dreams?
Dreams about women being
violently murdered by you.
( laughs )
Oh boy.
And what do you make of that?
He's internalizing his anger
and his subconscious is saying that his rival
wants to murder the object of his desire,
perhaps because subconsciously
he'd rather see her dead than with another man.
That's very interesting, Professor.
Then I guess this weekend is out of the question.
- You feel better, don't you?
- Yes.
Ah. It helps to talk about it.
My mother taught me that...
Before I killed her.
( both laughing )
( scraping )
( huffs )
What are you doing here?
( chuckling )
( bell tolling )
- ( hammer clicks )
- Freeze!
Hi.
- I said freeze!
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
That's him.
( thunder rumbling )
- Excuse me, are you Dr. Steering?
- Yes, I am.
I'm afraid there’s been a little
problem in your apartment.
- What kind of a problem?
- There was a break-in.
But don't worry, we got the guy
and it doesn't look like he got anything.
- There he is.
- ( police radio chatter )
( car starts )
You know, I think maybe we
made a mistake with you.
I think maybe we should
have listened to you before.
- Ever seen a belt buckle like this?
- No.
All right, let's start with April Harris.
Tell me everything you know about her.
- I've already told you.
- Well, tell us again.
Maybe there’s something we missed.
She went to school with you, right?
Is that where you met her?
I told you, I've never met her before.
Yeah, but you must have seen
her on the campus before, right?
I don't think so, no.
A good-looking girl like that?
You see a girl like that, you don't forget her.
Look, what is this?
I thought you guys wanted me to help you.
Well, I do. You're helping us.
Just try and answer the questions.
Now when did you first see her?
I told you, in a dream.
Oh, come on, Costello, you saw her before that.
Now why don't you tell me?
- No, Detective, why don't you tell me?
- All right.
You saw her on the campus and
you were attracted to her.
Then one day you... you met her,
and you were gonna give her a ride home.
But you don’t take her home.
You stop someplace and park
because you wanna talk.
She starts freaking. She's gonna call the cops.
You get upset.
You didn't realize how upset
you were getting, did you?
And then it all sort of just happened.
You didn't mean to hurt her, did you?
It was an accident.
It wasn't supposed to happen that way, was it?
You know, Detective,
I really don't know what makes me more sick...
Having to listen to your crap
or having to look at you.
- You slimy little jerk!
- Ricky: Hey, hey, hey!
Come on, come on. Come on now.
Take a pill. Have a coffee, all right?
Come on. Boy, oh boy, oh boy.
- Go have a coffee or something.
- Yeah, yeah.
Ricky: All right, look,
now we're getting all upset here.
Now, Patrick,
you wanna tell me what really happened?
You wanna talk to me now?
Well, that depends. Are you ready to listen?
I'm all ears, kid.
I know who the killer is.
- Oh, you do, do you?
- Yeah.
- Well, why didn't you tell us before?
- Because no one asked me.
So now I'm asking.
His name is Steering...
Professor Theodore Steering.
He's on the faculty at the University.
He teaches Psychology.
Looks like we're gonna have to arrest you, Doc.
Ricky: And this is the same Dr. Steering
whose apartment you just broke into?
That's right. I needed to go
in there and get some evidence,
something that would make you
guys believe me. He's the guy!
I know it. He's the one.
I just... I just can't prove it yet.
Can you tell me what he's being charged with?
- Hold on a second.
- Because if he's not
being charged with anything,
you can't just hold him.
Who the hell are you, kid, his attorney?
I'm sorry, sir, but this kid is yelling...
This report of yours, Doctor,
I read through it again.
It's kind of interesting.
"The killer is most likely a young man,
probably good-looking,
but he feels self-conscious.
Something sets him apart.
Relations with the opposite
sex are problematic for him.
He may be prone to fits of irrational jealousy."
I'd say that description fits
Patrick Costello to a tee.
- Wouldn't you, Doctor?
-  A lot of people could fit that profile, Detective.
The fact is I don't know Mr. Costello that well.
He seems to know you pretty good, Doc.
We have a... we have a mutual friend.
- Ricky: A friend?
- Mm.
There's a young lady I’m rather fond of.
Oh, yeah.
Seems young Costello is rather fond of her too.
Well, Detective, I think if you were to meet her,
you'd understand why.
- Is that all?
- That's all for now,
but we'll keep in touch, okay?
- Thanks, Doc.
- You're welcome.
- ( door opens )
- Ricky: Time to go, champ.
Dr. Steering has decided not to
press charges on the burglary.
Keep in touch, huh? Stay out of trouble.
Take this down to the lab and
see what they can give us.
Yeah, I don't know what the hell for.
He don't have a record.
There ain't gonna be nothing on file.
Maybe they'll find something else.
- You never know.
- No.
Excuse me.
( birds screeching )
( April screams )
woman: And then when I came back in,
she was talking with the same guy.
She was arguing.
And she said that she didn't know him.
She said that he broke in.
Now this guy, would you recognize
him if you saw him again?
Yeah, I just saw him.
He walked out of here 10 minutes ago.
- Where, in the elevator?
- Yeah.
- Hey, Adam, Adam.
- Yeah?
Got a match on Costello’s prints.
They're all over the dead girl's bedroom.
( phone clacks )
( banging on door )
- Yeah, what? Hey!
- Adam: Come on!
Hey, take it easy. What?
Yeah, what... Hey, what the hell are you doing?
- You can't just bust in here...
- This says we can.
- What's that?
- It's a warrant.
- A warrant for what?
- Check his room, in here.
- Costello's apartment.
- You think Costello’s done something?
Let me tell you something, Sonny,
your roomie's not such a great
guy once you get to know him.
Holy shit. What are... What are you looking for?
- Hey, get... Come on, man.
- Listen, your friend into jewelry, huh?
- What?
- Into jewelry, I said.
- You ever seen this before?
- What?
- Huh?
- No. What is it? I've never seen it.
Go sit down and read a magazine, kid.
- Hey, look, it's my place...
- I said sit down!
All right. Jesus.
Hey, what the hell’s going on here?
- Patrick Costello, you're under arrest.
- For what?
- ( thuds )
- Nick: Hey!
- Keep your hands off him.
- I said sit down.
- Okay, fine.
- Adam: Sorry about that.
- For murder.
- What do you mean murder?
Ricky: All right,
you got the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford an
attorney, one will be provided.
You understand these rights?
Adam: Clear out, guys.
Come on, get outta here.
All right, hit the lights.
Number two.
He's the one. Number two.
- Number two. Now you're sure?
- Yeah.
- Okay, thank you very much.
- Thanks a lot.
( door opens )
Mr. Costello?
I'm Randolph Fitzgerald.
I'll be representing you in court.
I gotta be honest with you.
I don't think we have a very good situation here.
I think we should have
a nice frank discussion about it.
I didn't do it.
- Excuse me?
- I just said I didn't do it.
Okay, Mr. Costello, there's a doctor arriving
to do a little psychological evaluation
of your fitness to stand trial.
Mr. Costello, this is Dr....
We've already met. Thank you, Counselor.
Coffee?
Before we go any further, Mr. Costello,
I want you to know that I think you're innocent.
I also understand that you don't
share the same feeling about me.
Detective Spencer told me about your visions.
Sugar?
Now I don't believe in so-called
psychic phenomena per se,
but I do believe that you saw
what you claimed to have seen...
Not in a vision and not in a dream,
but in person.
I believe that you were actually present
when one or more of these incidents happened.
I just want you to think about that.
You must have been there.
But how could I have...
How could I have done something
and have absolutely no recollection of it?
Have you been experiencing
any unusual behavior recently?
What kind of behavior?
Blackouts, dizzy spells, sleepwalking perhaps?
Have you been sleepwalking?
No. No, I haven't.
( knocks )
- Miss Young?
- Yes.
- You're working pretty late.
- Yes?
I'm Detective Spencer... Rick Spencer.
You have a friend...
Patrick Costello. Is that correct?
Yes.
Yeah well, we're conducting an investigation.
I'm wondering if maybe you could give us a hand.
Of course.
It's a murder investigation, Miss Young.
The killer used a belt with
a pretty unusual buckle.
It's a little something like that.
You ever seen that buckle before?
No, I've never seen anything like this.
And you've never seen Patrick
Costello wearing something
even remotely similar to this, huh?
No.
Well, I guess that’s that then.
Listen, if you think of anything,
anything at all, please give me a call.
- Okay.
- Get some sleep.
- Thank you.
- Good night.
Nick: Bail's set at $25,000.
Yeah, so what I’m wondering is...
Are you crazy?
Come on, man, where am I
gonna get that kind of dough?
You're the bail bondsman.
Yeah, yeah, sure, same to you, pal.
Jesus.
( knocking at door )
Jesus. Just a minute.
Hi, can I help you?
- You must be Nick.
- Yeah.
- I'm Laurel. I'm Patrick's friend.
- Uh-huh.
- Can I ask you something about Patrick?
- Yeah sure.
He said that he had some kind of psychic powers.
Is that true?
He must like you a lot.
He doesn't talk about this with anyone.
See, this thing happened when we were kids.
It really messed him up.
This girl we went to school with was murdered.
The cops figured that Patrick could help them out.
So he did his thing, you know?
They gave him some of the stuff
she was wearing at the time
and he told them who the killer was.
Mr. Solomon... Real nice guy.
No one could believe it...
Until they found out that Mr. Solomon
had been having an affair with Audrey...
That's her name.
She was underage.
Solomon kept insisting he was innocent
and he said he wanted to take a lie detector test.
The morning that he was going to take the test
they found him dead.
He hanged himself.
Then about a month later,
they found this other guy,
a transient.
They found things on him that
sort of linked him to the murder.
And then he made a confession, a full confession.
He was confessing to a lot of things though.
Patrick blamed himself, you know, for Mr. Solomon.
But he said he was so sure, you know?
As soon as we graduated, all he wanted to do
was get out of town, you know, where no one knew.
I think you're the first person
he’s told about it actually.
( sighs )
Thanks for telling me, Nick.
Yeah.
( police radio chatter )
- Ricky, you coming or what?
- Huh? No, no.
I'm gonna stick around. I'll see you tomorrow.
Come on. I'm buying.
( laughs )
What, you buying?
Nah, sorry. Rain check.
What is it?
Nothing.
( sighs )
I don't know, Adam.
Don't you think the whole thing's
falling into place a little too damn easy?
Ricky, never ever complain
about anything being too easy.
You hear what I'm saying?
Yeah, I hear what you're saying.
Let me ask you this.
Do you really think this kid
Costello is a serial killer?
( laughs )
Hell no.
But I think he killed April Harris,
and that's good enough.
I'll see you in the morning.
Yeah.
( sighs )
( phone rings )
Homicide, Spencer.
- Woman: Detective Spencer?
- Yeah.
I live across from Slater Park
and I'm calling about the girl
that was found dead there.
Uh-huh. What do you know about her?
Well, I think I saw the guy who left her there,
and I took his license plate number.
Hold on a second, please. Hey, Adam, hold up!
Okay, you wanna give it to me, please?
( chatter )
( keys jingling )
Rise and shine, kid. You're out of here.
- What?
- Yeah, we got the killer.
The guy's name is Francis Crocket.
He's a registered sex offender
and we got an eyewitness that
puts him at the scene of the crime
right about the time April Harris was killed.
Look, just because you
found this guy near the body
doesn't mean he’s the guy who did it.
We've got forensic evidence that places her
in Crocket's car that same evening.
- Oh yeah? What kind of evidence?
- What are you, a cop?
We got a hair sample, for one thing.
And as an added bonus,
we got a complete confession from the guy
not only to the Harris case,
but to three others as well.
Some sick shit, but there it is. You coming?
It turns out he's one of Dr. Steering's patients.
- Hey, Sammy.
- Hey, what's happening?
Huh?
That's one seriously screwed-up human being.
Could have been you, kid. Come on, let's go.
- Hi, I've just come to see Miss Young.
- ( elevator dings )
Sure.
Hello, Patrick.
Detective Markowitz just called
and told me the news.
Yeah, they finally caught the guy.
Yes, so they did.
Well, congratulations.
On your release I mean.
( door closes )
- Laurel.
- In here.
I don't know if I should take this sweater or not.
How cold does it getup in the
mountains at night anyway?
I really wouldn't know. I haven't been there.
Oh, I thought you were Ted.
I heard about what happened.
It must have been hard on you.
Yeah, well, it wasn’t a whole lot of fun actually.
No, not just now. I meant before.
Nick told me about Audrey.
He told you about Audrey?
( sighs )
Did he tell you the whole story?
Well, yes. I...
What I mean is did he tell you her last name?
No, huh?
Her last name was Costello. She was my sister.
Look, just forget it, all right?
It's ancient history.
Patrick, I'm so sorry.
I gotta go. I'll see you around.
Patrick, don't do this.
"Don't do this"? I'm not doing anything.
Look, you're free to do
whatever it is you wanna do.
Just take the sweater. He'll love it.
( door opens, closes )
( dog barks )
God, it's beautiful.
( classical music playing )
Good evening. I'm Dr. Steering.
I'm here for the symposium.
Ah, Dr. Steering,
it's a pleasure to have you here again, sir.
The only cottage we have left now is number 16.
That's about half a mile down the road.
If you'd prefer a double suite,
I'm sure we can arrange it at a similar price.
What do you think?
You wanna trek down the road a half a mile
or you wanna stay here in the lodge?
- It sounds fine. The cottage sounds fine.
- Okay.
All right, so you’ve been preregistered.
All I'll require is your
credit card for an imprint.
- Thank you.
- ( Laurel clears throat )
All right, Doctor.
- Doctor?
- Thank you.
- ( train horn blaring )
- ( sighs )
( screams )
( gasping )
( women choking )
Ted: Far from the madding crowd.
No telephone, no television.
Yuh! No central heating.
- ( laughs )
- Look at this.
Can't wait to get into this.
- Eh, well.
- Oh, it's lovely.
And the living room... Wait till you see this.
Upstairs are the bedrooms.
Nice, huh?
We have our choice of sleeping accommodations.
You like it?
It's great.
( wind howling )
( sighs )
- Are you cold?
- No.
Ted...
I don't know if I'm ready for this.
I understand.
I want to be here with you, but...
Laurel, you don’t have to explain, okay?
Oh boy, let's see what we've got here.
I brought something to warm us up a bit.
Uh-huh.
A 1985 Bordeaux. Does that sound good?
Sounds great.
Hi, yes, this is an emergency.
I'm trying to reach Dr. Theodore Steering.
Yeah.
Uh-huh. Green Peaks?
Uh-huh. How do I get there?
( engine starts )
It has nothing to do with male-female positioning.
I still don't agree.
I think your paper is an apology
for the male point of view.
( chuckling )
That's not what it is at all.
It's a summary of the current research
into the psychopathology of sexual violence.
I'm not... I'm not even sure
that I believe in it myself.
But then why would you encourage
others to believe in it?
I... Laurel, I am not encouraging
anybody to believe anything.
I'm presenting statistics.
Look, Laurel,
psychology is a very cynical business.
And I suggest that if you want
to pursue this any further
that we get another bottle of wine.
I'll get it.
But, Ted, your humor is no defense.
- You all right?
- I'm sorry.
Serves you right for talking about my humor.
( laughs )
So...
Anyway, what I'm trying to say
is the mindset of modern
psychology is male dominant.
It's time fora female
perspective to be acknowledged.
Believe me, there's nothing more interesting to me
than the female perspective.
Talk to me.
Talk to me about female perspective.
I'm all ears.
I think we should clean up.
Dirty dishes are not a defense, Laurel.
Laurel, what are you doing?
I want to hear what you have to say.
I want to hear all about the female perspective.
Stop please!
- Ah!
- ( tires screech )
( horn blares )
( horn blaring )
Tell me about Patrick Costello.
What do you mean?
You like him, don't you?
- ( cork pops )
- Yes.
Are you in love with him?
No.
You're not?
Good.
What are your feelings about me?
- Ted...
- No, wait.
Do you, ahem...
Do you think that you could love me?
( sighs )
You know, this wine has
definitely gotten to my head.
I think I should go to bed.
- ( bottle breaks )
- Stay right here and answer me.
Damn it, answer me!
( glass breaks )
That wasn't nice, Laurel.
Come on.
- Stop, stop, please!
- ( tires screech )
Uh!
We've gotta get out of here.
Get in the car, quick.
( engine sputtering )
Ah!
- No!
- Leave us alone!
Laurel: No!
Patrick!
( screaming )
- Please help me.
- No!
- Please! Please help me.
( grunts )
( gasps )
( screams )
( honking horn )
Patrick!
Ah!
- Patrick!
- What?
You okay?
- Oh yeah, fine.
- Come on, sit over here.
I almost got run over by a snowplow.
Never felt better.
How are you? You okay?
- Ah!
- Oh, sorry.
I gotta tell you something.
I hate Chinese food.
And you know that classical music?
- I hate that too.
- ( laughs )
Please don't make me listen to
that Bach guy anymore, okay?
Okay.