♪ I rise to a color ♪
♪ some shade but another ♪
♪ than yellow, green, or blue ♪
♪ the sounds of ♪
♪ hammers banging ♪
♪ tick tock ♪
♪ the clock is hanging ♪
♪ in the ear of ♪
♪ yesterday's fool ♪
♪ I wait for an hour ♪
♪ just to get in the shower ♪
♪ and wash my face in the sink ♪
♪ outside it's winter weather ♪
♪ the calendar knows better ♪
♪ somehow it's a summer's day ♪
♪ the chill has me freezing ♪
♪ thermometer's been easing ♪
♪ to a hundred below ♪
♪ in the shade ♪
♪ as rain fills the sky ♪
♪ don't ask me why ♪
♪ it could snow in a moment ♪
♪ I think ♪
♪ but it's a fabulous day ♪
♪ fabulous ♪
okay, people.
Let's remember what aristotle
said.
The aim of art is to represent
not the outward appearance
of things but their inward
significance.
All right, does anybody have
any questions?
Dylan.
Where do babies come from?
What?
Well... I...
uh, right.
You know what?
If there aren't any questions
about art specifically,
then I think that's it
for today.
Yes, dylan, do you have to go
to the bathroom?
No, I want to know
where babies come from.
I know.
I heard you.
But we're almost out of time.
So maybe we'll tackle that
subject next week.
But we still have
two minutes.
Thank you for that, lucy.
But please raise your hand
if you want to contribute to
the class.
We still have two minutes.
Okay, dylan, um...
I think it's best if you ask
your mom and dad about that.
I'll tell you later, dylan.
I know.
Wait, no, no.
I don't think that's a good idea
either.
Well, where do babies
come from?
You'll never believe it when
I tell you.
It's weird.
Whoa, whoa, it's not weird.
It's not weird.
It's, uh... it's natural.
Please don't listen to reggie
about this.
Who should we listen to?
Me, you should listen to me.
I'm an adult.
I know about these things.
Where do babies come from?
I'll draw it for you.
No, reggie, reg...
Okay, dylan, you have a man
and a woman, and...
what if it's two men
or two women?
Thank you again, lucy.
But please, raise your hand.
Okay, so you have a man and
a woman...
here, it's like this.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, sorry.
It's like this.
Please sit down, reggie.
There's a man and a woman
who are husband and wife...
your mother and your father,
okay?
And they have a special bond.
They...
they hug deeply.
And then, nine months later...
they hug for nine months?
No, they're lucky if they
hug for nine minutes.
But the point is,
because of this bond,
much, much later,
a baby arrives.
From a stork?
Yes.
Yes, dylan, from a stork.
Is a stork another name
for a vagina?
I think babies come from...
um...
hmm...
I don't know that.
From...
I think that babies come from
the sky.
From a truck.
I think babies come from
their mother or father's
stomach.
A truck?
That's... that's the silliest
thing I ever heard.
I don't know, but one time,
I saw on the computer
a panda having a baby.
And it just, like, shoots out
like... buucch!
Around 5 feet.
And I think that's how
babies come from.
Yeah, a truck!
I think babies come from
a baby store.
If they want to buy the baby,
then they need to just
pick them up.
But... but do we have some...
But do we...
Did you know that we're out
of soap?
Yeah.
Yeah?
You knew and you didn't say
anything or god forbid, maybe
replace the soap?
I did replace it.
No, you didn't.
Yeah, I did.
Hey, I was just in the
shower, and there was no soap.
Oh, well, that's 'cause
I hid it under the loofah.
Mm-hmm.
You... you hide soap?
You hide soap from me, why?
Payback.
Besides the fact that you never
replace the soap,
you never replace
the toilet paper.
Well, I never finish...
leaving one square
on the roll is finishing it.
No, no, you know what?
By definition, "finishing it"
is finishing it.
And if I finished it,
I'd replace it.
The only reason you never
finish it is because you use
kleenex instead of toilet paper
when it's down to one square.
How'd you know that?
Because I tested you.
The last time there was
one square left on the roll,
it lasted six days.
So that means you either wiped
your butt with kleenex
or you need more fiber
in your diet.
So what did you do for
six days with no toilet paper?
I hid it behind the plunger.
I love you.
You should.
Without me, you'd be walking
around with dingleberries
between your legs.
You're disgusting.
Well, you're lazy.
Well, thank god I'm lazy,
because lazy people are the
most important people
in the world.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, yeah, laziness breeds
efficiency.
It's because of the lazy people
that we have remote control,
automatic transmission, go-gurt.
Go-gurt?
It's all the handiwork
of the lazies.
Hey.
I love you.
Yeah.
Yeah?
I love you too maybe?
Every once in a while would be
nice to hear.
I should go.
Why, you don't want to
spend the night?
No, I want to,
but I don't trust you
to keep your hands to yourself.
I swear I won't touch you.
Yeah, last time
you said that, I got about
15 minutes of sleep.
Well, stay the night and
I can promise you at least 30.
No, oh, tiff, please.
I can't. I can't.
I got deadlines; I can't.
Oh, yuck, deadlines.
You sound like my ex.
I had a great time tonight.
Me too.
But I wish you wouldn't pay
for dinner.
I didn't.
Ned did.
That's the joy of alimony.
Still, if we want this to
work out, you're gonna have to
start treating me like an adult.
I agree.
I understand 100%.
You need help with your laces?
Ha-ha-ha.
So when does jenna get back from
spring break?
Did you just say that
to make me feel old?
No, no, I just want to know
how much longer I have you
to myself before your teenage
daughter comes home.
Mm-hmm.
I will sneak you in
through the bedroom window.
Oh, my god.
Mm-mm, no, no.
No, I got to...
I know what you're doing.
It's not gonna work.
What am I doing?
You're trying to seduce me,
mrs. Milton.
Oh, that's a cheap shot.
Run along, little boy.
Go home.
See you in a couple of days?
Will?
Could you do me a quick favor
before you go?
There's a box in the study.
Could you just close it up
and put it on the top shelf
of the closet?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
And don't look inside.
I love this neighborhood.
When did you move in?
Um, I don't know,
about a month ago.
I like what you've done
with the place.
Thanks.
I'm still unpacking obviously.
Can I, um, offer you something
to drink?
And please say beer.
If you don't say beer,
I can only offer you
some rubbing alcohol
in the bathroom.
I would love a beer.
Great.
So, um, I got to tell you,
I didn't know what to expect.
You know, most of my blind dates
end disastrously.
Well, we still have time.
So what did wendy tell you
about me?
Uh, that you had a great
personality.
Ugh, and you still wanted
to go out with me?
And that you were easy.
I am not easy.
I'm just... i'm highly amenable.
Whatever you do, don't kiss me.
Should we do it now?
No, let's wait.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Am I still waiting?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Okay, this is gonna hurt me
a lot more than it's gonna
hurt you.
Just... let's do this.
Okay.
I'm really afraid I'm not gonna
be very good at this.
I... i'm a little afraid of
that too, but I think
we can do it.
Whoo, oh, god.
Okay?
What do I do?
Do I jam the whole thing in?
Hold it like a pencil.
The tip?
Hold it at a 90-degree angle
to my skin and then you just...
Just do it really quickly
like a dart, like a dart.
Okay, but I don't
throw it in.
I'm... should I just get betsy
to do this at the office?
Because...
no, no, I can do this.
And don't forget.
When you put the...
After you put the needle in,
just pull it out a tiny bit,
check for blood.
If there's no blood,
then put the medicine in, okay?
Okay, but if there's blood,
you know, like I might...
I might pass out.
I know.
Like, for real.
There's not gonna be blood.
Okay, but if there is,
you're gonna have a needle stuck
in your butt, and I'm gonna be
passed out on the ground.
Maybe I should put some pillows
down or something
like a stuntman has.
You know what?
Am I just gonna do this?
I don't want to hurt myself.
Give me the needle.
Oh, no-no, no.
I'm gonna do this.
Let's go.
I'm ready.
I know; You can do this.
On three.
Mm-hmm.
One.
Yeah.
Two.
Okay.
Two and a half.
Brian.
Ow, ow!
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Fucker!
That hurts.
You said like a dart.
Well, not like a frickin'
javelin.
Well, I'm sorry.
What do I do now?
Ugh, pull it out a little
bit, see if there's blood.
Okay.
Oh, that's hurting me.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
No... there's no blood.
Good, then would you push
the medicine in?
Okay, I'm go...
ugh.
Can you be nice to me?
Can...
I have got a needle in my ass
right now!
Okay, okay, here we go.
Ready?
Oh, ow!
Eww, gross.
Okay, it's so gross.
Okay, okay.
The medicine's in.
Okay, great, great.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
I'm waiting.
What do I do now?
Get yourself a ham sandwich.
Pull it out!
Ach.
Oh, there's blood, babe.
Oh, there's blood.
Of course there's blood,
you frickin' stabbed me.
Oh, I don't feel good.
For god's sake.
Are you okay?
Yes!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, babe.
Ahh.
This is not gonna work.
So much blood, babe.
Next time, I'm just doing it
myself.
There was so much blood.
Ugh, you are a champ.
Shh, come on, come on.
Come on, come on.
Uh, honey?
In the bathroom.
Yeah, I think he's hungry.
Maybe you didn't hear me,
sweetie.
I said I'm in the bathroom.
Yeah.
You think you could deal with
our kid for, like, one second?
Yeah, I got him.
I'm just saying...
oh, shh.
Oh, shh.
Hey, hey, hey.
She's gonna be here any minute.
Sammy, come on.
Come on.
Baby?
Ah.
Shh, here she comes.
Come here.
Morning.
Hey, did you take a shower?
Why?
What do you mean, "why?"
You were just all sweaty.
I'm not sweaty anymore.
Well, you... still on you.
You know, we sweat in this
bed more than we sleep in it.
That's sex sweat,
not basketball sweat.
There's a difference?
Yes, did you take a shower?
Did you hear me
take a shower?
Go take a fucking shower,
hon.
Babe, I'm not sweaty.
I'm not sweaty.
Mmm.
You taste sweaty.
What does sweat taste like?
Salt, you taste salty.
Maybe it is salt.
Mmm?
Maybe I salted my whole body
before I came in here.
Ah, did you?
No.
No, you didn't, no.
So why don't you...
mmm.
Go take a shower?
Okay.
Pain in my ass.
I love you.
Thank you.
Fuck you!
You dancing?
Ba-ba-ba-ba.
♪ As we cut off ♪
♪ our legs and heads ♪
♪ people look round ♪
can I take your order?
Hi.
What do you want?
Um, coke, fries, a burger
with everything.
All right.
Will that be all?
Could you give us one second?
Before you order that,
I would like to point out
that when cows are slaughtered,
they are shocked with electric
prods and herded onto
the killing floor.
Then they are hoisted up
by one leg and hung on
a processing line.
Then their necks are slit open,
cutting the jugular vein
as they slowly bleed to death.
Hello, can I take your order?
If... if they happen to somehow
miraculously cheat death,
then the animals are fully
conscious as they reach
the scalding tank, as they moo
for mercy while they're being
boiled alive.
So tell me,
do you want to
change your order?
Definitely changing my order.
Um, could you hold the mayo?
And you?
Sorry about that.
So we'll take a combination
number one, no mayo,
and a caesar salad,
dressing on the side with
a diet coke, thanks.
Chicken caesar?
Hey, baby.
What the fuck?
Get your shit out!
Put the fucking bat down.
Shut up!
Just shut up and get out!
I don't even want to
look at you right now.
That was a $900 tv.
Get out, eric.
Jesus christ, carla,
would you look what you did
to the tv?
That's my bat.
That's my signed yankees bat.
You know what?
I'm not even gonna mention
the fuckin' bat right now!
Get out, eric.
Get out!
Don't talk to me.
Don't look at me.
Just get out.
It's over, good-bye.
♪ Guitar on the floor ♪
♪ and my girl on his lap ♪
♪ so I tapped off ♪
you didn't even ask me why?
Why did I fuck up
the television?
You just said,
that's a $900 tv.
That's all you can say.
Not, "carla, clearly something
is wrong.
Let's talk about this."
No, "that was a $900 tv."
Oh, "you ruined my bat"?
We...
eric, I am sick of it, eric.
I am sick of your selfish...
Me, me, me, me... all the time.
If just once
you thought of me first.
If just once you said
the right thing,
did the right thing for me.
Is that so much to ask?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
wait a minute.
Of course, I am gonna make a big
deal about this.
You just deep to the outfield
with the fuckin' flat screen.
Now, what is wrong?
You.
You are wrong.
Why me?
The money.
You took my money.
No, no, no, no.
Our money... it is our bank
account.
Who put that money into
our bank account?
That's not the point.
Eric, I had been saving
that money for two years.
What was it?
Basketball?
Football?
Fucking ice skating?
Look, I will get it back.
Great.
You can mail me that money
from your new address.
I'll get it back.
I promise.
I am not betting on you
anymore, eric.
♪ I killed robert johnson ♪
♪ with strychnine ♪
♪ rode down, rode down ♪
♪ rode down ♪
what is this?
Uh, a video camera.
Vhs.
You know what vhs is?
Yes, I once heard
my forefathers speak of such
a device.
Question is, what are you doing
with it?
I found it in the attic.
I was just, you know,
reminiscing, looking at some
old video.
Video?
What kind of video?
Personal video.
A sex tape?
I thought you had to get
to work.
Answer the question.
Yes, will, I was looking at
old sex tapes.
Tapes?
Well, how many have you... made?
A few...
dozen.
What?
Oh, come on, it's not
a competition.
Like, you've never made
a sex tape.
Yeah, you know, I sexted
a girl in high school once.
Sexted?
Yeah, I texted her a picture
of my dick, and she sent me
a picture of her boobs.
Wow, that sounds fun.
Oh, that's it.
It's on.
What?
What is on?
Oh, we're gonna make
a sex tape.
And it's gonna be so hot
that the next time somebody asks
you how many sex tapes you've
made, you're only gonna be able
to think of one.
Oh, making babies is hard.
How often do we have to do this?
Three times a week.
Ooh, no, no, actually
that's not good.
Oh, I know.
That's what I'm thinking.
I think you're gonna have to
find a different life partner.
I know.
I think you might be right.
Oh.
Well, you'll be happy to know
now we get to do the fun part.
You're gonna watch me
play video games?
No, I'm ovulating.
We're gonna have sex.
Oh, no.
What?
Oh, shit.
I did it a little while ago
with myself in the bathroom.
Babe!
You masturbated?
I had to.
You cannot masturbate while
we are trying to get pregnant.
Why not?
I didn't know.
I'm ovulating!
I only have, like, 12 hours!
This is it.
Well, I forgot... 12 hours.
I don't care.
You know what?
Take your frickin' clothes off.
We're fucking.
I have to take a rain check.
Nope.
Respectfully, I have to take
a rain check.
You cannot take a rain check.
Take your clothes off.
You are fucking me right now.
Honey?
Ah, yeah?
You feel me wet inside you?
Yeah, yeah, oh, baby.
It's so wet on top of you.
Yeah.
So wet inside you.
God, yeah.
So what's the fuckin'
big deal?
Why do I got to take a shower?
Oh, my god.
You... you have ten seconds
to drop this shit and move on.
Or what?
Or you'll be finishing
yourself off with your hand
on the couch.
I'm just saying.
I just want to fuckin' know.
Look, you're sweatier than I
ever was at my sweatiest, baby,
and we're in bed.
So I just want to know:
Why do I got to take a shower?
Ten, nine, eight...
you know what?
You go count all you want.
Seven.
I'll go finish myself off
on the couch.
I have more fun without you.
Five?
Yeah.
Four.
Three.
Come on, gina, don't be
a bitch.
One.
Forget it.
Oh, you fucking suck.
You know that?
I know.
What's the deal?
What deal?
The sticky note?
Sweetie, on the mirror.
I 'heart' you?
Seriously?
Mm-hmm, 'cause I do.
Hmm.
What?
I... it's a sweet nothing.
A sweet nothing?
Mark, come on.
What?
Honey, never once in 11 years
have you left me
a sweet nothing.
I can't believe this.
You're angry at me because
I left you a love note.
No, no, no, I'm not angry.
I'm suspicious.
Well, I'll think of that
the next time I feel like doing
something nice.
Oh, okay.
So what'd you do?
What do you want?
You're crazy.
No, I'm not crazy.
You... one of two things is going
on here: Either you did
something, something stupid,
and that's a preemptive move
to make sure that I don't
get mad later;
Or you want something.
You're deranged.
Really, I am?
Okay, what'd you do?
What do you want?
I didn't do anything.
I don't want anything.
You're paranoid.
I better be.
You are.
Okay.
I'm concerned.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Honey?
Thank you for the nice...
sticky note.
You're welcome.
I just want to know that
you're okay with it being me.
Sweetie, we discussed this.
It's better if it's you.
I know, but I just feel like
I forced you into the decision.
Okay, so how is that
different from every other
decision we ever make
as a couple?
I just don't...
sweetie, it's good.
This feels right.
Besides, if I have a baby,
I'm gonna die.
Have you seen my hips?
What are you saying about
my hips?
I love your hips.
I know, but if you just want
to discuss it, then we can talk
about it right now.
I'm happy, nik, really.
I know, but I just don't
want you to resent me.
I like it this way.
Okay, uh,
let me just look at it:
Vomiting, bloating, nausea,
no alcohol, cankles,
flintstone feet, hemorrhoids,
insomnia, stretch marks,
memory loss, back aches,
pelvic pain, postpartum
bleeding, postpartum depression,
nipple blisters,
having to wear a support bra
for the next two years.
You know what?
I think I'm all set.
You're really not gonna get
any resentment from me.
Thank you, baby.
It's so sweet.
Thank you.
You're gonna be amazing.
What if that stuff happens
to me, though?
What are you worried about?
Half those things happen
to you already.
I do not get nipple blisters.
Okay, so we'll bottle-feed.
Oh, no, no, no.
Health... health-wise, it's better
to just, you know, from
the breast.
Good for the immune system.
Good for bonding.
Baby, it's gonna be fine.
You're gonna be fine.
The baby's gonna be fine.
Should we?
No, no, no, I'm not ready.
Not yet.
Okay, okay.
It's amazing, huh?
What, that he's actually
quiet?
No, that he's six weeks old,
today, exactly six weeks
old today.
Fuck you, mark.
I am not having sex with you.
What?
That's what this was about?
The sticky note?
I 'heart' you.
Because you want to have sex
tonight?
I mean, I've been thinking.
Uh-huh.
But the two things aren't
anything to do with one another.
Sex and the note...
They're mutually exclusive.
You are so full of shit.
Could you not in front of
the baby?
What do you think he's thinking
right now?
I think he's thinking that
his dad's a selfish douche bag.
Okay, all... all I'm saying
is that the doctor said
wait four to six weeks
for clearance.
Did you see what went on
down there six weeks ago, mark?
Did I ask you at week four?
No.
It was like a grenade
went off.
Did I ask you at week five?
No.
I can't believe you.
God.
Babe, I miss you.
I want to make love to you
again.
Okay, save it, mark.
Seriously, it's not happening,
really.
Okay.
I just want you to know
that I'm ready whenever you are.
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
I will... I will carefully
consider that the next time
that I am feeling
even remotely sexual, okay?
Babe, from now on, no more
jerking off.
All right.
What'd you have for lunch
today?
Hot dogs.
No, you can't do that
anymore.
You got to start eating really,
really well.
You got to have a diet
high in zinc and antioxidants.
We need to up your calcium
intake, your vitamin "d"
intake... all of that
increases testosterone
and sperm count.
Okay, good,
I can eat all that.
And no more drinking.
No more alcohol.
No more caffeine.
No more sodas.
What?
Yes.
Really?
Yeah, seriously.
Sugar is bad.
Herbs, flax seed, all that.
Babe, I love flax seed.
Babe, you don't even know
what flax seed is.
And you're gonna have to
switch to boxers.
What, no.
That's a no-go, babe.
I wear briefs.
I need support.
Nope.
Overheated testicles inhibit
sperm production.
I know you have to say that
at the hospital 'cause you're
a nurse, but at home,
could you call them balls?
No.
Can't you say like,
your hot balls aren't good for
makin' babies?
No, no hot balls.
No hot saunas.
No hot baths.
No biking.
What, babe, I bike to live.
Babe, seriously, I have to wear
briefs because otherwise,
my balls will start sagging.
Have you ever seen my dad's
balls?
Babe, don't talk to
me about your dad's balls.
I have to fuck you right now.
It's only for
a couple of months.
Would you go without a bra
for a couple of months?
If it got me pregnant.
All right, fine.
You don't have to scream at me.
You know, brian, you're
really stressing me out.
And I'm not supposed to be
stressed.
It can get in the way of
the cycle of ovulation.
Well, I'm sorry, I guess
I didn't realize this whole
ovulation thing was happening
right now.
Yeah, in the next couple
days.
Wait, if it's in the next
couple days, what's the hurry?
No, no, no, it's really
good to have intercourse
before you ovulate because it
increases the chances
for pregnancy.
Those little guys can live
up there for, like, four or
five days.
Eww, really?
That's kind of creepy.
What are you waiting for?
Oh, I don't know.
I thought you're gonna help me
get this party started.
No, no, no, no, no.
We got to do missionary
position, babe.
You got to be on top.
It's better for penetration.
Uh, that just sounds lazy
on your part, to be honest.
And, big guy, I got
a news flash for you:
I have to have an orgasm because
the contraction helps get
the sperm up into the cervix.
I'd like to see proof of that
in writing, please.
Babe...
what are you doing?
Shh.
Do not shush me.
I am fantasizing.
Try to pretend that you're not
here.
Babe, I can do that for you
if you want.
We have to be at the
jacobsons in 35 minutes, okay?
I'm gonna have to lie here with
my hips elevated for 20 minutes.
It takes nine minutes
to get over there,
which means we have exactly
six minutes to get this done.
Oh, babe.
Mmm.
All this sexy schedule talk
has got me rock hard.
Let's do this.
Are you really not gonna help?
All right, fine.
Two can play at this game.
Did you fart?
This is really romantic,
by the way.
Super...
shh.
Sexy.
Shh.
♪ Ha-ha-ha-ha ♪
♪ easy baby ♪
hey, you want to, uh...
you want to do it?
Do it?
Yeah, you want to?
You want to do it?
What are you, 12?
What, I can't say, "do it"?
No, not unless you just
took me to the prom.
Okay, you want to, uh...
you want... you want to fuck?
Could you just come up with
a happy medium between
do it and "fuck"?
Well, congratulations.
I'm no longer in the mood.
Okay, let's do it.
Sorry.
Last chance, going once...
you know, maybe when
I learn how to properly...
going twice,
going three times,
four, five, six, really?
Come on, really?
Okay.
Let's do it.
Wow, you really don't seem
like you want to.
I don't... I don't understand.
I don't want to what?
Oh, my god.
We're gonna do this again?
No, I want to know.
I just want to know how you
are supposed to properly ask
your spouse...
have sex.
Do you want to have sex?
Yes.
Can I just finish this chapter
first?
I'm, like, a page and a half.
Sure.
Thanks.
J.t., it really bothers me
that you eat meat.
What do you want from me?
All right, it's meat.
It's a food group.
No, it's not.
Protein is a food group.
Meat is murder.
No, a food group:
Beef, poultry, fish.
Dried beans, eggs, tofu,
nuts.
All protein, all in the same
food group.
Look, all right, I've been
eating meat since I was two.
Okay, I can't just stop now.
What if I gave you
an incentive?
What if I motivated you?
How?
What if I slept with you?
You mean, we... we can have sex.
If you stop eating meat,
yeah.
When?
Tonight.
Okay, are you messing
with me?
Okay, you're messing with me.
No, I'm not messing with you.
I wouldn't be messing about
something like this.
If you stop eating meat,
I'll have sex with you...
tonight after dinner.
Yeah, hey, hey, can you...
Can you change that combo
number one to a caesar salad?
No chicken.
Thank you.
So is that, like, the most
incredible chapter in
the history of the world,
or am I just the most
boring lay ever?
No, no, no, no.
It's just... i'm almost done.
If I stop now, I got to pick it
up all the way...
oh, yeah, no, totally, honey.
I totally get it.
You know, if you'd just let
me finish, I'd be done by now.
If we'd had sex,
you'd probably by now too.
Wow, okay.
Book's down.
Top or bottom?
What, you want to flip for it?
Rock, paper, scissors?
What happened to us?
What, what do you mean,
what happened?
I mean, when did...
having sex become such a chore?
Ch... it's not a chore.
I love having sex with you.
Yeah, well, we're doing it,
honey, but I mean, when did
getting there become one?
This is so sad.
We should just put it on
the chore wheel.
Unload the dishwasher.
Take out the garbage.
Have sex.
That's ridiculous.
Is it?
Yeah, there's nothing I like
more than having sex with you.
Masturbating.
What about it?
When was the last time
we had sex?
I don't know.
Exactly, and when was
the last time you masturbated?
I don't know.
Oh, yeah, you do know
because it was this morning
in the shower.
Oh, no, don't deny it.
No one goes through that much
conditioner in one week.
All right, fine, you got me.
I... I like jerking off.
I don't know what to say.
Okay, well, I... look, honey,
I have no problem with that.
But you just said,
there's nothing I like more
than having sex with you.
And I would argue that you
actually enjoy masturbating more
than having sex with me.
I don't enjoy it more.
It's just...
It's quicker.
It's easier.
It's cleaner.
Because of all the hair products
you use?
Are you gonna start hiding
the conditioner from me now?
Oh, god.
Honey, look, I get it.
I'm not trying to make you
feel bad for jerking off
once in a while.
Well, you are.
I don't know.
I... I think about how we used to
be, you know?
All right.
Well, think about it this way,
think of... think of all the times
we fight and all the times
we argue,
when we were planning our
wedding, when we try and figure
out a trip to see your mom
or who's gonna walk the dogs...
I mean, all the times I'm not
jerking off.
I jerk off for peace.
I jerk off for harmony.
I don't just jerk off for me.
I jerk off for us.
So I'm asking you, please,
I would love to have sex
with my wife.
Not now.
Oh, my god, why?
Well, honey, I'm not
a charity, you know...
charity?
That's just humiliating.
I'm not... there's no char...
There's nothing I like more
than having sex with you.
Except for finishing
chapter nine of
harriet tubman's biography.
Screw her.
Mmm, okay, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
Honey, let's just do it
in the morning, okay?
Tomorrow morning...
When was the last time we had
sex in the morning?
We never have sex
in the morning.
I think kennedy was president.
Well, then there you go.
Sex in the morning.
It's a date.
Okay, we got a date.
Mm-hmm.
Wait, you're not even gonna
finish your chapter?
No, the sooner we go
to sleep, the sooner we wake up,
and then the sooner
we can do it.
Carla, I'm not walking out
that door till you look me
in the eyes and tell me you...
I really want you to leave.
I don't believe you.
Well, maybe you'll believe
me if I call the cops.
You're not gonna
call the cops.
Watch me.
Well, I still don't
believe you.
Hi, this is carla watkins.
I live at 4242 jefferson street,
apartment number "c,"
and I have an intruder.
I'm not an intruder.
Carla, hang up the phone.
He has a knife.
A knife?
Oh, great, a knife.
You might want to leave now
before you get shot.
Well, that is really adult,
carla, nice.
Really, you're gonna teach me
how to be an adult now?
Okay, well, I will sit down
and take notes while you explain
to me how to be an adult.
This isn't about the bank
account.
This is about something else.
Because me being upset about
getting robbed would be so
immature?
Are you seeing someone else?
Is that what this is about?
What?
Seeing somebody else, me?
Yes, that's the question.
No, I'm not seeing somebody
else, you fucking retard.
Well, do you think
I'm cheating on you?
Is that what this is about?
No, you're too unambitious
to cheat.
That would require having
a conversation with somebody.
Carla, I love you.
I would do anything for you.
Great, leave!
Fine, you want me to leave?
Yes.
I'll leave.
I'm fuckin' leaving.
Okay, great, and don't forget
your fucking bat!
Sayonara, bitch.
You know what, eric?
I will get down on my knees and
blow you right now if you can
tell me what language that is.
It's hong kong.
You are a retard.
Fuckin' chinese.
I thought you were leaving.
You can't even do that right.
Fine, okay, you want me
to ask some questions?
I would really like to know
what's wrong.
Besides you stealing
from me.
I didn't steal from you.
What would you call that,
eric?
I had money, and you took it
without asking.
What would you call that?
Relax, okay?
Don't you tell me to relax.
Don't ever tell me to relax.
Do you hear me?
Look, I am sorry.
Don't you fucking touch me.
Don't touch me.
We're not kids anymore, eric.
I was sitting at this stoplight
yesterday.
And I realized everybody was
walking or driving or going
somewhere but me.
I was just sitting still.
Well, that's what you do
at a red light.
We, eric.
We are sitting still.
You know, I don't know
why you hate me so much.
I don't hate you, eric.
That's the problem.
I wish I could fucking hate you.
Oh, don't even.
I am so exhausted.
How could something so tiny
make me so tired?
Do you need me to get you
anything?
Oh, my god.
I am not having sex with you.
I just asked you if you
wanted me to get you anything.
I could hear the subtext.
There was no subtext.
There was subtext.
So anytime I say something
nice, you're just going to
automatically think I have
an ulterior motive?
Honey, I love you, I do,
okay?
But I got to get some sleep.
That is so hot.
What?
The moon.
Oh, my god, mark, come on.
Just stop it, all right?
Leave me alone.
I have been leaving you alone
for six weeks.
Okay, you know what?
I'll jerk you off, hmm?
Let's do that.
It'll be fun.
That's not what this is
about.
It's gonna be fun, come on.
No, no, no, no, no.
You're missing the point.
This is not... i'm not...
This is not...
what, you're not what?
You're not turned on anymore?
What happened?
Is it... oh, it was this,
was what you liked?
No.
That's the thing.
That's what you need to...
That's good?
No.
No?
Wait, it's... yeah, actually,
that's hot.
Okay, good.
So what do you think?
A little journey?
A little night ranger?
Very weird.
I put some charlie perfume
on, get you going?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, no.
I want to make love.
My god.
Come on.
Mark, I can't.
Why?
I can't.
I feel... I feel disgusting, okay?
I feel fat.
And I just... I feel like there's
like an apron of skin
around my waist.
It's... I don't feel sexy.
I think you're sexy.
Yeah, well, that's 'cause
you haven't had sex with me yet.
Trust me, once you have sex
with me, you will see how
disgusting I am.
You're not disgusting.
You're perfect.
I am.
I have stretch marks everywhere,
on my legs, my butt, my boobs,
my... have you seen my stomach?
Yeah.
It's like an atlas.
It's...
I'm never gonna be the same.
My body is never gonna look
the same.
No, don't...
look, I love these marks.
I do.
I love the way they feel.
They're like... they're like
guides.
It's like... like a blueprint
showing me the way across
your body.
I love them. I do.
Oh.
Hmm?
Thanks for the effort.
Well, get some sleep, babe.
If I tell you to stop,
you have to stop right away.
And also, if you wake up
that baby...
uh-huh.
I will kill you.
I'm not gonna wake up
the baby.
Okay.
I'm gonna go slow.
And you can't touch my boobs
at all 'cause they're really,
really sore.
I know, but it's okay.
No, no.
And don't touch me there.
Where can I touch you?
Come here.
Mmm.
Oh, my god.
How's your dinner?
It's incredible.
You'll get used to it.
Can I eat fish?
Sure, to-fish.
To-fish?
Mm-hmm, tofu fish.
You can also have tofurky,
tofu burgers, and soysage.
S-soysage?
Is that... is that like
soy sausage?
Oh, sounds really good.
The rule of thumb is that
if it has a heartbeat or a face,
you can't eat it.
I saw on ebay once
there was this grilled cheese
sandwich that had the virgin
mary's face grilled into it.
What about that?
I'd allow it.
Yeah, I hate salad,
just so you know.
You'll grow to like it.
That feels good.
Whoo.
Good.
Further down.
Right there.
Oh, right there.
Mmm.
Further down.
Babe, I think I'm at
the right spot.
Mmm, go further to my feet.
Rub my feet.
No, boring.
Please rub my feet.
Grr.
You're tickling.
I swear you do that on purpose
so you don't have to
rub my feet.
It's not true.
If we have any chance of
lasting, you are gonna have to
learn to give me a proper
foot massage.
Oh, are we at risk of
failing?
Ten years and you still don't
know how to rub my feet
properly.
I just... I don't know if
11's gonna happen, babe.
Oh.
12 years, be a stretch.
Mm-hmm.
13 if you're lucky.
Okay, let's make a baby.
So are you ready?
Uh, ready... ready for what?
To go buy condoms.
Oh, I have one.
You have one?
Yeah, I have one.
Why do you have one?
Just in case.
Oh, just in case
susie rinkmeyers wants to
take you behind the bleachers?
No, you know, just in case
you and I ever had sex.
So you bought it for me?
Yeah.
Well, no, I've actually had it
in my wallet since the sixth
grade.
So you've been carrying it
around for four years
in your wallet.
Yeah, it's got
an expiration date on it.
Listen, babe, we don't have
to do this.
Okay, we can... we can go see
a movie.
No, I want to.
I do.
Okay.
Just give me a second here.
Well, this goes slow.
Are you gonna take off
your pants?
Oh, right, that would help.
Yeah, right.
Wait, um, we should probably...
we should probably put something
down on the seat.
Yeah.
This is so fucking weird.
Right?
Do you want me to take
my dress off?
Yes.
Okay.
Okay, wait.
Someone might walk by.
Yeah, okay.
Just waitin' on you, so...
anytime.
Right.
Here we go.
What's your favorite color?
I'm not picky.
Let's start with red.
We can work our way
through the rainbow.
Why don't we move onto
the bed?
No, I like it here.
You look good in red.
Huh, thank you.
♪ Get it into your head ♪
♪ that I live in a ♪
♪ bubble below ♪
♪ get it into your head ♪
do me a favor.
Anything.
Remind me to thank wendy.
♪ Get it into your head ♪
♪ that I am an adventurer ♪
♪ get it into your head ♪
are you sure we can
tape over this?
Yeah, of course, why not?
It's your daughter's ballet
recital.
My daughter hates ballet.
Oh.
So...
so...
are we rolling?
Yeah, we're rolling.
Mm, I don't know if this
is a good idea to have on tape.
Really, and why's that?
Well, it could be used
against me in the trial.
And what would you be
on trial for?
Fucking you to death.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I didn't call action.
Oh, that's mean.
What's our framing like?
Are we in a wide shot
or a close-up... what?
Uh, it's a wide shot.
Who's gonna watch
a sex tape in a wide shot?
Nobody.
No one's gonna watch it.
Right?
Well, you never know.
These days with the internets
and the kids and their sexting,
it could get out there.
You just fucking with me?
I don't know; Am I?
Am I?
Let me get the camera.
Baby, I think it's time.
Okay.
Oh, that's a lot of semen.
Well, it's mixed with
preservation fluid to promote
motility.
Mmm.
Okay.
Are you doing it right now?
Now I am.
Mmm, this is not how
I imagined it as a girl.
Not at all.
How did you imagine it, baby?
It was my wedding night
after a electric courtship
at a cliffside wedding.
Wait, don't move.
You have to stay on your back
for a few minutes.
Okay.
Good?
Yeah, okay, keep going.
Your wedding?
Uh, and it was a huge
ceremony with these fountains
of flowing champagne
and flowing silk.
And they were serving lobster
bisque.
And oh, there were white little
doves with my train in their
beaks flying like in snow white.
And, uh, yeah, a long parade
of naked bridesmaids.
Naked bridesmaids.
Yeah, I didn't figure that
one out until I was late
into high school.
They were there at my wedding.
And, uh, after the wedding?
Oh, well, of course
my gray-bearded husband
whisked me off into this
horse-drawn carriage, and we go
to our castle.
And the evening culminates
into the ultimate act of love.
Then nine months later...
baby.
Please, please don't make me
stop a second time.
What... what's the matter?
The water.
What is it too hot?
No, it just doesn't work
in here.
Sorry.
Oh, baby, you should've said
something.
Yeah, okay.
I'm ready.
Whoa.
What the fuck are you doing?
What?
Baby, that's disgusting.
You got to be kidding me.
You spit on your dick every time
we have sex.
It's my spit.
Okay, okay, no, go ahead.
Go ahead.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my god.
God, I love you.
What?
More spit.
Why?
'Cause it turned me on.
I thought it disgusted you.
That's why you turn me on.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Wait, what?
No, you said you had to orgasm.
I know. I just did.
No, I don't think so.
Usually when you orgasm,
it's really loud and you swear
a lot.
I know, but that's...
That's just for show, you know.
I just... I didn't want to make
any noise and push all the semen
out.
What do you mean
it's for show?
I mean, 'cause you like it.
Well, yeah... uh...
this just keeps getting
better and better.
Okay, get out of me.
Get out of me.
Would you get me a pillow
please?
Put it under my hips.
I need to keep my hips elevated.
All right.
At a 30-degree angle
for 20 minutes.
Why?
To keep the semen in.
Oh, of course.
Got to keep that semen...
what are you doing there?
I'm trying to relax
my vaginal muscles,
easing the cervical mucus flow
so that the sperm gets to
the egg more quickly
and effectively.
Cool.
Hey, could you do me a favor?
Can you never use the phrase
cervical mucus flow around me
again?
That'd be awesome.
Don't... don't make me laugh.
I don't want to spew out
all your splooge.
Wait, so you'll say splooge
but you won't say balls?
That doesn't make any sense.
Should I go get dressed
or is that gonna ruin
this incredibly romantic moment
we're having together?
Babe, I'm sorry.
I know this is all weird
and crazy.
I just really want to have
a baby.
I know.
Me too.
We're figuring it out.
I think this was the one.
You do?
I'm pretty sure I just
dumped a baby inside you.
I hope so.
Me too.
All right, I'm gonna go
get dressed.
Okay...
no, stay, stay, stay.
Okay.
I didn't gamble the money.
♪ Never want ♪
♪ to say good-bye ♪
♪ just hello again ♪
♪ birthday cards and ♪
♪ the wishes that you send ♪
♪ things are all ♪
whoa.
I fucking hate you.
Why didn't you tell me?
Well, after you beat down
the television,
I was reconsidering.
So...
will you marry me?
No.
Absolutely not.
I would die for you.
I know.
That's morbid.
It's sweet, though.
I would. I would die for you.
I'll keep that in mind
if the opportunity ever
presents itself.
Come make love to me.
Is it Korean?
Oh, shut up before I change
my mind.
Baby, this is so...
oh!
Oh, tell me you love me.
I love you, baby.
Oh, oh, louder!
Oh, baby.
Oh, my god.
Why else?
What?
Why else do you love me?
I can't help it.
You are the girl of my dreams.
You're the girl I used to
fantasize about as a kid.
And now, I got you.
I got you.
I fucking love you.
I love you.
Let's go to bed.
Yeah.
Right after you take a shower.
Okay, let's hear it.
Hear what?
Your sex talk.
My what?
Mmm, yeah, I want to hear you
talk dirty to me.
Oh, okay.
Um, okay, just give a second.
Mm-hmm.
All right, I'll jump-start
you, okay.
Thank you.
Mmm, oh, that feels good.
Oh, okay, yeah, oh, yeah.
Oh, your boobs...
Yes, I love it when you bounce
your boobs like that, like a...
Like a bouncy house, yeah!
Okay, can I start again?
Please.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay, that's good.
Fuck me.
Fuck me hard.
Fuck me hard!
Fuck me harder than hard.
Yeah!
Fuck me hard.
Fuck me hard, hard, hard.
Fu... harder...
that was good.
Maybe I should hold
the camera.
Yeah, good idea.
Here, hang on, hang on, hang on.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Shh-shh-shh-shh-shh.
What?
What do you hear?
Is it your ex?
Oh, don't be so jumpy.
I'm going over my lines
in my head.
Your lines?
You have lines?
Okay, okay.
Oh.
Oh, god, that's right.
That's the spot.
That feels so good.
God, I like it
when you fuck me like that.
Do you know how much I like it
when you fuck me like that?
Feels so good.
Uh, is that real,
or are those your lines?
Pretty good, aren't I?
Oh.
Come on, gimme this.
I thought I was holding
the camera.
No, no, I need you to hold
the prop.
Here.
Okay, turn it on.
Oh, my god, that is loud.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, oh, that feels good.
That is, like,
lawn mower loud.
Oh, it's working.
If it wasn't working,
I would be very concerned.
Oh, just move it slow, slow,
slow, slow, slow, slow!
Slow.
When you've used this before,
have the neighbors ever called
to complain?
Okay, you know what?
You hold this.
Hang on.
Whoa.
Mm-hmm.
That's right.
Here, come on.
Uh, you got lube on your
hands.
You might not want to...
okay, I want you to focus on
the sex, and I will focus
on the tape.
Okay, I'm just saying,
you might want to use two hands.
I know.
You think I'm not capable
of holding on...
oh, fuck me!
Oh, yeah, there it is.
Fuck me!
I knew you had it in you.
Oh, god.
Oh, god, I've got to get
some ice.
What?
Sweetie, your nose
is bleeding.
Oh, shit.
I'm okay.
I'm... i'm sorry.
I'm trying too hard.
Just...
I should get you some ice.
Wait.
Not yet.
That's the sexiest thing you've
said all day.
Mm, mm.
Mm?
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Mmm.
Morning.
Mmm, good morning.
You remembered.
Yeah, mm-hmm.
Baby?
Mm-hmm?
Did you eat a shit sandwich
last night?
Oh, my god, really?
Is it really bad?
Well, your breath tastes like
dog poo.
Is that bad?
Well, then don't kiss me.
Oh, no, no, I didn't say
I didn't want to kiss you.
I'm so gross.
Okay, I don't want
to kiss you.
I'm gonna hurl.
Way to kill the mood.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna brush my teeth.
Oh, no, it'll take too long.
Honey, I got to pee.
Well, you should've thought
of that before.
Do you want me to pee on you?
Yeah, now you're talking.
Seriously, I got to go.
Sexy nose strips by the way.
Hey, I wear these things
for you.
Hey, are you starting
without me?
It's my toothbrush, asshole.
Hey, come on, honey.
I've been waiting all night.
Well, you can wait a few
more minutes.
I have to go back to sleep.
God help you if I start reading
this book again.
Iincoln just freed the slaves.
It's starting to get good.
You ready?
Yeah, I'm ready.
I'm ready.
I'm about to send in
a search party.
Wow.
I stashed it in the bathroom
last night.
I figured, you know, since
it's been a while...
it's about to go a lot faster
now.
Ooh, don't threaten me with
a good time.
Oh, my god.
Honey?
Yeah?
I definitely want to add
this to our chore wheel.
We never made it to yellow.
Hmm, next time.
I mean, if there's a next time.
No pressure.
No, no, I'd like that.
Great, I look forward to it.
Me too.
I can't feel my feet.
I'm sorry if I'm squishing
you or anything.
What?
What is it?
The condom.
Did it break?
I don't know.
It's not here.
What do you mean, "not here"?
I... I mean, I think
it fell off.
No, no-no-no, don't say that.
Don't say that.
Don't tell me.
It's not here.
Fuck.
I'm sorry.
I fell asleep.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Do you want me to, uh,
help you look for it?
Oh, the bathroom?
Right there.
Okay.
Uh...
oh, fuck, fuck.
Oh... um...
it...
well, is it in there?
Fuck.
Is that a yes?
It's slippery.
I can't get a hold of it.
Oh, that is not good.
Um... um...
do you want me to get you
some... tweezers?
Or, uh...
oh, this is bad, isn't it?
It's not good.
Are you on the pill?
It's really hard to get
pregnant.
It is, isn't it?
I mean, really hard.
Some people, they try for years,
and they can't.
Right, it's hard.
So what are the chances,
right?
Close to none.
Probably none.
Yeah.
All right, well, I think
I better go.
No, no, you know, you don't
have to.
Yeah, I should go.
It's late.
Well, okay.
I had a really, really
good time.
Yeah, so did i.
I'm really sorry I scared
you that way.
No, no, you didn't scare me.
I'm the one who should apologize
to you.
I'm sorry.
It's fine, honestly.
But I mean...
no, it's fine.
Not a doubt in my mind.
Really, it's fine.
I'm sure of it.
Okay.
Well...
bye.
Bye.
Hmm, you still want to?
Shh, go back to sleep.
Come on.
We can.
Let's try it.
Gently, huh?
Baby, I don't want to make
you do this.
No, I want to.
If it hurts, we'll stop.
Okay?
I'll get a condom.
No, you don't need one.
I'm breast-feeding.
I can't get pregnant.
You can't?
Yeah.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, no, no, no.
We can't do that.
Haven't you ever heard
of an air embolism?
What?
An air embolism.
If air gets trapped in the
blood vessels, I could die.
But that's, like, just for
the first few days, right?
Do you really want
to test it?
Come on, get back up here.
Well, I mean, that's...
what... what are you doing?
Yeah.
I really, really, really
want to wait.
Why?
Until you're ready.
Well, I'm never gonna be
ready.
Oh.
Look, honey, this isn't
so much about me needing
to heal, okay.
I... I just...
when I look at what this did
to my body and my mind
and my sanity, I just kind of...
I don't know.
I'm freaking out a little,
you know?
Well, you know what
they say.
What do they say?
Got to get back up
on that horse.
Oh, really, horse?
That's what they say.
You think you're maybe
flattering yourself a little?
It's what they say.
I'm just... i'm just repeating.
Okay.
No, you're right, though.
If we don't do it now,
it's just gonna be twice as hard
tomorrow.
Yeah.
Think about it in a week.
It'll be brutal.
Okay, come here, come here.
Hey, baby?
Yeah?
Thanks for loving me
even though I'm falling apart.
I don't think I've ever loved
you more than right now...
ooh.
In this moment.
Really?
Yeah.
Aww.
♪ He doesn't know ♪
♪ any better ♪
are you gonna miss eating
meat?
No, not at all.
Are you okay?
Baby, does it still hurt?
It's not that.
That's not why I'm crying.
What is it?
No, I'm just... i'm happy.
You don't look happy.
I am.
J.t., I'm... i'm not delusional.
I know we're not gonna get
married one day.
We have our whole lives ahead
of us.
And life, college,
and everything that's gonna
pull us apart.
Hey, you don't know that.
No, I know that.
I know that as much as
I know you're gonna eat
another hamburger.
I'm not.
Okay, I swear.
Baby, it's fine.
All I'm saying is...
I'm glad this was with you.
Tracey, what are you talking
about?
All right, you're starting
to scare me.
Just promise me
that when you're married to
some lucky woman who isn't me,
and you have three kids,
big house, car, and a great job,
I need...
just promise me you'll think
about me once in a while.
Baby, I'm gonna be with you.
What's my husband gonna think
about that?
Shut up, okay?
You're just being stupid.
Come here.
♪ He doesn't feel ♪
♪ much like hanging out ♪
♪ he doesn't even ♪
♪ think to call her ♪
I'm sorry that this wasn't
as romantic as your childhood
dream.
No, this is better
'cause you're here.
Baby.
I love you.
Really, that's the face you make
when I say that?
No, no, I'm leaking.
Oh, no, that's normal.
All we need is one
motivated sperm.
It's good.
Men are messy.
I don't know how women do it.
15 more minutes, okay?
Okay.
What do you think of sam?
For a boy or a girl?
Either, samantha or samuel.
Mmm, I don't think so.
My top three boy names are
brandon, stuart, and gregory.
Well, samuel's in my top
three.
Nah, I don't think so.
What gives you a say in
my top three?
Taste.
Okay, baby.
What about girls?
So, mom, dad...
I wanted you both to know that
I'm pregnant.
Pregnant, how?
I didn't know you had
a boyfriend.
Well, actually, I went to
a fertility clinic, and I got
artificially inseminated.
This cannot be happening.
I am religious about that pill.
I mean, I am a birth control
junkie.
That's a nice try.
Ah, that's funny.
Susan said that when she
gave birth, the doctor told her
to push so hard, she...
She just took a giant shit
all over the delivery room
table.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh-ho-ho-ho.
Throughout my entire freshman
year at college...
didn't mean I was pregnant.
What is that?
It's a tumor.
No, it's not.
I know it's not.
Is that blue?
No, it's not blue.
It's not even a shade of blue.
It's more like a lavender.
But is it more blue than red?
Yes, it's more blue than red.
Shit.
I don't know your middle name
or your favorite food
or your favorite book.
I don't know what kind of
toothpaste you use.
Or do you surf?
'Cause you... you're looking like
a surfer, and I'm not.
Okay, you are clearly not
following me.
I am pregnant.
We are pregnant.
Holy shit, how did this happen?
Maybe we should watch
the tape and find out.
Gwen.
Gwen, tell me
you're full of crap.
That's right!
That's what I'm talking about!
Yeah!
Nailed it!
Ahh, ha-ha!
Uh, all right.
Don't forget to take your
art projects home.
Yay!
Mom, where do babies
come from?
♪ Morning breaks ♪
♪ with a shatter ♪
♪ as we put it back together ♪
careful, guys.
♪ Piece by piece ♪
♪ we're side by side ♪
♪ it's the last place ♪
♪ the night left us ♪
♪ when we fell asleep ♪
♪ in its arms ♪
♪ and like you ♪
♪ I'm lost and lonely ♪
♪ we embraced ♪
♪ yes, you and I ♪
I think babies come from...
I think babies come from
the sky.
I know where babies come
from, and it's mommy's vagina.
I think babies come from...
vaginas.
Why would you ask me
that question?
Maybe they come from...
I don't know... like, an egg?
I think babies come from
mommy's stomach.
I think they just appear.
They just grow.
They cut the belly,
and then they take the baby out.
And then it starts to be
a brother.
I think god puts them in
a mommy's tummy.
And then they just swim around
in the water that she's drunk.
So first the baby is in
the mommy's belly.
Then she has to go to
the bathroom.
She poops the baby out,
and that's why we always stink.
The doctor opens up
the zipper, and then their baby
comes out, and then
they sew it back together.
And then when the baby's
tired of swimming,
the doctor just tickles the
mommy as much as he can until
the baby just pops right out.
I saw on the computer
a dog having a baby.
And... and it doesn't come out
the dookie hole.
I think it comes out of
another hole.
And... and it's like poo,
like, uh!
Arr!
They have sex.
That means that they make out...
nude.
Out of the booby booby,
hee-yow!
Why are you taking a...
who's bigger than us?
When are you taking
the picture?
And... and we're not,
and we're not...
when are gonna take the...
a baby anymore
because we're big, big boys.
See?
Mark.
I'll hold this.
I'll hold it.
I'm just gonna put it right here
so we can...
♪ shining stars ♪
♪ well, I know they are ♪
♪ shining in your eyes ♪
♪ you hold them with grace ♪
♪ and elegance and sweet poise ♪
♪ now that I know those ♪
♪ shining stars ♪
♪ well, I know they are ♪
♪ shining in your eyes ♪
♪ girl, I can see ♪
♪ ooh, baby, I can see ♪
♪ oh, oh-oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ ooh, said, baby, I can see ♪
♪ ooh, baby, I can see ♪