OCEAN:
Since I was the last
of eight children,
my father overruled
my mother and named me
after God's best miracle,
the ocean.
My name's supposed
to mean endless possibility
like the ocean, but...
But much of my life,
I didn't really have
much possible.
And sometimes,
I'm not sure
I got any ability.
But today,
I'm trying to live like
Daddy always said,
"Make any new day
your best day."
I'm Ocean Jackson
and this is the
diary of a single mom
trying to get
ahead in the world
trying to hold her under.
Yeah, baby, you're gonna
make my life a lot easier.
Here, maybe you
should try it.
Apartment needs
a little work.
But then again, I hear
your father taught you
to fix any that's broke.
Maybe you can fix me.
Wow!
A little paint, bleach,
elbow grease...
This is a beautiful arch.
Yeah, it ain't beautiful
how they left the place.
Kids, go check it out.
Why is there a gas grill
in the living room?
BUDDY: It's probably stolen.
Look, I got some new
tenants moving in today.
It's all written
down for you.
So there you go!
Um, you got some
good-looking kids.
Then again,
you're a good-
looking woman.
And Ocean,
I like that name.
Which one you named after,
the Pacific or Atlantic?
Both.
Oh, I like that.
Mister...
Buddy, call me Buddy.
LUPE: Buddy Chase!
Buddy Chase,
are you in there?
I've been leaving you
messages for weeks.
I got leak city upstairs,
under my sink, my shower,
outlets don't work,
Ocean meet second
floor's Lupe Ramirez...
Okay, no, no!
Don't try and distract
me because I need
you to do your job, mister...
Ocean Jackson.
New apartment manager
and onsite repair person.
Oh, hell no.
She's a woman.
Oh, hell no,
how did
that happen
Girl, I don't
mean no offense,
but Tricky Dick, here,
like to play Houdini
and I'm sick of his
disappearing act.
'Cause it don't
scare me to move.
Move, Lupe. See who else
will put up with you
coming up short every month.
All right, listen.
Deposit slips
are in there,
any information you need,
it's in there,
contact numbers...
If you need anything else,
give me a call. Hello.
Whoa, whoa! Hold on.
What about my...
You know what?
I ain't through with
you Mr. Buddy Chase.
Mommy!
We measured and according
to my computations
we've gained approximately
270 square feet
of more living space
than what we
had at Grandma's.
Um, he's a genius
or something?
Sort of, he's on scholarship
at the Kennedy Academy
for the gifted,
so to be there,
you got to, kind of,
be a genius.
Mine can't even
spell genius.
Yes I can! J-E-E-N-U-S.
See, just like his daddy.
Okay, speaking of the devil.
Come on baby, let's go.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Go on.
LUPE: J.J., you and Sophie
just stay right here,
I'm gonna be
right back, all right?
Sophie, baby, don't cry,
I told you I was leaving
just play your video games.
Take care of your sister,
all right? I love you.
You know what?
You and your sister...
Mind Miss Ocean now.
Can I just go say hi to Dad?
Boy, I already told you, no.
If I don't go now,
there's no telling when I'm
gonna see your daddy again.
Girl, you know how it is.
Mama needs groceries.
Do I look okay?
Yeah, I already know my
breasts are my best feature
but I ain't bragging
about them.
You know how they say,
"God takes anything
you love too much."
LUPE: Juan, I'm coming!
Just so you know,
she won't be back
for a while.
Groceries, Sarah.
Come on,
let's go play.
Ian, please, Grandma
can't concentrate
with all that noise.
I didn't really read
the lease, so I don't
know what to put on.
Too many decisions.
How they could think
that this will make me
more independent.
If your Grandpa
Bill was here,
he'd have the...
Auntie said that whenever
you say Grandpa Bill's name,
I should shout, "He's dead!"
She said that?
What a bitch.
But you said Grandpa's
in heaven with my mommy
and Jesus, right?
That's right. Yeah.
I'm sorry, we're not
purchasing anything today.
My mom doesn't
wear much make-up.
Young man, do we look
like we're selling anything?
We're tenants.
Temporarily.
Oh! Well, come on in,
my mom's the manager.
Mom, Uncle Bo
and Trina's here.
So that's the bathroom
and you know...
Uh
A little paint
and a good cleaning...
Ah, baby, I know you,
you'll have this
place laid out.
I'm so proud
of you, Ocean.
And I know your daddy's
is up there with his
chest poked out.
And you know that Trina
can help you in getting
this place together.
Oh, no, Uncle Bo.
I mean, this building,
my kids and trying to...
You've got a lot
of your father in you.
Straight and narrow,
no detours.
But if you live long enough
you'll find out that life has
got a whole
lot of detours,
especially when
it comes to family.
Every time my sister
decides her
child don't exist
and she got a new man,
I'm supposed to...
At least my mama's
got a man...
Stay out
of this, Trina.
She started it!
So I'm gonna finish it.
See? Now that's
a detour I can't take.
Keep her at mama and yours
because I...
I'm just not going
to put up with her mouth.
Baby...
Do this for your uncle.
Before I had my
little drinking problem,
didn't Uncle Bo
try to save you?
You know a whole
lot of those things
that you did, remember?
It was Uncle Bo
that kept it from your
mama and daddy.
I was the one
that told you that you
you were moving too fast.
And to stay away
from that fool you
ended up marrying.
But, Uncle Bo, she...
I'm trying to stay
sober, baby.
And God knows I am,
I mean, see?
Almost steady.
I'm not quite there yet.
But I really want to
keep Trina from going
down the same path.
She's already done
come home drunk once.
And I don't want
it to be twice.
She needs somebody stable.
Like you.
There ain't nobody
in our family more
stable than you, baby girl.
That you got
from your father.
But Uncle Bo
is hoping that...
You got your
heart from me.
She got to know that
in my house I got rules.
No, Ocean's
my mama's
baby sister.
Yeah.
But I hate her.
Oh my gosh!
And everybody
else in my family.
They all get
on my nerves.
Yeah, but at least
she's not a drug
like the rest of them.
I miss you, too.
OCEAN:
There are three families
that stay in the building.
But they always seem to
congregate in my apartment.
Uncle Bo says it's
because of my name.
Everybody wants
to swim in the ocean.
I guess.
All I know is together
we seem to stay afloat.
You don't know
how hard I've tried to
like Mike-the-right.
Oh, girl! You and
your baby daddies.
You should go check
on the babies.
LUPE: Oh, they're all right.
They sleep late.
Stupid dial up!
Froze right when
I was in the middle
of something important.
Oy, what're you doing
that's so important?
You're on this
thing every time...
Um, what are you doing
on FriendSpace?
Uh, it's for school.
That's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
I was thinking that if we
pooled our money together
we could get
a high-speed service...
Oh, I already got cable.
No, a modem!
So that you could study,
we could pay bills online,
operate our lives
a little better.
Operate my life
a little better
What?
LUPE: Coming!
Oh, Ian...
What are you doing to him?
Where's his clothes?
I washed them.
Oh, and I've been meaning
to give Ian some of the
clothes J.J.'s outgrown.
He will look so fly.
We don't need
your handouts.
And I didn't tell you
that you could come up
here to see these people.
Okay, hold on a minute!
Lupe!
Who the hell you
calling "these people"?
Because all we was trying
to do is help you out.
Lupe, Lupe!
MIKE: Hey, what's
all this hollering?
You know what? I'm about
to get Miss Avon straight.
You must be Sophie's dad.
You spit her right out.
Ian come on let's go.
LUPE: Yeah, this is Ocean,
she's the new manager.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Ocean? That's a fly name.
Where the kids?
Where's Sophie?
Next door.
Lupe, what'd I tell
you about leaving
my daughter alone?
Don't even start that
mess because you come
up here twice a month
and all you do is find fault
and I'm tired of it.
Look, if you don't want
to take care of her,
I said I will.
Ian let's go,
get your clothes later.
I take care of my baby.
What, you're gonna
come here twice...
OCEAN: Wonder If the floors
of single mothers are more
worn out than other floors.
I used to hear my mother
walk the floor at night.
Mumbling and humming...
Especially if one of us
hadn't made it home.
Auntie Ocean.
Girl,
don't have a heart attack.
Let me tell you just
what happened, there was...
There was just...
They wanted me to go
and I said no,
but when I left earlier we...
We was driving, right,
and we just...
We just got lost, like,
"Where are we going?"
Hmm, well, we got lost.
And I went and it
was so much fun.
I didn't do anything bad.
We got lost, though... Yeah.
You are better than this!
You hear me?
Yeah.
Peggy?
OCEAN: Peggy?
Hi.
I didn't mean any
harm today and I'm sorry
and if I'm overstepping,
we had leftovers and...
We don't need anything.
But take it anyway.
No.
I hope I'm not
overstepping again
but Lupe and I have
a proposal and, um,
we were thinking if we pool
our resources together
we can help each other.
Thank you.
She really called me Avon?
Don't worry I've
been called worse.
Okay, if, uh...
Thanks again.
I'm... All right.
I went to mass.
Okay, and maybe
a few other places.
Can I sleep here?
I just can't face
Mike-the-right tonight.
Maybe my kids will be
better off without me.
OCEAN: So maybe
finding a way
to love people...
...in the midst of
their struggles
is what we're all here for
and to raise these kids.
Work Source, this is, uh...
We develop your
mind and body.
This is Ocean Jackson,
how may I direct your call?
Uh, please hold.
Just a little
setback, Ocean.
Having a little bit
of dyslexia is like...
Like having
a little bit of stupid.
You're not stupid, Mommy.
Aw, baby.
She's right.
You're so close.
Little more practice,
more computer time...
I practice at my desk.
But between
the phones,
Kayla and...
Yeah, well, some of
the staff thinks that, uh,
to be fair, maybe it's time
to enroll her in daycare
or preschool.
LOU: I just...
By the time
I pay for daycare
I may as well stay at
home with her myself.
I'll tell you what,
let me talk to your
case worker, maybe we
can work something out.
Work out me sitting in
the office all day before they
tell me I'm wasting my time?
Ocean, every problem
has a solution.
All we have to do is get
our knuckleheads together.
No matter how frustrating
it may be, we'll come up
with something.
Aren't you always telling
me your father said,
he didn't raise no quitter?
Kayla, come with me.
I got a little secret.
Come on.
What's going on, Lupe?
What?
Miss?
Peggy?
The school called.
Ian is there but he's
not registered.
Ian's at school?
I'm sorry.
OCEAN: Peggy,
somebody told me today,
that every problem
has a solution.
I don't know how
to do this by myself.
None of us do.
When my father died,
he left eight kids
for my mom to support.
Okay?
I dropped out of school.
So, I used the skills
that my father
showed me fixing things
and I ended up making
more money than
everybody else.
It wasn't a whole
lot of money.
But I did what
had to do.
All I'm saying is,
you've got to
start somewhere.
Where?
Turn.
Juan, stop.
Please just listen
to me for s a sec.
Look, I'm just say, would you
love me any less if I had
to go through the surgery...
You're tripping! You got
two tits, why would I
imagine you with one?
Look, I got somebody
waiting on me.
Okay, well, what about
your son who's waiting on you?
You act like that's
the only kid I've got.
Well, he's the only
one I got by you,
so, I ain't worried
about anyone else.
OCEAN: Lupe.
I didn't want
to say anything
in front of Peggy
but, uh, I need that
money back that I gave
Buddy Chase for you.
Okay, it's...
I'll get it from
Mike tonight.
OCEAN: Mike?
He said he was hoping
all of us would go
trick-or-treating together.
Um...
Oh!
Trina!
Yes.
LUPE: She looks
so good. Okay.
You look nice,
like a young lady for once.
I look like I'm
going to church.
But Lupe said
you'd like it.
She gave it to me.
Auntie Ocean?
Mm-hmm.
Why is Sammy asking
me about his dad
all the time like I know?
I don't really remember him,
but he keeps asking me
how he looks
and if he had
a middle name.
I don't know.
I told him
to ask you.
OCEAN: Ian, stop
eating that candy.
Sammy, I want to see your
homework before you go to bed.
And none of this
"I got it done, Mama."
'Cause the only way
you're gonna stay
in that school is...
BOTH: On scholarship.
PEGGY: Hey, guys.
I got the job.
I'm so happy for you.
Break it down, baby.
Only thing is,
I start working
evening shifts at first.
So, I might need
help with Ian.
Um...
I'll pay you as
soon as I get paid.
We'll work it out.
It was that makeover.
Every time!
I never could've done
this without both of you.
And, oh, now I can get
my furniture and have
some friends over
and I used to have
a lot of friends
and maybe even
invite my sister.
Okay, but first let's
get your costume.
Oh, I... I have
to start work tonight.
But Grandma,
we're all going together.
Oh, I know sweetheart
but we need the money, okay?
Save me a chocolate?
Okay.
Love you.
Have fun.
Bye.
All right!
Oh!
Great costume.
Thank you.
I knew it was you, Daddy.
Oh, you did, did you?
Do I have to go?
I'm supposed
to meet somebody.
Yes.
You look nice.
Daddy!
JUAN: Come on, guys,
want to check out
a real party?
Door-to-door's
for kiddies.
'Sup Mike?
Go ahead.
Me and Sophie will be
fine without you.
We always are.
J.J. come with us,
please. Mama?
Mama spends time
with you and your
daddy all the time, baby.
J.J. never gets to be
with both of his parents.
You have fun, love you.
Hey, let's go catch up
with the other kids, okay?
I wanted a family.
Even adopt J.J.
But while I was trying to be
our shutter from the storm,
Lupe's out there
wishing for a hurricane.
Hmm.
Maybe when she
finishes school
I can afford to
go back myself.
I want to teach
the little ones.
Hmm.
I ain't never met a man
that's wanted to be
bothered with little kids.
Well, maybe you need
to meet someone now.
You know, men can
impact a kid's life
just like a woman.
That's why I don't
know how much longer
I can take this
arrangement between
me and Lupe.
MIKE: Sophie.
There you go.
And Ian!
Yes!
SAMMY: We never
talk about him.
There's no pictures of him.
What could he have done
so bad for you to erase
him out of your life?
And mine, too.
He might want to know
I'm smart like him.
Oh, and you couldn't have
inherited your brains from
your dumb mama, right?
Boy, what's taking
you so long finding him?
There, that's him.
That's not your father, Sammy.
But he has the same name.
He said he was married to you.
I don't know who this is,
or what he's saying.
I've never seen that man
before in my life.
What did you tell him?
Did you tell him
where we lived?
Huh? He could be
some kind of...
He could be some
kind of child killer.
Did you tell him
where we lived?
I'm not a snitch.
You're not a snitch, boy?
Ocean, he's just scared.
Get your hands off of me!
Don't you ever touch me.
Don't nobody touch me! Ever!
OCEAN: Any nipple discharge?
Well, if I'm getting
my freak on, maybe.
Lupe, this is serious.
Ocean, I'm studying
to be a medical assistant,
I know the drill.
Spongy or hard?
I don't want
to talk about this.
Well, let's talk
about you and Mike.
What?
Girl, please!
He is a good man,
but I could never
be happy with him
but maybe you can.
Both of y'all are dull,
stubborn...
All right shut it up.
Why are you trying
to change the subject?
Okay, I'll go to the doctor.
I just wish
I wouldn't have
said anything.
I took her out.
I don't like her anymore.
I'm going to cook you
the most romantic
candlelit dinner.
Uh
And what about
the kids?
Trina can occupy them.
All right, well,
there's the kitchen.
And I'm going
to go in the back
and change my clothes.
Kayla? Baby, let me know
when you hear the bus.
Why don't I go
meet the bus?
You're on.
BOYFRIEND: Come here.
Stop playing, girl.
Come on now.
Come on,
you know you want it.
Get out of my house!
Auntie Ocean...
Ah!
Where's my bat?
Come near my niece
again, see if I don't
call the police!
She's underage!
BOYFRIEND: Whatever.
You go back there
and change them
nasty sheets.
Pack your bags
and call your Uncle Bo.
I want you
out of my house.
OCEAN: Uncle Bo,
I tried with her,
but she got to get
out of my house.
Well, I don't
call that trying.
Trying is not taking a drink
when you've drank everyday
of your life. That's trying.
Trying is not
throwing in the towel
after two months.
You know
she's going to
do something.
She's a kid.
A kid sleeping
with everything
walking.
No, I'm not.
He's my boyfriend!
OCEAN: You don't need
a boyfriend at your age!
You had one
at my age!
No, I didn't!
You sure about that?
Uncle Bo...
I'm just saying that
if you're really trying
to help her...
She's not my responsibility!
Sure she is!
She's your family!
No, both of you all
back up off me
because you're not going
to make me the bad guy.
Nobody's trying to
make you the bad guy.
But I got
to tell you
one thing,
you sure ain't
the Ocean
that I used to
take care of.
Bo, that's not fair.
Shoot!
Life ain't fair.
If you waiting for fair
you'll be waiting in line
for a long time.
The one thing
I asked you
to do for me...
It ain't one thing.
It's always something
if it ain't money!
Oh!
Now we going tit for tat.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that.
Yeah, you did.
You think you're
better than me.
No, no, I don't.
It's just...
You're trying.
Come on, Trina.
I'll be waiting in the car.
Because in a minute
I might ask your auntie
for a glass of water,
and Lord knows...
I want to watch her
try to get it.
MIKE: Happy Thanksgiving.
OCEAN: Our first
Thanksgiving
in the building
and we've all become
like family to each other.
He should have been
up here by now.
I, at least,
wanted everybody
together for prayer.
Huh. It's disconnected.
LOU: Hope I'm not late.
No!
Ocean, I really couldn't
decide on desert,
so I bought three.
My wife is...
You didn't have to bring
anything but yourself.
I bet you say that
to all of them,
especially if they have
a bit of good news.
I worked really hard.
Mm-hmm. Yes, you did.
I called in a favor
and got your results early.
Now, it's time to fill out
those college applications.
Everybody,
this is Mr. Lou Bailey.
My savior, my hero.
Mike, Lou.
I'm Mike, just Mike.
Not a hero, not a savior,
just Mike.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Hey, Lupe,
good to see you as well.
I'm gonna go tell Peggy.
Okay!
OCEAN: Sometimes our
problems are bigger than
we ever care to admit,
especially to ourselves.
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
They don't want to be
a part of my life,
they never did.
They
only tolerated me
because of my husband.
The very same
man that, um,
gambled my
very life away.
You know, Ocean,
I went from millions
to food stamps.
And since
I started working,
I don't even
get those anymore.
Guess what?
Well, I might now, since
I got fired
two days ago.
The owner
felt that I was...
Wasn't grateful
enough for his Viagra
show of affection.
Back to square one.
And I'm either too
stupid or too old
to master surviving
on my own.
Oh, Ocean,
how do you do it?
You.
I passed my GED
because you helped me.
You wouldn't let
me give up.
So let me
return the favor.
OCEAN: Everybody grab
hands, close your eyes.
We are so grateful
for each and every one
of us, who by blood
or by love have
become family,
and as family,
for every problem,
there is a solution.
ALL: Amen.
Anybody want to sing?
I just want to
say that, um,
I am thankful for
all of my blessings,
and, um,
which is,
every person in this room.
And I wish you all,
health and healing.
* Good bread, good meat
Good gosh, let's eat *
JUAN: Hey, hey, hey!
I don't get an invitation
to Thanksgiving?
I'm still part of
the family, huh?
Juan...
Are you going to call
the police on me?
What are you doing?
Watch where you're
grabbing, son!
Dad...
Juan, let's just stop,
not today, baby...
Let's go...
I don't want to be
disrespectful...
What are you trying to be,
the head of somebody's
household or something, man?
Baby, please not today,
Por favor!
I'm sorry,
he's just drunk and...
Come on, let's go
next door, me and you.
No!
Come on...
No, just...
Come on, you're
going home with Dad.
What about Thanksgiving?
Come on, right now,
you're going home with Daddy.
Mike, please don't do this!
I can't control what
you do with your life.
I can control what
you do with my daughter.
Mike, stop.
Please stop, Juan!
Mike!
Hey, baby.
Remember me?
Your husband.
This is my surprise.
Mike, what are you doing?
Are you serious right now?
Are you serious?
We are having
Thanksgiving dinner!
I can't believe you!
LUPE: There are people up
there who have been cooking
all day, just calm down!
Seriously, please.
MIKE: I'm taking
my child!
That's my child, too!
Look, I...
I'm not leaving her
in a dangerous situation.
This is not
a dangerous situation!
Sarah wouldn't want
you to forget this.
Sarah says thank you, J.J.
I have to take her.
No, you don't.
I can't leave her here.
I can't leave her with you
no more. I can't do this!
I love her too much.
I can't do this, sorry.
Okay, I love her, too.
I'm sorry. Sorry!
I love you, baby!
I need you.
OCEAN: Sometimes
you wonder if change
is really possible.
Please forgive me.
And if I can earn
a GED, when I started
out reading
at sixth grade level
I'm so alone.
maybe it's possible
that my ex-husband
could've found God and
never use me as
a punching bag again.
I'm asking for
another chance, Ocean.
If you're my daddy,
would you read to me?
Of course I will, baby.
Ah, goodness.
OCEAN: Children
are so forgiving.
They love even when
they're conceived
out of hate.
Don't leave me out!
I like baby stories.
I get the best seat
since I was the only
one at Grandma's
who told you where
to find Auntie Ocean.
Okay, that's fair.
"Where's Spot?"
OCEAN: Kayla only came into
being because her father
decided after years apart,
he wanted me
back one night.
He was drunk,
so he wouldn't take no
for an answer.
I survived.
I sometimes am working
so hard, to survive and
take care of them, I...
I forget how much
I just want them to
also be happy.
And right now,
they are.
Happy to have
a father again.
How can I ever take
that away from them?
OCEAN: Every morning, I try
to take a moment to pray.
Even if it's only
a second to close
my eyes.
And acknowledge God
for the blessing
of a brand new day.
And the hope
that this day
is going to bring
something different.
I just don't understand
why you had to
lie to him.
Girl, no man needs
to know that the ladies
have been under the knife.
Lupe, they did not
cut your titties off.
You had a biopsy.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Okay, today is just
not my day for saying
the right things.
Um...
I know it's scary.
I mean, it's got to be
the most scariest thing
a woman can go through.
You want me to fix
you something to eat,
before I go to work?
If I still have a job.
I've missed so much...
No, just go.
Um, I'm just going
to lie down before my kids...
I miss my baby
so much.
Sometimes, I hate Mike
for taking her away.
I'll see you later.
What you doing home?
How come you're not
at work?
Senior said I didn't
have to go to school,
'cause I wasn't
feeling well.
Hey, baby.
OCEAN: I did like
seeing him move in,
just on a trial basis.
He bought us
this new basketball hoop
I'm going to work
at having them see me
laugh every day.
Which is easy to do,
you know, with Mike around.
Who Lupe thinks has
a crush on me.
I'm like, "Girl, please!"
I don't need
somebody else's
baby daddy.
It's hard enough managing
the one I already have.
I was not under him!
I know what I saw.
Huh? Maybe
you giving it to him,
since you ain't
giving it to me.
Look, I'm sorry.
Okay, I just...
I got some good
news just for once,
I came into some money.
And I got you something.
Okay, look,
just don't go nowhere.
Mmm! Right?
Thought we could
go out, have some fun.
Go dancing.
Look, no kids.
Just want it
to be us again.
Hey, look, I got us
matching cell phones, too.
Sam, where did
you get the money
to pay for this?
So what,
you my mama now?
Huh? Then whoop
my ass then, since
I did something wrong.
I don't even have
the sense to
breathe right, huh?
Can't do nothing right
in Ocean's book.
Damn, Ocean!
Every time I think
we've taken
three steps forward
you make sure we
take five steps back.
Like do you know
what that feels like?
To not have a job?
To not be able to
provide for my family?
I know that you're trying.
But they're about
to turn the lights off.
The rent is paid
and nothing else.
All that money that
you spent, it could've...
Hello?
Yeah, this is
Ocean Jackson.
Are you two coming
back or what?
Ooh!
This looks like
it was made for me!
Don't you think?
I can work this!
I'll be there.
Uh... It's, uh...
Uncle Bo...
He's... He's been
in the hospital.
Trina put that dress down.
This goes back
to the store.
Y'all, um...
Clean up the couch
for Uncle Bo.
What?
No!
We are not having
that alki in here!
Another person
in this house?
Last I checked
all of this here, mine!
TRINA: I like
this dress, though.
You are so stubborn.
You can tell you're
my daddy's brother.
If Daddy listened
to the doctors,
he might still be here.
Okay, I promise
Uncle Bo'll take care
of himself.
If I stop drinking and
exercise and get the blood
flowing in my legs more.
Hey.
What?
Chicken butt.
Hey, you know
something else?
I love you.
I can always count
on my little Ocean.
I love you, too.
Hey, what's up, old man?
Heard they're going
to cut off your toes.
OCEAN: Sometimes,
it's easier to start
with what you're scared of,
the devil you know,
and to figure out what's
ahead for your life.
Is this your card?
No.
Hmm...
Is that your card?
OCEAN: I used to play
house and dream what
my children dream,
that one day,
I'd grow up and
live happily ever after
on a rainbow.
OCEAN: But now,
I think I dream in gray,
if that's the color of fear.
I'm so scared
that my life will
always be like this.
Sitting in a dirty tub
somebody forgot
to wash out.
Wondering
if this is as good
as it's ever going
to get for me.
Oh, Ocean,
I know it's early, but...
I was wondering
if I could borrow
your cell phone.
My service doesn't
seem to be working
and I wanted
to follow up
on a few jobs.
It's 6:00 A.M.
Nothing's open.
Good morning, Bo.
Good morning, Peggy!
What's wrong with
your cell phone?
I keep telling you
that you're qualified
for these programs...
I didn't come up here
to discuss services!
I just want to borrow
your phone to make
a few phone calls!
Okay, okay, you don't
have to wake up everybody
in the house!
Sorry, Bo!
Um, here,
I need it back before
I leave for work.
Okay.
Oh, I must have pushed
the wrong button! Wow!
Trina sure has a body
on her for a 13-year-old.
Looking good
behind that desk!
Work Source, we offer
a wide range of services.
How may we serve you?
Please hold while
I put you through.
Girl, you just keep
on surprising me.
So, that's a good
thing, right?
Yeah!
Where did you get those
earrings, I haven't
seen those before.
My girlfriend at school
makes them.
Those do not look
homemade.
Trina, there was
something that I wanted
to talk to you about.
Oh, no, I knew you
didn't invite me down here
to play receptionist!
What did I do now?
Nothing.
Trina, you're
a very smart girl.
Yeah.
For the first time in school,
I'm doing good.
Aunty Ocean, I'm getting A's
in math and science!
My teacher says I can be
an engineer or something!
I got to figure out
what they do first!
I am so glad that you
are finally motivated.
I just want you
to conduct yourself...
How do I put this? Um...
Senior loves
all you kids.
You know that
don't you? A lot.
But maybe Trina
somewhere in your mind,
you've got it twisted
that his caring
is something more.
So we talked
about boundaries...
Boundaries against me?
What are you talking about?
I picked up his phone
by accident, there was
a picture of you.
Not Kayla,
not Sammy...
Or you?
That's why you're
really mad, isn't it?
Senior said you were
jealous, that's why
y'all broke off before!
He shouldn't be talking
about me, to you.
Why not?
You discuss me
with him.
How I'm not
your responsibility.
That you only let
me stay 'cause
Uncle Bo asked you.
But I thought
we was doing better.
That you were even
starting to like me.
But you're just
like my mom.
Always accusing
me of something.
Me trying to take her man
when all I wanted was her.
And it's not like
it was a picture of me
naked or something.
God, so when you
want me to leave?
I'm not talking about
you leaving, Trina,
I love you.
Oh, good,
I need a hug, too.
What's wrong with her?
Growing up too fast.
That's how those girls do!
With their hot asses,
13 and on fire!
Anyway, girl,
I came here
for a reason.
I need you
to get my results.
You didn't make that call?
You work right next
to the hospital,
all you have to do
is walk five steps
and you could have
got your results.
I'm trying to work up
my nerve.
I'm starting
to hate hospitals.
Really, I'm starting
to hate everything
except maybe...
Well, except maybe Mike.
Hmm.
Girl, I tried to
give him to you,
but then you went
and pulled a husband
out of the hat.
Look, I'm telling you, just...
All this medical
stuff's just got
me so scared,
I can't do this
alone no more.
I need somebody
I can count on.
I know you know
what I mean, I mean
why else would you even
think about being back
with your baby daddy?
Give me the phone
and the phone number.
WOMAN: Medical clinic.
Hello.
Can I help you?
Hello?
Hold on, please.
How can I help you?
This is Lupe Ramirez,
I was just wondering
if you have my
biopsy results.
Please hold for a minute.
Inconclusive does not
mean that everything
is okay.
Before you start
celebrating, you need
to go see your doctor.
Girl, inconclusive means
Lupe dodged a bullet, and...
That's all I care about.
What is this stuff
on my floor?
Okay, look, starting tomorrow,
you, me and Avon
are going to be having
a fitness class,
'cause we all need
to get healthy
Lupe, you see
this stuff on the floor?
Uh-huh.
It looks like confetti.
Oh, man, I told them
to keep the lights
on for me!
Know I don't like
to come home to
a dark house!
ALL: Happy birthday!
Baby, Trina and I've been
planning this for a month!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
I kept it a secret
and you know
that's a lot of work!
Trina!
ALL CHANTING:
Ocean, Ocean, Ocean!
Happy birthday,
Auntie Ocean!
Make a wish!
You happy, baby?
Very!
Mmm! Rather tasty!
Building up my
husband points.
Whoo!
You go party.
I'm going to sit
here and relax.
BO: Let me show
you how to do it.
OCEAN: Whoa!
Auntie Ocean, I'm gonna
go lie down, I'm tired!
Oh, Trina, the
party just started!
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
we got a special project!
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
come on, Trina!
BO: Yeah, thank you!
Yeah!
It's beautiful!
We've been working
on this 24/7!
We?
Oh, yeah, I'll be real
happy to give you all
the credit, old man!
Since us peons went
back and forth to get...
I love it!
I love it! I love it!
Thank you!
Both of you.
Thank all of you for
making this one of the
best birthdays I've ever had.
* Party over here
Party over there *
Oh.
Wow!
"To Ocean, buy
something just for you.
"After all, a lot of people
wouldn't know what
to do without you.
"So, take care of you.
Love, Mr. Bailey.
"And flex."
I got the garbage out.
And I was going to vacuum
but I thought it might wake up
Bo and the kids.
It was a great party,
wasn't it?
Yeah, it was.
Where's my pillow
and blankets?
OCEAN: Mr. Bailey is right.
I'm flexing my mean muscle,
so what the hell?
It's my birthday,
and tonight I wanna
feel taken care of.
* Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Whoa! Don't you look
nice this morning!
So, what do you think
about me moving out?
You know, your mother's
always got a bed for me
and I'm thinking about
singing up with that
Older Workers' program.
Uh, I think that is
the worst idea I've
heard in a long time.
Somebody needs to
still take care of your leg.
And, Uncle Bo, I've asked
Senior to stop bringing
liquor into this house.
I do not want you tempted.
Well, keeping me
sober is really not
your responsibility.
Taking care of grown-ass
folks who are old enough
to know what they're doing,
should never be
your responsibility.
But taking care of you
is my privilege.
And Mr. GQ in there?
You know, baby,
I've been trying to hold
my tongue 'cause you grown.
But I gotta ask you,
why in the hell
did you let that
fool back in here?
The kids need
to know their father.
Then let him come visit!
Not lay up here on you
like he's been doing.
And what does he contribute
to the household besides
sleeping most of the day?
That's not fair!
He's been working
with this cleaning business,
and they clean
foreclosed homes
when people move out.
Oh, really? I don't know what
kind of cleaning he does,
because every time I see him
come back here, he's just
as clean as he left out.
You could do better.
Well, you know what they say,
"It's always easier with the
devil you already know."
Until he surprises you again.
Senior.
Wake up. Mr. Bailey's
on his way and we gotta go.
There's only one place
I wanna go but I need you
to take me there, baby.
Stop playing.
Slip some clothes on,
I don't want to keep
Mr. Bailey waiting.
Mr. Bailey.
Mr. Bailey this
and Mr. Bailey that.
Don't you think
he's a little old?
Got you thinking
you're college material.
You barely
finished eighth grade.
"See the dog
cross the street."
That's not funny.
Look, you can't
take a joke no more?
I'm just playing with you!
Come on, look,
you can't take a joke?
Uh-uh.
BO: What happened
to that happy face?
Um...
Can you keep
an eye on the kids?
I, uh...
I'm gonna wait
for Mr. Bailey outside.
You know the best
thing I learned at AA?
Simple.
Change your mind,
change your life.
That's what today's
all about.
So don't let nothing
or nobody get in your way.
Dad thought me
everything about houses.
So, I was thinking maybe...
Maybe I wanted
to be a teacher.
Maybe even a lawyer.
No, no, no. Don't laugh.
Don't laugh. It's not funny.
You see, Ocean,
that's all achievable.
Roll up your fist.
Come on, come on, come on.
Roll up your fists.
Now bend your arm.
Flex.
Every day I want you
to flex your "me" muscle.
to do something,
think something,
wonder about something,
pray about something,
anything you have to
do to make it about you.
What Ocean wants.
Me? Well didn't you
see what I wrote about
Senior and him cutting hair,
and, uh, how he wants
to open a barber shop,
and he wants to go
into business together.
Flex, Ocean! Flex!
I want you to start
that sentence again,
I want you to start it with,
"What, I, Ocean wants."
Oh, come on!
Ocean, give me another excuse.
Tell me about how you
had to repair your family.
How you had to
move everyone forward
and forget about you.
And you are not
moving you ahead!
Flex!
Don't stop flexing.
I'm flexing, damn it!
Hmm...
It felt good to
yell at me, didn't it?
This is for you.
That's more application
papers just in case
you lost the others.
And my phone number
is in there, just in case
you need to talk.
Thank you.
Oh! Just in time
to work out!
Girl, I told you, we
need a whole building
fitness program.
Let me show you, I've got
my routine worked out.
So, happy belated birthday.
Heard your party was great.
Would have brought
you a present
but your husband seems
a tad bit protective,
wouldn't you say?
You think?
Girl, come in and
workout with us!
Look, I've decided
no more hospitals for me.
I've decided to become
a personal trainer.
Look, I, I just can't
take it anymore.
And Mike, he went and
bought me all these books
on exercise and
physicology and stuff.
Look at me, I can't even
pronounce the word right.
But I am serious
about this, girl.
Hey, my grandma was
looking to take something
for her toothache.
She's spitting out blood
and I'm kind of scared.
I'm sure you knew your
insurance card is not valid.
Oh, my! Did my husband
send me with the wrong card?
Oh! I thought
you were a widow.
Oh...
Perhaps I could speak
to a supervisor, someone
who understands?
I already did that.
That's what took me so long.
That card hasn't been
valid for over a year.
Do you have any
other kind of insurance?
A DSS card?
Uh-uh. Why is she...
Let her handle it.
Peggy needs to advocate
for herself sometimes.
I'm sorry, what is that?
Medicaid!
You do understand
what that is, don't you?
I have a right
not to be shouted at.
Nobody is shouting!
Well, a public broadcast
would be quieter.
Look, lady, nobody cares!
Before you can see a doctor
for non-emergency ailment,
we need to know
who is gonna be
responsible for the visit.
I am responsible
for the visit!
Uh-uh. I'll do the talking!
Here's $100 down-payment.
Now. please,
may I see a doctor?
Excuse me, don't you think
you're being a little...
Little like a bitch!
Okay, look, here's how
it's gonna go, sister girl.
This is our friend here
and her mouth hurts!
So from here and now, we'll
just do the talking for her.
Now, we both know
how this works so get out
those special papers,
the ones for people
who can't pay,
we both know what they are.
And you really
need to stop acting
like her bill is gonna come
out of your paycheck, okay?
So, let's get to work
so she can see a doctor
or me and my girl here,
are gonna turn this place out!
And you ain't heard loud till
I start shouting those "isms."
You know the ones.
Racism, ageism,
classism, um...
Professionalism,
which you certainly
get a failing grade on.
And you know I work here,
so I know people.
So, should we do this
in Spanish or English?
And do you wanna add anything,
since, you were supposed
to be doing all the talking?
Uh-uh. You got it covered.
I just don't like
people trying to talk
down to me, that's all.
Hey, look, I'm willing
to talk up to you,
whatever you need, baby-cakes,
but she's gonna see a doctor
and that's right about now.
Thanks, sweetie.
Thank you.
Girl, I know you're tired.
It's past midnight.
There's no sense in waking
the kids up now, we'll just
get them in the morning.
Why don't you go on up and
I'll get Peggy settled in.
You sure?
Girl, you have a husband
waiting on you.
Avon and I ain't got
a soul waiting on us.
Do we, Avon?
PEGGY: Uh-uh.
I think I like the
sound of that.
Having a husband
waiting on me.
Oh! It stinks like
liquor in here!
So damn dark.
What are you doing?
You don't think I know
What are you talking about?
You've been cheating
on me, huh?
Huh
Do you know what
time it is? It's 12:30!
I know what I think!
You cheating on me!
OCEAN: Once again, I ignored
the writing on the wall.
Traded my heart
for so little in return.
And once again,
I let the devil fool me.
Mom, what are you doing?
Auntie Ocean, it is 6:00 AM!
The hardest conversation
a mother ever has to
have with her kids.
Is explaining away
her own failures.
I changed the locks.
So if Senior comes by,
do not let him in.
I don't care what he says.
What if he's not drinking?
You mean he can't
come in his own house?
This is my house!
Maybe that's the problem!
Okay, see, today
is not the day to mess
with me, you understand?
As a matter of fact,
I don't want to see nobody!
Mama, does is hurt?
Why'd you let him come
and live with us if
he'd done this before?
He's your father, Sammy.
What happened between
me and Senior is, um,
grown folks business.
But I know that he
loves you very much!
How can you say that?
If he beats you, how can
you say he loves me?
But why did he hit you?
That's what I wanna know.
He's never raised
a hand to any of us.
And we're kids.
You must've said
or done something.
I don't care what
I say or what I do.
No man is allowed
to lay hands on you, Trina.
That's not true.
Every man that has laid hands
on my mama did it because
she wanted him to.
A woman can make a man hit her
without speaking a word, okay?
For some children,
you need a magic eraser.
To erase every bad memory,
every violent event,
every bad excuse.
The ones some adult gave
them or the ones they
made up themselves
to excuse the inexcusable.
J.J., you're just being
stubborn. I'm not gonna
be gone for long.
It's just that your daddy
and I have some things
that we need to talk about.
Like, we might be
getting back together.
Would you like that, sweetie?
But I thought that
you and Mike were
starting to talk again.
We do. It's complicated.
But you know
your mama loves you.
No, you don't! At least when
Sophie was here you actually
stayed at home sometimes.
J.J...
You always do everything
for her and nothing for me.
That is not true!
Hey, little man!
Hey, sexy thing.
I can always tell when you
get dressed up just for me.
So, you ready?
What if we bring J.J. with
us so that we can get
a bite to eat together?
And then we'll just drop
him back off at Ocean's
so we could have our talk.
Don't spend it all
in one place, little man.
Come on, Lupe,
let's get out of here.
Maybe I don't want your money.
It's probably stolen anyway.
That's my boy!
Don't ever back down
from anybody, not even me.
Come on, Lupe.
Let's get out of here.
We really had a good day.
Yeah, you sure
are happy today.
Closest to perfection
as one could get.
I've got the bestest,
smartest children in
the whole wide world
and I did something...
Uncle Bo!
Oh!
OCEAN: No!
Girl, I'm glad you
don't play cards.
Because I look at your face
and see everything you
ever thought to think.
We all die of something,
might as well be diabetes.
Maybe I should
get you to emergency.
I ain't going nowhere
except to sleep on this couch.
Give me some of that
Ocean sugar so I can dream
me some sweet dreams.
I stink, huh?
My breath stinks,
my leg stinks.
I'm just a stinking
son of a bitch.
I'll get cleaned up
after a little shut-eye.
Be back on that
train to righteousness.
What
No. No, I'm not scared.
I was just putting the
pillow behind your head.
Well, stop looking
at me like that.
Not like I'm disappointing
you all the time.
I'm your Uncle Bo.
At least I got that
son of a bitch out of here.
Uncle Bo took care of it.
Nobody messes with mine.
If he stayed, no telling
what he would've done.
Uncle Bo took care of it.
Bo take care of his.
Yes, Uncle Bo,
you took care of it.
You take care of everything.
Okay. Okay.
I don't want to scare mine.
This diabetes
keeps me so dehydrated!
You got a beer or something?
OCEAN: Sometimes God
reminds you all is not lost.
Because if you have
a covenant with him,
to borrow Lupe's words,
there's always a snap-back.
An opportunity to change.
To start over.
To manage your fear.
And of course, prayer
is the best weapon we have.
Always.
If we ever hope to silence our
silent screams of despair.
You're two months behind
on your rent and I can't hold
the landlord off any longer!
And I'm not gonna
let him fire me!
Well, it's just that Ian's
medicine is so expensive.
I tried taking him off of it,
he was totally out of control.
Maybe next month I can...
You don't have another month!
He's gonna evict you.
He's gonna put
your stuff on the curb.
Peggy, you can't sleep
all day and bake all night,
pretending that things are
somehow gonna be different.
You gotta do
something different.
What about assistance?
No one in my family's
ever been on welfare!
Well, now the rich
are the poor.
I'm not poor.
Okay, you're not poor.
You just need a little help.
What about food stamps?
We have food!
Maybe welfare
is for you and your...
What you were gonna
say was welfare was best
for me and my people.
Look around you, Peggy.
You're my people now.
Actually, the color
of welfare has
always been white.
It's just the way
the economy is going,
it's getting painted
whiter by the minute.
Come here.
Oh! I'm scared for
you to answer that.
What is it, Trina?
Girl, stop screaming
in the phone!
I can't understand you!
Auntie Ocean, I didn't
know what to do!
I called Senior and
he came here right away.
All of us kids,
we were so spooked.
It was scary.
Uncle Bo was having seizures!
He was bleeding and
he was screaming!
Mom, it was so scary.
If Dad hadn't been here...
Sam, I'm always gonna be here
for you, no matter what happen
between me and your mama.
Mom, are you okay?
Dad and I had a talk.
And I understand where
he's coming from now.
It's like what you said,
when he's drunk
he can't help himself.
Mom!
I thought I told you to
take that back to the store.
But, Auntie, Senior let me
have it because you said
you didn't want it.
Oh, my God, man!
She's a baby. A baby!
How could I be so stupid?
When all you wanted
to do was just...
Uh-uh. Look,
I just gave her this dress.
Why you tripping?
I just came over here to talk!
Talk? Ain't nothing for
us to talk about. Get out!
Now!
You disgust me.
Auntie, Senior said
he was sorry.
Shut it up!
You are a kid and
you should be a kid!
Yeah, she got a woman body.
But this is a kid. My kid!
And I'll go through hell
and high water to protect
her from anybody. Now get out!
Look, Mama, he said he
wasn't gonna drink anymore.
I'm not, Ocean. I haven't
had one drink since I left.
I even apologized to Uncle Bo.
He promised.
His promises
ain't worth a dime.
You're always saying
you gotta forgive.
Son, there's one thing you
don't know about your mama.
She don't always
practice what she preaches.
Oh, okay, you want a sermon?
Is that what you need?
Okay, here you go.
I deserve better!
My kids deserve better!
And it don't
include you, ever.
Now get out!
I'm gonna count to three.
And then I'm gonna
call the police.
Okay.
Come here, baby.
Please don't go!
Mama, you don't have
to be so mean to Daddy!
I love you, baby.
I tried, Sammy.
Get out!
Man, shut the hell up!
You can't keep me
from seeing my kids, Ocean.
I'm gonna see them
with or without you.
I'll see you in hell first.
Yeah, I think we
can arrange that.
One...
Two...
What else I don't know, Trina?
All he did
was give me a few
gifts, Auntie Ocean.
Nothing else.
OCEAN: Some nights, all
I can do is ask God why.
What did I do to
deserve any of it?
Today was supposed
to be my day.
Got started out
with so much promise.
And then it deteriorated
into a lot of "what ifs."
What if I had stayed home?
Not left Uncle Bo alone.
What if I had never let Senior
come back in the first place?
But at some point I guess
the "what ifs" are nothing
but an opportunity
to renew your
faith and possibility.
I'm Ocean Jackson, and this
is the diary of a single mom
trying to get ahead in a world
trying to hold her under.