No, don't put me on hold.
How... You're the third person
I've spoken to.
Today, by the way.
I have water.
I don't have hot water, do you
understand there's a difference?
Can you get me some sugar,
honey?
- Okay, great.
- Thank you.
Then help me, please.
I had icicles in my hair
this morning.
Do you know what that's like?
No...
Oh! Oh! Oh!
- Oh, hey, are you okay?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry. Come on.
- Daniel!
Tomorrow, please.
Thank you.
Oh.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's...
Apologize to this nice lady.
Boys will be boys.
It's fine, really.
No, it's not.
Daniel, say you're sorry. Now.
Or do you wanna end up
on the naughty list?
I'm sorry I ran into you.
That naughty or nice list
really works, huh?
- What's she talking about?
- Nothing, honey.
I'll be right back.
I'm guessing by your lack
of stains, sweatpants,
and bloodshot eyes,
you don't have children.
No, I don't.
You probably popped right up
after eight hours of sleep,
took a nice, long, hot shower...
Actually, no.
My hot water heater's all...
Leisurely got dressed,
applied your perfect makeup
while watching
Good Morning America.
- That is so not my life.
- I love my children,
but parenting
is all your nightmares combined.
The one trump card parents have
is that kids know
Santa keeps a list.
So, yes,
the naughty or nice list
still works.
The world is a better place
because of it.
What?
Enjoy. Next.
Hi, can I get
a large vanilla latte
with a shot...
Make it three shots of espresso,
and a mocha capp to go?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
$7.75, please.
Thanks.
[chuckles]
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
Krissy Kringle?
Like Kris Kringle?
[laughs]
That's awesome.
You want some milk and cookies
to go with your latte?
I can get you some carrot sticks
for your reindeer.
Do you think any of that
is original?
[swipes card]
[beep]
Sorry, St. Nick.
Credit card's been declined.
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
Well, I don't have cash.
Here's...
Ah.
I need another quarter.
Come on.
Thanks, kid.
You're off the naughty list.
[cash register opens]
- [Krissy] Morning, Michaela.
- Morning.
- [Krissy] Hey, Jack.
- Hey.
- [Krissy] Hello.
- Hi.
Hi.
Everybody's a comedian.
Hey, there.
Hi. The usual.
Ah, thank you.
You're a lifesaver.
You look nice.
Oh.
Meeting a friend for lunch.
Does that say, "triple shot"?
- Hmm? Mm.
- Rough night?
Rough morning.
Jingle, jingle,
Miss Krissy Kringle.
And it continues.
She's heard them all, Philip.
Run along, now.
Helen needs to see you
in her office ASAP.
Get your sleigh bells
over there.
- Thank you, Philip. Bye-bye.
- Okay.
Oh, how do I look?
Like promotion material?
I don't have
any hot water at my house,
so I'm a mess.
You look great.
You really think
you're gonna get it?
I don't know.
I mean, I've brought in three
new accounts in the last month,
and the rumor is
they're gonna hire from within.
And two days ago,
Helen smiled at me
in the bathroom.
No teeth, but the corners
of her mouth did go up.
Go get it, girl.
[Krissy sighs]
[tense music plays]
[tapping keys]
[exhales]
Miss Kringle.
Yes.
We're setting you free today.
You can pick up your final check
from accounting.
Thank you so much for your work.
Have a good holiday.
[tapping keys]
I'm sorry, did you just fire me?
We released you, yes.
Released me.
Like an animal into the wild.
Why?
Cutbacks.
- Cutbacks?
- That's it.
Because I have been bringing in
new clients every month.
I thought
I was getting a promotion.
Oh.
No.
No, you know what?
You just... You can't... You...
You... You should know that...
You are going
on the naughty list.
[scoffs]
- Fired?
- Released.
Returning me
to my natural habitat.
Unemployed and going nowhere.
I thought this was it, you know?
I thought this was a place I was
gonna make a name for myself.
I'm clever-ish
and funny and smart, right?
Don't say anything
if you don't agree.
I agree.
God, and right before Christmas.
I knew her heart
was made of ice,
but this is really cold.
I know.
Well...
I let her have it.
Oh, my God.
Tell me what you said.
Told her she was rude
and oblivious and just angry.
And then I said a bunch of stuff
I can't even repeat.
You did not.
What I actually said
was more like,
"You're gonna end up
on Santa's naughty list."
[chuckles]
"Naughty" what?
She's intimidating,
and I'm weak.
I'm gonna die in the wild.
Maybe you should go back in
and give her a time-out as well.
Ha.
You know what?
They take all our best ideas,
we never get a raise or a bonus,
and nobody gets promoted.
Maybe this is a good thing.
I mean,
what am I supposed to do?
I literally had to borrow change
from a seven-year-old today.
Lance is making money.
I mean, he's almost
a partner by now, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, but I'm not
gonna take money from him
until we're married.
It's been six years.
I mean, how long
should a girl have to wait?
Apparently six years.
Ah, Jill,
my mom's gonna freak out.
I mean, now I'm unmarried
and unemployed.
I know this seems
terrible right now, Krissy.
You'll land on your feet.
Give me a call, and we'll
grab drinks or something.
Thanks, Jill.
[sad music plays]
[slow Christmas music plays]
[Krissy sighs]
I know, terrible.
[Krissy puffs]
[Krissy grunts]
[grunts]
Whoop!
[mysterious music plays]
Hmm.
That's weird.
[girl] Dear Santa,
thank you for visiting me
in the hospital.
You forgot this.
I know
it's important for your job.
Merry Christmas.
Your friend, Katie.
Okay.
[knocking on the door]
Hi, sweetheart.
Hi.
Sorry about your job.
I tried to get out earlier.
Mm, it's okay.
I just didn't wanna go
to Mom and Dad's
for dinner by myself.
I can hear the lecture already.
Don't tell them.
[laughs]
You know nothing gets past her.
- She's like a mind reader.
- Yeah.
Just go with the don't ask,
don't tell policy
and hope
she's having an off night.
Yeah.
We make it to dessert
without any mention of your job,
you'll be home free.
[Krissy chuckles]
[Lance chuckles]
[magical music plays]
Wow. Hologram reindeer.
Debbie's really going all out
this year for the title.
That's impressive.
She's not taking any chances.
She tried to get real reindeer.
Apparently,
they require a permit.
You know, Miss Kringle,
you should really
get into the spirit.
I'm getting a wreath.
- A wreath.
You're a Kringle.
Be better than a wreath.
Stop it. Everyone thinks
I work with elves.
It's horrible.
I'm just saying...
It fits my mood.
- Oh, poor baby.
- [Krissy chuckles]
[Christmas music plays]
Hello!
Mom? Dad?
- Ho...
- Ho!
Ho!
- Oh, kill me now.
- Just get to dessert.
- Hey.
- Hi, Daddy.
- Hi, darling.
- Hi, Mama. How are you?
- Ah, pumpkin, I presume.
- Mm.
Carol, I love your sweater.
Is it new?
Oh, thanks. I made it myself.
I made one for Krissy too,
but she hasn't worn it yet.
Oh, come on, come on.
Food's ready.
Yeah, yeah, come.
You guys just wanna start
with dessert?
[chuckles]
[both chuckle]
[Lance] Thank you, Carol.
Thanks, Mom. That was wonderful.
Thank your dad.
He did most of the cooking.
And now the reason
we have a main course
in the first place.
- No sugar.
- It's the holidays.
Every day is a holiday to you.
Well, what do you expect?
I'm a Kringle.
See, that wasn't so bad.
- We're almost there.
- You're almost there.
Portion control.
Your portion control
would starve a mouse.
[sighs]
- Here.
- Thank you.
I assume
the other one didn't fit,
so this one's a little looser.
- Try it on.
- Yay, bigger.
I'll try it on at home.
In private.
I really wish you'd get
into the Christmas spirit,
sweetheart.
Of course you do.
It's why you named me
Krissy Kringle.
Oh, come on, now.
Everyone always
thinks that's adorable.
- Daily.
- You were named after a legend.
Mother Teresa is a legend.
We could be actual descendants,
for all you know.
Yeah, don't be such a sourpuss.
You're the one who chose
to live on Candy Cane Lane.
No, no, no, they voted
to change the name
to Candy Cane Lane
after I moved in
because of this
holiday house contest.
Now every December, I can't
even open my front door.
You know, I think
it's so sweet that kids
still mail their letters
to Santa Claus.
Sure, it's adorable.
Except all those letters
end up at my house.
Well, you could always
sell the place.
I can't, I'm totally upside-down
like everything else in my life.
What's the matter?
Hmm?
Nothing.
You got fired.
What? How does she do that?
- It's a gift.
- It's a curse.
Wait, wait, wait.
I thought
you were getting a promotion.
You've been talking
about this for weeks.
- [Carol] Yeah, what happened?
- I don't even know.
She said it was cutbacks.
But that doesn't make any sense
'cause there's still
a position open.
Gosh, just before Christmas.
What are you gonna do for a job?
I don't know.
I mean, look,
I'll figure it out. It's fine.
Let's just talk
about something else.
I'm gonna help her out
till she gets on her feet.
You are not gonna help me out.
I am an independent woman,
I can handle myself.
You know, this really
wouldn't be an issue
- if you two were married.
- Mom. Really?
Well, you know, I would like
to plan my daughter's wedding.
Is that so wrong?
It is not 1950.
Women have other priorities
than getting married.
It will happen when it happens.
Hmm.
And I am not going
to take "no" for an answer.
No.
Okay.
[Krissy chuckles]
Where is she going?
She won't take "no"
for an answer.
I promise you. Now, look.
Your independence is not gonna
pay the mortgage or buy gas
or... or... or put food
on the table.
You should've never bought
that house.
Wait, you are the one
that told me to buy that house.
You said, "Krissy, now is the time to buy,"
and she is the mind reader
in the family.
How come she didn't predict
the crash?
Well, she does...
Doesn't see everything. Shh.
You said if we got to the pie,
we'd be home free.
- We should have skipped dessert.
- Mm.
Okay.
What is this now?
[Carol] That is your next job.
It's only temporary,
but it'll do
till something better
comes along.
Wrapping presents at the mall.
- I'm not doing this.
- [Carol] It's too late.
I already texted Gloria.
Her grandson is the manager.
I told him you would be there
at 9:00 a.m. tomorrow morning.
Mom!
Hey, come on, it's
the perfect job for a Kringle.
Okay, you understand
in other countries,
they force prisoners
to wrap presents.
It's a form of torture. No!
Don't be so dramatic.
I'm sure that Lance agrees
with me, don't you, honey?
Don't.
[chuckles]
And you get to wear
a cute little elf costume.
Oh, that
is definitely not happening.
I think elves earn
an extra 20 bucks a day.
Seriously?
Huh.
Do you wanna come inside and
watch an old movie or something?
[Lance sighs]
I can't.
I have a pile of research.
Big deposition tomorrow.
Sure.
It's okay, it's fine.
Don't be mad.
I'm an associate.
It won't be like this forever,
I promise.
So why were you so quiet
when my mom asked
about us getting married?
[Lance] So that's really
why you're upset.
Because I didn't jump up
and tell your mom
that she has a wedding to plan.
Your silence was deafening.
I don't talk
about weddings, Krissy,
because you hate them.
- What?
- You...
The overcooked steak,
the Chicken Dance,
that Shout song.
Everybody hates that stuff!
My wedding's
not gonna be like that.
It is gonna be different, okay?
Most girls wanna get married
so they can have
their own personal prom.
I just...
Ugh,
I just want a new last name.
So you're using me.
Well, yeah.
[chuckles]
I love you, Krissy Kringle.
Come here.
I need you to.
Good night.
Debbie?
Wh...
What are you doing?
Um, just
some last-minute decorating.
Oh...
Candy canes.
It's not really your theme
this year.
Yeah, I know, right?
No, these won't...
These won't work at all.
You know...
A porch light doesn't count
as a decoration.
It's a shame that someone
with such a festive last name
is such a grinch.
This is Candy Cane Lane.
Show some respect!
It was not Candy Cane Lane
when I moved in, okay?
You are the nightmare
before Christmas,
Krissy Kringle!
Yes, you are.
[sighs]
[shower running]
[Krissy] Oh!
Oh.
[shower running]
Oh, cold. Oh.
Oh!
[mysterious music plays]
[playful music plays]
Aw.
[cell phone rings]
Hello?
[plumber] Yeah, this
is the plumber.
This Krissy Kringle?
This is she.
[plumber]
That's your real name?
Yes.
[plumber] Krissy Kringle.
Candy Cane Lane.
Yes, Krissy Kringle,
who lives on Candy Cane Lane.
[rustling]
[plumber] Ma'am, you there?
Oh. Oh!
Oh.
[tinkling]
"Loses patience with plumber"?
"Opens other people's mail."
Hmm.
Krissy Kringle.
[tinkling]
[pants]
[cell phone rings]
- Hello?
- [plumber] Hello.
Miss Kringle?
Who is this?
Dean Patterson,
Patterson Plumbing.
We were cut off.
Dean Patterson, right.
I'm sorry.
[plumber] Yeah, look,
uh, Miss Kringle,
I'm... I'm sorry,
but my truck broke down.
I'm not gonna be able to fix
that water heater today.
[Krissy] "Lies to customer
about truck breaking down."
[plumber] What?
What was that?
Are you in your pajamas,
drinking coffee?
[plumber] What?
What are you talking about?
- Plaid pajamas?
- [plumber] No. I'm serious.
I'm sitting here
waiting for a tow right now.
- You're lying.
- [plumber] No. No, I'm not.
Yes. Yes, you are.
You're on your couch,
aren't you? Admit it.
[plumber]
Okay, okay, I'm sorry.
I had a late night, I'm
going through some stuff.
- I'll be... I'll be there.
- Okay. Okay.
The water heater's out back.
- And don't overcharge me.
- [plumber] I won't. I won't.
Or I'll know.
[upbeat Christmas music plays]
[man with Australian accent]
Yeah, that's it.
All right, you take point.
You gotta slay
the minotaur first,
then we get to the wizard.
Hi.
[video game sounds]
Oh, now I'm surrounded.
Hi. I'm Krissy.
Joe, Chen, hold on.
You're 15 minutes late.
I know, I'm sorry. It was, um...
It was a strange morning.
I mean, like, beyond strange.
I'm just...
I'm in a bit of a fog today.
Well, Grams said
you're gonna be an elf.
Yeah.
Is your last name
really Kringle?
Yup.
Well, then you've found
your calling, mate.
[chuckles]
Put this on, and meet me
in Santa's workshop.
Oh, wow. Where is that, exactly?
There's signs everywhere.
[clatter]
Are you...
Um...
- Okay...
- God!
[chuckles]
What, you think I like
all these extra decorations
in my office?
Is there no place else
to put all this junk
in the entire mall?
I'm the only one that's gotta
walk through this minefield
because, hey,
Justin won't care, will he?
Well, I do care.
For goo...
[grunts]
[clatter]
[train whistle blowing]
Hey.
["We Wish You A Merry Christmas" playing]
Hey. Come on, come on.
Pick it up.
Marco, meet Krissy Kringle.
Wow. You got a stage name
and everything.
It's my real name.
Sorry, I thought
you were kidding.
Well, welcome
to the fun factory.
Hey, keep it cheery, mate.
Or I'll make you wear the hat.
All right, Marco
will show you the ropes.
For now, start wrapping.
Let's go.
What's his story?
Well, to start with, he speaks
with an Australian accent,
yet he is not Australian.
- Shall I go on?
- What? Yes, please.
Yeah, rumor has it he watches
Crocodile Dundee every night
and then on weekends
goes on walkabout.
- Amazing.
- Yeah.
Name a complex, he's got it.
So how come the ladies
don't have to wear elf costumes?
That is a fair question.
The blue hairs
work at the senior center,
so they don't get to be
as fashionable as we are.
Hey, Ruth. Hey, Phyllis.
How's it going?
They can't hear me.
Uh, oh, did he tell you
that the elves
have to work at Santa's
photo gallery as well?
- What?
- Yup.
Put on a happy face.
You're gonna need it.
No, no, I'm not trained
to work the photo gallery.
Oh.
Okay, well, question.
Do you know
what this word means?
- Yeah.
- Great.
And...
Can you do this?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, wait for it.
And then back again.
Got it.
Guess what.
You just got trained.
[laughs]
Merry Christmas.
Got another load for the elves.
What?
I thought it was break time.
You were 15 minutes late.
That was your break.
Another hour and a half
till lunch.
What is this, Santa's workshop
or Santa's sweatshop?
You know what?
Let's get out of here.
He's gonna be trying
to level up for the next hour.
Let's go. Come on. Let's go.
Let's go.
Honestly,
I thought my old boss was bad.
I went from Helen of Troy
to a Napoleonic elf.
- Who's also a liar and a cheat.
- What are you talking about?
All right, well,
the wrapping station
is sponsored
by the senior center.
Uh-huh.
Justin's grandma
is the chairwoman,
so that's how he got his job.
Well, I figured
it wasn't based on merit.
Okay, but they used to give
a petty cash fund
for the managers to buy snacks
and drinks for the staff.
- That's sweet.
- Right?
- So where are the snacks?
- Exactly.
Ever since Justin took over,
he's like,
"Oh, sorry, mate.
We stopped doing it.
You know how it is."
He throws around
the word "recession"
like he knows what it means.
So you're saying he's stealing.
I think so.
But I can't prove it,
so what is an elf to do?
I got bills to pay
just like everybody else.
Don't wanna go
rocking the sleigh.
["Jingle Bells" playing]
Stop it.
Stop.
[gasps]
Ow!
A kitten hugging a puppy?
That's hilarious, Ruth.
And, Phyllis, I heard
you took second place
at the gin rummy tournament
last weekend.
Congratulations.
That's fantastic.
Ugh.
Excuse me, ladies. One second.
Are you kidding me?
I've seen five-year-olds
wrap better.
Let me explain.
Right, you fold it straight...
One piece of tape.
You use
more than one piece of tape,
you're doing it wrong.
Keep doing it wrong,
and you're fired.
Understand?
Or should I speak slower?
Good.
Keep up the Christmas cheer.
[Marco sighs]
Hat on!
[sighs]
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
Krissy!
Justin Reid.
[tinkling]
"Plays video games at work."
"Sleeps at his desk."
[tinkling]
Check...
mate.
[video game sounds]
Please go back to the workshop.
Okay.
Hey, um, sorry.
Is this about that thing
that I told you about?
'Cause that's
just between you and me.
- It's okay. Where's the money?
- Oh.
- What is this, a shakedown?
- Just...
The petty cash
from the senior center.
I told you,
cutbacks and recession.
Oh. You're sure about that?
Wait, what...
[Krissy gasps]
Justin.
You thief!
What would Grams think, Justin?
[without an accent]
Don't tell Grams.
If she finds out,
she'll cut me off. Please.
I'll do whatever you want.
It's okay,
we're not gonna say anything
on three conditions.
One, you are gonna buy
the staff snacks.
And lunch
for the rest of the week.
Yeah, and that means
actual food.
Something that's not
gonna make us diabetic.
Two...
Show some respect.
Stop demeaning everyone.
I do that?
- A lot.
- [Krissy] Three...
You're gonna let me borrow all
these extra holiday decorations.
You're gonna take all
of this stuff out of here?
No, no, mate.
You are.
My address is right here.
Forget that.
I mean, it's cool.
We can call Grams.
Yeah, we could
totally call Grams.
She's really good friends
with my mom.
No, no, no, fine. Fine. You win.
Uh, Marco,
order lunch for everyone.
With pleasure.
Oh.
There you go. That's better.
[sighs]
That was sick!
It really was fun
watching him grovel.
How did you know
where the money would be?
Are you psychic or something?
No, no, I had some help.
Well,
tell me about it over lunch.
Oh, I have to meet my boyfriend.
He's, um... where's...
He's actually not gonna make it.
- Oh.
- Figures.
Hey, it's all right, look,
you know
what'll never stand you up?
A sandwich, my treat. Come on.
Ah, I still can't believe
you called him out like that.
And blackmailed him.
You should consider politics.
We'll see how my yard
turns out, right?
Yeah, right?
Uh, I need a Turkey,
no Mayo, on wheat.
I'll get a veggie wrap,
gluten free.
Excuse me, you guys
not go to kindergarten?
Don't know how a line works?
- We were next.
- Oh, no!
We're not gonna get anything
in our stockings this year.
Wait, so you actually walk
around in public like that?
Aren't you taking the whole
holiday spirit a little too far?
Hmm, aren't you taking
your makeup a little bit too...
Psst.
Save our spots.
I'll be right back.
I have to get a picture of this.
- Putting this one on Facebook.
- [Marco] Okay, stop.
Stop. No, stop.
[tinkling]
- [Tiffany] Smile.
- [Marco] No. Okay, that's...
Do... Do not tag me.
[cell phone camera clicks]
[Tiffany] It's for Twitter.
Hi, Tiffany, Brittany.
A little holiday spirit
for you guys.
Brittany, stop telling everyone
Tiffany's bulimic. She's not.
- And, Tiffany...
- What?
Stop texting Brittany's
boyfriend she's cheating on him.
That's rude.
Why would you do that?
I would never
do something like that.
I can't believe you told
people I was bulimic.
- You know I'm not anymore.
- I didn't say that!
Happy holidays!
It may have slipped out
a long time ago.
What do you mean, "slipped out"?
Things don't slip out.
Okay, what is going on here,
all right?
Are you... Are you
like a witch or something?
It's a gift.
Hi. We're next.
Spill it.
Don't tell me it's a gift.
I wrap gifts.
This is not a gift, all right?
This is like voodoo
or something.
You're gonna think I'm insane.
Don't make me use
drastic measures.
I don't even know
what it is for sure.
All right, don't think
that I haven't learned
some tactics
from these kids, all right?
I have seen moms
break in seconds.
- I can break you!
- Fine.
I will tell you.
But you are the only person,
do you understand?
'Cause if anybody else
finds out,
I will end up in the loony bin.
Okay, I'm like Fort Knox,
I promise.
[man] Number seven, please.
[bell rings]
What is this,
your book of spells?
Sort of.
Can I ask you an honest
and direct question?
As opposed to a deceitful
and ambiguous one? Proceed.
- That's funny.
- Thank you.
Do you think there is
a real naughty or nice list?
The naughty or nice list.
Every year, because of my name
and the street I live on,
I get thousands of letters
intended
for the real Kris Kringle.
Right.
I'm sorry, back it up.
The real Kris Kringle?
Santa Claus.
Yes, I got the connection.
So just for argument's sake,
let's say
he really is watching us,
and he really does know
whether or not
we've been naughty or nice.
- I know how it sounds.
- Do you?
Good. No, hey,
sounds perfectly reasonable.
Look, I do believe that somebody
is watching over us
and all that,
but not Santa Claus,
'cause I was raised catholic.
Can you just go with me here?
[laughing] I'm trying.
What if there is a little bit
of magic this time of year?
And what if the list is real,
and it's not just this thing
that parents use
to threaten
their kids to behave?
And what if it was
accidentally sent to me?
Those are a lot of "what ifs."
And you thought I wouldn't
put you in the loony bin?
- Okay.
- Check this out.
All right.
Marco Webb.
[tinkling]
"Told girlfriend he was sick,
then went to a sports bar"?
How does it know that?
Shh, sit down.
And that... That is private.
How...
So crazy,
but this might be
the real naughty or nice list.
Who else would have
a book like this?
The CIA.
'Cause they care that you lied
to your girlfriend.
Hey, I am
a pretty important guy,
so maybe.
All right, this just appeared
on your doorstep?
- Yeah.
- And have...
Have you told anybody else?
No, I don't want anyone...
You know,
let's make that two, to go.
- [Marco] What's the matter?
- Oh, God.
It's my old boss and Jill.
- [man] That'll be $5.50.
- Okay, thank you.
Which one is Jill?
Is she foxy blue,
or the ice queen?
Shh!
Just tell me when they're gone.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
[gasps]
Oh, and she's looking at me.
Are they gone?
And we're clear.
What was that about?
"Foxy blue" is Jill.
I worked with her at my old job
at an advertising agency.
Wow, you went
from ad exec to elf.
That is a letdown.
I got fired, and now Jill is
coffee buddies with the boss.
Something's not right
about that.
Whoa, whoa. What are you doing?
You can't just wield that thing.
Jill Rhodes.
Or maybe you can.
[tinkling]
"Stole promotion
from Krissy Kringle."
[man] Number eight, please.
That backstabbing...
[bell rings]
All right, let's wrap this up
before you go all Vesuvius on us
and cover us in ash.
Can we take these to go?
Jill was my mentor.
And, I mean, I thought
she was my friend.
What do I know?
You two ever
go shopping together?
No.
Not a friend.
You know what? You're right.
She wasn't my friend,
she stole my ideas,
she passed them off as her own,
she told Helen
I was hitting on her husband.
That's insane. He's, like, 50.
Wait, so you knew him, then.
Yeah, we talked
about reality television
at company parties.
Well, that can get passionate.
Especially if they're about any
of the Real Housewives.
[chuckles]
She betrayed me.
I'm gonna go in there on Monday
and just tell them everything.
Tell them what, exactly?
That you found
Santa's naughty or nice list?
They'll have you committed.
And then what happens
to the book
if she gets her hands on it?
Well, I can't just
let her get away with it.
That's fine, but we gotta
be methodical about this.
All right, now,
probably got a line of kids
waiting to see Santa.
Let's deal with that,
then we'll get back
to "Operation Kill Jill" later.
All right? Let's go. Let's go.
And we'll go.
[soft Christmas music plays]
Unbelievable.
[chuckles]
Oh, gold star, Justin.
Debbie. Hi.
What do you think?
Compliments
the porch light, huh?
[Debbie] Very nice.
I love this little family
of snowmen! They're so cute!
Do you think I have a chance
of winning
the holiday house contest?
Well, it's nice not to have
a black hole on the street.
I'm sure
that's worth some merit.
Hmm.
I don't know,
I think I've got a real shot.
When do we vote?
Check your newsletter.
Huh.
Excellent.
[Lance] You've
reached Lance Leigh.
Leave me a message.
[beep]
Hey, Mr. Attorney.
I got your flowers. Thank you.
You're off the hook this time.
But call me, okay?
There's, um,
some crazy stuff going on.
I just wanna talk
to you about it.
I think.
[sighs]
- [sighs]
- [Jill] Hi, this is Jill.
Leave me a message if you dare.
I'll call you back if I care.
[Jill chuckles]
[beep]
Hey, Jill, it's Krissy,
your great, great friend.
Um, just wanting to get
those drinks
that we talked about.
So call me back. I can't wait.
Bye.
[mysterious music plays]
Debbie O'Brien.
[tinkling]
That little weasel.
Excellent.
[neighbors talking
indistinctively]
Hey.
Wow!
What is this winter wonderland?
This is unbelievable.
- I know, right?
- Justin really did a good job.
That Grams must be
a real gravy train.
Well, I just hope it's enough
to beat my neighbor Debbie
over here.
I'm calling out
that kleptomaniac tonight.
All right.
Thank you for coming,
by the way.
Ah, please.
This is better than shark week.
[both chuckle]
This is quite the turnout.
[Krissy] We're entering
the lion's den.
Ooh, maybe they got cake pops.
I'll be right back.
Marco.
Krissy!
I love what you did
to your house.
Oh.
Everyone is talking
about how beautiful it is.
I posted it on Pinterest,
and so far it has gotten
over 2,000 repins!
- Wow.
- It's a sensation!
Oh, yeah, thank you.
Okay, let's everyone
take our seats.
The meeting is about to begin.
Thank you.
They've got mini cupcakes.
Don't leave me alone
with these people again.
[laughs]
[bells jingle]
- [Marco] What does that mean?
- [Krissy] I do not know.
Take your seats, everyone.
Welcome.
Welcome,
Candy Cane Lane neighbors.
As you know, tonight
we are going to select
the best holiday house.
But I think,
with the huge turnout
of spectators
that we've had every evening
that it is safe to say
that we are all winners.
[applause]
[Krissy clears her throat]
[whistles]
Debbie.
Krissy has a question.
Oh. Krissy, I apologize.
You never come to these things.
You can imagine
why I might overlook you.
Oh, I just... I didn't get
a chance to cast my ballot.
Oh, that's unfortunate.
The ballot box
was right over there
by the dessert table.
Oh, well.
That's why punctuality
is the politeness of kings.
Oh, come on, Debbie.
- Just let her vote.
- Yeah.
It's so nice to have her
join in this year.
[applause]
Let her vote! Come on!
- Come on!
- Thank you, guys.
All right, okay.
It is Christmas.
Please, bring
your ballot to my assistant.
By the way,
you can't vote for yourself.
Yes, Debbie. I'm well aware.
Okay.
This is so exciting, right?
Ahh!
Do we have the results?
Here we go.
Second runner-up,
winner of a 60-piece
Tupperware set...
Sixty.
With four votes,
Brenda and David Weir.
That's great. We won.
There's your Tupperware.
[Brenda chuckles]
Fantastic.
[mild applause]
You are gonna keep
a lot of things fresh.
And now the first runner-up,
and the winner
of a one-year membership
to the cheese
of the month club...
Yum.
[chuckles]
Oh.
With seven votes,
Krissy Kringle.
Hey!
[applause]
Huh. Huh, all right.
- Whoo!
- Congratulations, Krissy.
You see what happens
when you participate?
You win nice things.
Noted.
Okay, okay, okay.
And here's the moment
that we've all been waiting for.
The winner.
Oh, my goodness! It's me!
Oh!
With eight votes,
Debbie O'Brien.
Thank you.
Thank you all so much.
It's such an honor.
Hey, hey, let's give ourselves
a round of applause, huh?
'Cause when Debbie wins,
we all win, don't we?
[applause]
Thank you, Krissy.
Now, I don't wanna put
a damper on the festivities,
but I do have to raise
just a small, little concern.
I'm actually missing
some key pieces from my display.
Does anybody know
anything about that?
Well, kids like to play pranks
this time of year.
- Oh.
- No, no, no, she has a point.
I had a bunch
of my candy canes go missing.
Brenda, it is so funny
you would say that.
I saw Debbie
with an armful of candy canes
just a few nights ago,
walking across her lawn.
Krissy.
Is anybody else
missing anything?
One of my wise men
and a camel are MIA.
Yeah, and my North Pole gnomes
have... psh... vanished.
[Krissy] How about that?
Now, look, I don't wanna
jump to any conclusions,
but my gut is telling me
if we take a peek
in Debbie's shed,
we could probably
solve this mystery.
Wha... What?
To the backyard!
- [Debbie] No, no! No, no, no!
- [Brenda] Everybody, follow me!
- Oh, this is crazy.
- No, no, no!
No, no, everyone sit down.
What are you doing?
This is crazy! This is crazy!
Go, go! Come on!
[Debbie] This is ridiculous!
Come back here!
[Brenda] This way!
[Debbie] What are you doing?
[man] Definitely been missing.
[Brenda] Get ready, everybody!
Open the doors!
[all gasp]
[man] Oh, my gosh!
Holy Moly!
No, no, no! Wait, wait, wait!
It's not what you think.
I...
I was gonna give it all back.
Under the circumstances,
I propose we revote
for the best holiday house.
- Yeah, I agree.
- Wha...
All in favor of my house,
please raise your hands.
- She did a good job.
- Yeah.
All in favor of Krissy's house,
please raise your hands.
- Yeah.
- Whoo!
- Great this year.
- Come on!
Finally, Debbie's house.
[Brenda]
Yeah, I didn't think so.
Looks like you lost your title.
Congratulations, Krissy!
Whoo!
[applause]
Debbie,
you've disgraced yourself.
I am taking my candy canes
and my Tupperware back.
That I won, fair and square.
- Congratulations, Krissy.
- Oh, thanks.
[man] See my wise man
in there anywhere?
- I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
[man] Honey, grab that.
Grab that. That's ours.
- That's our... That's ours.
- [man 2] No, there's two.
There's two of them.
[sad music plays]
Well, that was
my first Christmas lynch mob.
Hmm.
I kept waiting for somebody
to yell, "kill the beast!"
What?
Oh, don't tell me you feel
sorry for her, do you?
I didn't have to humiliate her.
Ah, she humiliated herself.
- Great.
- Oh, don't tell me.
Lance is working late again.
It's none of my business,
but why do you keep
putting up with that?
It's not his fault.
He's trying to make partner.
He's just trying to make
a good impression.
It's just sometimes I wish
he'd try to make
a good impression on me.
So what's his deal?
He doesn't wanna get married
until his career
is where he wants it.
He says he's getting
a good bonus this year.
Like I care about that.
So do you ever think
about, you know,
using the list?
Like, to give you peace of mind.
If I do that,
that's like reading his emails.
Where's the trust?
Look, if it were me,
I'd wanna know.
I'm just saying.
Okay.
Good night.
[sighs]
Lance Leigh.
[pages rustle]
[tinkling]
[gasps]
Oh.
[tense music plays]
Hi, um, I'm looking for, uh...
He's a guy. He's here with...
Found him.
He lives!
Krissy. Is everything okay?
It was.
Till I found out you are lying,
cheating scum of the earth.
Excuse us.
You know what? They need
to know your true colors.
Especially you, Mrs. Harris.
If you're considering
making him partner,
you should know
his true colors, right?
- Krissy, stop it.
- [Krissy] I trusted you.
For six years,
I gave you everything,
and this is how you repay me?
By lying to me
and cheating on me?
What are you talking about?
All those "late nights"
you were working,
you were really with Jill,
weren't you?
Guilty or not?
Okay,
that is not what you think.
I knew it! You just admitted it.
It's guilty!
Krissy, my boss is here.
I know.
Ms. Harris, you're a lady.
I'm sure you understand, right?
[Ms. Harris] Oh!
[man] Are you kidding me?
[sighs]
Excuse me.
[Marco] Big smile.
That's a great one.
There you... Oh, even better.
There you go.
All right, what's a mouse eat?
That's right. Cheese.
Okay, all right.
One more, just for you.
Excellent. All right, good job.
Merry Christmas.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, hey, no.
Up, now.
That's not
how we do things here.
Did you hear me say "next"?
- I wanna see Santa.
- All right, great.
You're gonna see Santa
when it's your turn.
What's the difference?
That Santa's fake,
and you're too big to be an elf.
This is lame!
Excuse me?
I want you to know something.
Santa's helpers come in
all shapes and sizes.
And some of us are just trying
to make a living, okay?
Whatever, lady.
No, not "whatever."
I want you to know something.
Santa has eyes everywhere,
and nothing, I mean nothing,
goes unnoticed.
Do you understand?
Krissy.
It's fine. I got it.
He is watching and recording
every naughty thing you do.
And trust me, in your case,
it is a huge collection.
You're crazy.
- I'm crazy?
- [kids laugh]
Oh, that's funny, huh?
All right.
You think
you can just lie and cheat
and not be held accountable?
You're so wrong!
Because Santa knows all!
He's got a list.
And one day, you're gonna
wake up and think,
"Oh, I'm gonna get
this great present
for Christmas!"
But instead, you are gonna
be single and unemployed
and too weak and intimidated
to do anything about it!
Okay, all right!
All right. Here we go.
Her blood sugar's way down.
Where are your parents?
Come on, now. All right.
What was that?
I don't know, I don't know.
Oh, God, Marco, I'm sorry.
I lost it.
Yeah! That's a bit
of an understatement.
What happened?
I checked on Lance in the book.
He cheated on me with Jill.
Yeah.
I guess I would've lost it too.
Um...
Maybe not in front of Santa.
It started earlier in the day.
At Lance's business lunch.
It was stupid.
It was so stupid. I know that.
But I was just...
I was hurt, and I was furious.
Lance isn't that guy.
It's not like him.
I wish
I'd never opened the book.
[sad song plays]
And initial.
Thank you.
[sighs]
[reporter]
We'll bring youmore on
the story as it unfolds.
Everyone's a little disappointed
by the lack of snow
on the mountains this year,
but maybe now we know why it
hasn't been a white Christmas.
Things got pretty heated today
when one of Santa's helpers
had a meltdown at the mall.
Shoppers captured this footage
that went viral earlier today.
Not be held accountable?
You're wrong!
Because Santa knows all!
So one day, you think you're
gonna get a beautiful present,
but instead, you are gonna
be single and unemployed
and too weak and intimidated
to do anything about it!
Okay, here we go.
It's okay, all right.
Her blood sugar is...
Where are your parents?
You better not pout,
you better not cry.
This is one elf
who will soon find out why.
- [doorbell rings]
- [reporter] I'm Jane Lei...
Mom? Dad?
[both] Oh.
Your mom thought you could use
some more ice cream about now.
- Huh?
- [Carol] Hi.
How are you, dear?
You guys know, huh?
Of course we know, it's
already gone viral on YouTube.
Hey, this is about Lance,
isn't it?
She who knows everything.
Well, I...
Come on, tell us
what happened, sweetheart.
[Krissy] Oh, Daddy.
He's cheating on me.
With Jill,
that girl I told you about.
The girl that stabbed me
in the back
and got me fired
and took my job.
Sounds like
a Country-Western song.
Are... Are you sure about Lance?
I mean, it just
doesn't sound like him.
Well, let's say I have it
on very good authority.
Sweetheart, you know,
this would not be the first time
you've jumped to conclusions.
No, but I... Ugh.
And this affair is...
Is happening now?
It's ongoing?
I don't know.
Does it really matter when?
Could it have happened
maybe two summers ago?
When... When you took a break
to find yourself?
We were still together then.
Really?
Because I had a depressed boy
calling me twice a day
for over a month,
asking how to get you back.
He thought we were broken up?
May I ask where you're getting
all this information
about his alleged tryst?
Oh, I wanna tell you.
I wanna tell you so bad.
I can't, though.
In mom's hands,
it would be a loaded weapon.
Well, it sounds
like it already is.
I will just say
there's two sides to every coin.
You flip it over,
there's always another side.
She's right.
You're right.
- You're right.
- Mm.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey! Come on, it's the holidays.
- I'm right.
- What a gyp.
[Carol chuckles]
[playful music plays]
Lance Leigh.
[tinkling]
Oh, that's so sweet.
[Carol] I couldn't hear
what you said, honey.
[tinkling]
"Has never lied to Krissy Kringle."
[Krissy sobs]
Just one sec.
I'm sorry, honey,
what'd you say?
Just thank you.
[Carol] Oh, honey.
Oh.
This better be good.
We don't go on the clock
for another hour.
I have a plan to fix everything.
With Lance?
With everyone.
All right, I'm listening.
What does this say?
Is that a trick question?
Something like that.
Just tell me what it says.
- It says, "naughty or nice."
- Except it's not "or."
It's not one or the other.
There's two sides to the book.
Two totally different lists.
Meaning you only had
half the story.
I never looked at it
from the other side.
- The nice list.
- Yes.
I mean, nobody's perfect.
Just because
you're on the naughty list
doesn't mean you can't be
on the nice list
a whole lot more, right?
That's fair enough.
Lance wasn't lying.
He really was working
late nights.
What about
his little escapade with Jill?
Yeah.
They were together, barely.
Once.
When we were broken up.
What?
I missed that part.
Turns out I missed a lot
with everyone.
Even Jill?
The woman volunteers
at a convalescent home.
She probably steals
their social security checks.
Well, I know she stole my job.
Get this, she's been on payroll
at a rival firm,
giving them insider information,
so they can steal
Helen's clients.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
The plan is to cripple
Helen's company,
then buy her out,
and then Jill will become
a partner in the new firm.
And the book had all of this?
All of it, in great detail.
This baby...
Oh! Oh!
Oh, no.
Oh, oh, okay. No, I got it.
- Come on.
- [Marco] Oh.
Oh, this isn't happening.
Krissy Kringle.
Oh, no, no. Please.
Krissy Kringle!
Oh, I ruined it.
Okay, okay.
No, you can fix this.
How?
Listen, remember
when you had your little episode
in front of everyone,
and you said
that you were gonna end up
weak and intimidated?
That is not the Krissy
that I met here on day one.
That's because I had this.
No, that is just a crutch.
You've always had
that strength inside of you.
But I didn't have all the names
and information
I need to make my case.
Okay.
Well, it sounds
like you need a good lawyer.
Well, we know
Mr. Hennessy was innocent,
because he was
at a family reunion
the night of August the 18th.
[woman] Miss, you're not allowed
to be on the premises.
[Krissy] It's an emergency.
[Ms. Harris] So if we do
our job, we can get him home
for Christmas with his wife
and lovely daughters.
- Hi.
- Krissy.
What are you doing here?
Everyone, it's okay.
I come in peace.
I know that you hate me
right now,
but we really need to talk.
This is not the time or place.
Please, go home.
Should I call security?
- No.
- Krissy...
Lance, I was wrong.
I jumped to conclusions,
and if I'd looked
just a little bit closer,
I would have realized
that you were only with Jill
after we'd broken up.
I was crushed.
I wasn't exactly myself.
But Jill? Really?
No, no, no, I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
You are the most generous,
loving, kind man that I know.
And he's not a liar or a cheat.
In fact,
he's the exact opposite.
He's everything
we look for in a man,
including being
very kind to a woman
in the middle of a meltdown.
Wait, you're the elf
on the news.
It's not my finest hour.
[woman] Oh, that's her?
Lance, I love you.
And I'm sorry.
I should not have done
what I did.
Please forgive me.
You should go.
Can you at least
please come over tonight
so we can talk?
It's important.
I'm not gonna go
until you agree.
Fine.
But we are not
getting back together.
I'll come by
to pick up my things.
Thank you.
Debbie, hey!
Hi.
Look, I just wanna apologize.
It's a little late for that.
No, no, no. Come on.
You shouldn't have done
what you did,
but I was really wrong too.
[sighs]
Look, I know
that you are
a generous philanthropist
who donates a substantial
amount of money
to a lot of local charities.
That's supposed to be anonymous.
[Krissy] Candy Cane Lane...
I mean,
we'd just be an ordinary street
if it weren't for you.
You can't leave.
[sighs]
Do you know
where this tradition came from?
During World War II,
wives and mothers
would decorate a tree
as a beacon of hope
for their loved ones
who were away at war.
I didn't know that.
My grandfather died
in World War II.
So this was my way to give back,
a way for me to remember him.
I realize that I went too far.
And I know that's no excuse,
but I meant no harm.
Believe me, I have been
doing a lot of that lately.
Doesn't mean we can't fix
our mistakes, though, right?
Before you go,
come over for coffee.
Tomorrow, can we say,
like, three o'clock?
I'll try.
Sounds like a yes.
Okay.
So you saw it, then?
It was
on the evening news, Krissy.
Everybody saw it.
Well, okay, to be fair,
after the whole
restaurant thing,
I was pretty upset,
and it was the last straw.
I mean, I thought
you cheated on me.
We were broken up, right?
I thought you were
with somebody else in New York.
Lance, there's never been
anybody else.
I know you're mad.
And I would be too,
so it's totally understandable,
but this isn't about me anymore.
I am really, really trying
to do the right thing
and help someone else out.
And in order to do that,
I need a good lawyer.
Go ahead. You have my attention.
Jill is conspiring
with a rival agency
to take over Helen's company.
Everyone's gonna lose
their jobs.
And I respect Helen.
You know,
she's a self-made woman.
She doesn't deserve that.
And you have proof?
I did, and then I lost it.
So if you can just do
a little bit of research
and find anything concrete,
I can take it from there.
[sighs]
Lance, I'm really trying
to do the right thing, okay?
Honest.
All right. I'll research it.
Well, I mean, you're leaving?
I thought maybe you could stay,
and we could work
on it together.
I can't concentrate here.
Oh.
Is it 'cause you still
find me irresistible?
Shouldn't you put
that sign up outside?
I have plans for that sign.
Don't worry.
I know what I'm doing.
Good night, Krissy.
[sighs]
[doorbell rings]
Debbie.
- Hi.
- Please, come in.
[Debbie]
Oh, why is everyone here?
It's for you.
We want you to know
how much we appreciate you
and everything you do,
not only for our neighborhood,
but our entire community.
[applause]
We didn't know that you helped
build a rescue shelter
for animals.
Or that you sponsored
our school's music program.
And lots of other charities
without receiving
any recognition.
Until now.
I... I don't know what to say.
Say you won't leave.
You think any of us
wanna organize
the Easter egg hunt
or the Valentine's Day party?
[all laugh]
I wish I could take back
what I did.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, Debbie,
there's so much stuff
I wish that I could take back
recently.
But when you care about people,
you give them the benefit
of the doubt.
And because you always
take the time
to make every holiday
so special,
we all would like
to make your house
the honorary holiday house.
Not just this year,
but every year.
[applause]
You know, this doesn't mean
that we're ending the
Christmas decorating contest.
Everyone here
still wants to beat you.
- [man] That's right.
- Fair enough.
Thank you all for seeing
the nicer side of me.
Enough of the apologies.
Let's celebrate.
[applause]
- Hey, there.
- Hi.
Congratulations, Debbie.
I hope this means
the hologram reindeer
will be back
in time for Christmas.
Of course.
I'll redecorate all night
if that's what it takes.
So looks like you were
on to something with Jill.
I feel a "but" coming on.
But there's no paper trail.
Without a bank statement
showing that she's on another
company's payroll,
we can't prove anything.
What do you need
a bank statement for?
Oh, my former co-worker
is trying to take down
my old boss
at Purcell Advertising
by poaching her clients
for a rival agency.
What company?
Pogue and Price.
They're an ad agency
and PR Firm.
I know them well.
We do their payroll.
Really?
So you could see
if Jill Rhodes
was working for them.
I could definitely look into it.
Why don't you come by my office
tomorrow around 2:00?
I'll see what I can dig up.
Debbie, thank you.
Oh, thank you so much.
I'm not doing it
entirely for you.
I also happen
to know Helen Purcell,
and she throws
this huge Christmas party
for underprivileged children
every year.
If she goes out of business,
a lot of kids will have
a miserable Christmas.
Wow.
I always thought
she was such an ice queen.
Well, there are two sides
to every coin.
So I've learned. Thank you.
So...
Looks like you really
are doing the right thing.
Well, I'm certainly trying.
- Does this mean that we're...
- No.
You're still
on the naughty list.
[both chuckle]
I bet Debbie wins
best holiday office too.
Where do you even buy
a fiber-optic Christmas tree?
Same place you get
a hologram reindeer.
Yeah.
Well, Krissy,
you are absolutely right.
Turns out your friend Jill
has been working
for Pogue and Price on the side
for over a year now.
And here is your paper trail.
That's public information,
but if anyone asks,
it just fell into your lap.
My name is never mentioned.
Absolutely.
This is exactly what we need.
Thank you.
I gave a heads up
to some of our clients
who might have been affected.
Really?
[Debbie]
Well, they're gonna be looking
for an honest agency.
I told them I know
a bright advertising executive,
that we'd all be fools
not to give her our business.
Debbie,
I don't know what to say.
Say "Merry Christmas."
Merry Christmas.
I'm really happy
we're still neighbors.
Me too.
Now go and talk to Helen.
These companies don't wanna stay
in limbo for long.
Thank you, Anonymous.
So, um, how are you getting
to the party later?
'Cause I'm probably
gonna need a ride.
[sneezes]
- [Krissy] Bless you.
- Oh, thanks, Krissy.
Wait, Krissy?
The product appeals to parents,
and they're the ones
with the pocketbooks,
so let's make sure
we take advantage of that.
Um, also we're hitting
both demographics with this.
Miss Kringle,
what are you doing here?
- I'm here to save your company.
- What?
This is my...
My attorney.
Mrs. Purcell,
with the help of Miss Kringle,
I have uncovered
some legal proof
that you have a mole
in your company.
This mole has been
selling key information
about your clients
to Pogue and Price
and, as a result, picking off
your clients one by one.
- Who is this person?
- Helen, are you okay?
I knew Krissy
would go postal one day.
I just didn't think
she'd involve you, Lance.
Speak of the devil.
If you take a look,
you'd see that
your employee Jill Rhodes
is responsible for the leak.
She's on the payroll
at Pogue and Price.
If her scheme works,
she'll be made partner there.
Helen, this is all a lie.
Krissy is severely delusional.
We've talked about this.
Delusional? No, no.
Delusional is thinking
you can still shop
in the juniors' section.
So did you finally
tell her about us?
What little there was
to remember.
Enough.
Miss Rhodes,
these documents clearly show
that you've been collecting
a secondary salary
for over a year.
Helen, she's psychotic.
She's got
incriminating evidence.
So what?
Are you gonna release me?
No.
[chuckles]
I'm firing you.
Security?
Please have Jill Rhodes
escorted out of the office
at once.
Fine, do this.
I'll take everything.
It's not like I haven't already.
That's not true.
I actually
have verbal commitments
from all
of these business owners
who are eager to start accounts
with your firm, if...
If you work here?
You can't do this.
I hope you have a good attorney!
Don't worry. I do.
- [guard] Let's go.
- Let go of me!
Thank you, Miss Kringle.
And welcome back.
Well, before I come back in
from the wild,
I have just a few requests.
I'd like an office.
And a parking space.
And a 20% raise.
[chuckles]
I was wrong
to assume the worst, Krissy.
You're very talented
and an asset to this company.
I agree to your terms,
with one exception.
The job comes with a 30% raise.
I think I can live with that.
[Philip retches]
[coughs]
I'm sorry.
I know this might not be
the best time,
but, Mrs. Purcell, I don't think
I can play Santa Claus tonight.
[Philip coughs]
Okay, Philip. It...
Just go drink some tea.
[coughs]
Thank you.
[Philip coughs]
[Krissy] You know,
I think I can help.
Um, I know
about the charity work you do
and the party you throw
for the underprivileged kids,
so if you can just get them here
at this time,
I can schedule
a private meeting with Santa.
Are you serious?
You know Santa Claus?
I'm a Kringle.
[chuckles]
[kids screaming]
Hi! Come on!
Hi, guys!
- [Marco] Hey, guys.
- Welcome to Santa's workshop!
We're so excited
you guys are here, right?
Absolutely.
We have a really big night
planned for you guys.
Santa Claus is coming
all the way from the North Pole
just to see you guys.
Are you ready?
- [kids] Yeah!
- [Krissy] Yeah? Good!
'Cause Santa Claus
is coming to town tonight.
[kids] Yeah!
And I think I see him.
Ho, ho, ho!
[kids] Yeah!
Merry Christmas.
This guy's pretty good.
Have you all been
very, very good?
[kids] Yes!
Well, let me sit down and see.
Who's gonna go first?
Up on the housetop,
reindeer paused
Out jumps
good, old Santa Claus
Down through the chimney
with lots of toys
All for the little ones'
Christmas joys
Ho, ho, ho
Who wouldn't go?
Up on the housetop
Click, click, click
Down through the chimney
With good Saint Nick
First comes the stocking
of little Nell
Oh, dear Santa, fill it well
Give her a doll
that laughs and cries
One that will open
and shut her eyes
Ho, ho, ho
Who wouldn't go?
Up on the housetop
Click, click, click
Down through the chimney
With good Saint Nick
Oh.
Hey.
Justin, that fits really nice.
Yeah, not bad, huh?
It's more comfortable
than I would have thought.
Right?
Thank you so much
for making all of this happen.
It turned out really amazing.
No worries, mate.
[laughs]
I'm glad I could help.
Hey, make sure
you tell Grams, okay?
Yeah.
Oh.
Merry Christmas.
You too.
- Thank you.
- You're very welcome.
All right. Come on out this way.
Can we all say
thank you to Santa?
- [kids] Thank you, Santa!
- [Marco] Thank you, Santa!
And you're very welcome.
Merry Christmas to you all.
You continue to be good,
and all your dreams
will come true.
All right, Santa's got
a lot of work to do tonight,
so say thank you again.
Bye, Santa!
- [kids] Bye, Santa!
- [Marco] Bye, Santa!
Oh, this is very kind.
Thank you.
It's Christmas.
That's what it's about, right?
Merry Christmas to you.
I hope Santa brings you
something very special.
Oh, he already has.
Thanks.
Can we all say thank you?
[kids] Thank you.
Oh, I'm so glad. Bye, guys!
[Marco groans]
[chuckles]
This has been a great holiday.
I'm glad you came to work here,
Krissy Kringle.
Marco, I wouldn't have
survived it without you.
Oh, please, I loved the drama.
I was glad to be part of it.
Did you get to ask Santa
for anything?
I just want off
the naughty list.
[both chuckle]
I think you did that
without Santa, all right?
Merry Christmas.
- You too.
- All right.
Hey, let me help you clean up.
No, no, no, no.
I'll do it in the morning.
It's my gift to you.
Thanks.
All right.
- Good night.
- Bye.
[chuckles]
Merry Christmas to all,
and to all a good night.
Bye.
[sighs]
[tinkling]
I love Christmas lights.
I do.
[Santa laughs]
Did you know
that, before electricity,
they used to light trees
with candles?
That sounds like a fire hazard.
Oh, it was.
That's why I made sure
that little Tommy Edison
had everything he needed
in his science kit.
[chuckles]
This red suit
is flammable, you know.
Do you need a ride or anything?
Oh, well, no, I...
I have a ride.
I came back for my book,
Krissy Kringle.
[tinkling]
Wait, are you...
No, no, I'm sorry.
That's... That's impossible.
That's for you to decide.
It's a magical time of year.
And you helped
prove that tonight,
right here with these kids.
Alas, I must have my book now.
Um...
Thanks.
You can let go now.
I'm sorry. I ruined it.
Oh, no.
You haven't ruined anything.
I've had many cocoa spills
over the years myself.
[both chuckle]
And I knew
you would work things out,
even without it.
Wait, did you send it to me?
Oh, no.
I just let you have it
for a while.
What did you say you wanted
for Christmas this year?
I wanted a new last name.
No offense.
Oh.
I believe the last thing
on your list
was to be recognized
for your hard work and talent
and to be happy.
That sounds familiar.
And were you recognized?
Yeah.
And are you happy?
I'm getting there.
Everyone makes mistakes.
It's how we respond to them
that matters.
Follow your heart,
and you'll always see
the nice side of others first.
Thank you, Santa.
[Santa chuckles]
Merry Christmas, Krissy Kringle.
[Krissy chuckles]
And to you, a good night.
[tinkling]
[chuckles]
[Krissy chuckles]
Hi.
I came here
because I wanted to tell you
I accept your apology.
So does this mean
you're my boyfriend again?
No.
I don't wanna be your boyfriend.
Okay.
I mean, I...
I understand.
[chuckles]
I wanna be your husband.
[Krissy chuckles]
I've waited six years for this,
since the moment
I first laid eyes on you.
Krissy Kringle,
will you be my wife?
Is that a yes?
Uh-huh, it is.
[Krissy chuckles]
I love you so much.
I love you.
[both chuckle]
What did you do?
I didn't think you were
ever gonna get to "yes."
[applause]
Mom.
Okay, let me see that ring.
[gasps]
Welcome to the family,
officially.
Thank you.
- Congratulations, Krissy.
- Thank you so much.
- Hi.
- [Brenda] I'm so happy for you.
How did you guys
know about this?
[Brenda] We're so happy for you.
Marco, what are you doing here?
Well, maybe there is a
little magic this time of year.
- Oh, buddy, thank you.
- [Marco] Come here.
Hi.
- This is Lance.
- Lance.
- Well done, sir.
- Thank you, sir.
Oh, honey, it's beautiful.
So that's why
I've been working so hard.
[sighs]
I love it.
I hope it's exactly
what you wanted.
You are all I ever wanted.
Well, that, and my last name.
Yeah, about that, um,
I was thinking maybe
I would keep my name
and just hyphenate it.
Hmm. Krissy Kringle-Leigh.
[chuckles]
It has a nice ring to it.
- I like it.
- I like you.
[wind blows]
- [man] Holy...
- [woman] Oh, my God.
Debbie, you didn't get
a snow machine, did you?
I had nothing to do with this.
- I don't believe it.
- I do.
- This is wonderful!
- This is perfect.
Oh!
It's beautiful.
[romantic Christmas music plays]