Subtitles by explosiveskull
[snoring]
[bird cawing]
[door opens]
Do you see that, Captain?
Yeah.
I see him.
[caws]
What do you think?
You think the beast is close?
What do you say, Duke?
[Duke] He's
down there somewhere.
Making up his damn mind.
[reel straining]
[chuckles]
Whoo-hoo! Yeah, boy!
- Holy fuck.
- All right!
Duke, get the fighting jacket.
[groans]
Dill, what are you doing?
The hook is set.
You're going to have to hand over
the rod to the paying customer.
No, Duke. It's him.
How can you possibly know
it's the same fish?
I can feel it.
Take the wheel
and hold her steady.
Okay, sir.
Can I take over the rod now, please?
Here we go, baby.
Sir, we paid you 700 bucks
for this.
Dill, you struck. He's hooked. Get out
of the chair and give the man the rod.
This is my brother's fish, sir.
Get off the fucking chair.
Get in the hold.
Oh, man.
Sit down and shut the fuck up,
the both of you.
- Son of a bitch. We paid you 700 plus gas.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- [screaming]
- Hey. Okay.
Get the fuck out of here.
Looks like this is
a trophy fish, guys.
Go get some beers.
Enjoy the show, yeah?
[grunts] Duke, take the wheel.
He's headed to open water. Follow him.
Oh. Here we go, kid.
[straining] Here we go.
[straining]
[exhales]
[coughing]
Fuck.
[grunting]
[sighing]
Yeah.
I got him.
Duke?
Take the leader. He's spent.
No. He still has
spunk in him, Dill.
No, no.
He's dead in the water.
Yeah.
Huh.
You got him? Bring him up.
[speaks Creole]
No, no, no. He's done.
Bring him up.
There he is.
- [Duke grunts]
- [Dill] Easy.
That's right. Come on, Duke.
Here we go. Nice and steady.
[Duke groaning]
We got him this time, kid.
No, no, no! No!
- [Dill exhales]
- [scoffs]
If you think we're gonna pay you a
fucking single dollar for this fiasco...
you're out of your fucking mind.
Ah.
[indistinct chatter]
Lieutenant Gonzales said without a paper
contract, there's nothing we can do.
So the gringos don't pay.
No kingfish to sell to Lionel
because you spent all day on tuna.
I'll pay you.
Okay?
Yeah? How?
[woman moaning]
Mr. Baker Dill...
I am increasingly fond
of the way you say hello.
[exhales]
Jack said he heard
two fat guys in the Rope
say you pulled a knife on them.
You ever thought about taking
a course in customer relations?
[Dill grunts]
And, by the way,
have you seen my damn cat?
I think he's up at Joe's.
I think old Joe's
feeding him sprats.
You made it
all the way up to the cannery
before you decided
to turn around and see me.
Why did you come, Dill?
Why do you think?
Well, it's just I heard you went to
the Mercantile Bank this morning.
Who'd you get?
Carter. Asshole.
How did you do?
Now, Constance,
you know damn well how I did.
Round here
everybody knows everything.
[Constance] Well, I heard the
bank refused to extend your loan.
So now,
you can't even afford gas.
I'm just a little hurt you got
all the way as far as Joe's place
before you decided
on the last resort.
Baker Dill,
you're no more than a hooker.
Hooker who can't afford hooks.
How's your son?
Still pumping gas
in Miami. Why?
Well, he was good
around a boat.
If he ever wants to quit pumping
gas, I'd take him on.
What's wrong with Duke?
[clicks tongue]
I don't know.
He's gone a little crazy.
Him or you?
[scoffs]
You know, Duke's got
a grandkid in college.
He needs work that pays.
How dare old Joe feed my cat?
I like my cats
to depend on me.
Hmm, my sweet kitty.
[thunder rumbling]
[indistinct chatter]
[whistling]
[man] Hey, Dill.
And one for old Wes.
There you go, Wes.
Heard you had
him on again, Dill.
Old Wes wonders if it isn't the same
big old tuna that broke his heart.
[sniffles]
You've hooked him five times
since New Year, right?
Four.
[man] Why don't
you give him a name?
Me and the boys were saying
you should give him a name.
Well,
I already gave him a name.
His name's Justice.
[indistinct chatter]
Tomorrow morning, 5:30.
You got money for gas?
Well, if I didn't,
where would we go?
So how many have we got?
Dill? How many paying customers
are we taking out tomorrow?
None, Duke.
Just you and me.
- You can't afford to waste gas.
- That was him today.
It was him.
Dear Lord, can't you put that
man and that damn fish together?
[jingle on radio]
♪ KBW Plymouth
[announcer on radio] Tomorrow's low
tide at noon and 25. High tide 2100.
Set fair
for a beautiful Plymouth day.
- [brake creaks]
- [car engine stops]
[meows]
Hey, there, kitty cat.
Mama wants you home.
Sorry, kid.
Could have sworn he was spent.
Could feel it in my hands.
[laughter]
- [man] Gonna fucking murder you!
- [woman screams]
[alarm ringing]
[music playing on radio]
[jingle on radio]
♪ KBW Plymouth
[announcer] Good morning.
This is Plymouth Radio, broadcasting to
Plymouth Island and the ocean all around.
It's another beautiful morning
here in Plymouth,
the most beautiful island
in this damn dirty world.
Temperature of mid-80s,
humidity just perfect,
and the air
smells of sweet sugar cane.
A perfect day to go out there on
the ocean and catch that damn fish.
[music continues]
That was "Mama Told Papa."
What did Mama tell Papa?
All right, Kali,
just give me the damn fish, yeah?
Duke.
Reel 'em in.
We're done for the day.
Up! Up!
I'll take the bait to Lionel and
at least get something for it.
No, Duke.
We don't deal fucking bait.
You know what?
Maybe it's about fucking luck.
Huh? Maybe you're bringing me
bad luck, Duke.
Ever since your wife died,
we haven't caught jack shit.
That's right. Find yourself
a commercial boat, huh?
[sighs] All right, kid.
Just you and me now.
[music playing]
Give me a swizzle.
You know, Dill, there's an Indian
woman up by Mace's boatyard
who says she can
adjust people's luck.
She got that Argentinian couple
a baby.
Well,
I don't need a baby, Jack.
You need something, man.
Yeah, I need a drink.
I thought we'd established that.
Percentages are not science.
You can't tell the future from the past.
You need instinct.
And I hear you just lost that.
Duke was in here
about half an hour ago.
Says he's available
for the morning shift.
Hmm.
Doctor Bob was in here drinking.
Said he heard about the knife.
Said maybe you should go and see him,
talk to him about your state of mind.
Was that before or after
his third tequila?
Yeah, you and I joke about that,
but some of the guys are concerned.
- [sighs]
- There's money in fishing swordfish at night.
No asshole tourists on board.
Lionel pays for grunts and flatfish, too.
I fish tuna.
You fish for one tuna, man.
And that's a tuna
that's only in your head.
I'll get that.
[gulps]
Good to see you, John.
I'll have
a sparkling water, too.
Ice and lemon?
Why not?
So...
what do you say?
I say
I'm not called John anymore.
Fate's funny, huh?
Okay, Karen, I don't believe
in coincidence.
Neither do I.
Welcome to Plymouth, ma'am.
[exhales]
Do you have a place here?
Maybe we can go to dinner?
Only place is the Rope,
and you're in it.
I'd like to talk to you
someplace private.
I'd like to know what the fuck you're
doing out here on the edge of nowhere.
I came to tell you you
were right and I was wrong.
[laughs]
Fuck.
I hear you have a boat.
[door closes]
[Karen] You own this boat?
[Dill] Well, me and the bank.
We take turns.
This is about as private
as it gets.
How did you find me
and what do you want?
Back in the real world,
they got this thing called Facebook.
- You ever heard of it?
- No.
Well, when I decided
to track you down,
I reached out to some
of the guys from school.
You remember Dotey?
The relentless one?
Well, she put together a class
reunion a couple of years ago.
The only two who didn't show
were you and me.
Nobody knew where you were.
Everybody knew about Iraq
and the medals.
So, little Greg
had gone fishing on this boat
on some island in the middle of
nowhere and he had caught a fish,
and had his photo taken with it.
And he said that there was this guy in
the shot who looked just like John Mason.
Only he said
the guy was calling himself...
Baker Dill.
Was it a big fish?
Excuse me?
If he had his photo taken,
it must have been a big fish.
So I tracked down the photo.
Couldn't tell if it was you
standing there or not,
but the name gave it away,
Baker Dill.
Dillon Baker was the only
teacher you respected at Morgan.
He taught math, right?
You still haven't told me
what you want.
I figured if you were using an
assumed name, you were on the run.
I'm just waiting on some things back
home to lose their significance.
I thought you being
outside the law would be okay.
In fact, it would be good.
'Cause like I say...
you were right and I was wrong.
About Frank.
He got richer and bigger
and drunker and angrier.
Hands turned to fists.
So get a divorce.
Except I guess you can't.
No, I can't.
He's even more connected than he was.
Cubans out of Miami.
If I tried to leave,
he'd find a hole for me
in one of his construction sites.
That's the truth.
[grunts]
I didn't come here
thinking you might forgive me.
Look, he's violent
with you, right?
Different kinds.
[breathes heavily]
He's refined it lately.
And how's my son
with that, Karen?
How's my son
with this refinement?
He hides away.
- [Frank] I swear to fucking God.
- [Karen] It's my fault. It's my fault.
He gets scared when we fight.
- [Frank] Fucking come back here, you bitch.
- [Karen] I'm sorry. Daddy...
He plays games.
- [typing]
- [indistinct shouting continues]
[Karen] He has his computer,
plays for hours and hours.
School says he's got...
[sniffles]
...a unique ability...
[crying] ...but he just
seems kind of broken down.
[Frank] I take that little fucking
prick in. Don't make me come in there.
John...
saving Patrick
is the reason I'm here.
I'm in hell now, John.
[sniffles]
This can be just business.
You need money.
Me and Patrick need a way out.
My husband is joining me here
the day after tomorrow.
I told him that I would
charter a boat for fishing tuna.
I want you to take him out on your
boat, let him get drunk...
then drop him in the ocean
for the sharks.
In return, I will give you
ten million dollars cash.
[laughs]
Listen, before the moon goes
down, I got fish to catch.
I need you
the fuck off my boat.
Ten million dollars, John.
[Dill]
Get the fuck off my boat.
I'm at the American Hotel.
- [engine starts]
- Mr. Dill! Mr. Baker Dill! Can I speak to you a moment?
Mr. Dill! I just need...
[panting] ...a few minutes of your time.
Ma'am. Do you know
the captain of that boat?
[music playing on radio]
[music stops]
Hey, Constance.
What are you doing up here?
Looking for my damn cat.
Uh-huh. Front pocket.
[Constance] I'm allowed inside?
[Dill] If you wipe your feet.
- [cat meows]
- Thank you, ma'am.
I hear
you got lucky last night.
Yeah, sure did. Three swordfish
over 50 pound. Eight hundred bucks.
Plus I cut out the cheeks for breakfast.
You want some?
They say she looks like
some kind of model.
[Dill] Who?
Consuela said the lady said her
husband's coming here to catch tuna.
[Dill] Doesn't anyone around here
do any work they're paid to do?
- [Constance] Is that why she came to see you?
- [Dill] Yep.
Are you going
to take him out?
Nope.
- [Constance] Where are you going?
- To take a shower.
[Frank] You're selfish, you fucking bitch.
You always have to go in.
[Patrick] Dad,
there's something I need you to do.
[Frank] Don't you fucking dare.
You show me no fucking gratitude.
[Karen screams]
[gasps]
[panting]
Patrick?
Is that you?
[vehicle approaching]
[bell rings]
[sighs]
- [door opens]
- [screams]
Frank! Oh, God!
- [stammers]
- [laughs]
Rolled in a day early, baby.
But there... [panting]
...there were no flights today.
I rented a Learjet.
I had to come and get you.
Let's get this fucking show
on the road, huh?
Mmm.
I paid a fucking jet
for this, so let's...
let's lose the robe.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. Turn around.
Nice and slow.
[inhales]
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
What's this? Huh?
Just a little scratch.
Ooh.
A little scratch, huh?
Playing with a cat maybe?
I don't know.
Hmm. You don't know.
[inhales] Okay.
Man of the moment.
Your ears burning?
I've come to settle up, Lois.
Well, if you want my opinion,
I didn't think she was so special.
- [chuckles]
- Parading right there on the quay
with some big hat and shades
like it's 90 degrees.
I owe you for 20 spoons, hooks,
and 1,000 yards of line. That's $25.
And her husband. Man.
Her husband arrived on a jet
decorated like a cake.
Consuela says he came early
to surprise her.
Gave Carlos 150 for finding
champagne at 10:00 a.m.
A dozen regular sevens and a couple
of feathers as well, will you?
- Going after swordfish again?
- Mm-hmm.
Guess you gotta pay the bills
now that Duke's gone.
Poor old Duke. He's got himself
some day work up at the boatyard.
Poor old Duke.
You shouldn't have blamed
his wife for your bad luck.
I don't. I blame your damn hooks.
Two cedars.
- For tuna?
- What else?
Swordfish at night, tuna in the day.
When are you gonna sleep?
When I've bought my boat
from the bank.
Nine dollars.
Then I'm gonna sail away to somewhere
where nobody knows your business.
[scoffs]
What name are you gonna
use there?
Consuela says the big guy beat
her with his hands and his belt.
Hour and a half.
She didn't make a sound.
Miami is some strange place,
right?
Yep.
Oh, there was some skinny guy
from Fontaine looking for you.
He left you his card.
Captain.
My wife says you're being
a little difficult.
Well, as I explained
to your wife last night,
I don't have
a first mate right now.
And by law, I'm not allowed
to take tourists out alone.
The law, huh?
Funny you should say that.
'Cause I ain't seen
any law around here
that'd cost more than
ten bucks since I left Miami.
I can't afford
to lose my license.
Well, take the cock
out of your mouth.
Four years in a line I won the
Bermuda Yellow Fin Tournament.
Fifty-four, 70, 73,
and a 56 pounds.
Well, your proficiency
does not alter the regulations.
My proficiency. Jesus,
he talks like a fucking college professor.
Huh? [laughs]
My wife, my beautiful wife,
she arranged this trip.
She sat up on the fucking
Internet night after night,
typing away to find the perfect
boat to make this trip perfect,
because she wants it to be
perfect, perfect for me.
Now, myself, well, I'd say a son of a
bitch runs a bucket same as any other,
and I'd fly
to some other island.
But I don't got time.
I only got two days.
So, let's be here at 7:00, just me,
you, and the motherfucking tuna.
I already told you,
it's not worth the risk.
I'm not gonna do it.
Please think about it,
Mr. Dill.
[Frank] It's okay, honey.
Every man has his price.
Tomorrow at 7:00 a.m.
I'm gonna be here.
So should you.
[Reid Miller] Mr. Dill!
- [engine starts]
- Damn it. Damn it. Mr. Dill!
There's something wrong.
There appears to be a 20-second
discrepancy in my allotted schedule.
[Lionel] Two nights in a row.
The moon change your luck?
[Dill] I'd say 110 pounds.
Hmm. And they're billfish, huh?
Say $800?
Yesterday when you came in
with the swordfish,
I thought, at last,
Baker Dill has seen sense.
But I hear from Lois
you bought new cedars.
So even though you're
making money on night fish,
you're still going out after
that fish that's in your head.
You do know
it's just in your head, right?
Well, hell, yeah.
That's why I gotta get him out of there.
Oh, and yesterday,
there was some skinny guy out of Fontaine.
Got here right after you left.
- [cat meows]
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing all the way down
here, kitty cat, huh?
I'll take you home,
collect my reward.
[Constance moaning]
In a hurry today?
Ah. I need to be
on the ocean before 10:00.
So tell me the truth, Dill.
You knew her before, right?
I hear she needs
to be saved.
Yeah?
He gets drunk, beats her up.
You don't treat me badly.
We just lean on each other a little.
I give you cash
when the fish don't bite...
and you find my cat
when they do.
Catch the cat for Constance.
Okay, Dill, say fate
gave you the choice.
You can get the lady or you can
catch that tuna that's in your head.
Which one would you choose?
Oh.
[announcer on radio] Another
beautiful day on Plymouth Island.
Tuna, albacore, swords, ready to catch.
Clear blue sky.
One little thing, if you have a boat,
and, man, of course you have a boat,
maybe, just maybe, that rare
thing, storm is coming.
Dill, the rich guy
is aboard your boat
already strapped
into the shotgun chair,
drinking champagne
from a bucket of bait ice.
Yeah, well, unstrap him.
And they say he drew 10,000
in cash from the Mercantile.
I guess you want
a piece of the action, huh?
You listen to me.
Consuela heard the guy say to his wife
that he was going to offer you
the whole ten grand,
that he was going to do it
to prove a point,
to prove that some little
fucking guy can't say no.
Yeah? So what?
So I need the money.
You need the money.
We take him out, let him fish.
I'll take two, you take eight.
The Sereni needs an overhaul. My granddaughter
needs money for the next semester.
Why would I
take you out, Duke, huh?
You're bad luck.
No, no. Constance told me
the real reason you fired me.
Pity is worse
than a fist in the face.
I'm not begging you, Baker
Dill, I'm just telling you.
When life offers you an opportunity
like this, you have to take it.
Okay.
But you stay close to me today, Duke.
You hear me?
I need you to deliver me
from temptation.
Temptation?
What temptation?
You don't need to know.
[speak Creole]
[Karen] John?
My husband's offering $10,000.
Ah, this is Plymouth.
I already know.
You gonna take him?
Yep.
I'm gonna take him out.
That's it.
My first mate Duke
will be on board with me.
[bird caws]
We will...
fish until the sun sets
and then return.
All three of us.
Then we'll go back and Patrick
will hear the key in the door.
And then on it goes and on.
The three of us.
I know you think about him all the time.
I know you do, Dill.
You talk to him...
about catching
a particular fish.
He hears you
through his computer screen.
[Duke] Captain?
The gentleman has brought
hard liquor aboard.
That's against the rules, right?
It's okay, Duke.
The rules have changed.
It's true.
He hears you
every time you talk to him.
You are connected.
John?
[bird caws]
[Duke] Take a look, Dill.
Yeah, I saw him earlier.
He was circling
right over the harbor.
A frigate?
Frigate don't fly over land.
I know.
It's the damnedest thing.
Like the son of a bitch
was coming to collect me.
Frigate don't fly over land, Dill.
You must have been mistaken.
There's some weird stuff
going on right now.
How do you guys live in a town
with only one fucking bar?
The Rope's not so bad.
It used to be called
the Hope and Anchor.
Then old Jack decided there wasn't
much hope to be had in Plymouth,
so he changed "hope" to "rope."
Lots of rope in Plymouth. Enough to
hang yourself. Isn't that right, Dill?
Is that right? Maybe we should
throw out some bait, huh?
Come on,
let's fucking chum the waters.
What do you guys
do for girls in this town?
You, what do you do?
Not much.
Not much, no?
What about you, Dull?
It's kind of a small island.
The guy at the hotel says in the poor part
of town, down by the commercial harbor,
you got little girls who take it
right in the ass for ten bucks a pop.
Right?
You know anything about that?
I wouldn't know
anything about that, sir.
Yeah.
Well, I'm gonna
fucking head up there tonight
and grab myself
some of that ten-dollar ass.
You don't have kids,
do you, Mr. Zariakas?
No.
My wife's got this son
from a previous fuck-up, though.
Creepy little fuck.
Open the door.
- [knocking]
- Patrick, open the door. Come on, I just wanna talk.
You know, I try.
I really fucking do.
I say, "Come on, kid,
let's go outside.
Let's toss a football around.
Let's play some football like men."
But he just sits there
staring at his computer screen
like he's staring out a window all day
fucking long with the curtains closed.
Get out here.
Have a fucking talk to me like a man.
- [knocking]
- He's got a maths teacher who thinks he's a genius.
That fucking genius can't
even screw a bell on a bike.
- Goddamn it!
- [banging on door]
You open the door,
you little prick.
One day I grab him, I throw him off
his chair, I wanna see what he's doing.
[grunting]
You know, I'm thinking whatever,
porn, ninjas, stealing cars.
You know what this little
fucking retard's doing?
Catching fish.
He's got this whole world.
And there's this guy on a boat
and he's catching fish.
I said, "How the fuck can you do the same thing
all day long?" And you know what he said to me?
If I didn't catch fish
all day...
If I didn't catch fish all day,
I'd find a way to kill you.
I swear to fucking God,
that's what he said to me.
Creepy little fuck.
I'll find a fucking hole for him one day.
Why would your son
wanna kill you, Mr. Zariakas?
How the fuck would I know?
What the fuck
is it to you, Dull?
Huh? Maybe you can give me
the name of that street
those little
harbor red-asses are on.
The guy at the hotel said
there's only one cop in town
and he's gone away
for the weekend,
so I can do whatever the fuck I want.
[chuckles]
Yeah, there's no law
in Plymouth right now.
Hey, give me that fucking rod.
Come on.
[grunting]
- All right, come on, give it here.
- No, no, no, it's just a shark.
I don't give a fuck.
- Give the rod to me.
- Nah, I'm gonna cut him loose and let him ride.
It's a shark.
You said you wanted tuna.
- Give me the fucking rod. Come on, clip me in.
- Duke, get the bucket.
What are we looking at?
Four-hundred-and-fifty-pound
great white.
Enough to give you a buzz maybe, huh?
That's what you want, right?
I can do that.
Come on, plug me in, baby.
- We gotta attach the reel...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Fuck!
Yeah, you... Whoa! Whoa! Hey, hey,
give me a hand, man. Jesus Christ.
[boat approaching]
[laughs] Hey, baby! You see what
Daddy caught? A big fucking shark.
Now, honey, I swear tomorrow,
I'm gonna get you a big fat tuna.
Or some fucking heads are gonna roll.
Come on, a kiss for Daddy? Huh?
You going out again tomorrow?
Yeah, baby, I got to.
I gotta show these boys.
They're all set up
for fucking sharks.
Tomorrow I show 'em
how to catch tuna.
Hey, school for you tomorrow,
Captain Dull.
You're the boss.
Fuckin'-A, I'm the boss.
I'm gonna wash my hands, okay?
You pay the guy.
Watch his eyes pop out of
his fucking head. [laughs]
So, tomorrow.
Pay me another ten,
we do the same thing again tomorrow.
- John...
- We fish, we come back.
You spent one day with him.
I have had ten years.
Karen, you got the money.
Go to Europe. Go anywhere. Just keep
that fucking animal away from my son.
And have him hunt us?
Him? Come on.
Honey, fucking blood
everywhere here! [laughs]
John, the ten million is dirty money.
It's in cash. It's yours.
Okay, John, you want the truth? Your son
wants you to do it. This is his idea.
You're his father.
He needs you to do this.
He wants justice.
[Frank] Baby, come on,
let's go up the hotel and get a cocktail.
Early to bed for you, boys.
School tomorrow.
Tuna. T-U-N-A.
Talk to me about temptation.
[Duke] I know you, Dill.
The way you looked at him.
The way you looked at her.
You knew her before.
Yeah. More than that.
What happened?
I went away to war.
War fucked me up.
I came back
and she was with him.
Except I didn't
really ever come back.
What about that kid
he was talking about?
You know, Duke,
you remember when I hired you,
I made rules
about discussing the past.
I'm not talking about the past.
I'm talking about today, on deck.
I've spent so long on boats with
you, I can hear you thinking.
So that kid "from a
previous fuck-up" is yours?
And how much did she offer you
to kill her husband?
[laughs]
Who's crazy now, huh?
Dill, even if
that bastard deserves it,
even if Lieutenant Gonzalez
won't raise a finger,
there's right and wrong,
heaven and hell.
You know, Duke,
you made two grand today.
I think it's best you go find
some place safe to put it.
- What about tomorrow?
This will blow over by morning.
You know it.
Am I hired to come along or are
you going out with him alone?
I'll sleep on it.
I doubt you'll sleep.
There is a God, Dill.
And you're a good man.
Catch the fish in your head.
That is the rule.
Do not kill the man.
[sighs]
[Frank] You fucking hear me?
Sit the fuck down.
- [Patrick] Dad!
- [thunder crashing]
[panting]
Oh. My poor sweet kitty.
[footsteps approaching]
What are you doing here?
He went looking
around the commercial harbor.
- [door closes]
- John?
All these years I never
stopped thinking about you.
Look.
You put it on my finger
when I was 16. You remember?
Outside the Fix in the parking lot.
I kept it. It's the same one. Brass.
You took it from the burner on
the stove of your dad's boat.
No. That's just some old ring
you found.
No.
You said, "With this stupid
ring, I thee wed, baby."
I remember it word for word.
And then you laughed.
I kept it.
I wear it when I'm alone.
You remember that night?
- [inhales]
- We went to the bridge.
You were fishing.
Eels and jacks.
Then...
you said
I was finally old enough.
First time for me.
First time ever.
[sighs] If we could go back
to that bridge that night...
would you go?
What do you mean?
No war. No fuck-up.
No body parts laying around in the sand.
My arms, my fucking hands.
John...
[cries]
I loved you
even after you were gone.
Listen up. Before this gets any
crazier, here's the deal.
I will take him out tomorrow.
He will drink. He will fall overboard.
Sharks will get to eat and I
will get ten million in cash.
Afterwards, I will go somewhere, you will bring
my son to me and then we'll see what happens.
But don't you
bullshit me about love.
I'm doing this for him,
Patrick, my son.
You and me
are not part of the deal.
Okay, okay.
People don't change.
Then I'm still
the girl at the bridge.
[breathing heavily]
[Karen crying]
We're both destroyed, right?
Both damaged.
Both damaged in different places.
[moans]
[moaning]
That's it.
I beat him. I win.
Make sure you don't get him
there till noon tomorrow.
I'll take him out on the ebb.
When the water's high, I'll do it.
Then the current will take away
what the sharks leave behind.
[door closes]
Your mother says you can
hear me when I talk to you.
How can that be, huh?
It makes no sense.
But you never know with her.
Opportunity's all around her.
It pours off her like rain.
We're gonna do this,
just you and me, tomorrow. Yeah.
Then maybe you can open the
goddamn curtains and step outside.
Mr Dill. It's quite a
bit unpleasant out here.
Can we go inside?
My name is Reid Miller.
From Fontaine.
The boat and fishing
tackle suppliers.
I am a technical representative
and head of regional sales
in the latitudes
that include Plymouth.
May I come in
and talk to you?
It's 2:30 in the morning.
You're out at sea mostly.
I keep missing you.
By a bigger margin every time.
But with the storm
keeping you ashore,
I thought
I'd take my opportunity.
What I have in my hands
may change your life
and give you the one thing
you've always wanted.
That sounds great, Reid,
but I've got kind of a big day tomorrow.
Yes, Mr. Dill.
I know all about your big day.
And I think you should hear
what I have to say.
Have a seat.
Can I get you something?
[clears throat]
- [uncorks bottle]
- Bigger hands.
What's that?
Uh, bigger hands.
Whenever I'm around fishermen,
I wish I had bigger hands.
Now, listen, man.
What the fuck do you want?
Mr. Dill,
inside this suitcase...
Don't tell me you're gonna try
and sell me fishing tackle.
Yes. Yes, I am.
At 2:30 in the morning?
As I say,
you're often at sea.
The electrical storm
is my only opportunity.
All right, listen.
I'm a man who can appreciate persistence.
- With me, it's a fish.
- With me, it's you.
[chuckles]
Okay.
Here's what you're gonna do,
little man.
I'm gonna pour you a nip,
gonna keep the cold
off of you.
Then you're gonna
get the fuck out of here
and go back
where you came from.
I got an early start
in the morning.
Actually, tomorrow
you don't sail until midday.
That is to say,
low tide is noon,
and as a rule,
you sail at low tide.
You know a lot about me,
don't you?
Yes.
Almost everything.
[coughs]
Drink up.
[clears throat]
What's in the case?
This, Mr. Dill...
is the all-new Fontaine
marine sonic fish finder.
A fish finder?
It uses sub-aquatic
sonar signals.
I know what the fuck
a fish finder is.
- But Mr. Dill...
- Let me see that card again.
Is this a joke?
The guys at the Rope
put you up to this?
It's no joke. We are prepared
to give you this model,
the Fontaine White Wave,
free of charge for one week. A trial.
Perhaps you could
try it out tomorrow.
What's so special
about tomorrow?
Hmm?
Mr. Dill, all I can say is I am
a representative of Fontaine...
and they really want you
to catch the fish.
And I want you to take this
piece of equipment on trial.
Just take the fish finder
and try it,
and it will work,
I promise you.
I am the rules.
You're the what?
Those are the rules.
You said you knew something
about tomorrow.
What do you know?
Mr. Dill...
please just decide
to catch the fish.
Don't kill that man.
Don't what?
I... I really shouldn't drink.
I can't say any more.
I have to go.
Who the fuck are you?
You're gonna tell me
what you know about tomorrow,
and if you don't,
you're not gonna see it.
Mr. Dill...
if you have to kill me,
then kill me...
but I am just playing my part
in the game.
What game?
What fucking game?
This game.
- Don't you get it?
- [Karen screaming]
Someone made the whole thing up.
[Frank] ...fucking me.
You and the fucking kid.
All of this.
Plymouth Island is a game.
There are lots of games
on Plymouth Island.
Catch the Cat.
Count the Sprats.
You get logs and frigate birds and
fish finders and bottles of rum.
You see, someone made a world
on their computer
so they could play games.
[thunder rumbles]
But his favorite has
always been Catch the Tuna.
The lighthouse.
Light, dark, one, zero.
The fundamental process.
The rule is you've got to catch
a particular fish.
That rule is your compulsion,
and your compulsion
is a rule in a game.
But now it seems
the fish is no longer the point.
The new game
is that you kill a man.
[Dill] I don't know
who the fuck you are,
but it's time for you
to leave.
Who the fuck I am
is I am the rules.
And according to the rules,
on Plymouth Island,
no one dies.
It isn't meant to be
that kind of game.
So, as a representative...
of the existing program...
my question is,
the big question is...
why has the creator
changed the rules?
[Patrick screams]
[clock ticking]
[grunts]
[groans]
[alarm rings]
[panting]
[sniffles]
[sighs]
[man] Unless you've been
living under a rock,
I think
I hardly need to motivate
machine learning and neural
networks to the present...
[man 2] We have these complex
systems of information relay points
and from that,
consciousness naturally arises.
[announcer] Good morning.
This is Plymouth Radio,
broadcasting to Plymouth Island
and the ocean.
Well, the storm's blown over.
Where the hell
did that come from, right?
Anyway, I would give you
the time,
but you don't care
what time it is.
- This is Plymouth...
- [turns off engine]
All right, Patrick.
I'm gonna kill a man today.
That's what you want, right?
I've just got so many holes
in my memory.
I don't know what they're from.
The war, the rum.
I mean, I don't even remember
how the hell I got here.
But I remember you.
You were three years old.
We went fishing.
[indistinct]
[laughing]
We didn't catch a damn thing.
I remember I got so mad.
Maybe that's why
you made me like I am, huh?
Mad as hell
to catch that damn fish.
Yeah, but lately I've been having
this thing in my memory where I...
where I see myself...
laying dead...
in the sand.
Mr. Dill?
Remember me?
Samson.
Constance's kid.
My mom said
you had a job for me.
I quit my job
pumping gas in Miami.
Here I am.
Are you okay, Mr. Dill?
[lighter flicking]
You did always say
I was good around the boat.
No.
I said
you were the lucky one.
The lucky kid.
I always thought if I got you
aboard, I might catch him.
The beast? The big one?
Yeah, I always asked the game to
bring you to me, and now look at this.
Out of the blue...
here you are.
You don't look so good,
Mr. Dill.
Huh.
I had kind of a strange night.
At the old Rope, right?
You sank a few, huh?
[chuckles]
I brought some lures
I picked up in Boca Raton.
I don't need a man today,
Samson.
He changed the rules.
He wants me to do it,
I'm gonna do it.
That's it.
But, Mr. Dill, please.
- [car door slams]
- [engine starts]
[music plays on car radio]
[announcer on radio] Perfect
day to get out on the ocean.
Today's low tide at noon and
25, high tide 2100.
Set fair
for a beautiful Plymouth day.
So just get out there
and catch that damn fish...
[brakes screech]
[revving]
Yeah, come on, you son of a bitch.
Come on. Come on.
[revving]
- [grunts] Okay, here we go.
- [hand brake creaks]
Baker Dill.
Come on in.
I got something for you.
Yeah? What you got?
It's a surprise.
The latest thing.
Specimen tuna lures
that wriggle like a bitch.
The latest thing on the Grand Banks.
Never fail.
I got tired of seeing your damn
face so disappointed all the time.
So I spoke to the
representative from Fontaine.
The skinny guy?
It's all right, Dill.
I know times are hard.
You can have those
free of charge.
He's kind of a strange guy,
right?
He gave them to me for free.
A free trial.
Yeah, he...
He knew a lot about me.
Who?
How do you explain that?
Explain what?
Huh.
Say, Lois,
you know how in Plymouth
they like to say
everybody knows everything?
Now, wouldn't it be funny
if the truth was that...
nobody knows anything?
Like where exactly it is...
that we are.
Where in the world are we,
Lois?
Dill, well, you have yourself a good
day, now, and do what's right, okay?
Yeah, and what's that?
Go catch that fish, Dill.
[clicks tongue]
[taps on counter]
[exhales]
[line ringing]
[woman on phone] Fontaine Boat
and Fishing Tackle Suppliers.
Hi, yes. I'm calling
about a Mr. Reid Miller.
He's a technical representative
with your company.
He tried to sell me
a fish finder last night.
I was just checking, he works for
you, right? He's real?
[woman] Real? Yes, sir.
Why do you ask?
And Fontaine Boat
and Fishing Tackle Suppliers,
that's what you do,
you're real?
[woman chuckles]
Why, yes, sir.
Great.
Well, listen, I'd like to leave
Mr. Miller a message.
[woman] Certainly.
Can I take your name?
He'll know who I am.
[woman]
Sir, there are rules here.
My message is, "Thank you."
[woman] I cannot leave Mr. Miller
a message unless I take your...
Hey, Dill.
Weather blew over
just in time.
I got your ice and beers
ready for you.
Won't need ice and beer today,
Jack.
Just a bottle of rum.
You got customers today?
Mm-hmm.
I thought you had rules about
taking strong liquor on board.
Well, the rules have changed.
You know, Dill,
if you're gonna catch old Justice,
maybe you should go out alone.
Tourists just get
under your feet.
Now, why would you say that,
Jack?
What's that?
Do you even know?
- Know what?
- Why you say things.
Do you even know
what this is all about?
No, it's just me
going crazy, right?
Probably need to see
Dr. Bob.
I think the island's
getting to me.
Oh, yeah.
It'll do that okay.
Exactly how many years
have I been here, Jack?
What's that?
How long have I been
on Plymouth Island?
Sometimes it feels like we've
all been here forever, right?
Yeah.
I'll get you
that bottle of rum.
I got a feeling
today's the day.
Yeah, today's the day all right.
[Frank] Don't. Don't you dare.
You come back here.
- [glass shatters]
- [Karen] I'm sorry, Frank.
- I'm sorry.
- [Frank] Come back here, you bitch.
[Karen] I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[Frank]
You shut the fuck up, bitch.
- [Karen] I'm sorry, Frank. I'm sorry.
- [Frank] Shut the fuck up.
I swear to God,
I will find a fucking hole for you.
- [banging on door]
- [Patrick] Mom!
[water flowing]
[gasps]
No, Duke.
I'm going out alone today.
Yeah. Alone is right.
You will be alone because
Mr. Zariakas won't be showing up.
Frank?
[gasps]
I made some arrangements.
He won't be coming.
What arrangements?
What happened?
[groans] I cracked my rib.
I don't feel so good.
I used my $2,000 to pay some Argentinian
cannery guy to break his hand.
You fucking what?
[breathing heavily]
There was fucking six of them
against me.
- [gasps]
- [grunting]
[groans]
- Fuck.
- [Dill] You what?
I didn't do it to save him.
I did it to save you.
No. No, Duke.
[groans]
No, you didn't
fucking do that.
You know, I don't think there's gonna
be any sport for me for a while, baby.
[breathing heavily]
[yells]
"Deliver me from temptation."
That's what you said.
And that's what I've done.
[yells]
Dill, you're not right
in your mind.
You should go see Dr. Bob.
Get the fuck off my boat.
- You should see someone.
- Get off my boat!
[roars]
Fuck.
I quit!
[roars]
Jack?
Give me a bottle of rum.
I already gave you a bottle.
No, I already drank
that bottle.
Give me a goddamn bottle.
[Jack] You're sitting
in old Wes's seat.
That's right, Jack.
[bangs table] Right here.
What happened?
You don't drink
before you go out, Dill.
That's because
I'm not going out.
Why not?
You want something to eat?
I got ham and eggs.
Mm-mmm.
[draws chair]
Okay, Dill,
here is how we all see it.
Three days ago,
you pull a knife on some tourists,
yell bad things at Duke.
Joe at the cannery says he sees
you running naked in the mornings.
Last night everybody saw you
sitting on the deck in the rain
talking to the air.
Hmm.
And whether you like it or
not, I'm calling Dr. Bob, okay?
[chuckles]
You're a part of it, Jack...
and you don't even know it.
This whole goddamn island's
a part of it.
But nobody knows it.
You wanna go call Dr. Bob?
Go do that.
[chair slides]
[tires screech]
[groans]
[song plays on car radio]
[brakes screech]
[song continues playing]
[announcer on radio] Okay,
this is a message for Baker Dill
from all your friends
on Plymouth Island.
"Come back, man.
You've got a fish to catch."
I'm so mad about this.
Oh, no, baby. They got
what was coming to them.
I so wanted my daddy
to catch me a big fish today.
I spent so long planning this.
All those nights on the Internet.
- I know.
- [sighs]
- I'm so sad my dream's not gonna come true.
I know, baby, but I'm...
I'm hurt pretty bad, baby.
Mmm. Okay.
[sighs]
Okay.
[groans]
I want you to pretend...
...that my throat
is your big old fishing rod.
- Baby, my hand is broke.
- See?
- Ah, baby...
- See if you can hold it. Just see.
I can't.
My hand's broke, baby.
- Oh, just try, Daddy. Just try.
- I can't.
[groans]
Oh, yes, Daddy,
I feel that.
- [grunts]
- That is so strong.
They can't stop you.
Nobody can stop you.
[sighs] You know, if you wanted to
go, I'd come with you.
I'd help you.
You would?
Yeah.
[groans]
How the fuck did you know
I was here?
Oh, come on.
In Plymouth,
everybody knows everything.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
Except what the fuck
is going on.
If it helps,
I don't much know either.
I just kind of know
what's supposed to happen.
Yeah.
Well, if it helps,
I called your office.
They said you are real.
That's very kind of them.
Did you ask them
what "real" means?
No, I didn't have enough coins
to get into that conversation.
[chuckles]
- Fuck.
- What's funny?
What's not funny, huh?
Like your theory
on my own existence.
It's very interesting.
Intellectually challenging.
But, I mean,
I gotta favor the notion
that I've just been
on this island too long.
Had so much bad fucking rum,
I lost my grease.
No.
You're not crazy.
No?
No.
Well, if someone invented me,
how come I know who I am?
You don't.
"We are such stuff
as dreams are made on."
So, in short,
nobody knows anything. Hmm?
Nobody except
whoever created us.
And who's that?
You know, don't you?
Know what?
Who the creator is.
If this is a game...
then I guess I do.
Everything is a guess.
Every wave that breaks
is a guess.
Come on, who is it?
It's a boy...
sitting in a dark room.
In some other part of the house,
he can hear some guy beating his mother.
So he sits in front of his computer
screen, wishing he could...
bring his dad back so he
could kill the son of a bitch.
There it is.
That's it.
So that's the new game.
Your new compulsion.
Yeah.
Real, not real,
I don't give a fuck.
He wants me to do it,
he needs me to do it, I'm gonna do it.
It's called "justice" or
something like that. I'm doing it.
Well, if that's the new rule,
I should help you.
Fuck fish finders, right?
Consuela told Lois
who told me,
in spite of all the obstacles
that have been thrown in her way,
Karen has persuaded Zariakas
to be on the boat at noon.
If the game is to kill him,
you don't have much time.
Here we go. Come on, baby.
That's right.
I'm the rules.
I am the rules, huh?
Gonna show you
how it's done, son.
Just like Iraq. That was a game, huh?
A shoot-'em-up game.
I was good at that game, huh?
That's right.
I was put to good use.
They call it justice, huh?
Here we go.
Uh-huh.
I gave him medication
and bandaged his hand.
He's been drinking rum.
He's been throwing up.
So let's get him on board
before he changes his mind.
This is fate, John.
He's so broken up, he can't fight back.
Stay calm, Karen.
I got this.
Does he have a gun?
No. I mean, yeah,
but I hid it.
It's fate, John.
[Dill] How are we doing,
boss man?
- What's that?
- Huh?
Hey.
Listen, you want
something cold to drink?
[grunts]
The tide's gonna be
turning soon.
We should get on board
if we're gonna do this.
He's badly wounded.
Just get him on board.
He wants to fish.
Hey, you wanna fish, right?
Fucking... Fucking show
fucking Captain Dull here.
There we go.
Let's do this.
On three. One, two, three.
[grunting]
[Frank] Motherfuck!
You got it. Easy does it.
[groans]
[Dill] Have a seat
right here in the king's chair.
[groaning]
[cat meows]
Get some rum in him.
All he can handle.
[Frank groans]
There you go, Daddy.
- You did it, Daddy. You did it. That's good.
- [boat engine starts]
You did it.
Oh, creator
of this Garden of Eden...
please understand
he's a good soul
whose mind has been disturbed
by temptation.
[Frank]
Come back here, you bitch.
[Karen] I just need...
I just need a...
[Frank]
I haven't fucking finished yet.
Mrs. Zariakas, please put the
fighting jacket on your husband.
- Okay, give me your hand.
- Huh?
- Okay. Can you sit up?
- Oh, yeah.
- Can you sit up?
[bird cawing]
When that fucking fish bites,
you be sure to put that rod in
my good hand, okay, Mr. Dull?
Hey, you're the boss.
Oh, yeah. Make sure he gives
the fucking rod to me, yeah?
- Yes.
- To me. Yes, what?
Yes, Daddy.
Yeah. Yeah.
You fucking hear that, Dull?
She likes to call me Daddy.
Yeah, I hear it.
How about your boy?
He call you Daddy, too?
[Frank] What's that?
The creepy one. Patrick.
- He call you Daddy?
- [Karen] John, stay cool.
What'd you call him?
[Dill] All right,
we got blood in the water.
Sharks are gonna come, my man.
Yeah, but we're after the fucking
tuna, though, yeah?
Goddamn right
we're going after tuna.
- When the time's right, we're gonna fucking do it.
- [Frank grunts]
[mumbles] Do what?
[Frank] I swear to fucking God,
look what you did to me, huh?
[Karen] Not the face.
Not my face.
[Frank] You fucking happy now?
I bend over
fucking backwards for you.
We catch the famous fish,
of course.
Hey, Mr. Dill.
I figured it was
last night's rum talking
when you said
you didn't need me.
I stowed away.
But I'm here to help.
Oh, fuck.
I wanna show you I am lucky.
[Karen] John,
who the hell is this?
I just... I thought
I'd bring you some luck.
[cawing]
[grunts]
John?
What the fuck
you keep calling him John for?
Shh.
[Samson] Mr. Dill, I'm sorry. I didn't
know. I thought you'd be fine with...
- You don't have to pay me.
- No, it's okay, Samson. It's okay.
Listen. I want you to go up
to the wheelhouse, tidy up.
When you're done,
fetch me a pack of cigarettes, okay?
Yes, sir, Captain.
Okay.
Mr. Zariakas,
stay in your seat and watch the rigs.
Mrs. Zariakas,
do you wanna know where the toilet is?
- Yes.
- Follow me.
[groans]
[boat creaking]
Okay, okay, okay. Offer the kid
money to keep his mouth shut, right?
No, no,
that's not a good idea.
I'm not doing that
to the kid.
What do you propose?
I can't go back to my life, John.
I can't go back to my life.
- No, no.
- Easy. Easy.
[Samson] Fish on!
Bang on the shotgun!
Gunnel! Gunnel! Gunnel!
Fish on.
- [Karen screams] No!
- [Frank] Now look what you fucking made me do.
[grunting]
[grunts]
Jesus Christ. It's him.
- [grunts]
- What do you mean, it's him?
It's Justice.
[Frank] You shut the fuck up.
- One more fucking...
- [Karen gasps]
Samson? It's him.
[Samson] It's him? [whoops]
I knew it.
I knew I'd bring you luck.
[Dill] Hold her steady.
[strains]
Are you fucking nuts?
[Frank] Give that line to me.
Come on.
You're mine now.
You're fucking mine, baby.
Are you seriously
going to catch a fish? Now?
[strains]
No.
He is.
[Frank] This time
I'm gonna fucking do it.
Daddy, do you wanna
take the rod? Huh?
- Yeah.
- Huh?
Yeah, give me
that fucking rod.
Samson, the paying customer has
insisted that I transfer the rod to him.
Okay, Mr. Dill.
- Are you sure you can handle this beast, huh?
- [Frank] Fuck.
[Dill] You man enough?
Because let me tell you,
this motherfucker is the beast.
Give it here.
Put it in my left hand.
- Here we go. Huh?
- Give me the fucking rod.
- [Dill] Here we go.
- [Frank] Clip me in.
[Frank] Six feet under,
you and the fucking kid.
- [Karen screams]
- You hear me?
I will fucking bury you.
Whoa, man.
- Big enough to have his own fucking name.
- Yeah.
[Dill] Now, the question is,
do you want him?
[sobs] Don't let go, baby.
Don't let go.
He's yours now.
And you're his.
[grunts]
Man overboard!
[yells]
Patrick!
[reporter] In the Pompano
Beach area of Miami last night,
police responding to a 911 call
arrested a 13-year-old juvenile,
Patrick Zariakas,
on a charge
of second-degree murder.
The boy's stepfather, Frank
Zariakas, a construction worker,
was found with a single
knife wound to the chest.
Patrick's mother, Karen
Zariakas, claimed she and her son
had been the victims of domestic
violence for many years.
She claims Patrick
acted in self-defense
and to protect his mother
during a drunken assault.
Lindsey Carillo has more.
[Carillo] I'm outside the Rosemont
High School in Plymouth Boulevard
where Patrick's principal,
Dillon Baker, has issued a statement
describing Patrick as a gifted IT
student living in a troubled environment
who had withdrawn into a world
he created on his computer.
We have also learned that
Patrick Zariakas's real father,
Captain John Mason,
was killed in action in 2006
while fighting in Ramadi, Iraq.
He was posthumously awarded
the Purple Heart for gallantry.
So...
it's done.
I was telling the truth
when I said I love you.
And Patrick loves you.
And you love him.
Somewhere you will find him.
Yeah, somewhere.
Where?
[reporter] Police tell us that Patrick
will undergo a detention risk assessment
and due to
the mitigating circumstances,
will be released
into the custody of his mother.
We understand that, so far,
he has yet to speak to anyone
about what happened.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Dad? It's Patrick.
Is that you? Can you hear me?
Yeah, buddy.
It's Dad. It's Dad.
Dad, I just wanna know, are you okay?
What happened?
I don't know.
I don't know what happened.
I don't know anything,
you know.
Nobody knows anything.
You know,
all I know is that
there's a you and a me
somewhere.
Dad, I...
I did something real bad.
I know, I know. It's okay. It's okay.
You did the right thing.
You hear me?
Sometimes we do...
we do bad things for good reasons.
Dad, I'm gonna
change the game...
so I can come
visit you sometime.
Is that okay?
I'm here, all right?
Come.
Come see me.
We'll meet at the Serenity.
Huh?
We can go somewhere,
anywhere we want, huh?
Yeah, we'll go somewhere.
Yeah?
We'll go fishing.
Okay.
I'll meet you at the boat. Hmm?
[hangs up]
[Patrick]
I'm gonna change the game.
[laughs]
There's a you and a me...
somewhere.
Subtitles by explosiveskull