[car horns blaring]
(Doctor) Hippocrates said war's the
only proper school of the surgeon.
Know why?
Astound me.
'Cause he never saw what comes
in here on a Saturday night.
Talk to me
after it's been 7 hours.
You do know she
doesn't speak English, right?
Even better,
by the time she figures out
how to file a complaint,
I'll be across
the state line headed east.
So, you're actually
driving to Long Island?
The Hamptons.
Which, as I remember,
is located on--
Long Island, but saying it your
way makes it sound so tacky.
But 3,000 miles, by car.
Beemer's gotta
get there somehow.
What about
Dr. Whattahunk, hmm?
Couldn't he fly out
and then drive back with you?
And miss out on
$2,500 a house call?
Besides, he'll be waiting
for me when I get there
with flowers, gourmet dinner,
shoulder massage.
♪♪♪
(Doctor) Navigate to Bridge
Hampton, Long Island.
♪♪♪
We'll be there soon!
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Hi, I can't
wait to get there.
Me neither.
How far are you?
Um, I'm about to
cross into Louisiana
and the
Ouachita Parish.
Is that even a word?
Don't worry, by tomorrow night,
I'll be on I-95 North
headed for civilization.
And 3 days from now, cooling
my toes in the surf with you.
Hello?
Okay, I love you too.
Steve, can--?
[engine revving]
[siren wailing]
Aw!
License
and registration, ma'am?
What seems to be
the problem, officer?
One moment, ma'am.
Please don't run my
license, please, please!
Please don't!
♪♪♪
How fast would you say
you were going, Miss Leland?
Um...
Drivers response
is, "Um..."
Okay, officer--
Lester.
Officer Lester.
First name's Lester,
last name's O'Toole.
Officer Lester O'Toole.
Lester, can we just
settle this rig ht here?
Is this some
sort of bribe?
No, not unless you
take Visa or MasterCard.
[laughing]
(Lester) Oh,
you have got quite a sense of humor
for someone
that's going to jail.
How am I going to jail?
I mean,
I was just speeding.
That is not
a jailable offense.
Having 23
parking tickets is.
I've got a warrant for
your arrest, Miss Leland.
Doctor.
No, I feel fine.
Ma'am, you're
gonna have to appear.
When and where?
(Lester)
A courthouse.
Okay, when?
(Lester) A courthouse.
Well, I'll call
and round up the judge.
He should be here
at 10:30 or so,
unless he's fishing
or something.
Follow me
to the courthouse.
[groaning in frustration]
[gasping]
♪♪♪
Help me out of these,
will you?
Your Honor?
Hold your horses, missy.
You asked me to help.
What'd had happen if
you'd fell in with these on
and couldn't get 'em off?
I suppose I'd finally
get some peace and quiet.
Shouldn't you be
wearing a robe or something?
It's gone missing
along with my powdered wig.
Would you prefer we
reschedule this proceeding
'til they can be located?
No, Your Honor.
(Judge) Wonderful,
then let's get down to business, Miss--
Doctor.
No, no, I'm fine.
Lisa Leland, Your Honor.
Approach the bench.
Now Lester,
what was Miss Leland driving?
BMW, Your Honor.
One of the 3 series with the new
N54 twin-turbo inline-6 engine.
Phew!
Pretty fast, is it?
(Lester) Oh yes sir,
[clocked her at 90 miles an hour.
(Judge) Well Miss Leland, you seem
to be a regular one-woman crime wave.
I don't know how they
do it in, Los Angeles is it?
But having a warrant
out for your arrest
is no small taters
around here.
I admit, Your Honor,
I neglected to pay
a few parking tickets,
but! was gonna take care of all
of that once I got to New York.
I'm sure you were,
Miss Leland.
Now Lester, remind me, how
fast was Miss Leland going?
That would be
90 miles an hour, Your Honor.
I don't think her fires
were touching, Your Honor.
(Lisa) Excuse me, Your Honor, if!
may.
How do we know for sure
I was going that fast?
(Judge) Miss Leland,
allow me to make this easy for you.
You're gonna plead
"No contest."
The state requires
$500 for speeding,
$300 for
reckless endangerment,
$75 for the {mm-that may
seem 3 “Ne steep to you,
but that's what we
paid for it 6 months ago-
and $1,125
for unpaid parking tickets.
Now, I'm gonna waive
the court cost of $150,
and mars gonna
bring it to $2,000 even.
Pay the bailiff
and we can all go home.
(Lisa)
Your Honor?
I don't carry that
kind of cash on me.
Do you take credit cards?
Nope, what
about a check?
Yeah, where I come from
we don't use those.
Well, here in the land
that time forgot,
we still find them useful.
ATM?
Over at the bank.
(Lisa) Great, I'll just mosey
on over and get you your cash.
ATM's broken.
Gonna put me in jail?
Not unless I have to.
Tell me, Miss Leland, exactly
what kind of doctor are you?
General surgeon.
Perfect.
In lieu of fine, the court
orders 16 hours, 8 hours a day,
community service.
[rapping his gavel]
It's a win-win for everybody.
The only doctor around here
is a senile old coat
who should have been
put out to pasture years ago.
You can't do that.
Sure l can.
I just did.
Rapped my gavel
and everything.
[rapping his gavel again]
I refuse.
Let's make it 24 hours,
now that's 3 days.
Care to go for
a full 40-hour week?
Oh, my God!
(Judge) Miss Leland,
taking the Creator's name in vain
could come with
a sentence more severe
than anything
I could ever hand down.
I'm sorry,
thank you, Your Honor.
Outstanding.
You're released ROR pending
completion of community service.
Court's adjourned.
That means you're released
on your own recognizance.
Evidently the judge doesn't
consider you a flight risk,
at least
not without your car.
Pick those up, I'm going
back to bait and a cork.
♪♪♪
Come on, signal, come on!
Come on!
Hey, you might
want to try that corner.
Excuse me!
What?!
You may have better ll
over at that corner.
Okay, Jethro.
See this,
it's called a cell phone.
Yeah, I know you've
probably never seen one before
except on TV or maybe in
one of them movin' pictures,
but it communicates with
a satellite high above our head,
so high you can't
hardly imagine it.
(male) So what you're saying
is my suggestion of crossing
the street makes about
as much sense to you
as jumping up and down to get
a better look at the moon?
Have a nice day!
♪♪♪
[phone ringing]
Deep breath, and out.
Excuse me.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Hey, well,
I had a little incident.
Is the car okay?
The real problem is
they found out about the--
(Steve)
The parking tickets.
Yep, so I'm, like,
kind of in jail right now.
(Sieve)
Jail?
Actually, it's not jail.
I have to stay and do
3 days of community service.
Hello? Hello?
(Sieve)
Hello?
I am trapped in Maybe
Just leave, babe.
Yeah, I can't,
they have my car.
But maybe you
could come down.
Come down there?
Yeah, I mean, you know, only
if you don't have appointments.
Honey, I always
have appointments.
Rig ht, right, okay.
I'll be fine.
(Sieve) Thanks for
understanding, babe.
[deep sighing]
♪♪♪
You've got to be kidding me.
Coffee?
Yeah, any chance
of a decaf latte?
See this green handle?
That means decaf.
If you add a little bit of
milk to it, you've got a latte.
You can thank me later.
- Morning, Carly.
- Morning.
The usual,
make it to-go.
Sure thing, Doc.
How's everyone?
I'm guessing you're not
having the best of days.
Why don't you allow me
to buy you breakfast.
Consider it a part of
your rehabilitation process.
So, a judge named Doc.
Is it a nickname?
Of sons.
How'd you get it?
By earning
a medical degree.
You're a doctor?
Please try to contain
your sense of shock.
In small {owns,
we tend to wear a lot of hats.
I'm also the coroner, regional
disease control supervisor,
and chief coordinator
for the local blood drive.
Care to donate a pint
before breakfast?
Yeah, I think I'll pass,
I was also the mayor, but town
meetings got a little lonely.
So, when you said the
only doctor around here
is a senile old coot who
should have been put out
to pasture years ago?
I do tend to have
a flare for the dramatic.
(Cam)
You ready?
Do you have any
egg substitutions?
Sure! Oatmeal,
farina, cold cereal.
We've got toast too,
both kinds, white or rye.
Eggs, grits, and a biscuit
for our visitor, Carly.
So, when you sentenced me
to community service,
it was so you
could have time off?
Oh, that's just great.
I mean, this is
getting better and better.
Dr. Leland,
right now you're thinking
being stuck here in Normal
is the worst thing that could
have ever happened to you.
Well, I'm here
to assure you it is not.
Who knows,
if you allow yourself,
you just might find
you like it here.
I seriously doubt that.
Have it your way.
Oh, I almost forgot,
cafe closes at 4:30.
Folks around here tend to have
dinner with their families,
so if you'd like to eat again
before tomorrow morning,
why don't you stop by
my place, say around 6.
One more guest's
always welcome.
Do you make it
a point to invite
all your convicted
felons to your house?
Only the most
truly hardened cases.
We gonna see y'all now,
ya hear?
(Carly) Oh sweetie,
you're gonna have to go across the street
if you expect to use that.
You see, me satellite's
way over our heads
in what they call
low-earth orbit.
It's about 15,000 miles up, but
it's skewed to the southwest,
so Tinker Mountain, which
is actually just a big ol' hill,
kinda gets in
the way of the signal
'til you get
a little further away,
and suddenly,
you've got a clear line of sight
to the satellite
and you are good to go.
♪♪♪
[knocking on door]
Looks like you
found us alright.
Come on in.
Lisa, allow me to
introduce my daughter, Mandy.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Likewise, I'm sure.
Adopted.
Doc took Lucas and I in
after we lost our parents.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Oh, we aren't.
He was a godsend!
There's my grandbaby,
Kimberly.
Hello Dr. Leland!
Hi.
(DOC)
Where's Lucas?
(Mandy)
He's running late.
Have a seat.
[door opens]
(male)
Hey everybody.
Sorry I'm late.
Not late enough,
apparently.
- Hi, Uncle Lucas.
- Hey, squirt.
Lucas,
this is Dr. Leland.
Dr. Leland?
Yeah, we met earlier.
She was kind enough to
explain the finer points
of communications
technology to me.
Cam say grace?
Of course you can,
sweetheart.
Dearest Lord,
we thank you for this food,
and we thank you
for each other,
and we thank you for
Dr. Leland being here, amen.
[together]
Amen.
(Kimberly) Miss Leland,
do you like it here in Normal?
Well, it's different
than what I'm used to.
Different isn't bad,
Miss Leland.
It's just different.
Well, you're
very smart, Kim.
What grade are you in?
Well, I'm not
really in a grade.
I'm home-schooled.
Oh.
(Lucas) So,
she was brilliant a second ago,
'til you found out
she was home-schooled.
Now she's not, huh?
No, I didn't say that.
(Lucas) Yeah, you did,
just not in words.
The second you hear a bit
of south-in-the-mouth,
your estimate of our IQ
drops about 20 points.
Pretty soon, you're amazed
that we can tie a shoe
or operate
a light switch.
Lucas, I don't know
if that's fair.
No, no, that's okay.
Lucas seems to think that
people from outside of Normal
can be closed-minded, quick to
dismiss the opinions of others,
and judgmental,
but he's showing us
that those traits aren't
limited just to outsiders.
They can come
from anywhere.
You're making friends
everywhere you go.
Thank you.
(Lisa) Okay, seriously,
I apologized.
Did you?
I wonder how one
might get the approval
of the great Dr. Leland.
What do you think?
Mercedes-Benz?
Weekends in the Hamptons?
Deep tissue massages?
Mandy, is that
peach cobbler ready yet?
Wow, you're
a mind-reader too.
What else can you do?
Oh, I bet the answer
to that is anything.
Yeah, you know, when you pulled
up in the truck this morning,
you know what
I was thinking?
“There's me man who knows
everything, can do anything,
and is never wrong.“
Well, forgive me
if! didn't fall
for the $5 charm
and the $10 smile.
Yeah, it might work
with some women,
but it isn't
working on me.
Five-dollar charm, huh?
I'll have you know
the people in this town-
Yeah, I'm sure you will,
or would if I were staying,
but I'm not.
Doc, thank you.
Mandy, what looks
to be a great dinner.
But you haven't
had any dessert yet.
(Lisa)
Maybe next time, Kim.
Mama's peach cobbler
is awesome.
It was nice
to meet you.
Oh, no you don't.
I'm going first,
otherwise you'll tell
everybody we threw you out.
After you.
Oh no, after you.
I'll have you know people in
this town do think I'm charming.
(Lisa)
Only proving my point.
Well Lord,
you answered my prayer.
You sent her, but now
how do we make her stay?
♪♪♪
Something wrong, Doc?
Can you drop me off
at the nearest motel?
There isn't one.
There isn't one?
(Lester) Nothing closer than
Asheville, and that's 40 miles away,
which is why Doc
called and asked me
to fix you up
a bed in the jail.
You're kidding me.
No, ma'am!
I took the liberty of grabbing
your things from the car
and putting them
in the trunk.
Hop on in!
Alright, buckle up, now.
♪♪♪
[sighing]
It's all yours.
Oh, you're not a suicide risk
or anything are you,
'cause then I'd need to take
your belt and shoe laces.
Are you asking me if I'm at risk
because of the speeding ticket
or because I have to spend
a long weekend in this town?
It was a civil question.
Sorry, I think I can safely
say that I am not at risk.
Okay.
Aren't you gonna
lock me in or something?
Why?
I mean, what if there's
a fire or something?
It's not like you're some
notorious felon or anything.
Oh, your cell
won't work in your cell.
[laughing]
Telephone's on the desk.
Just pick it up and hit 1
if you need anything.
It'll call
my place direct.
Good night, Doc.
♪♪♪
Excuse me, I came
to ask about my...
...car.
(Lucas)
What's the matter?
Afraid you'll have to be nice
to me to get your Beemer back?
Can we just start over?
Okay, you go first.
Look, I'm sorry
I wasn't so nice to you,
and I'm sorry that
I called you Jethro,
and I'm sorry that-
can we just save some time
and leave it at "I'm sorry"?
Thanks, Amman.
Yup.
Hey Doc,
apology accepted.
[engine revving]
He makes me so angry!
What, Lucas?
He's a great guy.
Once you get to know him,
he's a real charmer.
My car,
I need to see it.
Oh, she's beautiful.
You can have her back.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You got the paperwork saying
you completed community service?
No.
Then not really.
[deep sighing]
♪♪♪
[knocking on door]
(Lisa)
Hello?
Come on in.
I'm here to pay off
my debt to society.
(DOC) How was your
first night in jail?
Nicest jail
I've ever slept in.
Plus, I think half
the town said hello to me
on the way over here.
What do folks say
to each other in Los Angeles?
Nothing if possible.
What's weirder is they
were all calling me Doc.
I thought that
was your rifle.
Word gets around.
I don't see
a medical diploma.
What makes you
think I got one?
Lying doesn't strike me
as part of your repertoire.
What time's
my first appointment?
As soon as
you get there.
I'm doing housecalls?
"Go where y'all are needed"
is the Hippocratic oath.
No, it's not.
It should be.
Your bag's right there.
Your first call is Rita Caffey,
1725 Purdey Lane.
(Lisa)
How do I get there?
Your transportation's
parked in the driveway
next to the
white picket fence.
♪♪♪
[doorbell ringing]
Before Doc examines me,
we always begin with a prayer.
Oh.
♪♪♪
Where do we begin?
(female patient) Where we always
do, with Chester.
Oh, oh, no.
Doc always leads.
Chester needs his injection and
I can't bear to give it to him,
so Doc Shelby does it for us,
doesn't he Chester?
(Lisa) Dear Lord, hi,
let's help Rita get well, amen.
That's it?
'Fraid so.
Can you lift the sleeve
of your blouse, please?
[sigh of frustration]
I love you, love you,
love you, so cute!
(Lisa)
Please, please, please!
[groans in frustration]
Don't you people
believe in street signs?
I mean, I've been
circling for hours.
Just say the word.
Will you please
take me back to jail?
So, how'd you find me?
Doc felt sorry for you.
I tried to
talk him out of it.
How's it going so far?
Well, this town's really getting
its money's worth out of me.
How so?
Well, in the Hamptons,
I'd be making $2,500 a visit.
So, if these were paying visits,
they'd be good visits then?
You tell me,
my last patient had fleas.
What, you don't like dogs?
Not even a little.
No dogs, no cats,
not even goldfish.
The last patient
asked me to pray for her.
And?
Don't you think
that's weird?
I'm a doctor.
I heal people.
I guess I just always
thought that when patients
pray to be healed,
God listens.
Well, sometimes
his process benefits
from a prescription
of Amoxicillin.
(Lucas) Well,
I may be just a country boy,
but as I see it, there's
no conflict between the two.
You do know the earth
is round, don't you?
Yes I do, yes I do.
♪♪♪
What's that?
I know you're
from Los Angeles,
but don't tell me you
don't know that's a cross.
Of course
I know it's a cross.
What's it doing up there?
Making people stop and
think for a moment, I suppose.
You drove right past it
on your way into town.
And I'll drive right
past it on my way out.
♪♪♪
- I got it.
- Oh, thanks.
♪♪♪
There ya go, Doc.
You have a good night.
Thanks, good night.
♪♪♪
“Rae's Cate
dosed tomorrow.
"Pancake breakfast at church.
See you there, Lester."
♪♪♪
One day down, two to go.
(congregation singing)
I Coming for to carry me home ♪♪
He's the minister, too?
(DOC) "--who are weary and burdened, and!
will give you rest.
“Take my yoke upon you
and follow me.
and learn from me,
"for! am gentle
and humble in heart
and you will find rest
for your souls."
The Bible is always
giving us examples
mm simple folk
will understand.
But around here, we don't
have any mustard bushes,
or fig trees, or grape vines,
or vineyards, or wine presses--
at least, not in any number.
But what we do have
is pecans.
[congregation laughing]
Left to themselves,
pecan trees will overhear,
too much fruit on the branch.
So much so that even a
rainbreeze'll crack the bow,
meaning you lose both
the crop and the tree.
Well, our lives
are like those trees.
We need to go through and pluck
away those things in our lives
that initially look beautiful,
but in {he end
just weigh us down.
Whatever it is,
we need to trim it away,
and if we do our part,
God will do his part
by strengthening the bow.
John 10:10,
"I have come that
you might have life
and that you might have
it abundantly," amen?
(congregation)
Amen.
(Doc singing) I I'm climbing up on
the rough side of the mountain :
I I'm going to hold on
his powerful hand I
♪ I'm climbing up on me
rough side of the mountain ♪♪
♪♪♪
So, this happens
every week?
Yeah, we get
together every week.
It's sort of a tradition.
If any body's
having a tough time,
we try to make sure
they go home with leftovers.
Great pancakes, huh?
Yeah, I'll let you know.
How'd your
rounds go yesterday?
Unusual.
Rita ask you to
pray with her, did she?
Mm-hmm.
Come take a walk
with me, will you?
Pass me the syrup,
could you? Thank you.
(DOC) I've got to tell you that
my vocation, my true calling,
is serving others.
Medicine is my avocation.
It's part of howl answer my
calling, but it's not all of it.
I minister to bodies, but I also
minister to hearts and souls.
Are you sure the
AMA would approve?
Dr. Leland, I'd like to
challenge your experience
and training for just
a moment, in could.
Alright.
With all due respect,
I submit that if you accept
a patient into your care,
you manage to treat
his or her symptoms,
alleviate all unnecessary pain,
extend their days to the
full extent of your art,
yet leave them sad,
lonely, and in fear of death,
which comes for us all,
you've not reached
your full potential.
Think about it, will ya“?
Hey.
Hungry there,
ain't you boy?
Figured you were hungry.
Starved.
And I'm sorry for not
saying I was sorry before
when you told me
you were sorry.
That's a whole lot
of sorry.
- Truce?
- Truce.
So, you had a little
chat with Doc, huh?
Well, I can't say
I did much of the talking.
Yeah well, you come to church,
you're likely to hear a sermon,
whether you're
anxious to or not.
Now you're starting
to sound like Doc.
I'll take that
as a compliment.
I guess I believe that-
Yeah well,
I don't know what I believe.
That's okay.
The trick is is once
you do figure it out,
just not being
afraid to go with it,
no matter how weird
or different it is.
I'm not afraid
of different.
I see different every day
with my patients,
and I adapt with
each one of them
in order to save lives.
That's good.
Good that you've got everyone
else's lives figured out,
but! just wonder--now don't
take this the wrong way.
I just wonder if maybe you ought
to take that bottle of medicine
and give yourself
a couple spoonfuls.
You must think
you're pretty smart.
About average
for a country boy.
Isn't that right, squirt?
Kimberly Smith,
I told you to slow down.
Kim? Kimberly!
She can't breathe,
she's choking!
No, stop!
Grab her, follow me.
What are you doing?
Where's Doc?!
(Lisa) No, there's no
time, she's suffocating.
Follow me!
- It's okay.
- I'll go get Doc.
Lay her on the bed.
Easy!
Move.
[gasping]
Is she okay?
She's gonna be fine.
Oh, thank you God.
It's okay, it's okay.
What is that thing?
An epi pen.
It's loaded
with epinephrine.
Artificial adrenaline.
It'll raise your
blood pressure to counteract
the drop in blood pressure.
An allergic reaction
caused this.
(Lisa) I'm allergic to bees,
so it was my first thought.
I caught sight of
that welt behind her neck
and her eyes
told me the rest.
She's never
been stung before.
(Lisa) Yeah well,
you'll need to make sure
you have one of these
around at all times.
I'll show you how to
use it before I leave.
Good thing you were here.
Lucky coincidence.
Oh, there's no such thing
as a coincidence.
(Lisa) Funny, from the man
who sentenced me to be here.
♪♪♪
You're not gonna
believe what happened!
I saved a little
girl's life today.
That's basically something
you did about once per shift
back in L.A., right?
Well yeah, but, I don't know,
this time it was different.
(Sieve)
How?
I don't know.
We were at church and-
(Steve) Whoa, whoa,
since when do you go to church?
Since I wanted
to eat breakfast.
Huh?
How's it going
back there?
(Steve) Oh great, babe.
I really wish you were here.
You know how much
money we're losing
from the patients
you're not treating?
I can't imagine.
(Sieve) Well,
don't worry about it, babe.
Your new patients
can't wait to meet you.
[phone ringing]
Oh, gotta go, love you!
You too.
You know, it's beer
a pretty big day for
I guess you
could say that.
Rae's opens
at 2 on Sundays.
Mind in
buy you a coffee?
It's your town.
You know,
it could be yours too.
I don't think so.
Besides,
it's already got a doctor.
Not for long.
Are you moving?
I had a little chat
with the Father,
and he reminded me
that none of us
are gonna live forever
on this earth.
And 10 satisfy your
professional skepticism,
Duke University's
Chief of Oncology confirmed it.
What kind?
Doesn't matter.
(Lisa) I knew doctors researching
radio wave treatments,
vitamin dosage therapies.
(DOC) My 5-year prognosis
is less than 12%,
and that's if it
were caught in time.
Mine wasn't.
You know there are ways-
I'm not spending my remaining
days on this earth in a bed,
hoping for a
medical breakthrough
that may never come.
Not when
I can go fishing.
Why are you
telling me this?
So that maybe you
would consider staying,
and so mail could
make sure rm; patients
and this entire {own
is in good hands after I'm gone.
I appreciate you
telling me this,
but I'm almost done
serving my time,
and then I'm gonna
jump in my car,
while obeying the fine laws
of the open road, of course,
and get back to my life.
Well, if you have to
get back to your life,
then who's been living it
while you've been here?
Maybe you've
found a new way
01 living mm precious
life of yours right here.
Cam ca“ you Lisa?
Lisa, small towns
need doctors.
When they lose them,
the town begins to die.
Folks move away, gradually
at first, then more and more.
I've lived long enough to
see it happen a dozen times.
I don't want that
to happen to Normal.
I'm sorry.
Promise me
you'll think about it.
Please, don't mention
this conversation to anyone.
They say there are
no secrets in small towns,
but I've managed
to keep this one, 'til now.
I won't say a word.
I promise.
Good.
I've got to
get to the lake.
I'm sure the fish
are biting today.
♪♪♪
Nice ride.
Where are you going
all dressed up?
Why don't you
get in and find out?
I can't, I have
community service.
(Lucas) Nah,
[cleared it with Doc already.
It'll count
toward your time.
(Lucas) 1 want to thank
you for yesterday.
That little girl means the
world to my sister and to me.
No problem,
that's what I do.
Speaking of which,
what do you do?
I fight crime.
Wouldn't surprise me.
So, where are we going?
We're going to Asheville.
We're going to court.
More specifically,
Buncombe County Superior Court.
What on earth did you do?
I didn't do anything, but the
American Civil Liberties Union
seems to feel that
Normal represents a threat
to our free society.
What's Normal
done to offend anybody?
Well, you remember that
cross up on Tinker Mountain?
Suddenly the ACLU is
determined to make it go away.
So, who's
arguing your case?
You're a lawyer.
Nope.
But you're
going to law school':
No, this is one of the last
states to allow an attorney
to practice law
without a law degree,
as long as you
pass the bar exam.
A list which, incidentally,
includes California.
Okay, but who'd want an
attorney without a degree?
Yeah, you're
probably rig ht.
I mean, who'd want
a sew-educated lawyer
like Daniel Webster,
or Clarence Darrow,
Abraham Lincoln?
♪♪♪
(Lisa) It looks a little
crowded over there.
What do you
want me to do?
Why don't you just stack all
this stuff in a nice, neat pile.
When it all starts,
take notes.
Do you have a pen?
Make sure you
write small enough
so nobody knows
what you're writing.
Better yet, scribble
like a doctor, only worse.
If I lean in like this,
whisper something in my ear.
It doesn't matter what.
(lawyer) Is your co-counsel
admitted to the Louisiana bar?
Oh, Your Honor,
my associate here
is here on an
advisory capacity only.
She will not be
addressing the court directly.
I'll allow it.
Welcome Miss--
Leland.
Doctor--Lisa Leland,
Your Honor.
Welcome Miss Leland.
Now then, I understand
in the matter of
the ACLU vs. the Town 01 Normal,
that there is a cross.
It is lit by night and
it stands on public property.
That's rig ht,
there is, Your Honor.
And I also understand
that a petition has been filed
for its removal.
Has it been removed?
No, it has not.
Is the co-petitioner here?
Your Honor, Mr. Erwin Driscoll
lives in Massachusetts.
His presence
would be inconvenient,
so we, the ACLU,
are representing his interests.
Well, of course you are.
We request a motion
to dismiss, Your Honor.
On what grounds?
(Lucas) Nearly 182 years
without a complaint,
'til last week, Your Honor.
And I have here--
hand me that bottom one there.
I have here a petition signed
by virtually every citizen
above the age of majority
in Normal.
Objection,
irrelevant, Your Honor.
Objection sustained.
This case will proceed 10 {rial
on the 10th of this month.
Court is adjourned.
Excuse me, Your Honor,
what you're saying is it
really doesn't matter what the
300 residents of my town want,
it only matters
what Mr. Erwin Driscoll
of Cambridge,
Massachusetts wants.
As long as that cross stands
on public property, Mr. Craig,
you, sir,
are largely correct.
Well, I've gotta tell you, with
all due respect, Your Honor,
that doesn't seem American,
it doesn't seem civil,
and it sure doesn't
seem like liberty.
But thank you, Your Honor.
The people of Normal
will be ready by the 10th.
Yeah, that
doesn't seem rig ht.
I mean, someone who comes
into town for 5 minutes
getting to determine
what the people of Normal
can and can't do?
Fair's got nothing
to do with it, really.
I think the key word
is "public."
What do you mean?
Well, if you
buy the mountain,
the land would be
private, right?
Then you could
keep the cross.
If I buy the mountain?
I couldn't afford
that mountain.
My whole town couldn't
afford that mountain.
You'll figure it out.
You obviously believe in it,
so you'll figure it out.
Okay.
Are you hungry?
Yeah, I'm always hungry.
Great, it's time to
expand your horizons.
Okay.
♪♪♪
I don't know about this.
Trust me, I'm a doctor.
♪♪♪
[laughing]
Well, you know, for raw fish,
this isn't half bad.
Well, you're just
full of surprises.
So Doc, how come you don't
have a ring on your finger?
Surprise.
He hasn't asked.
Why not?
How long you two
been together?
- Five years.
- Five years?!
Would you keep
your voice down!
Well, it seems to me if
you love him and he loves you.
Well, it seems to me that you
should mind your own business.
Thank you, though.
I think I'd have
asked you by year 2.
Maybe year 3 depending
on how much work you were.
Well, there's no reason
to think that I would
say yes if you did.
Well, that's what makes
it interesting, doesn't it?
What's this
here green stuff?
Wasabi.
It's Japanese
horseradish.
But you don't
want to go there.
Never tell that
to a country boy.
Don't say
I didn't warn you.
Three, two, one.
Yeah, we're gonna need
a glass of milk over here.
[laughing]
How much is it gonna
cost me to keep you quiet?
How 'bout you get Jimmer
to give me my car back?
It's yours.
I still have 3 hours.
Oh well, Doc's
got enough fishing in.
Our dinners probably
from his haul this weekend.
I don't think he's
gonna be a stickler
about a few hours
of service.
Well, maybe you
should join Doc
on one of those fishing trips
every once in awhile.
Just saying,
I'll finish out my hours.
Why would you do that?
You can get on out
of here if you want to.
I finish what I start,
always have.
(Lucas) Well,
problem is sometimes it's only after
you start something you
realize it was a mistake.
Close your eyes!
- Why?
- Just close 'em.
- Keep 'em closed now.
- They're closed.
Keep 'em closed.
Watch your step.
Gravel.
Good, good, okay.
Now, we're gonna come
to some steps here.
Keep 'em closed.
Make sure you
can't see nothing, okay?
Now close your eyes.
Alright, nope!
Don't open 'em!
No.
You've seen the lights
of L.A., right?
I want you to see
the lights of Normal.
Go ahead,
open your eyes.
♪♪♪
This is so beautiful.
Oh, growing up here
must have been amazing.
I'd say growing up here
was mostly boring,
but then again, it can
be inspiring sometimes.
Well, that's really it.
Better get goin'.
Well, yeah, sorry.
Thanks for taking me.
Yeah, we gotta get goin'
'cause you got
a big day tomorrow
Oh, what's tomorrow?
Tomorrow's the
Founder's Day Dance,
and you are a celebrity.
You need your rest,
come on.
♪♪♪
I These footsteps in the hall I
♪ Well, they'll wake me
every night I
♪ There's not a soul in sight I
♪" And I see your face
in most everyone I meet ♪"
♪" I'm dying
and you're fast asleep ♪"
♪" You have more than
the memories, 'cause you" ♪"
(DOC)
Enjoying the party?
I am!
Happy Founder's Day!
Bet you never thought
you'd hear me say that.
Well, it does come
as something of a surprise.
Hi, Doc!
Miss Leland, do you
hate my uncle Lucas?
No, I don't hate him.
(Kimberly)
Sure seemed like it.
Well, sometimes when
people don't get along,
it's because they haven't
given each other a chance.
So you like him?
Yeah, yeah.
Do you like him a lot?
Well, I suppose
he's okay.
Are you falling
in love with him?
Kim!
No, no, I mean, I--
it's not that I couldn't
fall in love with him.
It's just that I'm already
in love with someone else.
Really?
Really.
May I have this dance?
♪♪♪
(Mandy) That little girl
just loves him to death.
I can see that.
(Mandy) Must be that
$5 charm and $10 smile.
♪♪♪
♪" You have more
than the memories ♪"
♪" 'Cause you,
you have a little piece of me ♪"
♪" I haven't slept in weeks
and I drink all day ♪"
I'd have thought
he'd be taken already.
There isn't a woman in town
who isn't interested in Lucas.
So, what's
holding him back?
I haven't seen him spark
to anyone in particular...
until recently.
I have to leave...
you know that.
I know.
♪" Oh yeah,
I'm dying and you're okay ♪":
[applauding]
(Kimberly) Uncle Lucas
taught me how to two-step.
(Lucas) That's only 'cause
two's as high up as I can count.
(Lisa) Oh, I don't know if!
know how.
Well, I didn't really ask you
if you knew how.
I just want to know
if you'd like to.
Okay.
♪" There's no pair
in your life or mine ♪"
♪" So I'll go about
my business ♪"
♪" Wait for somebody new ♪"
♪" And just pray
there's something like you ♪"
♪" Now, when l had you, girl,
that old sun, it was a-shinin' ♪"
♪" Lord, it felt right
to be next to you, yeah ♪"
♪ And yes, I may have-- ♪
I do believe you can dance,
Miss Leland.
That's Dr. Leland,
Mr. Craig.
♪" And just pray
there's something like you ♪"
♪♪♪
So, what else
do you believe?
What else do I believe?
I believe
in promises,
ones that last,
the ones we make to God,
and ones we make
to each other.
I think that you can
say something in 2 seconds
that you will regret
the rest of your life.
And I believe that some
folks are just meant to"
well, they're just
meant to bloom
rig ht where
they're planted,
and other folks,
why, they're destined
for some other place.
And! believe that
I could be happy
spending the rest
of my life by myself
if that's
what's meant to be.
I'd rather I didn't.
[cell phone ringing]
I'm sorry, excuse me.
Of course,
now l get reception.
Hello?
I've been trying
to call you for hours.
Where have you been?
Rig ht here.
What's going on,
another church breakfast?
No, it's actually
a barbecue with a dance.
Great, a dance.
Do you understand
how much you're costing us
by not being here?
You can bill me
when I get there.
What's gotten into you?
Look, I just have
to finish out my sentence
and I'll be up there
by the weekend.
Nothing's changed.
You sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
♪♪♪
That's a nice car
you've got there.
You must be
looking for Lisa.
How'd you know?
Just a wild guess.
So, do you know
where she is?
(Lucas)
Yeah, I do.
Well, I'll tell ya' what,
why don't you just hop in
and I'll take you
on over.
[engine revving]
- So, what brings you over?
- I called her last night.
She sounded
kind of strange.
I got worried, so I drove
all night to get down here.
Must have been
doing 80 all the way.
Yeah, something like that.
So, do the Clampetts
live here in Hooterville?
Bug Tussle.
Excuse me?
Green Acres
and Petticoat Junction
were set in Hooterville.
The Clampetts
were from Bug Tussle.
So, what kind of medicine
do you practice, Dr. Steve?
I'm a concierge doctor.
What's that mean?
I make house calls for those
who can afford my services:
$2,531) 3 ca“.
That's pretty impressive.
Nobody wants to get sick
around you, that's for sure.
So, you and Lisa are-
Yep, we're
getting married.
Is that right?
Does she know that?
Well, not yet, but...
Do you know
how many horses
we could feed
with those carats, huh?
A lot of horses...
I guess.
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder continues]
Hey Doc, prisoner 137
reporting to final
3 hours of duty.
(DOC)
Come have a seat, darlin'.
I've got
a confession to make.
When I sentenced you
to do community service,
sent you around
to see all those patients,
I wasn't pushing
them off on you.
I know.
You were grooming me
to take over for you.
I was sharing them
with you.
You see, the Father sometimes
works in not-so-mysterious ways,
like when you showed up here
the way you did.
I've thought a lot
about what you've said.
And whoever it is
you've been praying for-
And I understand you
wanting to make sure
that your town
is taken care of when you-
It's not me.
I just want a nice life.
Is that so bad?
No.
Not at all.
Which is why,
effective immediately,
I'm commuting
the rest of your sentence.
You're free to go,
to find whatever it is
you're looking for,
come what may.
{just hope that when you
look back on your time here,
you'll think of us fondly.
Some of us have
gotten attached to you.
♪♪♪
There's my girl!
What's wrong?
Uh, nothing, it's just--
you're here!
Hey, I'm all about grand
gestures when it comes to you.
So, how's my girl?
Um, I'm fine.
I know what you need.
A spa day, cucumber mask,
hot stones, mud bath,
sipping a chi tea latte.
How does that sound?
Yeah, great.
(Sieve) Oh, and by the way,
while you're lying there,
you can stare at this.
Oh, wow!
I mean, um...
did you even ask?
Well, I didn't
think I'd have to.
I would have thought
you knew what it meant.
I-
I know.
Yes.
Can you just give
me a minute, please?
Yeah, babe.
Lucas, I'm sorry.
My life is in
another place.
Yeah, I know.
You're gonna finish
what we started.
[engine revving]
♪♪♪
Gonna need more than a prayer
to win this one, Mr. Craig.
Mr. We", are you ready?
We are, Your Honor.
Mr. Craig?
Your Honor-
Respondent requests a motion
to dismiss, Your Honor.
Grounds, Mr. Craig?
(Lucas) Well, you see Your
Honor, the cross of question
no longer stands
on public land.
You moved it?
Not exactly, Your Honor.
I have here...
a certified bill of sale
for a plot of land
25 feet by 25 feet,
that's 1!80th of an acre
which just so happens
to contain that cross.
Mr. Well, your case hinges
on a public display of religion
on public property,
property that is now private,
therefore it is the ruling of
this court that your complaint
has no grounds, and your
petitioner has no standing.
Take some time and enjoy
our little town, Mr. Won,
before you go back 10
wherever it is you came from.
- But Your Honor--
- Case dismissed.
♪♪♪
I bet you think you're
pretty smart, don't you?
About average
for a country boy.
♪♪♪
Wow.
Okay, last-minute
checklist.
So, the maharaji's
in place,
and the harpist finally
got back from the bathroom.
Since there's no one
to give you away,
you'll be on your own.
So, make sure you
wait here until the end
of the "Wedding March"
intro, okay,
or you'll end up at the altar
with half the song left to go.
You got it?
Lisa?
You okay?
I think I got a glimpse
of the way my life show
Should be?
(Lisa) The way God
wants my life to be.
He tried to show me,
but I wasn't paying attention
God?
Yeah, my eyes
were opened to new things,
new people, and new ways.
I have a chance to
make a difference in life.
You make a difference.
What kind of life
are you talking about?
I'm talking about a life
where what I eat,
and what I wear
and what I drive
is less important
than who I am,
and who I love,
and who loves me.
And it's not about
making a living,
but about making a life,
and going to church,
and giving thanks
for a life
that you're genuinely
thankful for.
Which is why I can't
go through with this.
Wait, none of this
makes any sense.
I know,
which is why it makes
all the sense in the world.
♪♪♪
[car honking]
Well, shut my mouth!
It's about time
she got back here.
♪♪♪
Lucas!
Lucas Craig!
You let me go.
I had to.
Well that was
just stupid.
You drove 2,000 miles
just to call me stupid?
What about your fiancé,
or I guess your husband by now.
So, what do you
want from me?
I want what you've got,
and the thing is,
it's not like you were
looking to keep it
a secret.
You were offering it
the whole time,
only I wasn't willing
to accept it.
And now you are?
Look, you said it yourself,
you life is in another place.
I know, you're absolutely
right, I did say that.
Bet you think you're
pretty smart, don't you?
About average
for a city girl.
♪♪♪
(Doc voiceover) There are
those who claim it's impossible
to learn what we're
meant to do or meant to be.
But the folks who say that
end 10 be living
for a God who shouts
and completely miss
the One who whispers.
But! side with Paul
who wrote,
"We see only
a dim reflection
"as though through
a glass, darkly.
"But one day
we shall see face-to-face.
"And what we
now know in part
“one day
we shall know fully.
"But in the meantime,
these three things remain:
“faith, hope, and love,
and the greatest of these
is love."
♪♪♪