A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
At this pace, we will never finish.
It's really hot.
We're going to get sunburned.
He's taking so long
with the girls, right?
Yeah.
Damn kid,
put the drone down.
Calm down, Piporro.
I was following orders.
Yeah? No kidding!
Because the only orders
we follow here
are the ones from Cara Sucia,
my boss.
Come.
Hello.
- Hello.
- It's good to see you.
Oh...
Hey.
I wanted to talk with you.
I'm looking for Cara Sucia,
I called him on his cellphone
but he didn't answer.
He left really early
and I haven't heard from him.
Damn Cara Sucia.
Leave that.
Come with me,
and change your clothes.
- What should I wear, sir?
- I don't know.
Something decent.
Something that makes you look...
handsome, with personality.
- Go ahead.
- Yes, sir.
Come, come.
How many?
What are you selling?
I think that the important thing here
is what I'm offering to you.
As you know,
it's been very dangerous lately.
This place is full of immigrants.
There are a lot of criminals.
A lot of crooks.
We are offering protection.
Damn.
I support the local police.
Listen to him.
The local police have no idea
about what's happening
in the area.
And if you don't cooperate,
one day you'll wake up
to see your store burnt down.
What do you say?
I barely earn enough money
to pay my expenses.
What a shame.
You'll have to work more then.
You and everybody here.
Okay?
This is our territory now.
And those who don't cooperate,
get their stores burned down.
Is that clear?
Yeah?
Okay.
We came to see Mr. Revueltas.
The boss is waiting for you.
Go ahead.
- Open the door.
- You're going to see El Botas,
you'll explain
how these things work, the...
- Drones.
- Yeah, that.
So, this is it.
So?
- Are you leaving? I'm the boss.
- Yeah.
- The boss of everyone.
- Yeah, sure.
I want it to be very clear.
- Yeah, Boss.
- So, go ahead.
Let's go.
Let's go over there.
To the tent.
This time,
we'll give you a chance.
Next time, be ready.
I want my money.
All of it, okay?
Here.
Damn you.
Fuck.
Give him this.
Wow, it's so cool!
Mom, can you give us a ride?
Yes, but first...
open up your presents!
Presents! Presents!
One for you and one for you.
Choche!
- How are you, man?
- How are you?
Wow, you haven't come here
in years!
- What have you been doing?
- Well, you know...
Working. What else?
This is the Yankee.
And this man in front of you
is the best businessman
in all Sinaloa.
Thanks, man.
- Nice to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you.
- Good things, I hope.
- No.
Bad things.
- Do you want a drink?
- Yes, yes.
- Let me.
- Thanks, kid.
- Here.
- Cheers.
- It's a pleasure, sir.
- Thanks.
Yeah.
- Great.
- Yes.
Boss, I almost forgot.
Can you tell him I already have
the information he needed?
- The coordinates?
- Yeah, those.
- Okay. There's work to do.
- Yeah, Boss. Okay.
Bye, Boss.
What, fuckers?
Damn crooks.
Can I help you?
Hello.
Yeah, I want...
I want this tattoo
on my chest.
And do you want one number
next to the other?
No, I was thinking...
One number on top of the other.
- Like coordinates.
- Okay.
Where do you want it?
Here.
Okay?
Is this the actual size?
I don't know.
What do you suggest?
Well...
I can show you two different fonts
and you can decide
which you like best.
Okay?
Okay.
Hold on a few minutes.
Take a seat.
Sir.
Everything okay?
Is that its nest?
Whose?
The animal, the owl.
Didn't you see it?
They told me you like technology.
Yeah, I love it.
And drones.
Yeah, drones are my specialty.
If you want, I can be your supplier.
- Dad!
- Kid!
- How are you?
- Say hi, darling.
- You look so nice.
- Thanks.
Let me introduce you to a new friend.
The Yankee.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too. Malcolm Moriarty.
For an American
he speaks good Spanish.
My mom was from Caborca.
So, at home we had to speak Spanish or...
pay the consequences.
- It should always be like that.
- Sure.
- In every home.
- So true.
Look.
What's that?
Open it.
It's your cut
from Longoria Real Estate.
Malcolm and I are
the only owners now.
Phoebe, I know this isn't my business,
and I don't want to know where
this money comes from,
but you can't just be giving cash away.
If it hurts, tell me and I'll stop.
No, don't worry.
I'm used to it.
Okay.
What are these coordinates for?
Or, where do they take you?
These are the coordinates
of the desert.
I had an experience there.
I wanted to mark the place.
I understand.
What's your name?
Laura.
What a nice name.
And yours?
I'm Fidelia.
Gentleman...
proceed.
Turn around!
We're in the middle of an operation
implemented by District Attorney Del Toro,
in this all-out war on crime.
District Attorney Del Toro,
why did you make the decision
to carry out this operation?
Look, lady...
SECURITY REINFORCED WITH HELP OF THE ARMY
The figures you see here,
kidnappers use them
to scare the citizens
and to destabilize peace
in the region.
But why is the army here?
The police wouldn't dare to do it?
That's nonsense.
We're working together with the army
on this occasion,
as it concerns
our homeland security.
Okay, sir, and how do you think
this operation will have an impact
on the reduction of the rate of violence?
Excuse me.
Attorney Del Toro?
Follow me!
Okay, cut.
Move.
They are dead.
Cabe and Pacheco.
No way.
And Pl치cido?
He was with them.
They wanted to find us
to cut our tongues out.
- Shut up.
- No, no, don't kill her.
- No, I'm done.
- You're so weak.
Cheers, cheers.
All of it.
What's going on, guys?
Aren't you...?
Are you just chatting?
- Yes, Uncle.
- Yes.
Kid, I have to take him.
- What for?
- But, we are...
Yeah, fine. See you later.
See you.
I already told you...
Carlos Revueltas
is an important businessman,
but aside from that,
he's friends with Botas' cartel.
So, don't mess with her,
or you will see his true colors.
You'll have a lot of problems.
Yes, Mr. Cecho, don't worry.
Let me answer this call.
Wilson, what do you want?
I'm busy.
We have a problem.
Pacheco and Cabe were killed.
Hey, and...
What did you do
with the bodies?
We have them in the trunk.
We found them in the road
in really bad shape and...
we are looking for Pl치cido.
We don't know where he is.
This...
is not over, Wilson.
Relax.
I'm coming.
I need you to wait for me, okay?
Okay.
Hey, Yankee.
Where are you going?
- Hey, wait.
- Choche, I was betrayed.
They set me up.
If you want to be in this business,
get used to betrayals.
You will never have a calm day.
So, trust your people.
I know what I'm talking about.
I don't care.
No, let's go. This is an important day.
You have to meet these people
so they trust you.
Then, we'll figure out
the rest.
- What's up?
- What's up, girl?
- It's all good.
- Are you selling ice cream?
- No.
Are you waiting
for somebody?
Hello.
What's going on?
You look so nice.
Thanks.
- Give me another one.
- Yes.
She's paying...
- She's paying?
- My friend will pay, yeah.
- Here.
- Hey.
- I just saw a guy with a tattoo.
- What?
What?
I just saw a guy with a tattoo.
What's up?
- What's up, Peggio?
- How are you?
Arleen is already near the wall
waiting for you.
- Well, I'm ready if she's ready.
- You bet.
- Hello.
- This is Laura.
- I'm Peggio.
- Hello.
He's the owner.
Think of this as your house.
Do as you please.
Cool.
Hey, Fidelia.
- There's a guy with a tattoo.
- What?
You know what? Nothing.
I needed to go out.
I haven't been out in ages.
Well, girl,
if you want to have
a better time...
No one's forcing you.
Or what?
So, you are the gringo, right?
- Yes, sir.
- Oh, I said "gringo".
Yankee. I'm sorry.
I'm Parra.
Nice to meet you, sir.
Botas!
Come, Botas.
He's the kid with the drones.
- Sir.
- Kid?
At his age, I was already dominating
half of Sinaloa.
So?
How much coke
can those things carry?
Well,
about three kilos.
And those things,
how many trips can they make?
As many as you please.
If you have the people and equipment,
as many as you like.
Okay then. I like that!
Yeah, sure.
Hey, waiter!
Chocolate martini.
- I like these.
- Yeah.
- Cheers.
Cheers, sir.
Do whatever you want, darling.
Do me whatever you want.
Where were you, bitch?
What's going on, Pl치cido?
Why were you hiding?
I'm sorry, man.
I'm sorry, but...
I can't be seen with you.
I don't want any trouble.
What happened?
What do you mean?
We were attacked, man.
You were attacked?
And why are you alive
while Cabe and Pacheco are dead?
Huh?
Hold on, man.
Give me a chance.
Fuck you.
What happened?
Man, I...
I went to buy some beers.
And when I came back...
Piporro and his friends
were killing them.
I wanted to do something.
I wanted to help them,
but I couldn't.
- Piporro?
- Yeah, him.
- No way!
- Are you sure it was Piporro?
It was him.
I have a surprise for you.
Huh?
Damn Choche.
You already finished, bastard.
Yeah, I needed a four.
No, a five.
Can't you add?
- No, I wasn't aware of that.
- You're a bastard. You can't play.
- Stand up.
- Don't yell at me.
- Come on, move.
- I'm moving.
Hey, man, come.
You'll play with me.
You start.
Come here.
Where are you going?
Sir...
I have to go to Santa Ana.
I have an emergency.
No, no emergency.
- You have to stay here.
- No, it's important.
No, the important thing
is for you to stay here with them
right now. Come.
Eleven, bastard?
You can't play.
You're worse than him. Go, move!
Move!
Hey, can you play?
You, can you play?
- Yes.
- Have a seat. Let's play.
What does it say?
Fuck.
It's clear in the video.
We don't have to understand it.
Really? What do you mean?
It's not like we are selling pineapples.
- What does it say, Pl치cido?
- I don't know, man.
Watch the image.
So, move it forward.
Now what?
I think your luck is about
to run out.
- Go, Yankee, do it.
- Here we go!
Yeah! Come on!
That's my guy!
Botas, don't talk about luck,
my financial trader
has disappeared.
- Did the feds do it?
- No, I don't think so.
Neither the public ministry
nor the judge have him.
And the worst thing is that he
has problems with the Americans.
Besides...
Fuck that phone.
Sorry.
Remember, every time Americans
come to Mexico,
they want to do things their way.
Yeah.
Okay, well played, Yankee.
Thanks, sir.
I'll leave now.
- You win, and then you leave?
- I'm going to go see my wife.
We have been partying
for two days.
And if I don't show up,
she'll freak out.
- We'll be in touch.
- Don't leave.
- Bye, Parra.
- Yes.
Don't leave, Botas.
I'll introduce you to some girls I met.
I'll talk with your wife.
No. Let me walk you out.
Seatbelts.
Go ahead, guys.
You already went through a lot
to be here, right?
In a few days you'll be
on the other side.
- God willing.
- Wait, wait.
Wait.
- Damn, man...
- Shut up.
Now, go. Leave.
There he is.
Okay. I'm getting close.
Yes.
I'm getting close.
There, there.
He saw us.
- Get closer.
- I'm doing it.
Get closer!
There.
- Okay, okay.
- Fine!
No!
Where is he?
He's still alive.
No way!
Let's go, man.
What did you do?
This is so wrong.
No way.
- You are so dumb.
- What did you do?
- See?
- He's still alive.
- I told you to get close.
- He has a gun!
- Take it.
- How?
How? How can we kill him?
Move.
Go ahead, man.
Fuck!
Fuck, no way.
Kill him!
Fucker!
If I give you an order
and you don't obey,
I'll send you where we sent
those bastards!
Sir, they are all over the place.
The Contras control them.
They are extorting storekeepers
in the northern part of the state.
Hermosillo, Santa Ana, Nogales.
Who saw you?
Nobody, Boss.
We have to get rid of the body.
We have to recover the coke
they stole from us.
Morre, tell the bosses of...
Cabe and Pacheco that...
I'll take care of the funeral.
Yes, sir.
Close that. Let's go.
Come on, man.
Let's go.
How are you, Mom?
But is everything okay?
Mom, I wanted to ask you
if something weird
happened over there.
Okay then.
- What's up?
- What's going on?
Don't go over there.
Cara Sucia is drunk
and he tends to get violent.
I better leave.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Gringo, don't move.
Where did you take Piporro?
Are you kidding?
I'm not in the mood.
Don't act so stuck-up,
you are just an ambitious bitch
who thinks that he'll get away with this.
But you are just a bastard.
Fucker, you only think you are the boss,
calm the fuck down.
What did you say?
What the hell is going on?
Drop your weapons.
Drop your weapons!
Don't you understand?
Didn't you hear me?
Drop your weapon!
Now, let's grab some food.
Let's have a drink.
Okay, go to work!
Go to work, now!
Let's go!
Alright!
Calm the fuck down, bastards!
I can't believe this.
Enough!