So she mumbled to herself,
"That will be a good mouthful."
Then she grabbed Hansel
with her withered hand
and carried him to a little stall,
where she locked him behind a cage door.
Cry as he might, there was no help for him.
Every morning the old woman crept
out to the stall and shouted,
"Hansel, stick out your finger,
so I can feel if you are fat yet."
"Hey, Gretel!" she shouted to the girl,
"Hurry up and fetch some water.
Whether Hansel is fat or thin, tomorrow I
am going to slaughter him and boil him."
Oh, how the poor little sister sobbed,
and how the tears streamed down her cheeks!
"Dear God, please help us," she cried.
"Save your slobbering," said the old woman.
"It doesn't help you at all."
I am your flesh.
I don't want to suffer.
This is it, at last.
I can't wait.
I've got everything ready
You'll become a part of me.
My mother.
Take a seat, please.
I guess we've got a long night ahead of us.
Are you certain you want
to go ahead with this?
How shall I make my grand final?
They are nice shadows,
they look like creatures, like...
Fashioned from flesh.
Do you the long tailed beak there?
Do you see the aries?
You have nothing to worry about.
It's time to take things further.
Bite it.
Bite it!
You're too weak!
It isn't going to happen, is it?
You are too weak!
I can't wait to become one with you.
Perhaps, it would be
better if I were asleep.
Take me back to the station, please.
I want to go back to Berlin.
I know...
I'm able to do it.
It's my greatest desire.
Do you know where the toilets are?
I will show you the way.
No, I prefer if you'd wait here.
I need a few minutes by myself.
I need you to be tough.
Come back to the house with me.
Castrate me.
Then kill me.
Do it now.
I don't want anything to remain of me.
Do you feel pain?
I'm...
dying...
Early the next morning,
before the children awoke,
she got up, and looked at
the two of them lying there
so peacefully, with their full red cheeks.
So she mumbled to herself,
"That will be a good mouthful."