[dramatic music]
[atmosphere whooshing]
[blade swishing]
[metal clanking]
[woman yelling]
[intense music]
[metal swishing]
[atmosphere humming]
[dramatic uptempo music]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[staff thumps]
Ages and ages ago,
in the time of our ancestors,
the forces of evil
led by Shadower
had subjugated almost
the entire world.
[rumbling]
The kingdom of Golan Mor,
the last remaining
bulwark of civilization,
was on the verge of
succumbing to evil's fury.
[men shouting]
- [metal clanking]
- [soldiers grunting]
[dramatic uptempo music]
[whooshing]
[men yelling]
[fire whooshing]
My valiant warriors.
Sire, shouldn't we be in battle?
Hold onto your bold
enthusiasm my young Altar,
there is a much more substantial
task that awaits you.
And I did not want it.
We are the last stronghold
of the Ancestral World.
Shadawar spreads
death and destruction.
One last effort is
all I ask of you.
An extreme sacrifice to
slow down his advance
to completion of the
Great Wizard spell.
Don't worry, Sire.
We are ready.
No.
You cannot imagine
what power he wields.
I assure you it is
something beyond our means.
All we can do is slow him down.
[sinister music]
He's coming.
[dramatic uptempo music]
[hammer thudding]
You treacherous son of a bitch!
Your point of view is
limited, but I understand.
We were at peace!
All the kingdoms were at peace!
Are you crazy?
No, brother.
It was not peace.
It was a privileged
situation for us nobles.
It was a stalemate.
It was immobility.
It was death.
Things had to get started.
And this is the solution?
Complete destruction?
Yes.
While my King and
faithful friend strove
to hold back Shadawar
on the battlefield,
I, Melek, in those
last moments of my life
was preparing to cast
my darkest spell.
- [stone rumbling]
- [Melek groaning]
The King's valiant soldiers
fought fiercely
to stop Shadawar.
[metal clanking]
[dramatic uptempo music]
[King groaning]
But all seemed to be lost.
[whooshing sound]
[electrical humming]
[men grunting]
[sword clanking]
[blood squelching]
[Shadawar gurgling]
Is that all you have?
You're not worthy.
I am Shadawar!
- [power whooshing]
- [wind howling]
Hold fast, my King, hold fast!
We are the Last Keepers
of the Ancestral World,
and we will survive to
sing songs of this moment.
Why?
Why all this?
Are you a fool?
No!
I'm the god of destruction!
- Melek!
- [metal clanking]
Here I am, my friend.
- This is for you!
- [fire whooshing]
[fire rumbling]
That day, Shadawar,
the god of destruction,
and all his army,
were defeated by my sacrifice.
Golan Mor came at the head of
those who did not want to fall
into the alliance of Shadawar.
- [swords clanking]
- [soldiers shouting]
But war is terrible
and even a great leader
cannot win forever,
especially cannot conquer time.
More and more tired,
Golan Mor was waiting
for the moment
when he passed the
command to his two sons,
Iruma and Mairok.
The two brothers
were valiant leaders,
and under their leadership,
the forces still loyal to
Shadawar suffered heavy defeats.
The forces of chaos retreated.
Peace was coming back.
[dramatic music]
[dragon roaring]
[suspenseful tempo music]
♪♪
[swords swishing]
[metal clinking]
[grunting]
♪♪
[metal clinking]
And you're done.
Although, the enemy's not
gonna tell you the same.
You're more than
likely gonna have
a blade piercing your neck.
[Mairok chuckling]
I really thought
I was in trouble.
You know what amazes me?
Even after almost a
decade of fighting
Shadawar's evil forces, you
still carry a tender heart.
You know Mairok,
sometimes I just wish...
I just wish you would...
Be more like you, brother.
No.
I wish you wouldn't hesitate.
Because when it comes time
to fight those evil forces,
as you know, they are
not gonna show mercy,
so why should you?
All right, how about a rematch?
Go.
[whooshing sound]
[ominous music]
[monster growling]
[Mairok gagging]
[Iruma grunting]
[suspenseful music]
[Mairok grunting]
- Mairok, are you okay?
- [Mairok coughing]
- I think so.
- [portal whooshing]
[monster growling]
Iruma, behind you!
- Mairok!
- Iruma, no!
No, Iruma!
[foreboding music]
[inaudible screaming]
[dramatic music]
[door creaking]
♪♪
Get up, my son.
I'm sorry, Father.
We will find your brother.
Come with me.
[dramatic music]
Atia, I believe you
have news for us.
[Atia] Yes, my king, but
you have to act immediately.
[King] Explain, Atia.
[Atia] Prince Iruma
is still alive
but there is a reason that
he has not yet been killed.
Our enemies have hidden
their intentions,
which have been obscured
up to this point.
I ask you forgiveness, sire.
Don't ask me for forgiveness.
I want to know what's going on.
The forces of chaos are losing
the war with their weapons.
That's why they decided
to use a descendant
of the original ancestral
lineage of the world
to use one of our
weapons against us.
The Sacred Armor.
But I thought the Sacred
Armor was just a legend.
No, my son.
It was used in a previous war,
but considered too dangerous
by the Mother of All.
It was then broken into
four different pieces,
each of which was
entrusted to a Guardian.
But now it is possible
that the forces of chaos
will use Iruma to retrieve it.
Iruma risks becoming a puppet
in the hands of our enemies.
I will recover it.
I will find it before they do
and I will save Iruma.
It will be very
difficult, Prince Mairok.
If you move with an army,
or even a group of men,
you risk being attacked.
I know you have a spell
that can make only one person
invisible to their magic.
So I will go alone.
Sire?
[eerie music]
[electrical fizzling]
Atia!
I'm...
I'm fine.
The spell requires
a lot of energy.
You will not feel
anything, but it worked.
You will be invisible
to the enemies.
[birds chirping]
I promise, Father, I
will bring Iruma home.
I trust you, boy.
[dramatic music]
♪♪
[ambient humming]
Atia!
Open the portal.
- [portal whooshing]
- [electrical fizzling]
Good luck, my son.
[dramatic music]
[electrical fizzling]
Wow!
[dramatic music]
Do you think I
don't trust my son?
Monitoring him will
not be helpful.
Indeed, this spell of
connection, though protected,
could give our enemies
a way to re-trace us.
We'll run the risk.
I know he's the only one who
can complete the mission.
I don't wanna lose him too.
[somber music]
[hawk squealing]
Vo' Segh ngo?
Do you belong to
the ancient race?
[Mairok] Yes.
Are you here for
the Sacred Armor?
Yes.
I possess one of the four
stones that can summon one part,
but this stone keeps
the balance of my lands.
The entire Ancestral World
is in danger of being destroyed.
I need that stone in order
to keep that from happening.
You had entrusted
this in our care.
There's a war out there.
I've seen it.
I fought in it.
You don't want this to
end badly for everyone,
I beg you, please
give me that stone.
[guardian grunting]
- [thudding]
- [stone crunching]
[suspenseful music]
[sword swishing]
[Mairok groaning]
[weapons swishing]
[metal clanking]
[guardian groaning]
[punch booming]
And you would like to
save the Ancestral World
from the forces of evil?
[guardian laughing]
You make me laugh.
You're pathetic.
I've tried to be patient
with you, splinter face.
- [punch thudding]
- [guardian groaning]
[suspenseful music]
I am Mairok!
[punch thudding]
Son of Golan Mor!
I have fought on the
bastions of Orion!
I have defeated the
armies of Shadawar!
What do you know about me?
[sword clinking]
[guardian huffing]
[dramatic music]
[stone power whooshing]
[wind howling]
He succeeded.
Have confidence in
your son, my king.
The time available is
short, but he will do it.
[birds chirping]
[leaves rustling]
[foreboding music]
[arrow swishing]
[intense beat music]
Please.
Do not force me to kill you!
[sword swishing]
I am here to save the Ancestral
World and everyone in it!
And that includes all of you.
[suspenseful music]
[swords clinking]
[women grunting]
- [woman yelling]
- [metal clanking]
[suspenseful music]
♪♪
[chains clanking]
Sisters, get up.
[dramatic music]
Warrior.
Why disturb the
peace of my temple?
It was not my intention.
My sincerest apologies.
Why are you here?
To save the Ancestral World
from that bastard
Shadawar's tyranny.
Shadawar.
Get up.
Come inside and tell me more.
[chains clanking]
But, my queen.
Sister, quiet!
I can understand perfectly well
that this man has no
hostile intention.
Therefore, I want to listen
to what he has to say.
Free him!
[chains clanking]
[dramatic music]
[wind howling]
Where's the stone?
The stone that evokes
the Sacred Armor?
I have it.
How do you know what that is?
I thought by now the
memory of that stone
would have been lost in time.
How do you know?
You're so... young.
I am much older than you
can imagine, young one.
So, what do they call you?
I am Mairok, son of Golan Mor.
[woman laughing]
A prince, of course.
I am Lantris and I have
been here for many years
without being able to grow old.
Without being able to leave.
And all because of that bastard.
A long time ago,
Shadawar began to conquer
the surrounding territories
of your father's kingdom.
One by one, rulers devoted
themselves to his cause
betraying Golan Mor.
His evil reign reached
even as far as these lands.
My Amazons and I resisted
as long as we could,
but our efforts were futile
- and in our defeat
- [metal clanking]
Shadawar took over.
He possessed one of the stones
that could evoke
the Sacred Armor,
and he used that
power against me,
binding me to the stone forever.
You fought with honor,
and thus I'll spare the lives
of you and your Amazons.
I'll be back when
the time is rights.
Until then, you will be cursed
to be the guardian of the stone!
Over time, some of
the Shadawar's allies
tried to overthrow him
and seize the stone.
One of them managed
to mortally wound me
or, so I thought.
I did not die.
After that,
I met a clairvoyant named Atia.
I sought her help to figure
out what had happened to me.
Shadawar used the power of the
stone to make you immortal.
And only through that same stone
you can get back to being
an ordinary human being.
She did everything in her
power to break the spell
but Shadawar's curse
was too powerful.
[suspenseful music]
Only that one day
a warrior will come who will
be able to break the spell.
So,
why should I care about saving
this Ancestral World of yours?
It's not just that.
It is to save someone
very important to me.
Tell me more.
[fire crackling]
I don't have much time before
my brother becomes a
puppet in their hands.
With that armor...
they can destroy the
entire Ancestral World
and everyone in it.
And that includes your Amazons.
[somber piano music]
I understand.
And I will help you
but I cannot give you the
stone, so I will go with you.
No.
It's something I
must do on my own.
Don't be a fool, Mairok.
I'm immortal
and an ally that cannot
die may be very beneficial.
I don't know what to say.
How about goodnight?
[pleasant piano music]
[swords swishing]
Lantris!
Who are you?
Did Shadawar send you?
What have you done with Lantris?
[swords clinking]
[suspenseful music]
[power whooshing]
[swords clinking]
[woman groaning]
[suspenseful music]
[swords clinking]
Lantris!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
[Mairok crying]
I didn't mean to.
Lantris, I didn't mean to.
[Lantris gasping]
[somber music]
I thought you were the one.
I did not die, I will never die!
My family, my friends,
they've all disappeared
and I will stay like
this, alone forever.
Forgive me.
Forgive me, Mairok.
[dramatic music]
I really thought
you were the one.
I knew I couldn't
convince you to kill me.
I'm sorry.
[Lantris crying]
[dramatic music]
Wait here.
[somber piano music]
Sisters, get up.
I've decided to join
the prince's journey.
But, my queen!
My duty is to guard the stone.
Wherever the stone
goes, I'll go with it
and maybe on this
trip I'll find a way
to break the spell
that had cursed me.
Okay, but we come with you.
No.
The prince is
protected by a spell
that makes him invisible
to his enemies,
and even this curse allows
me to be invisible as well.
But...
I need you here.
[dramatic music]
[Atia] My king.
Well, Atia?
[Atia] The prince was able
to recover the second stone.
So,
everything is
going as it should.
Maybe there is a hope.
[Atia] I'm sure, my lord.
And now your son is also
being helped by someone.
What?
The mission has been discovered?
[Atia] No, my lord,
this is someone that I
have known a long time ago.
Mairok, are you okay?
[Mairok coughing]
Maybe we should slow down.
You don't understand!
We don't have time!
If even one of the stones falls
in the hands of our enemies,
my brother and the
entire Ancestral World
are doomed!
[Mairok coughing]
Mairok!
[gentle piano music]
[Atia] Mairok.
What happened?
The vital signs of Mairok.
[King] What happened to him?
- Is...
- No,
not dead.
But they are very weak.
Wounded in combat?
Was he betrayed by that
person you told me about?
No, my lord.
Your son is...
[Lantris] An idiot!
What a complete idiot.
I've never met someone
so devoted to his cause
to risk his own life for it.
Lantris.
What happened?
You fell unconscious.
Now could you
please explain to me
why you kept hidden the wound
that I caused you
during our fight?
You really are an idiot, Prince
Mairok, son of Golan Mor.
[birds chirping]
Ah.
Careful.
Better.
♪♪
Get some rest.
The stone should help you heal.
Yeah.
What about you?
You must be exhausted.
Since I've been given
this curse, Mairok,
I do not feel the need to
rest, nor drink, nor eat, nor...
[dramatic music]
[wind howling]
What's wrong?
What are you thinking?
Many men wish for immortality.
But if they really knew what
it meant to be immortal,
I'm sure they would
change their minds.
[dragon growling]
Oh, look.
[dragon whooshing]
[gentle piano music]
[dragon growling]
[suspenseful music]
♪♪
[epic music]
Look, there.
[electronic fizzling]
It seems too damn easy.
I agree.
That's why I will try
to take the stone.
But...
Mairok, use your head.
Right, you're invincible.
That's right.
[suspenseful music]
[hissing sound]
[electronic buzzing]
- [atmosphere humming]
- [Lantris groaning]
Lantris!
[chains clinking]
[suspenseful music]
Don't worry about me.
[Man] What are you
do in my reign?
Guardian!
Show yourself!
We're not here to fight,
we just need your help.
Guardian!
[Guardian] Prove to me you
are worthy of your first name.
Free Lantris!
[Guardian] Or what?
All right, then...
[power whooshing]
[Guardian] Do you
really want to generate
the wave of energy that
could destroy this temple?
Why not?
That way you won't be able
to hide like a coward.
[Guardian] And if
I were to kill her?
That's impossible.
She's immortal.
- [whooshing sound]
- [Guardian] Really?
[Mairok yelling]
You're just trying
to confuse me!
[Lantris yelping]
She said she wants to
get rid of the curse,
but not die right away.
Shut up.
[Guardian] And if now
that she has known you,
she no longer wishes to die?
Shut up!
And you!
Everyone would see that
you're madly in love with her.
You would not want to see her
die, right, Prince Mairok?
[Mairok yelling]
[punch thudding]
You can do better than that.
[sword swishing]
I'll be right back.
[suspenseful music]
Show yourself!
[punches thudding]
How about you try that again?
- [whooshing sound]
- [grunting]
[Guardian] How is this possible?
I can see you now.
[punch thudding]
[Mairok grunting]
- [Mairok grunting]
- [fire whooshing]
[electronic buzzing]
It's the connection
between the stones.
I can sense your energy.
Prepare to die.
[Mairok grunting]
[suspenseful music]
[blood squelching]
♪♪
[singers vocalizing]
[metal clanking]
[electronic fizzling]
I'm sorry, guardian.
This is not how I
wanted it to end.
Now, free Lantris.
Don't worry.
Your time will come soon enough.
Soon you will all die,
Prince Mairok, son of Golan Mor.
How do you know me?
I was created to protect
the stone from Shadawar
and he's making his return.
You've been here for too long.
Shadawar is dead.
Melek defeated him with
a spell 10 years ago.
All that actually died
was his physical form,
not his soul, which lived on.
He still commands
the dark forces...
and now has a new physical form,
a body from the ancestral race,
and once he finds
that Sacred Armor,
then nothing will
be able to stop him.
[Lantris] Mairok!
Lantris!
[dramatic piano music]
My brother,
the host body for Shadawar.
Look,
I'm not going to tell you
I know what you're feeling
but don't lose control.
You already have
three of the stones.
Only one is left.
We'll make it in time.
We will.
What do we do about him?
There's nothing
you can do for me.
I'm going back into the shadows
where I've always been.
But beware,
because Shadawar is coming back!
And the Ancestral World will
enter an age of darkness
it has never seen before.
[guardian laughing maniacally]
[dramatic music]
[King] He did it.
Yes, my king,
and every stone and each
test makes him stronger,
increases his powers.
There is only one stone left.
What do you see in the future?
Maybe he really will succeed
in saving his brother.
He has already
demonstrated many times
his value in battle.
Why do you doubt
Mairok, my liege?
Mairok has always
lived in the shadow
of his older brother Iruma.
I thought he was a poor
imitation of his older brother.
I was wrong.
He's a worthy son
and a great warrior.
[Atia] He has a pure heart.
And the man who can accomplish
this task is a man like him.
A man who deeply
loves his brother.
A man who believes in something
for which is worth fighting.
[dramatic music]
[wind howling]
There it is.
We're almost there.
We will find your brother.
I know.
I know!
You are not alone,
remember this.
[gentle piano music]
Lantris, I...
Whatever nonsense
you're about to say,
just wait until we've
recovered the last stone.
Right.
Let's go.
[gentle piano music]
- [wind howling]
- [tinkling noise]
Look there.
[chains rattling]
[suspenseful music]
[creature growling]
Go find the stone.
I'll take care of this.
Right.
[creature growling]
[suspenseful music]
[metal clinking]
[creature growling]
[creature groaning]
[creature snarling]
[wind howling]
[creature gurgling]
[eerie music]
[ominous music]
Welcome.
[electronic buzzing]
I just need the stone.
I don't wanna fight.
[swords clinking]
[ominous music]
Oh well, twice the fun.
[creatures snarling]
[suspenseful music]
[swords clinking]
[blades swishing]
[blades clinking]
[Mairok groaning]
[punches thudding]
[suspenseful music]
[blade swishing]
[guardian whooshing]
[Mairok yelping]
[explosion booming]
[suspenseful music]
[neck cracking]
[power fizzling]
[blades ringing]
[electronic humming]
[swords clinking]
[metal clattering]
[blades clinking]
[suspenseful music]
[punches rumbling]
[stone crumbling]
[suspenseful music]
[Mairok huffing]
[electronic humming]
[Mairok] Yes.
[creature snarling]
[suspenseful music]
[creature growling]
[sword slicing]
[creature gurgling]
[Lantris huffing]
Oh, come on.
[creatures snarling]
Mairok?
A little help?
[fire whooshing]
Perhaps you could
be a hero after all.
Perhaps.
Did you get the stone?
Of course I did.
[Atia] My king, he did it.
Sorry to have
doubted you, my son.
[dramatic music]
Lantris, where is your stone?
[stones humming and whooshing]
[wind howling]
Is that supposed to happen?
I have no idea!
I was just trying to
prevent someone else
from evoking the Sacred Armor!
[Atia] It is not possible.
What is not possible?
Atia, tell me.
When the four stones
came together,
their joint power
swept away the magic.
What do you mean?
Explain yourself!
That now Mairok is visible
to the forces of Shadawar.
Do something!
Warn him of the danger he is in!
My powers are not strong enough.
I can't reach it with my mind.
- Now Mairok is alone.
- [air whooshing]
The Sacred Armor.
[power whooshing]
Mairok, what's that?
Stay back!
That's the same
portal my brother...
My brother, Iruma!
Mairok, watch out!
Remember what the
Shadow told you!
[portal whooshing]
[Mairok] Iruma!
Brother!
Brother.
I was imprisoned by
Shadawar's forces.
They had me imprisoned until
someone gathered the stones
to evoke the Sacred Armor.
Iruma.
[dramatic music]
- [blade slashing]
- [Mairok gasping]
[suspenseful music]
Your weak-minded brother
tried to stop me.
Little did he know,
nothing can stop Shadawar!
Not even death!
- [kick thudding]
- [Mairok groaning]
[Mairok coughing and choking]
[Lantris] No!
- [punch thudding]
- [Lantris gasping]
[dramatic music]
[stones whooshing]
[atmosphere rumbling]
[electronic fizzling]
[Shadawar laughing]
[Mairok groaning]
You would have been
better off staying dead.
You want to fight me?
You really are an idiot.
Yeah, maybe,
but don't underestimate
this idiot.
[suspenseful music]
[Mairok groaning]
[fire whooshing]
[electrical fizzling]
Iruma!
Brother!
Please, tell me a part of
you is still inside there!
Mairok, please.
[dramatic music]
[electrical fizzling]
[Iruma's voice]
It's too easy...
[Shadawar's voice] ...brother.
[sword clinking]
[Iruma Voiceover] I wish
you wouldn't hesitate
because when it comes time
to fight those evil forces,
they are not going
to show mercy.
So why should you?
[sword swishing]
[Mairok grunting]
[suspenseful music]
[metal clinking]
[rapid punches thudding]
[Mairok groaning]
[gentle piano music]
[power humming]
[Shadawar whooshing]
Time to die, sweet prince.
And next up, your beloved king.
[fire whooshing]
Iruma,
Father, forgive me.
[dramatic music]
No!
[blood squelching]
[dramatic music]
[electronic whooshing]
[Shadawar gagging]
[Atia] I'm sorry, my king.
Everything is lost.
Mairok.
Iruma.
Shadawar!
How is this possible?
I swore I'd return, Golan Mor.
Atia!
Call the guards!
I fear she is so
overwhelmed with emotion
to be able to find her words.
What happened to my sons?
Your children are all
dead, my dear king.
[swords clinking]
And now it's your turn.
The era of the Ancestral
World ends here.
This is the rise of my kingdom.
The beginning of chaos!
However, this isn't the
right stage for my triumph.
[power whooshing]
Come, King.
It's time to die.
This time, no one and
nothing will be saving you.
[dramatic music]
Mairok!
[Lantris whooshing]
Mairok?
Mairok.
Lantris.
You're right.
I really am an idiot.
No.
[Mairok chuckling]
Mairok.
Mairok, stay with me.
Mairok, don't!
Mairok, please don't!
Mairok!
- Please don't leave me, Mairok!
- [dramatic music]
- [Lantris screaming]
- [dramatic music swells]
[inaudible dialogue]
[ominous music]
[wind howling]
The era of the Ancestral
World ends here.
You are a fool, Shadawar.
You may kill me, but
you will never win.
[ominous music]
[sword swishing]
- [Lantris crying]
- Please.
When you placed the last stone,
I could feel the spell breaking.
I haven't yet turned
back into a mortal
but I can now fully control
the energy that
makes me immortal.
- [Mairok gasping]
- [whooshing sound]
What happened?
Don't worry about it.
[gentle piano music]
I finally realized
what my purpose is.
You are the warrior
I was waiting for.
I love you, Mairok.
No.
Don't do this.
My life is worth nothing
compared to yours.
I lived centuries, Mairok.
But I've never felt truly
alive until I met you.
Lantris.
Lantris!
An important destiny
awaits you, young God.
- Go.
- [whooshing sound]
Save your kingdom.
Lantris.
[Mairok crying]
I'll come back, my love.
[dramatic music]
[Mairok screaming]
[Mairok sobbing]
[birds chirping]
[suspenseful music]
[power whooshing]
[blade whooshing]
[metal clinking]
[dramatic music]
[blood squelching]
[King gagging]
[electrical fizzling]
Shadawar!
You will pay for what
you've done to me!
You're still alive?
That damned immortal.
I should have killed you both.
[Mairok whooshing]
[metal clinking]
[Mairok yelling]
[punches thudding]
[Mairok coughing]
You don't want to understand.
This is the Sacred Armor!
[Mairok yelling]
[power rumbling]
Should this little
scene impress me?
- [electrical fizzling]
- [epic music]
It's the Sacred Armor, Shadawar.
Exactly like yours.
[Mairok Voiceover] Perhaps
even more powerful.
You see, the armor is a concept,
created long ago to store
a large amount of energy
in physical form.
What you wear is simply a
container of that energy.
And the stones that evoke it
are only one means
to harness it.
These arm guards given
to me by my father.
I created a bond
with that energy
and I'm now powerful
enough to evoke
a sacred armor of my own!
[suspenseful music]
[metal clinking]
[metal clanking]
- [Mairok yelling]
- [punches rumbling]
[Mairok coughing]
[punches rumbling]
♪♪
[Mairok yelling]
[punches thudding]
[punches rumbling]
[Mairok yelling]
[dramatic piano music]
[intense dramatic music]
[Atia] Only through
sacrifice and loss,
a prince learns how
to become a king.
And so...
a new history of
the Ancestral World began.
But this is another story.
[suspenseful music]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[fire crackling]
[atmosphere humming]
[upbeat music]