How we looking outside?
We got a shady hotel across
the street and a little bar
on the corner.
- Any apartments?
- None.
Looks like we're a go.
Load in tomorrow at sundown.
- That's 6:03 p.m.
- Then I'll see everyone at 6:04.
Oh, wait a minute.
I got one more thing.
- What's that?
- Police station's three blocks away.
Remember. No obstacles.
Only challenges.
People just trust some
stranger to pick them up?
Isn't that dangerous?
Which one do you want?
Neither.
Come on! It's your first time.
You gotta get into it
a little bit.
- Yeah. I'm not sure that I am going.
- What?
You're going.
I'm telling you right now.
Listen. I have a Tuesday
deadline on three chapters
that I haven't even started yet.
It'd be one thing if you were
working on the
Great American Novel...
- It's called work.
- Right. Work. You're just scared.
Look, Colin, if he doesn't
want to go...
Harmony, could you give us
a second?
- What?
- Come on. Just, please.
- What's going on, Colin?
- You have to go tonight.
It's a surprise for Harmony.
- What kind of surprise?
- A surprise. A big one.
Look. I'm not asking you just
as a roommate or a friend.
I'm asking you as a brother.
- Okay, where is it?
- It's in the city.
And I can leave if
I don't like it?
I don't think that's going
to be a problem.
So, what does this shit
do to you, exactly?
Increases the amount of the
neurotransmitter serotonin
by inhibiting its reuptake
in the brain.
Oh, I'm sorry, Doogie Howser,
what I meant to say was,
"How does it fuck you up?"
They fuck you
up. This enhances you.
Heightened awareness of your
senses, especially touch.
Feeling of connection,
openness, honesty.
It's like being a kid.
Hmm!
The AMA would be proud, Cliff.
Yeah, well, if you're going to
be a successful drug user you
gotta be well informed.
They're here!
- Ernest. Greetings.
- What's happening, my man?
Killer space.
Yeah. We're going for a
suburban living room meets
opium den kind of thing.
- So, see what you can do.
- Gotcha.
One ten just feels like
a codeine overdose.
Two twenty, on the other hand,
feels like your falling out of
a moving car.
- Hey, Billy Bob!
- What's up?
Maggie says she's burning
down here, man.
The only thing burning
down here is me.
Chaos is about to become order.
Hello? No. You know what, I'm
covered, but thank you.
Okay, cool, bye.
Oh, man! Hello?
Yeah, this is Leyla.
No. You know what,
I'm all set. I appreciate it.
Okay.
Gold dreads.
I'll look for you. All right.
Bye.
- Leyla?
- Hey. I really appreciate you guys coming to pick me up.
No problem. Our dorm is
right down the street.
- Great. You guys like Jungle?
- Yeah.
Cool! Thanks.
- What is that?
- A swan.
Oh, that's so sweet.
What's it for?
Well, 25th anniversary is
silver, and 50th is gold.
First, paper.
I looked it up on the Internet.
Well, it looks like
a pterodactyl.
Do you know what
three years is? Leather.
- A year?
- Okay, 11 months. I rounded up.
But it was a year ago tonight
we met.
- And you remember that.
- I remember because John Digweed was spinning.
And guess what?
He's spinning tonight.
Well, I just hope they don't
play any of that
Happy House crap.
Not on my anniversary.
Now, before we do this,
let's take a moment to send
out some positive vibes.
Safe party, no busts,
and some fucking electricity.
Fuck me!
Oh!
Let's do it!
What? Forget it!
I'm not parking here.
- Relax!
- It's just a map point.
- Oh, the map point.
- Yeah, just hold tight for a sec.
Yeah. Oh, for real?
No shit. Damn.
Oh, that's my bad, man. I'll
take it for the team, man.
Two bucks.
Yeah, I'll see you there.
No worries.
- All right? Cool.
- I only have a 20.
- Give me three.
- Yeah, no sweat, man.
- All right, brother.
- All right.
Hey, kids! Be sure to bust a
left at the second stop light,
not a right.
I fucked up the maps again.
Why don't we just go to the
map point like everybody else?
You want me to tell everyone
I used to babysit you?
Would you just admit you don't
know where the fuck it is?
Shut up.
- Hey! What's up?
- How you doing?
Good to see you!
How you doing?
You guys, this is my brother,
David. Beth. And this is Joe.
- Let's go.
- Come on, let's go.
Got a light?
Thank you.
- Nice braids.
- Thanks.
- I'm Anthony.
- Harmony.
I was going to say, I got a
massage room in the back.
Free massages all night.
Cool!
So, if you get tired of
dancing, come back,
I'll fix you up.
Thanks.
I'd like to buy a vowel.
- E or A?
- A.
Two, please.
I'd like to solve the puzzle.
Lysergic acid diethylamide.
Why don't you tell him
what he's won?
An all-expense-paid trip to
your cerebral cortex.
Thanks for playing.
- Hey.
- Where you been? I dropped a while ago.
Had to take a piss.
Where's the bar?
I don't think there's some big
bar in this place.
Hey! I know you!
- I don't think so.
- Yeah, you're that T.A. in Chem 302.
- That's so cool!
- No, I'm not.
Love is the reason. Plur?
Plur. Peace, love,
unity and respect.
Bring on the love.
Excuse me.
- It's free.
- It is?
Mm-hmm.
Hi, are you Leyla?
I read your e-mail.
- Oh. What's your name?
- David.
Oh, no, thank you. I'm fine.
Oh.
You can relax.
It's just a party.
Come on, man. It's time.
- Keep your eyes closed.
- I am, I am.
- What are you doing?
- It's a surprise. No peeking.
Oh, my God!
I'll take that as a yes.
David, look!
How's that for spontaneous?
- Oh, hey.
- Hi. Have you seen my brother?
- Who?
- Colin.
- He says that he knows everybody.
- Sorry.
- So, you're from New York.
- Just moved.
- Here for work?
- My birthday, I guess.
- Happy birthday. Did somebody just turn up the music?
- No.
- I'm from back east, too.
- Oh, yeah? Where?
East Lansing.
Michigan?
I don't think that counts as
back east.
You know, everyone here knows
what's going to happen to you
so, whatever you need to do,
feel free.
You're really nice for a
New Yorker.
What's your name again?
Leyla.
That's right, like that
Kinks song.
Jesus Christ!
Is there a telephone here?
- I got a... Tuesday...
- Just take a deep breath and let it out slowly.
I don't think this was
a good idea.
Keep drinking.
You know any of the other DJs
spinning tonight?
There's more than one?
Come on. I think there's
something you should see.
I can't tell what sound his
record is making.
You want to hug?
Sometimes it helps.
Hey, Neil, I've got an idea!
Let's take a disco nap!
Why don't you take it down a
notch. We're only a half hour
late, we're going to be fine.
Yes, but we're late.
- What are you doing?
- I'm driving.
- This is my car, Neil.
- I let you drive my car.
- I bought this two weeks ago!
- What? You don't trust me?
- Trust?
- Look. I know where we're going.
And I don't?
I've lived in this city
for five years with a car.
You drive like an old woman.
I'm sorry.
Would you like to drive?
- Ready?
- Mm-hmm.
Hey!
What's going on, here?
- Just a little party.
- Doesn't sound too little.
- Some friends.
- This building's been vacant for months.
- We just moved in.
- Who?
- Hm?
- Who just moved in?
- The company I work for.
- Yeah? What company?
Software startup.
- You on the lease?
- No.
I'm going to need to speak to
somebody who is.
- We got a cop.
- What?
We got a cop!
- What did you tell him?
- That's the funny part.
Make me laugh.
Me and my partner are
celebrating the opening of
our new office space.
My partner and I.
He wants to see the owner
of the building.
Hey, Colin, remember when
you were 13
and Mom busted you for
breaking that ugly-ass lamp
in the living room?
Yeah. Yeah, I didn't even
fucking do it.
- Yeah, I know. And I am sorry.
- Oh, it was you?
- I figured she already blamed you...
- Don't worry.
- I didn't get it that bad.
- It sounded pretty bad.
Not as bad as
you would have gotten.
Why, what do you mean?
The good kid always
gets it worse.
Hey! How you feeling?
- I think I'm in heaven.
- Oh, you are.
I just saw what's-her-name
from that trip, and I'm going
to go say hi and tell her.
I'll be right back.
Hey, Colin.
Why didn't you tell me
about the ring, before?
I said it was a surprise.
Don't you think it's
a little soon?
It's how I feel.
But you've only...
You've known her five months?
Let me enjoy this.
I'm asking nice.
It just seems fast.
Why is it, every time
something good happens in my
life, you have to judge it?
- Collin, I didn't mean...
- Just be happy for me.
You know, if you get past the
Tickle-me-Elmo backpacks
and the big floppy clown pants
some of these girls would be
pretty hot.
What's your pulse? Ballpark.
Todd, I've brought you
this orange.
If you don't feel anything in
half an hour, eat it.
- Vitamin C has a catalytic effect.
- Super.
No stickers, that's bad!
- Want some water?
- Thanks.
- That's so weird!
- What?
That you knew I needed water.
You look familiar.
- Hi. David.
- Hey, David!
- Well, hello. I'm David.
- Anne.
Oh, good!
Hey, the cops are here, man.
I coughed up two bucks a
square foot for this place
and I haven't even chosen
a color palette.
- That's a bitch.
- Yeah.
And you know what they say
about the three most important
things in business.
- Location, location, location.
- Excuse me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, go ahead. I'm finished.
What? You can't go in front
of someone else?
No, there's a guy...
There's a cop out there.
- Yeah? What's he doing?
- He's walking around. He looked right at me.
- Oh, God. Do I look high?
- Yeah.
- Shit!
- What are you worried about?
I'm doing something illegal.
Okay, let's just stay here for
a while and see what happens.
Okay, but remember, I don't
even know you.
If he finds anything,
it's your responsibility.
- What are you talking about?
- Well, you're carrying, right?
- Carrying. You mean drugs?
- Yeah.
You caught me.
- Want one?
- No, thanks. I don't... Yeah, please.
- That tastes incredible.
- You took some good shit.
It is an incredibly
enjoyable experience.
First time's always the best.
Thank you for helping
me earlier.
No problem.
- You're very pretty.
- You're very high.
If I weren't,
I'd still think you were.
I just wouldn't say it.
I'm not trying to hit on you
or anything,
I'm just telling the truth.
I'd watch how much you say
in your state.
You might embarrass yourself.
So, this will be the sales
offices. It's going to be
completely gutted
and renovated. We're going
to put in new tile floors.
You're probably going to want
to upgrade this
computer system, too, huh?
Yeah.
Excuse me,
I have something very
important to ask you all.
Has anybody seen a small
brown teddy bear?
- Oh, no!
- There it is!
- Thank you.
- Yay!
Have I showed you reception?
Could you do my shoulders?
So, you work out?
Yoga. Five days a week.
- I can tell. Where at?
- The Body Tree on Fourth.
- Oh.
- What do you mean, "Oh"?
Nothing. It's an okay place.
You know, you are all in knots.
- Really?
- You hold all your stress right here, don't you?
Yeah. I mean, no.
I don't have any stress.
- Well, something's off.
- What do you mean?
- Your kundalini energy. It's all fucked up.
- We're done.
- So that yoga ain't doing you much good.
- Whatever.
Namaste!
I imagine this party is the
last fun you'll be having
for a while.
Yeah, but it's an investment
in something I love, though.
Well, you're a
true entrepreneur.
I guess I am.
Now, here's my final piece
of advice for you.
Yeah? What's that?
Keep the music down and your
ravers inside, or all the love
in the world won't stop me
from busting your ass.
Yes, sir.
Hey, thanks, man!
Feels good, doesn't it?
- Colin, what's up?
- Nothing.
Don't you want to dance?
Forest is spinning!
She's our...
- Colin, what's going on?
- Nothing.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I gotta go.
- Hey, were you at Fantasia?
- Yeah. Two-year anniversary.
We were on the beach.
We smoked a bowl together.
- Ah! What's up, dude?
- How's it going?
- Good to see you man.
- Yeah.
Did you kick it for the
Digweed set that night?
He fucking shredded, man.
I was stoked to see him
tonight, man, that show
was phat.
So, do you know anyone who can
hook up any GHB?
No, man, I'm not doing
any drugs tonight.
I myself am pretty fucked up.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
Baked, not fried.
The healthy choice.
I'm glad. Really. I mean, who
would want to go to a party
that actually lets you know
where it is!
Okay, here we go.
It's our anniversary, and
we're going to have
a fucking good time!
- Let's just go home.
- We are not missing it!
What's that? More paper?
What is it, a crab?
Directions! Directions!
Come on!
spontaneous progress.
He loaded a continuous roll of
paper into his typewriter
took benzedrine 20 days
straight. No paragraphs, no
punctuation, nothing
just free-flowing words,
just like notes from a
jazz soloist.
And, two weeks later,
he rolled it up,
brought it to his editor
and the rest is history.
- You're talking about Kerouac.
- Jacques Kerouac.
You know before, when you were
talking about Hemingway...
No, I was not
talking about Hemingway.
- Yes, you were!
- No, you've got to keep up.
I was saying that William
Burroughs' economy of prose
is reminiscent of Hemingway.
- Hey, you want some glitter?
- No, thank you.
- How about a sticker?
- Okay.
- So, you write?
- Yeah, for a living.
- Published?
- Three books and a bunch of articles.
- Really?
- Really.
- Give me a title.
- I don't think they're the kind of books you'd know.
- Hey, I read.
- They're not, like, best sellers or anything.
- Come on!
- Well, there's the CD-ROM Toolkit Reference Guide
which is very big
in high schools
and, maybe, there's the piece
on configuring your PPP that
was in Macworld last month.
Hey, Ernest Hemingway did
write that whole series of
car repair manuals
before he hit it big,
so I think you'll be okay.
This is the Celtic love knot,
and this one is for eternity.
- Colin, you're so sweet!
- I don't believe it.
- Have you guys set a date yet?
- Maybe next year's summer solstice.
- Or, like, with a small ceremony in the woods.
- Are we all invited?
Of course, your all invited.
This whole place is invited.
I'm getting Forest to spin.
- Do I feel tight?
- No! You feel fine!
I know, I told that to that
fucking asshole Anthony,
my chakras are all good.
- Are you laughing at me?
- Naw.
What are you doing of such
importance to the economy?
- I'm making money.
- Oh, yeah? How's that?
Retail slut. Just until
I go back to school.
- What? Grad school?
- No, not exactly.
- But you're going back.
- Okay. I'm not exactly going back. I'm going.
- I don't get it.
- Undergrad.
Oh. So, what school?
Um, you know, UC Berkley,
if I get in.
You know, you should really be
downing some water because
you'll get dehydrated and...
- I'm really sorry if I...
- No, it's just...
Look. Not everyone has to
follow this exact path
that everyone else follows,
you know? It's like
I don't really think I have
to live this cookie-cutter
existence, you know?
- So, what are you thinking of studying?
- Pre-law.
- You don't strike me as a lawyer.
- Thank you.
- I mean that in the best possible way.
- Hm. Drink.
Excuse me. Everybody?
I'd like to invite you all
over for breakfast.
The address is
3899 Guerrero Street,
Number 2.
Thank you all for being here.
Really.
Has anyone seen Colin?
Where the fuck are we?
I turned left on Third,
right on Illinois, went down
two blocks...
- It says here, "1800 North Illinois."
- Yeah.
- Where are we?
- 1800 South Illinois.
I'm driving.
Wow.
What do you see?
I see crystal cities.
- What was that?
- Just a kiss.
No.
Nonono. Aisle 4.
You're at Safeway, right?
Yeah, the plastic gallons
with the handles.
We got more coming.
Five out of five dentists
recommend it.
Okay, you guys got two options:
get rid of the nitrous
or get rid or yourselves.
Okay, outside!
Okay. Listen to me carefully.
When we were getting ready
this morning
- where did you put the crate?
- In the car, like you told me.
- Where in the car?
- In the front seat.
- Where?
- In the front seat!
- And do you remember what's wrong with the front seat?
- No, not really.
Hey, Monte, you're on in 15.
The sun, the fucking sun!
It's vinyl, babe! It melts!
Well, it's your own fault.
I mean, who the fuck buys
vinyl anymore anyway?
- Step off!
- I told you you should have bought CDs!
Hey, Big Ernie, man,
I'm Audi 5000.
- Have you seen Digweed?
- No, Why?
We need to fill Monte's
time slot. Yeah, go ahead.
Don't say it. Shit!
Um, Polywog's in
the chill room.
Go find her, quick.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Todd. Todd!
Did you eat the orange?
Cliff, shut the fuck up and
give me the keys, man.
I don't understand.
You should feel happy.
I am.
I'm fucking happy I'm leaving.
You're telling me you don't
feel anything?
Dude, when did you get all
Haight-Ashbury on me, man?
I mean, you used to listen to
Nitzer Ebb.
I was 12, and I was a Nazi.
Cliff, it's a fucking pink
boa. Look at yourself!
I mean, Jesus Christ!
If you were honest with
yourself, you'd see you're an
unhappy person
who's been mean to others
in order to make himself
feel better.
Well, thank you, Carl Jung.
Now, if you'll give me
the keys
I'm going to go get pissed
drunk and pass out in
the gutter.
Like a normal person.
What's up, ladies?
Hey, we have some major issues
with the lineup.
And Ernie was wondering if you
had another set in you.
Cool. So that's...
The sweet cotton-candy kiss of
transcendental bliss.
Okay.
So, I'll take that as a no.
How did they get down here?
I thought these doors
were locked.
I don't know, man. I'm sorry.
Jesus, Joe.
What did he take?
Somebody gave this kid GB.
Great. Get back.
Come on, man.
It's pumpin', man, good luck.
- Okay.
- Here. Get him to drink this.
He's got to get something down.
I don't understand this guy.
Same story every party.
It's all right. I got it.
Okay?
Just watch him. Make sure he
doesn't fall asleep.
- Stay awake, shithead.
- Fuck you, Man!
Come on.
What are you? New? Eat dinner
before you take drugs.
What are you thinking about?
The last four years of my life.
- Trying to figure out where it went.
- The time. No shit.
- No. There's something else.
- What?
I don't really know what to
call it.
I remember when I was younger
I used to notice it in the way
I'd move my arms sometimes
or the way somebody bumps into
you in the store and says,
"Excuse me."
I could be folding my laundry
or reading in bed
and it would just occur to me
that I'm alive.
I haven't felt that way in
a long time.
But I feel like that right now.
Hey! Harmony, right?
You two know each other?
Colin, this is Harmony.
Hi.
I don't understand you two
just sitting here when
you could be
outside on the
dance floor dancing.
You're missing it all!
Zoe Jameson, one of my
best friends at the time
we traveled all over Madrid
and Ibiza and Amsterdam...
My brother, he tried to get me
to do the Eurorail thing.
It's so funny, because
I remember telling him
I didn't feel like going.
I can't believe that.
You would have loved Spain.
Oh, did you go to San Sebastian?
No, but I went to Club
Rohypnol and Club Insomnia
and Daydream. We got on the
ten clubs in eight days bus.
I told myself that I was
seeing the world, but I didn't
see the light of day.
How long did you two last?
I don't know. We kind of
just stayed there and came
back when our money ran out.
You know, did some shit jobs
and just worked to party.
And then what?
Zoe sort of...
I guess she went off to school
in Buffalo, I think.
I just kind of did my thing,
you know.
No one every OD'd, I never
had a friend die on me, and
I always felt like I was just
on the brink of something.
Did you ever see Zoe again?
I was coming back one morning
I have my ass
on the 1-9 train
and I saw her.
And, I don't know why
I remember this, but
she was wearing this watch,
this amazing gold watch that
I'd never seen before
and her hair looked different.
I said to her, "Hey!
"Sister, how's school going?"
And she looked at me for a
long time.
A long time.
And she said,
"I graduated two years ago."
And I promised myself after
that that I'd change,
you know?
But what am I doing now?
I mean, I moved here
and I ain't done shit.
Why not?
It just doesn't happen.
What are you waiting for?
What do you mean?
Well, what do you want to do?
I don't know.
Do you know?
I mean, I'm sorry,
but I don't know.
Yeah, I do know what I want to
do, but I'm not doing it.
The same as you.
So, come on.
I don't know.
This is safe.
I just want to commit
to something without any fear.
Yeah, I think that's what
we'd both like.
But it doesn't work like that.
I know.
This is good. It's weird,
'cause it's good.
I'm going to get you some water.
- Please stay.
- No.
I'll be right back.
Ernest! He's got to get
out of here right
now, man.
- They're coming from Oracle.
- What?
Roland's party, man.
It got busted and he gave out
this address.
- How big was it?
- About a thousand.
Joe.
Hey.
Joe?
Come on. Come on!
Hey, come on. Wake up!
- Asshole!
- What do you care?
You'd be dead if I didn't.
You don't fucking care.
Whatever.
You're fucked up.
What's up, kids?
We've reached capacity.
You can't come in.
Hey, isn't this Ernie's party?
No, this isn't his party.
There's tramps in there.
You wouldn't like it.
But you said I could get in.
He knows me, man.
Tell him there's an outdoor
next week Sunday.
Have him check the voice mail.
There's a free beach party,
an outdoor, on Sunday.
If you check with the
voice mail...
What do I do now?
Run.
Let's hit the road.
Officer, can't I just get my
records, here?
I'll just put them away.
We got to clear you out.
Come on, bud.
- Officer, I just need to get my records.
- Come on.
Let's go, son, move along!
- Shut her down right now.
- Okay, okay. Give us five. Relax.
Let's go. Get some air.
Keep on spreading the love,
right out the door.
Let's go!
Come on, you're going to be
late for school.
You need to come down.
Come on.
Let's go. Everyone out!
Right now!
This party is over!
Hey, Colin.
Maybe I'll see you out again
some time. Can you give me
your number, or...
Look, I normally don't do
that sort of thing.
Why? You don't have a phone?
You know exactly what I'm
talking about.
Oh. You mean our little
meeting of the minds?
- Look, I'm not... You know...
- What?
Neither am I.
Well, is there anything else
going on tonight?
Tonight. Neil, it's 4:00 a.m.
Fuck it. Let's go home.
I have an idea.
- David!
- Hey!
- I thought you left.
- No.
- You haven't seen Harmony, have you?
- No, I haven't.
- Just give me a hug, okay?
- Okay.
Hey, did you see Leyla leave?
Colin?
- Remember in gym, those little bags?
- What bags?
You know, those little kits
that had the razors and the
shaving cream in them?
Oh, right, right!
And deodorant.
You okay, Colin?
Me and Harmony kind of got
into a little fight.
But everything's going
to be okay.
I'm just really glad that
you're here.
I am, too, Colin. I am, too.
I'll go find her.
- Your ring is so beautiful!
- Thanks.
- You're so lucky.
- You know what they say about Geminis and Scorpios:
they're meant to be.
Why do you do this to yourself?
You don't even get paid,
you risk getting arrested.
For what?
- You don't know?
- No.
The nod.
- The nod?
- Yeah.
It happens to me at least once
every party.
Somebody comes up to me and
says, "Thank you for making
this happen."
"I needed this." "This really
meant something to me."
And they nod.
And I nod back.
- That's it?
- That's it.
Hey, guys. Sorry I'm late.
Is this party still happening,
or what?
Voice mail.
Change the message.
"Digweed just walked in with
a fresh crate of vinyl."
They'll be e-mailing about
this one for years.
I hate to interfere with your
reality, right now,
but we were busted.
You gonna let a little thing
like that stop us?
I wouldn't call getting the
power locked out and getting
our decks checked by the cops
a little thing.
I mean, everybody's gone.
- How about showing a little faith?
- How about opening your eyes?
It's over.
Guy, if there's one thing you
learn tonight I hope
it's this:
the shit ain't over till
the last record spins.
Watch your step.
Straight ahead.
Come on. It's on, it's on.
You have control of the bridge.
Look, Harmony,
there's something...
Vitamin E as an antioxidant,
some tryptophan to
stabilize serotonin
and some ephedrine to
pick me up.
- You want to hit the EndUp?
- Sure.
Thanks.
Glad you enjoyed it.
Thank you.
- Can I touch you?
- What?
I just want to say that I
touched the DJ that changed
my life.
I'm serious! I wouldn't be
spinning this crazy shift
if it wasn't for you.
That's why I'm here. That last
song you played was sick!
Tore the roof off!
I mean, you just can't find
records like that in Fresno.
I gotta mix... What's this?
That's the new Bedrock single.
It's the last track
I played tonight.
- No shit!
- Yeah, I heard you played a rocking set tonight.
Everyone said it was great.
Keep up the good work.
- Hey. Right on.
- Thank you.
- Nice meeting you.
- See you, yeah.
Hey, you know,
if you're ever in Fresno,
I do a weekly there.
- Friday night. It's rocking.
- Maybe I'll see you down there.
Yeah.
Hey, Ernie.
- Yeah?
- I'm glad I found you.
I don't know, I just wanted to
say, you know,
thanks.
No problem.
- So.
I'd like to call you,
if that's okay.
Got a pen?