♪♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪♪
[PEOPLE YELLING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
♪♪
[YELLING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE
CONTINUES]
♪♪
[WHISPERING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
♪♪
[WHISPERING CONTINUES]
[CONVERSING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
♪♪
[WHISPERING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
♪♪
DR. BLAUMAN: Now reaching the
right side of the colon.
That looks pretty clean.
And there's the ileocecal valve,
which is pink and looks fine.
Prep looks good.
Looks like he's well
cleaned out.
Going up the sigmoid colon.
Two scattered diverticula there.
Heading towards
the splenic flexure now.
That looks clean.
In the mid-transverse colon...
Wait a second.
That looks like a polyp there.
It's only about 2 cm.
We can take
some biopsies of that.
Yussi, I'm a block away.
YUSSI:
Where the fuck are you, man?
- I told you. I'm walking.
- I've got two guys.
They said they're gonna be
watching the business
the whole day.
What the fuck is going on?
Hey, man, who the fuck do you
think you're talking to?
YUSSI: They keep saying
they're friends of Arno.
Arno?
Tell them I'm coming up now.
Harvey, I need that.
♪♪
[DOOR BUZZES]
YUSSI: 30 inches.
That's, like,
about 35 carats in there.
There's like a side one.
[DOOR BUZZES]
- And right in the middle...
- You know what I see?
DEMANY: Yo, Howard.
What's popping, man?
This is my nigga, Ca$h Out,
I was telling you about.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- How do you feel? All right?
- No, it was good.
They're calling me
with the results.
- Hey, get some face on.
- Hi, how are you?
- I'm good, man.
- Congratulations.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
No, he's doing you a favor.
Believe me.
That guy is a fucking moron.
Arno's friend is here?
Yeah, I'm...
Guess you two have been
waiting on me,
so I'm sorry about that.
I'm Howard.
You didn't bring him any water?
- I'm good on the water.
- Where's his water?
I don't really need water.
Thank you anyway.
This is...
This is our own spring water.
We're the first on the block
to have that.
- Your parents happy for you?
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Alright. So I've got to tell
you, I'm in a bit of a rush.
I don't have much time because
I've got to... I've got to...
- What did I tell you?
- Hey.
I said no water.
Didn't I tell you no water?
I think it's in
your best interest that you
find some time for you and I.
We're right on
the same page, right?
- You all right, homie?
- Oh, yeah, 100% fine.
HOWARD: It's good.
I'll handle it.
I'll handle it. I'll handle it.
YUSSI:
We don't do that here, sir.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
ARNO: Arno Meradian...
- ...is not available.
- Okay. Alright.
- He's not answering.
- He... He knows you're calling.
He doesn't want to deal
with you anymore.
I understand.
No, I don't think you
do understand.
Come on. Come on.
It's not a fucking soap opera.
- Listen. Listen. Enough.
- What are we doing?
- What the fuck is...
- There you go again.
- Stop fighting me.
- This is not necessary.
PHIL: No, it isn't? Well, we'll
be the judge of that.
- What the fuck is this?
- Wow.
Literally my last
of my mom's cash that I had.
- What about this? What's this?
- This is not mine.
- It's not mine.
- Take the fucking...
HOWARD: Take the fucking watch.
Take it. Take it.
Fucking...
ARNO: Arno Meradian...
...is not available.
Arno, what the fuck
is this shit?
You're sending collectors
to fuck with me at my office?
Are you out
of your fucking mind?
I'm literally minutes away
from closing the biggest deal
of my Goddamn life,
and when I do,
you're gonna be embarrassed.
Oh, and by the way, the watch
they took from me,
it's worth $20,000.
I want that deducted
from the hundred grand.
You understand?
Call me back!
Look at this.
What's up, ladies?
- Shh, she's sleeping.
- She's sleeping.
♪♪
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
This is bullshit.
- Hey, Howie.
- Hey, Howard. How are you?
People coming in and out
of the apartment.
JULIA:
Oh, my God. Not this song.
You show up to work any time
you damn please.
Howard, I was
working all night.
I'm sick of this shit.
You're taking advantage of me.
Oh, Howard. Oh, my God.
Howard.
10:30.
It's time to wake up.
- You're so extra.
- So you had a party last night?
I did not have a party.
Did we have a party?
- That was not a party.
- Why didn't you call me?
Okay because I did call you
at around 9:30.
You said, "I'll call you
back in five."
- I waited for hours.
- Yes because I fell asleep.
- No, that's fucking rude.
- I was putting Beni to sleep.
- Oh, here we go with the lies.
- I had to put him to sleep.
- I'm not lying!
- You're so manipulative!
I had to fall asleep
on the floor again!
I'm exhausted!
Well, I didn't ask you
to have kids!
It's not my fault you have kids.
Oh, shut the fuck up with that.
JULIA: Look, do you want
to fucking stay mad,
or do you want to
get in bed and cuddle?
I know you want to cuddle,
Howard.
- Just come here.
- Come on.
Come on.
Just come here.
Come here, baby.
Come on.
I know you want to.
- God, I'm stressed out.
- I know you can't resist me.
I know you can't resist me.
Come on.
Don't. Don't. Don't.
You can't just do that.
JULIA: Don't you want to see
the photos I took?
- Yes. Yes.
- Look at this one, Howard.
- Look.
- Show me. What was this shoot?
WOMAN: She looked amazing.
Look at her butt in this one.
- It's insane.
- I took these pictures.
I think I really have a future
in 3500.
- And who is this guy?
- It's this guy, The Weeknd.
- He's mature.
- What the fuck is The Weeknd?
JULIA: He's gonna be major
even though he's from Canada.
This guy looks stupid.
- Hi.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
Howard Ratner.
How are you?
See, I have a piece.
You know this kid, The Weeknd?
That's Michael Jackson there
on the cross.
Gonna be a controversial piece.
It makes it more valuable.
The blacks are VS2s.
That's platinum.
Turn around. Don't even...
Don't even step in my place.
- Turn around.
- I've got some bets. 24 G's.
Don't even sit down. 24 G's?
Where would you get 24 G's?
I want the OKC/Lakers.
I want the fucking over.
- Alright?
- Yeah.
- I want Kobe's under...
- Kobe under.
HOWARD: ...because he's, fucking
all of a sudden, he's passing.
- Can't just go with the ocean.
- He's not scoring tonight.
[CELLPHONE VIBRATING]
I want the Sixers to cover.
- Plus one.
- The points...
- Let's finish the bet here.
- Let's... uh...
Hey, one thing at a time.
I mean, come on now.
- Go.
- Demany. Demany.
Can you finish the bet?
If he gets to the store
before I do,
you just fucking keep him there.
Okay?
- Better get here soon.
- You promise me?
DEMANY: Motherfucker said he's
going to be here any...
Kevin Garnett is coming
to my fucking showroom
- right now, right now.
- Finish the bet.
Eighth floor, going up.
PHIL: We've got to rewrite
the fucking...
[YELLING INDISTINCTLY]
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey.
Get the fuck out.
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
- What?
- Fuck you, man.
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
What the fuck is going on
out here?
That's on you, asshole.
- Come on.
- You see this?
I don't know
these fucking guys.
You're dead, fucker.
You're dead.
- I...
- You think I'm playing games?
Get your laugh out now, asshole.
- I didn't do nothing.
- When I'm shoveling dirt
over your fucking head,
you'll see how funny it is then.
DAVID: I have clients
in the office now.
- This is crazy.
- Turn around and walk away.
We're good. We're good.
Alright.
David, go back inside.
Everything is fine.
- Turn around and walk away.
- That's my... That's my shop.
DAVID: Everybody back in there.
Get back in.
- Hello. Open the door.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Okay.
- Jesus.
You're with KG?
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Okay. Well, you've got
to shut that door.
KG, huh?
That closed?
- That's my man?
- It's insane.
Howard. Howard.
What the fuck is going on, man?
- Nothing.
- They tried to fuck Yussi up.
Look at...
Look at his fucking shirt.
Look at his shirt.
Okay. Listen.
Hey.
Thanks for the security,
by the way.
Send those bitches back
to Paramis or Bay Ridge, yeah.
You take that and charge
it up for me?
All I've got is fucking Yussi
to protect me.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- Hey, let us talk.
- My nigga talking.
What's up? What's up?
Did Armario fucking time
on the clock?
Come on.
There's no time on the clock.
You're waving him up.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- I like the earrings.
- Like these?
Those are great.
I was coming here,
checking out some new ones, man.
When's the last time
you cleaned them?
Let me clean those for you.
Let me throw them
in the ultrasonic
for you for free, okay?
- What's this gonna cost me?
- For free.
Free, for real?
I would think you would have
bigger rocks than that
because you're a big guy.
Let me see what you all got
in here, man.
HOWARD: Who would win in a
fight, Ben Wallace or Tony Allen?
- T.A. all day.
- Oh, yeah? Okay.
- What is that?
- Fuck out of here.
What is that, gremlin?
Gremlin over here.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
DEMANY: Animal or some kind
of fucking,
some toy or some shit in here.
Just bring the bitch out.
Used to work with niggas on
early music videos,
all that shit.
He's, like, the first nigga
to start all that.
- You serious?
- I started that shit.
- Show him your fucking eye.
- I started... Yo. Alright.
So I did this,
so it fucks with you.
Oh, you serious?
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
That's why it scares the shit
out of people.
Yo, that guy.
DEMANY: Fucking older model,
but it's dope.
HOWARD: Listen.
- No, you can put that shit...
- The shit was slammed.
What's the length on that?
Alright.
Let me see the chain on that.
That's a 18.
I can get you a 14.
KG! Doc know you're here,
by the way?
No, he doesn't,
and let's keep it that way.
- Alright?
- It's game night.
- You should be stretching out.
- It's fucking insane.
I was about to say,
what is he, your coach?
No. He's just a fucking
crazy-ass Jew.
Throw these in the ultrasonic.
Yes, boss, as soon
as the other stuff is done.
No, now.
We've got to look
at that shit.
- KG, I wouldn't lean on that.
- Yo. Yo. Yo.
Kevin was just telling me
he's looking for some watches.
- Are you looking for watches?
- Yeah.
Let's go to the wall
of watches right here.
- What are we talking...
- I was thinking about,
you know,
seeing about the Presi though.
- You got that crazy-ass deal.
- That one for 16.
KEVIN: The crazy one though.
You know?
- Yeah. The...
- The Presi.
Yeah. Right. Right.
DEMANY:
Hey, look at this right here.
- Boom.
- Alright.
Well, that's a small watch
for a big man.
- I don't know.
- What are they retailing at?
- You got papers for this?
- No.
HOWARD: Listen, I don't have
the box and papers.
DEMANY: Of course
he's got fucking papers.
I don't have either one.
What are you talking about?
- You sold me the shit, dummy.
- I don't remember that.
Listen. Listen, man. Niggas call
niggas out for this, man.
Of course. Of course. If you
don't have the box and paper...
You find me one nigga,
one nigga with a KMH watch
- they called out.
- Okay.
It's a moot point, Demany,
because I don't have these.
Alright?
So how about we move on
to the diamonds here?
Listen. You got a girl?
Why don't you get...
get your girl a treat
- He doesn't have a girlfriend.
- Says who?
Says you.
KEVIN: How you know if I got
a girlfriend or not?
Howard, get the fuck
over here.
- Because you told me.
- I never said that.
- Fuck are you doing, man?
- What? What's up?
What didn't you bring my
Goddamn watches out?
- I'm not doing that.
- Nigga would have bought one.
I told you, you can keep them
in my safe.
I don't want you selling them
out of my showroom.
- You understand me?
- Fucking dumbass.
Where the fuck am I going
to sell them, nigga?
- On the Goddamn street?
- That's not my problem, man.
Oh, that ain't
your fucking problem?
- No, it isn't.
- That ain't your fucking...
He don't like shit in this dusty
motherfucking room.
Yes, he does.
He's having a fucking ball here.
What are you talking about?
What the fuck is he going
to buy, a Goddamn Furby, nigga?
Fuck you. Alright?
I'm gonna take his ass
to motherfucking Flawless.
I'm done fucking with you.
You're not taking him
to Flawless.
- I'm taking him to Flawless...
- No.
DEMANY: ...since you're acting
like a fucking...
KG, do me a favor.
Don't lean on that, please.
[DOORBELL RINGS] DEMANY: What the fuck.
You're acting stupid.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Okay.
Buzz them in.
Buzz them in now.
[DOOR BUZZES]
Now.
Oh, my God.
Is this... This is it!
- This is it! Hey.
- What's up?
- Okay, look at this.
- Got a package from Fishtonic.
- Where do you want this?
- Bring it in.
Bring it in.
Go into my office.
KG, don't you dare leave, okay?
What's in this package
is gonna blow your mind, KG.
- Is it heavy?
- Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
Give me that.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Man, I can't do this
anymore, bro.
What happened? What happened?
Tell me.
What happened?
There's three goons in there.
They attacked me, man.
HOWARD: Well, what did you say
to piss them off?
Listen, Garnett's crew
came in here.
They took a look around.
They see these guys.
They're like,
"Yo, who works here?
Who doesn't?
Who doesn't, get out."
I said, "These guys
don't work here."
Well, that was stupid.
You shouldn't have said that.
These guys grabbed me. They
dragged me over the counter.
They ripped my shirt.
They've got me looking
like a fool over here.
Here. Here. Take this shirt.
That's a Gucci shirt.
It's $500.
It's brand new.
Are you fucking serious
right now?
- The tag is still on it.
- It ain't about the shirt.
You know what I'm saying?
I gave you 8 years of my life.
Look how you're
treating me, man.
I... I... I put in everything
into this business.
I saved your ass
a thousand times.
I can't take this place
anymore, man.
I can't deal with your problems
every other day.
Listen, there's a lot of people
on this block
that would love
to do business with me.
When you're gonna see me
out there working with them,
you're not gonna
like it, man.
You're gonna be jealous.
You're not gonna like it,
Howard.
Howard. Hello?
I'm standing here, man.
There's a lot of people
I could be doing business with
other than you, Howard.
You're... You're falling apart.
You're looking like a fool out
here in the Diamond District.
Looking through fucking fish.
Come on, man.
I gave you 8 years of my life,
and you can't even fucking talk
to me
and look me in the eyes,
man to fucking man?
Holy shit, I'm gonna come.
YUSSI: Man, fuck you, man.
I'm finished
with this shit hole.
♪♪
KG.
KG. Yo.
- Howard, Yussi is gone.
- That's fine with me.
Let me get a phone from you.
Let me get that phone.
KG, you've got to come here.
Alright?
- I've got to show you.
- I've got to leave soon, man.
I know you have to,
but listen to me.
- I got to get out of here.
- Okay.
So I'm watching TV,
like a year ago.
Alright?
I'm watching one of those
fucking History Channel shows,
trying to learn shit,
and I stumble...
You ever hear African Jews?
- African Jews?
- Yeah.
- No. Alright? No.
- Nigga, where everybody got
- to be a Jew.
- Check this out.
Oh, no. Alright?
So these are black Jews.
Alright?
They're stranded in the middle
of Ethiopia.
It's deep shit.
- Stranded?
- Yeah.
Look.
They've got nothing.
They don't got cars.
They don't got shit.
And I'm watching this,
and I'm like,
"What the fuck are
these guys wearing?"
Look. It's over there.
It's everywhere. Right?
This is...
Where do these fucking guys
get precious black opals?
That's what that is.
- Black opal?
- I do my research.
These guys live near the Welo
mines, which primarily
is red opal,
which aren't worth shit, okay?
- Oh, okay.
- But these...
Now you can't get your hands
on these things.
- You understand?
- Really?
So look, I say to myself,
"How do I get a hold
of these guys?"
and I managed to track
these guys down.
- I buy one of them from him.
- Holy shit.
What is that?
It's right here.
That's the rock.
That's the stone.
- Holy shit.
- I got it.
KEVIN: Look how this is winking
in the light, man.
How the fuck did you
get this shit, man?
Took me fucking 17 months
to get this thing, okay?
Just look at this.
Hang on for a second.
Go through my loupe. Be careful.
That's my best loupe.
- Let me see this, man.
- Alright?
HOWARD: I want you to look...
look at it.
You really into
that motherfucker.
- Isn't that the shit?
- Oh, wow.
That's history right there.
You understand?
- How many carats is this?
- What, 4,000, 5,000 carats?
$3,000 a carat.
I'm not fucking
bullshitting you.
Why's it got so many colors
in it, man?
- What is that?
- That's the thing.
They say you can see
the whole universe in opals.
- That's how fucking old they are.
- Holy shit.
I've been telling you. That's
why I wanted you to see it.
How do I get it?
I've got to have it.
- Your ass is crazy, man.
- Fucking from stone to stone.
Garnet is a stone.
You know that.
That's a million dollar opal
you're holding,
straight from
the Ethiopian Jewish tribe.
I mean, this is old-school,
middle-earth shit.
KEVIN: Got a motherfucking
dinosaur gem in this bitch.
HOWARD:
Dinosaur, that's right.
The dinosaurs fucking staring
at this thing.
It's 110 million years old
at the least.
- It's deep shit.
- Basketball, basketball...
HOWARD:
Can't lean on the glass, KG.
- Yo!
- Oh, shit!
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
You all right?
Get a fucking
towel or something.
You heard me, man.
I was telling him not to lean.
- You all right?
- Don't cut your fucking self.
KEVIN:
That's a sign though.
That's a sign for me
that I need it.
That's what this is.
DEMANY: Got to make sure
my nigga good.
Demany...
I'm telling you,
it's a lot of weight
you were putting on it.
That's a sign.
I need this. I need this.
It's not for sale.
I can't... I can't sell it.
What do you mean
it's not for sale?
I can't do it.
That... Goddamn it.
I... I... It's set for auction.
I can't.
Why the fuck would you
show me something
if I couldn't have it, then?
The fuck would you
bring this out?
I don't know. Excited.
Excited to share it.
Well, let me hold it
for a night then.
Right? Let me wait
until the game tomorrow.
It'll be cool.
You know, I'm going to the game.
Nigga, I'll grab it from you
then meet you at Abby's
tomorrow morning, first thing.
- Boom. Boom.
- Just like that.
- It's perfect.
- Howard, come on.
- It's one night, Howard.
- Serious?
- I can't.
- It's one night.
They'll pull it
from the auction.
JULIA: He's good for it.
He's good for it.
KEVIN: You don't understand.
This stone, I'm really
connecting with this, man.
I feel like I'm gonna have
40 or 50 on this, man.
You understand that?
DEMANY: You see what the fuck
I'm talking about, Howard?
It's just speaking to him.
You know?
KEVIN: Man, I'm gonna destroy
Philly tonight with this.
- Yeah.
- Get your ass.
KEVIN: Nigga, this fucking thing
makes me feel like I can fly.
- Shit.
- Howard, you hear that?
DEMANY:
Yeah. Let him get that.
You're going to at me
at howiebling.
- Yes.
- 30 fucking pics, I want likes.
- Yes. I got you.
- He's talking about at-ing me.
HOWARD:
Let me get a fucking shot.
- There's a good idea, man.
- Come here. Come here.
- Look at this. Woo.
- You hold it up.
Look at this shit.
Boom.
KEVIN: Boom. Cool.
Uh... You can't just...
Give me a...
Give me the Celtic ring.
I want the ring.
- Howard, come the fuck on.
- Collateral.
No, no, no, no, no.
He's good money, my nigga.
I know he's good for it.
I want to make a deal.
That's a deal.
That's a deal. That's a deal.
- I give you that.
- Thanks. Alright.
I'll keep it right here,
right next to my Knicks '73.
KEVIN: Classic. Classic.
I like that.
I appreciate you understanding.
Got you. Right.
- But listen, you meet me.
- Yeah, I'll meet your happy ass.
- Yes. Alright.
- You will fucking
bring that stone to me,
9:00 in the morning.
Hey. Hey. Hey, listen to me.
No dicking around.
- You show up. You hear me?
- Chill.
I'll see you there,
motherfucker.
Alright. Let's roll.
Let's do it, nigga.
Let's do it.
- Buzz them out.
- I got his earrings.
HOWARD: Hey, the earrings.
Wait. Bring it out to him.
Keep them.
Keep them until tomorrow.
- I'll grab them.
- Black Jew power, nigga.
- He's so extra.
- Fucking out.
HOWARD: Who's gonna clean
this fucking shit?
Eddie, boy,
what are you doing?
What do you want?
Look what I got.
Look.
You're gonna love this.
Here.
- Hey. What's that right there?
- Howard...
- Will you leave me alone?
- What is it?
It's Kevin Garnett's ring,
championship ring, NBA, 2008.
I knew you would freak out.
- Alright. I love you, my boy.
- Alright. Bye.
Roberto, you came to work.
- Ronstein.
- Hey, Howard.
Hey. Break out your tray.
Where is he?
I'd shake your hand,
but I know where it's been.
Look at this.
It's Kevin Garnett's
2008 championship ring.
- Championship ring?
- Championship ring, 2008.
Alright. You want to pawn it
or you want to sell it?
I want to pawn it.
Let me take a quick
look at it.
I don't know what
you're looking for.
- Check the diamond.
- Okay?
That was just on
his fucking finger.
- It's single cut, Howie.
- Let me see it.
It's single cut.
It's not even full cut.
- Steve, take a look at it.
- You talk to the fucking league
about the way
they cut their shit.
MAN: I understand,
but they're worth less.
Take a look at this.
Alright?
MAN: Alright. It's his ring.
I understand.
It's from his Instagram. It's
fucking blowing up right now.
I hear you. Alright.
So what do you need for it?
I figure that thing
is worth 80 grand.
Just loan it to me.
That's it.
Just float it to me.
I'll be back Friday.
Number one, we both know
what's in here.
We both know that the value is
mostly because it's memorabilia.
But it is a memorabilia piece,
so that's how you're
gonna sell it, right?
STEVE: So I tell you what.
Give me 50 G's.
Just float it to me.
I'm gonna give you $25,000, but
I want an 8% fee on the ring.
8%? Fucking, how about
I give you a grand?
You take a grand off the top.
I'm gonna come back
Friday for it.
You know, last time you had
something here for 6 months,
- so we want to make sure upfront.
- Alright. Alright.
Last time wasn't my fault.
We fucking went over that.
I understand.
Let's make it quick.
$21,000, 7% fee,
and I want you to know,
said you'd be back Friday.
If you're not back Friday,
it's my ring.
HOWARD: If I don't bring it back
Friday, I'm a dead man, so...
- Alright. So we have a deal?
- Alright. Deal.
- Mazel. Mazel.
- Mazel.
HOWARD: Alright. Mazel.
Can you go to the safe
and get me the money?
MAN: Get him the money.
We'll get you the money.
HOWARD: Alright.
Hey, good pace.
This is great.
ARNO: 70th and 1st, what the
fuck is he doing there?
He's walking.
Oh, now he's stopping.
He's slowing down.
- What?
- He's doing something.
He's playing with his phone
or something.
He's playing with something.
I can't make it out. I can't see
him. His back is to me.
He's hunched over.
You can't see.
PHIL: I don't know.
We... We can't see anything.
Oh. Oh! Oh, here he goes.
Here he goes. He's going again.
ARNO: Wait.
I just got a text from him.
- What's he saying?
- It's a picture of money.
- This fucking prick.
- He says, "Arno..."
He's got fucking money.
ARNO: "...I've got your money
right here."
PHIL: Alright.
He's turning in somewhere.
A restaurant, Melo's.
- Hey, handsome, where's he at?
- He's in the back.
He's in the back.
Hey, you got him
making meatballs in the back?
Alright.
You have your romaine.
You have your croutons.
You have your eggs.
No carrots in the salad.
What do you want?
You made your bet.
I know. I know.
I've got to change the bet.
I've got $21,000 here,
so you add it on
to the 19 grand.
- $40,000 in all.
- Scrap the whole bet?
Scrap the whole bet.
I want to make a 6-way parlay,
Celtics-Sixers game,
what's the lineup?
- Still plus one.
- Plus one.
Okay, so I want the Celtics
to cover.
I want the Celtics halftime.
I want Garnett
points and rebounds.
- Alright.
- Garnett blocked shots,
Celtics opening tip.
Do you take lightning bets?
Yeah, but you don't want
any part of lightning bets.
Fine. $1,000 a point, okay?
Take this, and this is
a gift from me.
What's this?
HOWARD: For just tolerating me
for all this time. Okay?
No. No. No.
I already have a Rolex.
I don't need your watch. This
probably fell off a truck.
Listen, but what do you know?
Garnett this, Garnett that.
What do you know?
I don't know.
I just know.
Well, I tell you what I know,
that's the dumbest fucking bet
I ever heard of.
I disagree.
I disagree, Gary.
Shoot. Let him shoot.
Let him shoot.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
ANNOUNCER: Jrue Holiday,
who came out of a four game...
Fucker was five fucking steps
in to the...
[CELLPHONE VIBRATING]
ANNOUNCER: ...At 18 points,
hitting four of six
from 3-point range.
Christ.
ANNOUNCER: Many feel that they
stole game one at home....
That's it. Dump it to KG.
Finish it. Finish it.
- Back them down. Back them down.
- Garnett double.
Boo! Fuck you!
Yes, that's it.
That's it.
That's my man.
Go, get up on him.
Get up on him.
Fucking... Get the fuck
up on him.
Goddamn it.
Howard, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Howard,
Beni is waiting for you.
Okay, I'm coming up.
It's 25 minutes past
his bedtime. Go.
- Did he brush his teeth yet?
- Brush his teeth?
I sent you seven texts
in the dark. Howard.
- Yeah.
- It's the first quarter.
Guy was in my shop
earlier today.
- Look at him. Soft touch.
- I don't care, Howard.
HOWARD: Hit that fucking shit.
Boom.
Howard, go say good night
to your son.
Okay, let me get up there.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
Let me just get to a time-out.
This fucking ref is ridiculous.
- Now!
- Alright!
Alright.
Alright. Sorry.
I'm sorry.
God fucking...
ANNOUNCER: Time-out Philly.
[ANNOUNCER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY ON PHONE]
Garnett opening up with 4
on the shot clock again.
Garnett, vintage
game one for sure.
15 points on seven
for eight.
Oh!
Fuck you.
[WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY]
ANNOUNCER:
For the turnaround...
HOWARD: Hey. Hey. Hey.
EDDIE: Garnett's killing
it right now.
I know. I know.
Beni's sleeping.
- Keep it down.
- I'm sorry. I'm just so hyped.
NBA is always the last
2 fucking minutes,
so let's calm down.
- Hit that, KG!
- About to win money.
Jason's about to give me
25 bucks for the first half.
Double that up last half,
I might get 50 bucks.
Your father bet a lot
of money on this one.
Really? How much? How much?
- You don't want to know.
- A lot though, right?
Yes. Put that shit
in the fucking hole.
That's right. Come on.
He can dunk again.
Dunk again.
Boom. Boom. Boom.
Alright.
Fucking amazing.
Fucking amazing, right?
He's down.
He's asleep.
WOMAN #2: ...but no.
He's like, "You can paint.
You can follow your hobbies
and your bliss
and your entrepreneurial thing,"
and Stephanie and Annalise
went, "Ooh."
What would do if you had
two weeks to live?
- Uh, that's a big question.
- Could you flip...
flip it to ESPN
just for one second?
This is a huge game.
That's why he's going
so crazy up there.
DINAH: You know what?
I'm tempted to wrangle the kids
downstairs right now
and get it over with.
You really want to do that?
I don't know how
sensitive that is.
Oh, you're calling me
insensitive?
Thought we... we both agreed
that we wait
till after Passover.
Next, you'll be saying
you want to wait
until after the summer.
I'm not opposed to waiting
until after summer.
It's a commercial.
Can you just put the game
on for two fucking minutes
until my car gets here?
MAN #2:
Take our breath away.
Life is the only thing...
ANNOUNCER: Hey, that's no
Chuck the Body.
No words can describe that.
ANNOUNCER: 41? I don't know how
old these guys are,
but you can't tell by their age.
ANNOUNCER #2: You're saying ages
all older than you are.
ANNOUNCER #1:
Well, younger than the...
This is crazy.
ANNOUNCER #1: KG hits the shot
from outside.
He'll be 36 on Saturday,
and he puts the Celtics
over the century mark.
[ANNOUNCER CONTINUES
INDISTINCTLY]
Oh! Oh!
Yes!
Oh, God, yes!
Holy fuck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
ANNOUNCER #1:
First home playoff game
in the second round in 9 years.
- Hey, change of plans.
- What's up?
Take the exit,
49th Street and 3rd Ave,
Smith & Wollensky's.
- Everything okay?
- I just...
- Uh, what's your name?
- Dallas.
Davis, I just hit
very big, very big.
Oh, my God.
ANNOUNCER #1: Five-point tag,
spin back for the alley-oop,
and if it wasn't fouled, he was
gonna posterize somebody.
KG having fun.
ANNOUNCER #2: Oh, yeah.
HOWARD: Jules?
♪♪
Hey.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
♪♪
[RINGING CONTINUES]
JULIA: Hey, what's up?
Baby, where are you at?
JULIA: I'm just coming back
right now. I'm in the elevator.
Why, what's up?
I got held up.
I'm just on my way back now.
Yeah, Dinah was on
a tear tonight.
- Oh, that sucks.
- Yeah.
JULIA: How far away are you?
I am in the tunnel,
just getting in there.
JULIA: Oh, okay.
So you're very close.
- Yes.
- Um, so hold on. I got to go.
- I got to go.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Hey.
- What?
I can't wait to see you.
I'm in an incredible mood.
JULIA:
Okay, I got another line.
I got another line. I got to go.
- Okay.
- Bye.
♪♪
JULIA: As we speak.
Yeah, and I still have
to set up the steaks.
I still have to get ready.
Because his gem came.
Hello?
Do you not listen to me
as I've been talking
about it all day?
I'm gonna wear the...
Remember the green
that I took the photo of?
Yeah, I know.
I know.
♪♪
[CELLPHONE DINGS]
[TYPING]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[CELLPHONE DINGS]
- I'm gonna come!
- Ah!
I'm gonna come.
I can't help it.
I had to get you.
- Oh, my God!
- I had to get you.
- Why the fuck did you do that?
- No, no, no, no.
You see how fucking
sweet you look.
You look so gorgeous.
I just get so fucking big.
- I get so big.
- Oh, baby.
Do you feel how wet I am?
♪♪
DEMANY: I'm almost there.
I'm almost there.
What?!
You told me that already!
DEMANY: Yeah, I hit mad traffic.
What you want me to do about it?
We told... 9:00
we were supposed to be there!
It's fucking 9:43!
DEMANY: Look, all the city
is clogged up.
I can't do anything about it.
Alright?
Hey, not everybody is
on Demany time, man! Let's move!
DEMANY: I've been driving
since 7:00 a.m.
Okay, you can tell
Anne we're here.
Hold on one second.
Hi.
- Anne Deva...
- Mm-hmm.
...Howard Ratner
and his partner.
We're all ready to go.
Okay. Well, when your partner
gets here,
I will let her know
that you've both arrived.
[CELLPHONE VIBRATING]
Thanks.
You can sit over there
if you'd like.
- Yes?
- Yo, Howard.
I'm pulling up right now.
Come out.
I said, "I'm inside."
DEMANY:
I'm not gonna find parking.
- Double-park the car.
- Nah, I'm not
- getting no fucking ticket...
- Do it!
DEMANY: ...for you or nobody
else, so come meet me.
- I want to talk to you.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
DEMANY: No, I'm not
fucking kidding you.
Alright? I'm pulling up.
Come out.
Do you have any guests
or anything?
Okay.
We'll be right back.
Fuck. Fuck.
Stupid.
Howard, Howard!
Jesus.
How'd you find me?
Your office told me
where you are.
- You following me?
- Yeah, we need the money today.
My office would never
tell you that.
- This is the last straw.
- Get out of here!
You haven't been returning
my phone calls or texts.
You can't take 10 minutes?
What, you're bringing your
fucking heavy with you?
- Yeah. You got my money?
- Alright. You want money?
- Yeah.
- I got fucking money. Here.
- Fine, fine, fine.
- You owe me 32 grand.
Look, there's 30 grand.
Fucking sell that for 15 G's.
15 G's? Where?
Where am I gonna sell this?
Go to Wimpy's,
55th and 5th Avenue.
Go there. Now, put that
in your fucking pocket.
Hey, hey, where is it?
Where's it at?
- Where's the gem?
- Hey, get in real quick.
Give me the gem.
I'll run it upstairs.
Get in. Get in.
I want to talk to you.
I don't know anything
about a watch.
Hey, get the fuck out!
I don't want a watch!
You just gave it to me
for the money you owe me.
Shut the fuck up! I'm not buying
watches right now.
Back the fuck up! Don't touch my
shit. Alright?
HOWARD:
Walk the fuck away, man!
Come on, give me the opal.
Get in, my nigga,
so I can talk to you.
They're waiting on us.
We're late.
What am I getting in
the fucking car for?
- Get the fuck in!
- Jesus Christ!
Get out of here
with that fucking Fugazi shit.
- Who the fuck were they?
- Fuck.
Why... why am I
in your car right now?
- Alright. Alright. Alright.
- They're fucking waiting on us.
Listen. So, look, we're
at the fucking hotel.
We're getting ready to go.
We about to go party.
We got three bad bitches.
I don't have time for this.
Where is my opal?
And KG leaves his fucking
I.D. upstairs.
- Demany, we don't have time.
- Look.
They're waiting for us!
Where's the fucking opal?
Garnett got it!
Alright?
Garnett has got it?
He's fucked us.
I don't know what the fuck
you want me to do about that
- because you the one that got...
- Call him up.
Call him on the phone.
Let me talk to him.
I can't fucking call him
right now. He's at practice.
Tell him I will give him
another opal for free.
Howard, listen to me.
I can't call him because he is
at practice, my nigga.
He's not gonna answer
his fucking phone for me,
- God, nobody else.
- Fine!
Then we're going to practice.
We're going to practice.
So you want me to go
to fucking Philly right now?
He's in Philly?
Then we're going to Philly.
I... I can't. I just got back
from Philly, man.
I'm not driving to fucking...
It's two fucking hours
to get there.
Come on.
♪ Mr. CEO is what
my title say ♪
♪ Me and my homies did your ho ♪
♪ He feel some type of way ♪
♪ Way, way, way, way, way ♪
HOWARD: Got to be in and out,
in and out.
I got my daughter's
play tonight.
Who is that?
Is that KG?
Tell him we're here.
We're coming in.
Yo, you got to calm
your happy ass down.
Are we going
inside the facility,
or we gonna
meet him out here?
- Just chill the fuck out, bud.
- I hope we see Rondo in there.
Love to tell him, "Thank you,"
for dropping all those shots.
Man, no, that's not...
They busy, and what the fuck
is it with you Jewish
niggas and basketball anyway?
Huh? It sucks.
I'll have you know, the first
two points scored
in the NBA was a Jew.
- Yeah, yeah, Fred Flintstein?
- No!
Ossie Schectman, 1946,
played for the Knicks.
There we go.
Yeah, this is where
the big boys play.
Always, always got to practice
and always got...
Look at this.
This is sick, sick.
Oh, my God.
Hey, check this out.
Check it out.
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
- Yo, hey!
- Rondo, it's coming up!
He can't help himself!
He's gonna have to finish.
- What are you doing?
- And he scores!
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- Hey.
- Sorry, brother.
- What's changing for game two?
- Demany!
- I got one coming back.
- What's up?
- I'm with him.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
No, no, no. I'm with him.
Demany? What the fuck?
- Excuse me. Excuse me.
- What's he fucking...
- Hey, hi.
- I'm with him. I came with him.
You saw me walk
through the door.
What's your... No, I didn't see
you walk through the door.
What's your name?
Well, I won't be on a list
because I came with him.
I came with him.
What the fuck
is he doing to me?
Cocksucker fucking works for me!
WOMAN #3: Is Marcel excited?
DINAH: Yeah, I think
she's a little nervous.
WOMAN #3: Little nervous.
Well, it's the lead play.
DINAH: I'm very proud of her.
Yeah, Danny has got
a role, too.
WOMAN #3: Small part.
He's nervous, but...
DINAH: Good, yeah.
Yeah.
WOMAN #3: Nothing fazes him.
- You... you working?
- He said she was amazing.
HOWARD:
Hang on one second.
What are you guys doing
for the break?
Oh, um, we're not...
we're not doing
anything this year.
- Oh, really?
- Wow.
- That's not like you guys.
- Yeah, how come?
Howard, how come?
Howard?
- Everything okay?
- Howard?
- No vacation?
- No, we're... we're...
Next year, we're gonna take a
bigger trip, saving up for that.
Going to go to Europe.
Oh, that's nice.
So, yeah, do a little culture.
These kids are becoming morons.
- Well...
- Oh, yeah, well...
We'll be morons in Cancún.
Right, especially on this
trapeze, you know?
- Good luck to Danny tonight.
- Yeah, yeah.
HOWARD: When's he come?
- We just talked about Danny.
- Okay.
What are you going
to do for Passover?
- Is your sister coming?
- Aw, yeah.
HOWARD: What are you doing?
What do you got?
Watching from my phone,
I got six different people
playing six different games.
HOWARD: Hey, we're all
making... Hey. Who tapped me?
- Who was it?
- I'm not even sure about that.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
WOMAN #3:
That would be nice.
You gonna do the Questions,
the Four Questions?
- Yeah.
- You practicing?
EDDIE:
I've been practicing.
WOMAN #3: I don't know how we're
going to keep it in Mexico.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- Well, good luck to Marcel.
- I know and to Danny.
Where are you going?
Daddy has got to go the
bathroom. I'll be right back.
DINAH: She's gonna be on
in just a second.
I'll be back.
Thank you.
Howard, Marcel is about
to get on the...
- Okay, I'll be right back.
- Howard, everything okay?
♪♪
This is fucked up, guys.
What's so fucked up about it?
Could I speak
to you guys outside?
You sure you want to do that?
Yeah? Alright.
Excuse me.
♪♪
Hey!
What are we gonna do here, man?
Hey, you.
Come on, man.
Guys...
- Get the fuck off!
- Aah!
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
- Run!
- Hey, look out.
Coming through.
Are you kidding me,
how good you guys look?
- Dad, what are you doing?
- Marcel, break a leg!
We're all here.
♪♪
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Fuck.
♪♪
PHIL: Get him! Get him!
[TIRES SCREECH]
Fuck.
PHIL:
Come here, you motherfucker.
HOWARD: Hey, fuck you!
Fuck.
I'm fucked.
[CAR ALARM BEEPING]
PHIL: Come on. Come on.
Come on.
HOWARD: I'm up. I'm up.
I'm coming. I'm coming.
MAN #3: Hey, what the fuck?
You go and bit me?
HOWARD: I am! Fuck.
Arno!
- Get him in the fucking car!
- Arno! Arno!
- Arno!
Go, go, go. Come on.
Let's get out of here.
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
Arno, what is happening?
You don't know me.
Don't fucking speak my name.
- Give me the keys.
- The fucking Jew bit me!
Hey, hey.
What's happening right now?
I told you how things were
gonna go
if you didn't start to behave.
What?
How was I not behaving?
Explain to me.
I... I'm sorry.
I think I was very explicit
on the phone
about how things
were gonna go.
You like the way things
are going now, huh?
Give me the fucking keys
to your car.
What are you gonna do,
have them steal my Mercedes?
Look what the fuck you did!
You fucking bit my...
Arno.
Arno, fucking talk to me.
Don't listen to him, Arno.
It's not a game.
Stop saying my fucking name!
I have every intention
of paying you back.
- I'm broke right now.
- You broke?
- What's that?
- Look at that.
- Do you remember that?
- Look at it!
That is money that's not mine
that I sent to you
because I wanted
to calm you down.
We know for a fact that you
placed a bet with that money.
I never placed a bet
with that money.
- Yes, yes, you did.
- No, I didn't.
No, no, no, no, no.
Let me ask you something.
I heard that Beni and Eddie
are going to Timberlake.
And you know what else I heard?
I heard you've resurfaced
your fucking swimming pool.
Do you know how that
makes me feel?
Never resurfaced anything.
You think your life is
more important than mine?
- I don't know who said that!
- Give me the keys!
Give me the keys
to your fucking car!
Here's the fucking keys.
Fine.
Alright.
Listen. I do.
I did. I admit it.
I... I made a bet,
and guess what?
Here's the thing... I hit.
I hit the bet big.
You think I'm stupid.
You think I'm stupid, Howard,
you and your whole
fucking family.
I'll call the book right now.
You get on the phone,
and he'll tell you.
I saw your bookie!
You're talking about Gary?
You spoke to Gary about what,
about what?
About you, about how you're
taking my money all over town,
placing bets.
You know what that does to me?
You know how offensive
that is to me?
What, you stopped the bet?
What do you think, asshole?
You stopped the bet?
- Shut the fuck up!
- Ow!
Congratulations, Arno!
You fucked ourselves
out of $600,000.
- Shit!
- Take his clothes off.
PHIL: Give me your bracelet.
Give me that fucking bracelet.
Give me your fucking bracelet.
- Hey, what's this?
- Give me the fucking shoe.
PHIL:
Hold this motherfucker.
Howard, you did this
to yourself.
PHIL:
Take off your fucking pants.
Take the fucking pants!
[YELLING INDISTINCTLY]
I got to get...
The auction
is next fucking week!
Give me my glasses!
I need my fucking glasses!
Oh! Alright!
Pull up up here.
Come on. Let's go.
Let me explain
something to you, motherfucker.
Monday, I want the money.
Arno gets the money.
Alright?
I'm not fucking around anymore.
- You hear me?
- Get him out of the car!
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
PHIL: Come on, come on.
Let's go.
- Arno! Arno!
- Get in the fucking car!
Alright. Alright. Alright.
Arno, listen to me.
Arno, Arno, Arno!
- Get in the car!
- Take the opal, bro.
PHIL: Don't worry about it.
Get in the car.
No, no, I want the underwear.
No, no!
PHIL: Give me... give me
your fucking underwear.
Give me!
Give me your underwear,
you cocksucker.
Now fucking rot in there.
Fuck you, Arno,
you cocksucking motherfucker!
Help!
Help! Help! Help!
I am fucked.
[PANTING]
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
Please, please, please.
Please pick up.
Pick up the fucking phone,
please.
[RINGING CONTINUES]
- Come on. Come on.
- Howard, where are you?
- Dinah, Dinah...
- Marcel is up on the stage.
- What do you want?
- I... I locked...
I locked my keys
in the trunk of the car.
Can you please, uh,
can you come to the parking lot
and open it for me?
Shit.
[CAR BEEPING]
It's okay.
Thank you.
Okay.
Sorry.
I'll meet you right back inside.
It's all good now.
Let me get dressed.
What could you possibly be
looking for in the forest
dressed in such thin paper rags?
My wicked stepmother
has condemned me to die,
lest I fill this basket with
roses before the coming of dawn.
YOUNG MAN: Besides our cottage
is our magic garden.
It protects the roses
from the snow.
Go now and fill your basket
to your heart's content.
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
Just watch your fucking sister.
It's fine.
Thank you.
YOUNG MAN: We must bestow a gift
upon her.
I know.
Every time she speaks,
gold coins shall spill forth
from her mouth.
This will be our gift!
YOUNG MAN #2:
Quick, he approaches now.
WOMAN #3: This is Danny's part.
He's coming out.
DANNY: Hark!
Who goes there?
WOMAN #3: He did so good.
[AUDIENCE MURMURING]
Wow.
Fuck.
I... Jesus Christ.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
- Hello?
- Hey!
Oh, you picked up, huh?
When I block the call,
you pick up?
When you know it's me,
you don't?
What was that all about?
DEMANY: Nah, I knew
it was you calling.
Actually, that's why
I picked up.
Hey, where's my fucking gem?
DEMANY: Hey, hey,
you need to calm down.
Alright?
Something's happened.
Listen, motherfucker.
I want my fucking property.
- You understand me?
- Hey, watch your mouth!
Alright? You're not dealing
with some broke-ass nigga.
Hey, you fucking put me
on that bus ride home.
You think that was funny?
What the fuck was
that all about?
That fucking bus was disgusting!
DEMANY: What the fuck do you
want me to do, huh?
I go into a locker room
with your silly ass
that makes me look
really fucking suspect.
Where's my gem?
DEMANY: I'm trying to help you
not fuck everything up.
- Where is it?
- Jesus Christ.
- I have it on me right now.
- You have it on you?
DEMANY: Yes, I'm about...
I'm about to be back
- in the city.
- Oh, okay.
You going to this fucking
The Weeknd thing tonight?
DEMANY: I mean, I...
I wasn't planning on it,
but I could.
You could?
No, it's not you could.
You will.
You'll meet me there.
It smells good.
What is it, barbecue chicken?
So I wanted to talk
about the trunk scenario.
No. That was literally the most
awkward thing, like...
Where are you going?
I'm heading into the city,
late-night event,
gonna go...
- Is this the cake?
- ...until 2:00, 3:00,
you never know anymore.
So I'll be exhausted tomorrow.
Yeah, okay, sure.
[MICROWAVE BEEPS]
Good night.
Anyway, I'll finish
the conversation later,
but it was literally so awkward.
Like, were you there?
- Who are you talking to?
- Jessica.
Hi, Jessica.
How good was our girl tonight?
- You can't hear her.
- Okay.
Well, then, just...
just hang up for a second.
Let me talk to you, two secs.
I'll call you back.
What?
So I just...
I was very proud of you tonight.
You were beyond incredible.
Yeah, you told me, like,
five times already.
Well, I just wanted...
You really, really didn't know
how proud I was, okay?
So I really... I just really,
really want you to know.
Okay. Well, I do.
Everything is cool, right?
- What do you mean?
- I don't know.
I just thought I would
check in with you.
Okay.
Make sure everything is good.
- Why wouldn't I be good?
- I don't know.
- I just thought I'd check in.
- Okay.
Well, I literally don't know
what you're talking about, so...
That's right because
I'm an idiot.
So you love me.
Okay?
I'm gonna get into the city,
and I'll see you in the morning.
- Have fun.
- Like I always do.
Anyway, where was I?
You know how I have, like,
a complete resting-bitch face?
So...
♪ I just want to thank God ♪
♪ For all the pretty women
he led into my life ♪
♪ Wealth and health
for my family ♪
♪ And letting me ball
on these niggas ♪
♪ Now it's a lot bad bitches
in the building ♪
♪ Amen ♪
♪ A couple real niggas
in the building ♪
♪ Amen ♪
HOWARD:
I didn't see you out front.
I don't fucking see you
in here now.
I can't believe I'm still
looking for you.
What's that?
Pick up the fucking phone, man!
I don't understand this!
You better fucking be here!
DEEJAY: Hold up! Hold up!
Hold up!
Stop the music!
Stop!
Yo, someone pass
The Weeknd the mic.
THE WEEKND: Where the fuck
is the black light?
DEEJAY:
What's going on back there?
THE WEEKND: No, I asked
for black light.
I'm not performing until
there's fucking black light
- on this fucking stage.
- Who wants the black light?
[CROWD CHANTING "BLACK LIGHT"]
Y'all ain't gonna hear
The Weeknd
until I turn on the black light.
[CROWD CHANTING "BLACK LIGHT"]
My cousin.
♪♪
Alright!
That's what I'm talking about!
THE WEEKND: ♪ From the morning
to the evening ♪
♪ Complaints from the tenants ♪
♪ Got the walls kicking like
they 6 months pregnant ♪
♪ Drinking Alizé with our cereal
for breakfast ♪
♪ Girls calling cabs at dawn ♪
- Hey, hey!
- ♪ Quarter to 7 ♪
- ♪ Sky's getting cold ♪
- Demany!
♪ We're flying from the North ♪
Demany, Demany.
Yo, yo, what's good?
Hey, I want you to meet
my nigga, James.
Oh, yeah, you the guy.
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
Yo, where's that opal?
THE WEEKND: ♪ Gold all in my
chain, nigga, nigga, nigga ♪
- ♪ Gold all in my jet ♪
- I just want that opal.
- Give me the opal.
- Oh, oh.
Alright. You come by the shop
anytime you want.
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
What'd you say? Where is it?
I'm sorry. I don't have it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You don't have it?
- What do you mean?
- KG got it. I don't have it.
KG? What the fuck are you
talking about?
You said on the phone
you had it!
Hey, hey! Man, I don't even
want this shit.
Why the fuck are you here
if you don't have the opal?
The same fucking reason
everybody else here...
to see
The fucking Weeknd perform.
- That is The Weeknd.
- You got a problem with that?
I got a very big problem
with that, man!
- Whoa!
- Hey, hey!
We came here
for one fucking reason.
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
Calm your ass down!
Fuck you think this is?
THE WEEKND:
♪ Girl, put in work ♪
- We good?
- I'm good. I'm good.
THE WEEKND:
♪ Push it to the limit ♪
- ♪ Push it through the pain ♪
- You got fucking greedy, man.
THE WEEKND:
♪ I push it for the pleasure ♪
♪ Like a virgin to the game ♪
♪ A virgin to the money ♪
♪ A virgin to the fame ♪
♪ So this my only chance ♪
♪ And when I'm over only pray ♪
♪ That I flow from the bottom ♪
♪ Closer to the top ♪
♪ The higher that I climb,
the harder I'm gonna drop ♪
♪ These pussy ass niggas trying
to hold on to their credit ♪
- ♪ So I... ♪
- Fuck you.
Yeah, fuck you, man.
DEEJAY: Talk to them.
THE WEEKND:
♪ Why these niggas testing? ♪
♪ Always fucking testing ♪
♪ Shit that I got them
on straight bar hopping ♪
♪ To the music of the ambiance ♪
♪ Get shit popping ♪
♪ Zombies of the night ♪
♪ Niggas ain't talking if
they hyping to the crew ♪
♪ Get it in like ♪
♪ Downtown loving ♪
♪ But when the moon coming ♪
♪ Only place to find... ♪
Sure, sure, sure.
[SNIFFING]
Some on your face.
Yeah, don't look at it.
Is it off?
Mnh-mnh.
What are you doing?
Julia, what are you doing?
No touching.
I want to fuck you so bad.
How bad?
I'll show you.
Mnh-mnh.
- I said, "No touching."
- Feel this shit.
- Here, feel this.
- Oh, my God.
How are you even
this hard right now?
Yo, slow down.
Where you going?
It's, uh, I was already inside.
Listen, I don't remember
seeing you inside.
I'm friends with The Weeknd.
He told me to come
after his set.
Listen. If you're friends
with somebody...
- Hey, Flawless!
- Listen, watch the yelling.
Flawless!
- No screaming over here.
- Yo! Yo!
- Yo, use the phones.
- Tell this guy to let me in!
Come here!
FLAWLESS: The legend is in
the motherfucking building!
HOWARD: Come here!
He's not letting me through!
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Sorry. He's with me.
Yeah. That's my guy.
What's up, sexy?
How we doing?
- Fine.
- Hey, check this out.
You see this Rolls-Royce
that I did,
- the one from Miami?
- Yeah, yeah.
Richie showed me
that Porsche and shit.
Where's Julia?
She in there?
Yeah, she's
back there somewhere.
- With who?
- Do you know what's going on
- with my Michael Jackson pendant?
- What about that?
I really want to...
I need it back.
Yeah, it's in my safe.
I'm coming by tomorrow
to pick it up.
Just help me sell this thing
to The Weeknd.
- You understand?
- Yeah.
Where, where, where's...
Where is she?
You know?
Yeah.
Well, where?
Where, where, where?
I don't mean to get
in your business.
I don't want to get involved,
but I saw her go
the bathroom with The Weeknd.
Julia!
- Oh, shit.
- Julia, are you in there?
THE WEEKND: Yo, I said to hold
the door, bro.
Open up the door!
Shut the fuck up!
- Open up!
- Jesus!
Howard,
we were just doing coke.
- Nothing happened.
- What are you doing?
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
♪♪
♪ First you get a swimming pool
full of liquor ♪
♪ Then you dive in it ♪
♪ Pool full of liquor,
then you dive in it ♪
♪ I wave a few bottles,
then I watch them all flock ♪
♪ All the girls want to play
"Baywatch" ♪
♪ I got a swimming pool
full of liquor ♪
- ♪ And they dive in ♪
- Fuck you!
Fuck that motherfucker
right there!
♪♪
- ♪ Head shot ♪
- I'm sorry, Howard!
- ♪ Sit down ♪
- Fuck you!
- Let's go.
- Get the fuck out!
Yo! You tell that fucking guy
he's sued.
- He's getting sued.
- Howard, Howard, Howard!
And what fucking DJ is
gonna play his shit?
Howard, Howard, Howard.
I know every fucking DJ
in this town.
- Fuck all you losers!
- Howard...
Yeah, you smell like
his fucking cologne!
- We didn't do anything, Howard!
- Yeah, right, right.
- Fuck him.
- Howard?
Watching my fucking...
Get the...
You blew a huge fucking sale
for me!
What were you selling,
your fucking hot snatch?
Oh, my God.
Throw my whole fucking life
away for this skank over here.
Oh, wow!
Okay!
Now I'm a fucking skank?
Where the fuck are you,
you cock?
Listen, Howard!
You knew what the fuck it was
when you met me.
- That's right.
- Okay?
Yeah, that's why I never...
I wish I never fucking met you.
- Right here.
- Oh, wow.
- That's great, Howard.
- Get the fuck...
- Get out of my fucking way.
- Howard. Howard!
Go fuck The Weeknd.
Alright?
We didn't fucking do anything.
Get the fuck off of me.
Go, go, go.
It's fine. Go, go, go.
Good night. Bye.
- Get the fuck away.
- Howard.
- Go!
- Howard. Howard. Howard!
Get out of the fucking car!
Would you get the fuck
out of the fucking way?
Get the fuck out of the way.
Oh, what are you gonna
do, Howard? Huh?
What are you gonna do,
big, tough guy?
That's it.
I didn't fucking
do anything with him.
Get the fuck out of here.
Get the fuck away.
- Go fuck the guy.
- Fuck you, Howard!
I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow, Howard.
- Yeah.
- I'm not seeing you.
Let's go. Go.
Fuck you.
♪♪
What the fuck
are you looking at?
- Oh, oh.
- Nothing much.
Oh, funny, stupid bitch.
That's why you're in line
in the fucking cold.
Yup, bitch.
♪♪
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Howard.
- Listen, Anne, Anne.
- Howard!
I'm looking at it.
I'm looking at the opal.
- You're missing the point.
- I'm looking at it
right now, okay?
It's gorgeous.
ANNE: It is not you who should
be looking at it.
- It's just... I just...
- It's me.
Turn that down.
ANNE: Let me explain something
to you, Mr. Ratner.
Your opal is one of 75 items
I have to go through
for the auction.
All of them but yours
have been cleaned,
cataloged and appraised.
Listen, I'm doing some
appraisals of my own.
- Okay?
- Ugh.
And then I'm gonna
bring it to you today.
ANNE: No. I am on the precipice
of pulling it right now.
I swear to you, please.
Okay?
ANNE:
End of the day or we're done.
I'm getting a call
right now, so...
ANNE: End of the day, Howard,
and I'm serious.
...I have to go.
This is Howard Ratner.
- Hi, Jenna.
- Hi. How are you?
Thank you so much
for calling me back so quickly.
JENNA: That message you left
actually was very disturbing.
No, no.
No, I didn't mean to worry you.
JENNA: Will you mind telling me
what this is about?
I saw online that your boss
represents Kevin Garnett.
JENNA: Oh, I see. I'm gonna have
to put you on hold.
- One moment.
- Okay, sure, sure.
- I'll hang on.
- Howard, Julia is on line one.
No. No. Tell her no.
I'm not here.
Fuck it.
[BEEP, BEEP]
Where are you?
JULIA: Why aren't you
answering your phone?
I asked you a question.
Where are you?
JULIA: I stayed at Kat's house.
Where else do you think?
I couldn't fucking go home
with you acting that way.
No, no.
That's... So let me guess.
- You're not coming to work today?
- I would like to.
That must be nice to come to
work whenever you feel like it.
- Ugh, Howard.
- Is that good?
Is that good? Maybe you should
take a nap then. Take a nap.
JULIA: Can we just please, like,
talk this out like adults?
Get your rest. You need to
remain attractive, right?
JULIA:
You're being a baby right now.
Answer me.
JULIA: I just want to sit down
and talk to you, Howard.
Okay.
JULIA: I don't want to do this
right now.
- I don't want to fight.
- And I just need to work, okay?
I need to work to make sure
that your cheating ass
is taken care of.
WOMAN #4: Selfish Player
Personnel on line two.
- I'm trying to talk to you.
- Goodbye.
This is Howard Ratner.
WOMAN #5: Yeah, my assistant
told me that you called.
How are you doing?
I'm not gonna lie to you.
I could be better.
WOMAN #5: Sorry to hear that.
So what can I do for you?
I've been having a situation
with one
of your higher-profile players,
and I'm moments away right now
from making things
very ugly for you.
WOMAN #5: Right. Okay. Can you
hang on for a second, please?
No. I'm not hanging on.
I happen to be
a litigious individual.
WOMAN #5: Hmm.
And I am a second away
from hanging up right now
and calling my lawyer
and the police.
WOMAN #5: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Do you realize
that I have no idea what you're
talking about, right?
- Howard, KG is here with Demany.
- You talk very fast,
and you're starting to sound
like an asshole,
so maybe you want to back up
and start from the top.
Never mind.
Kevin!
Hey, hey!
- Hey, look at him, smart man.
- Buzz them in.
[DOOR BUZZING]
- Wow.
- Buzz them.
- I am. I am, Howard.
- Buzz the fucking door.
Go to the other buzzer, please.
Hurry up.
DEMANY: I'm trying to get at you
one more time.
HOWARD: Be right there.
Go ahead.
[BUZZING]
It's not working.
Goddamn it.
Hang on. Sorry.
- Open this shit up, man.
- I'm sorry.
DEMANY: We ain't got time
for this shit.
We got a game tonight.
The magnet sometimes
doesn't connect.
- You brought the gem?
- I'm claustrophobic.
- Oh, yeah. I got the gem.
- Okay. Alright. Good.
There it is.
Alright.
I'm gonna go downstairs
and wait.
You can't leave because
that one is locked also.
- We'll wait downstairs, man.
- Get a fucking hammer.
Roman, Roman,
he needs a hammer.
- We'll be right there.
- He needs a hammer.
- Let me get a hammer.
- Alright.
HOWARD: Honestly, it's gonna be
a sec. Move it!
- I don't know if this'll work.
- Give me the hammer.
- I'm on it.
- This usually works.
This'll work.
Give me...
Give me this
and get ready to buzz. Okay?
- Aah!
- Ah, God.
Sorry. Buzz, buzz.
[BUZZING]
That shit loud
as a bitch, man.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Buzz.
Hit it from the side, please.
- Flawless is here.
- Get rid of this motherfucker.
- I'm trying to get...
- Tell him goodbye.
MAN #4: Oh, my God.
Flawless is here?
Goodbye to fucking Flawless!
Roman!
- What?
- Come out here.
Oh, shit.
Listen, we're having
a fucking connection issue.
Just get me some
fucking metal shavings
and the tool fucking kit.
Alright? Goddamn it.
- Open the damn door.
- I'm going to get this open.
HOWARD: I promise you.
This'll work.
Hurry the fuck up, Roman.
Thank you. Thank you.
Hey, yo, Howard!
I'm here to buy the opal.
- It's game day for me!
- I know.
- I know it is.
- What the fuck is going on?
- Listen to me.
- I got $175,000 in here.
$175,000? I told you this thing
is worth over $1 million.
DEMANY: Howard, come on, man.
What the fuck are you doing?
Four courtside seats.
I live in New York.
KEVIN: Come on, nigga.
Nigga, listen.
Listen to him.
Listen.
KG, I want to give it to you for
free. I'm that kind of guy.
Just I'm tied into an auction
right now.
What you talking...
What auction?
The auction... Listen, make a
bid. Make a bid at the auction.
- When is it? When?
- It's Monday.
- Monday.
- Nah, nah.
Let him rent it then
for a couple nights.
- I hold it until Monday.
- I can't.
You'll get it
back Monday night.
Kevin, I hate letting you
down like this.
- Open the fucking door.
- You say no to everything.
- Say yes to something.
- I want to, Kevin.
I fucking love you.
I feel like an asshole.
- Believe me.
- You are!
Come down.
Let me fucking do this.
- Open the door!
- Jesus, fuck. I got this!
God fucking damn it.
I got to do everything.
Please, stop knocking.
It's not gonna help.
Go, go.
[BUZZES]
- Look.
- I'm so Goddamn sorry.
- Jesus Christ!
- I'm so sorry.
Got a door don't work?
- What's going on in here, man?
- Get them some waters.
- Get the cold waters.
- We don't need any water, man.
Go get my ring, man,
so I can get up out of here.
Get him his fucking ring.
He got shit to do.
- Come on.
- The ring.
- My ring.
- The ring, the ring, the ring.
- He's got a game.
- Get him the ring.
- Oh, my God. No!
I left the fucking ring
in Long Island.
KEVIN: Are you joking?
What the fuck do you mean,
you left it in Long...
- Oh, I'll give it to Demany.
- I don't have time for this.
- You'll get it to me!
- No, I'll give it to you.
- No, I need this.
- Listen, I can't do this.
HOWARD: You don't have to do...
I do need...
- I know, but I need the stone.
- Do me a favor.
Do me a favor. Listen.
- You need the stone?
- Yeah, please.
- Where's my ring at, though?
- I'm sorry.
I'll get you the ring.
I'm gonna give it to Demany.
KEVIN: Hey, get my ring for me.
I'll see you later.
- He'll go to Boston with it.
- Howard, this is bullshit, yo.
KEVIN: Hey, open this
fucking door, yo.
HOWARD: Forgive me for being
this fucking...
KEVIN:
Hey, yo, buzz us out, Howard.
HOWARD: We'll buzz you out.
Alright.
- Please, buzz him out.
- This is crazy.
KG, forgive everything I did
and the time I wasted,
and you fucking asshole!
- You fucking did this!
- Yo!
You!
What have you been telling him?
What the fuck are you
talking about, Howard?
Look.
This is how the shit works.
I bring niggas here to you
to buy jewelry.
That's how I get fucking paid.
HOWARD: You have a lot of nerve
talking to me right now...
DEMANY: The fuck are
you talking about?
...after that fiasco
you fucking caused.
The nigga just offered
a quarter of a million dollars
for a fucking rock, dummy.
That's all me.
That's cause of you, huh?
I had nothing to do with it.
DEMANY: That's 20 fucking grand
I'm out.
You spoke to those guys
in Ethiopia, right?
You put all the calls in?
- Yeah, my bad.
- Fuck you, my nigga.
I'm taking all my niggas
somewhere else.
- Where my shit at?
- Get the fuck out.
What the fuck are you doing?
Get out of there.
- Where's my shit?
- Get out of there.
DEMANY: There's only three
fucking watches in here.
- I don't want you in there.
- Where is the rest of my shit?
- Where my watches at?
- I loaned them.
- What you mean you loaned them?
These are fake Rollies,
so what?
- Nigga, it's my shit, nigga.
- They're $200.
Them boxes is mad expensive,
you fucking idiot.
Alright. Well, I owe you then.
Get out of here, I said.
Man, fuck you.
Get the fuck off of me, man.
WOMAN #6: Howard, I have
Dr. Blauman on line one.
- Where the fuck is my shit?
- Go ahead. Go ahead. Hi.
- Howard?
- Hi, Doctor. What's going on?
- Howard.
- Where's the Goddamn paper?
- Please be quiet.
- Is everything okay?
Where's the fucking papers,
Howard?
- Yeah. Shut the fuck up.
- Bitch ass.
- Howard, me?
- Go ahead. I'm sorry.
- Howard, I'm...
- What do I got?
DR. BLAUMAN: ...looking
at the results here
of your colonoscopy, so we're
good. You're all good.
- Everything came back clean.
- Bitch ass motherfucker.
Fuck you and that
Goddamn phone call, nigga.
Doctor, so we're clean 100%?
You said it's good?
DR. BLAUMAN:
Yeah, I said you're all clean.
Oh, good, good. Thank you.
That's a relief.
DR. BLAUMAN:
This is just routine.
You ain't fucking
listening to me, my nigga.
HOWARD: My father fucking died
from it, so of course.
DR. BLAUMAN:
I didn't mean to scare you,
but, you know,
given your family history,
this is something you got
to stay on top of.
I know. I know.
Jews and colon cancer,
what is that?
I thought we were
the chosen people.
DR. BLAUMAN: Colon cancer just
paid for my house in the Hamptons.
HOWARD: Don't tell me that.
Where?
What part of the Hamptons?
- How many acres?
- Whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
You're gonna kill the fish.
What the fuck?
My fish!
- Howard?
- My fish!
- Fuck you, too.
- You fuck! Get a glass.
- Get a glass.
- Fuck them Goddamn fish, nigga.
What the fuck are you doing?
You fucking asshole.
Get a fucking nother glass.
Get another glass.
Goddamn it.
Come here.
I got you, guys.
There you go. There you go.
I got you, sweetheart.
Joanie! Joanie, please get
some more glasses.
ROMAN: Can't see the water.
They're blind.
DR. BLAUMAN: Alright.
Howard, I'm hanging up.
ANNE: I thought I specifically
said 5:30 I am out of the door.
I told you I was coming
to you, and I'm coming to you.
I have the stone.
Don't you dare leave.
- I have a wedding in New York.
- Howard, Howard.
- No!
- Howard, Howard, stop.
You're being fucking
crazy again. Stop.
- Listen.
- Howard.
I got no time to talk.
I have to be to Adley's
in 15 minutes
before they close.
Alright. I'll go with you.
I'll go with you.
HOWARD: Then I got to see
my father-in-law.
Howard, please.
I'm really sick.
I don't feel well.
I got out of bed to come here.
I see you were in a big rush
to come over here, huh?
You got yourself
a fucking smoothie.
- I was in a big rush.
- I want you out.
You motherfucker!
You're out of the apartment
by the end of the day.
- Fuck you.
- Out of my life.
You have no idea.
[HORNS HONKING,
INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
♪♪
How you doing, Howie?
- Alright.
- How's it going?
- Hey, sucker.
- Alright.
Larry, you're a Jew again?
Welcome back.
- I got some diamonds.
- Have a good pay, sir.
It's all right.
Yeah.
♪♪
[SPEAKING HEBREW]
[ALL SPEAKING HEBREW]
Dip the celery.
[CELLPHONE VIBRATES]
NOAH: You know who kind of sucks
a little bit, overrated?
- Alright.
- Chris Paul.
- Come on, man.
AARON: He's all NBA, man.
He can't do it alone.
- He can't do it alone.
- Eddie!
- Please, that's enough!
- You don't know anything.
- What are you saying?
- I'm talking...
- Shut up, everybody!
- Alright. Alright.
- Please.
- Natalie, Natalie, you're up.
NATALIE:
Wait, you skipped my dad.
Where are we?
Howard, why don't you
read the plagues?
Okay.
Ma, you take the Hebrew,
and I'll take the English.
Yes, my dear.
Here we go.
- [SPEAKS HEBREW]
- Blood.
- Frogs.
- [SPEAKS HEBREW]
- Lice.
- Wild animals.
- [SPEAKS HEBREW]
- Pestilence.
- Boils.
- [SPEAKS HEBREW]
- Hail.
- Locusts.
- [SPEAKS HEBREW]
- Darkness.
[SPEAKS HEBREW]
Death of the first born,
hard-core back there.
Huh?
That can still happen if you
don't watch yourselves, kids.
[CELLPHONE RINGS]
JULIA: Hey, it's Julia.
Leave me a message.
- I don't text, so don't text me.
- Excuse me.
You send me something
like that
and then you don't
pick up your phone?
Huh?
You were fucking with me?
I'm trying to have a nice,
peaceful dinner with my family,
which is something
you wouldn't understand
because you don't have one.
You want to play mind games
with me?
Huh?
So whatever you meant
by your little link,
I meant when I said I want you
out of my apartment tonight,
and I want confirmation by text
not a link, via text.
"Howie, I am gone, 10:00 p.m."
Don't you fucking call me.
Arno, what the fuck?
Can we just fucking talk?
We're family.
We're here right now.
- Get out of my way.
- Yeah, you're not so tough
without your friends
around, are you?
Are you?
Fucking pussy.
NOAH: Oh, you like...
You love this roster?
- I love it.
- Baron Davis is done.
NOAH: Start fresh.
Melo, Amari...
- What about Lin?
- That's it.
- We got to bring back Lin.
- Hey, you know why fucking Lin
is not coming back next year?
Because Dolan saw everybody
was so fucking happy.
- They're not gonna ruin that.
- Howard fucking knows.
NOAH: On top of which,
you realize that I met my wife
at the first game
that started Linsanity?
You know what he says
to me, hmm?
He comes over to me.
He says, "Happy holidays,"
like it's Christmas.
It's like having an intruder
in your own home.
- And we'll never live it down.
- He's not bothering anybody.
- Alright? He's trying.
- Yeah, easy for you to say.
- He didn't marry your daughter.
- Shh.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You know Mike, you know,
who sells the vitamins
on Amazon?
- He's got the lisp.
- There he is.
- You good?
- Your guy is a schmuck.
NOAH: Man, KG wouldn't even
dare mess with Amari.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
GOOEY: This is KG, huh?
HOWARD: Oh, three for 11?
- What the fuck?
- Yeah. He looks tortured.
That fucking guy tried
to steal an opal from me.
- Your opal? Your opal came?
- The opal came, yeah.
Stupidly I lent it
to this motherfucker.
No. What do you mean?
He took it?
- He stole it?
- He didn't steal it.
He got carried away.
He thinks it has magic powers
to help him.
- Magic powers?
- Yeah.
- No, really?
- Look.
Look at him tonight without it.
He didn't have it tonight.
Look how fucking bad he played.
He wants to own it, so I
tell him come to the auction,
fucking make a bid
for it like everyone else.
- When is this auction?
- The auction is Monday.
GOOEY: Uh-huh.
So what do you think it's worth?
Well, listen, it's anywhere
from $1,000 to $3,000 a carat,
and it's 600 carats.
GOOEY:
Whoa, that's over $1 million.
- He's rich!
- Whoa.
Not as rich as Gooey,
but working on that.
Who's comparing?
Rich is rich.
I made a crazy risk, a gamble,
and it's about to pay off.
Unh-unh-unh.
Don't look at us.
Don't look at him.
Don't look at me.
Find it yourself.
Come on. Keep looking.
Now warm, warm, warm.
Warmer.
Very warm.
Keep looking.
- I found it!
- Yay!
- That's my boy!
- Woo!
[SPEAKS HEBREW]
Hey, find your stuff.
- We're leaving soon.
- Why not?
Just suck in a little bit,
and it'll fit.
MOTHER: Listen, let's show Dad.
Let's show Dad.
MARCEL: Dad, Dad, look!
This is mom's bat mitzvah dress.
It still fits her.
- Let's show grandpa.
- Ah, that's hysterical.
Hey. It's 9:00.
What do you think?
- Fine.
- Should we get going?
Yeah, let's go tell the boys.
I told them.
What?
You look gorgeous.
Oh, God.
I wanted to talk to you
for a minute and just sit down,
and we don't have to do it here.
We'll wait, but I, I, uh,
I'm having
very serious second thoughts,
and we're all together
right now.
We're all so comfortable.
It's... I... Is it too late?
Should we maybe...
What do you think?
Am I crazy?
- Are you serious right now?
- Yeah.
I know.
I know I fucked up.
- I know it.
- Yeah, you fucked up.
- I have no right...
- You are a fuck-up,
and I'm not having
this conversation.
Listen to me, please.
Stop.
Just stop for one second
and just look at me.
Look in my eyes, and they'll
tell you what I'm feeling.
- Please. Please.
- [SIGHS]
[LAUGHS]
Okay.
What are you thinking?
What? Tell me.
Tell me. I want to know.
- Oh, my God.
- I know. What?
Your face is so stupid.
- Okay.
- Oh, my God.
I'm gonna leave her.
I'll leave her.
I don't need her.
We're done. We're done.
- Okay.
- It's done.
- It was stupid.
- Okay.
- She's trash.
She's trash.
I know that.
It was stupid.
I'm done.
It means nothing, meant nothing.
Please.
I'm begging you.
Just give me another shot.
- You know what, Howard?
- Say yes. What?
I think you are the most
annoying person I have ever met.
I hate being with you.
I hate looking at you,
and if I had my way,
I would never see you again.
That's because you're mad.
You're mad, and it makes sense.
You can punch me if you want.
- Oh, thanks.
- Hey!
I was ready for it.
I don't even want
to touch you.
WOMAN #7: Oh, my God!
- Are you kidding me?
- Look how insane!
Wait, turn around.
I want to see the back.
- Did you see that?
- Oh, my God!
I hate you!
Does that fit you right now?
I'm 15 pounds overweight.
I am.
I'll get the car, okay?
I'll get the car.
- See?
- You look so good.
DEEJAY #2: New York and Long
Island's home of classic rock,
Q106.7, The Rock.
DINAH: She's always...
Like we want to see everything
she's doing at every moment.
- You think she's jealous of me?
- Yeah, she wants your life.
- She wants our house.
- She can have it.
EDDIE: Look at the way
you're playing.
Why are you taking Lex?
Take the tunnel, it's better,
less traffic.
EDDIE: No! Let me focus
and give me the phone!
Plus, I want to grab something
from the apartment,
- and it's right there.
- Oh, go left. Go left.
- Hit the boss!
- I hit him.
We're gonna stop
by the apartment, guys.
EDDIE: Oh, my God.
- Come on, Mom.
- Daddy has got things to do.
- Mom, it's so annoying.
- Some business.
- You died!
- No!
♪ Yeah, we all have a face ♪
♪ That we hide away forever ♪
♪ And we take them out
and show ourselves... ♪
- Hi, Mr. Ratner. How are you?
- How are you?
- Yeah.
- Anything in the trunk?
I'm just gonna be
up and down.
DINAH: Eddie is gonna go
to the bathroom, Howard.
- I got to use the bathroom.
- Go upstairs, honey.
Just hold it in. Alright?
It's 45 minutes
before we're home.
- I can't wait that long.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Eddie, go upstairs
and use the bathroom.
HOWARD: I'm tired.
I want to go to sleep.
You couldn't go at Grandpa's?
You had to wait until now?
Come on. We're going.
We're going.
Goddamn it.
Bathroom is all fucked up
because of construction,
so I asked the neighbor
if you can...
I don't want to use
the neighbor's bathroom.
- I'm taking a shit.
- You ever see the show,
- "Good Times"?
- No.
You're actually going
to like this.
This guy was the father
on the show.
What? I don't care.
I showed it to you.
- He was in "Coming to America."
- He's probably sleeping.
- I bet you he's a old man.
- Who is it?
It's Howard next door.
I live in E.
- Hey, how are you?
- What's up?
Unfortunately, my bathroom
is all fucked up,
and this kid has got to go.
Can we use yours for a minute?
No, sorry.
What a fucking dickhead.
Hey, stop that.
He's a fucking legend.
- Hello?
- Hi.
I'm your neighbor.
- Hey, how you doing?
- How are you?
I'm your neighbor.
I never introduced myself.
- Alan, how are you?
- My bathroom is all fucked up,
and my son needs to...
Can he use yours for a second?
What is it, number one
or number two?
One.
He's gonna go one, one.
Alright? So you go quick.
Alright. In the back.
In the back.
I'll meet you in the hallway.
♪♪
♪ Rain, feel it
on my finger tips ♪
♪ Hear it
on my window pane ♪
♪ Your love's coming down like ♪
- ♪ Rain ♪
- Julia!
♪ Wash away my sorrow ♪
♪ Take away my pain ♪
♪ Your love's coming down
like rain ♪
- ♪ When your lips... ♪
- "Have a nice life.
I hope you find everything
you're looking for."
♪ Could you see my tears ♪
[MUSIC SHUTS OFF]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Yeah.
I'm coming.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Yeah, yeah.
Come on.
Let's go.
Who's the girl living
in your apartment?
- What'd you say?
- Yeah, that guy told me
there's some hot chick
living in your apartment.
Who is that, Mom?
What are you doing talking
to that coke head?
He was talking to me
while I was...
I told you to go in there
and take a shit.
- I did take a shit.
- That was it.
Get on the elevator.
That's enough already.
Don't talk about that.
That ain't right.
♪♪
- Did you get what you needed?
- Yeah.
♪♪
DINAH: Put the recycling
and the garbage out
before you come in the house.
♪♪
Big day.
Magnolia Bakery from
the downtown original.
- Thank you.
- Have you had these yet?
Delicious.
- Thank you.
- You tell everybody here
thank you so much for
everything they've done for me.
RECEPTIONIST:
Alright. Will do.
These are on me,
Howard Ratner, and what's this?
- Is this the catalog for today?
- That's the one.
RECEPTIONIST: If they want
anybody else to come in,
they're gonna have
to be before him.
- It stops right on me.
- Alright. Thank you.
HOWARD:
What the fuck is this?
- This is a mistake.
- It's a correction.
No, it's a correction,
but it's a fucking mistake.
Where's Anne?
I want to speak with her.
I'm sorry.
Anne is in a meeting right now.
No, get her
out of the meeting.
It's an emergency.
I want to speak with her.
Call her on the phone, please.
Thank you.
If you promise to keep
your voice down...
- Yes.
- ...I'm happy to call her.
- Thank you.
- Jesus fucking Christ.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Hello, Anne. I'm down here
with Howard Ratner.
Can you ask her how this
fucking 155 bullshit happened?
Did you hear that?
Mm-hmm. Okay.
What? What is she saying?
I'm afraid that's
your appraisal.
I know that's what it says.
I'm asking who came up
with the fucking figure?
- Oscar in gems.
- Well, Oscar is fucking wrong.
I could go out and get
six appraisers right now,
five of them would say
at least $3,000 a carat.
He's saying he can go
to six appraisers and...
Give me the phone.
Can I speak to her, please?
- Can I speak with her?
- Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna have
to hand you over.
ANNE: No, no.
That won't be necessary.
- I'd rather you didn't.
- Anne.
- Yes.
- This is fucking outrageous.
ANNE: Okay. You need to calm
yourself down, Mr. Ratner.
No, I don't want to be calm.
This appraisal
is a fucking joke.
ANNE: Oscar happens to be
one of our
most experienced gemologists
who we were
extremely lucky to get.
Who clearly knows nothing
about colored stones
and why the fuck
am I hearing about it now?
ANNE:
Do I need to remind you
that you brought the opal to us
on a Friday night
for an auction set
on a Monday morning?
We were lucky to be able
to get it appraised at all.
I don't give a fuck.
I don't care. I don't care.
It needs to be changed.
Do it.
ANNE: That's not an option,
but if you like, we can pull it.
Pull it? No, no.
Not gonna pull it, okay?
Here's what you'll do.
You're gonna make
an announcement at the top
of the auction
that the correction was wrong,
and the original estimate
stands.
ANNE: No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
We are not
correcting a correction.
We can either pull it
or carry on as-is.
- It's entirely up to you.
- Okay. Thank you so much.
Okay, Anne. No. I'm sorry, too.
ANNE: I have bent over
backwards for you, Mr. Ratner.
- We are done here.
- Yes, that'll be perfect.
I'll let her know.
ANNE: Me and my staff had to
work the entire weekend
- to get your piece ready.
- Thank you so much.
Once again, from the bottom
of my heart, I apologize.
ANNE: I'm just happy
I won't ever have to work with
you again.
Okay, I'll tell her. Thank you.
Okay. So she said
that we need to take
the inserts
out of each catalog
before the auction starts,
so you have those.
If you want, I saw a box down
there, and I can start on these.
What is that?
What are you doing?
I just have a question
for Anne.
You don't need to call her.
I just spoke with her.
Oh, it's a separate question.
Don't worry about it.
- Howard!
- Hi, Anne. He's saying
that you told him it was okay
to take out the inserts.
Okay, hey, listen.
Just fuck it.
Put them back in.
I don't give a shit.
- Gooey!
- We're here.
- You're a sight for sore eyes.
- Is he here?
HOWARD: Huh, KG?
- He is... I didn't see him yet.
- Is he here?
I haven't seen him yet.
I got all these things
for him to sign.
Listen to me. Listen.
If you want that,
get it before
the auction starts.
Go to the auction room.
See if he's there.
- Find him in there.
- He's a great guy.
- You'll love him.
- He's excited.
So I want to ask you
a little favor.
- Can I...?
- Yeah, what? What favor?
So I need you
to jack up the bids.
What? No.
I... No.
- Absolutely not.
- Gooey, a little bit.
It's just here
and there, you make a bid.
I just got to ensure
we get it up to $250,000.
- What if I win at $250,000?
- That's easy.
I'll give it right back to you,
but you're not...
- Geez!
- Hey.
This is not really
a nice position
you put me in, you know?
I mean, I resent it...
I know.
You think I want to do this?
- ...very much.
- I fucked up.
I should've got
my own appraisal,
but I didn't have
the time, so...
- How much they appraise it for?
- $200,000.
- $200,000?
- Yeah, but these assholes...
What happened to 1....
They don't have
an opal specialist.
- My guy at the AGL says...
- $200,000?
...500 just based off the
pictures, so listen, 20%,
I'll give you
for the winning bid.
Be a partner with me.
KG is gonna buy it.
It's not a problem.
This guy is obsessed
with the stone.
Today was supposed to be about
Aaron meeting KG.
Mm-hmm, Gooey.
To show support, that's what
today was supposed to be about.
Well, this is support.
This is support like
you've never known.
AUCTIONEER: Sold to you.
Thank you so much, sir.
We move on now, ladies and
gentlemen, to lot number 38.
Lot 38, eh?
We have a sale-room notice.
I'm required to inform you
all that this fine
Ethiopian black opal,
presented here
before you all on your left,
my right, is now offered with
a revised estimate of $155,000
to $225,000 U.S.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is a fine piece,
a collector's work,
and most importantly, it
is windowed on either side
to reveal the full spectrum
of its dazzling color
and the pinfire pattern within.
So with that in mind,
ladies and gentlemen,
my colleagues are ready
and poised on the phones,
and you're all ready
with your paddles.
We shall start the bidding now
at $20,000.
$20,000.
$30,000.
Do I have $40,000?
$40,000, gentleman's bid.
Pleasure to see you, sir.
Thank you, sir.
$40,000 now.
Do I see $50,000?
$50,00 now in a new place.
Thank you, sir.
Pleasure to have you
back, too, sir.
$50,000 now
against you, sir.
Shall we say $60,000?
$60,000 now
against you, sir.
$70,000 now
- 100 grand.
- $100,000 now.
Bid with you, sir, and a great
place, a big, bold,
giant leap for a big, bold,
giant leaper at $100,000 now.
It's not longer yours, sir.
It's against you, sir.
Going to try one more, sir?
I will even break an ink
with you, sir.
Can I urge you to consider
a bid of $105,000, sir?
Come on, sir.
Are you sure?
Positive?
No further?
A defiant nod then.
Looking then for $110,000,
the room.
It's $100,000 now.
Is there any further bidding?
$110,000 now.
Welcome back, sir.
Once again against you, sir.
Shall we try $120,000?
$120,000.
Try one more, sir?
Let's try $130,000?
$130,000 now?
To try $140,000?
$140,000.
Come on, sir.
Let's up it again to $150,000.
Try one more and $150,000.
Now longer yours, sir.
To try $160,000?
$160,000 now.
Back against you again, sir.
Can we try one more
at $170,000?
$170,000 now.
Say $180,000?
Say $180,000, sir?
We agreed on $175,000.
- $180,000 now.
- It's fine.
AUCTIONEER:
Bid back against you, sir.
I'm looking for $190,000.
$190,000 is bid.
Against you, sir, $190,000.
- Confer with your advisor now.
- I am serious.
KEVIN: It's okay.
I need this stone.
Move this up any higher,
any further?
Relax. Relax.
AUCTIONEER: It's a last chance
for you, sir.
- Are you serious?
- I have to move this along.
We have a good bid at $190,000.
I'm looking for $200,000,
sir.
Going to move this up
any higher, any further?
You sure, sir?
Last chance, fair warning.
It's with you, sir, at $190,000,
against the phones,
against the rest of the room.
Sold to you, sir, at $190,000.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, sir, paddle 172.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
- Howard.
- Gooey, I'm so Goddamn sorry.
Shh.
Thank you very much.
I... I'm sorry.
Listen. I...
I'm supposed to be
on 48th street.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- It's 190 grand, Howard.
- Yes, that's temporary.
- It's 190 grand.
That's temporary.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I got to tell you I was going
to stop pressing him
- once we got past $200,000.
- Yeah, yeah.
Did I not tell you
that was gonna happen?
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
- So now what?
I'm sorry. I'll...
So your money is going
to go into my account,
and I'll wire it
right back to you.
Including you owe me 20%.
Absolutely.
It comes right out of my pocket.
That is nearly 38 grand,
Howard.
- I... I know that.
- That's 38 grand.
Okay, so I'm gonna need
a couple weeks on that,
but it'll be done.
I promise you.
Alright. Aaron, let's go.
Come on.
Dad, I got like
six autographs.
- Now.
- Alright.
See you, Gooey.
You got the autographs.
That's great.
- Yeah, great.
- Wasn't Garnett a champ?
- Hey, don't be mad at me, okay.
- Get in. Get in.
Please?
Please don't be mad.
Come on.
Can I get the opal?
- Let me get the opal.
- What for?
- Because I got to sell that.
- Take the fucking opal.
- Yes, all right. Okay, thanks.
- Close the door.
Get them going.
Open the fucking door.
What's he waiting for you for?
Okay, all right.
I know. I know.
I know.
Let him go.
Let him go, and then we'll talk.
- The fuck was that?
- Alright.
I fucked up.
It was a mistake.
Alright? I know it.
I admit it.
I got to... got to just...
Let's hit pause
for one fucking second.
Got to call Kevin because I know
he fucking wants it,
and you saw
he's got the $175,000.
And then everything
will be copacetic.
Alright?
KG, it's me.
I got great news for you.
I...
Hello?
No one on the fucking phone.
I... If you just give me
two fucking...
Shut the fuck up.
You're lucky there's people
around here, you prick.
Come on. Get out of here.
Let's go.
Hey, fucking...
[GAGGING]
[CLEARING THROAT]
[HOARSELY] Hey.
Hey.
[NORMAL VOICE]
Arno, Arno.
Just listen to me, please.
I spoke...
I spoke to Demany.
Remember Demany?
He's a business friend of mine.
He gave me the fucking number.
That's enough, Howard.
It's fucking enough.
Why are you being
so thick-headed and...
Fuck you, man.
Suck my dick.
Throw him in the fucking water.
♪♪
Where the fuck
are my glasses?
Fuck. Where are they?
♪♪
[DOOR UNLOCKS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Got the Versace for how...
I don't know if this is
a $400 value.
Maybe $250.
- Howard!
- Forget about Howard.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS
CONTINUE]
♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[INTERCOM BEEPS,
TELEPHONE BUZZES]
- Howard, Joseph...
- I'm not feeling good.
- Are you okay? What's wrong?
- I don't want to work.
Send everybody home.
WOMAN #8: Alright, sweetie.
[HORNS HONKING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Hey.
Sorry to bother you.
What is it?
I just wanted to see
how the auction went.
Terrible.
I don't...
I don't want to talk about it.
Okay, well, Damien and Joseph
brought this amazing sweatsuit
that I think would look
so nice on you.
Do you want to see it?
Just leave me alone, please?
Come on, Howard.
Don't... Don't look at me.
Oh, my God, Howard.
- Don't look at me.
- What the fuck happened to you?
Don't look at me, please.
[CRYING]
I don't know what I'm thinking.
I don't know what
everybody is...
It's not ever going right.
JULIA: I know. I know.
I'm so sad.
I'm so fucked up.
Hey, I'm really upset, too.
I'm sorry if this has anything
to do with me,
but I swear I really
didn't do anything.
I wish you were nicer
to me though.
It was not nice
what you did to me.
I try, but it's really hard.
I don't know what to do.
I don't have any place to go.
I don't have anywhere
to get better.
But you do, like, really,
Howard?
You're my home.
You could come to me.
I can't figure it out.
I can't figure out
what I'm supposed to do.
Everything I do,
it's not going right.
it's not going right,
and I don't know what to do.
I really don't, and I want
anymore of this shit.
I really don't.
I got to figure this out.
I really do.
Well, I got something
if you want,
but you can't make fun of me.
What?
My God, it's so stupid,
but I don't know.
I got it.
I thought it would make you
feel better.
Look.
Unzip my skirt.
Not like that,
just unzip my skirt.
It says "Howie."
What did you do?
Why would you...
- You don't like it?
- No, I do. I'm not worth it.
- Yes, you are.
- I'm not worth it.
- You are worth it.
- I don't...
- Look, Howie.
- You... I don't deserve this.
I'm so crazy about you.
Yes, you do.
- I love you.
- No, no.
- Yeah.
- You're gonna...
you can't even
get buried with me now.
Oh, it's okay.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Oh, this fucking guy.
Do not let him in.
Understand me?
Just ignore him.
Ignore him, Joey.
[SNIFFLES]
Ah, here.
Let's get you cleaned up.
It's not broken, right?
You don't think it's broken,
right?
- I don't know.
- This is crazy.
You can't be out here
looking like this.
Oh.
[CELLPHONE RINGS]
Can you answer that?
- Hello?
- Oh, hi.
This is Liz.
I work with Kevin.
I'm actually looking for Howard.
- This is Howard.
- Hi, yes.
I got your message from Demany
about the gem.
We're at the bank right now.
- Did... So does he want it?
- Yes, yes.
Kevin is still interested.
We could actually be...
It's like we discussed, right?
- It's still $175,000, right?
- Yes.
- In cash?
- Yes, in cash.
Like I said.
We're at the bank right now.
- You tell him we're at the bank?
- Kevin, yes. I told him.
- Howard, Howard...
- Okay, okay.
LIZ: I got to go. I'll see you
soon. Bye-bye.
See? I told you.
Arno, listen.
No bullshit.
Kevin Garnett
is coming to my office right now
with $175,000 cash.
Alright?
You said I got till Monday?
Today is still Monday,
so I don't know
if you're hearing this.
But, Arno, this is real.
Kevin is really on the way.
He was just at the bank.
Come get your money, buddy.
- I need the Celtic ring back.
- What happened to Friday?
- I know. I know.
- It's Monday, Howie.
- I know what we said.
- What did we say?
But it was a short
week, Pesach.
What happened to your face?
- Car accident, okay?
- What do you need?
So, listen to me.
I need the Celtic ring.
I'm gonna give you
the Knicks ring.
Alright?
You know what that means to me.
Swap them out, please.
You've had this Knicks
ring forever.
I just need
the Celtic ring back.
- Alright?
- No, no.
HOWARD: What do you want to do?
What do you want to do?
I own that ring right now.
HOWARD: No, I know you do,
and I'm gonna...
So I'll swap you the two rings,
but I'm gonna put
a 15% VIG on this one.
And if you're not here
by Friday,
it's gonna be
the same thing all over again.
You're gonna have
a third ring.
You're not gonna have to worry
about that. Make it a 16%.
I'm sorry I fucked you,
but I have...
Bubbie, what's going on?
You okay?
It's... I'm very good.
Everything is going good.
- Yeah?
- I promise you.
I promise you.
Hey, there he is.
KG, don't you got
a game tonight?
[LAUGHS]
I got your chip right here.
Alright?
Game night.
- We've really got to go.
- You must be Liz.
LIZ:
Can we make this quick?
HOWARD: Yeah, we're gonna make
it quick. Absolutely.
Julia, let's get these guys
some Powerades.
Powerades?
Water? Anything else?
KEVIN: It's fine. I'm okay.
It's okay. Yeah, I'm good.
You like it cold.
You know that.
Howie, let me get a second
with you, okay?
HOWARD:
Yeah, sure, sure. Alright.
Kevin, you need to be
wheels-up at 8:00.
I got it.
Give me two seconds.
LIZ: Kevin, we need to be there
in less than 1 hour.
Let me holler at you, man.
What the fuck is going on, man?
Ever since I met you, man,
you've been giving me
the run-around
with everything, man.
What do you mean?
And I feel like you're fucking
with my emotions.
You just playing with me
at some point.
This hasn't been straight
since I came here.
- You understand?
- Why you saying that?
I borrowed the opal.
It's just one thing, you know?
I come back over here.
I brought it back.
Howard, I brought it back.
I didn't have to bring it back.
You know, I show up
at the auction.
You had somebody bid against me?
All these fucking games,
like...
What the fuck
are you doing, man?
Like, you don't know...
You don't think I know this?
You don't think
I know none of this?
HOWARD: It's complicated, KG.
You see this face?
You see this?
Man, there's $165,000
right here cash.
I'm showing you because
it's... it wasn't easy, man.
6% goes to Demany.
I've already taken it out.
Alright. I guess.
I guess that's fair.
Let me get the fucking opal,
man.
Let me get the fuck
up out of here.
This opal, this opal
is very valuable for you.
- Absolutely.
- Okay? I did that.
Let me get the fuck
out of this...
I respect you. I respect your
passion. Okay?
I always have.
I thought you was
a fan, too, man.
- I'm a fucking huge fan.
- What did you pay for this?
Real shit, what did you pay
for this right here?
That's not a fair question,
Kevin. Alright?
This... We're talking months
and months of fucking my time.
I'm not gonna take
the money back
when I did the deal now.
I'm just saying.
Straight up, straight up me
and you, mano a mano,
[DOORBELL RINGS]
how much did you pay for this?
Fucking what'd I pay?
I paid a... that's...
this is... that's...
I'm telling you.
If I answer that question,
it's very misleading.
- Why?
- It's...
I paid 100 grand, okay?
- So you doubled your money?
- I'm the joke here.
Alright?
I got fucked.
A million dollars is what
I was supposed to get.
I get a fucking what?
Made 65 G's?
You gave some niggas
from Ethiopia 100 grand
for something you thought
was worth $1 million.
You don't see nothing wrong
with that, Howard?
Ethiopian miners?
You know what these
fucking guys make?
100 grand is 50 lifetimes
for these fucking guys.
A million dollars is more
is my point.
- You understand?
- Well, do you want to win
by one point
or fucking 30 points, KG?
Right? I see you out there
when the fucking stadium
is all booing you.
You're 30 up.
You're still going full-tilt.
Let's see what Vegas...
What does Vegas
got you guys at today?
Take a look.
- Let's see.
- Are you serious?
You gonna pull this up
right here?
HOWARD: Look at this shit.
The Sixers are supposed to win
the game tonight they think.
I don't keep track of none
of that shit.
They think on game seven,
you're not gonna
get fucking 18 points.
They don't think you're going
to get eight rebounds?
These guys don't know
shit about ball.
What the fuck are they doing?
Doesn't that make you want
to fucking kill them?
Doesn't that make you want to
say, "Fuck you for doubting me"?
Doesn't that make you want
to step on fucking
Elton Brand's fucking neck?
Come on, KG.
This is no different than that.
This is me.
Alright?
I'm not a fucking athlete.
This is my fucking way.
This is how I win.
Alright?
All the fucking hard work I do,
all the fucking ass kicking
and the dues I pay?
You're not gonna score
on the big one on game seven?
Fuck these people, right?
That's how you feel.
I know you do, so look.
Let's fucking bet on this.
Let's bet on this shit.
I'm fucking gonna bet all
this money on you tonight, KG.
You're here to win, KG.
These fuckers don't know.
Them out fucking west?
Do you think
they fucking know you?
They don't know you.
They don't know us.
It's about fucking winning.
It's about you, and I saw
your fucking conviction,
your fucking honesty
and your fucking magic.
KEVIN: Howie, you're talking
crazy, man.
Listen.
You even understand
how fucking great of a game
you're gonna have tonight?
- I know it.
- Listen.
We're a team tonight, KG.
This is a fucking lock.
It's a fucking feeling.
We both have it.
They don't know.
You and I know.
- Alright?
- Nice fucking trim.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
♪♪
JULIA: Hey, do you mind
watching the space
while I run to the bathroom?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Can I leave you guys
alone in here?
- Go ahead and do your business.
- Do you want company?
I don't think so,
but next time maybe.
[DOOR BUZZES]
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm looking for Howard.
I don't know where he is.
I'm sorry. We're closed.
He gave me
a fucking fake Rolex.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm not getting suckered.
Sir, please calm down. I don't
know anything about that.
Well, let me talk to you
about this.
You got to help me.
This is gonna be one
of the best nights
of our fucking lives.
Howard. Howard?
♪♪
Come on. Come on.
Where are you?
Howard, what the fuck
is going on?
- Take this.
- What is this?
I need you to listen
to me carefully.
I booked you on a blade, okay?
You're gonna land on top
of the Mohegan Sun.
- Okay?
- There's a bet in that bag.
I want you to take all of it,
all of it inside the bag,
and place it on that bet.
- How much is in the bag?
- There's a lot.
I don't want you
to think about that. Alright?
I don't even want you to look
at it until you get there
and you take it out
and give it to the teller.
- You understand me?
- Okay, okay. I got it. I got it.
I'm gonna fuck the living
shit out of you tonight.
- You know that?
- I wish I could kiss you.
Alright. You got to go.
You get going.
Alright. Love you. Bye.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
♪♪
[DOOR BUZZES]
Alright.
Let's get this over with.
Arno, you're never going
to believe this shit.
Believe what?
We're about to hit
so Goddamn big.
KG was just here.
You saw him, right?
I gave him the gem.
He's gonna fuck up
the moneyline so bad tonight.
Howard, where's
the money right now?
It's on the way right now.
- It's on the way to the casino.
- What?
What the fuck are you talking
about, Howard?
- The fuck is going on in there?
- Where is that girl?
The girl that went
to the bathroom.
I ain't seen her.
She didn't get back here?
- No.
- What are you not getting?
No, no, no, no.
It's in this room right now.
Go get her now.
Bring her back.
- Hey, hands up.
- Open the fucking door.
- Hit the button.
- For what?
What am I opening the door for?
Somebody fucking just
buzz me out.
ROMAN: I got it. I got it.
HOWARD: What are they doing?
- I got this. I got this.
- You're saying what?
Take your hands off me.
- What are you talking about?
- What the fuck are we doing?
It's gonna make sense
in about 2 fucking minutes.
You're gonna listen to what...
I'm listening to you.
You're gonna do
what I tell you to do.
Listen, you fucking goon.
I'm telling you
something good right now.
Alright. Listen to me.
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
Shut the fuck up.
Hey! Come on. Come on.
Come on.
No, no, no!
[SCREAMING]
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
We're gonna let him go.
- You gonna call her?
- I'll call. I'll call for you.
Are you gonna get
that bitch down here now?
I promise.
Alright. Come on. Come on.
Get him up.
Listen.
Listen to me.
Get yourself together.
Alright?
I want you to make that call.
Come here.
Give me a fucking second,
please.
You got plenty of time
after you make the call.
- My heart.
- Call this girl up.
I want her back here now.
[COMPUTER CHIMES]
She's at Mohegan Sun.
PHIL:
Yeah. Here, come on. Let's go.
Put it on speaker.
[DIAL TONE]
[DIALING]
There we go.
[DIALING CONTINUES]
This motherfucker...
Come on. Come on.
- I can't. I'm sorry.
- Oh, fucking my God.
- Unbelievable.
- I'm sorry.
I really am.
I am sorry.
Man, fuck this.
You're a moron.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
PHIL: It's not worth it, man.
Put that shit away.
- What are you doing?
- Come on. Buzz us out.
What are you doing? Why am I
buzzing you? Why are you going?
- Just buzz me the fuck out.
- But... but...
but just watch
the fucking game...
Buzz me the fuck out.
...and you'll be happy
with the results.
I'm telling you now before
I put your head
- through the fucking glass.
- Alright. Alright.
I'll buzz you out.
Alright?
[DOOR BUZZES]
Fucking...
I told you I told him.
Close it.
Come on.
Buzz me out.
What are you doing?
Open this fucking door.
Come on.
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
ARNO: Howard, open the door.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
I'm sorry.
- I'm not buzzing you out.
- Just listen to me.
Arno, Arno, the Sixers
shouldn't even be there.
- You understand?
- No, no, no.
She's at the Mohegan Sun
sports bar.
PHIL: Mohegan Sun sports bar.
- This is at game seven.
- Get over there now.
But you know what she fucking
looks like. Go find her.
They're gonna get
to the Garden in full.
You fucking under...
- Howard, open the door.
- I know you're upset, Arno.
Of course I'm upset.
I'm trying to fucking make
this all work for you.
MAN #3: Open the fucking door.
The NBA doesn't want
the Sixers to win.
They got fucking...
There's no money in that.
You understand?
The refs know that.
They want stars.
Buzz us the fuck out of here,
Howard.
- Stars get a buck laid.
- Right now.
- Open the fucking door.
- Open it now.
Hey, hey, hey.
This is fucking bulletproof.
You're only gonna hurt yourself.
That doesn't work.
- Phil, Phil, Phil.
- Arno, I'd duck.
You're gonna get killed.
Listen to me.
- You motherfucker.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
I'm talking to Arno.
Enough of you, enough.
You got to open
this fucking door.
- Listen to me.
- I got something.
Do you realize all you got
to do is get the opening tip.
Fucking buzz
that fucking thing open.
We're gonna get...
You know how many rebounds
this guy is gonna get, Arno?
Who is that?
Who are you talking to?
Who'd you call?
Who did you call?
MAN #3:
Open the fucking door, dick.
♪♪
[DIALING]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
PHIL: He got us locked in.
Yeah, it's me.
ConEd called the office.
- There's a fucking leak.
- What leak?
There's a gas leak on Pinoak.
DINAH: Well, for crying
out loud, Howard.
So they're evacuating
the whole block.
- Just slow down, okay?
- So get the kids out of there.
- You're not making any sense.
- You and the kids go to Amy's.
DINAH: Well, why would they call
the office and not the...
HOWARD: I don't know
why they called me. Alright?
DINAH: You are not making any
sense, Howard.
I'm not here to argue
with you, Dinah.
Get the kids out of the house.
I'm frightened, okay?
- You're freaking me out.
- Just get out.
Go to Amy's, and do not
leave there until I get home.
DINAH: Oh, my God.
You promise me?
Stay at her house, okay?
DINAH: Okay, but you'll
meet us there?
PHIL: Let me tell you
something, prick.
Thank you.
Open the fucking door.
MAN #5: Last year
I made $125 million.
I don't even know what to do
with my money anymore.
I have nobody to spend it with,
nobody to enjoy my life
with anymore.
It's horrible.
Today is a big day for me.
I met you. You're hot.
You want to have a drink
when we get there?
♪♪
Hi.
Hey, okay, so I'm betting
on the Celtics,
parlay, three-way, money...
I don't know.
Plus tip? Here, you just...
So you want a parlay,
three-way...
Make sure that when
you put it in,
it's exactly that, okay?
I will.
How much you want on it?
Okay. I'm not really sure.
You're just gonna have to.
Oh, okay. Chad?
Okay, just give me a minute.
I just have to have
my supervisor count this, okay?
Okay.
- Almost there.
- One second.
♪♪
Come on.
Let's go.
Feeling this?
Feeling this.
Beautiful.
ANNOUNCER: Number 5...
HOWARD: This is it, boys.
This is it.
[CELLPHONE RINGS]
Go ahead.
Tell me.
Okay. Listen.
Listen. Listen.
Say... say it.
Say the whole ticket out loud.
I want you to say
it really loud.
Give me a second.
I want some people to hear it.
Alright?
Hang on.
Hang on. Say the whole ticket.
Go ahead.
JULIA: I put $155
on the three-way bet.
Garnett's points
plus his rebounds
with the Celtics moneyline
with the Celtics
to win the opening tip.
HOWARD: Right.
Just read the whole ticket.
JULIA:
Okay. So it says here...
- You having a good time?
- Yes.
JULIA: ...to win $1,225,000...
Did you fucking hear
that number?
That's enough.
You don't have to say anymore.
The bet is in.
- The bet is in, okay?
- Fuck you.
I'm taking you to the fucking
Ritz Carlton, the Grand Cayman.
Alright?
With the fucking Jacuzzi.
JULIA: I'm here for it.
Alright.
Rub that tattoo for me.
JULIA: Okay, I love you.
Okay, here we go.
We grab this tip,
and we're in business, boys.
Alright?
Pound that chest, baby.
This is it.
We got to get this.
This is right out the gate.
Right out the gate.
Come on.
Come on, man.
Get that tip.
Let's go.
Get that fucking tip.
Get that tip.
[ANNOUNCER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY]
Get that!!
Yes, yes!
Fuck, we would have been fucked
if he didn't get that.
That was the fucking biggest
part of the whole
Goddamn parlay right there.
That was huge.
I knew he was gonna win that.
Alright.
That's it.
What?
One rebound.
Go, that's one.
That's fucking one.
Look at that.
Right out the fucking gate,
the man.
The man's feeling this.
Yep.
Go. Get it. Get it.
ANNOUNCER: Garnett down low...
HOWARD: Go, go. Finish it.
Finish it.
Hey, yes.
Alright.
That's fucking it.
That's the first shot
of the game.
He fucking hit it.
That's three now.
Two plus that fucking rebound.
That's three out of 26.
Okay, I bet on, um,
I bet on the Celtics,
specifically Kevin Garnett.
Okay. Two good bets...
Celtics are winning and Garnett
has got nine and seven,
so that's 16 right now on your
way to 26, he said, right?
MAN #5: Oh, my God.
The gorgeous one is here.
- Not even halftime yet?
- Hey, twice in one day.
I can't believe it.
How are you?
From the helicopter to here.
How you doing, baby?
I can't get you out of my mind.
- I mean...
- You're funny.
MAN #5: Oh, you're hot, baby.
You're definitely hot.
So what?
You got money on the Celtics?
- Let me see there.
- Is he gonna shoot?
- Is that...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
MAN #6: Come on, Garnett.
That one's gonna help.
MAN #5: Aw, come on, man.
I mean...
Oh, my God.
He missed his shot.
Who cares?
I have a great idea,
not for him.
What's that?
I'd like you to come up
to my room. I hired the chef.
I'm in Penthouse "A,"
and it's gorgeous. Best views.
I mean, who could ask
for more than that.
- Thank you.
- I love you, baby.
- Alright.
- I'll see you there.
- Okay.
- Penthouse "A," the Penny Royal.
- Yes, got it.
- Okay, baby? Nice.
JULIA: Okay, bye.
- Wow.
- Fucking...
MAN #6: He's like a cartoon.
- Oh, my God.
- What happened?
I got to go.
What's going on? You need help?
Thank you so much
for your help.
♪♪
[COINS JINGLING]
This is the beauty of betting.
This is the beauty of betting,
you know?
I'm fucking pulling
for the Celtics.
I'm a Knicks fan.
If the fucking 12-year-old
version of me saw me right now,
he'd be like, "What the fuck?"
Everybody is talking about
this fucking big bet here,
so it's got to be her.
He's with me.
We're gonna fucking flat her
and bring her back, boss.
Boss. Absolutely.
COACH: I need everyone in here
to lock in.
KG. Look at KG.
Remember this.
If you want to go quickly,
do it alone,
but if you want to go far,
you do it together.
We're like roaches,
and you can't kill us.
Quit fucking passing.
Get it to him.
And another.
And shoot.
Shoot.
Fuck that shit!
Fucking Doc!
Fucking threw his rhythm off.
He took him out of the game.
Fuck, man.
That's your fault.
You see that other guy though,
Phil?
One of your boys from Boston?
You got some boys in Boston?
You'll see what I'm talking...
Hang on.
This fucker?
Is that one of your boys,
that fat fuck?
Looks like you.
Look like one of your boys.
That's a fucking rebound.
That's it.
Three more. Three more.
Way to go.
What did it say up there?
What is the score?
- Are they winning?
- They're winning.
- Another rebound.
- Winning by three points.
Fuck that shit.
He fucking fouled him.
Doesn't matter.
He grabbed it.
He had it.
That counts as one.
Now what are we at?
23?
Alright.
Last possession, let's go.
Pick it up.
Alright. That's it.
That's it.
Shoot.
Come on.
Shoot it.
Aah!
Oh!
Holy fuck, yeah.
That fucking guard.
Just fucking...
That's all the jam.
It's all the jam.
That's... We're at 25 now.
One more.
One more fucking point.
Either a rebound
or a fucking basket.
Anything.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Either one, we fucking got this.
All right.
One more. Just need one more.
- Oh, my God.
- JULIA: Hi.
Come on in.
- Three times in one day?
- JULIA: I know.
- I mean, unbelievable.
- I know.
And I-I-I can't believe
it's you.
- Where's your boyfriend?
- Why don't...
- Why don't we watch the game?
- Oh, yeah, yeah,
without a doubt.
Go ahead, honey. Sit down.
- Make yourself comfortable.
- JULIA: Okay, how do I...
Where's the remote
What do I do?
- Uh, the iPad's over there.
- JULIA: Okay.
Do what you got to do
with the iPad.
Look. I got to take a shower,
okay?
I really got to take a shower.
I got to clean up, okay?
I got to get myself washed.
That plane ride, it got me all
messed up and everything else.
So what I want you to do...
If that doorbell rings, okay,
I got my friends, okay,
coming in,
or I got the food coming,
okay?
- You just answer it, okay?
- Okay.
WAYNE: And let them know.
Okay, baby?
- All right.
- WAYNE: Please.
♪♪
Garnett.
HOWARD: Hey, that's it!
That's it!
Thank you.
[SMOOCHES]
That's it.
Okay, that's two problem,
that's done.
We've got that... two.
Just got to win now.
Celts got to win it
with a fucking dunk.
We're done, Arno.
[CLAPPING]
- [DOORBELL RINGS]
- What do you got?
What's the score, baby?
68-73, Boston.
WAYNE: 68 what in the fourth?
ANNOUNCER:
...daring Rondo to shoot.
WAYNE: You want to call down?
Just cancel the fucking food.
I want to go out.
Baby, I love that
you're into this game.
[AUDIENCE CHANTING "DEFENSE"]
[ANNOUNCER SPEAKS
INDISTINCTLY]
Trying to get rid
of Brandon Bass.
Tries it again.
Up and under.
Shot misses.
The rebound.
Push it.
Pus... Push it!
Push it. Go.
Get it fucking home.
Get it.
Get it to him. Yeah.
Oh, don't fucking miss that.
Don't miss that.
That's all right.
It's all right.
K.G.'s gonna get
this fucking shot.
Let's ice this shit.
Sink this shot.
Sink it. Sink it.
Come on. Feel it.
Feel it. Feel it.
Feel it.
Come on.
He's got the jam.
Feel that fucking jam.
With 15 of 16 from the line,
again, we've only taken
four here in the second half.
Come on. Come on.
It's all right. It's all right.
All right.
We're up enough.
This is not that big of a deal.
This will just fucking
help seal it, but we're good.
Don't talk.
Just fucking do your shit, man.
Do your shit.
Do you shit.
Get this shit.
Come on.
...Celtics led by 3.
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
All right,
The Truth fucking feels it.
I feel it.
I'm confident now.
I'm confident.
Don't let him shoot that.
Get that. Man, that's it.
Yeah, yeah!
Oh! Oh, my God!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Ha ha.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
Holy fucking shit.
Oh, my God.
Howard, did we just win?
Oh, my fucking God!
Are you kidding me?!
Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
Oh, my God, baby.
I love you.
I love you. I love you.
I love... I love you.
I... Oh!
Oh, my God!
[POUNDING]
- He fucking did it.
- I did it!
- All right.
- Fuck.
- You always believed.
- You fucking did it.
- Yeah, I know.
I know.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
No, you, you, you.
I love you.
I'm so happy.
I'm fucking...
It's going down.
- It's going down.
- MAN: You're going too far, man.
- You won.
- Oh, I know.
- Thanks so much.
- You made your point.
- Let's go.
- All righty.
- You made your mark.
- HOWARD: Hey, hey, listen.
Hi. Yes.
- Just cash it in, okay?
- You guys happy now?
HOWARD: And make sure they
fucking walk him to the car.
And they're gonna... All right?
I'm gonna book you a Blade.
- ARNO: Howard.
- HOWARD: All right.
I'll call you back.
[BUZZER]
ARNO: Son of a bitch.
I can't fucking believe it.
[GUNSHOT]
[THUD]
ARNO:
What the fuck did you just do?!
What the fuck?
PHIL: Shut up!
- Get me the bags now.
- What did you just do?
I'm not gonna take it.
You... You...
Hey, get off me!
Shut the fuck up,
or you'll wind up next to him.
You hear me?
Don't fucking confuse me.
- Get away from me.
- Fuck you.
ARNO: Take your hands off
of me right now.
PHIL: Right now. Go ahead.
Go ahead.
[DOOR OPENS]
Do it. What were you gonna say?
Do it.
Do it! Do it!
I want out of here.
Let me out of here.
Let me out.
PHIL: Go get the...
Go get the bags now.
I'll fix this.
Get over here.
Stay right there.
Stay right fucking there.
Come on! Let's go!
MAN #3: Fuck.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
[DOOR RATTLING]
Get over here!
[GUNSHOT]
♪♪
Fuck this.
WOMAN #9:
...to the conference final.
How are you feeling?
When you win, that's
all that matters. You know?
The big "be quiet,"
the big "shut up," you know?
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
Ah, motherfucking money,
right?
And a personal one to you, bro.
WOMAN #9: ...celebrate your
36th birthday...
That's some strong shit.
Oh, that's my nigga
right there, boy.
Look at that motherfucker, baby.
Whoo. I know that man.
I know that man.
My dad's good with him.
- You...
- Hey!
Amy, he was naked and drunk,
okay?
I'm calling the police.
All the dues and everything
that I put into this,
you didn't think that
I would show up to game seven?
Clearly that's a joke.
WOMAN #9: He goes to the bench.
Did you feel that you needed
to shoulder...
- It's all there.
- Thank you, thank you.
[KEVIN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
KEVIN:
He does a lot for our team.
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
So I thought we all shared
that responsibility
and did a good job, you know,
but in the end,
I felt like it was just me
and the rock, nothing else.
WOMAN #9:
Is this the end of...
KEVIN:
No, I wouldn't say that.
I think we have a lot more
in our tank.
to prove...
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Oh, my God.
- Wayne, thank you so much.
- WAYNE: Ah, baby.
- My pleasure.
- Thank you.
- A lot of money. Listen.
- Oh, I know.
I want you to come
to the Avalon.
- Have one drink.
- No, I can't, I can't.
- I don't want to twist your arm.
- I got to go, baby.
- Come on.
- I got to go. I got to go.
- Just have one drink.
- We can go now.
♪♪
MAN #3: Go, go! Come on!
All right, go, go!
Go, go!
PHIL: Okay, I got it.
I got it.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
MAN #3: Nico, I can't find
the cabinet.
And make sure you get
all those electronics.
Everything that videotapes.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
♪♪
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYS]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ I still believe in your love ♪
♪ I just don't care
what you've done in your life ♪
♪ Baby, I'll always be here
by your side ♪
♪ Don't leave me waiting
too long ♪
♪ Please come back ♪
♪ I, I ♪
♪ I still believe in your eyes ♪
♪ There is no choice ♪
♪ I belong to your life ♪
♪ Because I-I'm meant
to love you someday ♪
♪ You'll be my baby ♪
♪ And we'll fly away ♪
♪ And I'll fly with you ♪
♪ I'll fly with you ♪
♪♪
♪ Every day and every night ♪
♪ I always dream
that you are by my side ♪
♪ Oh, baby, every day
and every night ♪
♪ Well, listen ♪
♪ Everything's gonna be
all right ♪
♪ And I'll fly with you ♪
♪ I'll fly with you ♪
♪♪
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS]