(♪♪♪)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
(♪♪♪)
(Puffing smoke)
(Sighs)
(♪♪♪)
(Birds chirping in distance)
(Cows mooing)
(♪♪♪)
(Birds chirping)
(Cows mooing)
(Dog barking)
Is that Marsha's sister?
What do we call her?
Aunt Jean.
She looks nicer than Marsha.
LIBBY:
She does.
Hey.
- Hi Libby.
- Hi.
Thank you so much for having us.
Oh, you're always welcome here.
Thanks.
- Oh.
- Who are these two beauties?
Well, um, this little one
is Tank
and this big one is Abby.
Hello, nice to meet you both.
Are those wands you have there?
Why don't you go over there
and try to turn that goat
into a goose?
- Might work.
- It's okay.
Go ahead.
Just be careful.
Goats don't bite, do they?
Course they do, they're goats.
(Both laugh)
Watch your fingers!
(Goat bleating)
It's so soft.
Wow.
JEAN: That's one of
my favourite pieces.
Frank always thought of himself
as an artist
and I guess I did, too.
He made that.
Yeah.
Who's Frank?
Frank was my husband.
Although we never married.
He passed 10 years ago.
Oh, I'm sorry.
He did that one up there, too.
Oh wow, that's um,
it's very um, rustic.
You done?
Frank was a fan of imperfection.
Yeah, I can tell.
Hey, are you full?
Aunt Jean,
where is your dishwasher?
You're looking at it, kiddo.
ABBY:
You don't have a dishwasher?
No dishwasher, no clothes dryer,
no microwave.
- TV?
- No, no TV.
Well, um, I hope you have
a bathtub,
'cause it's time for these two
to get ready for bed.
No, why don't you do the dishes
and I'll take them up.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Uh, I... we just have our l...
we have a routine.
It's fine.
Come on.
Okay.
Hey.
(Kisses)
You guys be good.
JEAN: The dish soap is where
you might expect it to be.
Okay.
(♪♪♪)
(Sighs)
Cool scar.
I got it in the car crash
with my dad.
Here, this one's my favourite.
It looks like a crescent moon.
Mine looks like a river.
Yes, they mighty Mississippi.
(Chuckles)
Come on, let's go.
Bed time.
LIBBY:
Oh.
Thanks.
I thought you might like that.
- Oh yeah.
- There you go.
It's cold.
Oh.
Oh!
There they are,
thank you.
(Cow moos in the distance)
You know, this won't be forever
just until I get us back
- on our feet.
- Yeah.
And I know
it's a lot with the kids.
It's just after Danny,
everything kinda just got away
from me
and it's hard to lose
your person and your whole life
in a year.
(Chuckles)
I really appreciate
you inviting us to stay.
I think it's gonna be
a little weird for a while.
You don't really know
what I'm made of
and I bet your mother's probably
filled your head with
a lot of chicken shit about me.
Well...
(Chuckles)
And you know Marsha,
she's got a lot to say
about a lot of things.
But I do remember you though,
I remember seeing you
at Granddaddy's funeral.
You and mom were fighting.
Oh yeah.
I was a doozy.
And your mother always was
a stellar sort of asshole.
But let's not talk about things
that make us wanna punch holes
in a sheetrock.
(Turkey clucking)
You have a lot of pets.
- We don't call 'em pets.
- Oh.
On a farm, they're animals.
And they all have jobs.
The hens lay eggs,
the cats keep the mice away,
the dogs protect the chickens
from the coyotes,
and the goats make milk.
(Turkey clucking)
What's his job?
Thanksgiving.
(Laughs)
(♪♪♪)
(Knocks on door)
Yes.
(Door squeaks)
Just in case you get cold.
Thanks.
Happy new year.
(♪♪♪)
Yeah, happy new year.
(Birds chirping)
(Cows mooing)
JEAN:
You both are doing a good job.
- It's so good.
Thank you.
- TANK: Thanks.
- You're welcome.
There she is.
Aunt Jean made pancakes
and I had a dream
I was a cute pink goat.
All goats are cute,
pink or not.
Try this jam, mama,
Jean made it.
(Gasps)
Strawberries and blueberries
from that field in the back.
Jean said we could pick 'em
in the summer.
And this was Wiggy the piggy.
She's delicious.
She was a good pig.
What would you like
in your espresso?
Wait, you don't have
a dishwasher, but you have this?
When it comes to coffee,
I don't mess around.
(Thuds)
(Grunts)
(Takes deep breaths)
(Door bangs)
This is James O'Connor,
my farm manager.
Would you please
quit calling me that.
You make it sound like
I got a desk out in the barn.
(Takes a deep breath)
You must be the uh,
the long lost niece.
Uh, yeah, that's me.
Nice to meet you.
This beautiful girl is Abby
and the tall, dark,
and handsome one is Tank.
How you doing?
It's just grease.
- TANK: Where do you live?
- Where do I live?
I live right out front there
in that silver bullet.
You look like a werewolf.
- Abby.
- I...
I look like a were...
or maybe I am a werewolf.
(Growls)
Don't worry, Abby, he's human.
O'Connor's gonna teach your mama
how to run the farm.
- What?
What, I'm sorry what?
- I need help, you need a job,
and he's not gonna stay around
forever.
Oh, I... trust me,
I know I need a job,
but I'm not sure
I'm the farming type.
Yeah, totally agree with that.
You don't know me.
Well, you're the one
who just said it.
Well, I... I can...
I can just tell.
Tell what?
You know what, I don't...
the point is
it's not a good idea.
Sure it is.
Drink up, get dressed,
and get outside.
Today?
It's a holiday.
There are no holidays on a farm.
I let you sleep in this morning,
but tomorrow's gonna be
a whole other deal.
Come on, kids.
Let's go see Russ
at the feed store.
- Wait, wait.
- ABBY AND TANK: Bye, mommy.
- Love you.
- Wait.
Bye, see you later.
Let's go, let's go.
Be... be... be careful.
Alright, two minutes,
out in the barn.
Where?
That the... that's
the big red structure outback.
(Chickens clucking)
(Goats bleating)
(Sighs)
Hey, hey, yo.
Here we go.
Okay.
- What is this?
- LIBBY: What?
You don't have a coat.
I forgot it at my mom's.
Well, these are chickens.
And these are goats.
She told me to start
from scratch,
so that's what I'm gonna do.
This one right over here,
that's Ms. Taylor.
The one right
there is Katy Perry
and the one right back
over there
that doesn't belong with anyone,
that's Susan Sontag.
These are Nubians,
the ones with the long,
floppy ears.
We don't have any Alpines,
but we do have a few Lamanchas
and don't show 'em,
we only milk 'em.
- Do they all have names?
- Yeah.
They all got names,
but I just call 'em "goat".
And why do you call her
"Aunt Jean", are you related?
Uh, no, no.
But, she's like family.
I'm fine.
Come on in.
Alright, you gotta wedge it
down first.
You know, I mean everywhere.
Front to back,
not back to front.
Alright, here we go.
Hand me those hoses that's right
over there, will ya?
These, yeah.
You gotta attach these.
Where?
Uh, exactly where you think
you might attach 'em,
to their teats.
Alright, slow and easy here.
♪ You and me going
fishing in the dark ♪
♪ Lying on our back
and counting the stars ♪
♪ Where the blue grass grow
You gotta sing to 'em.
You're kidding.
O'CONNOR:
No.
(Humming)
I'm not singing to goats.
I don't sing to goats.
♪ Feels so good to be with you
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah, see.
Just warm 'em up first,
that's how you get these girls
to give you their best.
Isn't that right?
Alright, now hit play.
♪ You and me going fishing
in the dark ♪
Just like that.
♪ Lying on our backs
and counting the stars ♪
(James grunts)
♪ Where the
golden grass grows ♪
I... I just... I... I thought
we'd have to do it all by hand,
you know?
Well, we got 30 goats
and four hands.
♪ We'll be fallin' in love
in the middle of the night ♪
♪ Just movin' so slow
And Frank set all that up.
Yeah, I oughta fix this.
(Grunts)
And he installed this big fridge
right over here.
♪ Feels so good
to be with you ♪
The plan was to add
a cheese business,
but then he got sick, so...
With what?
With Parkinson's.
Now Jean's got arthritis,
so I guess that makes you
next in line for the throne.
(Chuckles)
I don't know about that.
Yeah, you're telling me.
Here's the fridge.
Is it all goat cheese?
- Is it good?
- Yeah, yeah.
That's so cool.
You know, with all of this
Jean really could open
a cute little cheese store.
No, please save your ideas
about the hipster cheese shop
for your... your journal.
I don't... I don't really wanna
hear about that.
I don't think that's exactly
what I was saying, but...
Okay.
Okay, I'm... I'm... sounded like
you were talking about
a hipster cheese shop
you wanted to open.
Anyway, it doesn't matter,
this concludes our tour
of the fridge for today.
Here's the rule about gates,
you always wanna leave 'em
the way you found 'em.
If they're open,
you leave 'em open
and if they're closed...
Let me guess,
you leave them closed.
That's right, very good.
Now you just turn it over there
and open it like that, okay?
Here you go then.
Turn it.
You gotta turn it, turn it.
I'm turning.
You gotta turn it, turn it,
turn it, turn it...
- Ow, I'm turning it!
- Turn it, turn it, turn it.
Ow, ow!
- Ow.
- Okay, well,
maybe I should probably
fix that one.
Am I supposed to follow you?
O'CONNOR:
Yep.
Yo.
Yeah.
(♪♪♪)
(Libby grunts)
Can you hold up,
I need to adjust my shoe.
(♪♪♪)
(Grunts)
It's beautiful, huh?
(Taking deep breaths)
(♪♪♪)
(Birds chirping)
(Wheel rattling)
(Rooster crowing)
(TV in background)
Oh, she's alive.
I just sat down
on the edge of the bed
and I fell asleep.
You're late.
No, I'm not,
I just heard the rooster.
Dooby.
(Laughs)
He's all over the map.
He's a rooster.
Roosters can't tell time.
Um, okay, I um...
I will come.
I just have to get the kids up
and...
Done!
They're out watering.
They are?
Yeah, I've taught 'em how to use
the rain barrel.
O'CONNOR:
Yeah.
We're gonna go milk the goats.
And I'm gonna have you
run into town,
get some supplies,
you can take my truck.
Okay, okay.
Um, let me just take
a quick shower
- and then I'll come...
- Why?
You don't need to take a shower,
the beauty pageant's
not till Saturday.
I mean goats don't care
what you smell like.
Right?
I'm gonna brush my teeth.
Okay.
Yeah, that's probably
a good idea.
We need to hire a real hand.
She'll learn.
(Thunder rumbles)
(Quivering)
(Engine starts)
(♪♪♪)
(French song playing)
(Truck whirring)
(♪♪♪)
(Country song
playing in background)
(Grunting)
Okay.
SHOP ANNOUNCER: (On speaker)
(Indiscernible speech)
(Taking deep breaths)
(Cashier grunts)
There it is.
- Oh.
- Hi!
Hi.
(Takes deep breaths)
It's just these.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Good.
Okay.
You married?
Oh, I was.
Hmm, divorced then?
No.
Mysterious, what happened?
He's just gone.
Gone where?
How much do I owe ya?
That would be 48.25.
60.
So like gone as in dead?
Wait, your change.
(Grunts)
(Taking deep breaths)
(♪♪♪)
(Engine starts)
(Crying)
(♪♪♪)
JEAN:
There you are.
We're gonna have
our first cheese lesson.
Hey Jean, I just need like um,
I just need like a moment,
because I haven't really had
a shower in three days
and I'm exhausted.
And I just need a moment.
- Alright.
- Okay.
JEAN:
Go.
Take your shower,
I see you back here
in 10 minutes.
(♪♪♪)
(Water running)
- Feel better?
- Yeah.
Oh, and thanks for the...
the overalls.
And do they fit.
You're starting
to look the part.
(Libby chuckles)
Looks can be deceiving.
- What are we doing?
- God's work.
We're making chévre.
Come on.
(Smacks lips)
- That sounds hard.
- It's not hard.
Here, I want you to put
this milk into that pan.
- (Grunts)
- So here.
It's heavy.
Pour it all in.
Yeah, that... that's good.
Alright, now this is rennet
and bacteria.
You're gonna put
two or three drops in there
and I'm gonna put
this whole thing in there.
And this is gonna help
the milk coagulate.
My head feels coagulated.
You stir that now.
Stir that up.
Um, hey Jean, I just...
listen, I just wanna
thank you again
for letting us stay.
I mean you know,
you've been so amazing.
And the kids obviously
love it here and...
You don't have to
thank me anymore.
You work here now.
Well, I just... that's what
I wanna talk to you about.
I am not sure that
I'm actually cut out for this.
You know?
I want you to take
those around there
and put 'em on this parchment
paper, nice and even.
Come on, pick 'em up
with your bare hands, go ahead.
- I...
- That's good, go ahead.
Go ahead.
You can go on, I'm listening.
Well, I just... I don't know
how long we're gonna be here
and I don't want you
to depend on me just in case,
you know,
this all doesn't work out.
And I... I really appreciate you.
Okay, I understand.
Okay?
I'll take you
for as long as I can get you.
There.
It's alright, you can have
a little bit on your hands.
Just salt 'em lightly now,
'cause it's all done.
I'm gonna... it's a...
Just take a teaspoon,
just like you're putting
a little salt on your food
only you're not shaking it.
- There you go.
- Okay.
Yeah, you can do that,
pinch it on.
You're a natural.
(♪♪♪)
(Goats bleating)
(Kids noises in background)
Well, Bartley, sounds like
we have a full house.
What do you have
in your backpack?
Ooh, okay,
let's go, please hurry.
Come on, Abby,
I don't wanna be late.
Here you go.
Okay.
Bug,
you're doing such a good job.
Isn't the milk glass pretty,
mama?
It really is.
You know what else is pretty?
You.
(Chuckles)
We're having company for dinner.
We are?
You better go get cleaned up.
Yes, ma'am.
Can you go get the bread?
(Indiscernible mumbling)
Don't you tear it up.
ABBY:
Tank and I actually saw...
(Indiscernible speech)
(Knocks on door)
Evenin', one and all.
Oooh, it smells like
love in here, Jean.
(Indiscernible speech)
(Kisses)
Libby,
this is my boyfriend Russ.
- LIBBY: Hi.
- (Chuckles)
Give me a hug, I wanna hug you.
And this is his beautiful
granddaughter Sunshine.
Hi, how's it going?
Hi.
These are for you.
For me, why?
Well, you're the niece
of the woman I love.
It's a bribe.
Don't listen to her.
I need all the help I can get
with this one.
I need you on my side.
Now she is one of them
hippie Liberals
and I'm a Conservative lawyer.
Wait, I thought you owned
the feed store.
Well, I'm also entrepreneur.
Now just tell me you're not one
of them hippies or Liberals,
are you?
I'm not really sure what I am.
She's undecided,
that means she's a Liberal.
That's one for my side.
What?
Oh now, come on now,
that's not right.
Sorry, Russ.
Jean, how you feelin'?
Well, my fingers are
a little swollen
when I get up in the morning
these days, aching, you know...
- No, no, no, Jean.
- Just things like that.
I mean, how are you feeling?
I don't know.
Worried, hopeful.
How am I supposed to feel?
Well, you know
what I always say.
Yes, I do.
Then I guess
I don't have to say it.
No, you don't.
I feel like
maybe I should say it anyway.
What are you gonna do?
Hands high.
Ooh, solar plexus, nice.
Follow it up with an elbow,
right.
You.
Whoa!
Alright, Abby,
if that kid messes with you,
you know what to do.
Go to bed.
Goodnight, O'Connor.
- Goodnight, you guys.
- Goodnight, O'Connor.
LIBBY:
Where are you going?
- ABBY: Upstairs, mom.
- Okay.
Yeah, dishes are clean.
(Rooster crowing)
See what I mean?
Thank you for nothing, Dooby.
Man.
(Sighs)
That was nice.
What?
Just having a home-cooked meal.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Hey.
Um, I just wanted to say
I'm really sorry for
freaking you out at the store.
It's okay.
Give me your hand.
Yeah, you're probably freaking
her out again right now.
Yeah, no, I'm good, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
I just... come on,
I'm gonna read it.
- Okay.
- Oh, you don't have to, you...
- Let me.
- Okay.
- (Clears throat)
So it says you have
a very strong life line.
Ooh, that's original.
Ignore him.
Um, wow, and it says that
your past and your present
are about to intersect.
Your heart line says that
you have a lot of love
in your life
and huh, two family rings.
And what does that mean?
It means you have two families.
And everything in your life
is about to change.
(Snorts)
Newsflash,
I think it already has.
Okay, with that revelation
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna hit the hay.
Uh, Jean, thank you for dinner.
Goodnight, everybody.
JEAN:
Goodnight, James.
RUSS:
Goodnight.
(Takes a deep breath)
Your husband,
you said he was gone.
But he's not really gone.
Okay, actually now you are
freaking me out.
(♪♪♪)
ABBY:
Is he gonna get the day off?
LIBBY: It's not a day
off if you're sick.
I don't feel good.
Good morning,
my beautiful family.
LIBBY:
Hey, babe...
Is he gonna get the day off?
Can you take Abby
to school today,
I gotta take tank to the doctor,
he's burning up?
Yeah, yeah, sorry to hear that,
buddy.
Abby, I'm leaving
in five minutes, are you ready?
Yes, sir.
And you're going
to the bank today, right?
- I'm gonna drop off Abby...
- I don't feel good.
And then I'm gonna deal
with the new deal
that I've been working on
and yes,
I'm gonna go straight...
Tuition's due.
To the bank right after that.
You worry too much.
Everything's gonna be fine.
- (Kisses)
- Love you.
LIBBY:
Danny.
Danny!
Something bad is gonna happen.
I got it.
Scout's honour.
Stop worrying.
I love you.
- Danny.
- Serious question.
Um, who do you like better,
me or mama?
Danny!
We won't get into that.
Yeah, okay, come on.
Danny!
(♪♪♪)
LIBBY:
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
(Crickets chirping)
(Thuds)
(♪♪♪)
(Yelling)
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
(Grunting)
What?
You want the bad news
or the bad news.
The bad news.
The latch is broken,
I was out here trying to fix it.
Nobody's gonna be up
for the next five hours
to open up this damn door.
What?
Get...
(Grunts)
Five hours.
- It's stuck.
- O'CONNOR: Yeah.
(Taking deep breaths)
Why don't you call Jean
on her cellphone?
Uh, my cellphone's
right outside the door.
You got your cellphone on you?
No, I don't have my cellphone.
O'CONNOR:
Of course, you don't.
What's the other bad news?
It's about to get real cold
in here.
What if we scream,
maybe she can hear us?
It's a refrigerator,
it's insulated, no, y...
I mean you can go ahead and try.
Don't you have some wire
or maybe a screwdriver
and then maybe you could just
jam it open or something?
- Or just...
- Oh, that's a good idea.
I...
A stick of gum, a nail file,
a sock, and in 45 seconds,
I can have the door open
before the bomb goes off.
Thank you.
O'CONNOR:
That'll keep you warm.
What did I tell you about doors
and gates?
I don't need a lecture
right now.
Leave 'em the way
you found 'em.
I don't need a lecture!
Leave 'em the way you found 'em.
Ow!
If a door's open,
you leave it open.
If a door is closed,
you leave it closed.
Patsy Cline had a great January.
You should try that.
That's really good.
Hmm.
What if I have to pee?
Oh, you...
you're not peeing here.
You're gonna have to hold it in.
What if I can't?
(Sighs)
What are we in preschool?
You're gonna have...
you're gonna have to hold it.
I mean,
you gotta go pee right now?
No.
Then why... why are we even
talking about it?
Because I'm worried that
I might have to go later.
(Sighs)
(♪♪♪)
(Libby taking deep breaths)
So why'd you move out here
anyway?
I had to get out
of my mom's place.
Yeah?
Yeah, my husband died
and then I lost our house.
So it was a pretty great year.
And uh, then I had to move in
with my mom.
And Marsha's not easy.
(Taking deep breaths)
Why do you live here?
Uh, convenience mostly.
(Sniffles)
My ex got the house.
Your ex-wife?
No, ex-husband.
Shut up.
Really?
No ex-wife.
Oh.
How long you guys been divorced?
You know, I'd... I'd...
I'd actually prefer
to talk about Marsha.
LIBBY:
Marsha.
She's very beautiful.
She still is very beautiful.
Travel agent,
been married four times.
She's a piece of work.
I think I was like 6
when she'd decided
I didn't need a babysitter
anymore.
I remember I was so scared
whenever she would leave me.
(Yawning)
I would... I would stay
in my closet with the um,
you know the high horses.
You know, those like sticks
with the little horse heads
on top.
I would sit in my closet
with that.
And sometimes,
I would wake up there,
'cause I think she just forgot
to come check on me.
Well, that sucks.
Yeah, but no, not that bad.
(Quivering)
Hey, come sit.
Lean back against that.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Oh God.
(Grunts)
Oh, this stinks.
(♪♪♪)
Y'all have a little
cold weather campout?
(Grunts)
Oh God, oh.
(Russ laughs)
Thank you!
Oh God!
It was so cold.
Wooh!
This one got us locked in.
Who fixes a door
in the middle of night?
The one, who knows how to get
a job done, that's who.
Well, this one's got an answer
for everything, doesn't he?
Ooh.
Like you got an answer
for everything, too.
(Chuckles)
(Indistinct chatter)
(Bell rings)
GIRL 1:
See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
(Indistinct chatter)
Where did you get
that funny shirt, new girl.
You're so ugly you'd scare
a buzzard off a gut cart.
What are you gonna do, limper?
(Phone ringing)
- Mrs. Moran?
- Yes.
Hi.
Are you sure
it was Abby's fault,
because she's really...
she's not a fighter.
She's never even hit anybody
in her life.
- I mean...
- Well, it's never easy
starting at a new school.
But we have
a zero tolerance policy
for violence here.
Abby will have to use her words
instead of her karate chops
when she's teased.
Teased about what?
Mrs. Moran, Abby's not the first
and she certainly
won't be the last gawky child.
She... she has a limp
from a car accident.
It's the same car accident
that killed her father
and my daughter knows more
about pain and hard work...
Mrs. Moran.
This isn't a great way
to start a new school.
It's grounds for suspension.
What is going on?
I mean what...
this is not like you.
He called me "limper".
Okay, that kid is a jerk,
but you cannot just go around
hitting people.
You have to use your words,
okay?
(Sighs)
I mean how do you even know
karate in the first place?
O'Connor.
What?
(Goats bleating)
(Knocks)
It's Libby.
Mom.
Hey, oh hey, Abby.
Um, did you teach her
how to fight?
- Yeah, a couple of moves.
- Well, thank you,
because my child just got
suspended for a week.
You finally got that Jimmy kid.
I got him right
in the solar plexus.
- (Chuckles)
- Nice work.
No.
No, not nice work.
How does he know about Jimmy?
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm your mother.
Because I knew you would
stress out about it.
What, I'm not stressed out!
Mom, you're stressing out
right now.
Abby, I'm fine,
I can handle this, I'm cool.
You could've told me.
I need you to go to your room.
- Go to your room.
- Yeah.
Don't...
- Go to your room.
- Don't...
Don't ever do that again.
- Why are you mad at her?
- I'm not mad at her.
- Yeah, you are.
- No, I'm not.
She's been getting picked on
ever since
she got to that school.
I'm mad at you.
She didn't tell you, because
she's trying to protect you.
What?
Protect me from what?
I hope she kicked the piss
out of him.
(♪♪♪)
Hey.
You know what that kid said,
it was awful
and he probably got
what he deserved.
And I am so proud of you
for standing up for yourself.
I miss daddy.
Look, I know.
I know.
I do, too.
I like it here on the farm.
Are we gonna stay, mama?
I don't know.
You know what I do know that
whatever happens,
we're gonna be okay.
Promise?
Oh.
Promise.
(Chuckles)
- Can I spend the night?
- Yeah.
My feet are so cold.
(Laughing)
(Rooster crowing)
(Goats bleating)
♪ We wake up in the mornin',
love ♪
♪ And the sunlight hurts
my eye ♪
♪ And the something
we've got more than love ♪
♪ There's hay on my lap
♪ Then I look at you
♪ And you look so right
with me ♪
♪ One look at you
♪ And I know it's gonna be
♪ Loving it, loving it
♪ Loving it
♪ I love that day
♪ Loving it, loving it
♪ Loving it
♪ I love that day
♪ Loving it, loving it
♪ Loving it
♪ I love that day
♪ Loving it, loving it
♪ Loving it
♪ I love that day
♪ Loving it, loving it
♪ Loving it
♪ I love that day
♪ Loving it, loving it
♪ Loving it
♪ I love that day
(Laughing)
(Overlapping speech)
- Is that too much salt?
- Ready, just roll it.
JEAN: Yeah,
just put a little bit of salt.
- Okay.
- That one looks really good.
This costs $8,
this is handmade, too.
- LIBBY: $8!
- JEAN: It's handmade, too.
We can sell it to the shop or...
Well,
he can't afford this cheese.
(♪♪♪)
Now higher.
"...a long white apron.
And he informed her indeed
and precisely
that he had prepared
cu... curry..."
- Ooh.
- How do you say that word?
- Curry.
Curry shrimp.
It's too spicy.
(♪♪♪)
(Grunts)
Okay.
(Takes a deep breath)
What are we plantin'?
Nothing aspirational,
only what we can eat.
I'm not gonna plant another bed
of artichokes
for no good reason.
(Birds chirping)
It really is pretty here.
I thought you'd like it.
Hey Jean,
can I ask you a question?
Sure.
How long did it take you?
Plant all these?
- Not long.
- Mm-mm, you know, to um...
To...
to get over Frank?
(Sighs)
Initially, I was never gonna
get over Frank.
I hunkered down in my sadness
and I refused to come up
for air.
Then slowly,
I got back to living.
Life keeps chugging along
whether we like it or not.
Sometimes, I just feel like
I'm drowning, you know?
This kinda pain and loss,
it cracks you open.
But we are made of magic
and resilience, Libby.
Losing someone you love,
that scar
will feel ugly forever.
But it will heal.
You promise?
I can speak from experience.
(♪♪♪)
Is that too close?
O'CONNOR: Farmer's market is
easy, I don't...
I don't know why Jean waited
so long to show you.
I do.
I used to live in Houston,
haven't been back since we left.
You moving back?
I don't know.
I have to get a real job,
I can't run a farm,
I've gotta make money.
Excuse me.
Milking goats, isn't a real job?
You know what I mean,
I gotta send my kids to college.
College isn't necessary.
My kids are going to college.
O'CONNOR:
Why?
So they can have a good life.
- To...
- O'CONNOR: Okay.
- Did you go to college?
- Yep.
LIBBY:
Do you have a good life?
Not because I went to college.
- Did you go to college?
- Yes.
O'CONNOR: Yeah,
and how is that working out for you?
Okay, well, my life
didn't turn out
exactly the way
it was supposed to.
Well, that's true
for pretty much everyone, Libby.
So you're just against
higher education?
O'CONNOR:
Yeah, it's a racket.
The world is falling apart
anyway.
Look, what you should be showing
your kids how to do
is hotwire a car, how to hunt,
how to fish,
how to fend for themselves.
That, that is what's gonna
come in handy
when the apocalypse comes.
You realize you sound crazy?
Maybe I am crazy.
LIBBY:
Yeah.
Tank and Abby are gonna be
just fine,
they're both survivors.
(♪♪♪)
(Indistinct chatter)
(Laughter)
CUSTOMER 1: One Doris and
two Angelina Jolies please.
Good choice.
My son loves Angelina Jolie,
too.
She just has a way with kids
all over the world.
(Laughs)
Get it?
Okay.
(Indistinct chatter
in background)
Stop it, Libby,
it's not so funny.
Oh my God.
Libby Moran?
- Girls, it's Libby.
- (Jessica and friends gasp)
- (Indiscernible speech)
- Oh my gosh.
Hi!
- (Laughs)
- BECKA: It's Libby!
Hi.
Huh, look at you.
(Kissing)
L... Libby.
Hi.
Oh my God, we haven't seen you
since the funeral.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I miss Danny so much.
How are you really?
How are you?
I'm... I'm good.
I'm... I'm... you know, the kids
are really...
- Are you making cheese?
- Oh.
Um, helping out.
- And just selling.
- We buy it every week.
Yeah, no, that is so cute.
- Adorable.
- LANIE: We love it.
Ooh um, oh well, um,
I'll take a... a Rosie
and um a... a Doris.
Okay.
Um, Rosie, Doris.
Okay, okay, that is $10.
You can keep the change.
Oh no, we don't take tips.
Oh well, yeah, actually...
speak for yourself.
We do actually take tips.
- (Laughs)
- I guess we take tips.
(Chuckles)
I'm gonna... I'm gonna go grab
a cider.
Guess we take tips.
Okay, you work
with the hot farmer?
Who?
Oh, that's what we call him.
Him?
He's the reason we come here.
Mhmm, he's hot.
Ridiculously hot.
Wooh.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's yeah.
Okay, wait a minute.
Are you two... are you two
making cheese together?
- No.
- I mean, what?
- Are you?
- No.
- LANIE: Come on.
- Oh God.
- LANIE: You can tell us.
- (Jessica screams)
- I don't want to kiss and tell.
- You can tell us.
I mean,
we've made some cheese together.
- Oh!
- Sometimes.
- Wow!
- Wow.
- Well, good for you.
- Yeah.
You've totally moved on.
Oh, wasn't Danny
the sweetest guy ever though?
- Hmm, just exquisite.
- Miss you, miss you.
Ugh, a diamond in the rough.
(Grunts)
I... can you just give me a...
Hey, I'll be right back.
Thank you for sharing.
(Indistinct chatter
in background)
Hi.
- Bye.
- (Laughing)
Bye.
Go.
BECKA:
See ya next week.
Yeah.
(Taking deep breaths)
(Overlapping speech)
Hey, that was so sad.
Ugh, what is it about her
that is so irritating?
BECKA: She's just one of those
people, mhmm, mhmm.
JESSICA: Hey y'all,
you know I feel sorry for her.
Her husband dies
in a car accident,
- leaves them broke.
- Hmm.
I went to her estate sale.
LANIE:
Come on, you didn't.
- JESSICA: I sure did.
- LANIE: Oh.
She had the same
wedding china as me.
Y'all, don't judge, but I bought
every last piece of it.
(Chuckles)
Now I have plate settings
for 24.
That's amazing.
Good thing I'm popular.
(Laughing)
LANIE: Okay,
there's no way she's sleeping
with the hot farmer.
BECKA:
You don't think she's lying?
LANIE:
Oh, give me a break.
Hello, she looks like
she's wearing
a Halloween costume.
(Chuckles)
She's like a lumberjack.
LANIE:
It's... from a truck stop.
(Friend laughing)
Do y'all think I need botox?
- Oh.
- What?
- That here.
- You look beautiful, no.
No, you still look so young
from the last time.
- Yeah, mhmm.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
- I love it, I'm way behind.
Oh.
(Indistinct chatter)
O'CONNOR:
Yeah, alright.
Thank you.
Yeah, see you next week.
Hey, we need to leave.
- What?
- I need to leave.
I need to leave.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
slow down.
- What's... what's going on?
- We need to go.
Those women that were here,
they hate me.
They think you're hot.
I might have accidentally
told them that
we were making cheese together.
And... and... and they're just
they're terrible people
and I just really wanna go home
and they think I'm dressed like
a scarecrow, so...
(Sighs)
(Kissing)
(Indistinct chattering)
I hate terrible people.
Well, that's that.
Mhmm.
Well, that was gross.
- Shall we?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
LIBBY:
Yeah, I really do.
You are to,
you're doing pretty good.
(Thunder rumbles)
- I like it.
- (Phone ringing)
Hello.
(Sniffles)
When?
Alright, I'm on my way.
I'm on my way right now.
Okay.
What?
It's Aaron.
I'm sorry, I gotta...
- Oh.
- I gotta go.
It's okay, go, I got this.
(Truck engine starts)
(Thunder rumbles)
(Crickets chirping)
- I like yours.
I like yours.
You know we can switch off,
remember...
Yeah, we can switch 'em off.
- (Laughing)
- You guys look...
Hi, mama.
Mama, we made hats.
Oh my gosh!
The tinfoil makes
our brain waves move faster.
Well, who doesn't want that.
Look at you.
Are you guys done?
Okay, why don't you go upstairs,
wash up,
brush those dirty chompers.
What do you have on your nose?
(Kids laughing)
LIBBY: And um,
I'll come up and I'll read you a story.
- Sound good?
- Yeah.
Great.
Go!
- Goodnight.
Goodnight, Aunt Jean.
(Kisses)
Goodnight.
Ain't he sweet?
He's cute.
(Sighs)
JEAN:
How was the market?
Um, better than expected.
O'Connor had to um,
just run off.
Uh, something happened
with Aaron.
Oh goodness.
I'll have to call
and check on him.
Who's Aaron?
His ex-wife.
She had a stroke
some years back.
LIBBY:
How old is she?
Same age as him.
A nurse takes care of her,
but he's out there all the time.
That sucks.
(Knocks on door)
Who could that be?
I don't know anybody who knocks.
Nobody knocks in that order.
No.
Looks like they released
the Kraken.
(Chuckling)
I'm here to see my daughter
and my grandchildren.
(Clears throat)
What are you doing here?
Um, well, uh, making cheese.
Um, goat cheese,
and then...
No, honey,
I mean what are you doing?
What are you doing here?
You can come home now, you can.
I forgive you.
Forgive me for what?
For leaving.
Well, you made it pretty clear
that um, we were nearing
our expiration date.
You'd been sleeping on my couch
for six months.
I was having a hard time.
I know, and I was trying
to motivate you,
because I did not raise you
to be a victim.
You cannot throw your life away
if he was not worth it...
Marsha!
These kids have to go to bed,
so we need to say goodnight to...
- What?
- I didn't even...
Goodnight, Marsha.
Goodnight.
Goodnight, my babies.
Hey, Abigail.
(Chuckles)
Yep, you got taller.
I see it.
That's good, honey.
So stand up straight.
Come on, let's see it.
That's right.
I really... I can't believe that
you're being so ungrateful.
I'd given you everything.
I gave you an education.
I gave you
all those really nice clothes,
took you on
all those great vacations.
Mama, let's...
you left me hotel rooms, so...
They were very nice hotels.
LIBBY:
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
I just... I...
(Sighs)
You don't want this.
I'm staying here for now, okay?
Why?
This is not you, Libby.
This isn't you.
What's me?
Tell me, what is me.
You're not meant
for a small town,
you're not meant for a farm,
this...
Mama, what am I meant for?
'Cause I don't know
what I'm meant for.
Well, we can find out
when you come home.
I don't have a home!
Where do I go?
This is all I've got,
so I'm gonna stay here.
Okay?
This is all I got.
You can come back to me.
We'll find something bigger.
I really don't wanna do this
right now.
I gotta get the kids to bed.
Fine.
Alright.
Just give up.
Mama,
I cannot do this right now.
MARSHA:
No.
You... you get to choose the time
when you do this.
Okay, you know what,
thank you so much
for letting us stay
at your house.
Is that okay?
Thank you so much
and I hope you have
a safe drive back home.
Does that sound good?
There you go.
(Gasps)
Libby?
Stupid.
You look tired, Jean.
I was just gonna say
the same thing about you.
Hmm.
(Rain puttering)
I know you're trying to turn her
against me.
Did you tell her yet?
Not yet.
She's gonna be just
as disappointed in you
as she is in me.
Maybe.
Well, I know her
and she's gonna come back to me.
God, I hate this place.
S...
These people.
It's all so small.
Lucky for us,
you don't live here anymore.
Yeah.
Why do you even live here
when you could be living
up there?
I'll never live
in that house again.
'Cause you're stubborn,
just like Papa.
You've always been jealous
of me.
I never even think about you.
(♪♪♪)
(Car starts)
(Goats bleating)
Good girl, come on.
Let's go, come on.
- Hey.
Hey uh, I'm sorry
I guess I'm the new O'Connor.
Oh!
Yeah, uh, Jean asked me to come
help out with uh...
Have you ever done
any of this before?
How hard could it be?
(Chuckles)
Nice shoes.
Oh, thanks.
They're new.
Yeah.
Not for long.
Um, grab that feed.
Okay.
Hurry up.
The one with the long ears,
what are they?
Nubians.
Yes.
And that one over there
with the short ears?
Uh, Lamancha.
Lamancha.
Yeah, got it.
You got it.
- You're made for this.
- Um.
- It's fun, right?
- Yeah, no, it is fun.
It's just really messy work.
Yeah, kind of uh, it reminds me
of when I was in LA,
I uh, I bussed tables for
a couple of years
and at the end
of every single shift,
I was a mess.
I had food all over me.
(Laughs)
How long did you live there?
Um, couple of years.
Uh, I was a singer,
uh singer-songwriter.
What do you mean was?
You don't sing anymore?
No.
Um, not really.
Um.
- I didn't make it, you know.
- Yeah.
And uh, my label dropped me.
And I had a very toxic
relationship with vodka.
And uh, everything
just kinda went sideways.
I... I lost myself.
(Smacks lips)
And the reason I went out there
in the first place...
...I went out there
to be somebody.
And then, you know
I never thought I'd find myself
back here doing this.
(Chuckles)
Well, if it's any consolation
kind of the shiniest thing
in this town.
What do you plan to be
when you grow up, a farmer?
Oh gosh, I don't know
what I'm gonna be
when I grow up.
Kinda lost my compass.
What's that mean?
Something happened
with my husband
and I... I... I...
I just should've talked to him.
I mean the truth is
we were broke
and I don't know why
I just didn't talk to him.
And I just... so stupid.
I have an idea.
What are you doing tonight?
Come on, just because
you lose someone,
doesn't mean you stop
talking to 'em.
I come around here all the time
to talk to my grandmother.
(Laughing)
This feels like a terrible idea.
It's gonna be great, trust me.
(♪♪♪)
(Taking deep breaths)
(Laughs)
(♪♪♪)
This place is...
...it's so familiar to me.
Did there used to be
a driveway here?
Uh, I don't know.
It's where Jean grew up.
Nobody's lived in it for years.
Yeah, everyone calls it,
"the Halloween house".
SUNSHINE:
Come on.
(♪♪♪)
(Laughs)
If you wanna lose your virginity
or talk to the dead,
this is the spot.
Come on.
Okay, this is where we do it.
I really can't believe me that
you convinced me to do this,
'cause I... I don't believe
in this sort of stuff.
Close your eyes.
And take a deep breath.
(Taking a deep breath)
Together.
(Inhales)
Deeper.
(Exhales)
(Sighs)
We're uh, clearing the circle
to make space
for the other plane.
The what?
(Shushes)
Keep your eyes closed.
They are closed.
(Sighs)
Okay.
Mmm.
(Takes a deep breath)
We hope so we will receive
a sign of your presence.
Danny, if you're with us, please
join us when you're ready.
How do we see a sign
if our eyes are closed?
(Sighs)
I feel like you're not taking
this seriously.
Sorry.
(Sunshine takes a deep breath)
Can I give it a shot?
Yeah, sure, be my guest.
Um, Danny, you can hear me?
I miss you.
(Chuckles)
I really miss you.
Why didn't I talk to you?
Why couldn't we just see that
we had enough, you were enough.
We didn't need more.
Why am I so mad at you for dying
and leaving us?
You know, I mean I was the one
that asked you to take Abby
to school that day, I was
the one who changed the routine.
And I just feel like
it was my fault.
And I'm really sorry.
I'm really...
...sorry.
(Fire crackling)
And I love you.
And the kids love you.
And I don't know what else
to say.
I just hope that you're okay
wherever you are.
I don't think that
really worked.
You did great.
You nailed it!
(Taking a deep breath)
(♪♪♪)
(Kisses)
Don't make me one,
I'm not eating bread.
Hmm.
Jean, why didn't you tell me
about that house?
It's amazing,
it can be so beautiful.
- You went up there?
- LIBBY: Mhmm.
Last night with Sunshine.
It was crazy.
She convinced me to do
like a circle thing with candles
- and... and...
- A séance?
Yeah.
I don't know, it...
Did it work?
(Sighs)
I feel better.
Why'd you let that house go?
Must've been a great place
to grow up.
I really want that
for Abby and Tank.
Abbs, Tank, come on, let's go!
- We're gonna be late!
- ABBY: Coming!
You know, like a home, like a...
like a real home.
You know, with Marsha
we just moved from town to town
and husband to husband.
And just never got to lay
any roots.
I don't wanna end up like that.
Well, well, well,
look what the cat dragged in.
- Go.
- Jeanie, Jeanie.
- Mornin'.
- Hi honey.
Abby says there's dancing
at the party.
I don't know how, Jeanie.
It's easy.
Come on, now just fake it.
Is O'Connor coming
to the dance party?
Fingers crossed.
Jeanie.
Oh what?
Why yes, of course,
I want a present.
It's my birthday
for goodness sake.
But I have one rule, no one is
allowed to buy me a present.
We have to steal them?
- No!
- (Laughing)
What are you talking about?
- No, you make them, silly.
- You're crazy.
Look at your face, steal.
- Bye, Aunt Jean.
- JEAN: Bye.
- TANK: Bye, Aunt Jeanie.
Libby.
Yes, ma'am.
You're not your mother.
Fingers crossed.
(Sighs)
(Birds chirping)
(Cows mooing)
(♪♪♪)
Hey.
Hey, Libby.
You look tired.
Oh, thank you.
How do you feel?
Tired.
(Chuckles)
How's Aaron?
Um, well, you know,
considering the circumstances,
she's managing.
Something's gotta give.
I'm sorry, it's tough.
No.
We're gonna see ya
at Jean's party this weekend,
right?
Yeah, I don't... I don't know
if I feel much like a party.
That makes sense.
Right, you know.
- It was nice seeing you.
- You, too.
- LIBBY: Feel better.
- Hmm.
Hey, Libby.
Yeah?
The farm looks terrible.
I had a terrible teacher.
(James laughs)
Libby, the school called,
Abby's been hurt.
What?
I'll drive.
(♪♪♪)
- You okay?
- Yeah.
The head always bleeds a lot,
so that's why her clothes
are so bloody.
The wound's superficial.
Yeah, it doesn't look
superficial to me.
Bug, what happened?
You can tell me.
Jimmy Grevoski pushed me
into the fence.
So that kid
is still bothering you?
Yes.
I used my words
and he pushed me.
Unfortunately, it wasn't
the best choice of words.
Well, what words did you use?
I told him to back the eff off.
(Laughing)
That's great.
Mrs. Moran, can I speak to you
in my office?
Uh, sure.
- Thanks.
- What?
- I didn't do...
- That was nice, thanks.
(Chuckles)
You said that?
NURSE:
You're gonna be okay.
I believe we're looking
at another suspension.
You gotta be kidding me,
for saying a bad word?
That kid pushed her
and she's bleeding.
Jimmy is also going to receive
a suspension.
Unbelievable.
You know what?
I don't think
you are doing your job.
My child is supposed to be safe
at school,
she used her words
just like you said
and now you're going to suspend
her again for saying a bad word.
What kind of a school
are you running?
She's being bullied daily
and you have done nothing
to stop it.
Mrs. Moran,
we have a system in place.
Well, Mrs. Weeks,
your system is broken.
Yeah.
I'm gonna get that blood
wiped off you.
Okay, let's go.
(Indistinct chatter
in background)
That's him.
So what happened with you
and Abby earlier?
We were just playing.
Yeah, you want me to play
with you like that?
No, sir.
You touch her again
and I will find you,
you understand me?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
(♪♪♪)
♪ This place is strange
♪ Old and rank
♪ Seems better it rains
♪ (Indiscernible lyrics)
♪ As the oldest of trees
♪ Each from the ground
(♪♪♪)
TANK:
Mama, we're ready.
Okay, y'all go get
your shoes on,
I'll be down in like 10 minutes,
okay?
TANK:
Okay.
(♪♪♪)
(Indistinct chatter)
♪ To Lake Michigan
♪ I'm gonna throw myself
into the sea ♪
♪ I'm going down
♪ To Lake Michigan
♪ And that's the last
you're gonna see of me ♪
♪ I ain't got nobody
♪ Ain't nobody got me
(♪♪♪)
Look, they're dancing.
♪ And if you wanna tell
some story ♪
That's so good.
♪ Some story
Hey, where do you think she is?
♪ Before I'm go
Oh!
♪ About how things
Go get the birthday girl.
♪ Gonna get better
JEAN: Look at you!
Happy birthday, Aunt Jeanie.
You clean up pretty good.
So do you.
(Laughs)
Well, I never need to be...
wear my Sunday best.
(Laughs)
Jean, I... I... I don't know
what to say.
I... thank you for this.
It's...
Sometimes we just need
a pretty new dress
and someone to wear it.
Happy birthday.
It's really nice, I love it.
You hungry?
- Oh yeah.
- Come on.
I love these ribs, Aunt Jeanie,
I could eat 'em every day.
I'm so glad to hear that, honey.
And these are especially good,
because they come
from Mary Oak down 71.
This is quite a turnout.
Well, I have a lot of friends
who like a free meal.
You got a lot of friends
who like you,
'cause you're kind,
and you're generous,
and you're forgiving, and brave,
and you're beautiful
just like me.
You're crazy.
Alright, come on,
it's time for horse shoes.
And this time I'm gonna beat ya,
I don't care
if it is your birthday.
We'll see about that.
And you, go get a drink
and find yourself
a dance partner.
(Indistinct chatter
in background)
(Blows raspberry)
♪ Woah, woah
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
♪ Looking out
your window going ♪
Hey, um, I'll have drink.
♪ So high, so faraway
There you go.
♪ Some light that shines
in your eyes ♪
♪ (Indiscernible lyrics)
♪ Like the dark
at the end of the day ♪
♪ And the way the stars
over your house ♪
♪ Shine
SUNSHINE:
Hey, lady.
- ♪ Makes me feel that
- Hi.
♪ It's gonna be just fine
♪ Stars
Look at you, you look amazing.
Thank you.
I just... well, any idea how much
more of an impact
we could have on the world
if we didn't spend hours
on our hair.
We'd have a freaking cure
for everything by now.
- Amen.
- Yes.
Alright, let's dance.
- Really?
- Yes.
I'm going to lead.
- Oh my God.
- Yes.
Just trust me.
♪ Everywhere they're talking
♪ I ended up
opening your heart ♪
(Indiscernible conversation)
♪ (Indiscernible lyrics)
♪ And I saw you were there
on the night in a red truck ♪
♪ (Indiscernible lyrics)
♪ I'll never forget ya
♪ And wait...
(Applause)
♪ And I thought come on,
come on and break a frame ♪
♪ No cover charge,
drinks on me ♪
♪ Put all, your all,
it ain't the same ♪
♪ And it's a girls' night in
♪ Come on, come on
and crank it up ♪
♪ Shake what you got,
it's just us ♪
♪ It's all we need
to do it up ♪
♪ It's a girls' night in
Hi.
♪ It's a girls' night out
♪ Don't you know that I,
yeah, yeah ♪
You decided to come after all.
I did.
- Can I sit?
- Yeah, of course.
♪ Do it up, turn it up
♪ (Indiscernible lyrics)
Party, right.
♪ Crazy
You look great.
You wanna dance?
I don't know, do I?
I mean you seem to know
everything?
About everything, yeah?
(Laughs)
Oh my God!
Look, I'm... I'm just as lost
as the next guy, trust me.
♪ Come on, come on
and crank it up ♪
What?
♪ Come on, come on,
and turn it on ♪
♪ It's a girls' night in
I feel like you wanna ask me
something.
About Aaron?
(Chatter and laughter
in background)
Uh, I mean just if you wanna
talk about it.
I don't wanna talk about it.
I don't ever wanna talk about it
but...
(Sighs)
It doesn't seem to get me
anywhere.
Well, how long were
you guys together?
O'CONNOR:
Five years.
We moved out to a property
my parents left me
this side of town.
We were gonna raise Jerseys
and Herefords, those are cows.
And then she met somebody
in Austin.
She worked there
a few days a week.
♪ I do dig her
Wanted a divorce,
so I gave her one.
Did you want a divorce?
Nah.
No.
♪ 'Cause I want you to stay
Tsk.
Well, a few months later,
she had a... a stroke.
She's got
a congenital heart defect.
I mean you could eat
all the health food
in the world and still end up
in a wheelchair
for no good reason.
I mean it's...
(Sighs)
The irony of it,
you know what I mean?
And what about the guy?
Oh, he split, he's gone.
I mean, not really
the for better
or worse kinda guy I guess.
And do her parents,
do they help out, do they...
Her parents live in El Paso.
They're gonna move her
out there soon.
Well, at least that's what
I think they're gonna do.
- That's a lot.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
It's a lot.
♪ Every day
as they get restless ♪
Come on.
Wait, hold on, hold on,
hold on now.
It's hot.
♪ Oh, I know it sounds crazy
♪ I'm giving
everything I got ♪
♪ Everything I got
♪ I'm building
♪ A rocket ship
♪ Oh, it's made for memories
♪ So it's made
to make the trip ♪
♪ And I can go
almost anywhere ♪
♪ Oh woah
♪ When I get to
where I'm going ♪
♪ Or I'm never really there
♪ But I like the offence
♪ I guess
it's what you'd expect ♪
♪ For the cokes in hand
every once in a while ♪
(People cheering and whistling)
(♪♪♪)
(Laughs)
♪ I wish I was a baby bear
♪ Sleeping on the ground
♪ Winter grass in April
while the sun was going down ♪
♪ I wish my shoes were empty
and I was still in bed ♪
♪ With you there beside me
♪ With your dreams
inside your head ♪
♪ I wish the world would do
what I want it to ♪
♪ And I wish the wind
would blow me ♪
♪ Blow me back to you
♪ Well, I wish your mom was ugly
and your dad was ugly, too ♪
♪ 'Cause then they couldn't have
had a girl as beautiful as you ♪
♪ I wish
I was a tightrope walker ♪
♪ With legs made out of gold
♪ I'd hold you in my golden legs
and never let you go ♪
♪ I wish the world would do
what I want it to ♪
♪ And I wish the wind
would blow me ♪
♪ Blow me back to you
(♪♪♪)
Thank you.
♪ And I wish I could see Jesus
shining in the sky ♪
♪ And he could let me know
♪ That everything
will be alright ♪
♪ I wish I knew that God's love
was all I'd ever need ♪
♪ I'd cut my candy teeth for fun
and let the good times bleed ♪
♪ Oh, I wish the world
would do what I want it to ♪
♪ Wish the world would do
what I want it to ♪
♪ And I wish the wind
would blow me ♪
♪ Blow me back to you
(Ravens cawing)
(♪♪♪)
Hello.
YOUNG:
Please don't do that.
(♪♪♪)
Jean, what is this?
What is this?
Are you and Frank my parents?
No.
That's not it.
Then what?
I'm afraid if I tell you,
I'm gonna lose you again.
Afraid, what is that...
I... I don't...
(Chuckles)
I... nothing is making sense.
Why do I know that house?
I think we better go sit down.
The reason that house
seems familiar to you
is because you grew up in it
till you were 4.
Marsha lived in that house?
No.
Just you.
But where was my mother?
You lived with Mama and Papa
till you were 2 months old.
Frank and I came up,
because Mama got sick.
But where was my mother?
You were like a gift.
You were the baby that
I couldn't have.
Where was my mother?
She left you, honey.
She left you with us,
but it was alright,
because we were a family.
No, no, no.
(Taking deep breaths)
No.
Why don't I remember that?
(Taking deep breaths)
But she came back for me?
She did come back.
Mama died
and she came to the service.
She saw how happy we were
and she wanted you back.
She left me for four years
and you let her
come in and take me?
There was nothing I could do
to stop her from taking you.
You should've tried harder.
You're right, I should've
told 'em she was crazy.
I should've lied.
I should've fought harder
for you.
But she was your mother,
there was nothing we could do.
You've known this
this whole time.
I've been here for months,
why didn't you tell me?
(♪♪♪)
(Taking deep breaths)
After your Grandpa died,
your mom wanted to sell
that house.
All of my good memories
are in it.
And for a long time I was hoping
you'd come home again.
Is that supposed to make me
feel better, Jean?
Hmm?
You're just like her.
(♪♪♪)
(Car starts)
MARSHA:
I'm n...
Well, your skin looks dry.
I can fix it.
Come on.
There you go.
Sorry, honey, my lunch date
is gonna be here any minute.
Jerry, and he is a keeper.
He's in the energy business
and I met him
at the downtown club happy hour.
That sounds promising.
Maybe, we'll see.
I guess it feels good
to finally know why
there weren't any baby photos
of me growing up.
I used to think it was,
because I wasn't pretty enough
or my clothes weren't right.
Alright, well, she told you.
Yeah, she told me.
And now you're mad at me.
Huh!
I'm not...
(Chuckles)
...mad at you.
Well, good, you shouldn't be,
because I was a child
with a child.
And anybody who knew me at 18,
knew that I was in no way ready
to raise a baby.
See I was not natural mama,
not like you.
But I came back.
You didn't,
you came back for a funeral.
Don't be a martyr, Libby.
You just sound like Jean,
Saint Jean.
This isn't about Jean,
this is about you and me
and the fact that
you didn't want me.
That's not true.
It just feels like you wanted
what Jean had.
Wow, well, that is ridiculous.
I want you to listen to me.
You just have to know that
I was a mess.
I was a mess
and I had to grow up.
Alright?
And then when Mama died,
I came back for you,
'cause I did the right thing.
Because you're mine.
You are my blood.
And... and I made sure that
you did not have to grow up
in that place.
- You were better off with me.
- Was I?
'Cause I'm not so sure.
And I just don't know
if I can forgive you
for taking me away from there.
(Inhales)
Because I was happy
and I think you knew it.
That is... is crazy.
- Mama, please...
- MARSHA: Libby, I was...
Stop.
You've gotta get ready.
You look really pretty.
Oh, come on.
(♪♪♪)
YOUNG
Frank, take her.
Okay.
Bye, baby.
(Sobbing)
(♪♪♪)
I'm sorry.
No more secrets.
There aren't anymore.
Promise?
It's the truth.
I wanna live here,
in this house
with Abby and Tank.
I'll run your farm
and I'll pay off of the top.
Alright.
This is my home.
Oh look, there's a bird's nest
up there.
I wonder if there's
any little eggs in there.
(♪♪♪)
- Hey.
- There you go.
Hey, what are you looking at?
(Sighs)
JEAN: That was Easter Sunday,
you lost a tooth that day.
- Oh.
- (Laughs)
That was a good day.
Is your dress blue?
Mhmm, yeah.
I remember.
JEAN:
Look how tiny you were.
You know what, I don't know
what we were doing there
while I was handling you.
Get all dirty.
(Indistinct speech)
What?
I don't know what we were doing
and I can't see.
(♪♪♪)
O'CONNOR: Are you even
good at fixing those?
When did that happen?
Oh, this?
A couple of days ago.
It was when I got back
from El Paso.
How'd that go?
I think it was for the best.
(Grunts)
So are you back on the payroll?
Yep.
- Kids are gonna freak out.
- O'CONNOR: Yeah?
Yeah, they really missed you.
O'CONNOR:
They did?
Yeah, they did.
What about you?
You missed me?
(Sighs)
(♪♪♪)
(Kissing)
No, not really.
Oh, that's too bad.
(Laughing)
♪ There's a universe
that can't be seen ♪
♪ Just a feelin'
if you know what I mean ♪
♪ Delectable dimension
undetectable by sight ♪
♪ Fill up your heart
in the dead of the night ♪
♪ Some say
it's an astral plane ♪
♪ Can't be described,
can't be explained ♪
♪ World exploded in love
all around me ♪
♪ And every time I take a look
around me ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ I have to smile
♪ Is our love
just an illusion ♪
♪ There's no need
to figure it out ♪
♪ Separation exists not
in your love-filled heart ♪
♪ All in your mind
♪ Real story's around you
♪ Even now it surrounds you
♪ Even now I feel the power
♪ World exploded in love
all around me ♪
♪ And every time I take a look
around me ♪
♪ I have to smile
(♪♪♪)