drones]
[bright tone]
Are you ready to go?
[audience cheering]
One minute, everybody.
Stand by, camera one.
[man speaking indistinctly]
[cheers and applause]
All right, here we go.
Six, five, four,
three, two...
[cheers and applause]
[dynamic rock music]
"Real Time" is Bill Maher
is bull's-eye.
It's simultaneously topical,
it's insightful,
it's controversial
and provocative,
but it's funny as hell.
Trump's got a big trip.
He's going to Saudi Arabia,
Israel, and the Vatican--
the cradles of America's
three great religions:
Christianity, Judaism, and oil.
[laughter]
When did it all go to shit?
[laughs]
When your first
sexual experience is with
your cousin or a goat,
you'na be up for grabs.
[laughter]
Have you ever had sex
with a Republican?
I don't know.
I don't get their names.
But what I'm interested in...
[laughs]
Bill focuses
on important topics
but shows that you don't have
to choose between
being entertained
or being educated.
You feel like you left here
learning something.
Yeah.
This is so--
so much better than television.
[laughter]
It takes pretty giant balls
to be that comfortable
with a political show
where you don't know
what's gonna come up...
I'm gonna run out of time
before we hit all the issues
that mightet y fired
from your next movie.
[laughs]
[laughter and applause]
How can such
a nice-looking person
be so screwed up inside?
[laughter and applause]
Could you move
further away from me, please?
Don't recoil, Bill!
[laughs]
These chairs have got
wheels on them for a reason.
He's an iconoclast
and a freethinker.
And he says things that no one
else would say in public.
He is outrageous.
I think he's irreverent
to the point
it drives me crazy.
Preach, Bill, preach.
[laughs]
And yet he's probably
the funniest guy around.
If America had a government
as good as its people,
it wouldn't look like this...
Further consideration
of HR-7-6-1...
It would look like this...
[indistinct shouting]
Oh, I touched the "politically
correct" nerve there.
There iso dot that corporations
own this country.
[laughs]
What?
The truth.
Yeah, I...
What he is on television
is authentic,
and if you are authentic,
theris huge power to that.
Start the clock.
[dynamic rock music]
For subtitling services, contatct:
waqas.zahoor89@gmail.com
Right here with me.
Hmm...
Bill Maher, Bill Maher.
Comedian?
I first met Bill
at Catch a Rising Star
in 1979.
Uh, Monday night
was audition night,
and it was up to the emcee--
and that particular night,
it was me--
uh, to decide who got passed
and--and who would get
to go on during the week
and start working
out of the club.
Bill auditioned, and having
the tremendous eye for talent
that I do, I said,
"Hey, you're terrific.
"Why don't--why don't you
and start working out here?"
Bill Maher has arrived.
An Ivy League education
is not enough for some people,
the call of the stage
too great.
We were doing a story
on an up-and-coming comic
at t time, and who knew
that 35 years later,
we'd wind up
in the same stable?
[applause]
I first saw him
on "The Tonight Show,"
and I thought,
"Well, who's this guy?"
My mother is Jewish,
and my father is Catholic.
That is the truth.
I was raised Catholic formally.
Although I must say,
the Jewish mind comes out
even in the Catholic system.
Uh, give you an example, uh,
we used to go into confession,
and I would bring
a lawyer in with me.
[laughter and applause]
[laughs] Thank you.
It's true. You know.
Bless me, Father,
for I have sinned.
I think you know Mr. Cohen.
[laughter]
You know, it's interesting
where comics start out
and where they end up.
Some end up in movies.
Some end up in sitcoms.
Some end up just being
concert performers, you know.
And--and Bill ended up becoming
this guy.
[cheers and applause]
Okay, well,
thank you,
and hi, I'm Bill Maher,
and this is
"Politically Incorrect."
"Politically Incorrect" was--
I was 35 or something
when I started it.
The idea was always--
from the beginning
and to this day--
to approximate...
what goes on in my life
when I'm just hanging out
with my friends.
I always saw the show
as a cocktail party
with the audience as just
one more friend.
All right,
fasten your seat belts
for a bumpy ride.
Let's get to the issues!
[laughs]
Put your thinking cap on.
All right.
43% of--
of Evangelical Christians
believe that the devil
is to blame
for the gay rights movement.
The--the other 57% think
it is the, uh,
high school music teachers.
That's...
[laughter and applause]
You've said that 1995
is the year of the penis.
What can we expect?
[laughs]
I support hunters having guns
'cause that increases the odds
of two rednecks
blowing each other's heads off.
[laughter]
You seriously think...
Wait a minute.
You're gonna run out of air?
I do.
I think there's a hole
in the ozone layer,
I think there's global warming,
I think the ice caps
are melting,
and when I die,
I'm blaming you.
I certainly had never seen
a show like it.
He was deliberately
being provocative
because he's always been
infuriated by the fear
of shaking it up...
I'm leaving.
[laughter]
Of saying things that,
"Oh my God, what if people
get upset by that?
[laughter]
Now, I myself do not have sex
with men or with little boys--
I'm not nearly that religious.
[laughter]
But...
[cheers and applause]
ThePartnershipke
for a Drug-Free America.
Can you imagine America
without drugs,
without their coffee,
without their amphetamines,
their diet pills,
their scotch, their Prozac,
their Valium?
This country is floating
in drugs.
This was sharp.
This was take no prisoners.
And I thought, in that sense,
it redefined
whatou could do with comedy
and with political commentary.
Chris, uh, how did you find
New Hampshire itself?
This is, I assume,
your first trip up there.
It's, um--it's--
This is America.
This is-- this is a really,
really, really white town.
This is, uh...
I'm having a real hard time...
Yeah.
Trying to find
hair care products here.
[laughter and applause]
Really...
[laughs]
[applause]
Bill's biggest influence
in comedy
has always been Johnny Carson,
and so Bill not only
admired the interviews,
not only admired the monologue,
but he also admired
Art Fern or Aunt Blabby.
Good evening.
I am the beautifu.
[laughter]
Certainly don't want
any violence.
Let's bring her out!
Monica! Monica!
[audience booing]
So we did sketches
for a long time
that kind of served to be
a bridge between
more traditional
talk-variety formats
and then the absolutely
revolutionary format
that we were moving toward.
Once New York starts
going down--
or LA, which is certainly
going down,
um, as we speak.
'Cause of the earthquake.
I get it.
[laughs]
Do you want to screw
Margaret Thatcher?
Yes or no.
There's your answer!
It's been-- it's been a while
since I've been with
a older white woman.
[laughter]
[laughs]
[applause]
"Politically Correct"
was a designed train wreck
Oh, yeah!
The whole point of the show
was that you were
putting together people
who shouldn't be
talking to each other.
Cool!
Janeane Garofalo
right over there!
Glad you can join us.
It's great to be here,
especially for me to be
back together
with all these nuts again, huh?
[laughs]
You will treat me
and every other woman
with respect...
I don't mean here.
And dignity!
And sometimes it--
it just revealed
what a crazy
Democratic nation we are,
where everyone gets a say.
And everyone did.
I'm sure you do.
And I am tired of the press
getting beat up.
Oh, of course you are,
'cause you are the most
hypersensitive people in
the United States of America.
[laughter and applause]
I loved that he would
bring in guests
from opposite ends
of the political spectrum
d everywhere in between,
and he could talk
to everyone and challenge them
or agree with them
and back up his opinion
with facts.
I always learned something
from watching his shows.
I'm a communist,
and I think that the people
should have control
over their own destiny...
By the way...
And over the profits...
Did you read any
of the history
of the 20th century?
'Cause they did try communism.
You defended the Menendez kids.
What do you care about facts?
ll, e, you absolutely
don't know anything
about the facts.
I knew they blew
their parents' heads off.
No, they didn't.
What did they do?
They--they, uh,
unloaded shotguns
in their direction,
but they didn't
blow their heads off.
[laughter]
Hey!
I distinctly remember
all the critics saying,
"This person is crazy.
"The one area you never
want to do
for entertainment--
that's poison--is politics."
[laughter]
And definitely don't have
your own opinions.
[laughs]
You know, definitely the host
was not supposed
to have opinions.
Isn't a religion just a cult
that doesn't have
to pay taxes,
and shouldn't it pay them?
What about suggesting
that parents watch their kids
instead of trying--
as we seem to be doing--
to childproof the world?
Does show business
turn people into jerks,
or are jerks attracted
to show business?
[laughter]
Who is writing this show?
This is unbelievable.
I just fell in love with him
fr that first day.
He was irreverent.
He said things that
you thought to yourself,
"Did he just say that?"
If being single was a disease,
I could listhe symptoms:
extra money, self-reliance,
and not needing
a special holiday to remind us
to get laid.
And then you said, "Yes,
he just said that."
And it was really,
really funny,
and then you realize
that it was also
really, really wise.
Now, America, we're told,
is a land where anybody
can grow up to be president,
but I think even Betsy Ross
would have added, "Yeah,
but for God's sake,
not Donald Trump."
[laughter]
From the beginning,
people thought
"Politically Incorrect"
was just a cute...
saying, but it's actually
something
that meant something to me.
The world
was too politically correct.
I still think the world
is too politically correct.
Now, that's not to say
that there aren't some areas
where we do evolve.
I've gotten a lot of mail
from women who say,
you ow"When you bring women
on the show"--
I very often have
a bad habit of--
a lot of times, I know them,
and I say, "Hey, beautiful,"
or some word like that.
Hey, baby.
How are you, baby?
Hiya, doll.
[applause]
How you been?
Oh, man,
you must be getting a lot.
Eh, you don't want
to talk about it here.
Hey, beautiful.
How you doing?
Nice to see you.
Go ahead.
[whists and applause]
I'm gonna miss doing that.
I like it, but I have
learned something:
if it hurts a woman,
just don't do it.
Doesn't matter--you don't have
to know why.
So I promise
I won't do it anymore.
It and it didn't mean cept
liberal or conservative.,
It just meant the opposite
of politically correct,
which was bullshit.
I always used to definit
the elevation
of sensitivity over truth.
This just in,
you are looking at,
obviously, a very disturbing
live shot there.
Th is the World Trade Center,
and we have unconfirmed reports
this morning that a plane
has crashed into one
of the towers
of the World Trade Center.
Six days after 9/11,
the president,
George Bush, had said,
"Unless you go back to doing
what you normally do,
the terrorists win."
I took that seriously.
Now, I hope, panel,
that you answer
with total candor,
because
political correctness itself...
is something we can
no longer afford.
Feelings are gonna get hurt
so that actual people won't.
And then the first show back,
you know, I was like
the guwho--first guy
on that beach landing
when the thing opens
when they hit the beach...
[mimics gunshot]
Bullet right there.
One of the themes
that we hear constantly
is that the people
who did this are cowards.
Not true.
Look at what they did.
First of all...
We're the cowards.
You have a whole bunch
of guys...
Right.
Who are willing
to give their life.
None of them backed out.
All of them slammed themselves
into pieces of concrete.
Exactly.
These are warriors.
Right.
Uh, and we have to realize
that the principles
of our way of life, uh,
are in--in conflict
with people in the world.
And so, I mean,
I'm all for understanding
the sociological causes
of this,
but we should not
blame the ctim.
American's shouldn't
blame themselves
'cause other people
want to bomb them.
But also, we-- we should make--
we have been the cowards
lobbing cruise missiles
from 2,000 miles away.
That's cowardly.
That--that is...
Staying in the airplane
when it hits the building--
say what you want about it,
not cowardly.
You're right.
After the fact,
people were sensitive,
and anybody that moved into
that sensitive territory was--
was going to pay the price.
ABC had no problems that night,
the night of the taping.
It only became
a line crossed later,
when conservative
morning disc jockeys
started getting
their listeners--
who maybe had never seen
"Politically Incorrect" --
to start calling advertisers
and get them
to drop the show.
In the new
cultural mind-set known as
"post-attack Ameri
it is no longer okay
to be politically incorrect,
even on a show
by the same name.
FedEx, Sears,
and General Motors
quickly pulled out
of the irreverent
late-night program.
You only get in trouble
for telling the truth.
Nobody gets in trouble
for lying
or making up crap,
but when you tell something
that's really true,
they go crazy and you're fired.
[tense music]
It's amazing to me
that you could be
literally sitting under a sign
that says
"Politically Incorrect"
and that you have actually
said to the audience,
"If you don't like edgy,
keep-it-real stuff,
do not watch this,"
and they still don't care
and still want you to go away.
That's what blows my mind
is that people
who don't watch you
still get to have a say
in whether you're on or not.
When people say, "Why don't you
run for office?"
or, "Why'd you get fired?"
Folks, let me sum it up
for you:
I think religion is bad
and drugs are good.
[laughter and applause]
I think America causes cancer,
longevity is less important
than fun,
and young people should be
discouraged from voting.
[laughter and applause
So... d young people should be
[laughs]ouraged from voting.
It's insane
that the only person
who lost their job after 9/11
was a comedian who hosted
a late-night
television program.
That was--and remains today--
bullshit.
[cheers and applause]
I was not planning to leave...
[laughing]
When I got fired.
It seemed like the worst thing
in the world at the time,
but it was the best thing.
[TV static drones]
[bright tone]
[cheers and applause]
[saucy pop music]
Oh, stop.
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
Stop!
Oh, please.
It says a lot
about his character
that he didn't try
to change whhe was,
and so he decided
to find a venue that would be
more amenable
to his kind of comedy
and his kind of authenticity.
And to HBO's credit,
they took a risk,
and they were rewarded
handsomely.
ct is that any enterprise
that excludes women
almost always descends
into sexual deviancy--
at least at my bathhouse.
[cheers and applause]
Whether it's the Boy Scouts,
the Penn State locker room,
or on Wall Street,
sooner or later, a bunch
of innocent folks get fucked.
[laughter]
Americans don't want privacy.
They want attention.
They'll put a camera
in their shower
and show it on the Internet.
You need three qualities,
really,
to be a--a great comedian.
One is that, obviously,
you have to be funny.
He's not just funny.
He's quick.
It never ceases to amaze me,
some of the stuff
that he can come out with
on the spot on that show.
Go, Bernie!
Bernie!
[cheers and applause]
[both laughing]
You are more popular
than Stormy Daniels' lawyer.
[laughter]
And you have to be smart,
which he is.
He--he can handle discussions
on a wide variety of subjects.
And the third quality, I think,
and that's really
iswhat sets him apart. ve,
I think all Americans would say
to the police everywhere,
"We want to support you,
"even to love you,
but you have to remember
"it says 'to protect and serve'
on the side of the car,
not 'what the fuck
are you okinat?'"
[laughter and applause]
We have been chosen here
at "Real Time"
to host the fifth annual
fall fundamentalist
fashion show.
[laughr]
And you are gonna love this.
Could we have our first model,
please?
This outfit just screams,
"Look out, world,
I'm a woman
of the 12th century."
[laughter]
There's really not
a lot of avenues
for, uh, people
who speak their mind
and really speak the truth
in the face of sometimes
a lot of adversity.
My sense of why people tune in
to watch Bill is,
they're watching a week
of crap, nonsense, craziness...
[laughter]
And they're--they're waiting
for someone smart,
funny, and interesting...
Wow.
And, you know, no bullshit
to make sense of it.
We don't need new ideas.
We need the balls to implement
the ideas we already know work.
Cut corporate welfare.
[cheers and applause]
Slash the defense budget.
Tax the rich.
Support the strong unions
that created a middle class
in the first place.
[cheers and applause]
I am very lucky
to work with people
who are incredibly funny,
smart, uh, dedicated,
nice--
much nicer than me--
and the favorite part of my day
is the writers' meeting.
Every time I walk into
the writers' meeting,
it's been the same.
I walk in there
with a look on my face
like my mother just died...
because one time, she did.
[laughs]
And so I never want them
to know if something bad
is going on in my life.
And the other reason I do it
is because
I want to be a tough crowd
for those writers
and producers.
I-I know that
when they make me laugh--
'cause I'm pretty jaded--
then we got something.
What defense spending really is
is a giant welfare program,
a jobs program
for defense workers
to build crap we don't need...
You know, there's basically
two kinds of talk shows.
There's entertainment ones--
you know, the ones
on late night--
and then there's
the cable news shows,
but this is not like
either one of those.
It's totally original format.
Here's how Sean Spicer
explained alternative facts.
He said it's like
the weather report.
One weather report comes out
and says it's gonna be cloudy.
Another says there's gonna be
light rain.
No one lied to you.
Yeah, you know, sometimes
weathermen do disagree
on what the weather's
gonna be like tomorrow.
But not on what it was like
yesterday!
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
I think, as the show
has evolved, it's hit upon
a terrific structure
with the short monologue,
then the interview
with a single guest,
then the panel,
then someone comes out
in the middle of the panel
to kind of give it
a little bit of a bump,
and then you end
on a crescendo
with "New Rules."
New rule: I don't care
if Henry Kissinger
is a war criminal
when he starts melting.
[laughter]
You don't just there
and make vagina hands.
[laughter]
New rule: you can't look
at the before and after
and tell me these two
didn't do it on the ane.
New rul[laughter]'t look
at the before and after
New rule:
Sarah Huckabee Sanders
has to try to look
a little less
like the roommate who comes
to the door and says,
"She doesn't want to see you."
[laughter]
"New Rules" is genius.
If something can make you laugh
and also keep you engaged,
it's pretty great television.
New rule: since our new
national position
on science is, "Screw it,
we prefer witchcraft..."
[laughter]
Let's not just retire
the space shuttle "Atlantis."
Let's drive it to one
of the five stupidest states
and have the locals
beat it with sticks.
[laughter]
New rule: The people--
oh, you're not gonna like
this one...
[lghs]
The people who participate
in the ultra-Orthodox
atonement ritual of kaparot,
where you swing a live chicken
over your head three times
and read Bible passages
while someone else
holds a baby...
have to look me in the eye
and tell me
there's not some point
in the ceremony
where you're thinking,
"What the fuck are we doing?"
[laughter]
[laughs]
Okay, new rule:
if the tabloids are going
to continue to call
these two "Kimye"
and these two "Billary"
and these two "J-Rod,"
they must refer to these two
as "Shitstorm."
[laughter and applause]
My favorite pais the e.
It's sort of Bill
in his full intensity.
You feel like
watching the eclipse.
You know, you have
to wear glasses
because sometimes
it's so intense.
This country
is in quite a pickle.
Conservatives govern
without shame,
and liberals shame
without goveing.
Conservatives govern
[cheers and applause]
Some of them
are enormously complex.
And, as always,
they are very ballsy,
and they're very honest.
When did the American dream
become this pathwayndent,
this economic death spiral
where workers get paid
next to nothing
so they can only afford
to buy next to nothing
so business are forced
to sell cheaper
and cheaper shit?
Walmart employees can only
afford to shop at Walmart.
McDonald's workers can only
afford to eat at McDonald's.
And Hoers itresses
have to wear shirts
they grew out of years ago.
[laughter]
Europe and Latin America,
they take a break every day
between noon and 3:00,
and they call it a siesta.
But let's face it.
[laughter and applause]
They're fucking in the day,
and we're not.
[laughter]
Bill's editorials
are a lot like the show--
that it's this blend
of passion,
politics, and insights
but then also humor.
Now the white supremacists
are the federal government.
And it's liberal states
that are under siege
from federal overreach.
We're trying to defend
our way of life here
and what we believe in.
We believe in sanctuary cities
and pollution controls...
[cheers and applause]
And legalized pot
and gun control
and Obamacare and a woman's
right to choose,
and we're going to defend them.
theebels now!
[cheers and applause]
There's a specific group
of Americans out there
whose name I won't mention,
but it begins with "tea"
and ends with "baggers"...
[laughter]
No, in America,
when a man puts something
in another man,
it had better be a bullet.
[laughter]
There's only one thing
conservatives believe in more
than work, and that's
the God-given right
of rich people to leave
all their money to their kids
so they never have to work
a day in their lives.
[laughter and applause]
Meanwhile, on the other side
of the world,
this man--
ex-KGB agent Vladimir Putin,
AKA Vlad Bat
AKA The Bodfather...
[laughter]
Is looking to install a stooge
in the country he still hates.
But who?
Who's desperate
and dumb enough?
[sighs]
And the dience,
all of their defenses
are coming down.
All of their force fields
are lowered.
"Oh, this is fun.
I like this man.
He's making me laugh."
And then he--when those
force fields are down,
en he zaps them.
We tell our children
they don't have to fix
their flaws
because it's the world's job
to accept everything
about them and love it.
Like they say on reality shows,
the most important thing
is just you doing you.
But what if you
is a big asshole?
[laughter and applause]
He really sets up the argument
in a very logical way,
uh, like a procuto
and at the same time
makes you laugh.
That's an incredible gift.
I don't know
the exact definition
of white privilege,
but being able to talk about
grabbing pussies
and how big your dick is
and still getting
elected president--
that's gotta come close.
[with Southern accent]
You know, uh, we don't need
no outside agitators...
[laughter]
With their "Make America
Great Again" caps
coming in here
to our clean state
and telling uso ta down
our solar panels...
[laughter]
Or how to treat our interns.
Here in our state,
we use tiki torches
they way they're supposed
to be used--
for lesbian weddings
on the beach.
[laughter and applause]
After the show is over,
I start to go over it
in my mind:
"Oh, I should have said this.
Oh, I shouldn't have
said that."
That's why I love
the editorial,
because I get to work on it
all week long.
Sometimes I put in 12, 15 hours
to make five or six minutes,
but I get to say it
exactly the way I want
to say it,
and it's always something
that no one else is saying
and we make it funny,
and, uh...
that's--that's my joy.
[laughter]
Ready, four.
And take.
One of the ways in which
our show is unique
is that we have almost
a true hour on air
completely uninterrupted
by commercials,
so Bill is doing
this obstacle course
every week,
which is incredible.
We think of Megyn Kelly
as the sane one
over there at Fox News.
That's just because
she's surrounded
by Hannity and Bill O'Reilly.
She's like the blonde
dragon girl
on "Game of Thrones."
Everyone else is a zombie
or a dwarf
or fucking their sister,
so she looks normal.
[laughter]
If you think
about the monologues
of the late-night shows
that sometimes have politics,
it was all very tame,
very bland, and that--
that stuff came out
of the Bob Hope era,
if you will.
This was a whole
different thing.
Anytime someone
prefaces a statement
by saying, "I'm not a racist,"
some racist shit is about
to come out of them.
Now, I mean...
He wanted to outlaw blow jobs,
and he lost single women
in the state by 43 points.
But listen to this.
He won married women
by nine.
[laughter and applause]
And...
that is all I need
to know about marriage.
That's--that's all I'm saying.
The budget director also said
about the new budget
that the after-school
meals program--gone.
You know, I've always
said this.
You want Republicans
to care about kids,
you're gonna just have
to jam them back in the uterus.
[laughter]
There's almost nothing
on televisn
that goes out live-live
with no tape delay
and they can't bleep you;
you can say anything you want.
And I think that kind of
edge of danger
is very good for thshow
and I think
it's very good for him.
A lot of shows are like a play,
where there's a script
and it gets rehearsed
over and over
and then it gets taped.
And our show is more like
a sporting event,
where there are umpires,
there's--there's spectators,
there's one team,
there's the other team,
and then once the game begins,
nobody knows exactly
what's going to happen.
I'm sorry, but it's time
for a comedy bit.
Okay.
augh [mimics cracking]
[laughter]
[speaking indistinctly]
Can I use this for a second?
[laughter]
Being on "Real Time,"
it's like the most interesting
dinner party you ever had
with people that
you don't know very well
but you know of them.
And it's
a fascinating conversation,
and then you realize
it's all taking place
on a high wire 100 stories
above the ground,
and one false move
and you're cooked.
The Obama administration
really has to stop
completely blaming everything
on its predecessor completely.
And I really--
I'm sick of hearing,
"Oh, well, we were handed this.
We were handed this."
I know.
Everyone knows,
but we need to move on.
You think that's
what Obama's doing?
You think he's doing that?
I do, to a degree.
Not nearly enough.
Ronald Reagan
blamed Jimmy Carter every day
for eight years.
[cheers and applause]
No--and in the speech--
in the speech,
what President Bush said--
one of the things
he's had to adjust to...
Yeah, I wasn't born yet,
so I don't know.
Well, that's...
[laughs]
I-I wasn't born during
the French Revolution,
but know about it.
[cheers and applause]
[indistinct chatter]
It comes out this week
that Reince Priebus
was talking to the FBI--
he's the chief of staff.
That really is booze.
No, it's not.
[laughs]
You wish it was
after I finish this question.
[laughs]
Things that are in the Bible
that if we took it
literally true:
uh, "slaves must
submit themselves
to their masters,
no matter how harsh."
Right--right off the bat,
we're believing in slavery.
[audience murmurs]
Well...
[laughter]
Bill's success is that
you gotta come prepared.
There are no free passes.
Uh, he's not interested
in sycophants.
He's not interested
in the pabulum
of usual exchange.
You gotta bring your "A" game.
This is a tough guy
to argue with.
[laughs]
But I mean, look...
[stammering]
Okay, so, Bill, listen...
Hey, if it makes you
feel better, I feel like
I'm in high school again,
where I'm just sitting there
like, "I'm not passing
this class."
[laughter]
You always have said to me,
"I'm too stupid
to do your show."
No, no, I-- no, I didn't say--
Have you gotten smarter?
No, sadly.
I saw you a while ago,
and you said something
that changed it, and you said--
I think it was a compliment--
you said, "Oh, are you kidding?
We have guests
much stupider than you."
[laughter]
Listen, they gave me
water tonight.
I got nothing.
I know. I know.
Maybe you got his booze.
Is that what he said?
Could we get Darrell Issa's,
uh, Jack Daniels for...
Let's deal with serious issues.
I know.
You know, fuckups
are fuckups, but when you
don't bring Seth MacFarlane
his liquor...
You're wondering why
he's so quiet right now.
It's not gonna be
a good show.
You know it.
[applause]
Thank you so much.
Most other shows,
you only get people
to talk real once you get
off the set into the greenroom,
and what Bill has managed to do
is get the greenroom
conversation on the set.
What is it you never liked
about men?
No, I'm just kidding.
[laughter]
[smooches]
There you go.
[gravelly voice]
That's messed up.
[laughter]
Never thought I'd hear
Tucker Carlson say
"tapping her."
[stammering]
He was involved--
he was involved with her
when she was underage.
No, no, you were right.
Tapping.
[overlapping chatter]
You came out.
Um, George Takei--
Mr. Sulu...
[overlMm-hmm. atter]
Also came out.
Is it something with the ship?
[laughter]
Before the crash,
I had most of my savings
Lehman Brothers.
Ah.
I don't have a question.
I just want you to hold me.
[laughter]
Took me forever
to get you here,
but I knew it would happen.
Well, I had to start reading.
Yeah.
You...
[laughter]
Our show is the hardest show
on television to do.
You can't just come on
and give the same
talking points you give
on other shows.
Even celebrities have
to be on their feet with Bill.
He doesn't treat them
any differently
than his other guests.
I say this as a friend...
[laughs]
And as someone who I think
has impeccable credentials
as a stoner.
[laughter]
You smoke too much pot.
[laughs]
You smoke...
You are the most gorgeous
old lady in the world.
[cheers and applause]
You're beautiful.
You went to Haiti.
You went to Cuba.
You went to Venezuela,
Iran, Iraq.
What's wrong with you?
[laughter]
Is that why
you're on this show?
I can't...
[laughs]
I'm not sure why
I'm on this show
There is a litany of things
out there that can kill you,
but it--you...
Hair dye.
Oh, absolutely.
Come on.
But people--here's...
[laughter]
How many of your guests
have stalked off?
[laughter]
I just called him
a bad motherfucker.
[laughter]
I been waiting to use that word
on television
for, what, 15 years.
I know you're concerned
about bad language.
I tried to clean that up
for you tonight.
I'm telling you,
that could have been worse.
It usually is.
[laughs]
It is a great feeling
of freedom
when you can say anything
and they're like,
"No, say anything."
I mean, you know, you--
you could be a diva
and you're not.
First of all,
people who say they're divas...
I--you're not a diva.
I think--I'm pretty sure
you're a cunt.
Can I say that?
[laughter]
It is a dirty show,
but it's not really my fault.
The world is dirty,
the people are dirty,
and especially
some of the people
in your party are dirty.
[cheers and applause]
Politicians are reticent
to go on Bill's show,
and, you know, I think
that maybe they should be.
You know, God forbid
you say something funny
or controversial.
You give Street speeches?
Yes.
The--the author
of Dodd-Frank
with your name on the bill?
And I talk to them
for the same reason I'm here--
I'll be arrogant--
I'm interesting.
So people pay...
[laughs]
People pay to hear me talk.
So when the sea levels rise...
tammering] Obviously,
we could lose, like,
Venice.
We could lose Florida.
And who would know better
about losing Florida?
[laughter]
I just--I...
"Real Time"
is totally unpredictable,
and that's terrifying
to a lot of politicians.
When I told my third daughter
that I was gonna be
on your show, she, uh, said,
"Oh, my God, have you
completely lost your mind?"
[laughs]
Oh, come on, pal.
That's just bullshit.
Bill, I think you're
fading out here.
I-I'm not sure
I can hear the question.
Just wondering who
on my staff agreed
to accept this gig.
[laughter]
Will the next generation
of politicians
act differently
because their entire lives
will be documented on some sort
of online platform?
I think that's already--
I think we all--I mean...
Oh, look at the time.
I gotta get home.
[laughter and applause]
Taxi.
There's not a time
I come on here where
my political folks
are enthusiastic.
Uh, they're always
very pessimistic
about the outcome.
[laughter]
I remember, actually,
one time where I got there
and Bill said, "Ralph Nader
"is gonna be on the show.
one time where I got there
and I've got an idea."Nader
Michael and I are going
to get down on our knees
and beg you not to run.
Please.
[cheers and applause]
If there's a little
uncertainty there...
[indistinct chatter]
You know, something can happen.
[laughs]
I'm always telling people
who say two men
can't make a baby,
"Anything is possible for God."
Like, I'm nna ep
inseminating my husband
and keep my fingers crossed.
[laughter]
Maybe...
And, uh...
[speaking indistinctly]
Let's try to not make
these guys thr upin their moute
than already have.
I think it's always more fun
having the conservative guests
and having that--
that back and forth.
Uh, in fact, that's what makes,
I think, the show work.
I agree with you about labels,
but I notice you're sitting
in front of a billboard
that says "Runaway Slave."
I don't have time
to go through all of his lies.
We only have an hour.
Uh, but let's...
I can bat them all down.
Go.
I think you're a great guy.
I really hope you lose
your next election,
because I think
the world about...
I think you're colossally wrong
on a numbehings...
That's okay.
But if--exactly.
If I--if I banned everyone
from my show
who I thought was
colossally wrong,
I would be talking to myself.
I think it's important--
especially when you think
someone is dangerous--
to expose that
to as manyeoe as you can.
So giving someone like Milo
or Alex Jones, um,
or Anne Coulter a platform,
that's a public service.
You id after 9/11
what we should do
is attack Muslim countries,
kill their leaders,
and convert them
to Christianity.
Yes.
Do you still--
do you still stand by
that moderate position?
Absolutely fantastic policy.
I haven't heard a better one.
I love people
who stick by their guns
even when the crowd
does not agree.
I do think that there is
an element of racism
against white individuals.
I-I do.
I do see it.
I think it's been evidenced.
Well, since--
since I'm a conservative
and not a Trump person,
let me just say this:
that's absurd.
That's fucking crazy.
The pope made
a very strong statement
in support of my position
on climate change.
Not yours.
And your position,
when you heard that, was,
"Hey, let's leave the science
to the scientists."
Okay, first of all,
you're not doing that.
But second of all...
Oh--oh, I am.
You're not, because 97%
of all scientists believe...
It's a bogus number.
It's so not a bogus number.
It's so a bogus number.
Okay, yours is. Mine is.
Yours is. Mine is.
[laughter]
This show, like none other,
provides an opportunity
to articulate
deeply held beliefs,
cherished ideas
in the face of people
who are radically skeptical
about them.
[audience jeering]
ld on, Relax, liberal audience.
Let him get his bullshit out
before you boo him!
[laughter]
Thank you for having me
on this show
to present, uh, the other side,
but not every network
does that all the time.
This might be
the only place in the world
where we'd ever meet.
Right.
[laughter]
Everyone knows that
he gives people room to breathe
and he gives people
their time to talk
and make their point, um,
and he will give you your space
to do that.
But then when you look
at the Democrats,
you--you see who's up
against this guy.
This unbelievably useless,
terrible candidate
of Hillary Clinton.
I feel liberated to say
whatever I believe
and some of that is not
very popular.
I've gotten booed
several times by the audience.
Bill is clearly
someone who's a liberal,
but he's not a party-line guy.
You don't do your
political viewpoint,
party ideology any service
if you assume
they're always right.
Obama was against
gay marriage in 2008.
Does he have to resign?
Hillary came around
just last year.
Can she be president?
You can't purge everybody
who doesn't evolve
exactly on the timetable
you did.
remds me of the immigrant
who's been in America
for all of a year
and looks at someone
who came over last week like,
"Huh.
Boat people, am I right?"
[laughter]
Bill picks up on things
that the rest
of the press drops.
I'll be wondering,
"Why aren't people talking
abt this subject
or that subject?"
And sure enough, Bill gets it.
It'll be on his next show.
Denying racism
is the new racism.
Would you agree that there is
some sort of a medical,
pharmaceutical,
food industry complex
that are--where there's
a lot of profit
in getting us sick
and a lot of profit
in selling us pills that
don't really get us better?
[cheers and applause]
Um...
[clears throat]
It can't be the duty
of every American
to say something
if they see something,
except for the people
whose job it is
to do something.
When...
[cheers and applause]
When--when cops ask minorities
why they don't snih
on their own,
minorities have every right
to say,
"You first."
And...
[applause]
After a shooting,
Bill was the first one,
I think, on air to say,
"It's not enough
to say thoughts and prayers."
I'm so sick
of all the reactions.
I'm so sick of thoughts
and prayers.
First of all...
[applause]
[laus]
Thoughts are the opposite
of prayers.
[laughter]
[applause]
A thought is, "What should do?
A prayer is wishing on a star.
Thoughts and prayers are
the Republican way of saying,
"Tough shit."
Uh...
You know, I-I think--
I'm sure I was the first one
to call Bill
an American treasure on--
on my radio show...
[laughs]
And I meant it.
Uh, mostly because
the comedy is one thing,
but, um, taking on religion
is, uh, something else.
In your album, you say,
"Religion, question religion.
Question it all."Well.
You been watching me,
haven't you?
[laughs]
Religion is a bunch
of bullshit, and it's, uh...
That's what I wanted to hear
from you.
[laughs]
Good to see you, Bill.
Bill, ink,
has a slightly darker view
of all religion,
and so it's not surprising
that he has
a slightly darker view
of Islam,
and I understand that.
The trouble began on the set
of "Realime with Bill"
when author Sam Harris
and host, Maher, suggested
more liberals needed
to speak out
about Muslims' freedom
to peacefully practice
religion.
Islam at this moment
is the mother lode
of bad ide Jesus.
So we have--we have...
That's just a fact.
It's--it's not a fact.
It is a...
It's an ugly thing to say.
How about the more
than a billion people
who aren't fanatical,
who don't punish women,
who just want to go to school,
have some sandwiches,
five times a day,
and don't do any of the things
that you're saying
all Muslims do...
No, wait, wait, wait.
And stereotyping--
I'm not saying all Muslims--
Affleck heating up
as the conversation
quickly turned
to a fierce debate
about jihadists' role in Islam,
the video reaching
over 3 million views
online alone.
Women as equal citizens, um,
complete acceptance
of gay people,
uh, the ability to join
another religion
or have no religion.
If you are a liberal,
these are basic
human rights ideas
that you have to stand behind.
You know, most Muslims
around the world
uAmerican Muslims do
to practice the religion
any way they want,
and American liberals
should make that their cause
instead of conflating
criticizing a religion,
which is legitimate,
with bigotry,
which it is not.
We are never going
to, uh, defeat terrorism
if we don't reform Islam.
Yes.
And we are not going
to reform Islam
if we can't talk about it.
And if Muslims
can't talk about it.
Political correctness,
by and large,
narrows the argument
and locks you in
to identity politics
and all sorts of things
you're not allowed to say
or think because they're
off the table,
no matter how legitimate
or insightful they might be.
I saw a meme going around
the Internet last week
when it was
International Women's Day,
and it said,
"A woman should be...
whatever the fuck she wants."
[cheers and applause]
So...
liberals, you can applaud that,
or you can pretend
this is just a fashion trend.
You just can't do both.
There's a lot of ideas,
I think,
that were not mainstream
when we first started
to talk about them
that have become mainstream.
Atheism, you know,
being single is no wor tha,
marijuana...
I never met a mean pothead.
I've met a mean drunk,
a mean drug addict,
but every pothead--
even the stupid ones are nice.
I mean...
Right.
And--and I know it's supposed
to cure anxiety--
I prefer poppers, myself--
t however, if...
[laughter]
I know.
And it doesn't make you stupid.
Look at you.
[laughs]
[laughter]
Almost no one
comes out and says,
"I smoke weed," on TV,
even though God knows
how many millions
of people do every day.
Millions of Americans
are still trapped
in a no-man's-land
where a pot dispensary
can sell you weed
if you have a "card"
from a "doctor"...
[laughter]
Who certifies
that you have a "disease,"
which is just
"d't a, don't tell"
for pot smokers.
And...
[applause]
And it creates a culture
of dishonesty
that gives a bad name
to people like me
who genuinely suffer
from whatever it is
I told them I had.
You have given it up for
about a year and a half now...
Yeah.
Uh, and, uh,
I think that's great.
When we were in, uh, Hawaii
last year, in solidarity--
I didn't want to temp you,
so I didn't do it around you
when--when we were together--
but you were one
of tneers.
And I'm not gonna try
to get you back on the wagon
at all, uh, but I just want
to show you--
no, no, I just want
to show you some pictures
to reminisce.
Here's us this last year
in Hawaii
after with Jeff Ross, p pot,
and, you know, you look, uh...
you look okay but not ecstatic.
And, uh--
But here's the year before
when we were
completely baked, all right?
I'm just saying...
[laughter and applause]
But, uh...
That's a strong case.
That's a...
[laughs]
Maybe I should, uh...
[cheers and applause]
I thought,
"Is he allowed to do this?"
You know?
"Is he gonna get arrested?"
Please remember...
[coughing]
[laughter]
Please remember
that legalizing pot is a lg wa
from a done deal.
I know you're tired--
I am too--
of making the same old
obvious pot arguments,
like how pot is less dangerous
than other legal
adult activities,
but somehow,
you can drink alcohol;
you can smoke cigarettes;
you can do that thing
where you cut off your oxygen
with a belt and masturbate...
[laughter]
Which is not only dangerous,
but take it from me,
it'll get you kicked out
of Macy's menswear like that.
[laughter]
I'm not gonna see
Chuck Todd do that
on "Meet the Press."
That's...
[laughs]
I mean, where are you
gonna e that?
And...
see that person back
on the air next week.
[laughs]
Well, that's one
of the things he criticizes
Democrats for--
that they were late to pushing
for marijuana legislation
and late to pushing harder
on gay marriage.
And he was right out there.
I never understand why
the gays want marriage.
I always thought the hip thing
aboubeingay
was that you couldn't
get married.
[laughter]
Which is why you live
more of a gay lifestyle
than I do.
Hello.
[laughter]
If homosexual marriage
comes flooding in,
we will all be losers.
It's going to undermine
the future civilization.
Isn't this a flood
that you can't stop
no matter how hard you try
to put your finger in the dike?
[laughter]
He's been one
of the most pro-gay forces
in popular culture, and I think
he's more effective than most
'cause he's not
some simpering lefty
LGBTQRS kind of guy.
[laughs]
Where is the Democrat
who will stand up and go beyond
the half measures
of civil union
and, "Hate the sin,
love the sinner,"
and say loud and clear,
"There is no sin"?
It's not an abomination,
and no one can control
how Cupid aims his arrows.
And the ones who pretend
they can usually turn out
to be the biggest freaks.
[cheers and applause]
Another thing
about the show is, you know,
you get a sense some people
play to an audience,
including literally
their audience.
You don't get that, uh,
on Bill's show.
I mean, he'll challenge
the aud--
I think he enjoys
challenging the audience.
You know who's superstitious
about Friday the 13th?
Republicans.
They say the country
is having bad luck
because we let a black cat
in the White House.
[audience groans]
What the fuck was wrong
with that joke?
[laughter]
If the audience groans
or thinks a joke is too far,
he takes them on.
He doesn't ignore it.
Oh, go fuck yourself.
I mean, really.
An obvious joke.
Don't start groaning.
I'll go fucking nuts
on you today.
You can see, I am right
on the edge here.
Oh, nothatas fucking funny.
What is wrong with you people?
Fuck you, with the "boo."
What is the booing?
It's gonna be rough unless
you get that stick out
of your ass right now.
My relationship
with the audience
is the relationship of my life.
Kids?
I don't have time for kids.
I've got to reite this e.
[laughter]
It's always where I put
my energy.
It's what I love the most.
That's my truth.
That's the way I was born.
That's what my body
is telling me to do
and always has.
It's why I've always
eated e audience
like they're my friend--
and I mean a real friend.
I trust them enough
to say things
they may not want to hear.
We don't agree on everything,
and we don't have to,
because friends don't
leave each other over that.
We even fight sometimes,
because honesty is love,
and friends don't
bullshit each other.
The night that people
heckled him--
these hecklers kept
interrupting his show...
See, this is the problem
sometimes with...
[man shouting indistinctly]
Hey, do we have
some fucking security
in this building...
[laughs]
Or do I have to come over
and kick this guy's ass
out of here?
Would you get the fuck out
of my building?
Hey, hey.
Out! Out!
I just remember
that he had guts, balls.
I was impressed.
This isn't towa caucus!
[laughs]
Okay?
It's not a debate!
It's a debate between us.
You're in the audience.
"Audience" comes from the Latin
"to listen."
[laughter and applause]
What's going on here?
If you're watching,
you don't for one second think
that anything's been altered
to get a rating
or to get anyone's approval,
and I think that's
powerful television.
Before we go on further
with this topic,
we never really got to
the presidential campaign
last week,
and Donald Trump entered,
and I just want to--
weever really discussed it,
and I have to say--
I want to ask you two,
especially,
because I hear all over
the media, "He's just a joke.
"It's just a--it's just
a publicity stunt.
Don't worry about it.
It'll go away."
It's not going away.
Yeah.
I don't think that
Donald Trump's gonna stay
at the poll--stay at the top
of theollsor very long.
I do.
I really don't think so.
He makes everybody else
look like a midget.
Not in a good way,
but you know what?
ke, here-- here's the thing
about Donald Trump.
He never apologizes.
He's never wrong.
No matter what crazy thing
he says, he's totally--
He's the white Kanye.
[laughter]
But isn't this just a promotion
for "Celebrity Apprentice"?
I mean, really.
No.
That's what I think!
No, no.
No, you're wrong.
A lot of people,
in the beginning,
either saw Trump
as just funny
and didn't see the danger,
or journalists saw him
as dangerous
and did not see the funny.
I think Bill was the first guy
to see both.
I certainly don't want
to be shitting on Donald Trump
all night.
[laughter]
Why not?
Oh, I'm just kidding.
Believe me, there's plenty
more shitting to come.
[laughs]
Did you watch Tuesday?
Oh, he is--he is getting
a lot closer
to wrapping up the apocalypse.
I have seen this guy
change his position
from the beginning
to the end of a sentence.
Yeah.
"All I know
is what's on the Internet"?
This guy's gonna change
America's symbol
from the bald eagle
to a turtle fucking a shoe.
[laughter]
Where are the other Republicans
to condemn this?
When are they going to say,
"Look, I get it.
"We handcuffed ourselves
to this deadker
but at some..."
[laughter]
They see him as a strong
alpha man...
Yes.
Which is amazing to me,
'cause he's such
a whiny little bitch.
[all chanting]
Whiny little bitch.
[cheers and applause]
If there's anything scarier
than the fact
that Donald Trump thinks
he's the most important person
in the world,
it's that in eight months,
he could be.
Mm!
[applause]
New rule: Donald Trump
must immediately submit
to DNA tests to determine...
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
[clears throat]
To determine whether
he is, in fact, the love child
of a human woman
and an orangutan
from the Brooklyn Zoo.
[laughter]
Donald Trump was going after
President Obama,
pretending President Obama
wasn't born in America--
which was nonsense
and, I think, code language
to people with
racial prejudices
to tell them, "You don't
really have to honor
"the African-American
president.
It's okay.
He's not really one of us."
So Bill called him on it.
But given your face,
your physique,
your intelligence level,
and, of course, your hair...
[laughter]
The American deserve
some real proof
that your mother did not
spend most nights
in 1945
covering her body
in banana oil,
sneaking into the monkey cage,
and compulsively humping
an orange-haired ape.
[laughter]
Somebody had to say that.
[laughs]
He called me and he said,
"You know, maybe it would
make a good column for you
because Donald Trump
is suing me."
You're suing Bill Maher.
Yes, and my friends
at "Fox and Friends"
have it first.
Yeah, I'll sue him
about 12:00 today.
For how much?
For million,
all going to charity.
His lawyer sent me a letter.
I shit you not, this is real.
[laughter]
His lawyer sent me a letter
that says, and I quote...
[laughter and applause]
Bill will speak truth to power.
He will speak truth
to billionaires.
That's what's needed right now.
This may surprise you,
but I am not a big fan
of Rush Limbaugh.
[laughter]
However, if you're one
of the people with a website
devoted to making him go away,
you are part of the problem.
And, ironically,
you're not even
a proper liberal
because you don't get
free speech.
I'm telling you, this is gonna
be the death of liberals,
this nitpicky,
intramural attacking of friends
for insufficient purity,
compulsively cleaning up
a little corner theoom
that's already quite clean...
[laughter]
While there giant piles
of shit everywhere else.
[laughter and applause]
One of the reasons
I admire Bill
is that he says, "Screw that.
"Yes, I am liberal, but I'm not
"politically correct.
"I'm not in chains--
in the chains
of political correctness."
In a world where it's
too politically correct,
people go to some jackass
because, oh, it is a breath
of fresh air
from political correctness.
Donald Trump came along--
and he wasn't the first,
but obviously,
he was sort of
the most significant--
and said, "Okay,
if we currently live
"in a world where everything
is offensive,
I'm gonna create one
where nothing is."
And people defended that
as standing athwart
political correctness.
Now, that's not
what he was doing,
but because
political correctness
had gotten so absurd, he--
it really did allow him
to sort of jump off the cliff.
I'm sorry to have
to kind of be the--
the buzzkill here so early on,
but I think Trump is gonna win.
I-I'm sorry.
[audience booing]
You know what?
Yeah.
Boo if you want.
I am glad you're saying it.
Everybody should say that--
I don't want to say it.
No, no, the--the enemy
is complacency.
Yeah.
But you could tell
he was really raw...
and concerned,
and it's like he knew something
that no one else did.
And I didn't think
for a chance...
that his concerns
were accurate.
I'm gonna be honest with you.
I've had a couple of drinks.
[laughter]
I'm gonna be honest with you.
You've had more
than a couple of drinks.
[laughter]
I really have.
I mean, I'm shitting
in my pants
because, you know...
[laughs]
Let me take you back
a couple of years.
First they said--
everybody said
that Donald Trump,
when he talks about running
fopresident,
"Oh, he's just saying that."
Just saying that because
he wants to, you know,
burnish his brand
and get people
to buy his books or whatever.
Okay.
Then he announced
he was gonna run.
They said, "Well, sure,
he's a reality show star...
"and people think
that's interesting,
but he's not gonna get
any votes."
Then he got votes.
Then he-nd tn they said,
"He's not gonna win
any primaries."
Then he won primaries.
Then they said, "But he's not
gonna win the nomination."
Then he won the nomination.
And now these same people
are saying,
"He's not gonna win
the election."
Yeah, he could win
the election.
This is CNN breaking news.
Donald Trump will be
the 45th president
of the United States.
I mean...
[laughs]
They're gonna get rid
of Obamacare,
probably get rid
of Roe versus Wade.
So you know what?
Enjoy your victory,
Trump voters,
'cause when you're dying
because you don't have
health insurance
to treat the inftionou got
from a back-alley abortion
you had to get
'cause of fetal lead poisoning,
you can say to yourself,
"At least I didn't vote
for someone with
a private email server."
[cheers and applause]
It's interesting,
'cause sometimes
you'll watch the show
and he'll--
they'll be talking about
a particular subject
and you go...
[stammering]
You want everybody
to be watching this.
I ce read the list
of things that Trump does
that sound like
a third world dictator.
Uh, you put your name
on buildings.
You appoint your family members
to positions of power.
Your rallies are scary.
[laughter]
Yote the press and talk about
jailing reporters.
Uh, you want missile parades.
He doesn't have one,
but he wants one.
Uh, you use the ofce
for financial gain.
You love other dictators.
Does anyone agree with me
that he is not going
to leave until
he wants to leave,
including the 2020 election?
He'll probably be reelected.
52% of Republicans
would support postponing
the 2020 election
if Trump proposed it.
He takes their side
and not ours.
That's a traitor.
He calls you a lowlife.
You, who spent your life
defending this country,
especially after 9/11.
He's not on our side.
I know this is a comedy show,
and I'm gonna try
to keep it on that level,
but it's not fucking funny.
There is a slow-moving
right-wing coup...
going on.
Media, do your fucking job.
[cheers and applause]
Our job is to get
the information out
as best we can, and--
and start to mobilize people
to think.
And you can do it
with laughter, but you have
to do it with intelligence
behind it,
and that's what, I think,
Bill does brilliantly.
You can un-friend someone
whose politics you don't like,
but you can't un-friend
47% of America.
Roommates can move out.
Patriots can't.
America needs you
more than ever,
right here with me
and the rest
of the resistance...
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
Until we can figure ou
w to really
make America great again.
And don't ever
let them forget--
we're still here.
[cheers and applause]
Humor is one
of the best vehicles
by which to deliver
the things you want say
[introspective music]
And, sadly, too many people
on the left
have forgotten that.
You can have a program
that is as honest
as that one is
and is controversial
and still be on for 15 years.
Says a lot.
Two-minute mark.
Two minutes to our show.
I think it's
an amazing track record
of satire,
at the heart of which
is deeply serious
political commentary
which has a very clear vision
about America.
And yes, it's a liberal,
progressive vision,
and--and, um...
and why not?
Roll track A.
Coming to the floor
in 23 seconds.
All right.
That's one of
the great joys
is when people say,
"You say the thing
that's been rattling around
"in brain
and I thought I was alone.
And I'm not alone."
[cheers and applause]
For subtitling services, contatct:
waqas.zahoor89@gmail.com
[bright tone]