[skateboard rolling]
[jungle ambience]
떰
HARRY NARRATING:
Every day we make decisions.
Decisions that get us
from one day to the next.
Decisions that change our path
ever so slightly.
Most go unnoticed.
What should I wear today?
What should I have for lunch?
What route should I
take to work?
Should I respond
to that text message?
Will it warrant a rabbit hole
of unwanted conversation?
Then there's
the other decisions,
the kind that can change you,
maybe even forever.
Uh, don't.
Don't. You don't need to.
You don't need to turn around.
Who cares?
I mean, she's fine.
She'll probably be fine, right?
Probably fine.
Fuck!
I mean, who the fuck cares?
I don't even fucking know her.
Fuck! Fuck!
Time's running out,
and I'm ready for takeoff
Look to the sky and I'm-
Hey!
Oh, fuck.
Shit.
Come on, you crazy bitch,
vomit.
Come on, come on.
- [coughs]
- Come on.
There you go.
- Oh, gross.
- [coughs]
Put me down.
Who are you?
You can kill us both later.
I'm Harry, by the way.
You're the fucking worst.
You're welcome.
HARRY:
Well, she isn't entirely wrong.
Huh? I could be the worst.
Not that I'm a horrible guy.
I just don't always make
the best decisions.
[snoring]
[knocking]
[knocking continues]
Oh, shit.
[knocking]
What are you doing?
I've been calling you.
This is Lana.
We've been dating
for three months.
Maybe four.
Could be two.
The TV was on loud.
Come on in.
LANA: I had plans to
make dinner tonight.
It's date night.
Did you forget?
No.
Are you sleeping?
Are you drunk?
No.
Stoned?
Maybe.
When did you get a fish?
- Oh, yesterday.
- Why?
I don't know. He's cool.
What's with the interrogating?
Paul McCartney once sang,
"Yesterday, all my troubles
seemed so far away."
But to be honest,
yesterday was shitty too.
Except for getting a fish.
Welcome to my office.
I rob houses for a living.
It's not the best
career choice,
but it pays the rent.
The guy in the green hat?
My cousin Chris.
My partner in crime.
[car door closes]
[engine starts]
[beeping]
2-2-2-5.
2-2-2-5, 2-2-2-5.
2-2-2-5, 2-2-2.
2-2-2-5.
떰
I wanna burn my own bridges
Walk my own road to ruin
Don't waste your breath
trying to stop me
I know for well
what I'm doing
I got time on my hands
Salt on my tongue
I'm going downtown
I'm gonna get myself stung
Yeah, I'm crazy
'Cause all I wanna do
is wrong
Coming, milady?
I'll be the first
to be taken
When they start
calling out names
I can't even remember
half the bad things I've done
But I'll wear the blame for
anything they wanna pin on
Yeah, I'm crazy
'Cause all I wanna do
is wrong
I'm a bad penny, baby
Fuck!
Right from my head
to my tail
And sooner or later
I'm gonna fly off the rails
Anything else?
- No. We're good.
- Okay.
CHRIS: Why do you do it?
Do what?
You take a piss
in every house we rob.
Why?
Marking my territory.
Why don't you just take a dump?
That's disgusting.
- Whoa! What are you doing?
- I'm feeding him.
Stop that.
They can't eat that.
What? Why the fuck not?
Because they're carnivores.
You gotta feed 'em something
with a higher protein content.
You know, like betta pellets
or bloodworms.
What are you,
some sort of fish expert?
No. It's just common knowledge.
Okay.
Look, I wanna talk to you
about something.
What's up?
I've been doing
a lot of thinking and...
I got a job.
What area?
No, not like a rob job.
Like, I got a real job.
Okay, you know,
Aunt Lacy's friend, Esther?
Yeah. I lost my virginity
to her.
That's weird.
Anyway, she got me a temp job
at this company
as a paper distributor.
I thought it'd be a really good
opportunity for me.
Yeah, as long it doesn't
fuck up our shit.
Ah, man.
No, you're not getting it.
I'm getting a real job
so I don't have to do
our shit anymore.
You know, like, I'm gonna be
28 years old, man,
and I can't be
breaking into houses
and stealing shit
the rest of my life.
I don't wanna be some old loser
fucking robbing families.
Like, what if I want
a family someday, man?
[chuckles]
I'm not gonna lie.
You sound crazy.
You should get some sleep.
Hey, I got a good job
on Friday in WeHo.
It's gonna be fun.
Did you hear me?
Yeah, man, I heard you.
Okay, good.
But it's gonna be
my last one, Harry.
Your last what?
Robbery.
Why do you not take
anything I say seriously?
Can you please stop
yelling at me?
Good night.
Hey, I'll text you
Friday morning!
Protein.
HARRY: Okay, maybe I shouldn't
have stolen the kid's fish.
Great. Just what I need.
One more thing to take care of.
So how's work?
Usual.
- Chris is apparently quitting.
- What?
[sighs]
Yeah.
Some stupid temp job.
- Good for him.
- Good for him?
Why good for him?
It's just... nothing.
I'm happy for him.
Maybe you should
think about it too.
Think about what?
I don't know, quitting,
getting a real adult job.
Not always avoiding
getting arrested.
I like what I do.
I'm good at it.
- I enjoy it.
- Okay.
You know, it doesn't
make me less of a person
than someone with
some shitty office job.
Just means
I have more fun.
I'm not boring.
So how's work for you?
Hmm. Do you actually
wanna know?
I'm asking, aren't I?
Guys move locations
or something?
I didn't actually think
you were listening.
I'm a great listener.
Well, I like it. It's a little
farther from my house,
so it takes me
like 10 minutes longer.
You know, and with traffic,
it'd take like half an hour,
so yeah.
That's awesome.
HARRY: I think both of us know
this relationship is over,
but neither one of us
has decided
to do anything about it.
Oh, Harry, give it to me!
Oh! Give it to me! Don't stop!
Oh! Oh, don't stop!
Don't stop!
- [Harry moans]
- Oh, don't stop!
- Oh!
- [panting]
Hey, you wanna smoke some weed?
No. You talk too much
when you smoke.
- Harry, do you love me?
- What?
- What kind of question is that?
- Well, do you?
Let's go to bed.
You're acting silly.
- What are you doing?
- I'm leaving.
Oh. Okay.
- That's it?
- What?
I tell you I'm leaving,
and you don't try to stop me
or ask me where I'm going?
Where are you going?
Can't believe I tried
to make this work, okay?
You're stupid and immature
and selfish,
and I can't do this anymore.
That-- That's it?
Yes, Harry, that's it!
- Oh.
- Leaving you.
If that's what you want.
[screams]
HARRY: Well, I guess
she made the decision.
- [door closes]
- I could run after her.
- [click]
- [bubbling]
Looks good.
What are these scratches
right there?
Those? Uh...
- From my dog.
- You have a dog?
Yeah, yeah, he's ferocious.
Yeah, he's sleeping.
All right, bro,
I'll take it.
Uh, let's go this way.
Come on.
Hey, so what kind of dog
do you have anyway?
These are pretty deep
scratches.
It's a cock-a-doodle poodle
Spaniard thing.
I got a dog too, you know.
It's a West Highland Terrier.
They're really cute, you know.
Actually, he's really good
with aggressive dogs.
Since you got
an aggressive, mean dog,
- we could take 'em out.
- Thanks.
Take them for a walk
to the park sometime, and...
All right, bro,
I'll catch you later.
Do you have the money
from the last one?
- What?
- From the last job.
Did you sell everything?
Yeah. What kinda
fucking question is that?
I'm just asking, man.
I wanna be done after today.
[sighs] You don't think
I'm gonna pay you?
I didn't say that.
I just don't wanna have
to ask for it later, man.
It's awkward.
For someone having
an awakening of morals,
you sure are money hungry.
You'll get your cash, okay?
We'll just do this one today,
and then you can
move on to your real job
and start popping out
a shitload of kids
- or whatever it is you want.
- [engine starts]
And I've never seen anyone
so fucking excited
to sit at a desk.
Dude, stop sleeping, man.
Not sleeping.
Just resting my eyes.
Hey.
Look.
[scoffs]
Too easy.
Must be hard trying to
figure out which car to take.
[imitating woman] Oh, honey,
let's take the sports car.
Let's take the convertible.
Oh, let's take
the convertible sports car.
It's gonna be nice
this weekend.
Oh, this dude's
definitely a sugar daddy.
Yeah.
[engine starts]
Let's go.
Wait. These people
always forget something.
Dude, let's go, man.
I wanna get this shit over with.
- I said wait.
- I wanna get this over with!
Just wait.
[sighs]
[exhales]
See? What'd I say?
20 bucks says
it's a phone charger.
- Jesus fuck.
- Called it.
- You owe me 20 bucks.
- Fuck you.
[engine starts]
Come on.
Fancy.
What the fuck are you doing?
Getting into
the holiday spirits.
- Harry!
- What?
What are you doing, man?
Come on.
Chris, look around.
I mean, this is the life, man.
That's your problem.
You're always rushing around,
looking for the next best thing.
Tell me that this is not better
than your shitty
Tarzana apartment.
Am I wrong?
Yes!
Not about that.
Let's fucking go.
No! I don't want it!
Come on!
Yes, ma'am.
Grab the electronics.
I'll go upstairs
and check the bedrooms.
[tunes in pop music]
떰 [foreign language]
떰 [continues]
What the hell?
Hey! What the hell
is going on?
Whoa-ho-ho-ho.
Got you, you fuck.
- Son of a bitch.
- Harry!
- [whistling]
- [urinating]
- Harry!
- Harry?
He's back!
Come on.
Hey, monkey!
[speaking French]
Huh?
Harry! Get--
CHRIS: Harry, get down here!
Oh, fuck.
Harry, go!
Harry, Harry, Harry!
Get the fuck off me!
Get the fuck off!
[thuds]
Keys, keys, your keys!
Gimme the keys!
[woman yelling in French]
- [engine starts]
- [tires screeching]
[woman yelling]
Putain.
Holy shit!
Can you believe that?
I mean, I've never seen 'em
come back twice.
What are the fucking odds?
- Do you think this is funny?
- What?
No! My adrenaline is
just through the roof!
I mean, I hit a guy
with a fucking water jug!
[laughs]
This is fucking crazy.
We almost got killed, Harry.
- What?
- That guy wanted to
fucking kill me.
He wasn't gonna kill you.
Yes, he was! Are you insane?
This is why I don't wanna
do this shit anymore.
Hey, relax!
We're alive, aren't we?
- We're here.
- I'm going.
- Wait, wait wait.
- What, Harry?
I got a job
in Toluca Lake tomorrow.
You're kidding, right?
- This some kinda fucking joke?
- Wait, wait, wait!
It's a gold mine,
I swear to God.
No!
No! I'm done!
Okay, I told you, man.
I don't wanna risk my life
for some fucking jewelry
and out-of-date laptops.
Wait, wait, wait!
Don't you want your cash?
No! You can keep it.
- Wait!
- What?
Are you coming to Grandma's
on Sunday?
Yeah, I'll be there.
Hey, if you close that door
there's no coming back.
[sighs]
HARRY: They say you can't have
rainbows without a little rain.
I think rainbows are overrated.
- If I got to choose...
- He'll be back.
...I'd pick sunshine every day.
ANSWERING MACHINE:
Hey, it's Chris.
Leave a message
or just text me
like a regular person.
[beep]
Hey, where are you?
The job's at noon.
I'll text the address.
[spits]
Maybe I'll forgive you
for all the shit you said.
[spits]
[line ringing]
FEMALE: At the tone,
please record your message.
[beep]
Chris, what the fuck?
I mean, it's noon.
It's actually past noon.
I'm starting to think you
were actually being serious
about all the crazy shit
you were saying yesterday.
Maybe you're on your way.
I'll wait a little bit longer.
[engine starts]
[tires screeching]
[line ringing]
At the tone,
please record your message.
[beep]
Chris, you fucking blew it.
I'm telling you,
you fucking blew it.
I mean, don't even
think about showing up.
8-7-8-9, 8-7-8-9.
If I find a billion dollars
in a briefcase,
I'm not fucking
sharing it with you.
I mean, I don't even give a fuck
if we're cousins.
You know what?
You know what else?
- To listen to your message...
- Fuck you!
[dog barks]
Shit.
[distant barking]
[hinge creaking]
Ah, crap.
A-one, two, three, four
떰
Well, way down south
In Tennessee
They've got a dance
You ought to see
They burn a hole
Right through the floor
And come back up
And rock some more
Well, diddle diddle diddle
diddle diddley dee
I love you, you love me
We'll spend all night
rocking around the barn
Well, diddle diddle diddle
diddle diddley dee
I love you, you love me
We'll spend all night
rocking around the barn
[urinating]
Ah, fuck! Holy shit!
- Oh, fuck me.
- Oh, hey.
[snorts]
Are you okay?
Mm-hmm.
You know,
I'm robbing you right now.
I basically just stole
all your shit.
Yeah, that's cool.
Can you close the door
on your way out?
What are you doing?
Waiting.
Are you trying to kill yourself?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, these are antibiotics.
That's not gonna do it.
Oh, motherfucker.
Hydrocodone.
That'll do the trick.
Thank you.
Can you close the door
on your way out?
The door!
Crazy bitch.
[engine starts]
HARRY: So here I am again.
Decision time.
Save someone's life,
or go home and eat some popcorn
in front of my new TV.
I guess you know what I chose.
Fuck! Fuck!
Hey!
Come on.
- There you go.
- [coughing]
Oh, gross.
HARRY: Should I stay
or should I go now?
If I go,
there will be trouble.
If I stay,
there will be double.
I love that song.
I guess I'll stay, stay, stay.
[buzz]
[garbage disposal grinding]
떰 [acoustic guitar]
And my eyes were closed
for most of the ride
I crossed over
the borderline
And I don't know
where I'm going
But I will drive
Mm-hmm
And I wasn't bred
to waste my time
Biting my tongue
and forcing a smile
My hands are tired
and broken
-  But I won't lie
- [bells ringing]
No, I won't lie
I'm not afraid
I'll never change
It's in my blood
It's in my veins
The walls will break
The earth will shake
With this parade
of renegades
[light switch clicking]
- [TV playing]
- [groaning]
[grunts]
Morning, sunshine.
Fuck, my head fucking kills.
I'd offer you
some painkillers,
but I think
you threw them all up.
What are you still doing here?
Are you making sure
I'll blow my brains out?
You wouldn't do that.
Why?
Well, women don't
generally do that.
You know, you guys, like,
slit your wrists or take pills,
so you look pretty
when you die.
Men, they blow their brains out
and hang themselves.
- They did a study on it.
- Fascinating.
Did you dress me?
Yes.
It felt weird, staring at
a half-dead girl's tits.
Oh, dear God.
Are you actually
following me everywhere?
Why didn't you just
call the cops and leave?
Well, I was going to,
but you said you'd
rat me out if I called.
- I did?
- You did.
[scoffs]
So what's your plan then?
You know, you can't just
babysit me forever.
You say that like you think
I actually have a plan.
So, I mean, why do you wanna
kill yourself anyways?
- You're joking, right?
- Never mind.
You think I'm gonna have a
heart-to-heart with you now?
I said never mind.
At the tone,
please record your message.
[beep]
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Want me to turn that on
for you?
Nope.
You just wanna stare
at a blank screen?
Mm-hmm.
- Oh, my God.
- Are you hungry?
I mean, do you need to eat?
I don't know what the protocol
is after almost dying.
- Are you supposed to eat?
- I couldn't tell you.
You know what?
Let's look it up.
- Good.
- Mm-hmm.
How do you even word that?
[dings]
Is it okay to eat
after almost dying?
SIRI: I do not need
to eat anything.
I am only here to serve.
Should I look up food
and OD-ing?
That's what I'll do.
[dings]
What are you supposed to eat
after almost OD-ing
on painkillers?
SIRI: You should probably
go to the hospital.
Oh, my God, I'll eat.
Just stop talking, both of you.
- Pasta?
- Don't care.
- Eggs?
- Whatever.
Half a sandwich?
Eww.
Mmm.
Uh, let's go eggs.
Breakfast for dinner.
Where are your pans?
You're a lot of help.
Oh, there we go.
I take it your boyfriend does
most of the cooking around here.
What?
The guy who lives here,
is he not your boyfriend?
I mean, all the preppy attire
in the closet.
Oh.
[clears throat]
Yeah, no, we're not
together anymore.
Really?
That was fast.
What was fast?
Saw him here
a couple days ago.
I don't pick places at random.
I scope 'em out.
Make sure there's no gun owners
or mean doggies.
I don't wanna get myself killed.
How thoughtful of you.
I mean, that guy?
He drives a Prius and drinks
green smoothies for breakfast.
Definitely not a gun owner,
am I right?
You are.
Where are your knives
and forks?
I don't know.
Again, no help.
So?
So what?
So when did it happen?
Jesus Christ, dude.
You ask more questions
than my fucking therapist.
You have a therapist?
You should get your money back.
Ha ha.
It happened this morning.
Shit.
Yeah, we were engaged.
Double shit. I'm sorry.
[salt shaking]
That's a lot of salt.
What?
Do you always use
that much salt?
Yeah. Salt makes everything
taste better.
Well, it's not good for you.
Why? It's natural.
It's from the earth.
Why wouldn't it
be good for you?
It's just not.
For someone who tried to kill
themselves a couple hours ago,
you sure are worried
about your sodium intake.
Who would wanna kill themselves
when salt and butter exist?
I mean, these right here
are two reasons to live.
You're a hoot and a half.
Ah!
At the tone,
please record your message.
[beep]
Are you fucking kidding me?
Answer your phone, Peter!
Be a fucking man
and answer your goddamn phone!
Asshole.
Oh, my God.
You okay?
You wanna get high?
Yes, please.
[exhales]
I mean...
the guy actually thinks
he's gonna be happy
working at a temp job.
Yeah, fucking right.
I mean, who's ever happy
at a temp job?
No one.
Who's ever happy ever,
you know?
[giggling]
[inhales]
I mean, it just doesn't
make sense to me.
He has all this knowledge.
He knows shit about shit,
you know?
He even knows about fishes.
I mean, not just fishes.
He knows about everything.
[giggles]
What?
Fish.
- "Fish" is already plural.
- Fishes.
"Fishes,"
I don't think that's a word.
You're so high.
What? Just a little.
You're really stoned.
It's okay.
Don't get weird about it.
I'm high too.
Self-medication is key, bruh.
[chuckles]
- Hey, I got a question.
- Hmm?
Why the bathtub?
What?
Why kill yourself
in the bathtub?
I just figured
if the pills didn't take,
you know, maybe I'd drown.
There's a pool right here.
[laughs]
Oh.
I didn't think about it.
[laughing]
My mistake.
Fishers.
Fishermen.
Fishies.
Fisheesh--
- Facetious.
- "Fa-she-sess."
- It's facetious.
- Is that right?
- No, it's totally not right.
I mean, I wouldn't say I have a
horrible relationship with her,
but it's definitely not
healthy-healthy,
and she's my mom,
and I love her,
but sometimes I just wanna
throw her in a home.
Oh, God, amen.
I mean, people always
make you feel bad,
like your mom
gave birth to you,
and it's like
I'm 30 years old.
I didn't realize
that being born,
you have to be eternally
in debt to someone.
[laughs]
Oh, my God. I can't--
I can't pee
with you standing here.
- Why?
- 'Cause I'm like pee shy,
and I'm freaked out.
It's just freaking me out
right now.
Well, I don't like it either,
but we both know
you can't be trusted alone.
Can you make water sounds?
- Water sounds?
- Yeah.
- Just turn the faucet on.
- No, no, just make the noise.
Just make the noise.
[imitating running water]
Yeah.
- Ah, okay, thank you.
- [urinating]
[exhales]
- What was I talking about?
- [laughs]
I don't know.
Something about your mom.
Uh, for giving birth to you?
- No.
- Oh.
[screaming on TV]
Why is it always
the smallest girl
who survives in these movies?
- What do you mean?
- It's always the skinny girl
who's, like, disheveled,
but not actually disheveled,
like day two of Coachella
disheveled,
and then the bad guy's
always like,
"Can't grab tiny ankles
with giant hands."
It's like her ankles are covered
in grease or something.
Yeah, you're right.
Like this girl. Watch.
Come here.
Look, he's grabbing her,
grabbing.
She's like, "Let me go!"
Bam! She escapes.
[laughs]
Holy shit. That's so true.
Greased ankles.
[scoffs]
It's annoying
and offensive
to everyone else.
떰 [calm]
떰 [spirited]
You texting him?
Are you?
It's not your business.
Don't text him.
Gosh, I don't why you think
I'm gonna listen to you.
Well, I just figured
if I keep saying shit,
maybe something will stick.
I mean, honestly, what--
what is your plan here?
What?
I'm gonna kill myself, Harry.
I am, whether it be
tonight or tomorrow
or the day after that,
it's gonna happen.
And you can ramble at me
all you want,
and you can watch me
like a hawk,
but it's not gonna
change anything.
I don't wanna be here.
Why don't you get that?
- That's not true.
- It is true!
It is, and it's selfish of you
to make me stay.
I guess I'm selfish then.
Oh, my God.
[groans]
Stop following me!
I just don't understand
why anyone would wanna die.
Well, you know what?
It's not for you to understand.
Shit.
I don't know
why you care so much.
You don't even know me.
I know.
I mean, I don't know either.
Look, I'm gonna do it, okay?
And there's nothing
that you can do or say
that's gonna stop it
from happening.
Just stop making it
so fucking difficult.
- I just think--
- Please just stop!
Please.
Fine. I mean,
if that's what you want.
It is what I want.
One condition.
You need a last meal.
- What?
- A last meal.
Go big or go home.
Wait. You are home.
Look, even prisoners
get a last meal.
You need one.
God, what is your deal
with food?
Dude, you're like obsessed
or something.
I'm pretty sure
you're the only person on Earth
who isn't obsessed with food.
Look, I'll cook for you,
and if you still wanna
kill yourself after, I'll leave.
Deal?
Is this like you asking me out
in some weird, fucked-up way?
- What?
- I don't know.
It just feels like you're
cooking me dinner and stuff.
- It's kind of...
- No, it's like you said.
- The food obsession thing.
- Okay.
Come on.
So all I have to do is eat.
That's it?
- That's it.
- And then you'll go away,
and you'll let me die in peace.
Yes.
God, fine.
But make it super fancy.
Is filet mignon
fancy enough for you?
Yeah. Peter's a vegetarian,
so good luck finding that
in this house.
Figures.
Come on, I have an idea.
- No.
- Come on.
- Oh, God.
- No.
- Why? If you die,
I'll just be doing you
a favor, right?
[engine rumbling]
떰 [lazy]
DAISY: You're going too fast.
HARRY: You're welcome.
I've been down
and out of luck
Most of my days
Spent all my innocence
wrestling with the devil
In my way
My own prison,
behind bars
Learned a thing or two
about breaking hearts
And listening to the silence
through all the rage
Yeah
Hey, so how often
do you have to feed fish?
What, like in the ocean?
- No, like a pet fish.
- I don't know.
I mean, I think people feed them
pretty much like every day.
Really?
I think so. I don't know.
Daisy?
Oh, my goodness!
I thought it was you!
Anna, hey, yeah.
How you doing?
You okay?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- You remember Michael?
- Good to see you.
- Yeah.
Good to see you.
Is this your new boyfriend?
God, no.
No, that's Harry.
He broke into my house
and now he's apparently
kidnapping me.
Oh, honey,
you've always been so funny.
How you doing though?
You okay?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- Yeah? You sure?
Yes! Jesus!
We should do coffee sometime.
Okay? You still have
the same number?
- We gotta go. Yeah.
- I'll text you.
I'm so sorry
about you and Peter.
[engine rumbling]
떰
You okay?
- You ask me that too much.
- I do?
Yeah. It's a dumb question.
Fair enough.
[garage door closing]
You're a fucking coward, Pete!
I hate you!
God, I fucking hate you!
Don't you ever think about
calling me again, okay?
[line rings, beeps]
Hey, I'm sorry, okay?
I'm upset.
I really need to talk to you,
so please call me.
Please.
Don't.
I didn't say anything.
Dinner at seven.
Is that what you're wearing?
What's wrong with this?
Nothing.
Is there something wrong
with what I'm wearing?
No, not at all.
I just thought maybe you'd wanna
look better when you die.
Am I supposed
to like dress up?
You can do whatever you want.
It's not my last meal,
it's yours.
[ringtone]
Well, look what the pussycat
dragged in.
Look, hey, I got your messages.
- 떰 [rock]
- I'm sorry, man.
I just didn't want this
to end weirdly.
I'm sorry.
I can't hear you.
I'm too busy rolling around
in a giant pile
of hundred dollar bills.
[laughs]
That's good. I'm glad to hear.
What's all that music?
You're having a party?
What? No, I'm working out.
Oh, that's less exciting.
Gotta fit into the one suit
I have.
You took the rest of 'em.
So I take it
you're not coming back.
Nah, man.
I'm not. I'm sorry.
Your funeral.
Hey, listen.
떰 [rock continues]
Thanks for everything, Har.
It was really fun.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was all right.
And I'll still see you
all the time.
You know, it's just not gonna
be running away from people
trying to kill me.
[chuckling]
Yeah.
Well, hey, man, have fun
at that fucking paper job
or whatever the shit it is.
Try not to die of boredom.
- I'll try not to, man.
- All right, man.
Listen, I gotta run.
Oh.
Okay. Uh...
I'll see you at
Grandma's thing, right?
Yeah, man.
I'll see you then.
- Bye, dude.
- Later, man.
[beeps]
떰 [electronic]
My, my-my
My mama raised me right
I've always been
the honest type
You, you-you
You crashed into my life
And ever since that night
I just can't say
what I'm thinking
Wake up, this dream is
getting hard to believe that
I'm on your mind
You've been teasing
all this time
We ain't crossed
a single line
We both don't know
what's gonna happen
While we lay low
Ain't nothing gonna happen
Till you say so
Are you feeling
what I'm feeling
Don't tell me
that you don't know
Whoa oh
Whoa oh, whoa oh
Don't know
떰 [jazz]
Don't laugh, okay?
Wow.
Ugh.
I look ridiculous.
- No, no, you don't.
- I do.
I look like one of those girls
in the movie they make over
out of pity.
No, you look...
You look amazing.
This is fancy, all right.
You wanted fancy,
you get fancy.
Please.
Oh, thank you.
What?
Nothing.
This is just very datey.
So what if it is?
Whatever.
Nice suit.
Oh, this old thing.
Did you just find it
lying around?
That's exactly
where I found it.
Oh.
- To you.
- To me?
Yeah, this is your night.
Please don't toast to me.
Then what do you
wanna toast to then?
Literally anything else.
To me.
God, that's even worse.
Okay, to you.
Harry Last-name-I-don't-know.
[clink]
Here goes nothing.
- Good luck.
- Hah!
- Oh, my God.
- It's good, huh?
This is so good.
I'll let you in
on a little secret.
Salt. Fuckloads of it.
Revolutionary.
So...
what are you gonna do
after you die?
What do you mean?
Like what's your first stop?
After I die?
Yeah.
What, do you mean,
like, afterlife?
Of course.
Do you actually believe
in all that stuff?
- What, like God?
- Yeah.
I think so.
I mean, don't you?
No.
So what's the meaning
of all this then?
See, I knew you were
gonna ask that.
Well?
The question doesn't
make any sense.
Why?
The question should be,
"How did we come to exist?"
Or, "What can we do
while we're here?"
To ask why we're here,
it's idiotic.
- There's no reason.
- No reason?
No. Humans spend
their entire life wondering,
"Why are we here?"
when in actuality,
we're just a bunch of monkeys
running around on a rock,
trying to have sex with each
other and not get blown up.
So you don't think anything
happens after you die?
No, it does.
It just doesn't involve me.
With an attitude like that,
I know why you wouldn't
wanna stay alive.
Hilarious.
So if you're an atheist,
I mean, why do you wanna die?
What's the difference?
Like most people, they get
something after all this.
As far as you're concerned,
this is it.
Why would you wanna give up
the one thing you'll ever have?
I just don't think
it's all that great.
So will you tell me why then?
Tell you what?
Why you wanna do it.
Why do you need to know
so badly?
I don't know.
I guess I just want to.
떰 [calm]
I don't know how to explain it.
Try.
Okay.
[clears throat]
You know, there's like
those moments in life
that you'll always remember
because you were so, so happy
you couldn't forget it
if you tried?
Yeah.
I've never had one of those.
I've never felt that.
What about when you were a kid?
I mean, I smiled.
I went through the motions.
I looked happy.
But... nothing on the inside.
Wait here.
떰 [slow guitar]
You know, when I was a kid,
and I'd get sad,
my mom would throw on a record
and make me dance with her.
May I?
I don't know
where you've been
Someplace
What is this song?
I like it.
I don't know.
It's your record.
How do you feel right now?
Right now?
You still feel shitty?
I feel...
less shitty.
Less shitty is good.
The songs
I'd written for you
'Cause time and distance
won't play
The sentiment that is true
My old flame
Don't put me out
with your tears
No! No, no, no, no!
I'm gonna throw you in the pool.
You're going, you're going.
Stop!
You asshole!
[laughs]
Oh, I knew it.
I knew it.
Trust my instincts.
No, not again.
[laughing]
떰 [calm]
[distant dog barking]
[doorbell rings]
Did you hear that?
What?
[doorbell rings]
Officers.
Sir, we've received
a noise complaint
from some of your neighbors.
Yelling, loud music.
Yeah, I just, uh...
Sir, is everything okay?
Yeah, everything...
I also noticed some spray paint
on the sensor on your gate.
Looks like it
may have been forced open.
We've been meaning to fix it.
Is there someone there with you?
Yeah, there's someone here.
Honey, is everything okay?
Ma'am, there's been
a noise complaint.
Oh, my God.
I am so sorry.
You know what?
It is our one-year anniversary.
We got a little carried away
with the wine and the music.
I promise we'll keep it down.
I know you guys
are just doing your job,
and I really appreciate--
we really appreciate--
you coming out
and letting us know.
You know...
some of the neighbors around
here are a little uptight,
so we appreciate
your understanding.
- I know, I know.
- Yeah.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you.
And please be safe tonight.
- All right.
Happy anniversary, guys.
Thank you, thank you.
Holy shit!
Did you see their faces?
I mean, I froze.
How did you do that?
You know this doesn't
change anything, don't you?
Doesn't it?
No.
I think you're wrong.
- Harry...
- I do, I do.
I think you're making a mistake.
I think you could be happy.
Jesus Christ!
You told me all I had to do
was have dinner with you!
You said that was it!
Yeah, well, I changed my mind.
- You changed your mind?
- Yes!
- It doesn't work like that!
- Why not?
Because this is my life, Harry!
And I decide if I fucking
wanna be a part of it or not!
Well, I don't think
you wanna do this!
Well, I don't think you
fucking know me at all!
[ringtone]
Peter!
No, I'm sorry.
Please don't yell.
Hold on, hold on.
I'm going outside. Hold on.
[door opens]
[door closes]
떰 [somber]
[engine starts]
Wait, wait!
What are you doing?
Why are you leaving?
Just because
you wanna kill yourself
doesn't mean you should jump
in front of someone else's car.
I don't want that on my
conscience the rest of my life.
Well, where are you going?
Where am I going?
I'm leaving, Daisy.
I'm doing what you
asked me to do.
But why?
I don't understand.
Are you actually this crazy?
You wanted me to go.
What, do you want me to stay?
No! No.
What the fuck do you want?
God, you're such
a fucking asshole.
I wanted to be dead!
That's what I fucking wanted!
Well, I'm not stopping you
anymore, am I?
Fuck you, Harry!
Yeah, good luck!
Hope you cut vertically!
Go! Go!
Fucking go!
Shit!
[sobs]
Oh, you fucking idiot.
This is why you don't go
and help people.
[heavy breathing]
떰
Your hair, your lips
Things I'm gonna miss
Dear God
Ah, fuck it. I don't need
this shit in my life.
I don't need her.
I don't need my cousin.
I don't need anyone.
I'm a fucking Lone Ranger.
And the days and the days
and the days and the days
But I
I never meant
to make you cry
And I tried
To give you every bit of my
Heart
But we tore
each other apart
You wanted time
It's better now
we say goodbye
I know your telephone calls
They always felt so long
I tried to pick you up
I don't fucking care.
Baby, you brought me down
And I can't be your crutch
Gave you way too much
Who cares?
You're not my fucking problem.
Fuck her. Fuck!
I never meant
to make you cry
And I tried
To give you every bit of my
Heart
-  We tore each other apart
- Come on, come on.
Shit! Don't do it.
Don't do it, Daisy.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Better now we say goodbye
It's better now
we say goodbye
- [tires screeching]
- Shit!
[engine revs]
Daisy!
Daisy! Daisy!
Fuck.
Daisy? Daisy!
Daisy! Come on.
Daisy? Come on, Daisy.
Fuck!
Hey, Daisy!
Come on.
- HARRY: Like I said...
- Fuck!
...some decisions
can be life-changing.
[coughing]
Daisy? There you go.
Come on, there you go.
- Come on.
- [gasping]
Daisy?
What the fuck, man?
Why don't you just let me die?
I don't know.
Thanks.
Why do you like me?
I have no idea.
You don't have any marbles
left in your head.
Neither do you.
You're the one
who told a suicidal chick
another way
she could commit suicide.
Well, then I guess
we're both marble-less.
Where you going?
I'm letting you sleep.
Why?
'Cause it looks like
you're falling asleep.
Wait.
Can you stay?
Stay?
In here?
Yeah.
Can we just sleep?
떰 [calm]
[sighs]
Harry.
- Harry!
- Hmm?
I can't sleep.
What do you wanna do?
You know earlier when I said
I've never really felt happy?
I lied. I did.
I felt happy one time.
When I was a kid, there was
this girl named Shelby,
who used to get bullied
by these two asshole girls.
And one day,
they were yelling at her
and calling her names,
and so I ran over,
and I grabbed them both
by their ponytails,
and I shoved their faces
in the sand.
And they ran away crying
and screaming for the teacher.
That's what made you happy?
- Yeah.
- That's fucked up.
I know, I know.
Was Shelby grateful?
Not really, no.
She ended up
ratting me out later.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Wasn't that a dick move?
Fucking Shelby.
Fucking Shelby's right.
떰 [jazz piano]
How are you so sure
I won't do it again?
Back door was locked.
What?
When I got back,
the door was locked,
like you wanted me
to find you.
[chuckles]
That's ridiculous.
Maybe.
Are you sure you want
a crazy girl like me?
Not really.
I met a girl
with a lip tattoo
She looks skinny as a rail
in her high-heel shoes
She's got a spot
above Webster Hall
Gonna run this town
with her hair up in a ball
Ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh
Just a small-town girl, USA
Hell, her daddy's
bagging groceries
Living day by day
And I know she knows
it ain't her place
But she's tired of that
living and the same clichs
So she the first
to hold a degree
While her mama's waiting
tables down at Ruby Tuesday
But I ain't saying that
at all like it's mean
'Cause her mama
probably taught the girl
Damn near everything
I'm still mad you saved me.
I know.
[distant dog barks]
떰 [calm]
떰 [spirited]
- CYNTHIA: Oh, my God!
- Oh, fuck!
Here, take these.
Please don't rape me.
What the fuck
you talking about, lady?
PETER: Who are you?
This is my house.
How'd you get in here?
DAISY: Peter.
HARRY: This is Peter?
Daisy?
What are you doing here?
Peter, I'm sorry.
Hey, look, you can't
just show up like this.
We told you.
We could have you arrested.
I know. I'm sorry.
I freaked out.
I'm gonna call the police.
Okay, what the fuck's going on?
I mean, first with
the voicemails and--
What is this?
Did she tell you
that she lives here?
Oh, my God.
That is rich!
This is like a new level
of insanity for you!
Are those my lobster shorts?
Don't touch me, Cynthia!
Don't you ever fucking touch me.
Sweetheart, I think
you should get some help.
- Back off.
- Baby, don't. She's crazy.
What the fuck? Have you been
going through our mail?
- I can't believe this.
- OPERATOR: 911.
I'm calling to report
a home invasion.
No one's calling
the cops, buddy.
- The address is--
- Shut the fuck up.
Daisy, you don't live here?
I used to.
No, that was over a year ago,
you psycho.
You belong in an institution.
And then Peter
fucked my best friend,
and here they are,
all pregnant and happy
and living their perfect
little life together,
like nothing fucking happened.
- Her?
- Yes.
I said I was sorry.
That's not what happened
at all, okay? Look.
You and I were never
gonna work because of you.
Okay? Your mental issues.
This has got nothing to do
with Cynthia and I.
Hey, man, I don't know
who you are,
but every guy deserves to know
that this girl is crazy.
All right? She is not well,
she's dangerous, and...
I suggest that you run,
all right?
Run while you can. Trust me!
Do you have a home phone?
What?
- Do you have a home phone?
- No.
- Gimme your phone.
Gimme your fucking cell!
- It's okay, baby.
- Here's what's gonna happen.
We're gonna leave,
your wife's pregnant,
and you drive a hybrid.
- Hey!
- [grinding]
So I don't think we're
gonna have any trouble.
- Wait. You wanna say anything?
- What?
Daisy, these people
ruined your life.
Do you wanna
say anything to them?
It's okay.
Cynthia...
I trusted you.
You were my best friend.
I told you every little
thing in my life.
I was there every time
you got your heart broken.
I helped you get your clit ring
out when it was stuck, dude.
I told you not to get that.
It was nasty and stupid.
And, Peter,
you broke my heart, man.
You ripped it into
a million fucking pieces,
and I hate you for it, I do.
I look at you,
and I feel physically ill,
wondering how I ever
had sex with you.
I don't love you.
I fucking hate both of you.
You know what?
Fuck you and fuck you!
And fuck your stupid house,
okay?
It's boring
and poorly decorated.
And fuck your baby.
I hope he comes out retarded.
I don't think she meant
that last part.
[Daisy laughs and groans]
Ah! I hate this stupid house.
No one even plays the piano!
[no audible dialogue]
떰 [calm]
I'm honestly not feeling
super-stoked about lying to you,
so I'm sorry.
I broke into their house too,
so I can't judge.
I wonder who would win in
a who's more fucked-up contest.
You, by a landslide.
Yeah, no argument here.
Welcome to my humble abode.
Ah.
Oh, my God.
떰
People in this town
are fucking animals.
[laughs]
Well, you hungry?
I'll make you breakfast.
Why are you always
trying to feed me?
I'll put extra salt in it.
You'll love it.
HARRY: I guess in the end,
life is just a summary
of choices you make,
and every day is
an opportunity to decide
what you want it to be.
I told the people
I'm closest to
She's my favorite way
just to smile more
I'm able to call her mine,
and I'm lucky to have her
She knows
what I'm going for
I can't help but
feeling inspired
So much so
I just can't keep quiet
Outright, unequal
I'm afraid
to leave her alone
But who said be the change
you are looking for
You said
everybody is on their own
And that's the way
that they come and go
I hate to think
that I'm going away
I never had respect
for my proper home
So I never thought
I was gonna stay
But I never dreamed
I'd have to roam
I can't help but
feeling inspired
So much so
I just can't keep quiet
Outright, unequal
Oh, oh
Oh