I'm going to be a grandmother?
you are a grandmother and a great-grandmother also.
Did you like it?
Mom, I'm going to Paris tonight for a conference.
Will only be a few days.
Well, I need to go.
See you tomorrow?
Yes mom. See you tomorrow.
Let's welcome our distinguished speaker,
a pioneer in the research of Alzheimer's disease.
Dr. Alvaro Cruz.
Thank you for loving presentation.
Good evening.
The subject of my presentation today
is a disease that most of our community
considers an epidemic.
Disease for which there is no proper diagnosis,
has no preventive treatment and has no cure.
It affects many people worldwide.
And as some of you, I felt it in the skin
with my own mother.
As we know, it was in 1901 that Alois Alzheimer
He noted Mr. Deter Asylum in Frankfurt in Germany.
He was 51 years old and showed, among other things,
short-term memory loss.
Legend - rMonta -
- US connection.
- Yes thanks.
- Alvaro? - Angela.
Angela, how is she?
Alvaro, I'm sorry.
Zoom in here.
This is interesting.
Zevvy, I'm me.
I will not.
I will turn away an institute of the time.
Herbsaint.
Thank you.
Have you decided what to do?
About what, Mom.
You will marry the American?
With the blonde?
Angela?
We are already married, Mom.
Well, you like it?
Mom.
Tonight I go to Paris for a conference.
It will only be for a few days.
Can you see me another?
# Why should I feel discouraged
# Why should the shadows come
# When Jesus is part of me
# My constant friend is here
# His eye is on the sparrow
# And I know He watches me
Place the music for me, dear.
You know place?
Look, a storm is coming.
Keep trying.
Do not go too far, darling.
Do not go too far.
Dear?
I am fine. It was just a dream.
Just a dream.
# Every morning the memories will
# Through the sea where the flying toy fish
# And when night falls
# I find myself remembering
# The happy and exciting day
# I found my love in Avalon
# When the bay side
# I left my love in Avalon
# And I left
# I dream of him in Avalon
# From dusk till dawn
# And then I think I went to Avalon
I think enough for today, dear.
How are you?
Good and you?
Do not go too far, darling.
Not far.
Ah, it seems comfortable.
What have you been doing?
I grabbed a sandwich at the grocery store,
I went to the Frenchman Street, I heard a good song.
And then I took a "siesta".
"Siesta"?
It's all right. I'll change and make dinner.
"Siesta".
Hi, Queeny.
Hi dear.
My manager needs some strings.
- Hi, Kenny. - Mr. Stomp.
- Yes sir. - How are we doing?
Well, Kenny.
I'm doing fine.
What do you look?
I need four strings.
No problem. I have a return that can not sell.
I'll handle it. Just a second.
Big Butter and Egg Man.
I got it the other day.
The family sold me the entire collection.
Queeny. Lets go Girl.
Here, Stomp.
- Thanks son. - Everything is alright.
You know it.
- He took the strings? - Yes.
Thanks to Kenny.
- Bye, dear. - MS. Queeny.
- Be careful out there. - We're just going to the restaurant.
I can show you some others are interested.
- Just this one. - Good choice.
Here it is. $ 16.95.
Thank you.
You will like.
LOCAL MUSIC OUR SPECIALTY
# Do me a dais on the floor
# Do me a platform on the ground.
# Make it light
• Take it easy, so my good man will not know
# Do me a dais on the floor
# Do ... Make me ...
# ... one platform to the ground
# Make it light
• Take it easy, so my good man will not know
# Do me a dais on the floor
Thank you.
When you started
It was like hearing himself Sam Houser.
I have had many influences along the way, I suppose.
You are very good.
She will give it to the first person that comes along.
She does not know what money is.
She barely knows who sang the songs.
I care so she would not starve without realizing it.
Cruz.
Stomp.
She's One Life.
"Uma vida".
I saw a very interesting presentation today.
Somewhere on Frenchman?
No. In the old restaurant where I used to go with Mom.
An old man and a woman.
And the woman ... that wonderful voice.
But something was strange.
She lost in the music and then found again.
I've never seen anything like it.
Jessie, I'm going to the Gator.
Want something?
No. I'm fine, Stomp.
Queeny, I will get a rank.
Back in a minute. Want something?
If you need anything, Jessie's right there.
Are 25.
5. Have a good day.
I have to give a way out, Queeny.
Queeny?
- You'll be fine? - Yes darling.
Are you sure?
Dear Jessie.
Queeny!
Wait, girl.
Queeny, pare!
Queeny!
Stop! I'm coming.
Queeny, wait, wait!
Queeny!
Stop the car!
Sorry lady.
- Are you alright? - Woman!
Oh, she's ... a wandering idiot.
Always in movement.
Queeny, you need to sit still.
I just wanted some coffee.
Girl, never takes enough coffee?
Always in need of coffee.
If you need me, call me.
If you need anything, okay?
Good to see you.
Let's have a coffee. Come.
I can enter?
She is resting, Jessica.
Look, I'm sorry.
I know.
Tell her that I did.
Thank you.
I know her radio broke,
then recorded favorite songs it.
Thank you.
She will like it, Jessica.
That man,
what he wants to Una Vida?
I do not know.
A fan, I think.
It seems he's a doctor.
Maybe he ...
Maybe he what?
Another day with his musicians?
The woman...
almost hurt.
She looked confused.
Lost. I do not know.
And you will help her?
Sim.
- I called my office? - Whatever with One Life?
- As? - It's a simple question.
I'm fascinated by it.
For her music.
Are you a doctor?
How did you get my number?
Stomp.
Neuroscientist.
I am a scientist, doing research.
So you want to study it.
Yesterday she was confused.
He entered in traffic.
It could have been hurt.
I would like to help.
Stay away from her.
To stay away? It was you who called me.
# Sometimes I feel
# Like a motherless child
# Far away from home
# Far, far away from home
It's okay, Queeny. Go inside.
I'll be right in.
- Hey, Doc. - Stompleg, how is she?
She is fine.
We are fine.
How nice.
Jessie tried to you, is not it?
- Jessie? - Jessica.
She took her card to me.
I should not have shown her.
Who is she? What was that?
She is the closest thing to a family that has one life.
She has problems, but do not want to see anyone
interfere as a Life.
Do you mind if I talk to her?
Oh no. It's all right.
It's time the break even.
It is not Cuban.
Try it, you might like.
It's a good cigar.
Thank you.
What are you singing?
Singing?
You heard the wind, sir.
It has no wind.
Always venta.
It was the wind that took my butterfly away.
His butterfly.
Hi, Queeny.
I would like a coffee.
Thank you.
Do you like coffee?
Clear.
With sugar?
Definitely.
You like it here?
I used to come here with my mother.
Mom, this is pepper.
What you want is sugar.
I bet you were good to your mother.
Thank you sir.
Take a good breakfast, son.
Someone's having a birthday today?
I'll make your favorite sweet.
Sweet milk, the way I do ...
and that you like a lot.
Someone will anniversary these days?
Do you know why Satchmo had that name?
Do not.
When he was a child, I used
dancing in the streets for money.
There Storyville.
He picked up the coins and put in the mouth
to prevent the largest caught.
So they called him "Satchel Mouth".
How do you know this story?
What story are you talking about?
Queeny, time to go.
Stomp.
I can stay here with her a bit.
And you can take a break.
It sounds like a good idea.
I have some things to make it.
She probably like a walk if you are in order.
Sim.
Hey, Miss Queeny?
Why do not you join us?
I had some classes at Tulane.
If you want to know anything about the albums, I'm the guy.
Because this song is playing.
99% of people who come here will tell
which is Benny Goodman at the beginning.
Simple things.
Acknowledge this arrangement by far, but actually ...
It was Fletcher.
She is right.
I also went to school.
This is beautiful.
Do you like?
It reminds me of my house.
Where is your home?
Royal Street, 915.
Better get back to my manager.
Clear.
You were talking about your father.
He was a blues musician.
But because of the war and everything
he kept it suppressed.
He was a blues musician.
One Morning
I saw Dad
playing on the front porch.
You see that sheriff?
Excuse me?
That car.
The woman, the singer.
I believe she has dementia.
Or the beginning of Alzheimer's.
But she seems to be holding through music,
unlike Mom.
As if she ... I do not know.
Is different.
Hi, Pierluigi, is Álvaro.
I found a woman, is a singer,
and I spent time with her watching.
She has Alzheimer's.
But when she sings,
or have some music around it,
she is freed.
The fog is gone.
I remember that his team studied the influence of music
as memory stimulus.
You can send me what you found?
Thank you my friend.
Thank you, Pierluigi, bye.
What's it?
I have two tickets to a benefit concert tomorrow night.
If so, will be at The Little Gem Saloon.
Certainly.
Great.
I have a conference at the Monteleone.
But you can pick me up at 6:30.
I will be there.
Welcome to Little Gem Saloon with me, John Cleary.
Applause for my friend Kermit Ruffins.
Look at this.
I loved it.
You are very pretty.
... marks the address of the famous residence
Royal Street, 915.
Royal, 915.
What do you think of...
- Dear? - Unbelievable.
I thought we'd have a moment for us.
- Yes. Let's spend the night. - What?
Let's see if they have a room available.
... We can not just have the car and ...
we have to work.
You can get someone to replace you.
And what is life if you do not do something crazy once in a while?
I do not even have a toothbrush.
It's beautiful.
Alvaro.
My love.
Come my love.
Mom!
- Alvaro. - Mom!
Alvaro?
Excuse me.
Just another dream.
WC
- Good Morning. - Good Morning.
You want to tell me about these dreams?
Since Mom ...
Every night, or when I close my eyes I dream.
And every time I see me with 6 or 7 years old
in the field behind the house of my mother.
In every dream, there is a butterfly.
And I chase but never caught.
It's all connected somehow.
Look what I brought you.
What do you mean with on?
With my mother.
Do you like this book?
"Sam e o vaga-lume".
"The moon was high and Sam came out."
"Now it's time to have fun, he said."
"Quem, disse Sam."
"Quem?"
"Who wants to play?"
"But no one said anything."
"So Sam went to see why, and the fox was asleep."
"And Jay was sleeping."
"The dog was sleeping."
"And the pig was sleeping."
"The sheep were sleeping."
"And the cow as well."
We met?
Sim, Queeny.
We are friends.
Queeny, I will get the mail.
Whether your headphones?
I'll turn on the TV.
# Oh, it's only a paper moon
# Sailing on a sea card
# But it would not be make-believe
# If you believe me
# Yes, it's just a sky canvas
# Hanging on a tree muslin
# But it would not be make-believe
# If you believe me
# Without your love
# It's a party without grace
# It's a melody played
# With a coin in a video arcade
# It's a Barnum and Bailey world
# Phoney as possible
# But it would not be make-believe
# If you believe me
# The light paper moon
# Shines over a sea card
# It will always be real, my love,
# Since you mind me
No, Queeny.
It's okay, girl.
It's all right.
Oh, it's okay.
The old harmonica is only tune.
We'll go to Kenny. He'll tune it.
It's all right.
Louisiana Music Factory.
Here is Kenny.
Hi, Kenny. This is Dr. Cruz.
I found you with One Life.
Yes I recall.
Doctor, is it? What sends, Doctor?
Listen, have you seen Una Vida or Stompleg?
Do not.
Dude, do not see them some time.
What is going on?
Well, I do not see the
It has been a few days.
I am sure you are well.
What do you know of the One Life?
What's her story? Who is she?
I asked.
She does not like talking about it, so I left to ask.
Her memory and everything.
I do not think she could tell me, if I would.
Thanks, Kenny.
If you want to,
her name is Maisie. I know it.
Maisie.
One Life said she lived in Royal Block 900, if I remember.
Royal? No, she lives with Stomp On You call.
Do you have the address by chance?
Yes I have. Hang on.
They live in Dufranc, 2315.
Thanks, Kenny. Thank you very much.
Oi, Pierluigi.
Anything for me?
We know very little about the effects of music.
But we made some very interesting tests.
In one case,
catatonic two subjects,
a little less than 80 years old,
They emerged from the darkness
when we played an Elvis song.
They started talking to them
not about the music, but like old friends.
But when the song ended,
back to before state.
I understand.
Thank you my friend.
Goodbye.
It's that doctor.
Maybe there's something he can do, Jessie.
Stomp.
- Hi, Doc. - How are you?
More or less.
Lets sit.
So how will one life?
Not very well.
She's in there with Jessie.
There's something I want to tell you, doctor.
I was accepted.
Accepted for what?
The Music Maker Foundation
em Durham, Carolina do Norte.
They have family homes for street musicians like me.
And I passed.
I passed.
The best thing I did in 10 years.
And still I have a family there.
At my age, doctor!
I talked to them about the One Life,
but they can not accept it,
you know, being as it is and everything.
And she's not very well, doctor.
She just sits there staring.
It does not give a whisper or anything.
Do you think Jessie would take care of it?
Jessie is an addict.
One Life knows you're going?
Do not.
I did not tell her or Jessica.
It's a shame a woman like Queeny
have their choices reduced to someone like me.
What have you done for it has been great.
She did more for me than I do for her.
Can help you, Doctor?
I will see what I can do.
See you.
God bless you, doctor.
To you too.
Saint Annes?
Hi, Jane. Is Alvaro Cruz.
Would you have any available bed by chance?
No, we're sold out.
I get it.
Once you open a place I'll call you.
I've been with the musicians.
And Stompleg, man, is leaving.
And the only person who can take care of One Life
It is Jessica, and she is addicted.
Therefore, One Life has no one.
Herbsaint.
Herb o quê?
I see a dark rum.
Jessica is working tonight?
Yes, it is.
Thank you.
Why are you here?
Because I want to talk.
This has cost.
It's all right.
$ 100.
You can pay for it.
Come on.
We can talk here.
It's all right.
What do you intend to do with the One Life?
And why would I tell you?
Because I want to help her and because I paid you.
She needs someone to look after her.
Stomp.
Stompleg're leaving and she has no one.
- Hi, Doc. - Stompleg.
Queeny, you remember the doctor?
Are your?
Sim.
In Angola you have to find something
to fill the time while serving his sentence.
The hardest thing is the monotony.
I can still remember what I had for breakfast, lunch,
and dinner every day.
Doctor, I did some things
of which I'm not proud.
But I learned good things there.
I learned my music.
Because of that, I met her.
Mind if Una Vida and I were walking?
Do not.
I think she likes it.
# There is a place
# Called Lonesome Valley
# You have to go there
# Alone
# No one else can
# Go there for you
# You have to go there alone
# My mother walked
# At Lonesome Valley
# She had to walk through this lonely valley alone
# No one else will
# Walk through it
# She walked by this lonely valley alone
# We all have to walk this lonesome valley
# We must walk this lonesome valley alone
# No one will walk for us
Honey, it's temporary. It is only a few days.
Why you brought without talking to me first?
I know. I'm sorry.
I know. You are right. Excuse me.
Alvaro, this is a big problem.
You can not just ...
Angela, when my mother needed me,
I was not there.
I ... it ... please.
It's the right thing.
I know that.
Please.
How did you find me?
They found my card with you.
What happened?
I did something stupid, that's all.
Where is she?
It's in my house for now.
But...
I'll take you home and then we will see it.
We need to talk.
I'll change.
- Want a water? - Yes.
- Thank you. - I have to smoke a cigarette.
- Want to talk outside? - Of course.
My mother died when I was born.
Queeny was my mother until I was 12 years old.
And then she walked away again.
For the music.
I think she thinks she gave me all he could.
And then she came back?
I was 18 years old.
I walked around the house one night
and I heard her voice.
That voice.
We talked for hours.
All anger I had just passed.
She moved in with me and things were good.
My art was selling and ...
We were happy.
Then she began to forget things.
Little things at first.
We would meet somewhere and she did not appear.
Forgot the way home
and I had to search for it.
And when was that?
When it started?
About 10 years ago.
Then one day she got mad.
Broke all my parts.
I tried to stop her, but she dropped me.
Broke everything except the butterflies.
Why butterflies?
It's just what she speaks.
His music, his bow, his Firefly,
she loves that damn book.
Can I show you something?
Clear.
This is one of Queeny drawings.
It's a club in New York called Village Gate.
She talks about it all the time.
She sang there.
It opened in 1958.
As she remembers a club that opened in 1958,
but do not remember me?
My mother had Alzheimer's.
And that is what One Life has.
My mother was not aggressive. With nobody.
But sometimes she forgot who I was.
That broke my heart.
This is very good.
Sim.
She drew a lot.
She always put the drawings.
When he started to forget things, the designs have changed.
Things just changed her mind.
Oh yeah.
And wherever she went, always I wrote to my grandmother.
Paris.
I think it's time to go see One Life
and maybe you can stay with us for a while.
I think she would.
Why are you doing this?
Because I can.
Honey.
I thought maybe we could dine here.
Angela, this Jessica.
Where is she?
She's taking a nap.
But it will come down to dinner.
I'm Angela.
Jessica.
I will finish setting the table.
Give me a minute.
Honey, we can ...?
Clear.
You came.
Excuse me.
My dear.
My baby.
Queeny?
You are my sister?
Sim.
My sister?
You want me to read some of your book?
I call Stompleg to read the book?
You want me to read?
I do not want to be a burden to anyone.
Hello, Dr. Cross.
This is wonderful.
Thank you, Jane.
Thank you very much.
He was my friend in Saint Anne, the hospital assistant.
There is a room available.
No, no.
You have nothing to do with it.
She's my responsibility.
I know I'm not ...
But if you do,
never let me take her home.
She has Alzheimer's, Jessica. will not improve.
It needs professional care all the time.
She can not stay in a place like this.
Will stop singing.
Why you say that?
You do not understand, do you?
I dont understand?
Listen, missy. Do not tell me...
Must let me help.
She does not go to any asylum.
I appreciate everything you're doing.
But she goes home with me tomorrow.
Come here, honey. Mom has something to tell you.
- Who is my butterfly? - I.
Let me see how you're playing.
Take it.
Look at Mommy.
- What is it? - The moon.
The moon. Who is this?
You, Mom.
- Who is this? - You, Mom.
You see what I'm doing?
I'm right beside you.
Look at Mommy.
I want you to go with these people today.
I do not want to go!
They will take care of you better than I can now. Take this.
- What will you do with it? - Touch.
You will play and will be fine.
Mommy loves you very much, do not forget that.
Did you hear me? Never forget.
Say, I'll be big and strong, Mom.
I'll be big and strong.
I'll be big and strong, Mom.
Can go.
Make them go away!
Please do not let them take it.
- Do not let them take my baby. - Take some water.
Queeny? Tome.
Do not let them take my son.
It's all right.
It's all right?
I want to help.
Great.
What do you know about One Life to have a child?
We can get out of here? I will tell all I know.
Clear.
Let's have a coffee in the restaurant
and then I'll take you home.
Thank you, Shake.
"They're coming to get my son today."
His name is Sam.
He used to work at Tulane.
music teacher or something.
It has to do, no?
She used to talk a lot when he was a child.
He said he was a good boy.
I would like to play with him.
But I was kind of glad he's not around.
I was jealous.
Where is him now?
I do not know.
I looked for a few years
when things started to get weird.
I called the school, but he hung up.
Jessie, we have to find it.
Look, he wants nothing to do with it.
Sure?
He has to know that the mother still thinks of him.
The last memories she retains are the oldest.
I just said.
He did not want to be found.
What's his last name?
Waters.
Oh really? PM Dawn?
Oh really? You know where you are, is not it?
Let's go. Get out of here.
I'll take care of you in a minute.
Louisiana Music Factory. Here is Kenny.
Hi, Kenny. It is Dr. Cruz.
What sends, Doctor?
Listen, I need to find a faculty member at Tulane.
It's all right. What is the name?
Sam Waters.
He taught in the music department.
See if you can find an address.
I will try, doctor. We'll talk later?
Thanks, Kenny.
Kenny got the address with man
who directed the school to where Sam was sent.
I do not know if it is still valid, but it is across the river.
Come on?
You will not call him first?
As you do this by phone?
- Hello Love.
- Hi How is she.?
- She is fine.
- Great.
Listen, I'm leaving the restaurant with Jessica.
She told me about the boy of One Life.
She has a son.
Really?
Sim.
I'll call you later.
Sr. Waters?
We would like to talk.
What it is?
Sr. Waters?
My grandmother knew your mother before you were born.
I'm Jessica.
I'm the girl that you do not answer.
- Your mom ... - My mother?
My mother, whoever she was,
He gave me when I was 5 years old.
She did not give you.
His mother was forced by the court
to deliver it to the state.
She had no choice.
Where is she?
She's in my house for now.
I'm Dr. Cruz.
Sir, your mother has Alzheimer's.
That's why you're here?
Sr. Waters?
His mother does not remember me.
But she still dreams with you.
It's too late.
If you change your mind, you have my card.
Come on.
She still remembers the music?
It is the most amazing, she recalls.
The brings back.
And when that happens, it is something worth seeing.
She's upstairs in the bedroom.
She had a very hard day.
That place.
I visit her at any time, is not it?
Clear.
I'll get my stuff.
And then?
It's done.
She is hospitalized.
- And how is she? - Good.
I'm going back tomorrow, okay?
Are you coming tomorrow?
Today, more than 5 million people
They are living with Alzheimer's disease in the United States.
Currently, Alzheimer's costing this nation
203 billion dollars a year.
And this number will rise to 1.2 trillion
by 2050, unless we find a cure.
While we do not have all the answers,
can be proud of and trust in the progress we have made.
And we will not stop until we find a cure
for this devastating disease.
Thank you. See you next Tuesday.
I'm ready to see my mother.
Claro, Sam.
"Sam saw Gus do something cute."
"Did the Firefly die laughing."
"It was funny to see them go for free to the movies."
"Stop for free, said Sam."
"Not another word."
I like cinema.
Do you think they also let us in for free?
Sim.
Queeny?
You have someone here to see you.
Can you play?
- Alvaro. - Mom?
Follow my voice, darling. Come.
Mom!
Do not be afraid.
Institute of Neuroscience. This is Jane.
Hi, Dr. Cross.
THIS FILM IS DEDICATED TO
ALL MINDS silenced by Alzheimer's disease
AND neuroscientists WORLDWIDE TO SEEK HIS HEALING