Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[LITTLE GIRLS LAUGHING]
[MAMA CALLING FROM
DISTANCE] Patsy...
Patsy...
[MUSIC CUE]
Thank y'all so much
for coming out tonight.
Hey, You ready boys?
Aw, he's on the ball tonight.
♪ Come on in and sit right down ♪
♪ And make yourself at home ♪
♪ If I had one wish,
I wish I could ♪
♪ Go back to my
old neighborhood ♪
♪ Where the good folks they all
love you as their own ♪
♪ Then I'd go out to the
neighbor's house ♪
♪ Knock on the door,
they'd all sing out ♪
♪ Come on in and sit right down
and make yourself at home ♪
♪ I'd sing their praises
long and loud ♪
♪ Cause they're all my folks
and I'm mighty proud ♪
♪ Of the little old town back
home where I was born ♪
[LORETTA]
Jack Benny! You git back here!
Don't you take those back
there! Move!
Why're you squishin' him!
Take the lizard, put him back
where you got him
and get in the tub!
Cissy what happened
to your nighty?
[PATSY]
There you go sir.
♪ Now they don't lock
their doors at night ♪
♪ 'Cause they all know
they're a-doin' right ♪
♪ And the good Lord's bound to
have them for his own ♪
♪ If I'd go back to
hear them pray ♪
♪ In the little pine church,
they all would say ♪
♪ Come on in and sit right down
and make yourself at home ♪
[APPLAUSE]
Aw, Zip it, Bill. I'm not
flying out there so
some songwriter can
blow smoke up my skirt.
Now, Just let me
cut the damn song!
I get to pick what I sing.
That's our deal.
And I wanna sing
"Poor Man's Roses".
[MAN'S VOICE]
Well, if you do "Walkin'"...
"Walkin'" ain't a country tune!
I'm a country singer!
Patsy! This man's trying
to take our fridge!
What? Hold on Bill.
Just, hold on.
And what are you doing?
Repossessing
your fridgerator.
But I'm only two months late!
Four.
Mama, I gave
you the money.
Stop!
I know, I know it but you
needed that new costume
and I thought I was gonna
get some extra mending
and Mrs. Vernon said...
Ok It's fine, Mama.
You don't have to explain. I just, huh...
Can't we just work something
out there Delwood?
Look I can take cash. Or I can
take the fridgerator.
Check?
I can take cash. Or I can take
the fridgerator.
Don't move.
Still there Bill? Alright so
here's what we're gonna do.
You're gonna wire me
fifty dollars,
an advance on
future royalties.
Then we're gonna
put out a record
with your nothin' pop
song on one side,
and my "Poor Man's Roses"
on the other.
And I want it before
the Godfrey show.
Arthur Godfrey?
Yes isn't it great.
Well thank you,
Bill.
Now do me a favor and tell
my good friend Delwood
here what a big important
record man you are and
how it would be a
personal favor to you
if he left my fridge
where he found it.
Who the hell is Delwood?
[Delwood]
Hello?
Delwood? Listen, its
Bill West. You heard'a me?
Yes sir. Yep.
Well, put the lady's
fridge back.
Right away sir.
[CHILDREN PLAYING OUTSIDE]
♪ I met a liitle
girl in Knoxville ♪
♪ A town we all know well ♪
♪ And every Sunday evening,
out in her place, I'd dwell ♪
♪ We went to take an evening
walk about a mile from town ♪
♪ I picked a stick up off the
ground and knocked that... ♪
Loretta baby, you
sing so pretty.
Didn't realize I was doing it.
You sure you don't
wanna do it professional?
You... Why do you keep asking me
that?
'Cause you keep singing.
Doo.
Mm-hmm
I ca...
Doo, you want your dinner?
Stop...
Hey, hey Come on. Kids are
outside. Come on.
Come on.
Jack Benny, what did
I tell you about
letting that dog in the house!
I didn't mean to Mama.
What you got there?
Looked like a broke rubber ball.
We was playing fetch.
No, that's your
damn diaphragm.
You got no business
digging in my things!
You put that dog out
and you go to your room!
But Ma, it's still light out!
You want daddy to whoop ya?
[LAUGHS]
Oh, come on.
We'll have fun.
I don't like lying... not
one bit.
You need to find someone else.
But we're not lyin'.
You're Hilda Hensley.
We ain't gotta tell 'em
you're my Mama, too.
But I ain't your "talent
scout", whatever that means.
And that woman from the show
was pretty clear, 'no family'.
Which is why we ain't tellin'.
Hey, I get a hit record
outta this,
I will buy you two fridges.
[SIGHS]
Please.
Ain't nobody I want
there with me but you.
Ohhh. Fine.
Thank you, mama.
It's perfect. This is it.
This is what I'm gonna to wear.
You can't wear that.
I'll have someone take you
shopping after rehearsal.
Now, what are you going to sing?
uh, my single,
"Poor Man's Roses."
Hmm, What else
do you have?
Will you even heard it?
I like you, Patsy I do.
And I think you can
succeed here.
But if you feel
more comfortable on
the hillbilly circuit,
we'll understand.
Well what the hell's wrong
with being a hillbilly?
Well not a thing.
But every week millions of
people across this country tune
their radios and televisions in
to Arthur Godfrey.
You're singing for them too.
Now, do you have anything else?
[BELL RINGING]
Hmf.
[RADIO PLAYS]
Hello Miss Hensley,
who do you have
with us this evening?
Well, I have Miss
Patsy Cline with me
from Winchester, Virginia.
Winchester, you say?
Mama, can you sing
"In The Pines"...
Uh-uh, Turn around,
and sit still.
I want you to sing
a song 'for bed.
'm not sure baby, but hush up
now because it's fixin' to start.
[CLATTER OF METAL]
Doo come on.
Jeepers!
Let me listen to my
program in peace.
You do what ever you want.
[LOUD BANGING AND LAUGHTER]
Boys!
[RADIO PLAYS] Thanks to you,
we have Miss Pasty Cline.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS]
♪ I go out walkin'
after midnight ♪
♪ Out in the moonlight ♪
♪ Just like we used to do,
I'm always walkin' ♪
♪ After midnight,
searchin' for you ♪
♪ I walk for miles
along the highway ♪
♪ Well, that's just my way ♪
♪ Of sayin' I love you,
I'm always walkin' ♪
♪ After midnight,
searchin' for you ♪
♪ I stop to see a
weepin' willow ♪
♪ Cryin' on his pillow ♪
♪ Maybe he's cryin' for me ♪
♪ And as the skies turn gloomy ♪
Mama, you should
sing on the radio.
What'd I tell ya?
♪ Night winds whisper to me ♪
♪ I'm lonesome as I can be ♪
♪ I go out walkin'
after midnight ♪
♪ Out in the starlight,
just hoping you may be ♪
♪ Somewhere a-walkin'
after midnight ♪
♪ Searchin' for me ♪
♪ I stop to see a
weepin' willow ♪
♪ Cryin' on his pillow ♪
♪ Maybe he's cryin' for me ♪
♪ And as the skies turn gloomy ♪
♪ Night winds whisper to me ♪
♪ I'm lonesome as I can be ♪
♪ I go out walkin'
after midnight ♪
♪ Out in the starlight,
just hoping you may be ♪
♪ Somewhere a-walkin'
after midnight ♪
♪ Searchin' for me ♪
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDS]
[RADIO HOST]
I think you've won this thing.
Who's Charlie?
Mh-hmm?
♪ Those flirting eyes,
that told such lies ♪
How'd you find me?
Remembered you from the
talent shows back in school.
Asked around.
You're from Winchester?
Born and raised.
Hmm. Folks back
home talk a lot.
Sure.
I heard it.
You probably got the wrong
idea about me, then.
Didn't say
I believed it.
Thank You.
Ain't why I tracked
you down, anyway.
Oh Yeah? Then
why did ya, hoss?
I ain't never seen
no one like you.
[LAUGHING]
Sorry, ma'am.
But I couldn't possibly
accept you as a member
of the Turtle Club.
Oh come on, ask me
another one! Come on.
First rule of
Turtle Club?
Turtles are
never vulgar.
I'm afraid you've already
disqualified yourself.
Come on people
can change!
Give me a chance
to redeem myself.
[LAUGHS]
Alright one more.
What four letter
word starts with "f",
ends with "k," and
if you can't get it,
you gotta use
your hands?
[LAUGHING]
A fork, you filthy
minded woman.
A fork.
I ain't ever gonna be a member
of the turtle club.
[MUSIC PLAYS]
[HONKY TONK ANGELS]
♪ It wasn't god who
made honky tonk angels ♪
♪ As you said in the
words of your song ♪
Listen.
So serious?
Might as well get
this over with.
No sense wasting my
time with another
man thinks I'm gon'
change my mind.
I like your mind just fine.
You ain't given one second a'
thought to my mind,
with your hand on my ass.
Now shut up and listen.
There are two things
I want in this world.
Babies and
hit records.
You got a problem
with either,
I'd just as soon
you let me be.
No problem.
Not one.
And I sure ain't got
no plans to let you be.
♪ It's a shame that all the
blame is on us women ♪
♪ It's not true that only you
men feel the same ♪
♪ From the start most every
heart that's ever broken ♪
♪ Was because there
always was a man to blame ♪
♪ It wasn't God who made
honky tonk angels ♪
♪ As you wrote in the
words of your song ♪
♪ Too many times married men ♪
♪ Think they're still single ♪
♪ That has caused many
a good girl to go wrong ♪
[SCATTERED APPLAUSE]
Hey.
You weren't
even listening!
What are you
talking about?
You were flirtin'
with that trash!
No... I bumped in
to some lady.
I was... I was just
sayin' sorry!
Course I
was listening!
Well, nobody
else was.
Hey, You
did so good.
Come on. Come over here
and sit down.
I'm going to
get us paid.
Come on.
Can I get a soda please?
Sure thing.
Here you go.
Thank you.
That last one.
That was real good.
Oh you was listenin'?
Sure was.
Did you write it?
Me? Oh gosh, no.
Kitty Wells did.
Or at least I
think she did. I don't...
I guess I don't
really know.
Where you from, hun?
Butcher Holler, Kentucky.
How'd you get to Blaine,
Washington, Butcher Holler?
My husband, he...
Doolittle, he got a
job driving logs so...
Here we are.
Kids?
Four babies.
Yeah? I got four too.
My neighbor Sue is
watching them tonight
so I could forget
for a while.
Then you come along with
that song reminding me.
What? Sorry?
Their daddy left
a while back.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Shacked up with
some young tramp
about half a mile away.
Course I run in to her
at the grocery store.
Looking well fed.
Anyway.
Be glad you got
your man around.
Yeah.
He's around here somewhere.
♪ I was dancing with my darling
to the Tennessee Waltz ♪
♪ When an old friend... ♪
[MUSIC CUE]
Doo? Doolittle?
Hmm?
Doo!
What?
You get it in your
mind to leave,
you better wait 'til
the kids are grown.
I'm not going
anywhere Loretta.
Let me sleep.
[GUITAR PLAYING]
[HUMMING]
♪ I fill my glass
up while I cry ♪
♪ Now I'm a honky tonk girl ♪
♪ And now I'm a honky tonk girl ♪
[RADIO ANNOUNCER] That was Miss
Loretta Lynn and her hit song,
"Honky Tonk Girl"
on WSM Nashville,
home of the Grand Ole Opry.
Loretta just made her first
appearance on the Opry stage and
I got a feeling we'll be hearin'
a lot more from Miss Lynn.
I knew "I Fall to Pieces"
was gonna flop.
It ain't over.
It's a great song and
Decca's behind it.
It's gonna chart,
I promise you.
Long as you
work for it.
Like you always do.
What's the
schedule then?
[BABY CRYING]
'Course we can
cut it back.
Hand it over.
Now, Randy, It's been two
years since "Walkin'".
People get in line
for peanuts and beer.
Mamaaaa!
Julie, what's wrong?
You made her red,
but I wanted her blue!
Ugh, I only colored the one.
There's plenty other
princesses, baby.
Julie Dick, honey,
what did I tell you?
Maybe you should get your
own coloring book.
Mama's sorry, babe.
You sure you don't
want to cut it back?
I want to add country radio to
the front half of this schedule.
Maybe TV too.
That's what I want.
[DOOR OPENS]
Oops...
[LAUGHING]
Hey baby!
Gonna break that damn door.
Hey Charlie, how you doing?
Elegant, thank you.
Oh Jesus, you stink.
Now, what about, uh,
Town and Country Jamboree?
We got some time,
end of the second week.
Uh, Thursday a
week after that.
I can call Connie...
Tell me something, Randy,
You a member of
the Turtle Club?
Goddammit Charlie,
this is business!
It's the Turtle Club!
Now, you take your mess and
you get in the kitchen.
That meat drippin' all
over the coffee table.
Hey, you don't have to be
such a bitch about it.
So, you'll call Connie then?
You done a real nice
job at the Opry.
Oh, thank you.
Devine was real impressed.
Tubb too.
Devine?
- Ott Devine books the Opry, baby.
- There you go.
Oh, well, I know who
Ernest Tubb is.
Well.
Yeah well, Look I... I figure
we... we've come about as far as
we can on our own, but, uh, now
we could use the guidance of
experienced professionals
such as yourself.
Well, we're sure honored
you came to us.
Real honored.
Uh-huh.
Just gotta be sure
you're serious.
Now, you're still
living in Washington?
No, we're here for good now.
Kids are with her mama.
Mmm hmm, I miss 'em like crazy.
But we're gonna bring 'em
here just as soon as we
get enough together
to get a place.
Good. We just gotta do
some work on, uh...
How do we say this?
Uh, your presentation.
That's right. That's right.
Oh, uh... Mr. Wilburn...
Doyle, please.
Doyle, Uh... I'm just a girl
from Butcher Holler.
I mean, I can't be
something I'm not.
Well, you're still you.
Alright? You're just... more.
Mmm hmm.
You know, a little sparkle
on your outfits.
Are you opposed to sparkle?
Well, no sir.
And we're gonna get you
in some high heels,
put on a little makeup.
Nah, nope. Nah, nah, nah.
No. [LAUGHS]
Sparkle's fine but there ain't
no way she's wearing makeup.
Well, Doo, I mean... honey, you
said it yourself,
I mean, they're
the professionals.
Maybe we should listen to
what they have to say.
You ain't paintin' your face
up to look like a prostitute.
Ain't got nothin' to do with
the reason why people like you.
In fact, its the opposite.
And people like you 'cause you
seem like everybody else.
Right.
Well, she's got down home
charm, but, you know we need
folks in cheap seats to be able
to see that pretty face.
Well, yeah, people see
her face just fine.
Well, we're certainly not
gonna force you to do anything.
Well, I brought, um, my
songs like... like you asked and
I... I'd really love if you
could still help me with those.
Here, I got, uh... There, sorry.
It's just on a bit
of paper there.
Um, that's about my husband.
Ok.
Those are all just
sort of, you know...
Slice of life.
You wrote this?
Sure did sir.
Look who's home!
Oh, he's walkin'!
Look at you go!
Aww, I can't believe
I missed it.
Well, he ain't stoppin'.
Mamaaaaaa!
Ohhh, babe!
I heard you on the radio.
You did?
Can't stop talkin' about it.
Mama can stay now?
For awhile, yes.
Hey! Can I fix you some lunch?
Pancakes.
[LAUGHING]
Ok, sugar, let's go.
[MUSIC PLAYS ON RADIO] Wanda
Jackson "Hard Headed Woman"
♪ Well a hard headed woman,
a soft hearted man ♪
Loretta!
What's that, mama?
Your costumes need fixin'
and I'm all out of sequins.
So I'm going to the store.
What, they're not
in your toolbox?
Nah, I looked all through.
You must've moved 'em.
What would I want with
your wire cutters?
Well, I don't know, but they
ain't where I left 'em.
Well, if you really need'em
before they close
then let me go.
No, honey, you just got home.
I don't want you driving out
there in that rain.
Stay!
Oh sugar, I'll be fast.
You're doing great!
Ahh!
Hey, these work?
♪ A hard headed woman is the
thorn in the side of a man ♪
♪ Well, lets go one
more time, yeah. ♪
Loretta! What the hell
are you doing?
Wha... Doo, quit!
♪ Well, I heard about a
king who's a-doin' swell ♪
♪ Till he started playin'
with that evil Jezebel ♪
♪ Oh yeah, ever since the
world began ah oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ A hard headed woman is a
thorn in the side of a man ♪
[LOUD SCREECHING AND CRASH]
[COUNTRY MUSIC CUE]
Charlie?
It's about time you woke up.
I nee... I need a sip of
something.
I Fall to Pieces hit number
eight on the Country charts.
Seventeen on the pop.
And it's still movin'.
Your going to have a
crossover hit baby.
All it took was me crashing
through a windshield.
That was just the coup de grace.
Sorry.
You worked hard for it.
[RADIO ANOUNCER]
That was when I fall...
Gonna get me my dream
house after all.
With a Caddi
in the driveway.
And a fox fur coat.
A whole closet of 'em.
[PATSY] I only need the one.
[RADIO ANOUNCER] And now ladies
and gentleman, Miss Loretta Lynn.
We all know Patsy Cline's
been in the hospital.
And I... I just love her singing
and... and I been awful worried
so I... I figured I'd sing one
of her songs for her.
Patsy, we all hope you get
better real soon.
♪ I fall to pieces ♪
♪ Each time I see you again ♪
♪ How can I be just your friend ♪
♪ You want me to act like
we've never kissed ♪
Well, who the hell is that?
♪ You want me to forget ♪
♪ Pretend we've never met ♪
Thanks for going with
that last one fellas.
I think thats gonna
be real sweet.
Miss Lynn?
Yessir?
I'm Charlie,
Patsy Cline's husband.
She heard you and
wanted to know.
Well heavens!
Charlie Cline!
I can't believe I'm
squeezin on ya!
It's actually Dick.
You need something, buddy?
Baby come here.
This... This is
Patsy Cline's husband.
Charlie Dick.
Mooney Lynn.
Patsy heard you on the Jamboree
and was hoping you'd come by
and visit her tomorrow?
What?
Hey well she'll be there.
Mh-hmm.
[NURSE] You going to
behave today?"
Come on in.
You got a vistor.
Oh hey...
you must be Loretta.
Well come on now.
How we gonna visit if you
standing in the hall?
Oh. [LAUGHS]
Go ahead and shut the
door if you don't mind.
Those for me?
Um.
Oh.
I don't even like roses.
Toss those.
Put 'em in the
sink or something.
Yours will look real
pretty in that vase.
Miss Cline, I hope you're
not angry with me.
Angry? Why? And call me Patsy.
I wou... for singing your song.
Not at all.
I... I thought it was real sweet.
I wanted to thank you for it.
Doo told me I was being crazy.
You think I invited you here
to yell at you or something?
Well I don't know.
I don't always think
before I do things.
Doo says causes all
sorts of problems.
Well now I gotta
know who Doo is.
Oh, Doo's my husband.
Well, uh... Mooney most people
call him on account of he used
to deliver moonshine back where
he is from in Butcher Holler.
But before that his daddy
called him Doolittle.
I think because he is
such a little thing.
Sure did grow though.
Still, I just call him Doo.
Well you sure got
folks talking, sugar.
Now your with the
Wilburns I hear.
Uh... well sorta.
Doyle's been
working with me on
songwriting but... but I'm only
here 'cause of Doo.
How you figure?
Well he's the one that
wanted me to sing.
You don't wanna sing?
No, I like it.
Just it don't make no sense
anybody pay to see me is all.
Ain't nothing special.
So you just do whatever
Doo tells you?
You ain't got no drive
of your own?
I was real young when we met.
And he'd already served in the
army and traveled around,
lived a lot of life.
I was just, Loretta.
Felt real special he
even noticed me.
How old were you?
Fourteen.
Well I don't mean to sound
like I got regrets.
I... I love him.
He works hard.
Takes good care of us.
It's just, well it ain't easy,
disagreeing with him.
Shit sugar, disagreein'
ain't ever easy.
Doesn't mean it ain't necessary.
Hey let's say Doo
never happened.
What do you want?
I don't know I guess,
I only ever thought about
wanting to be a mama.
Want my family to
be taken care of.
And I want everyone to know
how much I love 'em.
Alright well lets think
about this a little more.
Let's say all thats guaranteed.
You ain't got to worry
about nothing no more.
What do you want?
I guess I want the same
thing for the world.
There's so much
heartache out there.
I start to think about it,
I just want to die.
I guess I just want everyone
to know their loved.
Someone cares about them.
I just don't want no one feeling
alone when they go to sleep at
night even if they are.
Sounds like you was always
gonna be a singer.
The Wilburns offered me a
management contract.
Well hey that's great!
Well it could be.
Well listen if you're
worried about the fact
that they're musicians too,
sure, there's plenty of stone
cold dumdums in this business.
But I tell you my Randy's a
picker and hiring him is the
best business decision
I ever made.
[CHURCH BELLS TOLL]
Oh lord, it's late.
You alright, little gal?
Sure, just, Doo's gonna be
looking for his supper.
Well alright now, give the
Cline a shove inside.
Alright, ready?
MmmHmm
Alright here we go.
Oh, hey now.
What are you looking for?
Dinner, damnit!
You been at the hospital
this whole time?
Patsy's real sweet.
Thank I finally got
a friend here.
Did Charlie give
you a ride home?
She gave me money for a taxi.
I don't like that.
You taking a taxi by yourself.
Well it seems like there's
a lot you don't like.
Oh yeah?
You looked at
that contract yet?
From the Wilburns?
Sure.
Well? I wanna sign it.
Not yet.
Why?
Loretta, you got a
fifth grade education,
what the hell you know
about contracts?
I'm frying liver tonight.
Won't take long.
See that it don't.
[SIGHS]
[MUSIC CUE]
Looks real fair to me.
I'd ask 'em to make it two
years, instead of three.
But if I was you
I would sign it.
Can I tell Doo that?
Well honey he's your husband.
You can tell him
whatever you want.
[DOOR OPENS]
Afternoon Miss Patsy.
Hey there Gertie,
you met Loretta?
I have.
I heard you on the Opry last
week, you were great!
Well thank you.
Now what form of torture you
bringing me today, girl?
Ohh Miss Pasty.
You make sure she eats
this, Miss Loretta.
I promise.
I'm going to grab you
some ice water.
MmmHmm
Dump that in the commode.
Patsy, that's good food!
Then you eat it.
Charlie was supposed to smuggle
me a cheeseburger but
Julie got sick.
Now come on, grab my wheelchair.
You...
[SIGHS]
Well, I ain't got a car
and you can't drive
so what are we doing?
Rotiers is down
the street relax.
Miss Patsy, you sure
wolfed that food fast.
Oh I couldn't help myself.
Courtyard's only open
another twenty minutes.
See you soon.
Lord have mercy this is good.
See it's going to be
downhill the whole way back.
How long you been with Charlie?
Well that depends on when
you start countin'.
Been married a little
over two years.
Of course I had to
divorce Gerald first.
And your babies?
Charlie's.
Gerald didn't want any.
Didn't want me singing neither.
That don't make no sense.
No, it did not.
Hey, how'd you even
start singing anyway?
Singing long before Gerald.
Fourteen I started.
Your mama and daddy
singers or something?
My daddy had a real fine voice.
Still does for all I know.
Didn't do it
professional though.
I guess I got him to thank
for the reason I started.
Him running off.
Had to help mama pay
the bills some kinda way.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Hey.
I went straight from daddy's
house right to Doo's.
I don't know what I would have
done without him there to talk
to people for me.
I never had any
problems talking.
Course everybody around town
figured was handing out hum jobs
like business cards.
Hum jobs?
Yeah it's when you
use your mouth.
Down there.
There's a name for that?
Of course. They've
got a lot of 'em.
Lets see there's
header, tongue party,
french tricks, lip service.
Pricknic, lunch box,
gum job, goop gobbler.
You... you're making these up.
Gobbledegoop, kowtow cow.
Woo!
Thanks Miss Pasty.
Knob bobbin'. Ham sandwich.
Man eatin'.
Patsy!
[LAUGHING]
Hello.
803 Maple Street please.
Uh, wait can we make a
different stop first?
Alright. Wash up,
babies, food's here!
I called Patsy's room and
Charlie said you left hours ago!
These kids are near starvin!
Well you're gonna have
to learn to throw
something together if I'm
gonna be out on the road.
Where the hell you been?
I stopped by the Wilburns
on the way home.
To drop off the contract.
You did what?
Their mama's real sweet.
She put plates together.
Pork chops.
They're a little cold, but...
What do you...
[PASTY] Doo!
We talked about this.
I gave it to Patsy to look at.
She said she thought
it was real fair.
What good goddamned thing
does Patsy have to do
with any of this?
You said it'd be a good
idea to get an opinion
from a professional.
She's a professional.
No I didn't say nothin'
to anything...
- Yes you did.
- No I did not!
Sure you did!
Yes last night right before bed.
Don't you remember?
I ain't never lied
to Doo before.
Never.
There. Hold still.
Am I going to hell?
For lyin' to your husband?
Every last girl I know
will see you there.
He's so mad.
He was supposed to
drive me to this gig
I got in Knoxville
tomorrow night and
he flat told me to
take the bus alone.
Want one of the
Wilburns take you?
No they're already
on the road.
I ain't never taken a bus alone.
I ain't ever even
played a show alone.
That don't even look like
I'm wearing make-up at all.
Now listen I ain't
gonna make a habit out
of this cause holy hell
sister, you better learn
to swim, you're gonna be
messin' with all them sharks
but I wouldn't mind a
trip to Knoxville.
Patsy, really?
Mmm-hmm.
[GASPS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Dressing room's this way.
We don't get too many singers, so
you'll just have to make do.
We're gonna be needin'
half up front.
What's that?
Her fee. Half of it before
she steps on stage.
Wilburn said something
about a Mooney.
You Mooney?
I'm Patsy.
You got the money or not?
Patsy, its alright.
Well, Lamar?
I'll go cut you a check.
Cash.
Right. You're on in 20.
Yes sir.
I know. I know
everybody hates it.
Yes, when I get
some money saved up
I'm gonna get one made.
That sparkles.
But for now this is as
good as it gets, ok?
Well, ok then.
[COUNTRY MUSIC CUE]
You practice in them things?
Till I got blisters.
Doyle made me.
Up and down the halls
of that dang office.
You ready, sweetheart?
Oh, she's good. Go on.
Don't move.
What do you mean?
When he calls your name
just stay right there.
Oh Patsy, you're gonna
get me in trouble!
No honey, I'm gonna
get you paid.
Ladies and Gentlemen, please
welcome to Knoxville, the latest
country sensation from the
Grand Ole Opry, Loretta Lynn!
[CROWD CHEERS]
[MUSIC PLAYS]
Loretta Lynn!
Get your ass out there now!
Half. Cash. Now.
Oh, you can't pull
shit like this.
Oh, make it the full fee then.
Listen, lady...
Alright, Loretta,
get your things.
I'm gonna go tell 'em
that the show's cancelled.
Wait, wait.
Oh, you wanna tell 'em?
I'll have the money to
pay you after the show.
Great. I'll go keep 'em company
and you can go find it now.
[AUDIENCE CLAPPING]
Is that Patsy Cline?
Well, hello there. For those
of you that don't know me
I'm Patsy Cline.
Oh, God.
Now, my good friend
Loretta Lynn is excited
to sing for y'all tonight, but...
Sing I Fall to Pieces!
Oh, I sure would
love to, but, uh...
I don't know if you heard but
I've been a little banged up.
Its hard to get wind
enough to sing when
a bunch of your ribs is broke.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Well, what you laughin' at?
You wouldn't there.
Get your ass out there.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Miss Loretta Lynn.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDS]
Thank you.
Well, lets hope I sing a
little better than I walk.
Now, what are you doin'...
skatin' or walkin'?
Well, I'm...
Pick up your feet, girl.
Well, if I pick up...
There you go.
Oh, those arms
look real natural.
[LAUGHTER]
Alright, now can you swing
your hips a little?
[LAUGHTER]
What?
I don't know how
to say this, sister.
Ugh! Oh lord, just say it.
How did you catch Mooney?
What?
How did you get his attention?
Cause it sure wasn't by walkin'.
Uh... pie.
Pie?
Mmm-hmm.
He tried my pie at the
school social and then he...
he wanted to meet
me after and he tried
to drive me home in his Jeep.
But I had never been
in a car before,
so I made him walk with me.
Can I ask you
something personal?
Of course.
Real personal.
Got nothin' to hide.
Do you... do you like
makin' love with Charlie?
Of course I do. Yeah.
Most of the time.
Doo gets so soaked in beer
some nights, he just...
If he's not too
drunk to pass out,
he's just drunk enough to
get on top of me and... sweat.
It ain't no fun.
Charlie ever get like that?
Charlie gets drunk, but we
do alright in the sack.
Truth be told, he
hadn't been drinkin'
much since the accident.
It's been nice.
Listen Loretta,
You tell him no.
And if Doo doesn't want to
listen, you find something heavy
and you make him.
Hello?
Oh, in here Mama!
I've got a surprise for you.
What? Patsy, you done enough!
Oh hush!
I heard someone needed
a new outfit for the Opry.
Hilda, its perfect!
Well, get in it girl
and see how she fits.
Ohhh sparkles and everything!
Thank you.
[LAUGHING]
You like it?
I love it.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS]
Hot damn. Welcome back.
Well hey there boys.
Hey, uh, Loretta's on next.
You haven't seen her have you?
Oh, she's probably with Mooney.
No, he's over at Tootsie's.
She better get here soon.
We've been stalling
for 5 minutes.
These boys wasn't even
supposed to be playin'.
Well hells bells, Loretta
Lynn, get your ass out here.
I don't think I can.
Of course you can.
What in the world?
This ain't me. I'm just a
girl from Butcher Holler
and people only like me
cause I'm one of them.
I go out there lookin'
like a glamour puss
and they're gonna hate me.
Well, who sold you that shit?
Nobody. I... I don't know.
Hey, people like you
'cause you're good.
Now, all this? This just means
you take the job serious.
And it is a job.
Now, you want to be good at it?
Well then pull yourself
together and lets go.
Well guys and gals,
this little ol' sensation
is making her third consecutive
appearance on the Opry.
Miss Loretta Lynn!
[AUDIENCE APPLAUSE]
She's walkin' pretty good now.
Praise the lord.
Well, how y'all doin' tonight?
♪ Mmm, mmm, mmm, could he love ♪
♪ The girl that I am now ♪
♪ Tonight I'm in his arms ♪
♪ But it just don't
seem the same ♪
♪ I cheated and I'm guilty ♪
♪ My heart can't
stand this pain ♪
♪ I let passions fill my mind ♪
♪ From my heart
and conscience blind ♪
♪ I'm feelin' mighty low ♪
♪ And I pray he'll never know ♪
♪ He loved the girl
I used to be ♪
♪ Could he love ♪
♪ The girl that I am now ♪
We might have ourselves a
little star here.
[LAUGHING]
♪ It almost breaks my heart ♪
♪ When he says that he loves me ♪
♪ I know that I'm not worthy ♪
♪ And that's what troubles me ♪
♪ If he knew what I had done ♪
♪ Would he still
feel just the same ♪
♪ Or would he feel the way I do ♪
♪ Guilty and ashamed ♪
♪ He loved the girl
I used to be ♪
♪ Could he love the
girl that I am now ♪
[AUDIENCE CHEERS AND APPLAUDS]
[ANNOUNCER]
Wasn't she great?
Let's hear it again for
Miss Loretta Lynn!
I don't know why I'm so nervous.
You're fine, little girl.
Hey there.
Hey.
How you doing?
Oh Charlie, Patsy
didn't do it justice!
- [LORETTA GASPS]
- It's something else. Isn't it?
We're drinking this.
Well, look at this.
Oh my goodness.
She's gonna tell you
it's not finished.
Not sure how it can't be,
all the money we've spent.
Patsy's downstairs with
the rest of the girls.
Head on down Loretta.
You gotta come see the garage.
Come on this way.
[LAUGHTER]
[CHATTER]
Excuse me.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Sorry, anybody seen Pasty?
Oh hey little gal!
How you like my rug?
Patsy! You don't look like you.
Yeah Max made it special.
I heard blondes have more fun.
You meet the gals.
This is Loretta.
I'll get your pop.
Well hey there, shiny new thing!
Dottie West.
Oh, Hi there.
Jan Howard dying to meet you.
Hi I'm June.
Oh Miss Carter, it is an honor.
I just love that song of yours.
Oh, Thank you so much.
Alright now come on sit
next to me. Scooch over.
Alright.
[LAUGHTER]
I told Porter, he grabbed my ass
one more time he's gonna have to
learn to play guitar one handed.
I won't stand near him.
How do you get away?
Every time I turn
around he's just there.
Hands where I can't see 'em.
I missed you, Dottie.
How long's it been since we all
been home at the same time?
Year?
Two?
We've been doing three hundred
days a year so long,
I'm not sure the point of
having a home anymore.
Gosh, three hundred?
That's if you're lucky.
And everybody wants you.
Patsy is never gone see
this dream home again.
Now you show Mooney your
playroom, babe?
Hey Mr. Cline, fill me up.
Your leg ain't broke no more.
Make your own drink.
Come on man.
Just got a little
chilly in here.
One down, two to go.
Whatta ya mean?
The dream house.
The silver Cadillac.
And a fox fur coat.
Once I get all three, that's
when I know I've arrived.
I'd be happy enough
with the house.
What's yours look like?
Oh, I don't know,
plenty of bedrooms and
enough for all the kids, plus me
to have my own for writing.
And another one for
Doo to pass out in.
Tell me something, you
ever step out on him?
Heck no. Never.
Why'd you think that?
Somebody talkin'?
[CHUCKLES]
No, just some of them
songs of yours.
No, that's just me guessing.
Imagining what it
might be like to
to be the sorta person
that does that kind of thing.
It's maybe why I don't.
Hmm.
Things good with Charlie?
Sure.
You know you can
tell me things, right?
What do you mean?
I just feel like I'm
always telling you all
my problems with Doo
and you never...
I don't know I just...
I just don't want you thinkin'
you can't tell me things.
Just a lot of stuff
with the house.
And I had Carnegie Hall and
those west coast dates.
And you know I like everything just how I
like it so everything took twice as long.
Hey when do you head
out with the Wilburns?
Wednesday.
For six weeks.
On our very own bus.
Your gonna want one of
them lavender sachets.
What for?
Matter of fact, I think
I got one inside.
What?
[SCREAMS]
[LAUGHTER]
Why don't I just look
for it tomorrow.
What am I gonna
do with out you?
Who said anything about
doing without, little girl?
It's going to be me and
you together forever.
Three hundred dates a year.
You're the one with
the imagination.
Hey you need to get
something off your chest,
you just picture me
sitting right next to you.
I'll be there.
[LAUGHTER]
[LORETTA V.O.] They fired our banjo
player, this guy Teddy Dubs.
He gets back to Nashville
and has the nerve
to fix his mouth to say
he's sleeping with me.
Course word gets back to
Doo who lost his damn mind.
That man drove straight through the
night, clear down to Tuscaloosa.
Wanting to drag my butt all
the way back to Nashville.
I tried tellin' him that
idiot picker was lyin'.
That this was my job now and
he had no right interferin'.
But he wouldn't listen.
I didn't mean to hurt him,
just knock some sense
into him, like you said.
But I guess that phone was
heavier than it seemed 'cause
I knocked his two
front teeth out.
He's fine, and I
got enough money
saved for a couple of fake ones.
Course that means I'm stuck with
those ugly drapes a while longer.
Anyway I sure do miss you.
Love Loretta.
Mommy's home!
Oh I missed y'all
something fierce.
Cissy! You must have
grown two inches!
I can almost reach the
pedals on the truck!
Well look out world.
Mama, there's a new Elvis
picture this weekend, can we go?
Well sure honey, that
sounds like fun.
Oh boys you been good?
Yes Mama.
Welcome home baby.
Hey honey.
Well hey Charlie!
Is that Pasty's new car?
She here?
It's a new car all right, but
she ain't back till next week.
I wanna check the traps.
Now? Honey I've been
gone for two months.
And we waited for you.
We'll only be a couple hours,
don't you want to unpack?
Why would I wanna unpack for,
I'm leavin'
again next week.
Go in and lay down and relax
you must be exhausted.
You're not even going
to take my bags inside?
Tell your mama
you love her kids.
Love you mama!
[CAR DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
Welcome home, gal!
Patsy! You are back!
Surprise!
Where'd those come from?
You like 'em?
What did I do to deserve you?
Oh, somethin' pretty
good I reckon.
Well babies I gotta
thank you for getting
us such a delicious dinner.
It was my trap that caught em.
Mine too!
[BELCH]
[LAUGHTER]
Either way, that was some
good cooking, ladies.
Looks good on ya too.
Well damn.
Can we go outside now
it's gonna be dark?
Clean plates?
Alright go on then.
Jars are on the porch
where you left them
if you want to catch
lightnin' bugs later.
Thank you, sugar.
Hey you want another one?
Nah, I'm good.
Alright.
Now that the kids
are out of earshot,
you gonna tell her or what?
Tell me what?
Well we haven't
told Julie yet so,
don't say anything
to the kids but...
You're having a baby?
Oh god no. Could you imagine.
Well heavens, you sick?
Oh jeepers Loretta,
I booked Vegas!
You booked? Oh Patsy!
What the hell, Loretta?
Honey, Patsy is playing Vegas!
Congratulations.
Aww thank you Mooney.
Now it is more money than I ever
heard of, let alone seen.
Loretta...
The fox fur?
Three outta three.
Patsy I'm so happy for you.
Then what are you crying for?
Because this is
my best friend here
and her dreams just came true.
And if I wanna cry about it
than dadgumit, I'm gonna cry.
Now now when do you live?
How long you staying?
What are you going to wear?
Well mama's working on a floor
length black sequin number.
It's real elegant.
The run's six weeks.
Seven days a week,
if you can believe it?
With all the driving
and the holidays
we'll be gone two
months and change.
I'm going to bring the
kids out for Christmas.
Palm trees and sand.
Ho ho ho.
So you'll be gone
before I get back?
See you next year!
Well that's still just about
the best news I ever heard.
Hey I heard the Wilburns
hired Harold Morrison
to play banjo for you.
You're gonna like him.
What the hell does that mean?
Oh that he plays good
and bathes regular.
You think I'm jokin'?
Doo.
She thinks I'm a joke.
Relax Mooney.
Damnit Doo! What the hell
is the matter with you!
- I ain't stupid Loretta!
- Oh no you're not. You're drunk!
You're out there every night,
all that mess on your face!
You think I don't know
what their lookin' at!
You think I don't know!
You think I don't know
what their thinkin'!
You don't get to be
mad at me when you
wanted this more than I did!
[SMASHES BEER BOTTLE]
Jesus, Mooney!
Hey!
No no no wait!
You go ahead and try
it little girl, go ahead!
I look like a little girl?
In a damn bonnet!
Let's get you outta here.
Your going to lose more
than your teeth this time!
Let me be!
[BREATHING HEAVY]
Heard Charlie found the
perfect song for you,
and you won't even listen to it.
We're talkin' about Charlie now?
We sure are. I'm sick of
talkin. It's your turn.
[KIDS PLAYING]
He came home the other
night and had been drinking
with that new kid
in town songwriter.
Hugh something.
Nelson... anyway.
Came home with a new song of
his at three in the morning.
Mind you.
And started playing it over
and over and over, top volume.
Hey babe I've got the
perfect song for you.
Woke up the kids.
I swear, sometimes its
like I got three babies.
Still. Be a shame to
lose a perfect song just
'cause your husband's an ass.
[RECORD PLAYING]
♪ Worry ♪
♪ Why do I let myself worry ♪
♪ Wondering ♪
♪ What in the world did I do ♪
♪ Crazy for thinking that
my love could hold you ♪
♪ I'm crazy for trying ♪
♪ And crazy for crying ♪
♪ And I'm crazy for loving you ♪
That is a hit song, right there.
Hey, you wanna hear what I'm
thinkin' for my entrance?
In Vegas? Shoot, yeah.
Alright so I asked for a
baby grand piano do this
real classy arrangement of
"Come on In", you heard it?
Mmm-hmm
So the theatre is dark.
You picturing it?
Yes.
Alright and the spotlight
is searching the room
and then bam there I am in the
back of the theatre.
And I'm walking down the
aisle shaking hands as I go.
Hey there sir.
You know its real
classy for Vegas,
with a little hillbilly
hospitality for the Cline.
I love it.
Hey why don't you come with me
to Little Rock this weekend?
Yeah you could open for me.
I'll split the fee with you.
I couldn't take half your money.
Oh sure you could.
I got a suite at the
nicest hotel in town.
And they've got a
breakfast buffet with an
ice sculpture you can't believe.
No I t... I told Betty Sue I'd
take her to that new Elvis picture.
Take her when we get back.
She'll understand.
She might.
I don't like going back
on things with the kids.
And I do?
I didn't say that.
You got it all figured out, huh?
I got what figured out? Now,
what are you talkin' about?
Nothing. I'm going to
get up to dinner.
Why don't I call you a cab.
[COUNTRY MUSIC CUE]
♪ If I had one wish,
I wish I could ♪
♪ Go back to my
old neighborhood ♪
♪ Where the good folks they
all love you as their own ♪
♪ Then I'd go out to
my neighbor's house ♪
♪ Knock on the door,
they'd all sing out ♪
♪ Come on in and sit right down
and make yourself at home ♪
♪ I'd sing their praises
long and loud ♪
♪ Cause they're all my folks
and I'm mighty proud ♪
♪ Of the little old town back
home where I was born ♪
♪ I wish that I could
hear them say ♪
♪ In the good old-fashioned,
friendly way ♪
♪ Come on in and sit right down
and make yourself at home ♪
[PHONE RINGING]
Lord who the hell's
calling so late!
[Patsy]
It's me.
What? What's wrong?
What's the matter? You ok?
I'm fine. How are you?
It's four in the morning.
[Patsy]
I know.
No post office in Vegas?
I'm sorry for not writing.
I just... I was
worried about you.
Oh, gal, you don't gotta worry.
I just... I was just... I don't
know. Embarrassed I guess.
Well what for?
[Pasty]
The place is a dump.
Well come on now,
can't be that bad.
Only difference between Vegas
and the dumps I came up
in is the size of my paycheck.
Ain't that enough?
Listen to me, what a jackass.
[SIGHS]
I'm fine. I'm great. I just...
If I gotta be away for so long.
Be nice to be comfortable.
Oh, but, huh, hey get
a load of this.
Randy bought a plane.
What do you mean, like a toy?
No, a real one,
for flying to gigs.
Who?
[Patsy]
Him and me.
He got his license a while back.
It will be great.
And I can spend so much
more time with the kids.
For one offs I can fly
out the same day and
come back the next morning.
You really gonna let that man
cart you around in the sky?
[Patsy]
Oh, Randy's solid.
Besides, scarlet fever,
car crash.
Third time will be the
charm if it don't kill me.
Patsy!
Huh?
Oh Sorry.
[Doo]
Hey Patsy how are you?
[LAUGHING]
[SIRENS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Well hey there little gal!
Patsy that you?
I'm damn near blind.
Oooh, look at you!
You ain't just a dish, girl!
You're the whole
dang set of china.
Come here. Wait, wait, wait.
Let me get a good look at her.
[GASPS]
Hey mister, can you
get a shot of this?
How's it feel, Patsy? Knockin'
Kitty Wells off the top spot.
Oh, well when you put
it that way, Ralph,
it feels mighty awful.
Congratulations anyway.
You too, Loretta.
Thank you, Ralph.
Patsy Cline, I'm libel to
run up a gum tree and stick!
That coat!
Ooooh, let me touch it.
Oh hey! Y'all just get here?
No, no, we been gettin' our
picture taken for 20 minutes.
Apologies ladies,
but mind if I get
a shot of all y'all together?
Well sure.
Fourth favorite
female performer.
I never even thought I'd
make it in the building.
[LAUGHING]
You'll be first next year.
What? That's ridiculous.
You're gonna win ten years in a
row, just like Kitty Wells.
Kitty won for
10 years 'cause for
10 years Kitty was the only one.
We shouldn't have taken
that picture without her.
So, we'll take another one.
What are you doin'?
You need a powder with a
little more yellow in it.
My powder's fine.
For the bruise.
Oh, my little rascal got to
throwin' his wood blocks...
Clocked me good.
I almost forgot about that.
Patsy.
Charlie and I was just talkin'.
Started out real calm.
He quit workin', ya know.
I didn't.
Yeah. We don't need his
paycheck anymore and this gives
him more time to help with the
kids, so less money for sitters.
We was just talkin'.
And its not like we don't...
Well, sure we get to
hollerin' plenty, but...
And he shoved me a couple
times but, never this.
I don't know what went wrong.
When?
Couple weeks ago.
Had his ass thrown in jail.
Yep. Got a lawyer.
Drew up divorce papers.
Oh, Patsy.
No I didn't file 'em.
He was cryin' and beggin' and
sayin' all the right things
to get me to drop the charges
and let him back in the house.
He's been doin' real good since.
Why didn't you call?
Still got those papers on
my nightstand, though.
Right where he can see 'em.
There he is.
Hey baby, you want a drink?
Loretta?
I'm fine.
You sure? You want a snack?
I thought I saw some
canapes around here.
Hey... there's a seafood
tower across the way
- y'all gotta see to believe.
- I'm fine, baby.
Hey... you seen Doo?
Yeah, he's around
here somewhere.
You know what? I think
I will take a drink.
What you got? Another whiskey?
You better get the
hell away from my man
'cause I don't plan on
takin' these rings off
before I take
you to fist city.
Oh, we was just talkin'.
Enough talkin'.
I don't know what you think
you saw here, honestly.
Get my coat.
Some son of a bitch stole it.
Now, it probably just got hung
with a different ticket.
She's gonna find it.
I just know it.
I'm so sorry.
Don't you say it.
We don't have the coat.
[SLAMS TABLE]
Ok.
I'm gonna get my Mr. Dick
here, we're gonna hire
a couple of private
dicks and if we find
who stole my coat,
I am coming for blood.
So how long y'all back?
Couple days.
Hey, this'll fit ya.
[SIGHS]
Then I got a one
off this weekend,
and then I'm home for
three whole months.
I swear, I'm gonna
sleep for two of 'em.
Hey, you can have this too.
Well, if you don't
like it don't take it.
No, I'm... I'm being so stupid.
I'm sorry.
Hey, what's wrong?
I'm not for sure.
It's just a feeling, but...
I think I might
be pregnant again.
[SIGHS]
[TOY XYLOPHONE PLAYING]
How am I gonna do this?
Why are you askin' me?
You got twice as many.
He's out there running
around and I'm gonna
end up all alone,
five kids, no idea
how the hell to feed 'em
cause I can't sing no more.
Now, hold your horses.
Your voice broke?
No, I just... I can't be
doin' this pregnant.
I was singin' at the Opry the
night Randolph popped out.
You know that story.
I'm not like you.
Now, don't you pull that
babe in the Kentucky woods
mess with me, Loretta Lynn.
What's eatin' you?
I don't want another one.
Oh, well. Now, that's
a different doctor.
No. No, no, no. Not for me.
All this time away, with kids
who can come to the phone...
I mean, that's...
that's hard enough.
But when they're tiny?
How am I gonna do this?
And if I don't, how am I
gonna take care of 'em?
Betty Sue is real good
with the little ones.
She... she'll help you.
And you can get a babysitter.
Maybe we can share.
How are they gonna know
how much I love 'em?
Oh, hey now...
You got the biggest
heart I've ever known.
Any baby of yours is gonna
know how much it's loved.
I hate the way it feels
bein' away. You know?
I'm not like you.
I can't just turn it off.
Is that what you think of me?
Hmm? What do you mean?
That I don't... that
I don't miss my kids?
No... No, Patsy,
that's not what I...
Hmph.
Of course not!
Patsy! Patsy, stop!
Patsy, I'm so sorry!
Its fine, Loretta.
You just need money
for a cab or somethin'?
What? No. See! This! What?!
No, I don't need money for a
cab. What's wrong with you?
I don't have the luxury of
feelin' any damn thing I want
any damn time I feel it.
I have been workin' at
this since I was a kid and
I'm always one bad
break from bust.
Not that you would understand.
Your husband just gives
you a shove and you fall
face first into a career.
That ain't fair.
Oh, its not?
I don't get to
break down, Loretta.
Ain't nobody to pick me up.
You got your mama.
Oh, and who puts
food on her table?
I'm here.
[Loretta]
Just talk to me.
Daddy didn't leave us.
That's what we tell people.
He married mama when
she was really young.
Like you and Doo.
Mama started gettin' older
and he didn't like that.
I got older and he...
[VOICE BREAKS]
We left him.
In the middle of the night.
Just disappeared.
Never looked back.
If I start cryin' I'm
just never gonna stop.
[SNIFFLES]
Hey come on.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
Let's get back inside. I don't
want to miss my appointment.
I need some new drapes.
Wanna go shoppin' on Monday?
Shoot yeah.
Don't go!
Come on, baby.
It'll be a real quick trip.
Mama'll be home soon.
I'll be home tomorrow
night, m'kay sugar?
No. Monday. You forget?
You said yes to that
Cactus Jack memorial.
[SIGHS]
I am so sorry.
Really. I didn't...
Monday's only 24 more hours
from tomorrow, ok sugar?
Why do you always go?
I am so sorry baby, but this
is how mama takes care of you.
No!
Hey, come on.
It's ok if you're mad at me.
I'm mad at me.
You be as mad as you want.
But I love you so much.
And every minute that I'm away
I'm just thinkin' about how
I'm gonna get home to you, ok?
I'll make daddy teach me
how to count to 24 hours.
[CRYING]
[AUDIENCE APPLAUSE]
[PATSY V.O.]
I know we all loved Cactus Jack.
He was a special part of
our country music family.
So tonight, I'm gonna sing
his favorite of my records.
We miss you, Jack.
♪ Crazy ♪
♪ I'm crazy for
feelin' so lonely ♪
♪ I'm crazy ♪
♪ Crazy for feelin' so blue ♪
♪ I knew you'd love me ♪
♪ As long as you wanted ♪
♪ And then someday ♪
♪ You'd leave me
for somebody new ♪
♪ Worry ♪
♪ Why do I let myself worry ♪
[SONG CONTINUES IN BACKGROUND]
It's supposed to clear
up in a couple hours.
Don't look good.
We'll get ya home.
You are not flyin'
in this weather.
Christ on a cracker, Dottie.
Can I get some breakfast
in me 'fore you start?
You can drive with us.
We got the room.
It'll clear up.
And if it doesn't?
Tell her Randy.
It's supposed to clear up.
Tell her, Bill.
That plane of his ain't
nothin' but a shitbox.
Thanks.
♪ I'm crazy for trying ♪
♪ And crazy for crying ♪
♪ And I'm crazy for loving you ♪
♪ Crazy ♪
♪ For thinking that my
love could hold you ♪
♪ I'm crazy for trying ♪
[PLANE ENGINE STARTS]
♪ And crazy for crying ♪
♪ And I'm crazy for loving you ♪
[RADIO ANNOUNCER] Ladies and
gentlemen, in all my 30 years on radio
this is the hardest job
I have ever had to do.
It pains me greatly to
announce that Patsy Cline,
Hawkshaw Hawkins, Cowboy
Copas, and Randy Hughes
flying from Kansas City to
Nashville have crashed
in the area of
Camden, Tennessee.
After an all night search
involving bad weather,
the plane has finally
been located and
all aboard have perished.
[HUMMING IN BACKGROUND]
[CAR PULLS UP OUTSIDE]
You need anything?
Can I feed ya?
We just came to say goodbye.
Ok. Oh, hey, I think your
friends are down there
messin' with the chicken coop.
You wanna go run down
there and see 'em?
You think so? Yeah?
Ok, go on. Ok.
Go on. We'll catch up with ya.
Let's go!
[SIGHS]
I think we might come
back in a month or so.
After things settle. For a...
For a visit, at least.
You're not drivin'
straight through to
Winchester tonight, are ya?
No, just to Roanoke.
[SIGHS]
How is Charlie takin' it?
He knows he's not in any
shape to take care of anyone.
He doesn't like it, but
he's not fightin' it.
Well, maybe I'll go on by
there and see how he's doin'.
You were such a good
friend to her, Loretta.
[CAR DOOR SLAMS]
[KNOCKING]
Charlie? Charlie?
It's Loretta!
[Charlie] Get out!
Hi.
I said get out, Loretta.
I'm fine.
I'll go soon enough.
I come to, uh, play you
this new song, though.
Sure you don't wanna hear it?
♪ I watched you leave ♪
♪ That's how I know you're gone ♪
♪ But this heart of mine ♪
♪ Keeps tellin' me I'm wrong ♪
♪ I see your face before me ♪
♪ Every night ♪
♪ In this haunted house ♪
♪ When I turn off the light ♪
♪ Sometimes I hear you walk ♪
♪ Across the floor ♪
♪ And my arms reach
out to hold you ♪
♪ Like before ♪
♪ I live for all the
things we used to do ♪
♪ In this haunted house
I filled ♪
♪ With love for you ♪
♪ This haunted house
I'm livin' in ♪
♪ Is killin' me ♪
♪ And the ghost of your love ♪
♪ Won't set me free ♪
♪ Each morning finds me ♪
♪ Crying and alone ♪
[CAR DOOR SLAMS]
♪ In this haunted house ♪
How's Charlie?
I reckon he'll be alright.
How are you?
I miss her.
Oh Doo.
[KISSING]
I love you, girl.
Take me home, baby.
[PHONE RINGING]
This the Lynn's...
Um... No, she uh, She can't
come to the phone right now,
but this is, uh, this is
her husband, Mooney.
Yeah, sure, go 'head.
Uh, yeah, well... I'll have
her give you a call back
and make an appointment.
Thank you very much.
Bye Bye.
[HANGS PHONE UP]
Loretta?
Yeah.
I guess we're havin'
another baby?
[SIGHS AND STARTS CRYING]
Hey, hey baby what's wrong?
What's the matter? Baby...
[SOBBING]
Gonna run out of water,
crying like that little girl.
Hey, you already got four.
What's one more?
[LAUGHING]
Come on, come on.
What's the matter, little girl?
[LAUGHS]
I was just thinkin' about Patsy.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ I said blue moon of
Kentucky keep on shinin' ♪
♪ Shine on the one that's
gone and proved untrue ♪
♪ Blue moon of
Kentucky keep on shinin' ♪
♪ Shine on the one thats
gone and left me blue ♪
♪ Well it was on
one moonlit night ♪
♪ Stars shinin' bright ♪
♪ Whispered on high ♪
♪ Your love said goodbye ♪
♪ I said blue moon of
Kentucky keep on shinin' ♪
♪ Shine on the one thats
gone and left me blue ♪
♪ I said blue moon of
Kentucky keep on shinin' ♪
♪ Shine on the one that's
gone and left me blue ♪
♪ I said blue moon of
Kentucky keep on shinin' ♪
♪ Well shine on the one that's
gone and left me blue ♪
♪ Well, it was on
one moonlit night ♪
♪ Stars shinin' bright ♪
♪ Whispered on high ♪
♪ Your love said goodbye ♪
♪ I said, blue moon of
Kentucky keep on shinin' ♪
♪ Shine on the one that's
gone and left me blue ♪
♪ He left me blue ♪
♪ Ohh left me blue ♪
♪ And left me blue ♪
[AUDIENCE APPLAUSE]
Patsy! Peggy!
Hey mama!
Hey babies. Come on,
give me some sugar.
Ok. Go wash up.
Ok!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org