[Bang!]
Worst... Birthday... Ever.
All I wanted was a small dinner
party with my closest friends,
finally introducing them
to each other.
What I got was a reality check.
For my 40th birthday,
I got the only kind of present
you can't return - the truth.
[BANG!]
♪
Maybe I should back it up a bit.
Everything was on track
for the perfect evening.
[cell phone ringing]
Hey, Evelyn.
Jaden, put that down!
Put that down right now!!
Are you and James on the way?
Don't be mad.
Mad? Why?
We can't make it tonight.
- Evelyn!
- I know, it's Jaden!
Josh's mother gave him a cupcake
after a playdate this afternoon.
Sugar, at that hour!
Can you believe it?
Well...
He's bouncing off the walls.
And what if he had
been allergic to wheat?
Did she even think about that?
She should be shot.
If I had a gun and
believed in violence,
and knew who this
kid Josh was, I'd do it for you.
James! James!
He's too close to the...
No, stop it! He's...
I gotta go.
We'll make it up to you.
I'm sorry, and happy...
Jaden! Put your clothes on!
Put your clothes on right now!
Just four for dinner.
I could handle that.
More for everyone, right?
And I knew that my pal Woody
wouldn't let me down.
Yeah, man, I'm really sick.
Are you serious, Woody?
Yeah, there's something
going around the office.
I think it's the temp
in the mailroom.
So, I just
can't get out tonight.
Especially in this weather.
So it's a little cold.
Ever hear of a thing
called pneumonia?
Ever hear of a thing called
a friend's 40th birthday party?
You'll have
another one next year.
Let me explain something
to you about milestones.
You'll be fine without me.
- But Evelyn and James--
-Can keep you company tonight.
I really gotta go, Doug.
Feel better.
Mmmm.
[SIGHS]
At least I could count on
my favorite employee, Philip,
and his partner, Terry.
I can't make it.
What do you mean
you can't make it?
A new client showed up,
totally last minute.
Well, just tell him
to come back tomorrow
- I would, but
-
But what?
Tell him
-
and use your nice voice -
that the owner
of the Pilates studio
is having a birthday party,
and kindly request that
he come back tomorrow.
But he bought
six months of daily, private,
one-on-one sessions...
In advance.
But that's not...
That's a lot of money.
I know, right?
But he insisted
he start tonight.
Why?
Something about watching the
biggest fatties on television,
and he's getting
married in six months,
and his fiancee was like,
shape up or ship out.
Something like that.
I wasn't really
paying attention.
Is this right?
Not quite.
Is he breaking the equipment?
Don't let him
break the equipment!
He's fine.
Or at least, he will
be fine, with my help.
So I guess this means
Terry can't make it.
He's been stuck in traffic for
an hour just trying to get here.
- He can totally still try to.
-
That's OK...
I'll live.
Well, say hello
to everyone for us.
And happy birthday, Doug-bug.
Is this supposed to hurt?
I had clearly
been deluding myself.
These people weren't my friends.
Real friends
show up no matter what.
This birthday sucks.
And not in a good way.
[doorbell rings]
Are you the big birthday boy?
Oh, no.
Uh huh.
I'm Bambi, with an i.
[giggles]
Great.
I was told there was
gonna be a party.
It was cancelled
on account of patheticness.
We... could still...
Hold on...
Have a party for two.
That would make it
a party for four.
Listen, you have the wrong guy.
You're not little Doogie?
Little Doogie?
Your brother says,
Happy Birthday!
My brother?
[Bambi giggling]
Oops!
Derek.
No need to thank me, bro.
I wasn't going to.
I just figured it was something
you didn't already have.
You do remember,
I sleep with men, right?
So does Bambi,
so you two have a lot in common.
Shut up.
- You having a good birthday?
-
No.
How was yours?
Just what I expected.
Karen asked Grace what we
should do for Daddy's birthday.
But Grace is six years old.
Seven, actually.
Thanks for remembering.
Sorry.
So where'd you end up?
You know, at the mall,
at a tea party,
in that store where they sell
those creepy-ass dolls.
Did Grace get you one
of those creepy-ass dolls
for your 40th birthday?
She did, indeed.
I'm letting her
watch it right now.
You're such a good father.
And you are old.
We're twins,
we're the same age.
But you just feel older.
I do tonight.
Why?
Because I'm all alone.
Everyone's abandoned me.
That's because you're ugly.
Fuck you very much.
What about that old guy
you've been seeing?
- Jacob.
-
Yeah, Jacob.
He's not old.
- He's 50!
- And I'm 40.
And you're old, too.
You're ten minutes
younger than me.
What does that make you?
Uh, lucky I'm not
in the dating pool.
So why don't you just
invite Jacob?
Well, we've only been out
a few times, and besides,
it's not serious or anything.
How do you know?
Well, because
on our last date...
Doug, I really like you,
but I'm not looking for
anything serious right now.
Well, there you go.
And I'm seeing him
again this weekend, so...
Well, you know,
if I lived closer, I'd be there.
Yeah,
I hate spending
our birthdays apart.
Karen and the kids wanted to
wish you Happy Birthday, too.
- Thanks.
- Enjoy your present.
[Bambi giggling]
Not a chance.
But...but I can stay.
Best offer I've had all night,
and yet, no thanks.
Hey, I'm--
Oh, my God!
My brother will not give up.
You, get inside.
Take your clothes off,
do whatever you need to do.
And you, thank you
for an abysmal evening.
What's that mean?
It means no tip.
Come in.
Let's get this over with.
- I'm--
- Paid by the hour, right.
Nice... You should wax.
What?
Never mind, amuse me.
Keep goin'.
Turn this day around.
Um, I think there's
a misunderstanding.
Yeah, it doesn't look like
you're wearing a g-string.
Some stripper you are.
I'm not a stripper...
I'm your new neighbor.
I got this mail by mistake.
Sorry.
Black briefs.
Huh?
No g-string.
I'm more of
a black briefs kinda guy.
Do you want some cake?
Cake.
Sounds fun.
Oh...
You have no idea
how much I needed that.
Was it on your
birthday wish list?
It is now.
I'd say I didn't have
time to wrap it,
but that's not
entirely true, is it?
And it was just the right size.
Good, you can't return it.
I'm so glad
you knocked on my door.
I'm glad you knocked
on my door in return.
I was talking
about my actual door.
I wasn't.
[both laughing]
You live next door?
Mmmm, yes, I do.
Just renting, but I like it.
So, what brings you
to the gayborhood?
Just time for a change.
You lived here long?
Five years.
That's commitment.
I do believe in commitment.
Good to know.
Where are you going?
I should get going...
Back to my place.
You don't have to.
I don't want to keep you up.
Besides, there's a tennis match
I want to watch.
The exhibition match from Dubai?
Yeah, you a tennis fan?
- Huge.
- Oh, nice.
I have my DVR set to record it.
Should be a really good match.
Maybe I should come over,
and watch it with you
in the morning.
Maybe you should just stay and
watch it with me in the morning.
Deal.
[doorbell rings]
Aha! I have to pee.
Come in, Evelyn.
Make yourself at home.
Let me tell you about all the
amazing sex I had last night.
A strange women just raced
through here to the bathroom.
She's not strange,
she's Evelyn.
On the other hand,
she's very strange.
Oh, my God,
so much better.
Doug?
Yes.
There's a strange man
in your bed.
I know.
I was gonna tell you earlier,
but I had to pee.
Just making sure
you knew he was here.
- I do.
- Excellent.
And...the introductions
would start...
Oh, sorry.
Evelyn, this is Colton.
Colton, this is
my dear friend, Evelyn.
Charmed, I'm sure.
I would shake your hand,
but I'm sort of naked.
Are you?
Nice to meet you.
And you.
I'm sure the pleasure
was all Doug's.
So, he is...
too young for you,
but that's beside the point.
Cut it out, Evvy.
He's my--
Birthday present.
I do take credit cards,
by the way.
- You didn't!
- I didn't.
Oh, yes, you did, sir.
Sir?
Thank you for untying me, sir.
This is so not what--
Oh, Doug, Doug,
you're a grown man.
You can spend your money
however you like.
Just be sure
to give him a big tip.
He's already done that.
I like him.
He's my neighbor.
Whatever turns you on, sweetie,
mmm hmmm.
I should get going.
It was...
nice to meet you.
And you.
Hope we'll be
seeing more of you.
And now we have.
Whoo!
Um... Happy Birthday!
Thanks.
It was yesterday, remember?
I remember, I remember every...
Oh, shit,
Jaden's still in the car!
I gotta run!
I love you!
You're terrible, Muriel.
Thank you, sir.
So what did you do?
Excuse me?
For your birthday.
How'd you know?
It's on your online profile.
Did you have a good time?
Yeah. Actually, it was...
[moans]
Nice, in the end.
Hmm...
Your end or his?
[breathing heavily]
No comment.
I thought so.
You look, shall we say,
very satisfied today.
I am. I mean,
I was having a shitty birthday,
and then something happened
that just made it feel like,
I don't know, like,
turning 40 wasn't so bad.
That must have been
some serious sex.
I don't know if I'm comfortable
talking about this with you.
Don't worry about it.
It's not like
we're exclusive or anything.
Did you ask me to go steady
when I wasn't paying attention?
It's no big deal.
You're dating other guys,
I'm dating other guys.
You're dating other guys?
Well, I would
if I could find them.
You know, if you hadn't
slammed into my car that day--
I barely bumped into you.
I almost had whiplash.
Oh, you almost had a headache.
Potato, po-tah-to.
You were parked
in front of my house,
and I was barely going
five miles an hour.
That's not the point.
If you hadn't hit me,
we wouldn't
have started talking,
and I would have never had
the courage to ask you out.
Here's to fate.
And here's to being rear-ended.
[glasses clink]
So...
Why were you parked
in front of my house?
House hunting.
You never mentioned
you were house hunting.
You never asked.
That's odd.
- That you never asked?
- Yeah.
You were being very polite.
Polite? How?
You weren't talking
with your mouth full.
Oh, yeah.
You should be on the welcoming
committee for the neighborhood.
Made me feel quite at home.
Good.
So, um,
did you find a place yet?
Not yet.
Staying with relatives
for a bit.
I still can't believe
that you were...married.
And...you have a son.
Two sons.
Oh, yeah, I forgot, wow.
Well, I don't talk about
my second son much.
Why?
He didn't take
my coming out very well.
What'd he do?
No, you can't be gay!
You're my daddy!
Ooh, yikes.
He was always
a little emotional.
Did he ever accept it?
I hate you!
You've ruined my life!
Not yet...
Someday.
But your other son's
OK with it, right?
Definitely.
But that's another story
for another day.
Read me a bedtime story, Daddy?
No, don't do that.
Why, you gonna spank me?
I'll spank you.
[both laughing]
You sure you don't want
to come out with me?
Ugh, that club
makes me feel so old.
But you are old.
Not that much older than you,
according to
your driver's license.
Clerical error at the DMV.
I'm not a day over 29.
What?!
I'll get you for that, my ugly.
Good Lord, you are gay.
Yeah, I am,
and why should you feel old?
You're dating a twink.
Oh, that's right.
You're also dating an elder.
Um, first of all, Colton is 30 -
that is hardly a twink.
30? I throw them back
if they're a day over 25.
Oh, yeah,
and that works for you?
Totally works for me.
OK, well what about
the time that we hooked up?
OK. A - I was drunk.
B - you were
a lot younger then.
And C - I was really drunk.
Whatever.
OK, and Jacob.
He's 50,
not close to an elder.
50?
Is he all wrinkly and shit?
Not that it matters, but no.
He's in good shape.
For a man his age.
Don't you dare
make a Viagra joke.
Oh, do you need some?
I have some extra.
Why do you have Viagra?
From that orgy
I went to last month.
Oh, my gosh,
you, my friend, are a whore.
You're so sweet.
Oh, big question -
underwear, yes or no?
Um, I'm gonna say yes.
No it is.
Why do you...date--
Why is it you're OK
with dating younger men
as opposed to older men?
Because younger men
keep me young.
Or at least,
they make me feel young.
And, really,
isn't that what it's all about?
Anyway...
Oh, that reminds me.
There's a bottle of wine
for you in the kitchen.
Happy Birthday, bud.
[knocking]
That was fast.
I told you I take credit cards.
What? Oh...
I was waiting for pizza.
Well, how about
a home-cooked meal instead?
I can hardly tell
that you just moved in.
The owners wanted
to rent it furnished,
and who am I
to turn away furniture?
Never say no to ottomans,
they get very upset.
Bone...
...appetite.
Classy.
I try.
Red or white?
Well, actually,
I'm one-sixteenth Cherokee
on my mother's side,
but mostly white.
I meant the wine.
White.
Coming right up.
It smells amazing.
It's the bacon.
Is the bacon hiding?
Bacon and sun-dried tomatoes
stuffed inside the chicken,
a bacon-infused
vinaigrette in the salad,
and the bread -
is a bacon-Gruyere scone.
So...you like bacon.
I like bacon.
Did you put bacon in the wine?
Yeah, I dipped the rims
in bacon fat.
No, you did not.
I did not...
But I might someday.
[door slams]
You could try knocking.
What are you...?
We're having dinner.
This is the guy
I was telling you about;
he lives next door.
That's where I...
I mean, I...
almost walked right up
to the house next door.
Totally not paying attention.
Funny, huh?
Hilarious.
And apparently,
I learned nothing
from meeting your friend
the other morning.
Introductions all around.
This is Doug, he...
Lives next door.
Yeah, good memory.
Doug, this is Jacob, my father.
Your--
Father.
Your father?
My father.
His father?
His father.
Well, that's just fucked up.
I know.
You're dating a father and son?
Well, that just sounds
dirtier than it is.
Well, just how dirty is it?
It's not!
I'm dating two men
who happen to be fath...
Oh, Christ.
Wow, that sounds bad.
Does this happen a lot
in the gay world?
No.
'Cause I've seen some
mother-daughter lesbian porn,
and that was pretty damn hot.
Please stop talking.
So, um,
what did the son, uh...
- Colton.
-
Yeah, Colton.
What did he say
when he found out?
Well...
I'll put that in the kitchen.
You two get to know each other.
That's your son?
You didn't tell me
you had a gay son.
You didn't ask.
I've got to start
asking more questions.
What are you two
whispering about?
How much we adore you, Son.
That's sweet.
See any family resemblances?
Now that you mention it.
Colton, can you get
me a glass of wine?
Sure.
I don't want to hear anything
about our...resemblances.
- Fine.
You're not staying, are you?
I live here.
Well, that's just awkward.
So you're the one that
thought my son was a stripper?
It was an honest mistake.
And sleeping with him?
That was on purpose.
What?
- Nothing.
Is there any more chicken?
Don't worry,
I'll eat it in my room.
Yes, I will get you that.
What do we tell him?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
Tell him nothing.
He's always been competitive.
It runs in the family.
But this is not a competition.
It will be soon.
You boys have fun.
I'm going to, uh,
eat this in my room,
which is ten feet that way -
behind those thin walls.
In case anybody needs me.
Night, Dad.
It was nice meeting you.
Yes, wasn't it?
And you continued
your date with Colton
like nothing had happened?
I tried, what else
was I supposed to do?
Move out of the neighborhood
due to sheer embarrassment.
That thought crossed my mind.
Tell me you didn't
stay over with Jacob there?
I did not stay over
with Jacob there.
I can't stay over
with your father here.
He won't mind.
Did I mention he's gay, too?
I know.
I mean, no, I just...
kind of figured it out.
Really? How?
Well... um...
Did he hit on you?
No. No!
Of course not!
I'm kidding around.
I mean, how weird
would that be, right?
So weird.
Completely weird.
Bizarro weird!
Then...stay.
I should get home.
What, beat the traffic?
Exactly.
That's a joke,
'cause you live next door.
Next time?
Next time.
So you slept alone,
while the two men
you're sleeping with
slept next to each other
in the house that they share.
That seems to be the case.
I'm gonna need a flowchart
to keep up with this.
So do you have
a Daddy complex,
or does Colton?
How do you know
about Daddy complexes?
I'm a therapist.
I deal with a lot of strippers.
No...
Nobody has a daddy complex.
Does Jacob like it
when you call him Daddy?
No.
Oh, my God!
You actually call him Daddy?
It was a joke.
Does Colton call you Daddy?
No! Nobody calls
anybody Daddy, OK?
Except for Colton and Jacob.
Because, well, he is his daddy.
Can we...say father instead?
The daddy stuff
is kinda creeping me out.
Hey, have you told
our father about this?
I'm hanging up now.
Hey.
Sorry about your birthday
thing the other night.
Here.
What does it mean
that every person I know
got me wine for my birthday?
That you're an alcoholic?
I'm not an alcoholic.
Do you drink at home alone?
[snoring]
Yeah, sometimes.
Classic signs of an alcoholic.
But wait, I live alone,
so of course I drink alone.
First step is the hardest.
Apparently the only steps
I need are the ones
leading right
to the local liquor store.
Them's the spirits!
Thanks for your support.
No, it's the best
liquor store around here.
Them's The Spirits -
it's the name of the store.
Oh, OK.
Good to know.
Hey, do you have a minute?
We should go to lunch.
- Oh, God!
- What?
Are you firing me?
Why would you
think I'm firing you?
You always take people to
lunch when you're firing them.
I do?
That vegan place
down the street...
You said that people
won't have the energy
to fight back
without any protein.
- I said that?
- A little bit.
I'm not firing you.
I just want to congratulate you
for landing that new client.
Oh, that. Thanks.
I'm just glad
we could fit him in.
I was looking at the schedule;
we are really
booked up this month.
All thanks
to your brilliant idea.
Which brilliant idea
are you talking about?
You're gonna have
to narrow that one down.
The senior citizens
Intro to Pilates class.
It's really taken off.
You really have a grasp
on that demographic.
- No I don't.
- Sure, you do.
You have this sense for
what really gets them excited.
Yeah, but I can relate to
the younger generation, too.
Of course you can, mister.
So can I.
After all, Terry is three
whole years younger than I am.
That's like 20 in gay years.
It's not that big.
Yes, it is.
Why do you think
I stay with him?
It's big.
That reminds me...
We need to schedule our
sexual harassment training.
[whispers]
You need to go.
I'll make a note of it.
This feels good.
Mmmm...
Good.
Great, even.
Great!
You're not making this easy.
That's because you're making it
very, very hard.
Be serious a second.
OK, serious, go.
What I'm trying to say is...
I like this.
I like spending time with you.
I like you, Doug.
I like you, Colton.
I know haven't
known each other that long,
but I think we have
a connection here.
Me too.
And I was hoping that we could
see a lot more of each other.
Kinda unavoidable.
We're neighbors.
You know what I mean.
You're not asking me
to go steady, are you?
Jeez, sounds like
something my dad would say.
Oh, I didn't mean
that in a bad way.
Is that how you see me -
some sort of father figure?
Jesus, you're not old enough
to be a father figure.
Why?
Is that something that
bothers you, our age difference?
No, I think you're
very mature for your age.
It is possible to be
a 30-year-old gay man,
and not be obsessed
with Lady Gag Me.
That's a relief.
[clears throat]
But I, um...
I am seeing other people.
One other person,
to be precise.
That's cool.
We'll play it by ear,
just see what happens.
Oh, my God!
Where did you learn to do that?
Saw it in one of those
sex manuals I read
when I first came out.
Never been with anybody flexible
enough to do it with before.
Pilates...
It makes all the difference.
So, when did you come out?
- Officially?
- Officially.
Eight years ago.
And unofficially?
I guess I always knew,
I just didn't want to face it.
So what pushed you out
after all those years?
Actually, it was Colton.
Really?
It's not like he knew
and encouraged me,
nothing like that.
Then what?
It was watching him grow up
100 percent comfortable
with who he is.
I learned a lot from him.
Did he come out early?
He was one of those kids
you always knew was gay.
All the stereotypes were there.
His mom says his afterbirth
was filled with glitter.
[laughs]
That's definitely gay.
I really loved
watching him grow up,
seeing him become his own man.
And it gave me the courage
to do it myself.
And your wife?
She knew.
Or at least, she suspected.
We were
best friends in college,
got married when
she got pregnant,
did everything we
were supposed to do.
And luckily we're still friends.
Did she remarry?
She did...
To a lovely philosophy professor
named Naomi.
Seriously?
Seriously.
We're the all-American family
for the new millennium.
Well, you did
a great job raising Colton.
We have to tell him.
I know.
[doorbell rings]
- Morning.
- Hey.
What, bad time?
No, uh...
- Hey, you're off today, right?
- Right.
Could you do me a favor and
call me if you see my father?
He didn't come home last night,
he's not answering his phone.
I'm sure he's fine.
Probably... Definitely.
It's not like
he hasn't stayed over
at some random guy's
house before, right?
Right.
But if you see him,
could you give me a call?
[cell phone rings]
I'll get that!
Dad?
Morning.
Doug!
What's going on?!
I think we found
a way to tell him.
Dude! That is classic.
Not so much.
So the old guy was just
standing there totally naked?
Naked, and still not old.
[SNAP!]
Um, that's how you'll feel
after doing Pilates for a while.
Not old.
Yeah, but what about
the naked part?
You'll look good naked too.
Yeah, that's it.
All righty then!
So who's bigger?
What?
If I have to hear about
your bizarre love triangle,
at least share some
of the disgusting details.
No!
One of them has a pencil dick,
just like you, right?
I do not have a pencil dick!
Forget you heard that.
So how did you explain
the sitch to young Colton?
Well, after he ran out,
and we caught up
to him at the house...
I meant to tell you.
We were dating first.
First?!
What does that mean,
you call dibs on him?
Don't be childish, Colton.
Fuck you!
Oh, wait, I guess
you covered that.
Well, uh, yeah--
Oh, my God!
You fucked my dad?
For the record,
I fucked him first.
- Jacob!
- Dad!
Too much information?
For a lifetime!
Just because I'm your father
doesn't mean I can't
have an active sex life.
Yeah, but not with my boyfriend!
Boyfriend?
Whatever.
You think of me
as your boyfriend?
Yeah.
I guess.
I thought I did.
And so what
do you think of me as?
Boyfriend seems such
a silly word for someone my age.
Yeah, tell me.
Fine.
I think of you...
as my...boyfriend.
And now, also apparently,
my son's boyfriend.
♪
Please tell me you
didn't have a three-way.
No, we did not have a three-way!
I care about you both.
You're both great guys.
I am.
Yes, you are.
You're not so bad...
sometimes.
I know.
So, can we find a way
to work through this?
How? I don't want
to stop seeing you.
Neither do I.
And I don't want to stop
seeing both of you.
It's just...
If you weren't...
you know, what you are.
If you weren't,
would it be such a problem?
No.
But we are what we are.
Yeah, which means we have
to be really careful
of each other's feelings.
Right?
- Right.
- Of course.
So why don't we keep dating
and see where things lead?
It's gonna lead you right to
a bad daytime talk show;
that's where
it's gonna lead you.
It's not that bad, Evvy.
It's some gay version
of Oedipus, or something.
I think you need to
read up on your classics.
Ah....whatever.
It's odd.
It will lead to heartache.
Or triple suicide.
Or bad '80s ballads.
Well, I think you're right
about the heartache part.
And the '80s ballads.
And you are a smart man.
How did you not see this coming?
Oh, right,
because this happens so often.
What, I should have expected it?
You should always
expect the worst.
Being a mother
has taught me that.
Yeah, but your son is...
A holy terror,
that's what he is.
You said it.
Hey, that's my kid
you're talking about.
Well, but you just said--
No, no, no,
I can say whatever I want.
You can not.
Mother's prerogative.
Why are we friends again?
Because no one else
will have you,
my anal-retentive sweetheart.
I am not anal-retentive.
I'm organized.
Compartmentalized.
Except in the bedroom.
Yeah, that's a little messy.
I was talking about
your father-son special.
Hey, I have been
really good up until now,
about keeping them from,
like, running into each other.
Let me get you a medal.
Ooh! I'll give you
one of Jaden's.
I swear they give kids medals
these days just for showing up.
Well, isn't that
supposed to be good for,
like, their self-esteem?
I don't know.
But have you ever tried keeping
your child's collection
of useless,
baseless medals on display?
Every single medal,
ribbon and trophy has to be out.
It's like something
from one of those...
those child abuse shows
on beauty pageants.
I don't think that's
a show about child abuse.
Potato, potato skins, whatever.
Of course you're anal-retentive.
You're gay.
We're all anal.
And I'm exceptionally anal.
I don't think that means
exactly what you think it does
in this context.
Since I don't know
what context means,
let's move on, shall we?
I do like that she used
that word, compartmentalized,
because that is so you.
- Is not.
- Is so.
How?
Easy.
Your bestest gal pal, Evelyn,
the one who gives you
such stellar advice?
Yeah?
Why haven't I ever met her?
You haven't?
You know I haven't.
I know.
We've known each other
ever since you moved to town.
And you've known
Evelyn since, when?
- College.
- So, how...
Wait, you didn't fuck her,
did you?
Woody, no!
So she wasn't
some college fling
that you've tried to forget
just by swallowing
as many dicks as you can?
Um, no.
But, thanks for asking.
I always thought you two
hooked up in college.
I'm gay, Derek,
I always have been.
I know, but still.
Have you had sex with a dude
just to see if you liked it?
- No.
- Exactly.
Not that there's
anything wrong with that.
Can I get back to my story now?
Please do.
Anyway, you've known me almost
as long as you've known her.
We all live in the same town.
And yet, you never bring
your different friends together.
Yes, I do.
I tried.
My birthday,
when you were...sick.
Oh, right... You did.
You know, you tried,
good point.
You failed miserably,
as you so often do.
Not helping.
I'm trying to help.
You just like to
have things in their place.
You have your employees at work,
who you order around,
which I know
you secretly like to do.
- I do not.
- Yes, you do.
And work gives you that.
And you have me,
for when you want to go dancing
or get fashion advice
on your pathetic wardrobe.
And you hang out with Evelyn
when you want to see
how the breeders are living,
or get fashion advice
on your pathetic wardrobe.
You gave me this tie, FYI.
Oh, honey...
it was a joke.
Bow ties are cool.
Are they, though?
The only time I've ever
approved of your wardrobe
was on that cruise,
when you coordinated
your cock rings
with your swimsuits.
[chuckles]
Well, who doesn't do that?
Oh, you'd be surprised.
Back to the subject at hand.
Everyone has friends that
do different things for them.
You have several of us,
and you're lucky to have us.
And we do have
one thing in common.
Bitchiness.
You.
So, yeah,
bitchiness actually covers it.
Thanks a lot.
I just--
I hope that your lovers
don't start getting
all competitive.
Not gonna happen.
By the way, I made
plans for dinner tonight.
Picnic in the park,
and a walk around the lake.
- Mmmm.
- Sound good?
Can't wait.
I made dinner
reservations for tomorrow night.
The new Italian place downtown -
supposed to be fabulous.
Mmmm, can't wait.
I got us tickets for that
concert you were talking about.
I thought it was sold out.
I pulled some strings.
Mmmm...
Can't wait.
I got us two tickets to the
philharmonic Saturday night.
Front orchestra.
Beethoven's Ninth.
His ninth seat,
in the front orchestra?
His ninth symphony, philistine.
[chuckles]
Can't wait.
Don't forget we're playing
tennis this afternoon.
Don't forget we have tickets
to the tennis tournament
at Indian Wells this weekend.
I'm busy this weekend,
but next weekend I'm free.
Super.
'Cause I booked us at that
amazing little resort
in Palm Springs.
You know, the one in
that movie we just watched?
That's awesome!
And unlike the movie, this one
really is clothing optional.
Oh, I can't wait.
The weekend after next?
No, I don't have plans.
You do now.
I booked us a suite at
my favorite hotel in Las Vegas.
Vegas?
I'm not much of a gambler.
That's OK.
We don't ever have
to leave the room.
Can't wait.
I'm exhausted.
Too much work, or too much sex?
Too much of everything.
Traveling, concerts,
dinners out, dinners in,
clubs, parties.
You name it, they have tried it.
And I'm supposed to go to
Vegas this weekend with Jacob.
Question:
Did the last restaurant
you go to
have crayons so you
could draw on the menu?
No.
Then don't complain to me about
being forced to go to Las Vegas.
OK?
Where's that delightfully
well-mannered,
so polite son of yours?
Playdate at the park...
It took us three months
to set it up.
The parents are very wealthy.
And why are you whispering?
Because that's what you do when
you talk about wealthy people.
Are you afraid
they're gonna hear you?
Yes.
Well, why don't you
just tell them to back off?
Your child's playdate's
wealthy parents?
No, your lovers.
I don't want to.
I just want...
I want...
What?
Jesús H. Christo!
Use your grownup words.
If I knew what I wanted
I wouldn't be
in this predicament.
Well, that's true.
And 25 points for the use
of the word predicament.
But you know what they say.
No, what do they say?
You can't have a predicament,
without a big dick
in the middle.
- They say that?
- Yes, they do.
- Who says that?
- Everyone.
T-shirts, bumper stickers,
license plates.
You have been
no help at all, thank you.
Want some wine?
It's in Mommy's
special sippy cup.
That is not wine!
[giggles]
Vegas looked a lot bigger
in the pictures.
I wanted to surprise you.
Surprise.
So no slot machines?
Vegas would have been fun,
but I thought this would be
a little more intimate.
But I brought clothes
to go out at night.
You can still go out at night -
to get firewood.
You brought me up here
to get you wood?
That's one way of putting it.
What's another way?
I wanted to keep you
on your toes.
How about on my knees?
Even better.
So, you rented this place
for the whole weekend.
I didn't rent it;
I own it.
You own it?
Every square inch.
I can't believe you own
a cabin in the mountains.
We bought it years ago.
Well, I love it.
- It's quaint.
- Thank you.
It's very...old fashioned.
I think so.
It's very you.
You can shut up now.
That's the boys' bedroom.
Sorry...
I forgot we aren't going to
mention Colton this weekend.
Listen, I shouldn't
have said that.
You can talk about
whatever you want.
He's your son.
Deal.
That is the small bedroom,
twin beds.
Please tell me
there's a bigger bedroom.
There's a bigger bedroom.
- With a bigger bed?
- With a bigger bed.
Tell me where.
End of the hallway,
past the bathroom.
Lead the way.
Just what I need -
peace and qui...
Hmm.
Whoo, peace and quiet,
and a shower.
[door closes]
You heard that, right?
I heard something.
Everything looks OK.
Go lock the front door,
just in case.
Good idea.
Feel safer now?
Much.
- Hey, didn't you--
- Let's go to bed.
[chuckling in distance]
[wood clunks on floor...
door closes]
Are there wild animals up here?
Besides me?
Besides you.
Oh, yeah, lots.
That must be it.
Must be.
Have you ever had
any break-ins up here?
Couple of times.
One guy was here for a week
before we caught him.
Well, that's not creepy at all.
I'm sure it's fine.
Don't be so nervous.
I'm not nervous.
Do you think somebody's
gonna walk in and catch us?
Maybe...
And maybe I'd like it.
Get your ass to bed.
Only my ass?
[shower running]
You said there were
wild animals up here.
Right.
And they sometimes
get inside the cabin.
Sometimes.
Have they ever
taken a shower before?
Not to my knowledge.
On three.
One...
two...
three!
[yells]
- Colton!
- Dad?
- Doug?
- Seriously?
Seriously?
It's not my fault.
We were right
in the middle of--
Ah!!! I don't want to know.
Who am I kidding.
This is hilarious.
Of course, I want to know!
Fine. We were just about to--
Bro, stop.
I don't want to know.
Fine!
It's what you and Karen did
for your last anniversary.
Nice.
Anyway...
What are you doing here?
I could ask you the same thing!
You were supposed
to be in Vegas!
Change of plans.
I thought I'd show
Doug the cabin.
I wanted to come the cabin
while you were out of town.
Where's your car, anyway?
I parked it around back.
And can we please
put some clothes on!
Can I use this as
a case study for my patients?
No!
You're not supposed to be here!
Yu were supposed to be spending
the weekend with your friends!
They bailed on me!
Besides, you know I come
to the cabin when I'm upset!
I didn't think you
were that upset!
- Of course, I'm upset!
- Why?
Because!
My father
is fucking my boyfriend.
And my boyfriend's
fucking my father.
Oh...that.
Look...
Clearly this is all my fault.
No, it's not.
Of course, it is.
You can't blame him.
Why not?
Yeah, why not?
I mean, I am
the one that started
seeing you both
at the same time.
You couldn't put
two and two together?
Was I supposed to ask
if your gay father
lived in the neighborhood?
Because that doesn't come up
in normal conversation.
Sorry.
Can't you understand
what I see in each of you?
I can see it.
I guess I can...
Even though he's old.
Watch it.
Your father is ten years
older than I am.
I'm ten years older than you.
How is that different?
Because...
Exactly.
Believe me, when you get
to a certain age,
it really doesn't seem
to be such a big deal.
Really?
Really.
I mean,
naturally there are differences
between the two of you.
Like what?
Yes, like what?
Serious?
Fine.
You are impulsive...
in a good way.
You go with the flow.
Like when someone
mistakes me for a stripper?
Like that.
And you care enough
about your father
to let him live with you
after his house sold so quickly.
Above asking price, I might add.
And he needed a place to live
until he could find a new house.
That was very nice of you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
And you are comfortable
in your skin
in the way that only people
who have made the decision
to come out late in life can be.
Later...later in life.
Not late, I'm not dead.
Later in life.
And you're kind and generous.
See, he wants your money.
He has money?
So not the point.
Sorry.
You're generous with
your time and your heart.
And you love
your son, unconditionally.
And I appreciate that
more than you'll ever know.
See...
You're both great guys.
Frankly, I don't see
what you see in me.
- I don't either.
- Clueless.
Shut up.
So.
I'm not ready
to choose between you.
Not yet.
- But--
- But what?
I have made a decision
about one thing.
Well, this isn't
what I had planned.
Ain't that the truth.
And we can agree that this
would be a little less awkward
if we didn't both sleep nude?
I think we can agree on that.
Doug is nice to
wake up to in the morning.
Stop talking...
Now.
♪
[door closes]
Morning.
Sleep well?
Not really.
Neither did we.
Sorry.
He snores.
I know.
And he shouldn't have
had beans for dinner.
Ooh, that can get ugly.
We were talking.
And we made a decision.
Do you want me
to sit down for this?
We thought...
We both thought this
would work itself out.
Either you'd have stronger
feelings for one of us...
Or one of us would have
stronger feelings for you.
But...it seems
we're at a stalemate.
I know, and...I'm sorry.
Unfortunately, that's not
enough anymore.
Meaning what?
Meaning we both decided
to stop seeing you.
Both of you?
Both of us.
It's not fair to us,
and it's not fair to you.
It's not fair to spend time
with the only two men
I've ever really loved?
Can you really love
two men at the same time?
I know it doesn't
make logical sense,
and I know it doesn't conform
to society's norms, but...
yeah, I do...
I love you both.
If we weren't in this
fucked-up situation,
we might give you
the time to figure it out.
But we are in this
fucked-up situation,
as Colton so aptly put it.
And we just can't
do it any more.
So that's it?
Both just gone from my life?
I guess so.
You couldn't make
a decision, Doug.
We had to.
Sorry.
We're both sorry.
♪
There we go.
First hint of a smile
I've seen in three weeks.
Sorry...
I've had a lot on my mind.
I know.
You've shared it with me,
over and over and over.
Have I been that bad?
Abso-fucking-lutely.
Careful...
That model child of yours
will hear you.
That kid learned the word bitch
on the playground last week,
and has proceeded
to call me a bitch ever since.
So he's perceptive, too?
Yeah, I guess he is.
But enough about me.
How can I help you?
Get them back?
Oh, sweetie, If I thought
it would help, I would try.
But you don't?
Do you?
I think so.
I don't know anymore.
You know, if Jaden
turns out to be gay,
just make sure this
never happens to him.
Oh, my God,
I hope he turns out gay!
Then I would actually have
something in common with him.
Unfortunately, that boy
is just like his father.
Behaviors do run in the family.
You know what I think?
I think it's all genetic.
What?
Everything.
Yeah, I think it's all genetics,
like DNA.
But it's just so random that
there's no way to understand it.
Well, I think some scientists
might disagree with you.
No, no, take you
and your brother.
Fraternal twins.
You don't look anything alike.
Which I find odd, by the way.
I think your mother's
hiding something.
Maybe we were switched at birth.
Ooh, fun.
But let's assume no,
that did not happen.
You're twins, you're raised in
the same house, in the same way,
but you're gay
and he's straight.
What's up with that?
Well, actually, studies show--
I'm not finished,
and I don't care
about your studies.
It's genetics, I tell you.
Take Jacob and Colton...
father and son, both gay.
Both inexplicably
attracted to you.
Why?
Genetics....
Genetics, like DNA.
Like, something deep down
in their DNA
is attracted to something
deep down in your DNA.
And vice versa,
but because they're both gay,
you're not sure which one
you're supposed
to be attracted to.
That makes absolutely no sense.
No, it does, it does.
It's genetics, it's like
the pheromones wafting around.
Yes!
It's like you're sensing
something from one of them,
but the other one
is giving off a false scent.
And I'm supposed to figure out
which one is real,
and which one is the placebo?
Yes!
Give me that wine.
That is the right answer,
my dear.
Doug.
Dougie.
Douglas.
Doogie!
Look on the bright side.
There's a bright side?
Sure.
You didn't want to have
to choose between them,
and now you don't have to.
My God, you should go
into motivational speaking.
I know.
Is it working?
Not one little bit.
OK, what did Evelyn
say about it?
She gave me
a lecture about genetics.
Why?
I have no idea.
Wait, how'd you know
I talked to her?
Because you always talk to her
about important stuff first.
And I don't mind.
I mean, after all, she has
made a relationship work.
And she even had a kid.
Well, you know
I value your advice, too.
Please, like I have
anything to contribute
to a conversation
about relationships...
Until now.
Wait... What?
I kinda met someone.
When?
Well, it was
right around that time
of that mountain
cabin fiasco, so...
And you didn't tell me?
I couldn't very well tell you
about something great
happening to me when
you're going through...this.
Yes, you can,
I want to know these things.
Lord knows you've
heard my share of drama.
Can I hear an AMEN?
And despite that remark,
I'm always here for you.
Good times, bad times.
Are you about
to burst into song?
Maybe!
But first...
Spill your guts.
I want the dish.
Oh, OK.
Well, he's just a little, teensy
weeny, itsy bitsy, tiny bit...
older than me.
Older than your real age,
or older than the age
you tell everybody you are?
Both.
And he wears the worst
sweaters you've ever seen.
I mean, really, really bad.
And yet...
he's really sweet.
Oh, my God...
You like sweet?
I do now.
Plus, he's hung
like an elephant.
That's the Woody I know.
Oh, my gosh.
Congratulations.
Wait, how...
where did you meet?
Get this...
My mom set us up.
How random is that?
Wow.
Life is random,
trust me on that.
I'm so excited for you!
Look at you...
You're all glowing.
And I will be happy for you,
no matter what happens
with Jacob and Colton.
So...
What do you
think's gonna happen?
[sighs]
Honestly?
I don't think I'll ever see
either one of them again.
Doug, you OK?
Fine.
Is my next client here?
No, but you do have a visitor.
- Hey.
- Hi.
He was asking about you,
so I just wanted
to make sure he found you.
There he is.
And thanks for the introduction.
I'm Philip.
I'm Doug's number-one employee,
and I'm in an open relationship.
Philip.
Just putting it out there.
Nice to meet you.
You must be Jacob, right?
No, I'm Colton.
Right, and I'm leaving.
I...
I wanted to see
where you worked.
I hope you don't mind.
No...
Not at all.
It's very...clean.
I'll take that as a compliment.
It is.
Clean. Organized...
Just like you.
Thanks...
I think.
Yeah, that didn't
come out so good, did it?
Why are you here?
Why do you think?
I miss you.
So, did you come here
to make your case?
Sell me?
Sell you?
Tell me that this has
all been one big mistake.
Well, would that be so wrong?
No.
I'd do the same thing
if I was in your position.
What would you say?
You know, if you
were in my position?
I'd say that you wanted
to get to know me better,
and that you could
see a future with me.
Well, that's all true.
Then why didn't you
just say that?
I don't want to say
anything bad about my father.
That's not how I was raised.
But as much as
I hate this situation...
I still love you.
When my father came out,
I wasn't that surprised, really.
But I was worried.
I didn't have to be.
Why not?
Because he's smart,
he's grounded.
He's everything I want to be.
Which is why I know
he'll be strong enough
to get through this
if you choose me.
♪
[doorbell rings]
Jacob...
What are you doing here?
Hope you don't
mind me stopping by.
No, not at all.
I brought wine.
Thanks.
Do you want to sit down?
No, I really can't stay.
But I have wine.
Which you may need after this.
After what?
After I tell you I think
you should be with Colton.
Why?
What happened?
What happened is that I see
how much this is hurting my son.
Don't get me wrong, Doug,
I love you...
I really do.
And I love you.
But I love Colton in a way
that you may never understand.
You make sacrifices for
your kids to make them happy.
Yeah, like staying in
a marriage that doesn't work?
Among other things.
You've sacrificed
for Colton your entire life.
What do you want?
What I want, more than anything,
is for my son to be happy.
And your happiness?
That comes second.
If you ever have kids,
you'll see.
He's stronger than you realize.
Thanks to you,
he could survive anything.
I know.
I've thought about this a lot,
and I'm content
with my decision.
And at least I'll still
have you in my life.
How did you know?
How did I know what?
How did you know
that Karen was the one for you?
Are you serious?
More than I have
ever been before.
I don't know...
You can't tell
anyone this, OK?
Your secret is safe with me.
When Karen and I
first started dating,
I was seeing other girls.
Just casual, nothing serious.
Yeah, I remember.
But when I made
plans with Karen,
I just felt...
different, excited.
Not excited,
that's not the word.
Um...
Then what?
I felt...content.
Like nothing could go wrong.
Like being with her was exactly
where I was supposed to be.
I don't know
if that makes sense.
Yeah, makes perfect sense.
I just want you to have
what I found with Karen.
So just ask yourself -
does one of those
men next door
make you feel content?
Not just happy, but content?
Yeah...
One of them does.
♪
[doorbell rings]
I made my decision...
I choose you.
Did you pick up the wine?
Do I ever forget the wine?
No, but do I ever
forget to remind you?
Never.
Is it on the table?
It's on the table.
- Evelyn likes red.
- We have red.
We have white.
We have champagne.
We have champagne?
Excellent.
And everyone's here.
Well, almost everyone.
Has anyone ever told you
you're anal-retentive?
Only 3,451 times.
- And you kept track of that?
- I did.
Anal-retentive.
Detail-oriented.
Potato, vodka shots,
whatever.
[door closes]
Fashionably late, as always.
Would you expect anything else?
Never.
Evening, boys.
Hey, Dad.
Is that for me?
You know it is.
I thought you gave me
my present earlier.
Sshh, not in front of the kid.
Happy Birthday, Sweetie.
I love you.
I know.
There you are.
Evelyn sent me in
to hurry it up.
She's dying for her
cake and booze fix.
More the booze than the cake.
Just like the rest of us.
So glad you could come.
And miss
his stepfather's birthday?
Not a chance.
Hey!
What did I tell you?
Don't call me your stepfather;
it makes me feel old.
You are old, remember?
You grab the cake.
You grab him.
And you grab me.
I can't believe
all this worked out.
The party?
No. This...
Us...
Colton...
Everything.
This has to rank as one of
my most unusual courtships.
More unusual than being married
to a lesbian for 20 years?
Pretty close.
Still think you made
the right decision?
I definitely
made the right decision.
I can't believe you chose me.
Sometimes, you just
got to go with your gut.
Deep down, I knew
Colton wasn't right for me.
It just took my heart
a little longer to realize it.
He's a good man.
And he seems to have
bounced back quickly enough.
That's all thanks to you.
♪
Now, let's go celebrate
with your friends.
[all chattering]
Wait, you never told me how
your father and Doug met.
Um, that's a long story.
Hey, it's the birthday boy!
[applause]
Best... Birthday... Ever.
♪