(ominous music)
[Man] Hello, Dr. Martin.
He can't find the lab. (laughs)
(humming)
(electricity zapping)
(laughs)
(Dr. Martin clears throat)
Dr. Martin.
Now you're mapping the facial muscle
control regions, right?
(clears throat) Yes.
Have you finished?
Not quite.
Well, I wonder why.
All right.
Go into the stacks, get
me two more Class 3s.
Class 3.
Yes, sir.
Right away.
(electricity zaps)
Paranoia.
Down there.
No, I need paranoia.
Paranoia.
(gasps)
(glass shatters)
Berkovitch.
Well?
What?
Not what, who?
Who?
Who fell?
One of the specimens.
Class 4, I think.
Theo.
I thought that we understood each other.
People, Berkovitch.
Individuals, minds, souls.
Every brain is a living record of a life.
A journey taken.
Who knows what journey
they're on now, hmm?
Now, who fell?
(Theo sighs)
Montag.
Phillip Montag.
That's parietal paralysis.
I think we're fairly well
covered on that area, but still.
The place just won't be
the same without him.
Gather up what you can.
Prepare a new bottle, 80% more gelatin,
and we'll see if we can
keep the old boy together.
Yes, sir.
(humming)
Morning, Mr. Hoffencamp.
How's every little floating thing?
Oh, yeah?
You don't say.
Feeling a little suspicious?
Persecuted?
I see.
Like somebody studying
you or observing you.
Right.
Well, that's correct.
Just remember, Hal, that
just because you're paranoid,
doesn't mean they aren't out to get you.
(ominous music)
Are you all right, Dr. Martin?
Oh, nothing that a little
brain surgery couldn't cure.
(chuckles)
Now, where was I?
Um...
All that we suffer.
Right.
Or enjoy comes from the
brain and its condition.
Whether it's hot, cold, moist, dry.
Madness, in particular,
stems from its moistness.
Hippocrates, 4th century BC.
I'll type this up.
Thanks.
The universe is just a wet dream.
By the perception of
illusion, we experience reality.
The inscrutable Professor Ang.
Ah, see?
The liberal arts course
pays off after all.
Have you been drinking?
You always get cryptic
after you've been drinking.
It's the only way I
can keep my lunch down.
I just spent the last hour
and a half being grilled
by the chairman over a
plate of calamari fungi.
He says I'm not people-oriented.
Now, what the hell is
that supposed to mean?
I don't know.
I'm brain-oriented and that doesn't seem
to have anything to do with people.
Exactly.
How would you know?
You're your own boss,
you do your own work.
You married the smartest,
prettiest girl in our class.
It was me or you and you lost.
That's about the only thing you ever lost.
No, I lost Halsey.
I lost the numbers.
Shit, I'm probably gonna lose my job.
What are you talking about?
Do you know Lakeside?
Yeah, it's a mental institution.
Correct.
We own it.
Oh, you own it, huh?
Well, the corporation has
very diversified interests.
From the tridium that feeds the rockets
to the powdered milk
that feeds the babies.
We're Eunice.
All right.
What about Lakeside?
There's a patient there, a
former employee name of Halsey.
The man was a genius, but he lost it.
Butchered his family and plead insanity.
But some of the board members
feel he might be dissembling.
Well, why would he fake it?
Halsey wasn't exactly happy
with some of the applications
his work might be put to.
Look, maybe he's just
trying to get out of it.
The point is, he's nuts.
He's not responsible,
but I am responsible.
You see, Halsey was my baby.
So now, I'm in shit city with the board
and he's in a rubber
room totally paranoid.
Oh.
Paranoid.
So, this is what it's all about, huh?
Hmm.
Jim.
I didn't know who else I could turn to.
I mean, nobody knows more
about paranoia than you.
You're the brain man for Christ sakes.
I don't do corporate science.
I told you that.
Aw, come on.
As a favor to me, would
you go to Lakeside?
Visit Ward 8, ask for Halsey.
I'm not a psychiatrist.
Then run a few tests.
See what you think.
Besides, aren't you getting a
little tired of bottle brains?
Here's one you can have fresh.
(ominous music)
♪ Oh, look at me ♪
♪ Look at me ♪
♪ Oh, look at me, I'm dancing ♪
♪ I love me, I love me ♪
♪ Look at me, look at me ♪
♪ I'm dancing, I'm dancing ♪
Excuse me.
I'm looking for Mr. Halsey.
Right over there.
Thank you.
(woman laughing)
Mr. Halsey?
Conklin send you?
No.
My wife send you?
My lawyer?
[Dr. Martin] No, Mr. Halsey.
I didn't say I was Halsey.
Well, I'm sorry.
You see, I was told that.
You're not from Conklin?
No.
Nor from your wife.
My wife?
What's she to you?
How long have you known her?
What do you mean?
Sit down.
Thank you.
I'm Halsey.
I've been expecting you.
Let's go somewhere where we can talk.
He didn't trust me.
I didn't trust her.
And she didn't trust him.
You see?
Yes, go on.
Smilin' Ed pays me in cash, right?
Always has.
Son, Conklin pays cash.
Checks are for bankers and grifters.
But when I look, I don't see Ben Franklin.
No, siree.
I see Conklin's greasy
face smiling up at me.
It was his way of spying on me
with his little face in my pocket.
And worse, much worse.
What?
He fucked my wife.
Right there in the factory
on the perfect sleeper.
And that man, he's the troublemaker.
He's even followed me in here.
He's in the hospital.
Dr. Martin, he wants to kill me.
Mr. Halsey, have you ever
heard of Eunice Corporation?
Eunice.
That's my wife's name.
No, this is a corporation.
Maybe you did some mathematical
work for them or something.
I work with numbers, sure,
but I work for Conklin.
Conklin Mattresses.
I'm an accountant.
Neat little rows and columns.
No equations.
Equations are too messy.
You get a few numbers left over and boom.
End of the world as we know it.
No.
I stick to accounts.
It's safer.
Safer?
Are you familiar with
the Hippocratic Oath?
Doctors take it.
Right, but maybe everybody should.
At least do no harm.
I think that's a fine rule.
We can't all do good,
but at least do no harm.
Mr. Halsey, would you mind
if I ran a few tests on you?
Just make a few maps?
All simple, all completely painless.
Would that be all right?
Does it pay cash money?
No.
I'll take it.
(machines beeping)
(computer beeping)
[Dr. Martin] Well, one thing's for sure.
Halsey's not faking.
Oh, really?
How do you know?
Well, look at these.
Brain maps of three certified paranoids.
See this green area here, here, here?
That's the abnormality.
That's the fly in the
ointment, if you will.
Now, here's Halsey.
See that?
Same thing.
[Jim] Fantastic.
How soon can you operate?
Operate?
No, no, no.
This is all theoretical work.
I need maybe two more years of lab work,
and then two years of animal research,
and then I think we might just
chance opening somebody up.
I haven't got four years.
I haven't even got four weeks.
Why not just cut it out?
No, no, no, no.
You open that door and
you step off a cliff.
It's awfully risky.
Especially for Halsey.
Halsey was working on something big.
Cornerstone technology.
That's all I can tell you.
It's classified shit.
When Halsey lost his marbles,
he destroyed his results.
We need those numbers
or we need to make sure
that nobody else will ever get them.
Jim.
You want him brain dead.
Who said anything about brain dead?
Don't you believe your own theories?
Afraid to put 'em to the test?
No.
Come on.
You can't stand there
and tell me you haven't
dreamed of an opportunity like this.
A living brain.
Think of it.
I...
I just wouldn't feel right about it.
Sorry, Jim.
I'd rather not.
Oh, for Christ sakes.
Would you quit thinking
about Halsey for a second
and think about yourself?
You see, in a sense, you
already work for Eunice.
Eunice?
Don't be so naive.
Who's research isn't
corporate funded these days?
I mean, it's either us or
the Department of Defense.
That doesn't mean that you own me.
Don't you want to change
the world and get rich?
What if Halsey refuses?
Well, Halsey's really not
in a position to choose.
And nor am I?
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
Look at it this way, it could be worse.
You could be the patient and
Halsey could be the doctor.
(laughs)
(horn honks)
Whoa.
He's got my brain.
Fuck, shit, my brain.
It's my fucking brain, goddamn it.
Shit.
Piss fucking shit.
Give me my fucking brain.
That's my fucking brain!
No.
Yes.
It's my fucking brain.
- No.
- It's my brain.
Sir, there must be some mistake.
There's no mistake.
It's my brain!
- This is my brain.
- That's my brain!
My brain!
No, you have your own brain.
This is mine and you can't have it.
- It's my fucking brain!
- Please, sir.
I'm afraid that it is not your.
(tense music)
(tires squealing)
(glass shatters)
(siren wailing)
(chatter on police radio)
(echoed chattering)
Let's put the cages over here
and the freezers along
this wall over here.
Oh, Martin.
How embarrassing.
Ellis.
Sorry to hear about your grant.
I think it's outrageous.
I mean, what ever happened
to academic freedom?
Bastards own us, Rex.
Lock, stock, and barrel.
You've got guts.
I'll say that for you, not me.
Do I question why the
US Army is interested
in endocrine secretion?
Chemical regulators of human behavior.
Well, you can bet your
bottom dollar I don't.
What do you want?
I know it's terrible of
me to barge in here so soon,
but, well, I have to be in
Washington all next week.
I'm sorry.
I thought they told you.
My grant has been doubled.
We need more space.
And you know, I love all this shelf space.
By the way, what are you
going to do with all of these?
I don't know.
Tell you what.
I can probably use most of them.
Of course, all I really need
are the endocrine receptors,
but I'll pay you by the pound.
Charge as much as you want.
Our Uncle Sam is picking
up the tab on this one.
Get out of here.
(chuckles)
What?
You heard me.
Get out of here.
Both of you.
No need to be nasty, Rex.
I'm just trying to do you a favor.
They're individuals.
They're special.
They're unique.
You're not going to grind them up
into your brain shake smears.
Get out.
All right.
No problem, Rex.
Just make sure that you
and all of your friends
are out by the end of the week.
Let's go, Bixby.
Just a minute.
(yells)
(tense music)
(metal clattering)
(glass shattering)
Oh, no.
(sighs)
Yeah.
Bad dream?
Oh, it was so vivid.
It must be an aftershock of the accident.
Accident?
What accident?
Oh, I had a little
accident this afternoon.
I think.
Or was that part of my dream?
Jim said you seemed a
little tense this afternoon.
When did you see Jim?
Since when do you and Jim get
together to talk about me?
Relax.
He called me.
He's my friend, too.
Oh, great.
You and Jim, huh?
We should both get together and decide.
What's the matter?
I don't know why you're so upset.
I'd think you'd be excited.
Oh, I don't know.
I guess I'm a little afraid.
I don't want to rush into anything.
You've been poking
around in people's brains
as long as I've known you.
What makes this one so different?
Halsey.
Halsey makes it different.
He was a full fellow at the
Institute for Advanced Studies
when he was 14.
I was still reading Tom
Swift, boy scientist.
So, what happened to him?
Tom Swift?
No, silly.
Halsey.
Oh.
Well, they said he went nuts.
He killed his wife, two kids,
and three research assistants.
Genius, maybe, but
definitely not a nice guy.
No, quite to the contrary.
He's a very sweet man.
I met him today.
He likes me.
I'm so glad you're making new friends.
Morning, boys.
Would you buy me a pack
of cigarettes, please?
Oh, sure.
My money's no good here.
Well, here's a couple of bucks.
No, no.
Give me your wallet.
You think I want every
Joe in the joint to know
who's buying me my cigarettes?
Trust me.
All right.
Here.
Old man RJ was nobody's fool.
You can learn a thing or
two from this beast's back.
Look real close.
You can see a man there.
He's pissing.
See?
It's Franklin Roosevelt.
There.
That's his willy.
Actually, it's Rosenfeld.
It's true.
He changed his name.
I read it in a book.
And there in the lion.
You can see a giant bald eagle
mounting a naked woman from behind.
Halsey, I need your help.
[Halsey] You do?
Yes.
Here, let me help you with that.
In fact, I think you're
probably the only one
who can help me.
[Halsey] Me?
Why me?
You and I, we have something in common.
[Halsey] What's that?
Well, for one thing, we
both had the same employer.
Son of a bitch!
Halsey.
[Halsey] You work for Conklin!
No, I don't work for Conklin.
I knew it!
Goddamn rotten spy!
No, I'm not a spy.
I don't work for Conklin.
Let me explain it to you this way.
We both know that pure
science exists above all this.
Do you trust me?
[Halsey] I do.
I need to open you up.
I need to examine your brain.
My brain?
You have a special brain,
a very special brain.
That's why we did all those tests.
But tests aren't enough for them now.
I need to show them.
My brain.
I know you feel like
I've railroaded you.
Try blackmailed.
I'm just helping you be you.
You know you want to do this.
And believe me.
Some day when you're rich and famous,
and you're the head of
Eunice's neuroscience division,
you'll thank me.
Mark my words.
You'll thank me for what I did.
Good luck.
(doors whirring)
(tense music)
Mr. Reston, surely you're not suggesting
that Eunice go into the lobotomy business?
We don't need that kind of publicity.
It's not the image
Eunice wants to project.
I was merely using these
unpleasant associations
to illustrate a point.
Dr. Martin's procedure is
quite a different story.
Rex.
He's right.
It's very different than the '50s.
You could call it the
kinder, gentler lobotomy.
Let's get to the point, shall we?
What about Halsey?
Theo.
Mr. Halsey's paranoid psychosis stems from
an abnormality near the sub-visual cortex.
Now I've been doing very
extensive maps on the area.
Skip the map.
Can you cure him?
Restore his mathematical genius?
Stimulate his memory?
At least get the numbers?
In the best possible case,
he may completely recover.
If so, he'll probably
remember the numbers you want
or be able to recalculate them.
If, and only if, he
believes it's appropriate.
And in the worst case?
Tabula rasa.
A clean slate.
It could completely wipe his brain.
Please, proceed, Dr. Martin.
You have our undivided attention.
(tense music)
(electricity zapping)
(laughing)
Mr. Halsey?
Yes.
Are you still with us?
Why are you at Lakeside?
(electricity zaps)
(elegant harpsichord music)
[Halsey] I don't know.
Oh, yes, you do.
What about your family?
They're dead.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
What happened to them?
They were murdered.
Really?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Mr. Halsey?
Yes.
(electricity zaps)
Who killed them, Mr. Halsey?
Conklin.
Black, and white, and red all over.
Shocking.
You didn't kill them yourself?
No.
[Chairman] But what about the numbers?
I'm just an accountant.
Bullshit.
Just give us those numbers, Halsey.
Gentlemen, please.
This is a delicate procedure.
Mr. Halsey.
[Rex] Can you hear me, Mr. Halsey?
Huh?
Yeah.
Mr. Halsey?
Yes?
Is the man who followed you,
the man who killed your family,
this Conklin, is he here?
Yes.
Do you see him?
No.
How do you know that?
He follows me everywhere.
Black, and white, and red all over.
Well, I can't see him, Mr. Halsey.
Why don't you take a look around
just to put your mind at rest?
There he is.
(laughing)
Now, I want you to just relax.
(electricity zapping)
[Jim] Knock, knock.
Mr. Halsey.
Is the man in white still with us?
Look for him, please.
Who are you referring to?
(sighs)
Thank you, Mr. Halsey.
By the way, Mr. Halsey.
What do you do for a living?
I'm a mathematician.
[Rex] And what are you working on now?
I'm not at liberty to discuss it.
I'm sorry.
[Rex] That's quite all right.
(people applauding)
Dr. Martin, you have
written and said many times
that reality is in the brain.
That's right.
Yes.
And yet you give yourself the power
to alter another human being's reality.
Um.
Ethical questions aside,
what are we really talking about here?
What's the growth potential?
I've got this one.
For the last decade
cosmetic plastic surgery
has out grossed every
other medical procedure,
bar none, by several thousand percent.
If people are so anxious to
change their faces and bodies,
what about their personalities,
their very souls?
Had a bad childhood?
We can fix it.
(laughing)
Resculpt your memory, sharpen
your perception, or soften it.
Why not?
And why not Eunice?
Hear, hear.
(people applauding)
See, they love you.
What did I tell you?
Look, I know I pushed you
a little hard on this,
but it's all for the best.
(laughing)
Now you and Dana are meeting the chairman
and I for dinner at eight.
Don't be late.
Yeah, fine.
We'll be there.
[Jim] Excuse me, chairman.
(Conklin laughing)
(ominous music)
(machine beeping)
Halsey.
Bank of Sleepyland.
Damn you, Halsey.
(Conklin laughing)
(tense music)
Get off my tail.
It's not funny anymore.
Hey.
Hey, who the hell are you?
What do you want?
I'll take Manhattan, but
I'll settle for dinner.
What's the matter?
How long have you been behind me?
I don't know, a couple of blocks.
Didn't you hear me honk?
No, I didn't.
But I thought that
somebody was following me.
I guess not.
I'm sorry.
My mistake.
Come on.
Rex, come on.
You okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Do you really think you should drink?
Oh, absolutely.
Now don't get mad, but I.
When you start a sentence like that,
it signals my brain something is coming
that I absolutely will get
mad at and before I know it,
ugly pheromones are
rocketing through my system
and I'm ready to kill.
Did you have a nice day?
All right, Rex.
What's going on?
What's wrong?
I guess I'm a little tired.
I don't mean just tonight.
You've changed.
Sometimes I feel like I hardly know you.
Well, Dana.
I just.
(ominous music)
Hey.
[Dana] Rex.
Hey, you.
Hey, watch it, buddy.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm terribly sorry.
It's my fault.
No harm done.
Yeah, no harm done.
We go back quite a ways.
We were actually roommates in college.
[Dana] Rex.
Rex.
Excuse me.
I'm back.
[Jim] Rex.
Excuse me.
[Jim] We're over here.
Um, do I know you?
Right.
Rex, honey.
Oh.
You need a drink.
Of course.
Excuse me.
I don't believe the two of you
have been formally introduced.
Res, I'd like you to meet Cyril
Vance, chairman of Eunice.
It's an honor and a
pleasure, Dr. Martin.
You're a moron at
your leisure, Mr. Vance.
(laughs) Don't mind
my husband, Mr. Vance.
It's cocktail hour and
I think he's channeling
the voice of Oscar Wilde.
Here we go.
A toast to madness.
Madness is merely moisture on the brain.
Here's proof.
I think he started
celebrating before us.
Cy, the possibilities of
this thing are unlimited.
I mean, this is gonna have
a revolutionary impact
up and down our service and product lines.
Well, I love your idea for
clinics within the communities.
Have you a name for them?
I've got the boys in marketing
revving up their engines.
How about attitude adjustment centers?
How does that grab you?
Awful.
There's no harmony to that.
It's not user friendly.
You're absolutely right, sir.
How about...
I've got it.
The new you from Eunice.
The new (chuckles) you from Eunice.
I love it.
(laughing)
Why not?
Why not a doc-in-the-box
on each corner, hmm?
Slogans, come on in
for a jiffy spinal tap.
$19.95 for a quick lube and lobotomy.
Bang, drive-in service.
You could even do it to yourself.
Self...
I don't know if anybody's
told you about me,
but I'm a purple people.
No, I'm a person pimple.
Uh, people person.
There we go.
People like me, generally,
when they meet me.
Excuse me.
Cy, wait.
Please, let me explain.
He's been under a terrible
strain these last couple weeks.
Shit.
I like people.
Have another drink,
you dumb son of a bitch.
You're finished.
Fine, fire me.
Take my wife, take my life.
That's why I'm here.
[Dana] Rex, calm down.
You're not well.
(tense music)
(sighs)
(laughing)
(breathing heavily)
Oh great, it's home.
Maybe it's stress.
B12 deficiency.
A slight concussion.
I'm glad to be back.
Feels good.
(ominous music)
(Jim yelling)
(screaming)
(Conklin laughing)
Oh, my god.
(doorbell rings)
What's the problem, huh?
I didn't do it.
Okay.
I didn't.
I didn't do it.
Of course you didn't do it.
It's all right.
You're awake now.
Awake?
Just another dream.
Thank God.
Thank God I didn't do it.
Of course not.
Same dream?
Same as what?
As the one last night,
and the night before,
and the night before.
Where am I?
You're in Lakeside, of course.
Lakeside Sanitarium.
Don't you remember, Mr. Martin?
No, I don't.
How did I get here anyway?
What am I doing here?
I would like to speak to
somebody in charge, please.
Well, how are we doing this morning?
It's you.
It's him.
He did it.
He killed them.
He killed them all.
Don't go.
No.
Get away from me, you maniac.
I don't know what's going on here, but.
Did I follow you?
Did I torment you?
Did I, perhaps, even kill your loved ones?
Yes, you did.
Good.
That's very frightening.
Those are very frightening thoughts.
Are you frightened?
Sometimes we have thoughts
that are so frightening,
we can't even admit to
ourselves that we have them.
The only way we can
deal with those thoughts
is to believe that somebody else has them.
Don't do that.
It's not reality yet, but it's progress.
Now, may I have your arm?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
No, you don't.
No, you don't have to
get into any of this.
Now, Mr. Martin.
Dr. Martin.
All right, Dr. Martin.
No, no.
Get away from me.
You don't want me to call
Fred and Dewey, do you?
I don't care who you call.
Now, this has gone far enough.
Now, I demand that return my clothes
and tell me what's going on here.
And I warn you, my wife is a top attorney.
Fred, Dewey!
All right.
This can hurt.
(metal bangs)
Hear that?
(grunting)
I'm gonna sue you.
I'll sue all of you.
There.
That wasn't bad, was it?
Thank you, gentlemen.
Wait at the nurse's station.
I'll call you if I need you.
I wish that you would
stop treating me like.
What?
Like you're what, Mr. Martin?
Whoa.
I'm staring to feel a little racy.
Something...
That was no sedative you gave me.
You are the man who's following me.
I know that.
That's right.
In my best white suit stained with blood.
You killed Jim and Dana.
It's possible to be
distracted by too much detail.
For instance, your dream
could be very simple.
You create yourself as that
which you have always wanted to be.
But some part of you, or
some part of your mind,
is not very comfortable with that,
so you fragment into
another part called Halsey.
And in your dream, Halsey
becomes your patient,
as in actuality, you are my patient.
But in real life, Mr.
Martin, there is no Halsey.
You are Halsey.
(ominous music)
(woman laughing)
(people chattering)
Now, do you think you can behave yourself?
I should think so.
All right.
You can unbuckle him.
Easy, easy.
You all right?
Yes.
Okay.
Toni.
Toni, it's you.
Of course, sir.
I'm here as always.
See, she knows me.
But...
What is this?
How did we get in my office?
Make yourself comfortable, Mr. Martin.
My office is your office.
You can sit in my chair of you'd like,
but I think you'd be more
comfortable over here.
Then I can close the door
and we can start our session.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
What, Mr. Martin?
Rex Francis Martin
born December 7th, 1956.
Pearl Harbor day in Chicago.
The oldest if three children.
My mother's name was Willoughby.
And that's a lithograph, 1548.
I graduated from the University of Chicago
and I have my MD and PhD in neuroscience
from the Miskatonic University.
Got married, Dana and I, in 1979.
She was a lucky catch.
We got married outdoors
in a garden, barefooted.
See, I drive a Volvo with 30,000 miles.
My shirt size is 17-35.
I have no scars, I have no birthmarks,
and I know where the wastepaper basket is.
(paper rattles in can)
Boom.
My office is in the Beaumont
Building, 8th floor.
And this is my office.
Now, will you kindly tell me who you are,
why you are here in my office,
and generally what is the meaning of this?
Those are very reasonable questions.
Very reasonable questions.
Of course, certainly.
- Thank you.
But before I do that,
I'd like you to have a
look at a few things.
Oh.
Now you say your office
is in the Beaumont Building.
You know very well it is.
The 8th floor?
- Yes, this is my office.
- That would be a city view.
This is my office.
A city view, yes?
I don't know how we got here.
Would you take a look out that window
and just tell me what you see?
(birds chirping)
No, it can't be.
It's all right.
I'm fine.
I know, I know you're fine.
It's all right.
Now just...
Over here.
Just look, please.
I can't believe it.
I'm sorry, I can't believe it.
You think you're being hoaxed?
Yes, I think there is
a very real possibility.
It's a very remote possibility, surely.
Why don't you sit down?
You say you're a man of science.
Can you think about this scientifically?
Excuse me, Dr. Ramsen.
Jim.
Jim, Jim, thank God.
Get me out of here.
There's a crazy mix up here.
You remember Jim, our accountant.
Accountant?
No.
Jim's a trained administrator.
He runs the whole R & D department.
Maybe some day, Mr. Martin.
Dr. Ramsen, it's Mr. Martin's account
I came to see you about.
You see, Mr. Conklin's way
behind on his payments.
Conklin?
Who's Conklin?
What's he got to do with my account?
You were his prize accountant.
I don't see how the mattress business
survives without you.
I don't think we need to
discuss this anymore in front of.
(tense music)
You've really been busy.
Must be very satisfying.
Keep up the good work.
Henry.
No, no.
Just don't get up.
Are you lost?
They sometimes send the
lost ones here to me.
This is the lost and found.
Well, it's my idea in the first place.
Oh, it's very good.
I'll take you.
I know where to go.
Without me, you'll never
choose the right door
or you could be eaten
by a tiger. (laughing)
[Rex] This is a closet here.
[Woman] No, it's not.
It's my office.
[Rex] This is a closet.
These are clothes here and
I'd like to get out, please.
[Woman] No, it's my
office, and you're my client,
and you can't go.
[Rex] There's some mistake.
[Woman] Ow!
[Rex] Get away from the door.
(people shouting)
(breathing heavily)
(tense music)
(people groaning)
I see you've just
visited my little museum.
Antique neurological devices are my hobby.
Mankind's efforts to tame madness
make a fascinating history.
Museum?
How can you do this to people?
What people?
These people.
But I saw...
What's this?
People in cages.
You've become overexcited.
Perhaps a little shock
therapy will help you relax.
(fingers snap)
No, I think.
Just a light one.
(tone warbling)
(electricity zapping)
(muffled screaming)
(door creaking)
Halsey.
Shh.
What are you doing here?
They keep all of the psycho
killers on the same floor.
Then it wasn't a dream.
[Halsey] No.
They just don't want to upset you.
But I didn't do it.
You don't need to tell me that.
I know who did it.
You've seen him.
Who?
You know who and he's
here in the hospital.
Halsey, you're crazy.
Hey.
Residents of glass structures
ought not hurl projectiles.
Now, listen to me.
You be whoever they want you to be.
You understand?
It's the only way.
All right.
The more you resist, the
crazier they think you are.
If they don't see any real progress,
they're likely to take extreme measures.
Now whatever you do,
don't let them take you into surgery.
(door closes)
Shit, it's them.
I'll go hide in the closet.
Okay.
Halsey, come out.
Coast is clear.
Halsey.
(ominous music)
(breathing heavily)
(door creaking)
Oh, Halsey.
Dr. Martin.
Oh boy, am I glad to see you.
Halsey, you gotta help me.
Where am I?
How long have we been?
Settle down, settle down.
They said that you didn't exist.
I know.
They said that we're the same person.
I know the whole stinking story.
They told me the same thing.
They did?
Yes siree Bob.
They said you didn't exist.
That I was a creation of your mind?
Some sort of character in your dream?
Right as rain.
That's what they said.
[Both] I know I'm real.
(gasps)
No.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Hey, have we done this before?
Are we doing this now?
(door closes)
Shit, it's them.
I'll just duck into the closet.
Don't go in the closet.
Trust me.
[Halsey] There's no place else.
(tense music)
(machine beeping)
Dana?
Wait a second.
I know I'm here.
[Dana] Rex.
Fine.
Great.
PS, you've got brain damage.
Oh, Christ.
You dumb bastard.
Why don't you ever look
where you're going?
Oh, this should be interesting.
You smarmy son of a bitch.
Jesus.
Dana?
I can't watch this.
Halsey, you still in there?
(yells)
(ominous music)
Everything's gonna be all right.
He's in the best possible hands.
Dana, I just want you to
know I'm here for you.
I always have been.
Help me.
I'm not dead yet.
Did you hear that?
(grunting)
That's funny.
I could've sworn I heard something.
(panting)
(Rex yells)
♪ Hello ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ Hello, hello ♪
Halsey, where are we?
We're in my brain.
Your brain?
Hey, don't bug me.
I'm keeping my head above water.
I'm maintaining.
I am real, real busy here.
(thunder rumbling)
Hey, did you hear that.
What?
A storm's coming.
A storm?
A brainstorm.
(laughs)
Shit, that's no storm.
What is it?
Undersea monsters of the Id.
Are they dangerous?
Not to me, but then this
is my brain, my dream.
You can't get hurt in your own dream.
But you, you better watch.
(yells)
Halsey.
Shit.
What?
And we're gonna kep on dumping on you
till you get your ass out of here.
What?
You heard me.
Move it.
You're scaring off my customers.
Make sure he's gone.
He stinks.
Look, if you want to
come back after we close,
maybe we can get you some food
from the kitchen or something.
Hey, he's serious.
If you're not out of here,
he's gonna call the cops.
(subdued music)
(tense music)
(sighs)
What the hell?
Boom.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
[Man On Phone] Ah, Dr. Halsey.
Glad to find you back in your office.
I'm not Halsey.
[Man On Phone] (laughs) Of course not.
You are in Dr. Halsey's office,
you answer Dr. Halsey's private line,
but you are not Dr. Halsey.
Who is this?
[Man On Phone] Wait right
there and you'll find out.
Halsey.
Halsey, Halsey.
(suspenseful music)
Okay.
Well, hopefully he's still in there.
Uh-uh.
In tact this time, huh?
Let's do it.
Shit!
Jack?
Jack Halsey?
How's the golf game?
How's Mrs. Halsey and the kids?
I haven't seen you in a while.
It's me, Ellis.
I'm, not Halsey.
Repeat that.
- What?
Repeat it!
You're not Halsey.
Thank you.
(tense music)
(breathing heavily)
(man laughing)
You cocksucker!
I know I'm a cocksucker.
(laughing)
You.
Hey.
You!
Hey!
No, wait!
I'm not gonna hurt you!
(can clatters)
[Man] Spare change?
Do you know me?
Sure.
Yeah, sure.
Sure, I do.
Mr. John Q Public.
No.
No, you know me.
You know who I am.
You know me.
You know me!
Look, I don't know you from Adam,
but I'll tell you something.
You look like you got
Eunice written all over ya.
(horn honks)
Jim.
Hey, Jim.
Jim, Jim.
Oh, thank God it's you.
You just...
You gotta help me.
Hop in.
All right.
Oh, Jim.
I've gotten so lost.
Everything has gotten out of hand.
I mean, get this.
They think that I am Halsey.
But then, I thought he killed you.
No, I killed you.
I killed somebody.
And then Dana was there, too.
Try to relax.
It's just bad dreams.
No, I'm not dreaming this.
It's not a dream.
I ruled that out.
It's more like that I'm
being dreamed by Eunice.
You too.
Everybody, the whole thing, this car.
We're all being dreamed by Eunice.
For the universe is like a wet dream.
By the perception of
illusion we experience reality.
Are you experienced, Mr. Halsey?
That's Mr. Conklin, Eunice security.
He's been looking all over for you.
All right.
I'd like to tell you that
you have the wrong man.
I'm sorry, Mr. Halsey,
but it's important.
We really do need that equation.
Where are you taking me?
Home, to Lakeside.
Where you belong.
Farmhouse, this is The Shepard.
We're coming in.
Go.
(engine starts)
Where should we begin?
At the beginning, of course.
That's it.
Just relax, Mr. Halsey.
What do you want?
Just the facts.
I don't know what you're talking about.
But you can't do this.
We own you, Halsey.
You, your ideas, your
thoughts, your very brain.
It's all ours.
You, Halsey, are a wholly on subsidiary
of Eunice corporation.
I'm not Halsey.
Are you sure?
Zhuang Zhou wondered whether he was a man
dreaming of being a butterfly,
or whether he was a butterfly
dreaming of being a man.
Are you sure you're not a butterfly?
This doesn't seem to be working.
I don't see what we're
accomplishing here.
He's of no use to us this way.
[Woman] Just make sure no one else
will ever get it out of him.
Tabula rasa.
The clean slate.
Wait, let me try.
Can you hear me?
Halsey, can you hear me?
Okay.
Martin.
Rex, can you hear me?
It's me, Jim.
I know who you are.
Good.
Now listen very carefully.
It doesn't make any difference
anymore who you are.
When you get out of here, you
can be whoever you want to be.
We'll help you.
Start a whole new life.
You want to be a neurologist?
Fine, you've got it.
But you've got to work with us.
Look, my ass is on the line, too.
I could lose my job, but
you could lose much more.
Much, much more.
I don't know what you want.
We want the right side of the equation.
You erased it.
Don't you remember?
No.
Well, you did.
It was on a Monday.
The last day you came to work.
You'd had a tough weekend.
Hard work killing and
dismembering your family.
I mean, that's real aerobic exercise.
Something to get the heart pounding.
Ring any bells?
It was three little numbers.
What were they?
Tell me, you dumb son of a bitch!
Where's my wife?
Just burn out the core and let's go.
(electricity zapping)
(tires squealing)
(yelling)
(glass shatters)
[Doctor] Brace him, for God sake.
[Man] EEG was very spiky.
[Woman] Yeah, but the
screaming and the operation.
[Doctor] He's just experiencing
a vivid dream, that's all.
And we all know dreams can't hurt us.
Dr. Martin?
You called me Martin.
[Doctor] Of course.
Then I am Rex Martin.
Yes, you're Dr. Rex Martin.
Thank God.
I've been so lost.
[Doctor] You've been in an accident.
You're in surgery.
You've had severe cerebral hemorrhaging.
Zone?
[Doctor] Rear visual.
We just now isolated it.
Seizures.
I've been having seizures.
[Doctor] Yes.
Did I kill my wife?
[Doctor] No, of course not.
If you'll look through the glass there.
Can you see her?
And who's with her?
Jim.
Yes.
They've all been very worried about you.
I'm ready to go in now and see
if I can't repair the damage.
All right?
Right as rain.
I'm in your hands, Doc.
I'll adjourn your fee.
After all, it's old man Conklin's money.
Beg your pardon?
Conklin Mattress Factory.
They gave it to Halsey,
Halsey gives it to me,
I give it to Ramsen.
Just relax, Doctor.
I'm a bit nervous myself.
I've never operated on
another brain man before.
Just do no harm.
What?
No harm done.
(ominous music)
(toilet flushes)
(paper rattles in can)
Boom.
(suspenseful music)
(breathing heavily)
[Man] Doctor, we're losing pressure.
[Doctor] Increase the O2.
[Woman] It's cranial bleeding, Doctor.
[Doctor] What are the numbers?
No respiratory response.
[Woman] It's down.
(steady tone)
Flatline, Doctor.
[Doctor] This has stopped.
Party's over.
Well, at least he didn't feel any pain.
(ominous music)
[Rex] Where am I?
Am I dreaming...
or is this death?
I'm dead.
Great.
I'm dead, I think.
I think?
Oh, this should be interesting.
♪ Where should we begin ♪
(uptempo music)
♪ He's got my brain ♪
♪ I'm so sorry ♪
♪ A toast ♪
♪ To madness ♪
♪ Brain dead ♪
♪ Hey, try to relax ♪
♪ It's just bad dreams ♪
♪ Try to relax ♪
♪ Then it wasn't a dream ♪
♪ Brain dead ♪
♪ What about the numbers ♪
♪ I'm sorry, Mr. Halsey ♪
♪ Then it wasn't a dream ♪
(tires squealing)
♪ Don't you want to change the world ♪
♪ Yes, go on ♪
♪ Don't you want to change
the world and get rich ♪
♪ Yes ♪
♪ I'm sorry, Mr. Halsey ♪
♪ Just bad dreams ♪
♪ You know me ♪
♪ You, you know me ♪
♪ Brain dead ♪