Subtitles by explosiveskull
[blows]
[whirring]
[suspenseful music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[professor] There was nothing
in their backgrounds
that would suggest,
you know, something like that
would happen.
I was at a loss.
[woman] They were
pretty darn good kids.
These boys weren't criminals,
they didn't have records.
And, you know, for something
like this to happen,
to the boys and to the
school, of course,
it was a big loss at the time.
[suspenseful music continues]
[Mr. Reinhard]
We were in shock.
I mean, we did not expect that
from our son, ever.
It's like we woke up
in a nightmare.
[Mr. Lipka]
Everything in our family was
geared towards our kids
to be successful.
It was just a...
a moment which we lost him.
[sobbing]
Sorry.
[clock ticking]
[interviewer] Spencer.
Thank you for waiting.
We've been very impressed
with your portfolio
and the exceptional
commendations of your teachers.
But now we're hoping
to find out,
a little more about you
personally.
Um, like my family background,
stuff?
[interviewer] Whatever you
think is most relevant.
Just tell us a little bit
about who you are.
Well...
My name is Spencer Reinhard.
I'm from Lexington, Kentucky,
and I'm 30 years old
for another,
less than a month, I guess.
My father, he is, uh,
an engineer.
My mom is a stay-at-home mom,
I guess.
Let me stop you there.
That's great.
I suppose,
what we'd really like to know,
is about you.
Like, uh, hobbies and stuff?
What do you hope
to express with your work?
I mean...
Who are you as an artist?
[clock ticking]
- [rap music playing]
- [indistinct shouting]
[indistinct yelling]
Next one! Next one!
Mr. Reinhard,
the honorable man, if you will.
Um, he strives for the
generosity of the generous.
[crowd booing]
For the humility of the humble.
- The honorable man is...
- [crowd shouting]
[crowd chanting]
Suck it up! Suck it up!
- Suck it up! Suck it up!
- [man] Hit it!
- [chanting fades]
[solemn instrumental
music playing]
[Spencer] Growing up, I had a,
a desire for some kind
of life-altering experience.
I started to read
about other artists.
They were always affected by some
kind of tragedy in their life,
and had to suffer a great deal.
Van Gogh ended up
killing himself.
Monet went blind.
I felt like they understood
something more about life
that I wasn't getting
to experience.
Art has to be about
more than just,
"My life is great, and I'm
really good at drawing."
- [sighs]
- [cell phone beeping]
[line ringing]
- [Warren] About fucking time.
- [chuckles]
What do you mean
it's about time?
[Warren] I left you
like a zillion messages.
You haven't left me
a message in weeks, Warren.
Anyway, do you
wanna do something?
- I think I'm gonna go to bed.
- I'm coming over.
Seriously, man,
fuck fraternities.
The reason to be
a part of that is
so one day you can walk in the door
of an office you never wanna go in
to see a guy you
never wanna meet,
on the hopes that he might give you
a job you never wanna fucking do.
Something I've often
thought about, is how,
my life would've been different
if I hadn't met Warren.
So this is the, uh,
dinosaur, T-Rex,
trying to turn off
a ceiling fan.
[Spencer] Warren was
definitely somebody that
my mom did not want me
to be friends with.
We were not thrilled with
the relationship with Warren,
but we accepted it because...
that was his friend.
You need to have
a little bit of spice...
in the broth.
And Warren,
probably was that spice.
People have said that
I was the ring leader,
but that's just not true.
There was no ring leader.
Yes! Shit!
Did I work here?
Half of this shit got wasted.
Literally,
thrown in the fucking trash.
Hand me the flashlight.
[Spencer] Uh, Warren,
what are we doing here?
Did you know, that 40%
of restaurant food in America
gets thrown in the trash?
Just thrown away.
We are the fattest
fucking nation on the planet,
- and we still throw nearly half of our food away.
- [exhales]
- I mean, kids are starving in Africa, dude.
- Fuck, man.
It's fucking tragic.
What the fuck are we gonna do
with this, huh?
We're saving it from landfill.
Do you eat avocados.
They're over...
- No one's buying, Warren...
- [door opens]
- Shit.
- Run! Run, run, run, run, run!
Don't drop the fucking meat.
Goddammit.
Next time, you're gonna get
a fucking bullet, Warren!
Fuck 'em up in their ass!
[both laughing]
- Whoo!
- [laughing]
- Drive. Drive.
- I'm driving. I'm driving. I'm driving!
- I'm driving! I'm driving!
- [tires screeching]
[horn blares]
♪ I'm alive ♪
♪ And I see things
Mighty clear today ♪
♪ I'm alive ♪
♪ I'm real ♪
♪ I can taste and touch
And see and feel ♪
♪ I'm alive ♪
[Warren] Look at these fucks.
We should just rev up and put
them out of their misery.
I don't even know
what we're doing back here.
- [man] Whoo!
- [tires screeching]
So, did you meet
any new cool people, over there?
No. Bunch of jocks.
You?
No.
Uh-uh.
[clicks tongue] It's not
what I thought it would be.
Do you ever wonder,
you ended up being born.
You, here, and not someone else?
Do you ever feel like you're
waiting for something to happen,
but you don't know what it is?
But, it's,
[clicks tongue]
that thing that could, um,
make your life special.
Yeah.
Like what?
Exactly.
"Like what?"
[Reporter on TV] Good news
if you woke up wondering
if you're living
in the right town today, folks.
'Cause Forbes Magazine
votes Lexington
14th best place in the US
for business and careers.
[Betty] If there is
a book you cannot find,
either on the shelves
or on the computer,
please make a point of asking a
member of the library staff.
Through these doors,
live the special collection.
And in future, you will require an
appointment to go through these doors,
and you will need
to be accompanied
by a member of the library staff
at all times.
[lock beeps]
Someone take the door.
Thank you.
Many of the books
in this library
have been here since
the 19th century,
and we are very pleased
to be home
to some of the rarest editions
in the United States.
John James Audubon
is responsible
for this masterpiece here.
First edition,
Birds of America.
He lived here in Kentucky.
He had some misfortune
in business.
Went to prison for debt.
When he left prison,
he headed for the wilderness
with a gun, some paint,
and a deep desire to paint
every bird in America.
And when he came back
into civilization,
he was acclaimed as one of the
foremost figures in American art.
[female student] So, how much
is it worth?
Well, we don't discuss
the worth of our books,
but I can assure you, that Mr.
Audubon would never have imagined
that his book would be
the most valuable in existence.
Now, most of you are
familiar with this book.
Arguably among
the most important ever written.
Darwin's
On The Origin of Species.
Please look at line number ten
and tell me what you see.
[woman] Species is spelt wrong.
[Betty] That's correct.
Species is...
[enchanting instrumental
music playing]
[Betty]
Will you be joining us, sir?
[indistinct chatter]
I'm pretty sure he told me
about it at Richard's party.
I remember being cool.
A book?
In what world can a book
be worth $12 million?
It's not really a book.
It's more like
a collection of paintings.
I think I told him
about it in the car.
Maybe November. It was cold.
I still don't understand how a
book could be worth $12 million.
It's like if Picasso
had a bunch of his paintings
in a book.
When you say it's in the
library, it's like, what...
[clears throat]
[chuckles softly]
sitting on a shelf?
No, it's in the, uh,
special collections room.
Which is what? Like a vault?
More like a secure room
with glass cases and stuff.
With guards on the doors
and shit?
No, but obviously,
you can't just walk in there.
Hey, pull in here.
Because there's
security everywhere?
Not that I saw.
[Warren] Whoa.
What then...
Because, you have to make
an appointment.
So, this is how you remember it?
Not exactly.
But if this his how
Spencer remembers it,
then let's go with it.
[Warren] It's $12 million.
Could we get it? [chuckling]
You know, like,
what would it take?
It would take
extraordinary effort to get it.
Not ordinary effort.
What?
I think you know what.
There's been so much, "Who brought it up?
Who kinda started it?"
I feel like he was fishing,
[chuckles]
and that I took the bait.
It would be true to say that
once Warren latches on
to an idea,
that he's not easily
going to let it go.
[suspenseful music playing]
[keys clacking]
[Warren] Look, all I'm saying
is that nothing will happen,
unless you
make something happen.
We're supposed to be
hunter-gatherers, man.
And our whole life,
we're just unwrapping shit.
Packaging, packaging, packaging.
The illusion of choice.
It's bullshit, man.
Everyone in here thinks that
they're gonna win the lottery,
but no one likes a ticket.
Well, yeah, a prison would be
a nice change of scenery.
Well, what about ending up on a
fucking boat in the Caribbean?
- [laughs]
- Like the end of Shawshank Redemption.
Oh, my God.
What about that?
He'd been in prison
for 20 years.
And sorry to burst
your bubble, but, uh,
it doesn't work like that
in real life, Warren.
Bad guys, they don't get
to ride off into the sunset
- with the money and,
- Wait a second.
the gold, and, uh...
How will we be the bad guys?
Uh, we'd be the robbers.
Aren't you even curious?
Your little, little brain, to find
out what would actually happen?
Aren't you curious?
Find out what?
To find out what would
really happen in real life.
[sighs]
I've lost count.
Can you go, man, please?
I work here, Warren.
- I work...
- Listen to me.
- Come on.
I gotta do this shit.
[sighs] We're gonna need
the blueprints.
We're gonna need to know
the exits and entry points.
the staff entrances
and the fastest way out
of the building
at any given point in time.
What do you say?
We're don't need blueprints.
We can just draw it.
[man on TV]
These guys are fools.
They can't afford
to weasel out on the deal.
If they did,
they'd be washed up, okay?
- [man 2] Okay.
- Any other questions?
Well, let's take
a look at this, then.
This is a rough drawing
of the track as I remember.
[Warren]
There aren't exactly books
that instruct you
on how to steal [chuckles] art.
I want you to go over this
thing with me inch-by-inch.
Add or subtract
the slightest change,
even if it's something as small as
the placement of a hot dog stand.
[Spencer] 5:10, tall, redhead,
librarian one, leaves for the evening.
[suspenseful music playing]
5:11,
short, male administrative
assistant, returns.
[Betty] Hold the door, please.
Many of the books
in this library
have been here
since the 19th century.
Neither of us were really
serious about the idea.
I took it very seriously
from the start.
[knocking rhythmically]
Warren, there's no secret knock.
Yeah, well, there should be.
Hi.
You lost your fake ID already,
didn't you?
Actually, I came
to talk to you about something.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
What's up?
[sighs]
What if I have something
to get rid of?
What thing
are you talking about?
Something rare.
So, you're looking for a fence?
I'm looking for a guy who's
gonna buy something rare.
Right.
I don't wanna hear anything
about this.
But, I know a guy
you might be able to talk to.
But I've only met him once.
And, I don't know
if I can vouch for him, so...
- Do you understand?
- Absolutely, I get it.
Okay.
[clears throat]
He's out in New York.
He does not like phone calls.
How do I get in touch with him?
- [Spencer] What is this?
- [Warren] That's a fence.
What's a fence?
"What's a fence?"
A fence is somebody
who buys stolen shit.
We're supposed to email that
guy, asking for a meeting,
and sign off
with the name "Terry".
And he said to never email
from the same account twice.
How fucking cool is that?
- Good work.
- Thank you.
"Best, Terry."
Happy?
- I wanna change that...
- Oops.
[Warren chuckling]
I just don't get, like, what
a "good faith" payment him is.
I mean, we give him
500 bucks for a meeting?
It's to show we're serious
and not time-wasters.
I would've thought, driving
across the country for 12 hours
was a good demonstration
of that.
It's just how it's done, man.
Oh, you know this
from all your previous heists?
Would you relax?
What would you do
with the money?
Aren't artists
supposed to starve?
[RJ on radio] You're listening
to your favorite oldies station.
Back-to-back hits
from the '50s, '60s and '70s.
["New York Groove" playing]
♪ Many years since I was here ♪
♪ On the street
I was passin' my time away ♪
[Spencer]
We were out of Kentucky,
and nobody knows
that we're gone.
There was
a sense of possibility.
Real things were actually starting
to happen, and they were...
It was changing...
changing our lives right then.
♪ Here I am, and in this city ♪
♪ With a fistful of dollars ♪
♪ And baby
You'd better believe ♪
♪ I'm back
Back in the New York Groove ♪
♪ Back ♪
[Spencer] I was fearful
at the time that,
if the guy didn't show up,
that this fantasy
would be over,
and we'd be going back
to Kentucky,
and things would kinda resume
their normal, uh, course.
[indistinct chatter]
[Spencer] And then, suddenly,
Warren's talking to a guy
with a ponytail
and a blue scarf.
Or was it a purple scarf?
The guy was in his 50s.
I mean, white hair,
and well-dressed.
He hands me the piece of paper,
and that was that,
he didn't even count the money.
Hi.
What's up?
What'd he say? What'd he say?
[panting]
He wasn't the buyer.
He gave us a contact.
The fence.
So, that guy wasn't the fence?
I thought you said
he was the fence.
I guess not.
We just...
We spent $500
on an email address.
Now all we have to do
is contact this guy.
He says he speaks English.
What?
He's...
Let's go get some food.
Come on, I'm freezing.
Uh, why wouldn't he
speak English, Warren?
Warren.
[Warren] "Sir, thank you
for your email.
I'm afraid we only do
business in person,
but, we'll welcome you and
your items in the Netherlands
at your earliest convenience."
[clears throat]
- We have to go.
- To Holland?
To the Netherlands.
- Can you stop? Warren?
- No, I'm not stopping until it's burned.
- Warren.
- It's evidence.
Hot. Motherfucker.
Thank you. Sorry.
So, you wanna go
all the way over there,
to meet some actual criminals
we know nothing about,
to talk about something
we don't even have?
Yes.
What's your suggestion?
[sighs] Maybe it's time,
you know, to face reality.
Maybe it's something
we're not able to do.
So we're just gonna
sit here and do nothing?
That is so disappointing.
I can't even tell you.
[Mr. Lipka] How about you, Spencer?
You keeping your game up?
Uh, not so much.
I mean, I'm trying to take
the whole art thing seriously.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
[laughing] Well, I guess
somebody has to, huh?
But, you know, you wanna keep
that blood pumping, son.
And speaking of which, uh,
I ran into Burt Morris
last week,
and he said you missed
a couple of practice games.
- Yeah.
- Now, Warren,
you're there on a scholarship.
And that's what it means.
You're there to play.
- I had it the same way.
- [kitchen objects crash]
- [Mrs. Lipka] Fuck!
- Jesus Christ.
You okay?
Remember, quitters never win...
- And winners never quit.
- [Mrs. Lipka] Spencer.
[Mr. Lipka]
Yeah, something to live by.
So, how is your mom, Spencer?
Uh, she's doing good.
- Good. You tell her I said hi, for me.
- Yeah, I will.
I need to speak
with you, please.
What, now, Sue?
- [Mrs. Lipka clears throat]
- Now?
[Mr. Lipka] Excuse me, guys.
What I wanna do is just
have dinner with the boys.
[Mrs. Lipka] What is this?
[Mr. Lipka] You're holding my...
[door slams]
[indistinct yelling]
[footsteps approaching]
I'm divorcing your father.
I'm sorry.
And then, I think
I looked over at Spencer, and...
I mean, who knows if this is how
it really went, but he said...
[stutters] I remember it
being like, "Whoa."
I should go now.
[door slams]
[Warren] Is he fucking crying?
Are you fucking crying?
[Spencer] Warren,
I'm gonna go, man.
Yeah, let's go.
[suspenseful music playing]
[retching]
You should chew your food,
man, seriously.
[Warren groans]
We're carrying on with the plan.
What are you talking about?
Holland.
Amsterdam, and then gone.
Come on, Warren,
you know I can't go.
Even if I wanted to.
[sighs]
Come on, man.
[Warren] Fuck.
Look, maybe I can, uh,
find some money,
and put it towards
half the ticket.
- Really?
- Yeah.
But,
it'll be only you going.
That's okay.
- [chuckles]
- What?
- Give me a kiss.
- [chuckles] Don't you even touch me, man.
- All right, bro.
- Thanks, brother.
- Go get 'em, all right?
- Yeah.
["Hurdy Gurdy Man" playing]
♪ Thrown like a star
In my vast sleep ♪
♪ I open my eyes
To take a peep ♪
♪ To find that I was
By the sea ♪
♪ Me gazing with tranquility ♪
♪ It was then
When the Hurdy Gurdy Man ♪
♪ Came singing songs of love ♪
♪ Then when
The Hurdy Gurdy Man ♪
♪ Came singing songs of love ♪
♪ Hurdy gurdy, hurdy gurdy, ♪
♪ Hurdy gurdy, gurdy, he sang ♪
♪ Hurdy gurdy, hurdy gurdy ♪
Hi, I'm David.
I work with Mr. Beckman.
Hi.
You mind if I sit?
[Warren clears throat]
- You guys are the guys, that we...
- You have some books,
and you have some paintings.
That I do.
[chuckles nervously] That I do.
Now, uh, we have a number
of items pertaining to,
the existence,
for which I'm here.
Um...
The books, the Audubons.
They're very rare.
Yes.
That's why I'm here.
That's why you're here
with your piece of paper.
[stutters] Well, uh,
I didn't know...
Mr. Beckman is your father?
[coughing]
No, uh, Mr. Beckman
is my employer.
[sighs]
[chuckles] Actually,
we are kind of related.
He's, uh, he's actually my,
my mom's sister's husband,
which makes him sort
of, uh, uncle.
You have authentication?
[clicks tongue] Okay,
when you say authentication...
We take items
from various sources,
and we don't inquire
where they came from,
as long as
we have authentication
with a very famous
auction house.
Yeah, um...
So, you're saying, with the
correct authentications,
that these items would be
of interest to you?
Yeah.
[chuckles] So...
Mr. Beckman's gonna be very pleased
about this, by the way. Um...
So, can I ask, roughly,
[breathes deeply]
in terms of, um...
- It's hard, I imagine, to...
- How much?
Yes.
How much?
Thirty to forty percent
of the valuation price.
- That's, um, millions of dollars, right?
- [laughing]
Yeah!
Look, I've been thinking
just, uh, you know,
we're gonna need a bigger boat.
We're gonna need a bigger boat?
I mean, we're gonna need
somebody else.
Um...
Why do we need someone else?
We need somebody with skills
that we don't have.
Somebody who's good
with logistics,
and, chess.
[lecturer] Accepted
accounting principles.
Statements,
on auditing.
So, in 1992,
we get SAS 82.
Anyone dare to explain
the significance of this one?
[metal music playing
on earphones]
Mr. Borsuk.
[Eric]
I was majoring in accounting
because I wanted a career
at the FBI.
At the time, that was only
one of the two majors
they accepted
straight out of college.
[professor]
Eric was a gentleman.
A good student.
Gave made no pause,
or concern, uh, whatsoever.
I always felt like I was, um,
[clicks tongue] kind of a loner,
for some reason.
Um, yeah, um, SAS 82
states that
auditors have the duty
to actively look for fraud and not
just report it if they find it.
That's correct.
[Eric] Except, in reality, it doesn't
always work like that, does it?
Arthur Andersen.
Remember them?
Auditors to Enron?
Um, thank you for that,
Mr. Borsuk.
[cell phone vibrating]
[lecturer] So, in 2002,
that leads us to SAS 99...
- [beeps]
- [whispering] Don't cancel me.
Shit! What the fuck
are you doing here?
I need to talk to you.
But not here.
[funky music playing]
Warren and I lost touch.
We had a falling out.
Been about three months
since we had last spoken.
[Eric] I thought that
we weren't speaking.
[Warren] What? Wait.
No. Uh, no, no, no, no.
Can we just agree and put all that
stupid shit behind us, please?
I mean, no.
- Hey.
- So, what's up, man?
What's with all the mystery?
I'm here to talk to you
about something deadly serious.
I figured
you must want something.
Actually, I came
to offer you something.
- Oh, really? Yeah?
- Yeah.
There's no one else
I could trust with this.
You're either in
or you're out, right now.
How can I tell you
if I'm in or I'm out
without you telling me
the first thing about
what I might be in or out of.
I would just need you to say
"in principle," okay?
Because this might be something
not exactly legal.
And there's a chance
that we would have
to leave everything behind.
Okay, when you say
"not legal"...
I'm gonna say this one time,
and one time only.
You're either in
or you're out. Right now.
I'm gonna need
more than this one.
Not till you commit.
This would be something
dangerous,
and very fucking exciting,
that I need you to be a part of.
This could change everything.
This is your red pill or
blue pill moment, my friend.
How's college?
Would we have to go tonight?
I think I was just saying yes,
because I knew that,
I wanted to, um,
regain our friendship
more than anything.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Eric] So what's your part?
[clears throat] This is
partly where you come in.
Just take a look for me, please.
- [Eric] It can't be done at night.
- [laughs] What?
What's the one time a day when no
one's supposed to be in the building?
It'd be impossible to get in
without triggering the alarms.
It would have to be done
during the day.
[Warren] See?
I knew you were
the man for this.
Look at him.
Just like a fish in water.
Sure.
Let's just walk in there in broad
daylight and rob the place.
Oh, yeah, well,
while you're at it,
- you're gonna dynamite the canteen, right?
- [chuckles]
How many cameras,
did you say were
in the special corrections room?
Because they're gonna be
watching everything
from the campus safety office.
The cameras, the alarms.
They're gonna know
who's coming in and out.
What are you doing?
I'm taking notes.
This is good stuff.
Are you fucking retarded?
No.
Why don't you just
email the FBI and ask them
where they have access to leave our
fingerprints? You can make it easy for them.
Guys, we need to find out
who's watching
the special collections room
and when.
I concur with that
[sighs]
[Bill] Come in.
Hey.
- Take a seat, Warren.
- Okay.
I assume you know
why you're here.
Uh...
Not really, sir.
Right. Mr. Lipka,
you came here
on an athletic scholarship.
Perhaps it doesn't seem like
a particularly big deal to you.
No, sir, it does.
Well, son, you have
a funny way of showing it.
Because I warned you
countless times
what would happen if you
continue to fail to show up.
Assistant coach suspects drugs
or alcohol may be involved.
Now, it pains me
to see you lose
this scholarship.
But it's gonna pain and probably
embarrass your father a whole lot more.
So you might wanna reflect on
what that kind of disappointment
will mean for him.
Yeah.
That will be a disappointment.
Thing is,
I worked to get on that team,
since I was about five.
And I have absolutely
no idea why.
To be honest, sir,
I think this whole place
is a disappointment.
I think you're
a disappointment.
And I think this whole
goddamn town,
is a disappointment.
Get out.
Is that it?
[Warren] The cameras
aren't cameras.
They're motion detectors.
We're gonna email the library,
asking to have the Audubon
and the illuminated manuscript
on display when we arrive.
They will be here and here.
Can you please not touch
the model?
Thanks.
[sighs] As I was saying.
Back here,
is target priority number one,
the Audubon.
Now, directly behind
the display case is a doorway
which leads to a staff elevator
that goes straight to the basement.
Now, once in the basement,
we can access the fire exit
at the side of the building.
Uh, where's the librarian?
- [Warren] Thank you.
- Just watch it.
The librarian,
is the single biggest risk
to this entire operation.
She needs to become a
non-factor as soon as possible.
Now, once inside the room,
you two will bag up
the smaller books,
and I'll unlock the cases containing
the Audubon and the Darwin.
We should be in and out in less
than three or four minutes.
- Good afternoon. Come in.
- [Spencer] How are you?
I'm Betty Jean Gooch, and I will
need your names for the log, please.
I am, uh, Spencer Green.
[Betty exclaims]
["A Little Less Conversation"
playing]
♪ A little less conversation
A little more action, please ♪
♪ All this aggravation
Ain't satisfactioning me ♪
♪ A little more bite
And a little less bark ♪
♪ A little less fight
And a little more spark ♪
♪ Close your mouth And open up
your heart And, baby, satisfy me ♪
♪ Satisfy me, baby ♪
♪ Come on, baby
I'm tired of talking ♪
♪ Grab your coat
And let's start walking ♪
♪ Come on, come on
Come on, come on ♪
♪ Don't procrastinate
Don't articulate ♪
♪ Girl, it's getting late
You just sit and wait around ♪
♪ Yeah
A little less conversation ♪
♪ A little more action
Please ♪
♪ All this aggravation
Ain't satisfactioning me ♪
- [Eric] Stop.
- [music stops]
Wait.
Doesn't work.
We need two guys,
at least, in the room.
Then you need a third guy,
downstairs in the library,
keeping lookout.
Then, we're gonna have to have
a getaway driver.
Who's your driver?
- The three of us isn't enough.
- He's right.
I just wanna see
how any of this is gonna work.
I mean,
does this seem realistic or...
Well, you got
a better idea, Spence?
No. Fuck.
I was torn between
the desire to keep
the adventure going,
and waiting for
the insurmountable obstacle,
that would,
stop everything in its tracks,
and return things to normal.
We need someone else
that we can trust.
Wait, wait, wait. Someone else?
You wanna bring in someone else?
You got a better idea?
Who else can we trust with this?
Someone with a fast car.
Or the money to get one.
[Spencer] I'd only met him
a couple of times
in high school.
I'd never really got along
too well with Chas.
The decision to bring on the
fourth person came from Eric.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
it was Warren's idea.
I definitely wouldn't have ever
suggested we bring Chas on.
My names is
Charles Thomas Allen II,
but, people call me Chas.
My dad built me for success.
I started my first company
at 12 years old.
At 16, bought my first
real property.
He's been a little entrepreneur,
as long as I can remember.
You know, mowing grass, uh...
You know, he followed
his dad around.
He was a little Tom.
He just followed him
around all the time,
wanting to be, you know,
business and, you know,
do everything his dad did.
Chas, interestingly enough,
I knew his dad. [laughs]
Uh, he worked out at the same
gym that I did for a while.
Just a wonderful person.
Uh, you know, I mean,
a prince of an individual.
I think the qualities that we
thought Chas could bring was money.
- [screams]
- Jesus fucking Christ, Warren.
- Stop doing that shit.
- Sorry. [laughs]
Sorry, man.
Can we talk to you
about something?
Yeah, what's up?
[Chas] Once I realized they
were serious about the plan,
I thought they were
smoking too much.
I think you guys are
And, I thought
they're likely to get themselves
in a lot of trouble
and get caught.
And likely to get yourselves
in a lot of trouble,
and get caught.
- Chas?
- Mm-hm?
You really need to see
how easy this is gonna be.
Wait. What the fuck are you guys
even talking about here?
We're talking about $12 million
in rare books.
And only one old lady
guarding it.
[Warren] Names first.
Eric, Mr. Black.
Spencer, Mr. Green.
Mr. Yellow, that's me.
Chas, Mr. Pink.
[giggling]
Fucking really, dude?
- What?
- You're making me Mr. Pink?
What? [laughs]
What's wrong with Mr. Pink?
You know exactly what's
wrong with Mr. Pink, okay?
I'm sorry, can I just say
how dumb this entire thing is?
Okay?
Because in the motion picture,
the whole point of the names was so that
nobody knew what the others were called.
So they couldn't
give each other a...
Relax, okay?
It's just protocol,
so we don't address each other
by our names during the robbery.
- Okay?
- [Spencer] Mm-hm.
No names.
- Mr. Pink.
- It's fucking ridiculous, man.
Didn't they all die
in the end of that movie?
[Warren] Spencer was Mr. Green,
because he smoked lots
of green.
Eric was Mr. Black because
he said his soul was black.
I was Mr. Yellow because I was,
I was my mom's sunshine.
And I named Chas Mr. Pink
just to fuck with him.
I'm not gonna be Mr. Pink.
I'd be any color but pink.
[chuckles]
It's probably my least favorite
Tarantino film.
Okay. Housekeeping first.
Mr. Green, you will see
to the disguises.
Makeup, prosthetics,
outfits, wigs, etcetera.
Costume party?
Making a movie.
Mr. Black, your first task,
is to find
a reliable getaway vehicle.
Ford or similar,
nothing flashy.
Which you will purchase
- using cash and a fake ID.
- Yeah, thank you.
Mr. Pink. Your first job,
is to identify
the quickest route
from the library
to the drop off point, here.
I mean, practice it
over and over again
until it becomes second nature.
[tires screeching]
[funky instrumental music
playing]
Fourteen minutes, eighteen
seconds, mostly green lights.
Mr. Yellow.
That's me, of course.
I will make
the authentication appointment
in New York for the weekend,
immediately following
the robbery.
Meaning, that even if
the books are reported missing,
they won't yet show up on the
national index of stolen art.
Once we have
the authentication,
we will arrange a rendezvous with
the buyers in the Netherlands.
[Warren] Dear sir,
my name is Walter Beckman.
I'm a collector of rare
manuscripts, based in Texas.
I would like to arrange
an appraisal
of some of the items
in my collection.
Now, I have emailed the library
to make an appointment
to view the books
on the penultimate day of term.
That's eight days from now.
The library
will be almost empty,
as everyone will be in finals.
I have an exam that day.
- Me too.
- Yeah, me too, I have art history.
Exactly.
What do you mean "exactly"?
I mean, who's gonna suspect
a group of robbers
who all happen to be
in exams that day?
Mr. Green, would you like to
walk us through the disguises?
So, the idea is,
we go in disguise as old men.
I'm sorry. Why the fuck would
we go disguised as old men?
Because, being old is the closest
thing to being invisible.
[Eric] I have a question.
I'm still unclear on what's gonna
happen with the librarian.
- Who's gonna be doing...
- We should probably decide that
by drawing lots
or a vote or something.
Well, I vote to have nothing
to do with it whatsoever.
Yeah, me too. I don't wanna
do that. I'm not gonna.
Hey. Whoa. What the fuck?
Obviously,
nobody wants to do it.
That's why we need to decide it
by drawing lots
or a vote or something.
Isn't there maybe a...
a way to make her
not be there on the day?
No. Of course,
there isn't a fucking way.
That's how you get to be
in the room.
Someone has to be
in there with you.
That's how you get to be
in the fucking room!
What if she starts
screaming or something?
- Yeah, or has a fucking heart attack, man.
- Yeah.
Guys, when this is all over,
we're gonna send her
an anonymous package
filled with thousands
of fucking dollars.
- She's gonna be happy.
- Look, I'm not doing it.
Okay?
I'm not comfortable with it.
Wow.
Fuck it.
I'll do it.
I'll fucking do it.
[Spencer]
There was no obstacle.
Nothing was gonna prevent us
from doing it.
We had started it,
and it could be done.
There were
so many opportunities,
looking back,
where I could have completely,
that I
could have gotten out, or...
Or change what we were doing.
And I didn't.
- [Warren] Duct tape.
- [Spencer] Check.
- [Warren] Change of clothes.
- [Warren] Sheet.
- [Spencer] Check.
- [Warren] Ski masks.
- [Spencer] Ski masks.
[Warren] Cell phones.
Zip ties.
-Taser. Check
No taser.
Shit!
Whose job was it
to order the taser?
I believe it was your job.
Fuck it, I can't think
of everything.
["Peace Frog" playing]
[lecturer] Open your books.
You have two hours to complete two
of the three essay questions.
When I give the signal,
you may turn over your papers.
Any problems, raise your hand.
And begin.
♪ Blood in the streets
In the town of Chicago ♪
♪ Blood on the rise
It's following me ♪
♪ Think about
The break of day... ♪
This could be just what
your mom's looking for.
Light Cobra stun gun.
How long would that
disable someone for?
♪ Blood in the streets
Runs a river of sadness ♪
It's up to my thigh... ♪
- Don't you have exams today?
- Yeah.
Uh, hey, listen,
I gotta borrow the van.
Pencils down. Close your texts
and exit the room.
The scores will be posted
by the end of next week.
You're seven minutes late.
Let's go!
[exam professor] Time's up.
Pens down. Close your books.
Please pass them to your left,
and leave in an orderly fashion.
[Warren] 11:02.
♪ Blood in my love
In the terrible summer ♪
♪ Bloody red sun
Of Phantastic LA ♪
♪ Blood screams her brain
As they chop off her fingers ♪
♪ Blood will be born
In the birth of a nation ♪
♪ Blood is the rose
Of mysterious union ♪
- [music stops]
- [thudding table rhythmically]
[Warren breathing heavily]
Fucking, really?
[suspenseful music playing]
[clears throat]
There he is.
Like clockwork.
[sighs]
[exhales sharply]
[clears throat]
[rap music playing on radio]
- [music stops]
- Just focus, man, please.
I think I'm gonna be sick, guys.
[Chas] Don't even
fucking think about
throwing up in this car,
Spencer.
[suspenseful music continues]
Remember, you're old.
- There's people everywhere.
- Just stick to the plan.
Let's do this.
[suspenseful music continues]
[sharpener creaking]
[creaking]
[watch ticking]
[shuddering]
[whispering] Abort, abort.
- Abort.
- What? Why?
[suspenseful music continues]
There's four fucking librarians
up there
having some kind of meeting or something.
I don't know, I can't...
- I can't do it.
- Who's up there, all right?
- There's a man...
- It doesn't matter who's up there.
- There's four of them.
- We're not gonna tie up four fucking librarians.
What's going on?
There's a fucking meeting
up there or something, okay?
There's four librarians. We can't
tie up one of these people.
I'm not...
I'm not staying, okay?
They're all looking at me.
I'm losing a side burn.
Okay, listen. Everyone,
just chill out, all right?
We haven't done anything.
We can wait, all right?
They aren't gonna be
up there forever.
[sighs] Okay. Who wants to wait?
- Well, fuck this. I'm going.
- [Eric] Man.
I'm leaving.
[exhales]
["Summer Comes Sunday" playing]
♪ Summer comes Sunday
My, oh, my ♪
♪ Soon I'll see the sun
And the summer skies ♪
♪ Soon I'll see
The love in your eyes ♪
♪ When I wake up
She'll be there ♪
♪ See the morning light shining
In her hair ♪
♪ Feel the morning sun
Everywhere ♪
[Spencer] To get out
of that situation
without having done
anything wrong
was an incredible feeling.
The plan was off,
there was gonna be no heist.
And it was glorious.
The sun was shining,
and it was like a new,
a new beginning.
I don't get to control who gets to
be in the goddamn fucking room.
[Eric] That's it.
After all that, that's it.
That's the end of it. It's over.
[Chas] Did you not think
for a moment?
- Did you fucking think? To call me fucking...
- I'm tired of all this shit.
Fuck!
Maybe we dodged a bullet.
We didn't dodge anything, 'cause
we didn't fucking do anything.
We just fucked it up.
Fuck!
Pull in here.
I need something to drink.
[man on TV
speaking indistinctly]
Hey, you got a pay phone?
I just called the library.
We're back on.
Tomorrow morning, 11:00 a.m.
She says there are
no other appointments scheduled.
- [Warren] Whoo!
- [engine starts]
[Mr. Reinhard]
You rang the theater?
[Mrs. Reinhard] I guess you
didn't realize how bad it was.
[Mr. Reinhard] I guess you just
never know how you're gonna react
in a situation like that.
Wait, what? She let
her husband practically die
because she didn't wanna
interrupt the concert?
Maybe she just never
really liked it all that much.
Well, now, everybody
has their preference...
You okay, Sweetie?
- Not hungry?
- I'm just tired.
Exams and stuff.
Honey, you gotta take
better care of yourself.
Are you sure you're okay?
I just, uh, I just remembered,
I have an exam tomorrow.
I didn't study for it, so...
- You okay, champ?
- Spencer. [sighs]
[woman on headphones] All
limitations are self-imposed.
Warren.
- Warren.
- What? What the fuck, man?
I'm done.
[sighs]
I can't see it ending well.
I just can't go back in there.
Okay, well, just... All right.
Look, today was bad luck.
But we got a trial run, okay?
Now, we can
make adjustments, and...
Dude, nothing bad
is gonna happen.
- Nobody's gonna get hurt, nobody's gonna know it's us.
- Stop saying that, Warren!
"No one's gonna get hurt." How do
you know no one's gonna get hurt?
- Huh?
- What are you talking about?
I'm talking about
my family, okay?
They're good people
and they don't deserve it.
Have you even thought about...
I mean...
What could happen, like, if it
goes wrong, with our futures?
Which fucking future
are you worried about?
The one that's fucking indistinguishable
from everyone else's?
Where you fucking beaver away
to get the shit you're told
you need to have
by some fucking asshole
that's gonna tell you
what a great big success
you are once you get it all?
Spence, you are the one
who wanted to fucking change.
You started this
whole thing, remember?
- Huh?
- Yeah, I do.
But, I think we should just quit
while we're ahead.
Dude, this isn't fucking
ahead.
This is just more
of the same shit.
Nothing has changed.
What has changed?
Tell me.
I'm just not cut out
for it, Warren.
Okay? I'm not cut out
for it, so I'm not...
I'm done.
- Look, you just...
- I'm done.
You really wanna come
all this way,
and not find out
what happens next?
I mean, tell me this hasn't been
the time of your fucking life.
Man, I don't want you waking up,
ten years from now
wondering what
could've happened.
And who you could've been.
[sighs] Fine.
I'll see you around, man.
One day, you'll be dead!
[suspenseful music playing]
[panting]
[Spencer]
You can go through life,
with this expectation that something
fantastic is gonna happen.
Something life-altering, that's gonna
make your life different and unique.
I realized that I had to,
actually make something happen
on my own.
So, plan B.
We've agreed that Chas
will be the driver.
He stays in the van with the engine
running, and the doors open.
Myself and Eric, will be the only
ones to go inside the library.
No disguises. It just
creates unwanted attention.
What about him?
Spencer will be outside
on lookout.
What, why?
Well, he can't go inside.
People will recognize him.
We can't risk that.
So, then who's gonna be
the lookout inside the library?
[Warren] You.
You're gonna be downstairs
until I call you
to come bag up the books.
You know that I can't be involved in
dealing with the librarian, right?
- You get that?
- Like I said,
I will take care of that,
and then I will call you
once she's been...
She's neutralized.
This time, it's gonna work.
Okay, so, when I go up,
she'll be dealt with.
It'll be done?
Yes, Warren?
It's what I just said.
- Isn't it?
- Yeah.
[van door opens]
[suspenseful music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[suspenseful music continues]
[exhales]
[breathes heavily]
[exhales sharply]
- Mr. Beckman.
- Yes, hi. Walter Beckman.
Yes, Betty Jean Gooch.
Nice to see you.
- Nice to see you, too.
- Come in, please.
I have to say,
I expected someone much older.
- [chuckles]
- [laughs nervously] Yeah, you never know, do you?
No, you never know.
Now, I'm gonna ask you
to sign in for the log,
by your printed name.
- Right there, thank you.
- Thank you.
And then,
if you would date it, please.
[Betty] And how is
your day going, thus far?
It's going fine, thank you.
Um, I'm very sorry about
the other evening.
Uh, the other day,
[laughs nervously] sorry.
We, uh... I had a family
emergency I had to take care of.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
- Yeah.
- I trust everything is okay.
- It's okay now, thank you.
- Good.
Well, what you have
requested to see,
are among our most
treasured items.
I have laid out
the illuminated manuscript
and the Hortus Sanitatis
on my left.
Please remember to use
the gloves at all times
while touching any of the pages.
Sure.
Uh, is this a personal
interest of yours,
or are you working on
some kind of a project?
Uh, I just, um,
heard a great deal about them.
Ah.
Well, as you can see, one of
the volumes of the Audubon
is displayed here.
This case will remain locked
at all times.
However, if you do wish to see
some of the other plates,
I can help you to turn
some of the pages,
if time permits.
[cell phone vibrating]
You can come up now.
[suspenseful music continues]
[breathing heavily]
[clears throat]
[Warren] Ms. Gooch, uh,
my friend is right there.
Oh.
- Thank you so much.
- Sure.
Hello. Come in, please.
I will need your name
for the log book.
You need to sign in, John.
[Betty] John.
John?
Rutherford.
- Please sign by the...
- [muffled screaming]
- Warren, what are you doing?
- [Betty groans]
No, no, no! That's hurting me!
- I'm sorry. Just relax, all right?
- No, I can't. I got to get out.
- We're here for the books. We're not gonna hurt you.
- No! [crying]
Just relax. This will all
be over in a second.
[Betty] No, no, I can't.
Shut the fuck up! Shut up!
We're not gonna hurt you.
You keep struggling,
it's gonna fucking hurt more.
- [muffled crying]
- Shut up!
- Oh, God. Oh, God, help me.
- Tie her legs.
[Betty crying]
Start tying her fucking legs,
right now!
[Betty] Don't tie my hands.
Please, I can't...
- I can't have my hands tied.
- Goddamn it.
- [Betty] God, help me.
- Shit. Shit.
[Warren] Drop the fucking gloves.
What are you doing?
- [Betty] I just wanna go. I just wanna go.
- Let's go! Let's go!
Just relax, all right?
- I can't breathe. You're hurting me.
- Can you be calm?
I'm not gonna fucking hurt...
Oh, shit.
- Fuck!
- Why? Why are you doing this?
- Why?
- [Warren] It's the books. We want the books.
Not you.
You good? You good?
[panting]
[Warren] Fuck.
[rattling]
Find the keys.
Find the fucking keys!
Hurry the fuck up!
There's no keys.
- What?
- There's no keys. There's no fucking keys.
- I can't find any fucking key.
- Find the fucking key!
- Goddamn it.
- There's no fucking keys.
Get the fucking door.
Get it out of the case.
Shit!
[panting] Fuck.
[suspenseful music continues]
[Betty moaning]
[groaning]
[Warren] That's it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Get the fucking books,
right now.
What the fuck?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
She's moving towards the door.
I'm not fucking touching her.
I'm done touching her.
That's it.
- Fuck, I'm trying to get the thing out.
- I'm not touching her anymore!
- I'm done. I don't give a fuck.
- Goddamn it, I gotta do everything, my fucking self.
I'm not fucking
touching her anymore.
[moaning]
All right, that's it.
[muffled screaming]
[Warren] Shut the fuck up.
Shut the fuck up!
I'm sorry, okay?
We're getting out.
[stutters] I got it!
I got it, I got it, I got it.
[suspenseful music continues]
[Warren] Let's go.
[Warren grunting]
- Oh, shit.
- Shit.
[suspenseful music continues]
Fucking wrap this up.
[Warren] Wait, we need
another one. Another one.
What the fuck are you talking about?
This shit could be the fucking thing.
Leave it. Fucking leave it.
- What the fuck, man?
- It's fucking good enough.
This is good enough.
- The Darwin. Get the Darwin.
- No, fuck the Darwin, man.
- Fucking leave the Darwin, man.
- Yeah. Fuck.
This is fucking gold, man.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
[both panting]
Hit B, hit B.
[beeping]
What the fuck?
- [hysterically] You hit one? You hit one?
- Oh, fuck!
- [both panting]
- Fuck.
- It might not be bad.
- [elevator dings]
The fuck.
This is bad, man.
Oh, this is real bad.
[both panting]
Oh.
What the fuck?
- Wait here. Hold the door.
- It's pitch-black. Fuck.
[Eric] Goddamn it, Warren. This
isn't supposed to be like this.
[Warren] Oh, shit.
Where's the exit?
- [Warren panting]
- [Eric] This is really bad.
- Fuck!
- This is really fucking bad, Warren.
Oh, shit!
Fuck! Fuck!
Where's the fucking exit?
- [Eric] I don't know!
- Fuck!
What the fuck?
What are we gonna do?
- We have to make a run for it.
- What?
- We gotta make a run for it.
- What do you mean, "make a run for it"?
- We need to make a fucking run for it.
- They're gonna fucking see us.
- We have no choice. We have no choice.
- [Eric] Fuck, man, this is bad.
[panting]
This is so fucking bad.
[elevator dings]
[Warren whispering]
Go, go, go! Go, go, go!
[indistinct chatter]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Warren yells]
[yells] No! No!
- Keep fucking going. Fucking leave it. Go.
- No!
- [Eric] Go!
- Oh, fuck!
Oh, shit!
[tires screeching]
Warren, what the fuck
are you doing?
Shit.
Hey, stop! Fucking idiot, stop!
[Eric] Fucking go, go, go, go.
Hey, Eric,
where are the books, huh?
Where the fuck is Warren?
- Hey!
- [tires screeching]
[groans]
[Eric] Holy fuck.
[gasping]
Drive. Drive, drive, drive!
[tires screeching]
- [retches]
- Jesus Christ!
[coughing]
- Fucking drive.
- Oh, man, oh, man, oh, man.
Slow down.
You gotta fucking cool it.
Don't tell me
what the fuck to do.
- [Eric] Oh, man, oh, man.
- Where are the books, Warren?
- Fuck.
- Warren, where are the fucking books?
We dropped the fucking books!
Okay, Chas?
There's no fucking books!
- What are you telling me? We got nothing?
- We fucking dropped them!
- They fell out of our hands.
- We got fucking nothing.
Nothing, there's nothing.
Shut the fuck up!
- [Chas] Hey, fuck you, man.
- [Eric] Please.
[Chas] If you got nothing, why
did you take so long up there?
What the fuck happened
up there, man?
You know, fuck the both of you.
You guys fucked this up again.
I knew it, I knew you were
gonna fucking do this again.
[Eric stammering]
You didn't fucking go in there.
I have the Darwin.
[Warren] What do you got?
- Oh, gee.
- Eric, what do you fucking got?
Please, give me
a fucking second, please.
Your fucking backpack,
man. Check it!
[Chas] What's he got?
He got something?
Yeah.
[siren blaring]
What are you doing?
- Get out.
- What?
What are you fucking talking about? I'm
not getting out of the fucking car.
Dude, they're gonna be looking for a gray
van with three guys in it, okay? Get out.
- What the fuck is this, man?
- Get the fuck out, man!
Hey, I'm not moving this car with
the three of us in it. Get out!
- I'm not getting out of here...
- Get out!
I'll come back for you. I will
come back for you in my car.
- Just get the fuck out.
- You fucking promise?
- You're not gonna leave us here.
- I swear to fucking God I'll come back.
- I'm not getting out...
- Get out! Get out!
Eric, get the fuck out
of the fucking door!
Get the fuck... Get the fuck out.
- Get the...
- All right!
Please take your fucking bag.
Close the fucking doors.
Hurry the fuck up.
Fuck.
[suspenseful music continues]
- [sighs]
- Okay.
You gotta watch this, okay, buddy?
Fucking guard this.
Give me your clothes.
Give me your fucking clothes.
You can't stay here, okay?
Get your shit. Let's fucking go.
Get it together. Let's go.
There is a special collection
room inside of this library.
Now, we're told that some of
the books inside that room
date back to the 1700s.
They're very rare
and expensive.
This morning, two men
took advantage of that.
[reporter on radio] This is Dave
Wachinski from Transylvania University,
where the audacious robbery was
carried out in broad daylight...
- [Spencer] Listen to this.
- [Chas] Shh. Turn it up.
...forced their way into
the special collections room,
home to some of America's
most valuable books.
Police say the group knew exactly
what they were looking for.
Officials are helping police search
for the two men who stole the books,
and the two men who drove
the getaway vehicle.
- How did they know there were four of us?
- Quiet!
...described by witnesses
as a gray Dodge mini-van,
license plate number 331094.
Police are appealing for...
They got nothing on us.
How did they know
there were four of us?
[Chas] They don't know shit.
They have plates
from a different car.
...they violently restrained
a female librarian,
leaving her bound...
[indistinct chattering]
Okay?
[Melanie] Absolutely stunning,
aren't they?
And did Mister...
Beckman.
Did Mr. Beckman
give you any information
regarding the provenance
of the books?
Only that he inherited them
many years ago.
Uh, and wishes to realize their
value through a private sale.
Right.
They're extremely rare.
Yeah, [stutters]
his eyes are failing.
He says the books
no longer receive the attention
they fully deserve.
Any does he possess
any documentation
pertaining to his ancestor's
acquisition of the books?
Um, I mean, they've been
in his family for generations,
so, there's really
no documentation to speak of.
Well, they're exquisite,
and, uh, undoubtedly genuine.
So, let me talk this over
with Mr. Leckey,
and then we'll be in touch regarding an
estimate and steps toward a private sale.
Not today?
I'm afraid Mr. Leckey
is out of the office all day.
Well, you see, um...
- I'm sorry, I've forgotten your name.
- Melanie Halloran.
Ms. Halloran, we are really
hoping to supply Mr. Beckman
with a, um, estimate today.
That's why we came up here.
I wouldn't be able to
give you that
without Mr. Leckey's sign off.
And no one else who could
maybe take a look today?
As I say, this is really
Thomas' department.
And he'll be back here tomorrow.
Is there a number we can reach
you on while you're in town?
Ah, fuck.
So?
- [pants] It went well.
- And?
The main guy wasn't there, so we had to
talk to the, uh, junior executive...
Uh, deputy.
Deputy, and, uh...
She said what we got
is very valuable
and, uh, we just gotta wait
for the main guy to get back.
So, we gotta wait for the call, and
then we can get in touch with the...
- For the meeting.
- When you say wait for their call,
you mean at the hotel, right?
[exhales]
They're gonna call my cell.
Turn the engine off.
Ring you cell phone number.
Ring it now.
Fucking ring it!
Spencer! Okay, you know what,
I'll ring it for you, dipshit.
[line ringing]
Let's see.
[Spencer on voicemail] What's up?
This is Spence. You know what to do.
Does that sound like a fucking
art dealer to you, huh?
Look, Chas,
we can change the message.
Hey, hey, hey, shut up, Eric,
all right?
Shut the fuck up!
You need to go back in there.
You get whatever piece of paper that
has your phone number on it back.
- How?
- Right fucking now,
because I shit you not, that number's gonna
put us all in jail, you fucking asshole.
You just need to calm down.
Hey, don't fucking tell me
to calm down, Warren.
[stutters] You guys are sending
us to jail, you fucking idiots!
Do you not understand
what I'm saying?
or are you too fucking stupid?
If you're so smart, Chas,
why don't you go in there?
You know what,
I'll show you what
I can do, bitches.
[Chas cursing indistinctly]
What you got, Mr. Pink?
- [Eric] Whoa!
- Fuck! Okay, okay, what?
- What're you doing?
- What the fuck did you just call me?
- What the fuck, man?
- What'd you call me, you fucking bitch?
- Yeah. What? Where's the talk now, bitch, huh?
- Fuck!
This is my life you are
fucking with, man, okay?
This isn't some fucking game.
You gotta go back in there and
get that number back. [chokes]
You gotta go back in there and get that
fucking number back right now, Spencer. Go!
Chas, man, you know
we can't go back in there.
- We can't.
- I don't give a fuck what you think you know.
[sniffles] You've killed us.
You shot us all
in the fucking head.
[exhales]
[somber instrumental music
playing]
See you guys around, I guess.
See you around.
I'll call you later.
Yeah.
[Spencer] To have this,
this need to know what is on
the other side of that line,
and realizing the only way
to actually do that
is to cross it,
there's never a point
in your life after that
where you haven't
already crossed that line.
Um...
you know, it's... it was...
It was definitely
a terrifying thing.
[lecturer speaking indistinctly]
[Eric] I distinctly remember hearing that
scream in my head over and over again.
Just the scream
of the librarian.
What have I just done.
I felt so confident this was
gonna be what I needed.
It was this really, "Did I
just do something horrible?
Did I just hurt someone forever?
Did I just, um,
just take part
in something awful?"
You know?
You know, I'm sorry I haven't been
to your games lately. I just...
It's okay.
How's your form?
Never better.
How's the new place.
Well, it's great, you know.
It's actually very convenient.
It's near the shops,
and close to work
and everything.
[Warren]
We tried to say things like,
"We're not gonna hurt anybody."
"We're just gonna try to scare,
and get in and get out."
"We're gonna call
the cops afterwards."
"We're gonna talk to her and tell
her we're not gonna hurt her."
[tearfully] But we did.
[sniffling]
And we just tried to,
get past it, but there's no...
There's no looking past it.
[phone line ringing]
[Warren] It's the middle
of the fucking night.
[stuttering] Warren,
it's worse than we thought.
- What are you talking about?
- We, uh,
we used the same email address
to make the library appointment
that we used
to email Christie's, man.
They'll find the email,
they're gonna find Halloran,
find me, us, my phone number.
Fuck!
Chas was right, man.
Chas was right, Warren.
Dude, you're overthinking this.
You just gotta chill out,
and go back to bed, all right?
Peering that way
will destroy you.
[man on TV
speaking indistinctly]
[woman]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
I didn't know.
♪ Happy birthday, dear Dad ♪
Get us all a flurry, come on.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- [applause]
- [blows candle]
- [Mr. Reinhard] Okay.
- [Mrs. Reinhard] All right, good job.
[Mr. Reinhard laughing]
- [Mrs. Reinhard] Good job.
- Happy birthday, Dad.
Thank you.
Cheers.
[indistinct chatter]
[suspenseful music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
I love you.
Oh. All right.
Okay. [chuckles]
Thanks for coming.
- All right.
- Love you.
[suspenseful music continues]
[indistinct chattering]
Excuse me, sir, stop.
Stop right there!
Stop there!
[screams]
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Fucking asshole!
Is that all you fucking got?
Come on!
[panting]
[car alarm blares]
[suspenseful music continues]
["Who By Fire" playing]
♪ And who by fire ♪
♪ Who by water ♪
♪ Who in the sunshine ♪
♪ Who in the night time ♪
♪ Who by high ordeal ♪
♪ Who by common trial ♪
♪ Who in your
Merry, merry month of May ♪
♪ Who by very slow decay ♪
♪ And who shall I say ♪
♪ Is calling? ♪
♪ And who in her lonely slip ♪
♪ Who by barbiturate ♪
♪ Who in these realms above ♪
♪ Who by something blunt ♪
♪ Who by avalanche ♪
♪ Who by powder ♪
♪ Who for his greed ♪
♪ Who for his hunger ♪
♪ And who shall I say ♪
♪ Is calling? ♪
♪ And who by brave assent ♪
♪ Who by accident ♪
♪ Who in solitude ♪
♪ Who in this mirror ♪
♪ Who by his lady's command ♪
♪ Who by his own hand ♪
♪ Who in mortal chains ♪
♪ Who in power ♪
♪ And who shall I say ♪
♪ Is calling? ♪
[female reporter] After pleading
guilty to a robbery, conspiracy,
and theft of major artworks,
Spencer Reinhard, Eric Borsuk,
Charles Allen, and Warren Lipka
now know their fate.
A federal judge sentenced them each
to seven years at federal prison
after the four plotted
for months to steal
millions of dollars worth
of manuscripts and sketches
from Transylvania University's
special collections.
[Warren] You're taught your entire
life that what you do matters
and that you're special.
And that, there are things
you can point towards
that would...
which'll show that
you're special,
that shows that
you're different,
when, in all reality,
those things don't matter.
And you're not special.
And so, the idea that
we were doing this
extraordinary thing
absolutely appealed to us.
Appealed to me.
[Spencer] Looking back on it,
I've often wondered which events I
remember from Warren's point of view,
or I remember from my own.
And, if it was easier
to choose one over the other
because of what
it provided for us.
I don't remember if the guy
I saw in Central Park
was someone that I saw
or somebody that
Warren told me I saw.
- All right, bro. Go get 'em.
- Yeah.
All I remember
from his Amsterdam trip
was dropping him off at the
airport and picking him up.
I definitely don't have
evidence or actual proof
that Warren went to Amsterdam.
[Chas] Over the years,
I've definitely come to think
that Warren's whole story
about meeting with
an Amsterdam buyer,
that, most likely,
he just made the whole thing up.
I guess they just have to
take my word for it.
There was a version of the story
that I wanted to believe,
and, that I chose to believe.
And often times,
it was Warren's.
But the pain that I caused,
both to my family and to BJ are,
were never worth the adventure
that we felt at the time,
or the change in our life
that we were craving.
[Betty] I think they wanted
things to come easy for them.
They did not want to work for
a transformative experience.
They didn't want to help
other people
to achieve
a transformative experience.
I find them all very selfish.
And I see they all have trouble
figuring out how a person
crosses a line
in their own mind,
to be willing to hurt
another person
to get what they want.
And I think that,
once you've crossed that line,
I think it's
a dangerous line to cross.
[solemn instrumental music
playing]
It makes me wonder if they
really know why they did it.
[solemn instrumental music
continues]
["Crucify Your Mind" playing]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
♪ Was it a huntsman
Or a player ♪
♪ That made you pay the cost ♪
♪ That now assumes
Relaxed positions ♪
♪ And prostitutes your loss ♪
♪ Were you tortured
By your own thirst ♪
♪ In those pleasures
That you seek ♪
♪ That made you
Tom the curious ♪
♪ That makes you
James the weak? ♪
♪ And you claim
You got something going ♪
♪ Something you call unique ♪
♪ But I've seen
Your self-pity showing ♪
♪ As the tears
Rolled down your cheeks ♪
♪ Soon you know
I'll leave you ♪
♪ And I'll never look behind ♪
♪ 'Cause I was born
For the purpose ♪
♪ That crucifies your mind ♪
♪ So, con
Convince your mirror ♪
♪ As you've
Always done before ♪
♪ Giving substance to shadows ♪
♪ Giving substance ever more ♪
♪ And you assume
You got something to offer ♪
♪ Secrets shiny and new ♪
♪ But how much of you
Is repetition ♪
♪ That you didn't whisper
To him, too ♪
[violin music playing]