(tugboat whistles)
(seagulls screeching)
(puppies whimpering)
Look at those feet.
Does that mean...
Yeah, he's going
to be a big one.
Wow.
What do you say?
Thank you.
Thanks, Sam.
You take good
care of him.
Bring him back in a couple
of weeks for vaccinations, okay?
Hi, Lydia.
Hi.
Bye now.
Bye-bye.
Thanks.
Which one did she take?
The floppy-eared one.
How're you doing?
I know.
Good.
Almost finished.
Want to go see
the Taj Mahal?
I'll go anywhere with you, baby.
Oh, you picked
my favorite one.
If I might be so bold,
I called him Bentley.
Get out of there.
All right.
How am I supposed to know
when my next appointment is?
Oh, it's in
a half an hour,
but it's Elmer.
If he's on time,
I'll do cartwheels.
I'd like to see that.
No, you wouldn't.
(hammering)
(saw buzzing)
I thought they'd be
further along.
We've had a lot of rain.
Hey, Sam.
Lyddie.
Hi.
What's up?
Came to take a look.
What do you think?
Nice hole.
Well, we've had
a lot of rain.
That's what I said.
Can't dig in the rain.
You guys in a hurry?
You want to fill this house
up with some babies?
Yup.
Someday.
We get some good weather,
we'll be fine.
Sure.
I've got
the Turleys' sheep,
and then a checkup
on Joe's pregnant cow.
Okay. Call me when
you're headed home.
Bye.
Hi, Sam.
Hi.
How's your dog doing, Brad?
He's looking good, Doc.
Dermatitis is
practically all gone.
Yeah, but he's got
a rash of his own. Show him.
He wants to use
the dog medicine.
I wouldn't do that.
I told him that.
Why? Won't it work?
Not unless you want
to wake up one morning
barking like a dog.
That would be
an improvement.
Wouldn't it?
See ya.
Hey, kid!
Get over here and help me.
Hurry!
Come here!
Come on!
Get up here! Ooh!
(playfully grunting)
(laughing)
Tetracycline.
Campbell's hound
lacerated his paw.
Did you find it?
No.
Where is it?
Tiny hairline fracture,
right above the joint.
Hmm.
You don't need
reading glasses, do you?
No.
Just wondering.
Hi.
Hey.
What's up?
Oh, just passing by.
I thought
I'd stop in.
Busy?
Yeah.
Don't mean to interrupt.
I saw her.
How come you
didn't tell me?
I was on a call.
I saw her, too.
Down at the gas station.
Hi, Ross.
Need some help?
Elmer just showed up
and I've got
the Campbell dog.
Elmer's appointment
was yesterday.
That's Elmer.
All right.
You take him, would you?
I'll take the Campbell dog.
What brings
you here?
He needs a distemper shot.
She asked about you.
I'll catch up with her.
Trooper!
Look what I found.
What is it?
What do you mean,
"What is it?"
A drum set, doofus.
Whose are they?
They belonged to
an old friend of mine.
What was his name?
Ben.
He asked me to
keep them for him,
because he didn't have room.
Can I play them?
Can I play them really loud?
Yeah...
Just do me a favor
and wait till
I get downstairs.
Let 'er rip!
So what'd you think?
About what?
The movie.
Oh, I liked it.
You did not.
Why do you say that?
You kept looking
at your watch.
I guess I did, didn't I.
Sam, where are you?
I'm right here.
That ought
to do it, Walter.
Just give it
a week or so.
I can't pay you
till next week, Sam.
Don't look at me.
We know where you live.
Your 3:30 cancelled.
I guess I'll run out to Joe's,
check on that cow.
Weren't you just there
yesterday?
Yeah.
She's very close.
You're acting like
an expectant father.
Are you going
to hand out cigars?
(ball bouncing)
Hi.
Your mom around?
No.
She went to the store.
My name's Sam.
I'm an old friend
of your mother's.
I used to live next door.
This was my house, right here.
That was my room, right there.
I see you're quite
the basketball player.
Mm.
(grunts)
How about that?
Well...
I'll just...
I'll come around
another time.
ROSEMARY:
Okay, Joe.
I'll tell him.
Okay.
Okay!
Where's Sam?
Oh, I don't know.
He said he was going to
check on Joe Lieber's cow.
Maybe she's already
had her calf.
Well, she did.
But Sam wasn't there.
Where'd you go?
Well, I had to go
check on Joe's cow.
Joe called.
The cow had her calf.
He said you
weren't there.
Ah, I didn't make it, so...
How come?
Is Sam back?
Oh, Sam, someone
wants to see you.
Right.
I think we've solved
the mystery.
That dog's cute.
Hi, Sam.
Kind of expected
a bigger hello.
I'm... surprised to see you.
Trooper, is this
the guy who stopped by?
Mm-hmm.
Well, I-I heard that
you were in town.
I'm just...
surprised.
So, you already met
my son, Trooper.
No, not officially.
I'm Sam.
Hi.
Dude, what do you do
when somebody
offers you
their hand?
And what else?
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet
you, too.
I told Troop that
you were a veterinarian,
and he wanted
to come by right away
'cause he loves animals.
Is that right?
Well...
I might know a puppy
who needs a home.
I don't suppose
you'd be interested?
Please, Mom?
Mmm, well...
Come on.
you have to take care of him.
I will. Come on.
All right.
Just wait
right here.
Do you even know how
to take care of a dog?
What are you gonna do?
Made a deal.
A gummy bear!
You want another?
Okay.
I'm Rosemary.
Trooper.
Ah.
Oh...
Sam.
Oh.
Hey... oh...
(Rosemary and Trooper laugh)
TROOPER:
What's his name?
No, it's up to you.
Thanks, Sam-- I think.
Just be good to him--
bring him back here
whenever he needs anything;
it'll be on the house.
(laughs):
I'll take good care of him. Hey!
Oh, come on. Oh...
Good girl.
SAM:
Hi, Alice.
Go ahead and take her
on back to number two.
I'll be there
in a minute.
Yes, I...
Alice?
It's me, Dee Dee.
Dee Dee Michaud?
Yeah. And this is
my son, Trooper.
Well, hello, Trooper.
Why, my goodness,
I haven't seen you since...
Yeah. About 13 years.
Are you just visiting?
No. I'm here to stay.
Well... good for you.
Sam, I-I can see
that you're busy--
we'll catch up later?
Okay.
(quietly):
Trooper!
Thanks for the puppy.
You're welcome.
Bye, Rosemary.
Good-bye.
SAM:
Give him a good home.
I will.
(crickets chirping)
LYDIA:
Why didn't you just tell me
the truth at the office?
I didn't want
Rosemary gossiping.
About what?
About Dee Dee.
What about Dee Dee?
(groans):
Oh, just... nothing.
You were worried she'd
gossip about nothing?
We were friends.
We grew up together--
I mean, I've known
the girl since I was
three years old.
She and Ross
and I hung out.
I mean, she was fun.
Fun?
We were just
friends, okay?
(laughs)
People gossip
about friends here.
It's a small town, Lydia.
What do you know
about small towns--
you grew up in Boston.
Oh, I don't know, Sam,
why don't you tell me
what it's like to grow up
in a small town.
Tell me about your "friend."
What do you mean?
I don't know.
What's she like?
She was a free spirit.
'Kay? Everybody in town
knew her.
Me, I was this shy little kid
afraid of his own shadow.
Once there was
this kid who was...
sort of the neighborhood bully,
he stole my baseball cards.
Now, I pretended
that it didn't matter,
but it mattered to Dee Dee.
She found him,
she beat him up,
and she got 'em all back for me.
Oh, that was nice of her.
But you know what,
she didn't even care
about what people thought
about her.
In the ninth grade,
she gets caught smoking
in the school bathroom.
The principal
takes her into his office.
Before he can even
get a word in,
she offers him a cigarette.
Mm-hmm.
Anyway...
on graduation day, she ran off
with Bobby Langford.
Could you pass me
the olive oil?
Is she the one
you were gonna give
your class ring to?
Who told you that?
Ross.
A long time ago.
Yeah. She was the one.
Pass me the pepper?
Not until you tell me.
Nothing to tell.
Try me.
Well, I was planning on
giving her my class ring
the night before
graduation.
We were standing
out on her porch,
and I had it out,
I had it in my hand,
and I'm about to give
it to her, but before
I could say anything,
she pops out with the
news that she's going.
Next day, gone.
You never heard from her?
Couple of postcards.
Uh, one.
From some small
town in Kansas.
Home of the world's
biggest ball of twine.
"Ain't life a hoot?"
That's what it said,
nothing more.
How come
you never mentioned her?
I didn't think it
was that important.
It's just that
she was your first crush.
I mean, if my first
boyfriend came into town...
Look, I...
I got over it.
I married this woman that
I am absolutely crazy about.
Really? What's she like?
Eh, you'd have to know her.
Is she pretty?
Pretty? No.
Movie-star beautiful.
Smart as a whip.
And let's see...
terrific veterinarian.
Did I mention that?
Loved by people
and pets alike.
I think we should
ask them to dinner.
Really?
You got to know
the competition.
Oops.
Hi!
Hey, Dee Dee,
Trooper.
Lydia.
Nice to meet you.
Hi. Nice to meet you, too.
This is Trooper.
Hi, Trooper.
Hi.
(tsks)
Hi. It is really nice
to meet you.
Well, come on inside.
This is for you.
Oh. Thank you.
Should I open it now?
Sure.
Okay.
(Lydia chuckles)
Oh, they're lovely.
(laughs):
I'm glad you like them.
I made them.
Uh, they're beautiful.
(laughs)
We can use them
tonight at dinner.
I'm still working
in the kitchen.
Oh, good.
Let me help you.
What are you making?
Nothing fancy.
Some roasted chicken,
mash potatoes, carrots.
Nut?
Okay.
LYDIA:
Oh, I love candlelight dinners.
Mmm, me, too.
Maybe you'll be
a customer.
A customer?
I'm gonna open up
a candle shop.
Here?
Is that a bad idea?
Well, no...
it's not a bad idea.
(chuckles):
But...?
He's such a terrible liar.
He's learning.
Well, I just...
wonder if it's, uh,
if the town is
large enough for a...
a candle store.
Yeah, I thought
of that, but...
I figure if I offer
candle-making lessons,
you know.
What do you think
Lydia?
Oh, I-I think you'll just
have to try it and see.
Well, would you be interested?
Me? I don't have
that much free time.
So, how did you get interested
in candle-making?
Oh, you know, it started
as a hobby, but then
I had to make a living.
And, uh... I guess I just love
what candles symbolize.
Which is what?
Home.
I guess hopes
and dreams and wishes.
People light candles in church.
They use them
for prayer.
Dude,
you can't just eat
before everybody starts.
No, it's okay. It's okay.
Dig in.
(clears throat)
So, Trooper...
how'd you get the
nickname "Trooper"?
It's not a nickname.
It's my real name.
We've traveled around
so much, we're like
a small theater troupe.
So you spell it with a "U"?
Hmm?
T-R-O-U-P-E-R.
No...
T-R-O-O-P-E-R.
I gave him the name,
so I figure he can
spell it however he wants.
Well, not really.
Oh. Yeah, that's right, because
last year you wanted to spell it
with three O's.
(laughs)
Troop, weren't you gonna
ask Sam something?
Oh, yeah.
Uh...
do you have lots
of animals downstairs?
We sure do.
Can I see 'em?
Sam, why don't you take Trooper
down and show him our zoo.
Good.
All right,
come on, Troop.
Can I call you Troop?
If you want to.
Everybody
calls me Sam.
He's a nice boy.
Yeah.
He reminds me
of Sam.
Shy at first, but there's
a lot going on underneath.
I understand you're living
in your childhood home.
Yeah. Lots of
memories there.
(chuckles)
What brings you back
after all this time
My mom died, and the house
was just sitting there.
But mostly for Trooper--
I keep boring him
with all my stories of how
great it was to grow up here.
How'd you and Sam meet?
Oh, at Cornell, in vet school.
He always wanted
to be a vet.
I guess you knew him
pretty well.
Yeah. Hard not to--
he lived next-door.
We spent every
day together.
Especially in
the summertime.
So you moved back here
after vet school?
I was a city girl
pining for country life.
Slower pace,
nicer people.
You must have a lot
of friends here.
Yeah, I... I guess I do.
But you married my best one.
Well, this is where we operate.
Is there a lot
of blood and stuff?
Sometimes.
How's that puppy
doing, by the way?
Oh, he's fine.
What do you
call him?
Chewbacca.
Nice name.
How did you come up with that?
He tried to eat
my shoelaces.
Are all these yours?
No. They all belong
to other people.
Except this
little guy.
Actually, this is
Chewbacca's brother.
Want to see him?
Sure.
Do you get to
play with them?
It's kind of hard
to find the time.
Thank you.
Dinner was so good.
You're welcome.
Do you want me to
walk you guys home?
Nah. We know the way.
Don't bother.
Go ahead, Sam.
I'll be right back.
Got it?
Yep.
Remember that
bike I bought
with berry-picking
money?
The one you sold
to Jimmy Farrington?
I wish I had it back.
I'd give it to Troop.
What's wrong
with the one he has?
Nothing. Just
pure nostalgia.
Nostalgia?
Coming from the woman who could
not wait to get out of here.
It's funny,
isn't it?
Guess it's true
you never appreciate
what you have
until it's gone.
Hey, Trooper.
This is Cee Jay's--
that place I told you about.
Same old place.
Same old geezers.
Except now I'm one of them.
Where's his dad?
Troop never knew his dad.
He was less than
a year old when Bobby left.
Bobby?
Yeah.
Where did he go?
Alaska.
He never really
wanted kids.
I can't say that
I'm surprised.
Sam, is that a polite way
of saying, "I told you so"?
How about
you and Lydia?
Any plans for kids
in the future?
Kids? Yeah. Someday.
I just want
to be sure.
Sure about what?
We're financially
secure.
That we're ready.
Time to devote
to a family.
You haven't
changed a bit, Sam.
I guess not.
I wish I were
more like you.
Never thought I'd
hear you say that.
Oh, shut up.
I have learned something
in the last 13 years.
Last few nights, I can't sleep.
I wake up, I go to my window
and look out at your window.
It used to make me
so comfortable,
just knowing
you were there.
I'm so sorry, Sam.
I'm sorry
I fell off the map.
Bobby and I
married right away.
Trooper came
a year later.
I'm not making excuses, but...
I do really apologize.
No need.
It's kind of hard for Troop,
you know,
moving again to a new place.
He's got to make new friends.
He seems
like a great kid.
You know,
in the meantime,
I could use some help
around the clinic.
Someone to feed and
look after the animals.
He would love that.
Thank you, Sam.
I... I... I have
to make trips
back and forth
to Boston...
This is perfect.
What are you doing in Boston?
Oh, I have to pick up supplies.
Umm... Lydia seems great.
Yeah, she is great.
I guess I got lucky.
I hope you don't mind.
No, it's fine.
It'll be good for him.
And good practice
for you.
You okay
about tonight?
Yeah. It wasn't as awkward
as I had imagined.
She seems nice enough.
So, you check the brand
of the food
with the amounts
on the card,
and then you feed them
out of the right one.
Okay.
Which one is it?
This one here.
When you're working
with a puppy,
sometimes they
can be tentative.
You want to try to coax
them into a behavior
with a reward--
a treat--
like this,
so we want
to have him come
down the stairs,
but keep your hand here
so they don't fall.
Come on, sweetness.
Can I play with them
after I feed them?
Oh, I'd say that's
a big part of the job.
Really?
Uh-huh.
You got to feed
them first. Here.
Wait, no. Hey. No.
Reach right in. They're
not going to come out.
There you go.
Come on. Yeah!
Okay. There you go.
Do you want to
give him the treat?
Yeah.
Okay.
Reward him.
Come on. Here you go.
Good job.
What's the dog's name?
Jesse.
Hi, Jesse.
Hey, girl.
Perfect, except he's a boy.
Oh. Sorry, Jesse.
Here. Come here.
Oh, good.
Oh, I think
he likes you.
He likes me.
He does.
Now, don't be
nervous now,
Naomi.
It's just the entire
fate of the game.
Oh.
This isn't over.
Better luck next time,
sweetheart.
Excuse me.
Go. It's your turn.
How's the
house coming?
It's just a hole
at the moment.
Rick's as slow
as molasses.
Took him a year to do
my Uncle Ned's place.
He's careful.
And Ned has a great house.
Oh, and Sam
likes careful.
Boy, does he ever.
Yeah, well, if you
don't push him,
it'll be your retirement home.
Push who? Sam or Rick?
Rick.
Come to think
of it, Sam, too.
You better push
them both, Lyddie.
What's the hurry?
Funny you should ask.
Hey, Cee Jay,
you got anything
to read while
we're waiting?
(mock snoring)
Oh! Tell me you weren't
sleeping through that,
were you?
Sorry. I missed it.
Oh. You weren't sleeping,
were you?
Mom?
What?
What are these?
These.
Where did
you find them?
In the drawer
in the kitchen.
That's Sam.
That's Sam?
He's so serious.
Grr!
He's kind of chubby.
Who's this?
Your dad.
Can I keep it?
Sure.
Here. Put these back.
This is 154 degrees in here.
But don't worry.
You can stick your finger
in here,
and it kind of feels good.
You won't get hurt.
Umm... Okay.
The key to making candles
is you can't hurry.
You have to have patience.
When I use that word
with my son,
he rolls his eyes at me,
but I guess that's payback
for all the times
I did that to my mom.
Okay. So each of us needs
to take a wick.
Thank you.
You want to hold it
in the middle and, uh...
just keep it apart
so that it doesn't
get stuck together.
Dipping candles are made
a pair at a time.
Now, dip the wick
into the heated wax.
How long do you leave it in?
Oh, just trust your gut.
It's kind of like
cooking without
a recipe.
A recipe?
What's that?
(laughter)
So you want to put it in
for, like,
I don't know, three seconds,
and then keep it out
for about three seconds.
And then we're going
to cool them off
for about
three minutes.
I know that they look
kind of skinny.
Skinny? What's that?
(all laughing)
That's what he said!
That's what he said.
Lydia! Hi.
Hi.
Hi, Lydia.
I was just passing by.
I thought I' d...
Oh, come on in.
I'm so glad
that you came.
Well...
Oh, come on, Lyddie.
This is fun.
I'm just not so crafty.
Oh, we all aren't.
So...
when I sell my candles,
I like to put a little message
in each box.
If you're going to be
using them as gifts,
you might want to do the same.
Like what?
I think
candles help us
explore the darkness.
You know?
People used to sit
around campfires,
keep the predators away.
I think
firelight...
makes us feel safe.
You know? I do.
Can you imagine?
There were, like,
a half dozen of us...
all women... gathered...
learning how
to make these candles.
It was kind of magical.
Sitting there
in that room,
I really did feel
a sense of something.
Fire hazard,
probably.
I'm serious.
All right.
What did you feel?
You know, for as long
as I've been in this town,
I've never felt
a sense of that
so strongly as I did tonight.
What?
A sense of community.
You know, I really do like her,
much more
than I thought I would.
Good.
Tell you the truth,
I was a little jealous of her.
No kidding.
You knew?
Oh, please.
I just can't seem to get
him to take his pills.
Oh, well, you just
hold him like this,
open his jaw, take the pill,
and put it back like that.
Lyddie, the Frieden mare
is having trouble foaling.
I'm going
to take Trooper along.
He up to it?
We'll find out.
Your call, but if
he faints or heaves...
Sorry.
We have a young helper.
Oh.
Hello, Doc.
Hey, John.
This is my new helper.
Meet Trooper.
Hey.
(soft whinnies)
The foal hasn't dropped
into the birth canal.
She could start to lose
blood supply soon.
All right,
hand me my kit.
Put it right here.
Yeah.
Okay, Sophie,
Be a good girl.
This is known as the
jugular groove, see?
It's easy to find.
You just trace from the jaw
angle down the neck.
I like to go in
towards the north.
I press here.
See that?
It increases the blood
pressure in the vein.
That'll take effect
in a few minutes,
be less
dangerous for her--
and for us.
Okay.
The foal is in a good position.
Have both forelegs
extended forward,
one a little less so
than the other,
with the chin resting
on the knees.
Now, if the neck was
flexed to either side,
the foal could get his head
caught on the way out,
which would be... trouble,
but this one
looks fine so far.
The only worry is
how long it's taking.
See the tiny
little hooves there?
Bottom's downward,
towards the mother's feet.
We'd better move
things along here
and apply a little traction.
All right.
In my kit is a set of OB chains.
They're shiny, narrow,
stainless steel.
Do me a favor and
go get them. Go.
(chains rattling)
Sit down.
Since they're looped
just above the ankles,
it's not going to
hurt when we pull.
All right.
When she pushes, we pull.
Ready?
Pull.
Okay. Stop. Stop.
Okay. Wait
for the contraction.
This is the most difficult part.
Pull!
Good. Good and hard.
Oh. Okay.
All right.
Wow. Wow.
Wow.
(laughing)
Hey, thanks, Doc.
If he isn't up and
nursing in an hour,
give me a call.
Yeah, I'll
do that.
I'll do that.
Hey, that's some
little helper you've got here.
Sure is.
Yeah.
Good job.
Thanks. Oh.
Oh. Thank you.
Your shirt.
See you, John!
Take care, Doc.
Trooper, right?
Yeah.
I'll see ya.
You did a good job.
I was a little scared.
Nothing wrong
with being scared.
You hung in there.
Come on.
Sam?
Yeah?
Did you know
my dad?
Your dad?
Yeah.
Oh, I didn't know
him really well.
He was only
in town for a year.
What was he like?
Well, let's see.
He was a cool guy.
I could say that.
My mom says he was a dreamer.
You could say that.
He left us to go to Alaska.
Dreamers have to
follow their hearts.
They sure do.
Come on.
The kid thinks he's
some sort of romantic hero.
I couldn't even believe
what I was hearing.
A dreamer?
Come on.
The guy was a lowlife
who abandoned them.
Maybe you were just a little
jealous of him, Sam.
Lyddie,
the guy spent
half the year he was
here working on his car,
the other half dealing pot.
How do you
romanticize that?
What if she's just
protecting her son?
By lying to him?
If he were your son,
what would you say?
I don't know.
Well, looky!
Hey, Cee Jay.
How you doing?
I heard you were
back in town.
Yeah. You want to check
my ID for old times' sake?
Darling, you
never had an ID.
That's how come I used
to throw you out of here.
Nice to have you back.
It's nice to be
here-- legally.
Hey.
Hey, we were
wondering
if you were
going to show up.
Yeah, I know.
I had to drive to Boston
to pick up supplies
for the candle business.
Oh! Candlemania
sweeps the town.
I know.
Even Rosemary joined the group.
Oh, no. Where
will it end?
Maybe it won't.
Everything ends.
Hey, Cee Jay,
can we get another glass?
You know what?
We have three-fourths
of the band here.
What band?
Sam's band.
Oh, it wasn't
my band, it was Dee Dee's.
I didn't know
you had a band.
I didn't.
I wouldn't have even
been in the band
if Dee Dee hadn't
of browbeaten
the others
into taking me.
What did you play?
Guitar.
If you call
that playing.
I don't.
Come on, Sam.
People liked you.
Because you did.
If Ben and Ross
and I would have
started the
band on our own,
it would have lasted
five minutes.
Hey, I was good.
Yeah.
You were
awful.
Dee Dee, she
was, was good.
When did Ben move?
Um... a couple
of years ago.
I think he went
up to Dallas.
Yeah.
Do you still sing, Dee Dee?
It drives Trooper crazy.
So. How about a song?
Yeah.
Oh, we don't have Ben.
Unless you want
to do Ben's part.
Are you kidding?
(Sam laughing)
Sam, you never sang for me.
Profoundly good reason.
♪ People say I'm the
life of the party ♪
♪ 'Cause I tell a joke or two ♪
♪ Although I might be
laughing loud and hearty ♪
♪ Deep inside I'm blue ♪
♪ So take a good
look at my face ♪
♪ You see my smile
looks out of place ♪
♪ If you look closer,
it's easy to trace ♪
♪ The tracks of my tears... ♪
(drumming)
Hey, kid!
It's too late for drums.
Go to bed.
Guess what I did today?
What's that?
I delivered a horse.
All by yourself?
No, not by myself,
but I helped.
Yeah?
It was so cool!
And guess what else?
Sam...
he said my dad was
a really cool guy.
Oh.
Yeah.
Yeah, really cool.
Just like you,
Mr. Horse Doctor.
Now go to sleep!
(smooching, giggling)
I love you, Mom.
I love you, too, baby.
Here's your friend.
'Night.
Good night, angel.
See you in the morning.
Hey, let's go to sleep, okay?
(sobbing)
Guys, give me a hand
with the wall?
Let's get it up.
Would you like some coffee, sir?
Good. Okay, slide it.
Looks good, Rick.
When do you
think the framing
will be finished?
It's hard to say.
Can you give us a guess?
Well... That's good.
Not really.
Well, by fall?
Early fall or late fall?
Any fall.
Depends, really.
Well, if we get
into the winter
and the house
isn't finished...
Yeah, it could happen.
Wouldn't that hurt
the house?
Not really. Why?
I'd just prefer it
if it didn't fall
down in a heap.
Picky, picky.
Hey, Doc.
How's that colt doing?
Oh, fit and fine,
like last week.
Not used to seeing
so much of you.
Thank my assistant
for that.
Oh...
What's his name?
I don't have one yet.
Got any ideas?
Solitaire.
Huh. Pretty good.
How come you
picked that one?
(whinnies)
He doesn't have anyone
to play with.
Well, then that's
what we'll call him.
Solitaire.
Quick, quick, quick!
Mom, it's my fault.
Look at him!
No, it's not,
sweetheart.
I should have been there!
Honey, it's okay.
Come on.
Come on. They'll
fix him right up.
(sobbing)
Cody got hit by a car.
Oh, my. Here, bring
him on back. Sam!
What does it look like?
Crushed lumbar vertebra.
Spinal cord damage
looks irreversible.
Abdomen's full of fluid,
probably a ruptured spleen.
Maybe I'll take Amber outside
while you talk to Val.
Okay.
(Amber sobbing)
Do you want to go come
outside with me?
Hi.
Want to go over
the X rays?
No, that's okay.
It looks bad, Val.
Is there anything we can do?
Well... we could try to save
him, but it'll be painful
and I can't give you
any guarantees.
What would you do
if he were yours, Sam?
I think I'd let Cody go.
Okay.
I'm going
to talk to Amber.
Sure.
I'll let her come
and say good-bye.
You're just going
to let him die?
Well, I'd do anything
if I could save him,
but he's been hurt
pretty badly
and he's in a lot
of pain.
I don't think we should
let him suffer like that.
Troop, where are you going?
(doorbell chimes)
Hi.
Hey.
Is Troop home?
Yeah, he's upstairs.
Can I speak with him?
I want to explain
something to him.
I already talked to him.
He's pretty upset.
Come on in.
It isn't just about
the puppy, Sam.
What is it?
You know, I've been
making trips back
and forth to Boston.
Hm-hmm.
It's not to pick up supplies.
I've been going to a hospital.
What for?
Cancer.
Non-Hodgkin's lymphoma.
I'm dying, Sam.
It's widespread.
It's in my lymph nodes,
bone marrow,
liver.
You must have had
treatment.
Yeah.
It's just
a matter of time.
How much time?
I was hoping to make it
to Troop's 12th birthday,
but it's moving too fast.
Does he know?
More or less.
But he's hoping.
I haven't told him the latest.
Sorry. It's really why
I came home.
So you can die here?
No, I want Trooper to live here.
I need to find him
a place, a family.
I had this crazy idea.
I built this place up
in my mind, you know?
It seemed
so magical to me
and I thought all I had to do
was come home.
Clearly, I haven't
learned a thing
'cause when I was 18
I thought everything outside
of this town was magical,
and I just had to leave.
How about his dad?
Oh, come on.
You've never liked him.
You were right.
He got into drugs
and dealing,
and it only got worse
as time went on.
After Troop was born,
he took off for Alaska.
Said he had to get work.
He, um, got busted
and did two years.
Then when he got out,
he went right back to it.
He got himself killed,
and I never found out how.
I chose so badly, Sam,
not just for myself,
but for Troop.
Aw, Dee Dee.
I'm so sorry.
I know.
I know you are.
I need your help, Sam.
I have no one else.
Anything.
I need you to help me find
a place for Troop.
Please?
I just sat there with this
stupid look on my face.
I felt like such an idiot.
But I didn't know what to say.
What are you going
to do?
I don't know.
Look for somebody,
I guess.
But who?
I thought
of John Frieden.
John Frieden?
Yeah. He likes Trooper.
He's got horses...
He's over 60 years old.
50-something.
And Trooper would love
being on a farm.
What does he know about
raising boys these days?
They raised two kids.
That was over ten years ago.
His kids are married.
They have families
of their own.
You think he's forgotten how?
No, but raising kids
these days
is a lot different
than it was then.
It was just a thought.
Sam?
Mm?
I was thinking last night.
Yeah? So was I.
About what?
Going over the names
of everyone I know.
We could take him.
No, we couldn't.
Why not?
It wouldn't work,
Lyddie.
Where we going
to put him?
We're building a house.
She doesn't think she's
going to make it that long.
We have a spare room.
We can fix it up.
It's not a practical idea.
Why not?
Because we're not set up for it.
We both work.
Who's going to look after him?
You have to make plans
for things like this.
It takes time.
Oh, come on, Sam.
I don't think this decision
is about being practical.
We've thought about this
for one night, okay?
It's a huge responsibility.
We've thought about having
kids for a long time.
What about Val?
I think Val's a good idea.
Her husband's out of work.
I don't think she can.
Well, then there's
the Grubers.
There's, there's
lots of people.
Why don't we just see
how she does?
Maybe she's wrong.
She could live
for another year.
for two years.
In the meantime,
I've got to go
inoculate the Holden
pigs, okay?
We'll find somebody.
Hi, Trooper.
Hey. Is Sam here?
He'll be back soon.
Lydia,
I'm sorry
I ran off like that.
It wasn't very
professional of me.
Well, you know,
I could use some professional
help with this fellow.
You want to hold him?
Hold him by the collar.
Okay.
Give him some comfort.
Sunny's having
his operation, huh?
Yup.
Is he going
to be okay?
He'll be great.
That's good. I was worried.
You ever think
of having more kids?
Beyond the two
little hellions
we're raising now,
you mean?
Yeah.
Why do you ask?
Just wondering.
You been talking to Naomi?
No. About what?
Lydia been talking
to Naomi?
Not that I know of. Why?
Naomi's pregnant.
Congratulations.
(laughs)
Thanks,
but I don't know how
we're going to do it.
We're barely making it
now on two teachers' salaries.
Yeah, it's not easy.
You and Lydia
thinking of...?
No. Not yet.
You still remember how?
It'll come back to me.
Sam, come on.
What'd you ask me for?
For Dee Dee.
(thunder crashes)
Sorry I'm late.
Oh, you're
never too late.
We were just going to start
to read our messages
we're putting
into our gift boxes, right?
Rosemary, do you want
to go first?
Oh, sure,
it's always me.
Oh, this is for
my brother-in-law Jack,
who is a real... pill.
Well, he is.
"Jack be nimble,
"Jack be quick,
"Jack jump over
the candlestick.
"But don't burn
your rear
"or you will see
exactly the pain
you are to me."
(laughing)
Not exactly what I had
in mind, but it works.
You don't know Jack.
(siren wailing)
(phone ringing)
Don't get excited.
Remember last week
when the cat, like,
went through an alarm
and went all over the place.
It happens all the time.
Constantly.
Doc... it's
your new house.
Come on, Dennis,
I'll give you a ride...
ALL:
Oh no!
I'm so sorry, Lydia.
It's just the framing.
It's not even a house, yet.
It's a dream.
Maybe we can dream it again.
RICK:
I kept the generator
going to run the pump.
I was afraid it was
going to flood.
It must have been
an electrical short.
I'm sorry.
LYDIA:
It's not your fault, Rick.
It was an accident.
When can we
start rebuilding?
RICK:
I'll have to clean
this mess up.
Labor Day is coming soon.
I say we wait
until spring.
Once the bad
weather starts
we're just
going to have to stop.
What do you think, Sam?
(crashing)
Sam?
Talk to me.
I had Rick do the house because
he's so... meticulous.
Every nail, every joint,
every angle...
just so.
I had him prepare
the house for a hurricane.
Did I tell you that?
When was the last time there was
a hurricane around here?
I don't know.
A hundred years?
He was going
to truss the gables,
reinforce the garage door,
put a special adhesive
on the shingles...
You can't protect
against everything.
Not everything.
But everything you
can think of.
But you can't think
of everything either.
It was a freak accident.
My mother was so afraid
of hurricanes.
I don't blame her.
Nah, she was afraid
of pretty much everything.
Every time my dad would
leave on a sales trip,
he'd make sure we had
everything we needed.
Check the tires,
check the house,
the rain gutters,
the shutters,
did we have enough firewood,
and on and on and on.
And still, this woman,
she was afraid.
Of what?
Oh, you name it.
I used to hear her walking
around the house late at night,
making sure all the windows
were locked.
And every time
I'd leave the house,
my mother would ask me
if I had enough money?
Where are you going?
Are your socks warm enough?
I used to think I could
actually hear...
her worrying.
It got to the point
where I didn't even
want to leave the house.
It was easier
just to stay at home.
If it hadn't been for Dee Dee,
I probably would have never
left the yard.
She sounds like she was
a good friend to have.
She was more than that.
She was my friend,
my sister...
(sobbing)
Do you...
do you think I'd be
a good father?
Sam, yes.
Yes, I do.
Then let's take him.
Are you sure?
(doorbell ringing)
Hi.
Hey.
Can we come in?
Sure.
What's up?
Where's Troop?
He's upstairs playing
with Chewbacca.
We want to take him.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
When the time comes.
We're still hoping it won't.
I don't know what to say.
You don't have
to say anything.
I couldn't have even
hoped for this.
Oh, Sam, I'm so
proud of you.
Oh, we're both crazy about him.
That's great, but that's not
why I'm proud of you.
Okay, why are
you proud of me?
Because you married well.
I want to have a party.
A big one.
A party?
Might be my last chance.
Hey, Trooper, can I come in?
Uh-huh.
Did you have fun
with Rosemary today?
Mm-hmm.
Want to snuggle?
Remember how we always
said we'd hope
for the best when
I got sick?
Yeah.
Well, sometimes the best
doesn't happen.
And then, we have
to make other plans.
We have to make the best
of things as they are.
So, it looks like the best
isn't going to happen.
And if I'm not going
to be around...
...if I'm not
going to be around,
we're going to have to find
a place for you, Troop.
I don't want to.
I know, baby.
But we got to make
the best of things, don't we?
Maybe... maybe
my dad will come back.
Oh, Troop.
He, he could.
It's been a
very long time.
But he still could, Mom.
But in the meantime,
we have to find a place for you
where you'll be safe and happy.
Where people love you.
And they'll take
care of you.
You know, Sam and Lydia?
They love you very much.
Do you know that?
I know it.
Do you know how I know it?
'Cause they said that if
anything happened to me,
if I didn't get
better,
that they'd love to
have you live with them.
How would you feel
about that?
I don't want to, Mom.
I know, baby.
But as long as
we're talking about
making the best of things...
can you think of a place
you'd rather be?
Do you like them, Troop?
I like them very much.
In fact, I can't think of
anyone I'd rather you be with.
Can you?
Can we still hope?
Hope what?
That you'll get better.
Come here.
Yeah, we can still hope.
I'm still going
to hope then.
Me, too.
(indistinct conversations)
Have you been
taken care of?
Did you get something?
Oh, you did get something.
Excellent.
Who else?
Who else needs their drinks?
DEE DEE:
I'm going to sit down.
Yeah, go sit down.
Go on.
I'll, I'll fix the table.
I'll keep it going.
Go on.
Ladies and gentlemen,
for one night only,
we present the return
of...Dee Dee and the Deadbeats.
(cheering)
Dee Dee, would you do us
the great honor
of leading us
through our theme song?
Oh, Sam.
ROSEMARY:
Come on.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
(crowd shouting encouragement)
I want to watch you guys. Go.
What's the name
of the song?
"You've Got a Friend."
Oh, I know that one...
Well, get up here.
Go get them.
Yay, for me.
And we do have a special guest
on the drums tonight...
Mr. Trooper Michaud!
Yay, Trooper!
What key do you guys play in?
What key do you
sing it in?
Oh, it doesn't matter.
That sounds fine.
♪ When you're down
and troubled ♪
♪ And you need a helping hand ♪
♪ And nothing, nothing,
nothing is going right ♪
Come on, girls.
♪ Close your eyes
and think of me ♪
♪ And soon I will be there ♪
♪ To brighten up even
the darkest night ♪
♪ You just call out my name ♪
♪ And you know wherever I am ♪
♪ I'll come running
to see you again ♪
♪ To see you again ♪
♪ Winter, spring,
summer or fall ♪
♪ All you have to do is call ♪
♪ And I'll be there ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ You've got a friend ♪
♪ Winter, spring,
summer or fall ♪
♪ All you have to do is call ♪
♪ And I'll be there ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ You've got a friend. ♪
Trooper!
(applause)
Whoa!
What is that?
A little welcome home present.
It's huge!
Well, open it!
Open it, Dee Dee!
Come on.
Okay,
okay.
You got it?
Give her help.
Yeah, you got it,
you got it.
Rip that sucker open!
There.
There you go.
All right.
(gasps)
Hey...
Look at that.
My bike!
(excited murmuring)
Where did you find it?
Well, I thought Jimmy
Farrington had it
but he'd sold it to
Marty and Neil Halfon.
Neil thought
Marty had it.
Marty thought
Neil had it, but they
both forgot that they gave
it to their little sister,
and it was in
her basement,
collecting cobwebs.
But it looks brand new.
That's just a new seat
and some fresh paint.
Troop, this is the bike I rode
when I was your age.
It's... it's cool.
Well, sort of.
(laughing)
Excuse me,
it's the coolest bike ever.
I'm going to take it on a ride.
Move it.
Let me help you.
Okay, I got it,
I got it.
All right now.
Don't go crazy all at once,
you know.
Shut up, you guys.
We'll find a place
over here.
I put it into first gear,
so, you know...
Okay, yeah, Ross.
I've ridden a bike before.
Okay, well, this is
just like that.
All right.
Thank you.
Okay.
Whoa! Whoa!
Go, Dee Dee.
Sam, maybe
she shouldn't.
Well, you should
know her by now.
(cheering)
Whoo!
(cheering continues)
(squealing)
Hey, Rick.
Hey.
How's the
clean up coming?
Ah, it's coming.
I want to start
the new construction.
You mean now?
Right away.
Soon as you're finished
with the clean up.
I don't know if it
makes sense, Sam.
I mean, we'll be caught
right in the middle of winter.
Ah, let's take a chance.
We might have
decent weather.
What if we don't?
Then we'll shut it
down till spring.
But then we'll be left
with all this material
just hanging around
all winter.
It's not going
to hurt it, is it?
Well, I...
I suppose not.
What's the hurry?
We're going to fill
that house up with kids.
Thanks, Rick.
Is Lyddie pregnant?
No. Not yet.
It takes nine months, you know.
Not always.
Amber's going to take
Chewbacca's brother.
Oh, great, Amber.
I'm glad.
Are you going to take him today?
Uh-huh.
Trooper, go bring him in.
He'll need a shot.
Okay.
Are you going to do it now?
Yep.
Right now.
I'll come back.
Oh, it'll just
take a minute.
I hate shots.
I'll... I'll come back tomorrow.
Trooper, put him up here
on the table.
Here.
Where's Amber?
She didn't
want to watch.
Yeah, she's not
used to this stuff.
This'll just pinch a little,
okay, puppy?
Ouch.
There we go.
You okay? Hmm?
You okay?
He's fine.
Here he is.
There we are.
What do you think?
Getting big.
Come on,
come on.
You want to feed him?
Sure.
Well, grab a hold
of that bucket there.
Here we go.
Come on around here.
Hey.
Here we go.
Yeah, I'm going to have
to have somebody
come out and ride him
this spring,
so he don't get too frisky.
Don't suppose you know anyone
who'd be willing to do that?
I'd ride him
if I knew how.
You would?
Yeah.
If I knew how.
Well, now.
Here you go.
I never would have thought
that he would have done that.
Would you, Sam?
Never even
crossed my mind.
He's awful busy,
though.
What with being an assistant
veterinarian and all.
Oh, yeah, he probably
doesn't even have time.
Not much.
Well, I'd have time,
it's just...
I don't really know how.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I forgot that.
Too bad.
Well, of course
there's always Sophie.
Yeah, lots of folks
learned to ride on Sophie.
Sophie's very gentle.
Very gentle.
Sort of like sitting
in an easy chair.
Well...
I'll keep looking.
Hey, say, you know,
I just got an idea.
Now if you wanted
to come and learn
on Sophie...
Yeah, I would.
Well, how about that,
I think we got a deal.
Well, son of a gun, I wish
I'd thought of that before.
Well, you come on back
any time and we'll
get started.
Okay.
Ain't that something?
Never even thought
about old Trooper.
♪ The one thing
I am certain of ♪
♪ Is time will change
each one of us ♪
♪ Before this
you're out on your own ♪
♪ So open your voice
and be strong ♪
♪ You are not alone ♪
♪ You are what you believe,
you are not alone ♪
♪ You're part of everything ♪
♪ When life gets you down,
set your soul at ease ♪
♪ You are not alone,
you're part of everything ♪
♪ Part of everything ♪
♪You're part of everything ♪
♪ The cheapest secret
is the truth ♪
♪ Until you finally
set it loose ♪
♪ Such an unbelievable game ♪
♪ Well, if you got something
to say, then let it out ♪
♪ Give us something
to talk about ♪
♪ So that you're not
on your own ♪
♪ So open your voice
and be strong ♪
♪ When life gets you down,
set your soul at ease ♪
♪ You are not alone ♪
♪ You're part of everything ♪
♪ You are not alone,
you are what you believe ♪
you're part of everything ♪
♪ When life gets you down,
set your soul at ease ♪
♪ You are not alone,
you're part of... ♪
♪ You're part of everything ♪
♪ You're part of... ♪
♪ You're part of everything. ♪
(song fades)
Okay, ready?
All right.
One, two....
Are you okay?
Yeah.
All in?
Uh-huh.
Everyone in?
Where are we going?
You'll see.
I bet it's
the Labor Day picnic.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
(whispering weakly):
What's the big surprise, Sam?
It wouldn't be a surprise
if I told you,
now, would it?
(electric saw whirring,
hammers pounding)
How about that?
(gasps softly)
Sam, I didn't think
that we could...
We took a chance.
We've been working overtime.
I talked the guys into
coming in over the holidays.
Thanks, Rick.
Okay.
All right, you,
walk the plank.
(laughs):
Rick.
Thank you so much.
The guys wanted to help--
they're good guys.
Here we have
the living room...
(laughing)
kitchen...
bedrooms...
family room.
I wanted you to see it.
(whispering):
Thank you, Sam.
Well, in case
it burns down again.
RICK:
We need 16 more
four-by-eight sheets
to complete the outside
sheathings, so I'll call...
Will this be my room?
It'll be all yours.
Do you want to put
a bunk bed in here?
Nah.
A single?
Whatever you want.
I bet you'll be able
to have a really nice
view of some stars.
Yeah.
It's a pretty nice view.
Hey.
Hey, Chewie.
Where at?
Right there.
Why don't I see about
fixing us some supper.
SAM:
That'd be great.
Aren't we gonna go
to the town picnic?
I don't feel
up to it.
Troop, I'm sorry.
Maybe you and I
can stop by later.
That's a good idea.
Go into the kitchen
and help Lydia.
There's some cold
spaghetti in the fridge.
Okay.
Okay, go help her.
(groans)
(exhales)
How much of this
are you taking?
It's never enough.
You in a lot of pain?
I can manage.
Thank you for today, Sam.
I owe you so much.
Oh, I don't know about that.
I'd say we're pretty even.
And I don't just mean
when we were kids.
I mean now, as well.
You keep showing me
how to live my life.
You're doing just
fine without me.
It's different without you.
You know...
I never told you this.
But that night
before you left,
we were sitting
out on your porch...
I know.
(laughs)
What?
You were gonna give
me your class ring.
(both laugh)
How did you know that?
I just knew.
(laughs weakly)
I didn't want to hurt you.
You mean so much to me.
I love you, Sam.
You and Lydia both.
Now, listen.
On that bookshelf, up...
underneath the... basket,
there's a letter--
will you get it for me?
Come here.
I want you to give
this to Trooper when
you think he's ready.
I wrote him a letter
about his dad.
I always thought he should have
a dad he could believe in.
He has one now.
(quiet, indistinct chatter)
My gosh.
What's that?
Dee Dee, Sam, you've got
to come check this out.
(indistinct chatter continues)
ROSS:
There she is!
(all cheering, laughter)
Hey!
ROSS:
We, uh,
we figured you couldn't make
the picnic, uh, Dee Dee,
so, uh, we decided
to bring the picnic to you.
OTHERS:
♪You just call out my name ♪
This is so cool.
♪ And you know ♪
♪ Wherever I am ♪
♪ I'll come running ♪
♪ To see you again... ♪
(insects chirping)
(birds call and squawk
in distance)
(organ music playing)
(indistinct chatter)
PASTOR:
And so, we turn to the Scripture
passages just read
and we look to the memory
of Dee Dee Michaud's life
for consolation in our sorrow
and for inspiration
in our lives.
And now, Dee Dee's son, Trooper,
has requested a moment.
When...
When my mom said
we were gonna move here...
I didn't really want to...
'cause...
'cause I didn't really know
anybody then.
She said...
she said that
this town was special,
and she told me
lots of stories about it.
But... she said every place
we lived was special.
So I didn't really believe her.
But I liked the stories anyways.
Now...
Now I see what she meant.
Wherever I go...
it reminds me of her.
It's like...
It's like she's still here.
(exhales)
I'm glad we came.
I'm glad.
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ How sweet the sound ♪
♪ That saved a wretch ♪
♪ Like me ♪
(others joining in):
♪ I once was lost ♪
♪ But now ♪
♪ Am found ♪
♪ Was blind ♪
♪ But now ♪
♪ I see ♪
♪ 'Twas grace ♪
♪ That taught ♪
♪ My heart to fear ♪
♪ And grace my fears relieved ♪
♪ Relieved ♪
♪ How precious did ♪
♪ That grace appear ♪
♪ The hour I first ♪
♪ Believed ♪
♪ Through many dangers ♪
(birds call and squawk)
♪Toils and snares ♪
♪ I have already come ♪
♪ 'Tis grace hath bro't me ♪
♪ Safe thus far ♪
♪ And grace ♪
♪ Will lead me home... ♪