(ominous music)
- What you mean there wasn't
an earthquake last night?
Ground was shaking like
my old lady's cellulite.
- Man, I'm not saying
the Earth didn't shake,
I'm just saying there's nothing
humanalogical about it.
- Well, it was on TV, genius.
4.5 they said.
- Hey, our TV says
a lot of things.
- This another one of
your conspiracy theories?
- Can you keep a secret?
- Maybe.
- It was aliens.
- Aliens?
- Yeah, aliens you heard me.
They're practicing death
rays on us all the time,
earthquakes,
hurricanes, tsunamis.
Now tell me this,
if the Earth is made
out of 71 percent water,
how come they are always hitting
densely populated areas, hmm?
Now what--
- You dumber than a box
of hammers, you know that?
Well, you so dumb, you,
you dumber than Roux over there,
and that's saying something.
(both laughing)
- That one Roux
is pretty stupid.
- Hey, you fellas feel
that earthquake last night?
- Man, that wasn't
no earthquake,
and I don't care
what you or him say.
(Roux groaning)
- You okay there, big fella?
(Roux groans)
- Something bit me last
night, something fierce.
- Last night, huh?
Sure it wasn't a woman?
- Couldn't have been a woman,
I was in bed at the time.
(both laughing)
- What are you two slack
offs laughing about?
- Nothing boss.
- Good,
'cause I want those eggs
loaded and in town tout sweet.
Roux, front and center.
- Yeah, boss.
- Something getting
in the henhouse.
Found two of them
dead this morning.
- You think it's a fox?
- Well, that's what
you're gonna find out.
Take the shotgun
head on over there.
- You want me to kill it?
- That's the general idea.
Just be careful don't
point that at anything
walking on two legs, you hear?
- Yeah, yeah boss.
You, you can count on me.
- Whoa!
- Whoops.
(Roux laughs)
(suspenseful music)
- [Worker] Get on out of here!
(ominous music)
- Eww!
Oh!
(Roux groaning)
(Roux groaning loudly)
(spider hissing)
(suspenseful music)
(Roux groaning)
Argh!
(spider screaming)
(upbeat country rock music)
* Well all the girls
I've known before *
- Paul!
* Have left me hungry
* Left me poor
- Aren't you
forgetting something?
- Hey, I didn't
wanna wake you up.
You know, I'm late for work
and uh, you looked like
an angel laying there.
- Call me.
* So won't you marry
me a whiskey bottle *
* Give me a kiss and let me
take a sip of your love *
* Suzie left me
with a broken nose *
* And when Amy left she
took all my clothes *
* Jenny turned out to be a man
* And Katie took
off with my van *
* Another one just
walked out the door *
* I ain't got no damn luck
baby that's for sure *
* So won't you marry
me a whiskey bottle *
* Give me a kiss and let me
take a sip of your love *
* So won't you marry
me a whiskey bottle *
* Give me a kiss and let me
take a sip of your love *
* So won't you marry
me a whiskey bottle *
* Give me a kiss and let me
take a sip of your love *
* So won't you marry
me a whiskey bottle *
* Give me a kiss and let me
take a sip of your love *
(birds squawking)
(distant people chattering)
- [Woman] Nice set!
- Seriously, two hours late.
That's a new low, even for you.
- Oh, sorry Pops, you're right.
Things just got a little
out of hand last night.
- Well, I hope you had fun.
It just cost us the first big
money charter of the season.
It's coming out of your pay.
- What, they canceled?
- Yeah well that's what
tourists do when they show up
for a grand tour
the Louisiana swamp
and their transportation
is missing!
- Missing?
What's he talking about?
- You don't remember anything
from last night, do you?
- Uh, it's all a little hazy.
- Dammit, son.
You didn't even
know who she was?
- Good news, I
just talked to Moe
and our boat is caught on a bank
about a mile below Gators Way.
He saw her on his
way in this morning.
- Please, please tell me that
she's still in one piece.
- As far as he could tell.
- See, good news!
Glass half-full, Pops.
- Yeah.
- Uh, y'all have any Bayer?
- Don't you think it's
a little early, Paul?
- Ugh...
Bayer, you know
like the Tylenol?
You know, I was asking
if you had any Bayer.
- Come here, come on, I
wanna show you something.
- Pops, Pops.
- Get, get, come on.
I wanna show you
something over here.
You see this?
- Who's that handsome devil?
- That's me, when I
was your sister's age,
defusing mines in
the Gulf of Tonkin,
risking my ass every day.
What the hell have
you ever risked, huh?
Except for STDs and
a swollen liver.
- I put my time in Pops.
- Yeah, yeah,
the least amount that
you can get away with.
That boat was your
responsibility, Paul.
It was your only responsibility.
From now on Pepper is gonna
handle the boat tours.
- What?
- You're demoted to
driving the trolley bus.
- Pops you said I'm the
face of Lacrosse Adventures.
- Yeah and if you ever
wanna be the head,
you'll shut up and
do like I tell you,
or you're gonna be shucking
oysters the rest of your life.
- You won't regret this, Daddy.
I'm gonna restore some
pride to the family name.
(Paul mumbling)
- Let's go, honey.
You got a bus tour
leaving in an hour.
Don't screw this up
or you're outta here.
There's no more second chances.
(melancholy music)
(girls chattering)
- I hear it's really
massive, but...
(girls giggling)
- Whoopsies!
- Take a picture,
it'll last longer.
- I just did, heh heh heh.
- That's disgusting.
- [Charlie] Alright girls,
come on, get on the bus.
- We gotta get going Charlie.
I scheduled this tour for noon.
- I know, I know, I know,
I gotta wake up Barb.
Hey, Tam, Tam, Tam, do you
know where my hard-working
punctual assistant
is by any chance?
- She said she wasn't
feeling well, Coach.
I think she's still
up in her room.
- Ha ha ha, I told her to
take it easy on the champagne,
I swear I did.
Hi, guys.
- Hurry up, Dad.
- Come on.
- I'm hurrying.
(knocking at door)
Barb.
Come on, wake up, we
got a long drive today.
You decent?
Barb?
(Barb groans)
(dramatic music)
Oh, my god!
- Help me.
- What happened to you?
- Whoa let's see New Orleans.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah,
you know what?
That might be a
bit of a problem.
- Now what?
- Barb can't go.
It's like she had
herpes on her face.
- [Katelynn] I could
care less about her.
I want you to come
with us on the tour.
Don't come with us, and there's
gonna be a huge problem,
between all of us.
- Well, you know what?
It's not my fault that
she got bitten, okay?
- Bit, by what?
- I don't know.
She wasn't making
a lot of sense.
She had these like weird
scary cysts over face.
- Maybe it's the Black
Death, that causes cysts.
- Oh crap, really?
- Yes, it does,
but I don't think
they have a plague
from the Middle
Ages in New Orleans.
- Could be leprosy.
- It's not leprosy, it's
not the Black Plague.
- It doesn't matter,
I called an ambulance,
so they'll take
care of it, right?
It'll be fine, it'll
be fine, and you guys,
you guys are late for
the tour, alright?
So, you guys gotta get there.
- What, you're really
not gonna come?
- Barb's gonna be
out of commission
for a little while, okay?
Somebody's got to
drive these Amazon's
back to Houston, right?
- Dad, I'm not
sleeping in there.
It's probably
infested with bedbugs,
- Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah you're right.
You guys should get a hotel.
- Some vacation, huh?
- It'll be fun.
I'll make it up,
I'll make it up.
Have fun guys.
* Walking through these hills
* Walking through these shores
(knocking at bus door)
(man groaning)
(lighthearted music)
(ears ringing)
- Hey yo, what's up homie?
You our driver, yo?
- Yeah, looks that way.
- You look like you
been through hell.
Well anyway, I'm Glen,
this is my wife Tina.
- Hello.
- Enchante, madam.
- Ooh, honey did you hear
that, he speaks French.
- Yeah, whatever.
- He must be Cajun.
- Anyway, come on, come on.
- Okay, thank you.
- Ha ha ha, that's what
I'm talking about, baby.
I told you, I'm
legend Cajun in life.
- You're special.
- You enjoying yourself?
- This is so exciting!
(both chatting quietly)
- I see we're short a few.
I guess black bus
couldn't make it, so.
You must be Mr.
Gram-po-what-ska, or
something another.
Can I just call you Gramps?
- If you want my
cane up your keister.
- Alright.
- Sorry, we're late,
Blackwells party of three.
We're short one, my
husband couldn't make it.
- Uh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Ah, we're ready to
roll, excellent.
(clears throat)
Oh...
My name is Paul.
I'm gonna be your
tour guide today.
If you have any
questions, please,
a dollar in the tip
jar and ask away.
- Let's get this show on the
road, how's that for a tip?
- Buckle up your seat belts.
- [Justin] Hey, we don't
have any seat belts.
(lighthearted music)
- Canal Street was in
fact named after a canal
that was meant to be
built and never was.
It was once the widest
street in the world,
and to your right,
Bourbon Street.
Most people don't realize
that Bourbon Street
was actually named after
the French royal family,
not the whiskey,
although there's one
last place in the country
you can still drink
on the street.
- Hey, you know that's right.
- Ooh, I'll bet the booze
is really good here.
Hey driver, can we hop off
and get some cocktails?
- Sure if you wanna
tuck and roll.
'Cause this tram don't
stop for nothing.
(funky music)
- What is with you
and those peas?
- It's protein.
It puts hair on your
back, you should try it.
- I can see that.
- Justin, eat them,
open your mouth, Justin.
- Annabelle, cut it out!
- Open your mouth!
- Ugh, it's like I
swallowed the Sun!
- Please?
Can I ask a question?
Last night there
was an earthquake.
I mean, that's not common
in these parts is it?
- [Paul] It it depends on
how much bourbon you've had.
- We felt it too.
I almost peed in my pants,
but Glen thought it was funny.
- It says here that New
Orleans is below sea level
and sinking all the time.
Maybe that's what we
felt, the city sinking.
- You're thinking of Venice.
- I am not, it
says so right here.
- Hey, a voodoo shop,
can we stop please?
- Young lady like I said before,
this tram don't--
- Stop!
(ominous music)
- I need y'all to stay put.
- What is that?
- It smell like natural gas.
- I'm lactose-intolerant.
- There's a huge shale
layer under Louisiana.
Maybe this is some
sort of biogassing.
- Hey, look, look at
that, out of my way!
- That's disgusting.
- It's not just
disgusting, it's nature.
- Oh, I didn't know
they came that big.
- Let me see that.
Huh.
It doesn't have any eyes.
It's blind.
- Oh, poor little guy.
- Well, it probably lives
underground in the dark.
It doesn't need them.
- Somebody should get
him a little white cane.
- Are you some
kind of scientist?
- I teach eighth grade biology.
- I knew it.
- Let me see that thing.
- Ew, gross!
(spider hisses)
- Feisty little fella isn't he?
- Hey, I'm gonna need
y'all back on the bus.
- Uh, guys.
(all whimpering)
- Something on my face?
(all shrieking)
Ooh, what is that?
- This tour officially sucks!
Gimme that!
- What are you doing?
- [Justin] This thing
is obviously dangerous.
- [Annabelle] I was
gonna keep that.
- You always do this.
- Now, out!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Hey, I got him, I got him,
I got him, I got him.
(spider thumps)
(Paul breathing heavily)
I have to work on my putt.
- What was that?
- Did you see how big it was?
- Gramps, get on the
bus, get on the bus!
(banging on metal roof)
(spiders squealing)
- Back on the bus!
Come on, get on
the bus, come on!
- [Glen] You drive us now!
- Please tell me
that was a coconut!
- Something is on the roof.
- Shut the windows,
shut the windows.
- [Paul] Everybody
grab your seats!
(tires squealing)
(dramatic music)
(spiders thunking)
(electricity crackling)
(spider hissing)
(suspenseful music)
- What are we stopping for?
- Gotta get gas.
- Are you sure this
is a good idea?
Those things are
right behind us.
- [Glen] Yeah, but I
think we lost them.
- Yeah, maybe they found
someone else to chew on.
- Spiders don't eat people.
I don't care how big
or how blind they are.
- On Okinawa I saw a
tarantula size of a grapefruit
suck a man's eyeball
right out of his head.
Of course, he was
dead at the time.
- Come on, let's go.
- Where you going?
- See if they have
some bug repellent or,
or bear traps or something.
- Good call.
- Hey, wait up.
- Guys, stay where
I can see you.
(suspenseful music)
- What can I do you for?
- Hey, do you have
any Raid or bug spray?
- You got a couple
critters to whack, huh?
- Yeah, you got any
insect repellent or not?
- If I do, it'd
be on aisle seven.
- Aisle seven.
- Seven.
- How is 9-1-1 busy?
- Did you see those things?
This is definitely
a brand new species.
- Yeah, maybe they'll
name it after you.
- You don't get it, I
have a master's in zoology
and I have never
even heard of this.
- You must be a big hit
with the eighth graders.
- This is not funny.
- Depends on your
sense of humor.
(Katelynn sighs)
- Life must be
easy for you, huh?
You flash that dopey smile
and things go your way.
This is different.
- Whatever this is,
it'll be wrapped up in
time for the 6:00 news.
- Don't you care that
people are in danger?
- Yeah, I care, but
I'm a tour bus driver.
I'm not the Green Power Ranger.
- Oh, watch it!
- Watch this!
(walk sign beeping)
(Katelynn whimpers)
- Come on!
(mellow jazz music)
- That's it.
- This expired two years ago.
- Beggars can't be choosers.
- Guys, they're coming!
- Spiders!
- They're coming,
they're coming!
- Jumbo's spiders,
some as big as dwarves.
- Jumbo dwarves?
- Call the police,
call the exterminator.
- Exterminator?
- Am I speaking Chinese?
- What part of jumbo spiders
don't you understand?
- Call somebody, anybody.
- What did I miss?
- He's calling
the exterminator.
- Man, I don't feel so good.
(bubble pops)
(women shrieking)
(all whimpering)
- Oh, God.
(spider chattering)
(suspenseful music)
(all groaning)
(eggs crunching)
(spiders chattering)
- [Paul] Oh!
- Argh!
- Come on, Paul!
You disgust, argh!
(dramatic music)
(spiders chattering)
- This what you want, playboy?
Huh?
(Justin shrieking)
(both whimpering)
(Anabelle screaming)
(dramatic music)
(wine gurgling)
(fire roaring)
(spiders screaming)
(cans rattling)
- You think it's dead?
- I don't know,
check it and see.
Looks pretty dead to me.
- Glen!
- Go, go, go, go!
- Oh, there's a giant
spider right there!
(all whimpering)
- What, what do we do now?
(suspenseful music)
- What, what did I do?
- You're in control,
what do we do now?
- Uh, just a second.
- What, who are you calling?
- My boss.
- Your boss?
- No, babe.
(phone rings)
- Yeah.
- Pops.
This is Paul, listen
there's a problem.
- I don't wanna hear
any problems, Paul.
- Listen to me.
- You listen to me.
I told you what would happen
if you screwed this up.
You're 30 years old,
start acting like it.
- Pops.
(phone beeps)
(suspenseful music)
Pops.
- Everything's gonna be okay.
He hung up on me.
- Be cool.
- Hey, listen to this.
This says here that
the shale layer
goes all the way to Houston.
- No way.
- What does that mean?
Is it happening back home too?
- Charlie.
(swamp life chattering)
(hip hop music)
(girls chattering)
- Whoo!
- Woah, come on!
- Go girl, dancer.
- Dig it.
* It drives me crazy
* I got it baby
* Girl
- [Charlie] Hey,
this is Charlie,
leave me a message,
and I'll hit you back.
- Dammit, Charlie!
(glass shatters)
(Katelynn screams)
- Why is there another spider?
There's another spider.
- Another spider?
- Okay, listen, get to the bus.
Get them out of here, okay.
I'll hold this one
off, y'all go, go!
- But, baby!
- Listen, babe, go.
I'll be there in a minute, okay?
Just go!
(spider hissing)
(can thunks)
(dramatic music)
- Y'all hold up!
Come on, sir, come on.
- I'm coming, I'm coming,
I'm coming.
- You can do it.
- Huh, wait, oh dear!
(spider hisses)
(muffled groaning)
- Paul, come on, leave
him, he's dead already.
(tires squealing)
- Give it some gas, honey.
(motor revving)
Alright, we got it.
Alright, okay,
keep this together.
- Throw me the rope.
(Petra gasps)
Dad!
- What?
- Look.
- Is that?
- Well, that's Armand alright.
Damn, you see that
scar right there?
Propeller did that
to him back in '02.
What the hell happened to him?
- What are those things?
- Beats me.
You know, Armand
was getting old,
but he was still the toughest
son of a gun in a swamp.
- Hope Mama is okay.
- Ain't nothing alive
that could take on
one Louisiana Gator
let alone two.
The old girl is
probably in mourning.
We'll report it when
we get back to town.
Come on.
- Alright.
(motor rumbling)
(dramatic music)
(sirens wailing)
- They're blind.
They must be using some
sort of echolocation
to find their prey.
- Like bats, like bats.
- You alright?
- Yeah.
- Aw, what's this?
(suspenseful music)
- What are you stopping for?
What the hell are you doing?
Make a left.
- Dude left is gonna take
us back into the Quarter.
Those roads are made for
horse carriage, not trolleys.
- We appreciate the
trivia and everything,
but enough is enough!
- Yeah!
- Right, okay this tour
is officially over.
You're no longer the captain.
Give me the keys,
I'm going back.
- Dude, you ain't the tour
guide of nothing, chill out!
- Don't tell him to chill out!
At least he's trying
to get us outta here.
- We're on the same side.
- Forget that.
You screwed up and
you're messed up.
Whoever want me to drive
this bus, raise your hand.
- See?
Hey, come here!
- Dude, dude, we
can talk about this.
- Gimme the keys!
- Calm down.
- Nope!
Nobody picks me, put me down!
Nobody picks me up, man!
- Gimme the--
(ominous rumbling)
(suspenseful music)
(woman screams)
- What was that?
- I don't know, I think
another earthquake.
(explosion echoes)
(dramatic music)
- [Paul] Get outta there!
- Gimme the keys!
- Get off me, man!
Sit down!
Sit in!
- Just get us outta here!
- Mom?
- Her inhaler has run out.
(engine rattling)
- I can't find the spare.
- She always keeps
it in her purse.
- I know, but I can't
find it, Justin.
- No, she's not
looking too good.
- No kidding, we gotta
get her to a drugstore.
- A drugstore, now?
- There's one right across
the street from the shop.
- How far?
- Uh, 10 minutes tops.
- It doesn't matter,
anywhere but here, go go go!
- Yes.
(engine roars)
Come on!
(tires squealing)
- Oh my God, Dad.
The French Quarter.
- [Dad] Your brother
better not have anything
to do with this.
- [Paul] Hey, this is
Paul, I'm not in right now,
probably because I'm out
doing something awesome.
- Stay with the
boat, don't move.
- Where are you going?
- I'm gonna find your brother,
and when I do I'm
gonna kill him.
(suspenseful music)
(spiders hissing)
(guns firing)
- I don't wanna hear it.
- [Glen] Why would you
even stop right here.
- You said go this way.
- You the one, you,
this is your city.
- [Paul] How is supposed
to go through the town,
make any difference if you're
driving or if I'm driving.
We'd still run into cops.
- [Glen] This is crazy,
they're shooting at everything.
(phone ringing)
This is why you
have a dollar tip.
- Hey, I earned that dollar.
(girls screaming)
- Yeah, girl!
- Go get it, girls!
(electronic dance music)
(girls moaning in disapproval)
- Hey, calm down,
I got a call.
- What, why are we
not getting--
- Hey!
How's my little princess?
You guys enjoying your tour?
- Dad, there's
spiders everywhere.
- You guys at the zoo?
- No I'm not at the zoo.
I'm in front of the drugstore.
- Drugstore?
(gun firing)
Hey wait a minute, is
that gunfire I hear?
- Dad, I need you
to listen to me.
Now, there's giant spiders
and they're coming
out of the ground.
I think that's what got Barb.
- I told you if I caught
you huffing that crap
one more time, I would--
- Dad, they're everywhere!
- Grounded for life,
I'm not even joking.
- Dad, I'm not high!
Mom's having an asthma attack,
and I can't find a refill.
- Calm down, okay, it'll
all be taken care of...
What the hell is that?
(girls chattering)
Holy crap, hold on!
(tires squealing)
I'm very nice!
(bus crunches)
- Dad, Dad?
- Are you insane,
Mr. College Boy,
you don't have to show me,
you got to show me
your master's degree.
You don't have a master's.
- I'll show you my master's.
(steam hissing)
(Charlie panting)
- What are you thinking,
you look divine!
I like that.
- Is everybody okay?
(siren wailing)
(Katelynn gasping)
- I'm sure there's
something we could do.
I know mouth to mouth.
- Don't even think about it.
- That won't work, asthma
constricts the airways.
Oxygen can't get into the lungs.
- [Paul] Hey, wait
a minute, heliox?
- What?
- Heliox.
It's the helium oxygen
mix that divers use.
- And?
- At the bottom of the ocean,
you can't breathe normal air,
'cause it's too much
pressure, so they use heliox,
'cause it takes less energy
to ventilate the lungs.
I think it's the same
principle as an inhaler.
- Can you get us some?
- Yeah, he's got two tanks on
his boat with his dive suit.
- Great, where's the boat?
- Five miles up river.
- What?
- You gotta be
kidding me, right?
(horn honking)
- Pops?
Pops, move!
- This place is crawling
with giant spiders.
Please tell me this
isn't your fault.
- What?
- Just follow me.
- Okay, but keep an eye out,
'cause this place is
crawling with spiders.
- Come on!
(suspenseful music)
- One, two, three, push, push!
(engine rumbling)
Come on, put some nuts into it!
- Coach, it's no good,
it's really stuck!
- Tammy, you take the wheel.
You know what, maybe we
need to shift the weight
to the back of the
bus, so get back there.
Alright, go, go.
You're supposed to push
the gas when I say go.
- What?
(suspenseful music)
- Hey, Petra, what's up, girl?
Come out on the water!
- Hi.
(distant hip hop music)
(ominous music)
- [Dad] Make yourself useful
and get some water
for these folks.
- Can you save the
attitude, please?
- My wife and want
a full refund.
This is by far the worst
vacation we've ever had.
- Yeah, your brochure didn't
say anything about spiders.
- Well my ma'am, it does
actually say in the fine print
that we're not responsible
for local wildlife.
See, it's right there.
- Forget what the
brochure said, okay?
And you're not gonna
talk to my wife that way.
Let me tell you something,
playboy, I'm from the hood.
I've done and seen things
you have nightmares about.
You understand?
- Baby stop it.
Just let it go.
- No, no they need
to hear this, baby.
- Let it go.
- This is ridiculous!
We didn't sign up for this.
- Babe!
- Spiders everywhere,
this is crazy.
Let me tell you something.
Forget what the old man
said about Iwo Jima.
That was a cakewalk
compared to this.
I'm not gonna let
some bust ass spider
ruin our vacation, okay?
So strap on the cup and buck up.
If you wanna survive this thing
we have to stick together.
(spider chattering)
(Glen screaming)
- Everybody back to the boat!
(all screaming)
- Please.
- You gotta let him go,
come on.
- Everybody back to the boat!
- To the boat, go!
(gun firing)
(dramatic music)
- Go!
(spider chattering)
- Petra, you got them keys?
- Yep!
(gun firing)
(engine rumbling)
- Alright, come on girls,
you're up, hurry up.
Come on, come on!
- What is it?
- I don't know.
- What the hell is it?
(spider hissing)
- Oh, God.
- Oh, my God!
(all screaming)
- Oh, my God, run, hurry, go!
- Guys!
(spider chattering)
- Hit him, Coach!
Seriously?
(Coach whimpering)
(bat thuds)
(spider screams)
(spider explodes)
(Coach laughs)
- [Coach] Now, that is why
you were my number
one pinch hitter!
Whoo!
(melancholy music)
- Breathe deep.
- Hey, what are you doing?
Nobody touches
that stuff but me.
- She's having an
asthma attack, Pops.
I figured these heliox
would help, it's your call.
- [Justin] Keep breathing, Mom.
- Better?
- Thank you.
I'm gonna be okay.
- Hey, good job, brother.
- It's all part of
the tour package.
- So, where do you
think the spider is now?
(suspenseful music)
(girls sobbing)
- Coach.
(Coach screams)
- Crap.
- Those things breathe fire.
- Well, hey, as long as we
stay in here we'll be okay.
(girl sobbing)
Come on, come on, you
guys are gonna be fine,
as long as you
stay calm and hey,
stay away from those
windows, we'll be fine.
Okay, we'll be alright.
(ominous music)
(spider chattering)
(suspenseful music)
(boat rumbling)
- Is it abandoned?
Dad, is it abandoned?
- Unfortunately not.
- They can't see us, can they?
- They can hear us.
Everybody be quiet.
- [Tina] What are
you stopping for?
- Tina, calm down.
- No, no.
No, he knows we're here.
(Tina whimpering)
No, no.
(spider chattering)
(Tina spazzing)
- We're gonna get outta here.
- No, no we're not.
They're gonna get us
just like they got Glen!
They're gonna get us,
they're gonna get us!
(Tina sobbing)
No, no, no!
(Tina screaming)
No, no, no, they're gonna get
us just like they ate Glen!
- [Petra] What are you doing?
- No, no, no!
- What are you,
get, get, get off!
(engine roars)
- No!
- Hold on, Petra.
- Alright, beat it.
- I'm not gonna let you go!
(Tina screaming)
- I'm not gonna let
you go, you hear me?
Look at me, I'm not
gonna let you go!
(Petra screaming)
I'm not gonna let you go.
- They can do that too?
- Get back here, now!
- No, no, please!
- I'm not gonna let you go.
Look at me!
Come on, come on, I've got you.
Come on.
(Petra shrieking)
(gun firing)
- [Tina] No, no!
- Come on!
(spiders hissing)
- Let go.
- Hold on.
Get!
(Petra sighs)
(boat rumbling)
(Tina groaning)
(boat thuds)
(Tina screams)
Abandon ship!
- Let's go, let's go, let's go!
(suspenseful music)
- Come on, right over here.
- Tina, are you alive?
- I'm okay.
(Tina shrieks)
- Take cover!
(muffled Tina groaning)
(Tina screaming)
- Don't move.
Don't even breathe.
- Here.
Take care of the others,
I'll distract them.
- What me?
- Look, you can do it.
I have faith in you, son.
- No, Pops.
- It's our only hope!
(spiders growling)
(suspenseful music)
- Hey, Moby Dick, hey.
You, over here.
(spider shrieks)
(dramatic music)
(Dad groans)
(spider chattering)
(fire roaring)
- Dad!
- Pops!
Pops!
- Dad!
- Pops!
- Oh, my God, Dad!
Dad.
(Dad groans)
(spider chattering)
- Behind you.
(Petra screams)
(alligator growls)
Nobody messes with Mama.
- Come on, man, let's
get you outta here.
(Dad groans)
(swamp life chattering)
(girl sobbing)
(spiders chattering)
(banging on bus)
- Hey, you hear that?
- It's almost like they're
talking to each other.
- No, no, it sounds
like a truck.
(bang echoes)
What the hell?
(guns firing)
(dramatic music)
(gasps)
- Tammy!
- Daddy?
Daddy!
- Oh, baby.
Baby, you're okay.
Oh, okay.
(Charlie screaming)
- Now that is how you
make jambalaya, yeah!
What?
(majestic music)
- [Petra] It's
gonna be okay, Dad.
We're gonna get you some help.
- Pops, just gimme an
arm, let me help you.
- It's okay, son, I got it.
(ominous music)
(bushes rustling)
- Did you hear that?
- Yeah.
(birds chirping)
(ominous music)
(footsteps rustling)
- Whoa, don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
- Who the hell are you?
- The name is Jean
Jacques, this is my bayou.
I don't like outsiders, I don't
care how many legs you got.
- Whatever happened to
Southern hospitality?
- We got an injured man here,
my father, he needs help.
- Those things do that to you?
- Yeah, they breathe fire.
- See, I told you.
You don't go skinny dipping
with snapping turtles.
- How are you still alive?
- Don't.
- Okay, follow me.
(suspenseful music)
- What, ow!
- Grab the medical kit, we're
gonna put him in the barn.
- Yes, boss.
- We need to get him
back to the city.
- That ain't gonna happen.
- Radio said National Guard
is setting up a safe zone.
- Yeah, and there could
be 1000 of those things
between here and there.
You wanna take that chance?
- We have to try.
- There's gotta be
something we can do.
I mean, these things have
to have a weakness, right?
Something we can use
to get past them.
- He's right.
If I can get my hands
on one of those things,
I can dissect it, and maybe
we can find that weakness.
- You wanna try and capture
one of those things?
- It doesn't have to be
alive, just in one piece.
Kindaú.
- Okay, let's hear your plan.
(suspenseful music)
- Does that thing work?
(radio squelching)
- I tried to call you, but
when I couldn't get through,
I just--
- Baby, it's okay.
It's alright, I understand,
you're gonna be fine now.
- Girl, slide on down.
- Sir, hi.
I'm Charlie Blackwell,
I'm the coach.
- Coach Blackwell, of course.
We're gonna get you and the
girls back to Houston pronto.
As a matter of fact, why
don't you ride up front.
- No, listen, my wife and
kids are in New Orleans.
- New Orleans, listen,
I've got orders to
secure the perimeter
and keep all the
civilians outta there.
- No, you don't understand.
- No.
- Listen to me.
- You don't understand.
- Daddy, if it weren't for
him, we wouldn't have made it.
- Please.
- Fine, you can ride with me.
You, go straight home.
(truck rumbling)
(suspenseful music)
(spider chattering)
(people chattering)
(Mariachi music)
(spider squealing)
(suspenseful music)
- You got one.
- Yep, pretty big one.
- Anyone have a knife?
- Use this.
- That'll do.
Alright, here we go.
(ominous music)
Okay, can you hold this?
- Aren't I supposed to
use gloves or something?
- [Boss] Do like
your mama told you.
- These are the vocal cords,
very well developed
as one might expect.
- What's that
plum-looking thing?
- Well, let's find out.
- Oof!
- Nasty!
- Yes, bladder.
- Fuel supply for
the flamethrower.
- [Katelynn] That
would be my guess.
- You know, the shale layer
around here is full of biogas.
- Well, the species
evolved there.
That wouldn't be a surprise
if they adapted to utilize it.
- Alright, so what are
they doing here now?
- [Katelynn] My guess,
their habitat was disturbed.
- [Petra] By what?
- Oil companies down here,
they fracture the earth
to get at the fossil fuels,
it's called fracking.
- You mean, humans did this?
Typical.
- Says here that fracking
causes earthquakes.
Maybe the spiders
dug their holes
and the fracking started
a chain reaction.
- You running iOS 5?
- Yeah.
- All I know is, you're
digging around enough,
you could destabilize
the sediment.
- I'm gonna destabilize if I
see another one of those things
- [Paul] Alright, so what
are they doing here now?
- I bet if you boil
them spider legs
and dip them in some
butter and some hot sauce.
Mmm, whoo!
It just seems like a waste.
You know how in other
countries they eat grasshoppers
and scorpions and
crickets and such.
- You been sniffing
the turpentine again?
- No!
- I'm gonna tell
you this one time.
Lay off the 'shine.
- We ain't got no more 'shine,
'cause he drank it all.
- Well, you're the one that
brought it all out here.
- Boss asked me too.
- Boss didn't say that, he
said bring the medical kit.
You brought the medicine.
Box of rocks.
- This is a ovipositor.
- An ovi what?
- Egg layer, remember the
clerk at the gas station?
Well, I think this species
incubates its young
inside a living host,
and it needs
something really sharp
to get through all
that bone and skin.
Okay, alright now
that's strange.
The nervous system is
really rudimentary,
even for an arachnid.
I can't even find a brain.
All I can see is a
whole bunch of ganglia
for the motor control.
- So, they're not too smart.
That's a relief.
- They're coming, they're
coming, they're coming.
(suspenseful music)
(guns firing)
(dramatic music)
(spiders hissing)
- Guillaume!
(fire roaring)
(Guillaume screaming)
Box of rocks.
(spider chattering)
(man whimpering)
(dramatic music)
(groans)
(suspenseful music)
- How you doing
back there, Pops?
- Oh, decent.
I'm right behind you.
(dramatic music)
(gun firing)
- [Justin] What do we
do, she can't breathe!
Breathe, breathe.
(spiders growling)
(gun firing)
(Justin whimpers)
(dramatic music)
(ominous music)
(Katelynn screams)
- Mom!
(gun firing)
- Let her go!
- Mom, Mom!
- No, no no.
- Annabelle!
- You can't do
nothing, come on boy.
- [Justin] Annabelle!
- No.
- Where's Dad, Dad?
Dad!
- Wait.
- Dad?
- Wait here, wait here!
(spider chattering)
(suspenseful music)
(Dad groaning)
- Pops, Pops, easy, easy.
Pops, easy, it's me.
It's me, Pops,
it's me, I got you.
I got you.
Come on, we gotta
get Petra back.
We gotta get Petra back.
Come on, there you go.
(Dad screaming)
I know I know, just come on.
- Okay, listen to me.
- No no.
Save your breath, Pops.
- You've been a pain in
my ass most of your life,
and I've been hard
on you 'cause,
'cause you, when you needed it.
I realize now that
I have been trying
to fit round peg
into a square hole.
There's no...
You're not me.
That's okay, you're
still my son.
And take Petra, and you
get her to the safe zone,
'cause it's your only chance.
- Pops, we're all gonna get
to the safe zone, all of us.
Come on.
No.
Pops, they got Petra.
- No.
- Pops, Pops.
Hey, hey.
I'm gonna get her
back, Pops, okay?
- That's my boy.
(Dad groans)
- Dad, Dad...
(somber music)
- Your father?
You gonna need this.
- Where's everybody else?
- Annabelle, she went after Mom.
- [Paul] Get him back
to the safe zone?
- [Jack] Boy, follow me.
- What are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna save them.
(suspenseful music)
(ominous music)
(water splashing)
- Annabelle!
(suspenseful music)
Annabelle!
(ominous music)
(spiders chattering)
(Paul groaning)
(ominous music)
(spiders chattering)
Petra, come on.
Oh God.
- [Petra] Thank you.
- Alright, come on, come on.
Let's go.
- How's Dad?
Paul!
Paul?
- He's gone.
- No.
No!
- I'm sorry.
He made me promise that I
was gonna get you outta here.
Don't make a liar
outta me, okay?
(distant coughing)
Come on.
- Okay.
(ominous music)
(spider chattering)
Whoo, whoo, whoo!
- Shh, shh!
- Do you see her?
- Her?
- The queen, she's the
brain for all of them.
They're completely
dependent on her.
Kill her, they won't
be able to function.
They'll all die.
- You, you guys, uh...
(spider growls)
(all screaming)
- Come on, this way!
- Come on, Mom.
- [Paul] There's a
way out, guys come on.
- [Annabelle] This way, Mom.
- Come on, you got it?
Go, go, go!
(dramatic music)
(spiders screaming)
- Go.
- Ugh!
- Petra, I'm gonna
need you up at the top.
I'm gonna push.
(spider screaming)
(computer beeping)
(Paul groaning)
(tree crashes)
(Paul breathing heavily)
(Paul groaning)
(dramatic music)
(trees crunching)
(melancholy music)
- Hey, that's my Dad!
Dad!
- Oh my God, son!
Oh, oh man.
- [Justin] Yeah, Dad, I'm fine.
- I'm gonna need to
confiscate that weapon.
- This my gun.
- I was worried about
you, where's the others?
- The spiders, they took Mom.
- What, who did?
- Her asthma, she
couldn't breathe,
and the spiders they took her.
- Wait, the spiders took Mom?
- Yes.
- Where's Annabelle?
- She went after them,
I, I couldn't stop her.
- Say again, Zulu Six?
This keeps getting
better and better.
We got a problem, a big one.
(suspenseful music)
(helicopter rumbling)
- Is she coming?
- Yeah.
And she ain't too happy.
(missiles firing)
- Yes, whoo, yes!
Mom, Mom!
Look, Mom, the helicopters,
Mom, they're here.
Mom, they're coming.
- I, uh...
(Mom gasping)
- Mom?
Mom.
Mom, Mom!
(dramatic music)
- On me!
Listen up, I want
that thing stopped
before it reaches
the city, understand?
Failure is not an option.
- Oo-rah!
- Look!
- That is a big mother bugger.
- That's Paul.
- Who's Paul?
- Our tour guide.
- Tour guy?
(spider growling)
(dramatic music)
(guns firing)
(fire roaring)
- She's on the move.
(spider screeching)
(car alarms wailing)
(dramatic music)
- [Pilot] Major Crandle, I
have a visual on the target.
- You think?
(people screaming)
(spider screeching)
- What's she doing?
- She's feathering her nest.
(dramatic music)
- [Pilot] I have
target locked, sir.
Fire on your command.
- Hold your fire, Zulu Six,
we've got civilians
in that building.
(suspenseful music)
- One, two, three!
One, two...
Mom, mom!
- [Petra] What are we gonna do?
- Katelynn said if
we kill the queen,
it'll stop them all, right?
- Well, we don't even
know if that'll work.
- We have to try.
- Hello, Paul.
Missiles won't even stop her.
- These things are only
tough on the outside.
We have to go in.
- What are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna prove
your mother right.
- How can I help?
(dramatic music)
This is all I could find.
- Perfect.
- At the risk of
stating the obvious,
I want you to know I
think this is a bad idea.
- Duly noted.
- But whatever happens,
I believe in you.
- [Paul] Really?
- Nah, I'm just
messing with you.
(epic music)
(gun firing)
- Hey, that's
Annabelle, she made it!
- Oh, my God!
- [Charlie] Major Crandle!
My daughter, she's down there.
You guys gotta help her.
- [Crandle] Bravo team,
we've got civilians on
Iberville and Decatur,
Iberville and Decatur.
Roger, out.
- Time to show daddy long legs
how we roll on the bayou.
- Where the hell is he going?
(epic music)
(sirens wailing)
- Let's get her in the back.
- [Annabelle] No, no
please, let me go with her!
- You are not going.
Gentlemen, take this lady.
- [Justin] Annabelle!
- Justin!
(people screaming)
(dramatic music)
(gun firing)
(tires squealing)
- Who was that?
- That Cajun dude.
(sirens wailing)
(gun firing)
(guns firing)
- Annabelle!
- Dad!
- How's Mom?
- Her asthma.
She didn't make it.
(guns firing)
(spider screaming)
(dramatic music)
- You going fishing?
- [Paul] Yeah,
wanna be the bait?
- We come to say hello.
Time to dance, you
big beautiful bitch!
(bazooka firing)
(missile exploding)
(spider screaming)
(Jack groans)
- Woah, woah, woah,hey!
Woah, come on right here.
Come on, right here, get me!
Uh-oh.
(Paul screaming)
- Can I see through
the binoculars?
That's my brother, please.
(spider screams)
- It's not much of a safe zone.
- Ugh, I'm stuck.
- You need some help?
I'm kinda busy right now.
You'll help yourselves.
- [Paul] I just gotta get loose.
She's coming back.
(dramatic music)
- Don't start what
you can't finish, boy.
You hear me?
- No.
(spider screeches)
(Jack screaming)
(suspenseful music)
(spider chattering)
- [Paul] Ugh!
Ugh!
- Aw, man, he did not
just do that, did he?
- Ugh, I can't look.
(Paul groaning)
- The guy has got guts.
- Yeah, in more ways than one.
(gun firing)
- [Paul] Where is
it, where is it?
There it is, ugh!
- Gas bladder, he's going
for the gas bladder.
(spider farts)
(Paul screams)
(Paul whimpering)
- [Paul] Come on.
(spider screeches)
Come on!
This one is for you, Dad.
Ooh!
(explosion echoes)
(spider screeching)
(melancholy music)
- Get a squad over
there double time
and make sure every part
of that thing is dead.
Say again, Echo One?
I need visual confirmation.
Do you have eyes on?
Outstanding.
They're dying, all over the
city the spiders are dying.
Oo-rah!
- Oo-rah!
- Oh, Dad!
- Yeah!
(siren wailing)
- Did you know that man?
I'm sorry.
Listen, I'm gonna see
to it that he's awarded
the highest commendation the
military can offer a civilian.
You have my word on that.
Wait a minute, is that...
- Paul!
- Team Bravo, somebody
get him down from there.
- Little help?
(dramatic music)
(serene music)
(spider screams)
(lively music)
* Left my home in
search of another life *
* But all I found
was how to get lost *
* Maybe tomorrow will
be a brighter day *
* But I don't think so
* 'Cause I got a
bad bad feeling *
* Got a bad bad feeling
* I got a bad bad feeling
* It's always
gonna be that way *
* I headed down
* To where the water is warm
* Hoping to find
a place to rest *
* But I got chased out
* 'Cause I couldn't pay
* And I guess that it's
always gonna be that way *
* I wish that I
* Had someone to love
* Someone to talk to
* Someone to hold
* But I got nobody
* And I suppose it's okay
* 'Cause I guess that it's
always gonna be that way *
* I left my home in
search of another life *
* But all I found
was how to get lost *
* Maybe tomorrow will
be a brighter day *
* But I don't think so
* 'Cause I got a
bad bad feeling *
* Got a bad bad feeling
* I got a bad bad feeling
* It's always
gonna be that way *
* Well I just met a woman
* Prettier than the Sun
* And she says
that she loves me *
* I never thought that
I'd ever see the day *
* When somebody loves me
* And somebody wants me
* And I pray-ay-ay hey
* It's always
gonna be that way *
* And I pray-ay-ay hey
* It's always
gonna be that way *