[peaceful music]
Dad?
Yes, Carlton?
There's something I gotta know,
and I don't want you
to spare my feelings.
I can handle the truth.
- Okay, son.
You have my word.
What's on your mind?
When I grow up, will I be
able to grow a beard like that?
You're a Lassiter,
and Lassiter men have been
growing legendary face wigs
for generations.
It's a king's beard
born in your blood,
perfected through centuries.
But never forget, it's not
the beard that makes the king.
- I know, I know.
It's the queen.
That's right, son.
We're almost there.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
Dad?
Dad, where are you?
♪ ♪
Don't leave me!
Dad!
This is Chief Lassiter.
Shots fired.
I'm down.
I have been ambushed
and shot multiple times.
I need backup...
immediately.
♪ ♪
[groans]
Hold it.
Please, I have a family.
[gun clicks]
[sinister music]
♪ ♪
Carlton, do you even remember
why you're here?
Think, son.
Think.
♪ ♪
[gunshot]
- We have an officer down.
All units respond.
2016 Arkenstone Road.
Situation critical.
Suspect still at large.
Approach with extreme caution.
Both: Surprise!
- Ah!
- Surprise, surprise!
What is wrong with you two?
Check it out.
- What is that?
- That is a gift for you.
[whines]
Meet Morrissey the rescue dog,
here to rescue you
from your own handsomeness.
- That dog's Chief Vick's.
- He was.
He kept biting her daughter.
Affection gnawing
is what the vet called it.
He called it rabies, Shawn.
Either way, the Chief, Gus,
and I have come
to a little agreement.
She set him loose in my office
and sped away in her car.
Then you called us to come
down here
and the whole thing just felt
like a win-win.
That dog is eating my foot.
- Morrissey!
- Stop it.
- Psst.
- Fsst.
- Stop it.
Excuse me, Carlton,
I didn't realize
you had visitors.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sorry, no pets.
- Pets?
I'm sorry, I...
[whines]
Oh!
That's Morrissey.
He's a therapy dog.
Does he have a vest?
He does, though, he prefers
to call it a "waistcoat."
I think you'll find it all
checks out.
Hmm.
This an old Theraflu T-shirt
with tape over the "flu"
and "py" in Sharpie.
You're good.
One point for you, Dolores.
[chuckles]
My name is Shawn Spencer
and this is my partner
Bill Poopingtons.
- No.
Shawn?
- What?
- Sidebar.
All right.
Carlton, what is happening
right now?
- Let it go.
- Yes.
- Bill Poopingtons.
What kind of nickname is that?
- Transylvania Dutch.
Why?
No, Shawn.
No more embarrassing nicknames,
especially in front
of peers and professionals.
Gus, don't be the night
your dad fell asleep
inside your mom.
We can't just stop doing bits
we've been doing for ten years.
We have fans;
They have expectations.
There'll be a huge backlash.
- Shawn, we are two dumbasses.
We do not have fans.
[clicks tongue]
From now on, I do the nicknames.
- No, no, no.
Absolutely not.
That's disgusting.
Counterproposal:
You have right of refusal
until we land on one you like.
It's a Band-Aid,
but okay for now.
I'm terribly sorry, Dolores.
What I meant to say was,
my name is Shawn Spencer
and this is my full-fledged
partner All-The-Pips-In-One.
- Accepted.
Hello.
Could you fellas take
a little walk with me?
- [clicks tongue]
- Hmm.
Lassie, is that
what I think it is?
[laughs]
Guys, I love animals,
but I'm sure you know
what a prestigious place
the Herschel House is.
We do, but let me just say,
although the dog
is not fully certified and ate
one of the two gas pedals
in our car
on the way down here...
Two what?
We had hoped that
this visit alone would
start to help Carlton heal
his tangled memories.
He's a tough man
with the thick skin
of a northern white rhino,
but the heart of a smaller,
less-white rhino.
I know, and you're right, um...
It's Burton, but you can call
me Jermajesty
or whatever you'd like, Dolores.
Well, Jermajesty,
I am gonna kick myself
for falling prey
to a dapper, smooth-talking,
devil's food cookie
with a perfect cranium,
but I'll make the exception.
"Dapper" and "smooth-talking,"
that doesn't sound right.
Mr. Wilkerson, beautiful day.
Okay, dog stays, but he's on
a very short leash.
Short leash.
[laughs]
And, in exchange,
you guys can tell me why
you're really here.
- Damn, she's good.
- Yeah.
All right, Lassie called us
last night.
He's seeing things.
- Ghosts.
- Not necessarily ghosts.
But probably ghosts.
But there's a lot
of strange stuff
going on around here:
Eerie voices in pipes,
bodies being dragged
out into the woods at night,
black Jell-O.
We're checking to see
if this joint was built
on an Indian burial ground.
Uh, it was built
on an old Kmart,
and he's never mentioned
a word of this to me.
That's because he doesn't
want anyone to know.
We've sworn silence.
Shawn can't tell his wife.
My girlfriend thinks
I'm working a double shift.
I can't even take her calls.
Well, you can't take her calls,
because you downloaded
a rogue app
that changes all of your emojis
into little Jamaicans.
- Seventeen viruses.
- I see.
- So you have a girlfriend?
- I do.
Dolores, I'm gonna be honest
with you.
I only said "black Jell-O"
because that was Gus' nickname
in our adult dodgeball league.
Mm.
And Lassie's terrified
that he's going crazy.
Anyone finds out,
it could cost him his job,
his dignity,
maybe even his family.
Carlton doesn't even remember
why he went
to that abandoned building.
His only recollection
of his shooter is a silhouette,
he's on nine different
medications,
and as you both know,
he suffered a massive stroke
during surgery.
So of course he's seeing things,
but feeding into these fantasies
is the least helpful thing
you can do right now, okay?
Now, I know this goofy
little white guy,
sexy black dude routine
the two of you have going
like the back of my scrubs.
But you really wanna help?
Just be the grown men
that you are.
Okay, what is going on here?
What, Dolores?
The nurse from "Color of Night"
fawning all over you.
I don't know,
maybe she's attractive,
but, Shawn, I'm with Selene now.
I can't keep track
of every shorty
that wants what they can't have.
[chuckles]
Where the hell have
you two been?
Sorry, Lassie.
We were on our way up the stairs
when Gus spotted a Jamba
right across the street.
We made it happen.
Where's the dog?
He jumped out the window
the second you walked out
the door,
took my Jell-O, and ran
straight into the woods.
That makes sense.
He is a hunter-gatherer
of the highest order.
That wasn't the last Jell-O,
though, was it?
- Doesn't matter.
We don't need the dog.
Lassie, I'm gonna cut
to the chase.
It's gonna be
a hard pass for us.
We simply cannot keep lying
to our ladies
to cover up your spooky
ghost sightings, okay?
It's too hard.
They know each other.
We're grown men with real pubes.
Let me give you a visual.
You remember Eddie Murphy's
mustache in "Raw"?
Well, that's what Gus has
going on right over the twig.
Now look, whatever you think
you're seeing, it's up here.
You've been through a lot
and hospitals are creepy,
even super luxurious ones.
Trust me on this, man.
You're just really high.
High.
[door creaking]
[eerie music]
Uh, Shawn.
What's in that dog's mouth?
Gus, please.
It is nothing more
than a human hand.
Oh, my God!
It's... it's a human hand.
And it's covered
in leaves and moss
and it's human and it is a hand.
I'm gonna have to call my wife.
I'm gonna have to lie again.
Lassie, we're in.
Of course you're in, you morons.
There's a hand in your hand.
- Go ahead, Gus.
Knuck it up softly.
Get that dead hand
away from me, Shawn.
♪ ♪
[jaunty rock music]
♪ In between the lines ♪
♪ There's a lot of obscurity ♪
♪ I'm not inclined to resign
to maturity ♪
♪ If it's all right ♪
♪ Then you're all wrong ♪
♪ But why bounce around
to the same damn song ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You'd rather run when
you can't crawl ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I know, you know ♪
♪ That I'm not
telling the truth ♪
♪ I know, you know ♪
♪ They just don't have
any proof ♪
♪ Embrace the deception ♪
♪ Learn how to bend ♪
♪ Your worst inhibitions ♪
♪ Tend to psych you out
in the end ♪
♪ ♪
[laid-back music]
Shawn, I don't like this.
Gus, you heard Lassie.
We need to get this hand
to Woody ASAP.
If it's ASAP,
why did we stop first
at Pokey Jack's Smoky Shack?
Because I'm not an animal, Gus.
Either way, it says
right there on the wall
we're not allowed
to ship living material.
Well, if this hand
was still living,
that would be inappropriate,
but it's not.
Now, we need our gear
if we're gonna find
the rest of this body
before we drive home.
All of our stuff
is back in Psychphrancisco.
Or is it?
Ow.
Oh, you wanna bumble
with the bee, huh?
[buzzes]
[curious music]
Yeah.
♪ ♪
Gus, we're home.
[triumphant fanfare]
Now give me some Chewie.
[imitates Chewbacca]
It's getting better.
Oh.
[cats meowing]
[playful music]
♪ ♪
Are we on the same page
right now?
Yes, alternative Spider-Verse.
No.
Oh, bienvenue au Litière,
Santa Barbara's only
pop-up cat restaurant.
Ah.
- Sure.
- Of course.
A cat-fé.
How nice.
Do your parents know
you're doing this?
- What?
How old do you think I am?
- Nine.
- Forty-one.
- Forty-one?
- Like the girl from "Orphan."
Congrats, business is booming.
Um, we don't open
for another 15 minutes.
Oh, so the cats
aren't the customers?
Who the hell are you guys?
I'm Shawn Spencer, this is
my partner Ding Dong Ditch.
- Nope.
- Claude O'Dirt.
- Mm-mm.
- Big Poppa Pump?
Warmer.
Lemona-lemona-lemona-lime...
Hello.
How did either of you
reach adulthood?
Don't worry, you will too
as long as you keep
taking your vitamins.
- Okay, I am not a child.
What do you want?
- Isn't it obvious?
We want love.
And companionship.
And the end of the ivory trade.
But most importantly,
we wanna know what you think
you're doing opening
a cat-feteria in our office.
Well, I am a legit entrepreneur
and I rented this space
and it's mine
for the next 19 days.
Oh, those are for cats.
I see.
Okay, I'm gonna be
honest with you guys.
I am in a real Dickens
of a stare down
with the health department,
so I'm gonna need you
to get to the point.
All right, here's the nutshell.
I'm a psychic
and he's a sympathetic pooper.
We're back to retrieve
dozens of detectiving tools
that we've stashed
in the walls, ceiling,
and air ducts.
And that may require punching
a hole or five.
Well, you're gonna need
to take that up
with the landlord,
and he is not gonna like it.
- Back there.
- Thank you, old woman.
Or young child,
whichever you may be.
- What do you want?
- Hi.
Looking for approval
to destroy your drywall
and possibly remove
your air conditioner.
- No.
Bug off.
- "Bug off"?
- Hmm.
[knocks on door]
Sir, if you would just allow
me to explain the magnitude...
- No.
- Yeah, wait, hold on.
Back up.
We can't help but be
disturbed by how low
the register of your voice is.
You're clearly putting on
some sort of bellowed timbre.
- This is not a timbre.
- It just got lower.
- It's the same voice.
- So you admit it's a voice?
Yeah, who are you doing,
Tom Waits?
- Kathleen Turner?
- Harvey Fierstein?
- Diedrich Bader?
- Shawn.
- Get in here.
- Dad?
How in the hell could
you afford to buy
the Psych office?
I didn't buy anything.
You neglected to tell
your landlord
that you were moving.
What?
I simply picked up the payments
and started subletting
to every hipster pop-up
coming into town.
I am literally rolling
in disposable income.
[whispers]
Tax-free.
This seems illegal.
Why are you bothering
my tenants?
We may have left behind
a few items when we moved.
You left behind a slow cooker
with a 3-pound roast in it.
You nearly "This Is Us'd"
the entire block.
"This Is Us"?
Dad, why are you watching
that show?
They have the same show
on ABC, but newer.
[knock at door]
What do you want?
Uh, this is embarrassing,
but I think I'm allergic
to these cats.
- [sneezes]
- Not my problem.
Wha...
Look, Dad,
this is a Lassie mystery.
The stakes are possibly
life and death,
which means I need
my night vision goggles
and my collection of mustaches
in order to snoop around
undetected.
Will you please help us?
For Lassie.
[sighs] Of course.
You're using the voice again.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[gun clicks]
[gunshot]
Surprise!
I can see all your teeth,
O'Hara.
Like, all of them.
I'm sorry, I'm just
inappropriately giddy
to see you.
- Wait a minute.
It's not Monday.
Why are you here?
Carlton, you are
absolutely paranoid.
I miss you.
Really?
Okay, fine.
Truth is, I snuck out
this morning when I saw this.
[dramatic music]
Is that Conway Twitty?
This is Reese Kessler,
the monster who shot you
in cold blood six times.
They picked him up yesterday,
made a full confession,
waived his right to an attorney.
Still ironing out a few details,
but it smells like...
what?
Nothing.
I know that face.
Is this not the guy?
- I don't know.
Believe me, I wish I did.
I don't remember.
I'm working on it.
But maybe the reason
you're making that face
is because this is not
the right person.
Look, the truth is,
I didn't come down here
all the way from San Francisco
just to be a messenger.
I came down here,
because he doesn't mention
a second gun in his confession.
And I know they never found
a slug for it,
but I also know
there's a bullet missing
from the crime scene.
O'Hara, you've already been
reprimanded twice
to stay off this case.
Please stop jeopardizing
your career.
Look, I just wanna help.
- "Help"?
Great.
There you go.
That's a grocery list.
- Untrue.
There's also some errands.
There are 93 of them.
Yeah, so it shouldn't take
you that long.
Gus, we've got everything
we need right here.
Best damn tracking dog
in the history
of the Half Moon Bay
Animal Shelter.
Morrissey already
found the hand.
Now he will meticulously sniff
this entire place
and lead us directly
to the rest of the body.
Morrissey, take a sniff of this.
Huh?
[growling]
Now, watch and learn.
[panting]
[adventurous music]
♪ ♪
I probably should have left
the leash on.
Ya think?
Damn, he cleared
the horizon quickly.
You are the strongest person
I know.
[chuckles] Nah.
Yeah, and I am watching you
get stronger
every single day.
And I love you, and I don't know
what I would do without you.
[sniffles]
And I will be back on Monday
for our regularly
scheduled visit
with a completed errand list
and seven pounds
of Ghiradelli chocolate.
Okay.
Oh, and I almost forgot.
What?
I thought you might want it
so you never forget.
And I promise next time
I am here, zero police talk,
unless, of course,
you wanna talk about putting
a guard outside your door.
- Deal?
- Deal.
We've gotta be honest
with each other.
Why is Morrissey's dish here?
Whose what?
Shawn, we've been lost
for an hour.
That dog's never coming back.
[phone rings]
Babe of all babes.
I can't believe
you're in Santa Barbara.
- What?
I can explain, babe.
I was just trying to help.
- Please don't.
Just stop.
I'm here too.
I need to talk to you
about dinner.
Right, dinner.
- Cancel.
- I'm not gonna cancel.
I think we should cancel.
- No, we're not gonna cancel.
Don't be silly.
I already have something
in motion that's amazing.
Tonight's gonna be a night
we remember forever.
Um... okay.
I'm just... I'm stuck
at the airport,
and I may need
a little extra time,
so maybe we should just...
Hey, what you said is perfect.
I'll see you tonight.
I love you.
[sighs]
She was giving you an out.
She sounded really strange, Gus.
Like Lupita in "Us"?
No, well, which one?
- "Tethered."
[clicks tongue]
No, not that strange.
I just feel like I really
let her down this time.
- You're protecting Lassie.
He begged us not to tell her.
It doesn't matter, Gus.
I can't keep sneaking around
and lying like this anymore.
She's probably sitting
at the airport all misty-eyed,
wondering if I'll ever be
the truthful grown-ass
man she deserves.
What am I... Let's go home.
[foreboding music]
♪ ♪
This is Chief Lassiter.
Shots fired.
I'm down.
[gunshots]
I have been ambushed
and shot multiple times.
[gunshot]
- We have an officer down.
All units respond.
[gunshot]
Situation critical.
♪ ♪
They never found
the slug for it.
♪ ♪
There's a bullet missing
from the crime scene.
♪ ♪
[rustling]
- I didn't see anything!
Don't shoot.
- I'm not gonna hurt you.
- I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have come back.
Look, you need
medical attention.
And I need that bullet
in your leg.
♪ ♪
[Dean Martin's "Ain't That
a Kick in the Head"]
♪ ♪
♪ How lucky can one guy be ♪
- She's later than us.
Go!
- Dude!
- Go, do it!
She'll be here any second, man.
Make it romantic.
I'll plate the dinners.
You set the mood.
♪ Ain't that a kick
in the head ♪
Ooh, next level petal-ing, Gus.
♪ She's telling me
we'll be wed ♪
Shawn, why did you
choose the menu
from "A Charlie Brown
Thanksgiving"?
Because it's the only thing
they had
at the gas station, Gus.
Come on, son.
- [phone ringtone plays]
- ♪ I'm Mr. Bootyman ♪
Don't... don't answer that.
I couldn't if I wanted to.
My phone is even worse now.
None of the buttons are working.
Well, we reap what we sow.
- ♪ I'm Mr. Bootyman ♪
[keys jingling]
- She's coming.
Okay!
I gotta get the candles.
You sneak down the fire escape.
- Cool.
Wait, fire escape?
I am really proud of how
you've handled all of this.
It was big of you to bail
on Lassiter's case,
especially with goblins
on the table.
Thank you, but I also know
that you're not sold
on the guy who confessed
to shooting Lassie.
But, babe, your neck
is way out there on this one.
Shawn Spencer, are you
the one worried about me
sniffing around
where I shouldn't be?
That's right, it feels good
to be the adult
in this relationship.
- [laughs]
- Just this once.
Yeah.
Seriously, though, please
promise me
that you'll let
the locals handle this one.
- Of course.
That being said,
I'm gonna take this list.
I'm gonna do all
these errands for you,
which include
"polishing Lassie's rod."
But first, I'm gonna
wrap both of us
in your favorite green Snuggie.
[gasps]
And we're gonna be in there
for a while.
It's in the big dresser
drawer with all the bedding!
Heh.
[yelps]
What are you doing?
That fire escape was steep,
Shawn.
- Come on, man.
It's been a couple of hours.
Look, I told her all afternoon
that you were gonna be gone.
Now you've turned me
into a liar again.
- You are a liar.
- Your dad's a liar.
Did you tell her about the hand?
No, because the hand
is not important,
because we're off the case.
- Now give me this damn Snuggie.
- Get your own damn Snuggie.
This is my damn Snug...
- Ow!
- [grunts]
What's that?
Nothing, hon.
Hey, babe.
It's weird.
I can't find the Snuggie.
But you know what?
We don't need that particular
Snuggie, because...
- [phone ringtone plays]
- ♪ I'm Mr. Bootyman ♪
Is that Gus' ringtone?
That is Gus' ringtone, isn't it?
He must have left his phone
here, silly black goose.
I just remembered
where the Snuggie is.
It's in the bedroom,
but it's deep.
I think there's a depth to it.
Will you go look for it?
You just wanna see who's calling
so you can decide whether
or not to pick it up.
Will you marry me?
Only if we can have toast
and jelly beans for dinner
every night.
- Deal.
This is it.
- That's where it's at.
- This is home base.
Yep.
Good God, man, turn that off.
- I'm trying.
It's Woody.
- Well, answer it.
He's got the hand.
I thought you said the hand
wasn't important.
Where did you get
a Nutri-Grain bar?
Don't worry about that, Shawn.
Mmm.
Guys, first of all, thank you
for the delicious smoked meats.
- He ate the hand?
- He didn't eat the hand.
I put some smoked meats
in with the hand.
Why would you do that?
Because it was $26
to mail the box
whether it was full or not, Gus.
I thought you of all people
could appreciate
that level of frugality.
Woody?
I have good news
and I have bad news.
The venison, scrumptious!
[chuckles]
Oh, also there was
a usable print
on one of the dead guy's
fingers.
I got a name for the victim.
Some hotshot manufacturing CEO
named Devon Tileback.
- Devon.
Okay, okay.
What's the bad news?
Shawn, the buffalo was chewy.
Tasted a little bit
like fingernails.
- That makes sense.
It was actually tofuffalo.
- Oh, tofuffalo.
Okay.
Damn it, now we've got
a real murder case
and a real victim.
Nope, no, no, no.
He wasn't murdered
or dissolved by a witch.
He committed suicide.
- Suicide?
- Yeah, about a week ago.
Jumped off a bridge
into the Santa Ynez River.
Body was never found
until now, I guess.
[clattering, baby coos]
Luka, no.
No, sweetie.
Butterfly's baby is playing
with a spleen again.
- I should go.
- Yeah, you should.
Well, this great.
There's no ghost.
It's open and shut.
We're off the hook.
No, Gus, this is bad.
The suicide, the hand
turning up behind the hospital
where Lassie's seeing ghosts...
Come on.
Jules is gonna go right back
down there
when she hears all this stuff.
We have to save her
from herself.
What does that even mean?
It means we go back
to Santa Barbara
and start lying again.
Be careful for spiders.
[stammers]
- Shawn!
- Here comes the tickler!
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[exclaiming]
[gunshot]
[whines]
Morrissey?
No.
What have I told you
about getting up on the bed?
Down.
Off.
I can move you off me
any time I want to.
[whines]
[sighs]
Actually, that's not true,
is it?
[high-pitched whine]
You think I'm a fraud,
don't you?
You think they're gonna
retire me,
gonna be a burden to my family.
Gonna sit in the La-z-Boy
the rest of my life
yelling at the TV.
Oh, crap, that would suck.
I'm gonna level with you, dog,
just between you and I.
I don't know if I'm ever gonna
walk again.
[grunting]
What are you looking at?
[groans]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- [moans]
- You see that, right?
[groans]
I mean, that guy's
really bleeding.
Come on, dog, tell me
I'm not crazy.
- Of course you're not crazy.
You're a Lassiter.
I thought I told you
to leave me alone.
I know, son, but we have
so much catching up to do.
♪ ♪
Oh, Lassie, Lassie, Lassie.
Look, we believe that you saw
something last night,
but why would a man
soaked in blood
sneak into some stables
at a recovery house?
- I know what I saw.
- Did anybody else see this?
Yes.
A dog?
Oh, my God,
Morrissey ate Dolores.
Dolores is fine.
Look, Lassie,
we're trying here, man.
We are.
But that hand, remember?
The hand that Morrissey found
belongs to
some techie CEO that
took a dive into the river.
It has nothing to do with you
or the Herschel House.
And keeping these trips secret
is proving very difficult.
Gus slept in a drawer
last night.
Full disclosure,
it's the best sleep
I've had in years.
I might even stay there
again tonight.
- Yeah, guess again.
- You'll never know.
Regardless, your only
witness is a dog,
who I'm not convinced
didn't eat a nurse.
Guys, please,
just check out the stables
and then you can tell me
I'm crazy.
- He said "please."
- He did.
Shoot.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
[phone rings]
[gasps] Selene.
Oh, hi, Juliet.
Do you know where I can file
a missing person's report?
Oh, yeah, I can do
that for you right away.
- Who's it for?
- Gus.
Gus?
Yes, he's not at work
and he hasn't answered
his phone in two days.
And I've called
from lots of phones.
- Selene, come on, it's Gus.
It's fine.
He doesn't have
a deceptive bone in his... oh.
You know what?
He left his phone at our house
when they got back
from Santa Barbara.
What?
He didn't tell me he was going
to Santa Barbara.
Neither did Shawn.
That's 'cause they were
sneaking around
on a case they didn't want me
to know about.
- And that doesn't upset you?
- No.
It makes it easier for me
to sneak around and investigate
cases they don't know about.
Juliet, there's something
or someone
he's not telling me about.
Oh, is this about the nurse?
What nurse?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
Lassiter's nurse,
she's just very sweet,
and she just seems
to really like Gus.
Super innocent.
Sorry, why would Kessler
contradict his own alibi?
Unless he was forced to.
You know what, Selene?
I am sorry, I have to go
to Santa Barbara
and get a prisoner to recant
his confession.
Gus is way into you.
Try not to spiral over nothing.
Bye!
A nurse isn't nothing.
[laid-back music]
All right,
I guess the bloody figure
would have had to come
through here.
Man, even the stables
are spotless.
- I'd even eat off this floor.
- You'd eat off any floor.
Now, why would they keep
all this medical equipment
down here?
That doesn't make any sense.
What are these?
Ice chips.
They give them to patients
during therapy
when they can't hold down
solid food.
What are you doing?
Are you eating that?
Dude, there's, like, five
different flavors in there.
- You can't do that, Shawn.
It's impolite.
Impolite?
You ate a Nutri-Grain bar
that you found in an armoire.
Exactly, it didn't belong
to anyone... oh, my gosh.
Blue raspberry.
Now you see what I'm saying.
This is like a Concord grape.
- Excuse me.
Good morning.
Are you eating
the patients' ice chips?
- I am not.
He is.
- That's not true.
- We're sorry.
We're just... we're both fans
of delicious flavor.
- We're friends of the Chief.
Carlton Lassiter.
Ah, friends of the Chief's.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- I'm Dr. Herschel.
This is my facility.
Those are my ice chips.
Oh.
I'd like to remind you,
gentlemen,
that the areas marked
"restricted" are restricted,
because they are restricted.
- That feels fair.
- Mm-hmm.
We were wondering, did you
have any unexpected visitors
late last night
who had been attacked violently
and perhaps large pools of blood
in this general area
maybe headed that way?
No, no pools of blood.
Any people living in your pipes?
Maybe speaking their own
tongue, perhaps Parsel.
I'm fairly certain we do not.
I feel like we're making
some serious strides here.
Yes.
What about one-handed patients?
Be it by birth,
industrial accident,
or voodoo.
100% of our patients have
100% of their appendages.
May I ask, gentlemen,
what is this about?
Say nothing.
Carlton may have seen a zombie.
[quacks] What are you doing?
[grunts]
It was not a zombie, sir.
It was a normal man possibly
infected with rage,
drenched in his own blood.
And, oh, did you know there are
bodies in your fields?
- [squeaks]
- Now I'm doing it.
You.
You're good.
You are very good
at extracting confessions.
Impressive.
I know that the Chief
has been seeing things
that are unexplainable.
Believe me, we are doing
everything in our power
to help him work through this
during his recovery.
We even sent for a specialist
all the way from the island
of Cuba to help,
Mr. A.V. Catalon, a renowned
homeoneurotraumatist.
Dr. Herschel, I'm going
to be honest with you.
That title sounds like you
made it up right this second.
Do you have a picture
of this alleged Dr. Catalon?
All you have to do is look
into the flap of his book.
[in British accent] What?
He wrote a book?
[both laugh]
May I be honest with you,
gentlemen?
Please, sir.
The Chief's behavior
is perfectly within
the realm of normal for someone
who has experienced
such severe trauma.
The only danger is if somebody
were to fuel his fantasies.
Am I being clear?
- Yes.
- Good.
Now, if I am ever to see
you two gentlemen again,
I hope it is in the area
marked "for visitors,"
because that's where visitors
do their visiting.
It tracks.
Good day.
- Wait for it...
- Good, good.
- Clear.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
I like to suck on the tips.
What?
♪ ♪
- O'Hara.
- Hmm?
- There you are.
- You got it, didn't you?
Police Commissioner,
I can't believe it!
You'll come back
and visit us, right?
No, final interviews
are later today,
and I'm just one of three.
- It's an honor to be considered.
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, scratch that.
I want it, I need it,
it is mine to lose.
Yeah.
So why'd you wanna talk
to me so bad?
Ballistics is having
a little trouble identifying
this slug that
you brought in yesterday,
and I don't recall
the case it's from.
Oh, I was just crossing some Ts
in the Embarcadero Shipping
case.
- Okay.
Then, good.
- Yeah.
- And, O'Hara...
Yes, Chief?
If you're going to go
after Lassiter's shooter,
please do us the courtesy
of clocking out first
and never lie to me,
even if you think
it's for my own protection.
I'm sorry.
I thought they had
someone in custody.
- They do.
- And he confessed?
He did.
- I can explain.
- Oh, I didn't ask you to.
And I don't need to remind you
how many cold-blooded killers
get off on technicalities.
[elevator dings]
So, you're going
to Santa Barbara to see
about a prisoner, huh?
Well, I'm going to see
about a nurse.
[whimsical music]
[cat toy jingles]
Gus, is this place starting
to mess with your head?
I suddenly have the urge
to give myself a tongue bath.
- Focus, Shawn.
- Right.
Look, I don't get it.
Devon Tileback's life
was perfect.
His company just went public.
Why would he jump off a bridge?
He just started spending
his money like a boss.
He had everything left
to live for.
I don't know, Gus.
But Lassiter is spiraling
with every single
unanswered question.
We need to prove something,
even if it's not what
we wanna prove.
We've ruled out the hell hag.
Maybe we take a harder look
at Tileback.
Now what are we missing?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- That doesn't make sense.
- What?
Our guy worked from
morning till night, right?
So what's he doing driving
all the way into the hills
to the Vikings Den Ice Bar?
- An ice cream bar?
- No, no, no, ice bar.
The ones where
they give you a parka
and they have
subzero temperatures.
They're either
for tourists or Eskimos.
- He could be an Eskimo.
What?
Let's go get loaded for Lassie.
[indistinct announcement]
[door buzzes]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
You're not a public defender.
No, wait, Mr. Kessler.
I just don't want you to make
a mistake by going to jail
for a crime you did not commit.
Look, I know you've had
a lot of heartbreaks
in your life,
but you can get out of this.
I can help you.
No, you can't, okay?
They're everywhere.
They're here.
They know everything.
- Think about your wife.
- Look, you don't get it, okay?
I can't trust anyone.
I'm fully exposed in here.
Don't let anybody force you
to do this.
- Think about your child.
- Wait, wait, wait.
You have a kid, and you're
willing to go to jail
for nothing?
What the hell is wrong with you?
- The hell is this?
- Nobody.
Nobody?
- I'm your best friend.
- Best friend?
What, you brought
your best friend with you?
Look, you know what?
I'm done.
- I'm done with you guys.
- You know what?
You're right, we are done,
you ol' deadbeat D'Andre.
- No, look, wait...
- Peace out.
- What?
Kessler, wait.
- Open the door.
- We are not done.
You know what?
I may have overreacted slightly.
May...
[sneaky music]
♪ ♪
I don't like this, Shawn.
We're the only non-motorcycle
in this parking lot
and these people are
extra white,
which is never good.
Well, you'll just have
to be extra black, then.
You bet.
[dramatic music]
These mittens are
awfully restrictive,
and I'm afraid my hat
used to be a raccoon.
The fur is fake, Shawn.
What we should have done
was waited to see if
any more of those fancy brown
earmuffs became available.
Let's just get
the information we need,
drink some chilled moonshine,
and bounce out of here.
Hello.
Hi, you must be
the vodka consigliere?
What the hell is this?
What can you tell us
about Devon Tileback?
Don't talk about Devon in here.
Why not?
He owed a lot of money.
- What?
That dude was loaded.
Look, he was a good guy,
but he was starting to lose it.
Kept going on about
all of his dark secrets
being exposed.
First of all, thank you
for being so forthcoming.
- It's refreshing.
- Yeah.
What secrets do you mean?
[speaking Norwegian] Hello.
[speaking Norwegian]
Hmm?
- Ova.
This is my place.
- Both: Oh.
- Yes.
You're just the man we'd like
to speak with.
Question: Do you have
any more of
those smoky topaz-brown
earmuffs?
Those are for our VIPs,
and we're all out.
Have you ever been to Norway?
Just once
with my brother-in-law.
We don't talk about that, Shawn.
Ova, I'm going to be honest
with you.
Neither of us have heard
of this joint,
and I wasn't even aware
this mountain existed.
Well, we just opened last year.
This is my second chapter.
I used to run
a different business,
successful and rewarding
in its own way,
but life has a way
of giving you a new direction.
It does.
Can I treat you to
a favorite of mine
from back home?
Is it Oreo-flavored?
It is not.
It is cask-aged
by my family in Flekkefjord
for the last 120 years.
Not to seem ungrateful,
but do you have
anything Russian?
Gentlemen, Norwegian tradition.
First, we look
into each other's eyes...
Mm.
And we say:
[Singing in Norwegian]
- Skal!
- Cheers!
And cheers!
- Ah, kerosene.
- Uh!
[dramatic music]
Tell me, who is the bearded
Daryl Hannah over there?
- That's Per.
He's my son.
Both:
Ah.
He's also clearly
within earshot.
He's already displeased
with me and my career choices.
Perhaps we all stop
gawking at him?
- Fair enough.
Gus, we need to go.
We do, but first, I need to go.
This vodka went
right through me.
Thank you
for your hospitality, Ova.
We'll be back to wear
these coats again,
I can assure you.
Can we reserve two pair of
the extra plush
russet brown earmuffs?
Be sure to put you
on the top of the list.
♪ ♪
[zipper hisses]
[phone ringtone plays]
♪ I'm Mr. Bootyman ♪
♪ I'm looking for a cutie ♪
♪ With a booty, understand ♪
♪ I'm Mr. Bootyman
I'm Mr. Bootyman ♪
- Stop it.
Stop it.
[camera snaps]
What the hell?
That was not supposed to happen.
My cousin partnered
with Greg Grunberg on an app
called "Jamaica Me Alla Way."
There are some bugs,
and that's what caused me
- to photograph your...
- [yelps]
Hairless genitals over there
twice.
I will erase the photos
immediately.
- [phone whooshes]
- [gasps]
[Twitter app whistles]
Bad news, I just tweeted that.
You are one sick individual.
- [phone chiming]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, no!
Don't retweet that!
Damn it!
You know, sometimes,
I really hate my followers.
You know what we do
with sick individuals?
You give them the space
and care they deserve?
They get what they deserve,
all right.
- What could I do?
I pulled the man's finger.
- Let's go.
Let's go!
Psst.
It was nice meeting you, Ova.
- And you.
- Let's go!
[speaks Norwegian]
Dude, what the hell happened
in there?
I will tell you
on my deathbed, Shawn.
- We go on foot.
- What?
- Run, Shawn!
[screaming]
[speaking Norwegian]
Come on!
[distant yells]
- Dude, dude!
Motorcycle.
Let's go!
- No, no, no, no, no.
I can't do it.
You can't do what,
ride a motorcycle?
In all the years I owned one,
how many times did you actually
see me ride, Gus?
I don't care.
Shawn, there's a bunch
of angry Viking bikers
coming this way now.
- No.
- Let's go.
I promised Jules I wouldn't
ride anymore,
and I gotta be honest
about something.
Dude, now is not the time to try
to suddenly live up
to your vows.
- Let's go.
- That's fair.
[motor revving]
- Make a hard right!
Hard right!
Turn right!
[speaking Norwegian]
[groans]
That wasn't a hard right, Shawn.
I tried to tell you, man!
What do you we do now?
I guess we just lay here
for a while.
Who the hell are you guys?
- Who the hell are we?
Who the hell are you?
You're Devon Tileback.
Dude, our dog found your hand.
You're supposed to be dead.
You need to stop whatever it
is you think you're doing.
You have no idea
who you're dealing with.
More people are gonna die.
Just let me stay dead.
You're ruining everything.
When you say "everything"...
[gunshot]
[thudding]
Where did that shot come from?
Play dead.
[tense music]
- Buzz frickin' McNab.
- In a suit.
It's even his size.
What's going on with the hair?
It's a douche-hawk, Shawn.
Oh, there's a piece
coming loose.
Dude, he's got my phone.
Buzz, you look big and slick.
Shawn, Gus, what are you guys
doing in Santa Barbara?
Well, I left a Frisbee signed
by a German film director
Florian Henckel
von Donnersmarck when I moved,
and I've come back
to collect it.
Gus has a new love interest
down here
who happens to be a nurse.
Not true.
- Can I have that?
- It's evidence.
It's mine.
You guys got here too quick
for us to fish it out
of the ditch.
Did you kill that guy?
Buzz, please, the man was
dead before we spoke to him.
What?
- He died a second time, Buzz.
Keep up.
- Why are you here?
- Super top secret, man.
I can't tell you or anyone
from your department
or any former members
of your department,
especially not J...
Jules?
That means she's
still working this case.
She lied to me, Gus.
She lied to me.
I'm so turned on right now,
dude.
Shawn, don't be happy
about this.
You are setting
a dangerous precedent.
Honesty is the key component
in any...
- Who's she talking to?
- This doesn't look
- like a hospital.
- Selene.
What the... dude,
we gotta get out of here.
Selene found me.
Damn it, I knew I was gonna
get caught!
- Just act natural.
- What is happening?
Buzz, you never saw us.
But this is a crime scene.
Okay, listen very closely.
- Guy in a ditch.
- Named Devon.
- Faked death.
- Owed people money.
- Got found.
- Got shot.
- Now dead.
- Case closed.
We will waive our fee
for solving this,
because you still have to
figure out who shot him.
Okay, but how am I...
Whoo-whoo.
- Nope.
- Yep.
- Move, sir, move, sir, sir.
- Do not let her in here.
This is a crime scene.
♪ ♪
What's going on here?
I'm not sure,
but if I had a guess,
a guy faked his death
and then got shot
by the people
he was hiding from.
How long have you been here?
- Ten minutes.
- Wow.
That's impressive.
- Thanks, Juliet.
It means a lot.
Hmm.
Here is the ballistics report
on the bullet
that went through Lassiter.
There was a second gun,
which means the guy
who confessed is a liar.
Don't tell anyone
how you got this.
You understand?
I'm not sure I understand
anything right now.
That's the Buzz I know and love.
How's Francie?
Oh, she's teaching yoga
to horses now.
[panting]
A cop!
[grunts]
[panting]
Nice hiding space, Shawn.
Then where do you suggest
we go, Gus?
We're in the forest
and we look like bears.
Yeah, but there's cops
everywhere.
No one is paying attention
to us, Shawn.
- No one.
- You're right, that's weird.
Juliet, if you would simply
take me to the hospital...
Selene, I am working a case
I have no business working on.
So I am super sorry,
but I would like
to respectfully request
that you shut the hell up.
- Excuse me?
- I'm sorry.
I should have said heck.
You brought a friend with you?
- It's Gus' girlfriend.
- Hi.
Oh, you're the nurse.
No!
Shawn, Selene's coming back.
- Through the car.
- Good call.
Hurry!
Careful, you're getting
footprints
all over Jules' seats.
Stop kicking everything.
You kicked everything
everywhere.
Shawn, she's coming.
There is no reason
that keeps us here right now.
Dude, there kinda is.
[heartbeat pounds]
- Shawn, she's gonna see us.
Come on.
Juliet, I'll just
get there myself.
[grunts]
[suspenseful music]
[car door slams, engine revs]
♪ ♪
I don't know what I did,
but I'm so sorry.
- Buzz.
- Mm-hmm?
I'm gonna need your car.
Keys?
- I left them in the car.
- [scoffs]
♪ ♪
Oh, man.
Dude, will you snap out of it?
- It's impossible.
- What's impossible?
I think I'm pregnant.
- What?
[clicks tongue]
When did you all start trying
to have a baby?
I don't know, Gus.
I thought we were waiting.
I assumed that we would start
with a hamster,
maybe a mini-leopard.
You know me, man.
I'm not ready for this.
You know the windows in the loft
don't even fully close, right?
I'm gonna have to replace them.
Otherwise this is
"Baby's Day Out" all over again.
Shawn, calm down, calm down.
You're spinning.
No reason to get worked up
over John Hughes' worst idea.
Are you even listening?
[phone chirping]
Lassie just texted, all caps.
He saw Wilkerson running
down the hallway.
Wilkerson?
The comatose dude
in a wheelchair?
I think Lassie's hit a new low.
We're gonna have
to deal with this.
Uh, shouldn't we be dealing
with this whole
fatherhood thing?
Yes, but later.
This Lassie thing is
the perfect reason
not to deal with
anything real at all.
How lucky is that?
And what exactly
are you thinking?
Well, it is that time.
What time?
So now Lassie's seeing
some comatose man
up and running around,
but we've got a real dead guy
on our hands.
We're concerned
we've lost him forever.
- Sh...
- Shawn!
I did not steal
your moustache collection.
What is your problem?
Well, then you misplaced it,
Pop, or you used it
as part of your bedroom play
for whatever
unfortunate jezebels
you convinced to participate
in your sick game.
Ah!
[meows]
This cat.
Look, I just want 'em back.
I need 'em back!
You better walk that tone
some place else
if you want my help.
All right, can I step in here?
Shawn is having a lot
going on right now.
Big picture life stuff.
My only concern at the moment
is that my dad is
a liar and a thief.
Do we even know if that merkin
on your face is real?
Stop!
I thought maybe,
when you got married,
you might take even
half a step toward
being an adult, but you are
regressing big time.
Oh, well, I am way further
down that road
than you can imagine being.
And this just in, I will never
steal from my child.
[laughs]
I can't wait for you to feel
what it's like
to have to deal with a mini-you.
I am counting the minutes to it.
It'll be the redemption
of my life,
watching you fail.
And all those years
you thought you were telling me
things I didn't already know.
All right.
Lassie is spiraling.
We thought we were helping him
by looking into his visions,
but now we're concerned we're
just fueling his imagination.
- Okay, guys, come on, come on.
Now, look.
Carlton is one of the best cops
I've ever known.
He survived six bullets
and a stroke.
His body may be playing
catch up,
but his mind, it's as sharp
as I've ever known it.
Come on, let's face it.
He's never had much
of an imagination, right?
So when he says this guy
Wilkerson is faking it,
maybe you should do
the crazy thing...
Believe him.
Believe him?
Gus, you know what this means.
- We have to go full...
- Dirty...
- Rotten...
- Scoundrels.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- Afternoon, Wilkerson.
- How you doing?
- We're new here.
Name's Shawn Spencer.
This is my partner,
L'Eggo My Eggo.
- No.
- Norman Brownbutter.
Try again, Shawn.
- Dijon Hounsou?
- Accepted.
Why are you rejecting
nicknames in front
of a comatose guy?
Because I'm a pro.
Penny for your thoughts, Vic.
- Save your pennies, Dijon.
I got this.
I see it, Jack Daddy.
You play it straight, huh?
Tough guy
from the old neighborhood.
Probably didn't even cry
when Liz Berkley
got addicted to speed
in "Saved By the Bell."
But guess what.
- Even tough guys...
- Are ticklish.
[gasps] Uh-oh.
Looks like a very bad boy
is about to get attacked
by the French tickler.
- Tickle, tickle, tickle.
- [laughs]
Give it to him, Gus.
Just give it to him.
Give it to him clean, please.
- Yeah, work it.
Prepare it.
Get in there.
Take off his sock, Gus.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
Come on, Wilkerson,
you know you can feel that.
Come on, man.
You're gonna break,
and when you do,
you can take the window
or the stairs.
♪ ♪
- Harder, Gus.
- Oh, it's about to get hard.
- Mm-hmm.
Aw, yeah.
Harder.
Harder, Gus.
- Gus, go hard!
- [grunting]
- Are you getting up in there?
- Oh, it's getting hard.
- Get up in there.
Finish it!
- I'm going hard, Shawn!
- Excuse me.
What are you two doing?
Oh, we're just visiting
Mr. Wilkerson here.
Why have you removed
his stocking feet?
Dr. Herschel,
we have reason to believe
that your Wilkerson is faking.
Yes.
- Faking?
Faking?
Yes.
This man suffers
from severe catatonia.
He has had imparity
of all bodily functions
for quite some time.
We're not even sure he's going
to recover at all,
and you're tickling his feet?
- Well, that's a regional term.
Gus prefers "playing football."
Ow.
- Ah.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
At first, I thought you two
had this harmless, idiotic
Ren and Stimpy thing...
- Stimpy.
- Going.
Now, you're proving
to be dangerous.
I want you out.
Shawn, Gus, what is going on?
- Dolores, great.
I can explain.
Have you ever seen
"Dirty Rotten Scoundrels"?
Oh, we talking, like, you and I,
like a Netflix and chill
scenario?
Nurse O'Riordan, kindly
escort these two pedofetishers
off the premises and then attend
to Mr. Wilkerson
and examine his feet
for signs of violation.
Violation?
Get your hands off
that man's eyeball.
[clears throat]
There is a sign
marked "exit."
It is marked "exit"
for the purpose of exiting.
Find it, use it.
Gentlemen, my dander is rising.
[uneasy music]
I don't really know what to say,
but I guess you guys
should probably come with me.
Oh, come on, Dolores.
You don't think maybe
there's another reason
that dude just got
a dander boner?
Maybe the "Good Doctor"
isn't so good,
and we're on to him
and so is Lassiter.
On to what?
Dr. Herschel's an incredible
doctor and humanitarian,
who took on Carlton's case
at his own expense.
What does that mean,
like, for free?
- That's just bad business.
- [scoffs]
Okay, you know what?
Feel free to reach out
for updates,
but at this point,
I see no other option
than for you guys to stay away.
Good-bye.
[sultry music]
- What is that?
That's surreal.
I'm... I don't...
Shawn, we're done.
I need to get a hold of Selene
before she turns me
into a voodoo doll.
Nope.
What we need to do is get back
into that hospital
and help Lassie.
Why can we never just reach
the end of the line?
Because we're close, Gus,
and we need eyes
on Dr. Herschel.
What is that?
That is called plan B.
Arrival papers
and a security pass
for renowned touring trauma
specialist Dr. A.V. Catalon
from Cuba.
Now, he could pick
them up himself,
but I suspect he's gonna get
a phone call later...
[gasps]
Canceling his trip.
Who do we know in
the whole wide world
that could possibly
take his place?
- Who?
- Oh.
- What?
- We.
[imitates whipping noise]
[imitates sizzling]
Oh, my gosh.
This is why I needed
my mustache collection, Gus.
[coughs]
[in Cuban accent]
Hello.
My name is Amerigo Vespucci
Catalon Estevez.
- And you killed my father.
- No.
- Yes.
- Yes, you did.
- I did not.
- Prepare to die.
- It's not gonna work, Shawn.
- Are you kidding me right now?
This is a lock.
I'm virtually unrecognizable
to myself.
Somebody in here?
[acoustic Latin music]
[speaking Spanish]
I'm going into your dad's office
and I am calling the police.
I know what you're thinking:
"Does he have a plan C?"
No, he does not.
But does he have a plan D?
[in Cuban accent]
Yes.
[dramatic Latin music]
♪ ♪
Woody, the mustache is
spectacular.
From my lip to God's ears.
Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
Did you get the materials?
Do you need us to fill
you in on anything?
I studied everything about
him on the plane.
I know exactly who this guy is.
I know what makes him tick,
what excites him,
his biggest fears.
I like that very much,
but, Woody,
for our purposes here,
we should probably focus
on the type of medicine
he practices
and how he helps the patients
at this facility.
I must disagree to disagree,
Shawn.
Sure, that will come into play
down the line, yes.
But more importantly,
how does Catalon feel
about his mother
and her unriddling dominance
over him and his seven siblings?
He's an only child.
In his mind, yes,
but that's how he managed
to survive
in a world he distrusted
and the loss of the only woman
he had ever loved, Esmerelda,
hostess at the tobacco farm
where he spent
his formative summers.
Editor's note: His bicycle had
a banana seat.
- None of that is in here.
- [laughs]
Well, of course it isn't,
dear, simple Gus.
But that doesn't make it
any less true in here and here
and just a little down here.
I feel woozy.
Woody, I need you
to concentrate, man.
We need you on the inside,
and we really need this to work.
Shawn, I am calm.
I am collected.
Not since Ben Affleck in,
well, anything,
has an actor been more prepared
for a role in his life.
- You're not an actor.
- You're barely a coroner.
You planning on doing an accent?
[in Cuban accent] Yes, I am.
- Less is more.
- A lot less.
- Guys, I got this.
[clicks tongue]
Adios, hombres.
♪ ♪
Is he doing a limp?
You're doing a limp?
I got this.
♪ ♪
Buenos tardes, señorita,
or young lady.
I am Dr. Amerigo Catalon
from the island country
of Cuba reporting for work.
Dr. Catalon, wonderful.
Could you just spell that
for me?
- No.
No, I cannot.
Okay.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
You're gonna do great.
I know.
These were marked urgent
for you.
Thank you.
I will check them
after my interview.
[exhales]
♪ ♪
Welcome, Karen.
It's exciting to be nearing
the conclusion of our search.
As you know, the process
has been an exhaustive one.
- Uh... oh.
[clears throat]
Yes, and thank you
for considering me
for such... such a... lofty...
I can't believe... it's an honor
just... just really
to... to be considered.
And I never thought
that I would reach
such a lofty...
I have to go.
Excuse me?
We're making our decision today.
- Oh, I know.
Um, choose Pradhan.
She's much more cut out
for this,
and this room is ridiculous.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[horse whinnies]
- Woody.
- Oh!
- What do you got for us?
Did you see Lassie?
- I got all his pills.
- Great job, man.
You were born to do
undercover work.
- I am deep in, guys.
- That's great.
Woody, can you hand us
the pills, please?
We don't wanna get caught
in here.
- Sure.
[chuckles]
Okay, I just want to point out
that you guys requested
that I take Lassiter's pills.
See, I thought you wanted me
to be the guinea pig on this,
but now I understand your way
is a much better plan.
And the good news is,
they're time-release pills,
and I have one painfully lodged
in my throat,
but watch the problem solver
at work solving the problem.
[gagging and wheezing]
- [coughs]
- Come on, man.
[gasps]
Do you have a surgical glove
by chance?
Forty-three pairs... they also
come in wine and burnt pumpkin.
I'm a hoarder.
[groans]
Okay, first of all,
that's a Chiclet.
Wait, there's more.
[grunts]
What the...
Someone did not want us
to find this.
Bandages, stitches...
[sniffs]
Peroxide.
Dude, this is all
for an emergency patch job.
Somebody was coming here
for help on the down low
from a doctor.
Okay, great.
So which doctor was on duty
the night Lassie saw
the bloody guy?
- We were here that day.
Dr. Herschel.
[ominous music]
Guys, I could get
in huge trouble for this.
Dolores, all the pieces
are falling into place,
so Lassie could be
the next victim.
I cannot believe Dr. Herschel
could be a villain.
Really?
It's not like
he emanates warmth.
Okay, look, I will sneak
you in to protect Carlton,
but you cannot leave this room.
Of course, thank you, Dolores.
You're the best.
- Ice chips.
- Funyuns.
- You can get 'em both.
- Me?
Why do I have to risk
sneaking around?
- Jackal says what?
- What?
[smacks lips]
Man.
[stealthy music]
♪ ♪
Hey, Lass.
Quick ask, you know,
between two gentlemen.
When you first found out
that Marlowe was "with child,"
would you say that you were
overcome with joy
or was it more like
panic and confusion
and, um, a lack of oxygen?
Asking for a friend.
Eh.
Guster.
- Henry?
What are you doing here?
I need to see Shawn,
but first, you're gonna tell me
why he was having an extra
sensitive cow earlier.
- Something is going on.
- Oh.
- I know my son.
- No, mm-mm.
- Guster.
- Mm-mm.
Spit!
- Fine.
I'ma tell you one time.
Shawn, Juliet...
- "Eliminate hippies."
[chuckles]
Gus, don't you come in here
without those blue ice chips.
I'm gonna make you feed me
like a Jamaican baby bird.
What are you doing here?
And why are you looking
at me like that?
I think I might have crossed
a line back at the office.
I saw something
that I'd never seen.
I think I hurt you.
- No.
No, you didn't hurt me.
Maybe just a little.
- That's not possible.
I'm impervious.
Shawn, look.
Being a dad, it isn't easy.
Is this your version
of an apology?
Shawn, would you let me finish?
It isn't easy, but it may be
the best thing a man can do
in his entire lifetime.
Look, what I'm just trying
to say is
that if you're so lucky,
you'll see the day
that your kid is born.
No... whenever that happens.
Your heart, it goes from being
inside your chest
to outside your body
to this other being
it attaches itself to,
who now owns it.
And it swings around
like a frickin' tether ball.
Boom.
[chuckles]
You never get it back
and that's the torture.
And I recommend it highly.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
Yeah, well, I don't know
if it's recommended for me.
All due respect, Dad,
I'm not like you.
- No.
Oh, no, you're not.
♪ ♪
And that's why you'll be
better than me.
♪ ♪
This is weird and uncomfortable.
- Yeah, weird.
How can I help?
Well, I'm supposed to finish
this list of errands for Lassie.
There are 93 items
and I'm on number two.
Who the hell writes this small?
- Uh... that is really small.
Let me show you something.
You can use the camera.
You click that and then pinch.
[clicks tongue]
zhoop.
- Ooh.
- Magnification.
That is sweet Daddy blue eyes.
[chuckles]
Wait.
What is that indentation?
"Silent partner."
Dad, he wrote "silent partner,"
and that's the date
of the shooting.
That's why he went
to the warehouse,
to meet with the victim.
Do you think
you could get this...
- Analyzed?
- Yeah.
- I'll be back in two hours.
- Great.
We'll stay here and watch
Lassie, like real men.
- I got greedy, Shawn.
I took everything.
I sure hope none of
these patients get dry mouth.
- My God.
Is that a bundt cake?
The nurse's lounge
was unlocked too.
- Did you bring forks?
- Come on, son.
And we're back.
- Thanks, Dad.
[sighs]
Sweet.
That looks unusually moist.
- Ow.
- That's yours.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[snoring]
[all snoring]
[distant gurgling
and spluttering]
Gus, goo-gooing
in your sleep again.
Knock it off.
[gurgling and spluttering
continues]
♪ ♪
[gurgling]
What the...
[toy squeaking]
[gurgling]
Mary?
What?
What the hell are
you doing here, man?
- I'm a baby, Shawn.
It's glorious.
I just finished teething.
Hey, have you
ever been swaddled?
It's like a joyful
mummification.
[gasps]
- What is that?
Why are you doing that?
Hey, could you do a quick pivot
and get me out of this diaper?
Because I just filled it,
and I am a little uncomfortable
with how right that felt to do.
- Okay.
Okay.
I see what's going on here.
I got news for everybody.
I don't know how to change
a diaper, okay?
I'm not ready for you.
I don't care what my dad says.
- [toy squeaks]
- And what does that mean?
Let's talk about that.
Let's unpack that.
What it means is that
I get why you're here,
but the only thing I know
about fatherhood is
what I learned from all eight
episodes of "Manimal."
What I need to know is,
where do you land
on the whole
nurture versus nature thing?
I.e. might you offer up
your teat?
I absolutely will not.
- [groans]
How 'bout a lullaby, then?
Something in G major maybe,
if it suits you, sir.
All right, but if I sing to you,
will you go to sleep,
you strange little baby-man?
That's the idea.
- ♪ So, kid ♪
- ♪ May I please ♪
♪ No, you can't
have this teat ♪
♪ Such a tease ♪
- ♪ So, kid ♪
- ♪ Just a squeeze ♪
♪ It's just a figure
of speech ♪
♪ Would you please go to sleep ♪
♪ How can I fall asleep? ♪
♪ When I can't have this teat ♪
♪ But you can't have
this teat ♪
[snores]
[shushes]
- Shawn.
- [shushes]
Who are you gently
and sweetly singing with?
- Gus!
Oh, you look beautiful.
I'd hug ya,
but my nappy's packed
and I could spit up
at any second.
Do you wanna hear
something funny?
Gus can totally change a diaper.
You must be
out of your damn mind.
My point is simply
that you have been ready
for fatherhood your whole life.
You dated a woman with a kid.
You accidentally abducted
some other kid.
All you have to do is copy
what your dad did with you,
because look how you turned out.
- [scoffs]
- [spits]
That was really sweet, you guys,
in a extremely convoluted way,
but two questions.
One, is there a ladybug
looking over my shoulder?
And two, is there anything else
that you could please
put me in,
so I'm not bouncing here
in my own poop cage?
I don't want to belabor
the point,
but it is getting sloppy.
Whoo!
Have you guys ever seen blue?
Aww.
Gus, are you seeing
what I'm seeing?
- Wilkerson?
We got jackaled.
[suspenseful music]
Now, that would be huge
if I wasn't dreaming.
Mary, let me ask you... Mary?
♪ ♪
[exhales]
Oh.
[groaning]
- Gus, what is this?
Why are we doing this?
He's resisting, Shawn!
- Get off of me!
- Are you sure?
It seems a bit one-sided.
He's a merman!
He's a merman, Shawn with gills!
I can't hold him down
on account of his slippery,
scaly epidermis!
What is wrong with you two?
Excuse me, sir.
Are you or are you not a merman?
No, I'm not a frickin' merman!
- Gus.
Gus!
No gills.
[both panting]
So let me get this straight.
You've just been pretending
this whole time?
No, not the whole time.
I mean, I still have
some numbness on my right side,
but I can get around, obviously.
And you can't tickle for crap.
- Why are you doing this?
Is this an insurance thing?
And is that a cactus
growing out of your head?
No and no
and stop touching my scar, man.
- I gotta wake up.
Wake up, Gus.
- Gus.
- Wake up, come on.
- Gus, Gus, Gus!
- What?
We're not sleeping, dude.
I think baby Mary
was a hallucination.
I'm pretty sure Wilkerson's
the real deal,
but we're tripping on something.
No, not something, psychotropes.
You suddenly feel like
you wanna confess something?
Yeah.
I used to have a major thing
for Jewel,
even after the Civil War movie
and the Bollywood song.
I mean, the tooth
and the van story,
she could yodel...
Somehow they're getting them
into the patients' meds.
I stopped taking mine,
but it didn't help.
[crunching]
Carlton may have seen a zombie.
[quacks]
Did you know there are bodies
in your fields?
Oh, gosh, it's the ice chips.
- What?
- Oh, that's just diabolical.
They know everything.
That's how they get you.
Hey, look, if they find out
that I'm still lucid,
I'm a dead man walking, okay?
I have money.
I can pay you guys.
But please don't give me up,
not after what they did
to my best friend.
- Devon Tileback?
- Yes, how'd you know that?
- We didn't.
- Until now.
You're the silent partner.
Tell us everything you know
and your truth
will be safe in the vault
of secrets.
Um, we had an IPO coming up
and, um, we were cooking
the books that the company...
- No!
- It was Tileback's idea.
- Shame.
- I just... I went along with it.
The lying was killing me.
I was having panic attacks.
And the next thing you know
I'm recovering here
from a stroke.
And apparently
I spilled everything
to Herschel during therapy,
because a few days later,
a guy shows up
at our office saying
he knows everything.
And he offers to keep
his mouth shut for a price.
A steep price.
Tileback played along
for a little while,
but once the IPO was announced,
they wanted to bleed us dry.
Tileback tried
to secretly meet up
with Chief Lassiter,
and they shot the Chief.
They tracked Tileback down
and they cut off his hand
as a warning.
He tried to disappear,
but they found him
and then they killed him.
- Who is "they"?
- I don't know, I don't know.
They have someone working
on the outside,
doing all their dirty work
so that they can't be connected
to the recovery house.
Devon was so scared
and now he's dead.
And I will be too
if they ever see me walking.
Then why are you packing up
your stuff and leaving?
Because obviously, it's not safe
for me here either.
Hey, hey, hey.
Your secret is safe
in the vault of secrets.
Redundant.
From one jackal to another,
sit tight until we figure out
who's on the outside,
because that's the guy
who shot the chief of police.
[indistinct voice]
- It's Herschel and his twin.
- What?
There's one guy standing
over there, Gus.
How many of those ice chips
did you eat?
I just ate the last one.
You kept eating them
after we knew
they were laced
with hallucinogens?
- I can't help it, Shawn.
I run island hot.
- Ha!
Dr. Hersch... Woody!
- Well, hey, guys.
How are we doing?
What are you two
still doing here?
I get to cover the night rounds
for Dr. Herschel.
Dr. Herschel's gone?
Tell me that isn't the guy
I was supposed to be watching.
You know, not to pile
on the criticisms, Woody,
but we're actually trying
to close up this case quietly,
which means keeping
the evidence hidden
until we know who
the outside triggerman is.
- This is new stuff.
- What?
Yeah, I went looking
for that Chiclet I coughed up...
You know, five day rule
and all...
I saw that we missed
some of the hidden bandages.
Wait a minute.
Is this a smoky topaz-brown
earmuff or am I imagining it?
I don't know anybody who
would wear a bloody earmuff.
Gus, I know where
the outside man is.
Shawn, will you get
your hand off my knee?
[crunches]
Gus, for the last time.
Someone from this ice bar
went to the Herschel House
covered in blood
and got stitched up
mob doctor style.
Our highly skilled tracking dog,
along for the assist
with this earmuff,
is going to lead us
right to them.
Shawn, we've done
this routine before.
Do you not know the definition
of insanity?
Gus, please, I'm going to leave
the leash on this time.
- So?
- Morrissey, smell this muff.
[growls and chews]
Ow.
Good news, bad news.
What's the bad news?
He ate the earmuff.
What's the good news?
He clearly took on the scent,
Gus, body and soul,
and he will now lead us
to the owner of said muff.
Come on, son.
[barking]
I'll be damned.
- You're almost in, man.
Come on, come on.
[groans]
- What?
- Ah!
It took four minutes for you
to get inside that window.
Juliet Spencer O'Hara.
Shawn, I have never been
more angry with you.
- You can't be angry.
- Why?
Your blood pressure, obviously.
- What?
My blood pressure is fine.
What are you doing here?
We are trying to solve this case
so that you don't get busted.
We have evidence that the guy
Lassie thought he imagined
is actually real,
came from this place,
and is a VIP.
More importantly,
what are you doing here?
You shouldn't be alone.
I'm not alone.
I wasn't gonna let her
come here alone.
And where's this evidence?
- Currently?
Morrissey's stomach.
Or in his intestines.
By the way, it could come
back up at any time.
What's your lead?
Final bullet that shot Lassiter.
I found it.
And I found the gun
with the information
she didn't directly give to me.
- Nice, babe.
I'm proud of you.
Now, is there anything else
you'd like to say to me?
- Yes.
- Wait.
[fake sobs]
All right, I'm ready.
The slug was traced to
a rare Norwegian-made pistol
registered to Ova Asblorn.
- No, not that.
- Ova?
The bar owner?
[laughs]
No, no.
He's just a sweet retiree
enjoying the second chapter
of his life,
owning a mountaintop
watering hole.
We're talking about Ova Asblorn?
- Yes.
- The Butcher of Bodo?
The Butcher of what?
- No, Bodo, Bodo.
Purse your lips.
That's a dope nickname.
Unless he's an actual butcher.
Then it's a little on the nose.
No, Ova's a gunrunner,
a drug dealer, an extortionist,
ran a major crime syndicate
in Norway.
At least, before he almost died.
I used to run
a different business.
Please stop touching my scar.
- Oh, my gooshen, Gus.
Ova had a stroke.
He was a patient
in the Herschel House.
He's the outside man
and Lassiter's shooter.
Which means Dr. Herschel's
on the inside
digging out the dirty secrets
of his rich-ass patients.
Feeding them to Ova
on the outside
to shake down the victims.
Nobody ever put those two
together until now.
And we just figured out
the final piece.
- Nasty dance.
Wood on wood.
Nasty dance.
[barking]
- Guys.
- Morrissey?
Uh-oh.
[menacing music]
♪ ♪
I guess it's not Ova.
- It's Ova.
- Yeah, but it's not "ova."
Shawn, it's Ova.
Gus, this is
nowhere near "ova."
- It's Ova right there, Shawn.
- Guys.
[howling]
[barking]
Well...
That dog doesn't care
about anything.
[bangs]
Okay, we gotta get out of here.
[sinister music]
♪ ♪
Oh, come on, dude.
Did you just put
on a dead man's earmuffs?
He can have them back
whenever he wants them back,
Shawn.
Got him.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Per... Pern... Per...
- What am I looking for?
- [purrs]
I have to roll the R like that?
Yes.
- [exaggerated trill]
Per, listen to me, man.
- I see it.
- That's Per. He's my son.
He's already displeased
with me and my career choices.
Your dad, sweet old Ova, right?
He suddenly has a stroke
and then boom,
he wants to go down
the straight and narrow, huh?
He wants to turn over
a new leaf and he gives up
the family business.
[speaks Norwegian]
- What?
- What are you saying?
I waited my whole life
for my moment.
Right, fathers,
they disappoint us, man.
That's what they do, trust me.
I know.
Sometimes, in very rare cases,
the hospitals
that care for them use
their secrets
to blackmail their families,
right?
Well, they tried,
but I changed the deal,
made myself a partner.
[speaking Norwegian]
No, you're going
into Norwegian again, man.
We don't have the...
Your friend Lassiter,
he got too close.
I didn't think he'd make it
after I shot him.
[speaks Norwegian]
- Chief, help me out here.
What is he saying?
How should I know?
Aren't you Swedish or something?
No.
- Then did he see my face?
Did he remember anything?
Well, there was only one way
to find out.
Get him into the right recovery
home and watch him.
- Gus?
[gasps]
What are you guys doing
back here?
How many of you are there?
- Selene?
- Gus?
I went to the hospital.
I saw her, your nurse.
- What?
- Yeah.
You know, I don't hate her.
She's kind, pretty.
I mean, I really wish
she wasn't your choice...
- She's not my choice.
- No, just stay here!
- Stay here!
- Stop, stop, all of you!
There's only one way this ends,
so let's just get on with it.
- She dies first.
- Oh, no, you won't!
Shawn, step back!
You will not shoot my wife.
She's pregnant.
- What?
- Jules, I know and I'm ready.
That's a lie.
I'm not ready.
I'm not even sort of ready,
but I mean, I figure
once the whole two-year
gestation period
plays itself out... I mean,
how far along are we?
Shawn.
I'm just trying to figure out
how much time we have.
I have.
We're not talking hours, right?
Like, nothing's gonna break
and start cascading, right?
Nothing like... [panting]
Shawn, if this some sort
of weird distraction move,
stop it.
Step out of the open!
I'm not gonna let you shoot
Shules' baby either.
What's a Shules?
You people are making
my head hurt.
Shawn, step out of the open
or I will shoot you myself.
I am not pregnant.
Can you two figure this out
in your own time?
Sweetheart, I get it,
you wanted to tell me yourself,
but I saw the pregnancy test
in your car.
- What?
- Excuse me.
Um, may I speak to my friends,
please?
Well, by all means.
Gus, I couldn't find you
for two days.
You went radio silent on me,
and I wanted to see
how you really felt about us
before I told you.
Told me what?
The pregnancy test is mine.
[gasps] Praise be.
[gasps]
Me.
[thuds]
- [grunts]
- [groaning]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I know you hate
the late night routine,
Carlton, but bottoms up.
Hey, I don't recognize
any of these pills.
Hmm?
Oh, that's 'cause those ones
are different.
Those are designed to make
you go to sleep forever.
And if you don't take them,
then I will just throw a shot
of this into your drip
and Bob will still be
your uncle, I'm afraid.
Go for it.
Oh, have it your way, Carlton.
That gorgeous black friend
of yours
and his sidekick are not
gonna make it back.
They were easy to manipulate.
Truth be told, I like you,
Carlton.
You got soft lips
and a chest full of hair
plentiful enough to wig
all of Destiny's Child,
so trust me when I say
this is the last thing
I wanted to do today.
How can you be mixed up
with something like this?
Mixed up?
Oh, right, this couldn't
possibly be my idea, right?
I mean, as a woman, I must have
been compromised
or forced to participate, right?
This was all my idea.
All my baby.
And that Boy Scout Herschel
couldn't be more oblivious.
And all you had to do
was lie there
and eat those ice chips, but no,
you and the get-along gang
just could not leave
well enough alone.
[tense music]
[exhales]
[gloves snap]
Open your eyes, Carlton.
You're not going anywhere.
I'm afraid I'm gonna have
to put my foot down.
I think I'm done.
I'm no good to anyone like this.
Can't think straight.
I can't walk.
I'm just so tired, Pop.
Aw, is it your daddy?
Is he back?
Well, you tell him
you're gonna see him very soon.
- So tired.
- Think about Marlowe.
Think about Lily.
They need you.
Like I needed you?
I am so sorry
that I wasn't with you,
but I promise I didn't miss
a single thing.
The day you caught
your first fish...
When you hit your first
and only home run,
it was a foul ball.
I know.
Well, I wasn't going
to tell anyone.
- I was dead.
- [laughs]
I'm so proud of you, Carlton.
You said you were gonna be fine.
You said Lassiters tough it out.
I never got to say good-bye.
Yeah.
It was supposed to be
a routine bypass.
It was a blood clot.
But you, you have a choice.
You are not done yet.
What if I don't get better?
How am I supposed to teach Lily
how to fly fish
with just one working hand?
You will get better,
so live for us both.
Be the husband and father
that I didn't get to be.
You gotta fight, Carlton.
Fight for your family.
Fight for your queen.
Just so tired, Pop.
Just let me sleep
for ten minutes.
Oh, that's it.
Sweet, sweet surrender.
It's all gonna be over soon.
Carlton, get up.
Don't give up, Carlton.
Open your eyes.
[solemn music]
[shushes]
Good-bye, Carlton.
[gun clicks]
[gasps]
[gunshot cracks]
That's my boy.
How did you get that gun
in here?
He actually has three.
One in the chair,
one in the fireplace,
and one right up his chute,
a little John Dilly.
Dad, I got this.
And I forgive you.
I'm sorry.
I just miss you so much,
and I'm damn proud
to be a Lassiter.
You have the right
to remain silent.
[indistinct radio chatter]
He can go by Danger,
he can go by Shaft,
He can go by Shafty,
he can go by De'Shaft.
That's God's comma.
Yes, it does... has
the God comma in it.
- Excuse me, Shawn.
- Yes?
Can I talk to my baby's daddy?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
- Come on, son.
How are you feeling,
my little chocolate chippy-chip?
Oh, I'm fine.
You know I didn't really
faint before.
I was just resting my legs.
- Yes, rest those legs.
- Mm-hmm.
Now listen.
I know all of this happened
very fast.
Yes.
So, Burton Guster...
- Will you...
- Oh, timeout.
Uh, Selene, I think
you've flipped-flopped
the situation here.
- Shawn.
- You're ruining everything.
This is exactly how
I imagined it would go.
I'm gonna be a godmother.
- Chief.
- Hmm?
She's my best friend.
[shushes]
So, Burton Guster,
will you make me
the happiest woman
on this planet,
on Ares and Pluto...
- And Pluto?
- And marry me?
Yes, I will do that.
[both squealing]
- Now...
- Ooh.
Selene, will you marry me
and protect me from spiders
and polar bears and...
agree to live next door
to Shawn and Jules
and have connecting pools
in our backyards
and a lazy river running
through our living rooms?
- Oh, that's a ton to unpack.
- It is.
- You know what?
Yes, I will!
- Yes!
- What?
[laughter]
Aww, ooh, yeah.
[both squeal]
[both moaning]
Sure you're not upset
about the whole no kid thing?
- What?
Oh, not even a little.
- Oh, I love you.
- Oh, yeah.
- You're my person.
- Yeah.
Mwah.
Now, we just have one tiny,
little detail to iron out.
- What's that?
- I'm still married.
- What?
- Don't worry about it.
- We'll figure it out.
- What?
[squeals]
[cheering]
[upbeat music]
How's it feel?
Blessed be the fruit, huh?
♪ ♪
all: Yay, yay, yay, yay!
You guys, uh...
You guys go ahead.
I'm gonna stay behind.
Wait, here?
Yes.
I spoke to Butterfly.
She just wants me
to live my best life.
Also, she hates me.
I think this is where
I'm meant to be.
From now on,
I will be Dr. Catalon,
and you two are sworn
to keep my secret.
- Excuse me, Dr. Catalon.
- Oh!
I'm sorry to say
I'm a bit flummoxed.
There appears to be someone
here claiming to be you.
Oh, really?
[chuckles]
Gentlemen, the door.
Carlton, that is what
they call a collar's collar.
And I knew the second
they admitted you to
this beautiful facility
that, someday,
you'd find a way to discharge
your weapon inside.
Thank you, both of you.
- What for?
- How much time you got, Henry?
So, are you ready
to see Marlowe?
The question is,
is she ready to see me?
Oh, I think she's ready
to see you.
Oh, O'Hara, I made her go away.
I know you did.
I couldn't stand the thought
of her seeing me like this
one more day stuck in that bed
and stuck in this chair.
That woman's the greatest thing
that's ever happened to me.
- Agree.
- To agree.
[hopeful music]
♪ ♪
Hello, my love.
- Stop.
Please.
♪ ♪
I-I'm sorry.
Did I...?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[inspiring music]
[shaky exhale]
♪ ♪
[sniffles]
- Hi.
♪ ♪
I just wanted
to look my wife in the eye
when I said,
"Let's go home."
[gasps]
[laughs]
♪ ♪
I love you so much, baby.
- I love you.
I love you.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
Bye, Pop.
[devious music]
- There he goes!
- Hey, hey!
- Hey, wait up!
- Sir... sir, stop!
♪ ♪
[whimsical music]
♪ In Paris, they are free ♪
♪ In Stockholm, they roam ♪
♪ In Denmark, they wear
little clogs on their paws ♪
♪ They have no fear of death ♪
♪ They don't steal
children's breath ♪
♪ That's a rumor
concocted by dogs ♪
♪ Ah, the cats, the cats,
the cats ♪
♪ Round and round they go ♪
♪ Call them gato or chat ♪
♪ Tell you I will not ♪
♪ I will not throw away
mon chat ♪