♪ ♪ ♪
[Peeing]
[Toilet flushes]
♪ ♪ ♪
[Moaning, heavy breathing]
[Moaning]
Sorry, I didn't understand you.
I don't speak French.
Do you speak English?
Yes, a little. Not very good.
That's what every
French person says.
But it's true, no?
No.
Bonne morning.
Good morning.
Do you want to have a shower?
Well, I guess I could use one.
Yes, me too.
[Shower running]
So, where did you do these bruises?
Oh, it's from a movie.
I did a fight scene.
You should be careful with
your home movies,
Mister James Bond.
Where am I, by the way?
Paris.
Yeah, I know that. But where?
Umm, Monmartre.
Uhh, Pigalle.
Do you know Pigalle?
No.
Sacre-Coeur?
Moulin Rouge? Moulin Rouge?
Oh, Moulin Rouge.
Yeah.
That's something I know.
You've heard about Moulin Rouge?
Yeah.
I saw the movie.
It's a place first.
It was a place, before
being a movie.
It's right here.
You can see it from the balcony.
Really?
I think you're clean.
Okay.
I like water. I like air, too.
You like what?
Air, air.
I like elements.
Water, air, wood.
Oh, where are my clothes?
What clothes?
I do hope I had some
on last night.
I'm joking.
I washed them.
They're drying.
They should be dry.
Here. All nice and clean.
And here is everything that
was in the pockets.
Oh, just like in prison.
Excuse me?
Well, I haven't actually been
in a real prison.
Just, you know, in the movies.
Don't worry, I didn't take anything.
I just looked through it to
see if you had
an address, or name.
Yeah, well, I don't carry
anything important
around with me.
I'm losing everything!
Wait - you don't know who I am?
No. You didn't tell me your name.
You were very drunk last night.
You had no identification on you,
and I didn't know where
you were staying,
so I brought you here.
Yeah, I was completely wasted.
Wasted?
Very drunk.
So, what's your name?
Mine is Claude.
My name? Brad.
My name is Brad.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Nice to meet you, Claude.
Nice to meet...
What? This is how we do it
in France, right?
Yes, of course.
What's this weird accent?
Funny.
My accent?
You find my accent funny?
Yeah, where does it come from?
Arizona, I guess.
Yeah. Let's say Arizona.
Are you in a hurry?
Well - no, actually.
Great! How about some breakfast?
Sounds great.
I think I have some eggs, and
maybe some sausages, too.
Sounds good.
Do you have croissants?
No croissants. Coffee?
Yes, please.
Do you have a cigarette?
No, I don't smoke.
What? You don't smoke,
have sausage and eggs for breakfast
instead of croissants?
What's next, are you going to
tell me you don't drink wine?
No, I don't drink much wine.
Are you sure you're French?
Yeah, of course.
Joking.
And you are American, so what
are you doing here?
Having sex, and smoking, and drinking?
Shouldn't you be shooting a
gun somewhere,
and going to church?
Wow, you do know American well.
Yeah, I lived there for one year.
Oh yeah? When?
It was a long time ago.
I was your age.
I was in Texas. San Antonio.
Why?
I had a love there.
The one true love of my life.
So I moved there to
live with him.
I think that's when I started having
streak and eggs for breakfast.
So what happened?
It just ended.
I moved back to Paris.
I've never gone to
America since then.
That's too bad.
It's okay.
Like I said, it was a long time ago.
It's romantic, though.
Running away to be with
your true love.
It's impractical, though.
I suppose.
I've never been in love.
Never?
No. Not yet, at least.
So what brings you to Paris?
I am... I'm here with my friends.
We came on a college trip.
I'm here for another week.
So it's your first time in Paris?
Yeah.
I was here as a kid, but that
doesn't really count.
What do you think of Paris?
So far?
I love it.
[Knock on door]
Who is that?
I don't know.
It's my friend.
No, no, no!
What are you doing?
Don't answer it!
I have to, it's my friend.
Don't worry, I'll get rid of her.
Goodbye, Mister America!
She's gone.
I should get going.
It's okay, she won't be back.
She's harmless.
A little crazy, but harmless.
No, it's not her. It's just that...
I have to meet my friends.
I don't want to be late and
have them worry.
Finish your breakfast, at least.
Thank you.
Thank you for breakfast, and...
And everything.
I really should run.
Bye.
Are you doing anything later?
No, I don't have plans.
Great! So...
How about dinner?
I could be here by 9ish.
Yes, that could be nice.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
Great. Okay.
Umm, what about my hat?
Do you have it?
Thanks!
What about my sunglasses?
Yeah - I'm very sensitive to the sun.
See you tonight?
Alright.
Hello?
♪ ♪ ♪
Thank you!
[Door closes]
♪ ♪ ♪
Catherine...
Aww, baby.
No?
♪ ♪ ♪
[Knocking]
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
Oh, it's you.
The shy American.
You're late.
I know, I...
Shhh!
Come in.
I was just leaving.
Turn around!
Come in, come in, come in...
He's up there.
Don't break his heart.
♪ ♪ ♪
Good morning.
Hung over?
Yes.
It's all your fault.
Where were you?
I'm sorry, I was running late.
My friends... I couldn't get away.
I texted you.
I don't know how to get texts.
Why can't people just call?
You're sparkling.
Oh, yeah.
I was at a stupid party
with my friends.
I couldn't get away.
I'm staying with them.
Where is your phone?
How old is this thing?
It's from the '60s.
It's vintage.
See, here are all the texts I sent.
Uh-huh.
Oh, no! Stay in bed.
Let me take care of you.
Do you want some aspirin?
Yes.
Okay. Breakfast?
Look, I'm sorry.
Let's spend the day together.
I'm free. Are you?
It's Sunday, right?
Yes.
Then yes, I'm free.
This is for you.
I call them the "I'm sorry" flowers.
♪ ♪ ♪
Hey! What are you
doing out of bed?
I'm awake. Do you need help?
This is your aspirin.
Thanks.
But I'm afraid I'm rather
useless in the kitchen.
I can make coffee though.
It's okay - I have these.
Oh, croissants!
Oui oui, you are a French man!
♪ ♪ ♪
[Moaning]
[Phone ringing]
No, uh-huh, okay.
Who was that?
My mother, wishing me a
happy birthday.
You're kidding, right?
It's your birthday?
Yes.
No way!
Happy birthday!
Ow, thanks.
Oh, we should do something.
No, I can't. I have to go to work.
I have to go see my friends, too.
I hate birthdays.
We should do something special later.
Okay...
Don't think, don't think!
You can't say no, you can't say no...
[Laughing]
♪ ♪ ♪
So, why did you want to meet here?
This is where we first met.
No - actually, it was over there.
In the gutter.
Oh, well... I was kind of, you know....
Out of it.
A bit.
Let's go to a bar.
No. Enough with bars.
Let's go for a walk.
Your choice! Show me Paris!
♪ ♪ ♪
Why are you shaving?
I like your beard.
Don't worry, it will grow back again.
Don't you think I look younger?
Brad: Well, I
wouldn't say that.
Brad: What about mine?
Brad: Does it make
me look older?
Claude: No.
Shut up, old man!
Happy birthday!
Careful, you're going to
make me cut myself!
Brad: It's okay. I like scars.
Claude: So, you must be
disappointed.
Because my skin is perfect!
Yeah, you think so.
Did you find some
imperfection somewhere?
Brad: No, not at all...
...Elephant Man!
♪ ♪ ♪
[Door unlocks, opens]
[Text message tone]
"I am sorry.
Please don't hate me."
"I don't really know
how to explain."
"I'm sure you know
everything now,"
"about who I really am,"
"but the truth is, when I
was Brad, with you,"
"that is who I really am."
"That is the real me, but he
doesn't exist anymore."
"He loved you, but he can
never see you again."
"Love, Brad."
[Crying]
Hello, Claude?
Oui?
Mind if I sit down?
Do you speak English?
Yes, a little.
Great.
My name is Michael.
I'm Aaron...
Um, Brad's manager.
I hate to meet you under these
circumstances, but...
I'm gay myself,
so I understand what
you're going through.
The thing is, um,
Aaron - or Brad...
Signed a contract which had
a morals clause.
And it's a very big film, a
very big part of a franchise,
so, with this morals clause,
if anything were to get out in
the press about him being...
Um, not to the
studio's liking,
and let's just say they're a
very conservative studio,
it could really hurt Brad.
He would be fired.
He could be sued, even.
Because of something like this.
So, I have some form for you.
It's a confidentiality
agreement, there's that,
there's a prepared statement
we've written for you,
which basically states that
nothing happened
between the two of you.
It would be really great if
you could sign these for me.
Um, I have a pen here...
If you could just sign here,
and... here.
Here as well.
And... here.
That would be so... we'd
really appreciate it, so much.
And Aaron really
appreciates this, as well.
I mean, Brad.
[Cell phone ringing]
I'm sorry, I have to get this call.
I hope you don't mind.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll be there in five minutes.
No, it's not a problem.
Okay, yeah.
Okay, see you in five minutes.
This weather here is just
terrible for my allergies!
Oh.
Oh, make sure to sign
this one, too.
Yes, thank you.
And Brad thanks you, too.
So, um... great.
And we have your contact
information, so...
Here's my card.
Feel free to call me anytime.
I'll be sure to have tickets for you,
for the premiere here in Paris.
And if you're ever in LA,
give me a call.
I'm behind the scenes, so I
have no morals clause.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you again.
And I'm sorry to bother you.
[Cheering]
[Horror film music,
wolves howling]
♪ Pop music ♪
[Sigh]
♪ ♪ ♪
[Knocking]
Your movie sucked.
I know.
But it's going to make
a lot of money.
Can I come in?
I'm sorry.
Yes, I know.
You are drunk, so you come
crawling back here...
No. I mean, yes, I'm drunk.
But that's not why I came back here.
And why did you come back here, Brad?
Or is it Aaron?
Actually, my real name is Scott.
Scott Aaron.
But I had to change it
to Aaron Davis,
because there was already
as Scott Aaron
in the Screen Actors Guild.
Great!
I'm even more confused now, thanks.
[Cell phone vibrating]
I'm shutting it off.
Cheers, Scott...
Aaron...
Brad.
I came back here for you.
What am I going to do with you?
Whatever you want.
♪ ♪ ♪
[Moaning]
How long are you in Paris for?
I was just here doing press
and publicity for the movie.
My flight is at 8:00 AM.
Oh, I see.
Hey, come to LA with me.
Are you crazy?
Yes, I am.
I can buy your ticket.
You can stay with me.
I don't think so, thanks.
I dropped everything and moved
to the States before.
It didn't work.
Yeah, but that was Texas!
This is LA.
It's still not Paris.
This is where I live, where I belong.
I can't just leave myself behind.
Besides, I don't think your manager...
He's not my manager anymore.
I do what I want from now on.
Until...
It was really nice to see you again.
I think you should get going.
I'm sure you have packing to do.
Can I stay here until my flight?
Yes, I suppose.
What time do you have to leave?
Set the alarm for 5:00 AM.
Yes, it should be.
[Alarm clock ringing]
[Alarm clock stops]
♪ ♪ ♪
langeect
Closed captions by Michael
Vassallo for TLA Releasing.