[children laughing
in distance]
[woman announcing
in Mandarin on PA]
[indistinct chatter]
[announcement continues]
[cell phone vibrating]
[Nai Nai speaks Mandarin]
[Billi] Nai Nai, hi!
[conversing in Mandarin]
[Nai Nai speaking]
[indistinct announcement
on PA]
[stammering]
[in English] Do you have
a second to save marine life?
[speaks in Mandarin]
- All right.
- [in English] I was gonna say
something snarky,
but I used to work this job.
Ooh, what happened, girl?
You got fired?
I quit! Because I was
about to get fired.
- [both laugh]
- [Nai Nai speaking Mandarin]
- [announcement continues]
- Hey.
[stammering]
Okay.
[machine whirring]
[radiologist speaking]
[indistinct conversation]
[Haiyan in English] So one
day, the wife goes out of town.
And when she returns,
the husband says,
"Honey, the cat is dead."
And she says,
"How can you tell me
so abruptly like this?"
You have to ease me
into bad news.
Like, um, "Honey, the cat..."
"he got on the roof.
"And, uh, so..."" [chuckles]
Now...
a few months later,
the wife
goes out of town again.
And she returns
and the husband
greets her again.
But this time,
he learned his lesson.
And as the wife comes
through the door, he says,
"Honey, your mom,
she got on the roof."
[all laughing]
[continues conversing
indistinctly]
[door opens]
[objects clatter]
[wings flapping]
How did you get in here?
[cell phone vibrating]
- Nai Nai.
- [Nai Nai] Billi!
[Nai Nai speaking Mandarin]
[Nai Nai chuckles]
[Mr. Li] Huh?
[Mr. Li] Oh.
[Billi speaking]
[Nai Nai speaking]
[sighs]
[Billi speaking]
[chuckles]
[Nai Nai] Eh?
[Nai Nai speaking]
[in English] Okay.
I love you, Nai Nai.
I love you. I love you.
[siren blaring in distance]
[car alarm blaring
in distance]
For what month?
For this month? May?
And what happened to April?
My mom says
you didn"t pay April yet.
[sighs]
You know,
if you moved out right now,
we could literally
double the rent?
[Jian] So what,
you"re broke again?
Are you always
going to live like this?
Poor but sexy, I hope so.
Why you not try to save, huh?
You should change
your expensive lifestyle.
Mom, if you"re gonna
give me shit
every time I come home,
I"m not coming home anymore.
Lower your voice.
Dad"s sleeping.
Sleeping? It"s 6:00 p.m.
What"s wrong with him?
[Jian] Nothing.
He"s just tired.
Is he okay?
He"s fine,
we"re just busy that"s all.
[Billi] Busy with what?
What"s going on?
Hao Hao"s getting married,
so we have to go to China.
What? Since when?
Hasn"t he like just started
dating that girl?
You don"t need to go.
No one"s expecting you to go.
I mean,
he"s my only cousin.
Don"t you think
I should be there?
Okay, okay.
Do you think
he knocked her up?
[sighs]
How many wontons you want?
- Five.
- Five? That"s not enough.
[Billi] Make a dozen then.
Ten"s good.
- Okay.
- [cutlery clanking]
What"s wrong, Dad?
[Haiyan] Nothing.
You and mom
got in a fight?
You"ve been drinking?
Please tell me
what"s going on.
You"re scaring me.
Something"s going on.
Just tell me what"s going on.
Your Nai Nai"s dying.
She has
a stage four lung cancer.
The doctor says
she has three months.
Could be faster,
you never know.
- [Billi] I need to call her.
- You can"t do that.
- I need to go see her.
- Can"t do that.
She doesn"t know.
The family thinks
it"s better not to tell her.
So you can"t say anything.
I don"t understand.
She doesn"t have a lot of time
left, she should know, right?
There"s nothing they can do.
So everyone decided
it"s better not to tell her.
Why is that better?
Chinese people
have saying:
"When people get cancer,
they die."
It"s not the cancer that
kills them, it"s the fear.
Okay, when were you guys
gonna tell me this?
How could you
let me find out like this?
How should I have told you?
"Oh, your grandma"s on the roof"?
[sighs]
W-What about the wedding?
The wedding is an excuse,
so everyone can go see her.
We leave
first thing in the morning.
I need to go.
- [Haiyan] Billi...
- I need to go. [sniffles]
[Jian] Everyone thinks
it "s better if you don" t.
Look at you.
You can"t hide your emotions.
If you go, Nai Nai will
find out right away.
[sobs]
[all singing]
♪ Happy birthday to you
♪ Happy birthday, dear Tony
[inaudible]
[train approaching]
[man announcing indistinctly
on PA]
[drivers clamoring in Mandarin]
[instrumental music playing]
- [knocking on door]
- [muffled chatter]
[Mr. Li speaking Mandarin]
[Billi speaking]
[Mr. Li speaking]
[indistinct chatter]
[chatter stops]
- Billi!
- Huh?
[Nai Nai speaking]
[chuckles]
[Nai Nai chuckles]
- [Nai Nai exclaims]
- Shoulda called first.
[Nai Nai laughing]
[Billi] Mmm-hmm.
[Billi chuckles]
[oil sizzling]
[in English] Stop fooling around.
Oil is hot.
Don"t be mad, Mom.
Where"d you get the money
to buy a ticket?
- Credit card, right?
- [Billi sighs]
Mom, I"m fine.
Look at my face.
Look at my face,
look at my face, look.
[Jian] Take to table.
[all speaking Mandarin]
[Little Nai Nai speaks]
[Mrs. Gao speaking]
[Aunty Ling speaks]
[Nai Nai speaking]
[Nai Nai] Hey. Billi.
[Nai Nai laughs]
[muffled chatter
laughter]
[indistinct chatter]
[upbeat club music playing]
[indistinct announcements
on PA]
[Uncle Haibin speaks]
[Billi speaks]
[Billi, in Mandarin]
I know.
- [sighs] Billi...
- Hmm?
[lively chatter]
[Billi speaking]
[Michael speaking]
[both panting]
- [Billi speaks]
- Ah.
[Michael speaking]
- [Billi speaking]
- [switch clicks]
[Michael speaking]
[Billi panting]
[Billi] Uh...
[Michael] Ah.
[Billi speaking]
[Michael speaking]
- [Billi speaking]
- [door opens]
[Michael] Ah. Okay.
[stammers]
[Michael] Ah.
[in English] Thank you.
[metal rattling]
[rattling continues]
[Nai Nai shouts kiai]
[shouts kiai]
- [shouting kiais]
- [balls clacking]
[continues shouting kiais]
Ha! Ho!
Ha! Ha!
[Billi chuckles]
[Nai Nai laughing]
Ha! Ha!
[continues speaking
in Mandarin]
[both laugh]
[Nai Nai speaking]
Billi.
[Jian speaking]
[overlapping chatter
in Mandarin]
[chatter continues]
[Jian speaking]
[Nai Nai speaking]
[chatter]
[Nai Nai mocking]
[labored breathing]
[Haibin speaking]
[sighs]
[in English] So what "s
goin" on with the fellowship?
Nothing.
Oh, you still
haven"t heard anything?
No.
Well, when are they gonna
let you know?
I don"t know, Dad.
[sighs]
How are you
doing with money?
I"m fine.
- Can you afford this trip?
- Yes, I"m fine.
- You need help?
- No, I"m fine.
[Gu Gu speaking Mandarin]
[Billi in English]
What is mei nu?
- Uh, it means beauty.
- Ah.
[speaking Mandarin]
[sighs]
[Billi speaking]
[Gu Gu speaking]
[Billi"s masseuse speaking]
- [Billi speaking]
- Hmm?
[Gu Gu speaking]
[Gu Gu"s masseuse speaking]
[Gu Gu scoffs]
[photographer speaking]
[Nai Nai speaking]
[scoffs]
[Billi groans]
[photographer
instructing indistinctly]
Mmm? [chuckles]
[both chuckling]
[Nai Nai speaking]
[Nai Nai sighs]
[Billi speaking]
[Nai Nai clicks tongue]
[whining]
[Billi] Mmm.
- Huh?
- [in English] Okay.
[continues speaking Mandarin]
[Nai Nai clears throat]
[Yuping speaks]
[all toasting]
[Jian speaks]
[in English]
What"s that mean?
They say
you"re a stock investment
and you"re gonna make us
a lot of money.
[in English] But I can"t
expect that from you, right?
You"re the losing stock.
[Jian speaking Mandarin]
[Nai Nai speaking]
[Jian] Mmm.
[in English] Mom, that church
is not representative
of all America.
We have a lot of problems.
Guns, health care.
If you think
China"s that good,
why don"t you move here?
[speaking Mandarin]
[Nai Nai speaking]
[sighs]
[Jian speaking]
[scanner chimes]
[door opens]
[Nai Nai coughing]
[indistinct chatter]
[coughing]
- [continues coughing]
- [indistinct chatter]
[conversing indistinctly]
[Uncle Haibin
speaking indistinctly]
- [in English] What happened?
- I don"t know.
[shouting in Mandarin]
[Haiyan in English] Hey!
Billi, it"s the wrong way!
[Billi]
He says it"s fine.
- [Haiyan] We have to go around.
- [Billi] He says it"s fine!
[Billi] Watch it,
watch it, watch it.
[indistinct conversation]
[Billi] Which way are we going?
Dad, do you know
where we"re going?
- [Haiyan] This way.
- [Billi] My umbrella...
[indistinct conversation]
- [Billi] Is this the right way?
- [Haiyan] Yes.
[Billi] Are you sure?
[all continue arguing
indistinctly]
- [coughing]
- [Uncle Haibin] Ma?
[Nai Nai] Huh?
[speaking Mandarin]
[Little Nai Nai speaks]
[Nai Nai speaks]
[Nai Nai shooing]
Nai Nai...
[scoffs]
[inhales deeply]
[exhales deeply]
[coughing]
[Nai Nai speaking]
[in English]
Visit from America?
I went to school
in the UK for many years.
[Billi] Oh, that"s cool.
Where do you live?
Uh, I"m in New York.
New York.
I always wanted
to visit New York.
It"s a very beautiful city.
Yeah, it"s very beautiful.
Uh, question:
Do you know about
my grandma"s condition?
[speaking Mandarin]
[Nai Nai] Uh...
[whispers] Ma!
[in English] How bad is she?
You can tell me the truth.
[Doctor Song in English]
The cancer is quite advanced.
[Billi] Shouldn"t we tell her?
[Doctor Song] In her situation,
most families in China
would choose not to tell her.
When my grandmother
had cancer,
my family didn"t tell her.
Isn"t it wrong to lie?
[Doctor Song] I mean, if it"s for
good, it"s not really a lie.
[Billi] I mean,
it"s still a lie.
It"s a good lie.
How"s your grandmother?
She passed away, a few months
after she was diagnosed.
[speaking Mandarin]
[Nai Nai speaking]
[Doctor Song speaking]
[coughs softly]
[coughs]
[footsteps approaching]
[Haiyan speaking]
[indistinct announcement
on PA]
[in English] Illegal.
How do you say "illegal"?
[speaking Mandarin]
[Billi sighs]
[Haiyan sighs]
[indistinct chatter]
[Little Nai Nai] Ellen!
[Nai Nai speaking]
- [vocal-like yipping]
- [all exclaiming]
[chuckles]
[indistinct chatter]
[piano playing]
[playing faster]
[Jian speaking]
[Billi in English] Mom,
can we not do this right now, please?
[Jian speaking Mandarin]
- [Billi] Mom!
- [Haiyan speaks Mandarin]
[Billi in English]
Can we not right now?
[Haiyan speaks Mandarin]
- [scanner chimes]
- [Jian speaking]
[Billi in English]
Just leave him alone.
[Jian speaking in Mandarin]
[Haiyan grunting]
[scanner chimes]
[in English] Nai Nai should
not be organizing this wedding.
Well, if she enjoys it,
then just let her do it.
She"s sick.
She should be resting
or in a hospital.
Not stressing
about a fake wedding.
You really don"t know
your Nai Nai.
You know she enjoys
bossing everyone around.
Makes her feel important.
Makes her feel in control.
- Mom.
- It"s true!
That"s why she hated to stay
in America in our house.
You know? Because she could
not tell anyone what to do.
Whatever I do,
never good enough for her.
But she can"t say anything,
because it was my house.
Mom, stop!
What?
[speaks Mandarin]
You have always had issues
with her, but right now...
I don"t have a problem with her.
She"s the one that have a problem with me!
She "s dying. Can" t you be
a little more sensitive?
What you want from me?
To scream and cry like you?
You know, when my father died,
I also very sad.
But I don"t act like you.
When I went back to China
for the funeral,
everybody was watching me.
They all were expecting me
to fall apart.
And they think if I don"t
cry, I don"t love my father.
No one"s asking you to cry!
[Haiyan speaks Mandarin]
[in English]
I don"t like, you know,
put all my emotion on display.
Like I"m in the zoo.
But in here, if you don"t cry,
you don"t put a show,
they think that
you don"t love your family.
You know, in here,
they even hire some professional criers.
Just to show how sad they are.
It"s just so ridiculous.
I hate that.
[wailing loudly]
[continues wailing]
[speaking loudly in Mandarin]
[wailing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Gu Gu speaking]
[Nai Nai speaking]
[exclaiming]
[in English] Pour, just pour.
Yeah, pour, very good.
[speaks Mandarin]
[Billi] Mmm.
- Hey.
- [Haiyan grunting]
Hey.
[all laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
[chatter continues]
[Nai Nai speaking]
[Little Nai Nai speaks]
[Gu Gu speaks]
[Nai Nai speaking]
- [Nai Nai speaks]
- [Gu Gu speaks]
[Billi in English]
Hey, this looks so familiar.
[Haiyan speaks Mandarin]
[Haiyan in English]
Do you remember that house?
You used to love to play
in the garden.
[Billi] Where is it?
[Jian speaks Mandarin]
[Nai Nai speaking]
[coughing]
- [Billi in English] Dad?
- Hmm?
[door opens]
- Are you smoking?
- [Haiyan] Hmm?
Uh, I thought
you said you quit.
I did.
I will.
[speaking Mandarin]
[in English]
Go back to bed, Billi.
[speaking Mandarin]
[Haiyan sighs]
[Billi in English] What"re
you guys talking about?
Nothing.
[speaking Mandarin]
[Uncle Haibin sighs] Billi.
[sighs deeply]
[Hao Hao speaks]
[gasps]
- [in English] Mom?
- Yeah?
I want to stay in China
and help take care of Nai Nai.
[Jian] What?
You stay here, to do what?
You can"t cook,
you can"t clean.
[speaks Mandarin]
[in English]
I"ll figure it out, Mom.
[Jian] So you just stay here.
And what?
Wait for her to die?
What about the fellowship?
Just forget about it, huh?
You"re 30 years old,
but you can stop your life
and stay here?
And every day
she has to look at you,
with that sad-looking face?
That"s not nice
for anybody, right?
You know, one of the few good
memories of my childhood
were those summers
at Nai Nai"s.
They had that garden.
Ye Ye and I would
catch dragonflies.
[sniffles]
And then we just moved
to the States.
Everything was different.
Everyone was gone.
And it was just
the three of us.
[sniffles]
I know it was hard.
It was hard for us too.
[sniffles] I wanted to believe
that it was a good thing,
but all I saw
was fear in your eyes.
And I was confused
and scared constantly
because you never told me
what was going on.
And then Ye Ye died.
You didn"t even tell me
he was sick.
So it felt like he just
vanished suddenly.
And you wouldn"t even let me
go to his funeral.
You were at school.
We didn"t want you
to miss school.
We did what we thought
was best for you.
But I never saw him again.
And every time
I came back to China,
he just...
he just wasn"t there anymore.
[sniffles] And I come back
and he"s just gone.
The house is gone,
A Die"s gone,
our Beijing home is gone,
and soon she"ll be gone, too.
[exhales]
[all speaking Mandarin]
[drums and cymbals
playing loudly]
[indistinct chatter]
[Nai Nai] Billi!
[Nai Nai speaking]
[Little Nai Nai speaking]
[indistinct chatter]
[Sun Ao speaking over mic]
[lively chatter]
[indistinct chatter]
[exhales sharply]
[mic feedback whines]
[Uncle Haibin speaking]
[chatter stops]
[scattered chuckling]
[voice breaking]
[Uncle Haibin sniffling]
[all applauding]
[indistinct chatter]
[chuckles]
[in English]
Does everyone know?
[Haiyan] I think
most people don"t know.
But I"m not sure.
[Nai Nai exclaims]
[speaks Mandarin]
[speaking Japanese]
[speaking Mandarin]
[Aunty Ling speaking Mandarin]
[Aiko speaking Japanese]
[speaking Mandarin]
[guests applauding]
- [upbeat music playing]
- [indistinct chatter]
[speaking Mandarin]
[General Mu speaking]
[General Zhu speaking]
[chuckles]
[all laughing]
[laughing]
- [clears throat]
- [mic feedback whines]
[in Mandarin]
[man speaking Mandarin]
[in English] Thank you.
[guests applauding]
[in English] I"m sorry.
Sorry, how do you say
congratulations? Dad?
[both speaking Mandarin]
- [guests applauding]
- [in English] Thank you.
[both singing in English]
♪ And so I came to see her
♪ And listen for a while
♪ And there he was
♪ This young boy
♪ A stranger to my eyes
♪ Strumming my pain
with his fingers ♪
♪ Singing my life
with his words... ♪
[both singing in Japanese]
[speaking Mandarin]
[Aiko and Hao Hao continue
singing in Japanese]
- [exhales]
- [chuckles]
[upbeat music playing]
[all chanting in Mandarin]
[all exclaiming]
[groans]
[continues in Mandarin]
[speaking hesitantly]
[laughter]
[shouting in Mandarin]
[music continues]
[woman singing
operatically]
[operatic singing
continues]
[inaudible conversation]
[operatic singing
continues]
[Hao Hao sobbing]
[Uncle Haibin
speaking Mandarin]
[speaking Mandarin]
[Uncle Haibin speaking]
[all in unison]
[camera shutter clicks]
- [footsteps running]
- [door slams]
Hey. [speaking Mandarin]
Hey, hey, hey.
[man sighs]
[Billi sighs]
[chuckles softly]
- [knock on door]
- [door opens]
[Little Nai Nai speaking]
[sighs]
[Jian speaking]
[Billi grunts]
[car engine starts]
♪ O gather up the brokenness
♪ And bring it to me now
♪ The fragrance
of those promises ♪
♪ You never dared to vow
♪ The splinters
that you carry ♪
♪ The cross you left behind
♪ Come healing of the body
♪ Come healing
of the mind ♪
♪ And let the heavens hear it
♪ The penitential hymn
♪ Come healing of the spirit
♪ Come healing
of the limb ♪
♪ Behold the gates of mercy
♪ In arbitrary space
♪ And none of us deserving
♪ The cruelty or the grace
♪ O solitude of longing
♪ Where love
has been confined ♪
♪ Come healing of the body
♪ Come healing
of the mind ♪
♪ O see the darkness yielding
♪ That tore the light apart
♪ Come healing of the reason
♪ Come healing
of the heart ♪
♪ O troubled dust concealing
♪ An undivided love
♪ The heart beneath
is teaching ♪
♪ To the broken heart above
♪ And let the heavens hear it
♪ The penitential hymn
♪ Come healing of the spirit
♪ Come healing
of the limb ♪
♪ O let the heavens hear it
♪ The penitential hymn
♪ Come healing of the spirit
♪ Come healing
of the limb ♪
[horns blaring]
[train passing]
[sighs]
Ha!
[continues shouting kiais]
[speaking Mandarin]
[continues kiais]
[speaking Mandarin, laughing]
[man singing "Without You"
in Mandarin]
[man]
♪ I can"t live ♪
"♪ If livin" is without you ♪
♪ Can"t live ♪
♪ Can"t give anymore ♪
"♪ If livin" is without you ♪
♪ Can"t live ♪
♪ Can"t give anymore ♪
[chorus]
♪ I can"t live ♪
"♪ If livin" is without you ♪
♪ I can"t give anymore ♪
♪ I can"t live ♪
"♪ If livin" is without you ♪
♪ I can"t give anymore ♪
♪ Can"t live... ♪
[laughter, applause]
[woman singing light jazz]