[MAN]
I CAN SEE YOU.
SORRY.
IT WAS JUST ONE.
I SWEAR.
WHY HAVEN'T YOU LEFT
FOR THE REUNION ALREADY?
MAYBE I SHOULD JUST
STAY HOME TONIGHT.
IT'S GONNA BE GOOD
FOR YOU TO GET OUT
AND SEE ALL YOUR FRIENDS.
I HAVEN'T TALKED
TO ANYONE IN YEARS.
IT'S GONNA BE AWKWARD.
NO, IT'S NOT.
JUST PLEASE COME WITH ME.
I HAVE TO WORK.
I'M RUNNING THE COMPANY NOW.
EVERYTHING FALLS ON ME.
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO SCREW UP
YOUR FATHER'S LEGACY, DO YOU?
NO...
I DIDN'T THINK SO.
BUT I'LL MAKE YOU A DEAL.
WHAT'S THAT?
I'LL GO TO THE NEXT ONE.
THAT IS FIVE YEARS FROM NOW.
WHAT'S GONNA CHANGE?
[SIGHS]
WHAT'S MORE NOSTALGIC?
WALDEN OR EARLY BIRD?
PUT THAT AWAY TONIGHT.
[GRUNTS]
PLEASE.
WHAT IS THE POINT
OF ALL THIS?
DON'T YOU WANNA FIND OUT
WHAT ALL YOUR FORMER
CLASSMATES ARE UP TO?
BRAD STONE.
STUDIED ENGINEERING
AT STATE.
JUST GOT ENGAGED.
MARIANA TEMPLE.
ALSO ENGAGED,
AND PREGNANT.
I REALLY HOPE THAT'S WATER.
MAX KLEIN.
JUST TOOK OVER HIS
FATHER'S USED CAR LOT.
REALLY LIKES
CATS IN COSTUMES.
WEIRD.
SOCIAL MEDIA HAS RENDERED
THE HIGH SCHOOL REUNION
OBSOLETE.
HALF THESE PEOPLE MADE
MY TEENAGE YEARS
A LIVING HELL.
I'VE GOT A GREAT JOB.
I GREW INTO MY NOSE.
LET ME HAVE THIS.
DO WE REALLY HAVE
TO WEAR THESE?
YOU MIGHT.
YOU BLENDED.
I DID NOT.
YOU WERE VOTED
"MOST LIKELY TO MATCH
THE WALLPAPER."
I WASN'T VOTED ANYTHING.
EXACTLY. [LAUGHS]
NOW, COME ON.
I HAVE ENEMIES TO IMPRESS.
CAN'T BELIEVE I'M BACK
IN BATON ROUGE,
SURROUNDED BY PEOPLE
WHO DON'T CARE I EXIST.
IT'S LIKE I NEVER LEFT.
AT LEAST WE HAVE
ALCOHOL THIS TIME.
IS THAT KAREN?
[LAUGHS]
HEY.
IT IS.
AND IT LOOKS LIKE
SHE CAN USE A SAVE.
FAMILY EMERGENCY?
MM-MM.
TOO DRAMATIC.
DOUBLE-PARKED.
[GROANS]
HEY, KAREN.
HI.
HEY.
CUTE DRESS.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT,
BUT YOU'RE DOUBLE-PARKED.
I AM?
AND THE TOW TRUCK DRIVER'S
WIFE JUST WENT INTO LABOR.
OH. UH,
GOTTA GO.
THANK YOU.
SHOTS.
WHISKEY.
WHATEVER YOU HAVE.
THREE SHOTS.
NICE MOVE.
THE PREGNANT WIFE
WAS A BIT MUCH.
YEAH.
SHE WENT OFF SCRIPT,
SO...
JOSH.
UH, HI. I'M-- JESSICA.
OH, YEAH.
RIGHT. NAMETAG.
NO, NO.
I JUST REMEMBER.
I SAT BEHIND YOU
IN ALGEBRA 2.
YOU USED TO DOODLE
COMICS IN YOUR TEXTBOOK.
I WOULD LOOK
OVER YOUR SHOULDER
AND READ THEM.
THEY HELPED
PASS THE TIME.
HAPPY TO HELP.
[LAUGHS]
SO, HOW LONG
YOU IN TOWN FOR?
I, UH, HAVE A 6:00 A.M.
FLIGHT OUT
TOMORROW MORNING.
WELL, NEXT TIME
YOU'RE IN TOWN,
YOU SHOULD LOOK ME UP.
PAUL BARNES.
REALLY?
YOU MARRIED THE PROM KING?
YOU WIN THE REUNION.
EVERYBODY GO HOME.
WAIT. I THOUGHT HE WAS
ENGAGED TO REBECCA DREIDER.
WEREN'T THEY SUPPOSED
TO GO TO YALE TOGETHER?
I HATED HER.
PLEASE TELL ME
SHE CRIED WHEN
SHE FOUND OUT.
NO. IT'S NOTHING
LIKE THAT AT ALL.
SHE'S ACTUALLY STILL
REALLY CLOSE TO PAUL.
SHE WAS AT OUR WEDDING.
SO,
WHERE IS HE TONIGHT?
HE HAD TO WORK.
I'M GLAD YOU MADE IT.
ME TOO.
I REALLY MISSED YOU GUYS.
TO THE REUNIONS THAT
ACTUALLY MATTER.
HERE, HERE.
I'LL DRINK TO THAT.
I THOUGHT I'D FEEL
DIFFERENT COMING BACK HERE.
LIKE I'D FINALLY
FIT IN OR SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS SUCH A MESS
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
SWEETIE, NOBODY WAS
COOL IN HIGH SCHOOL.
[GIRL] DEFINITELY.
LET'S TOTALLY HAVE
AN AFTER PARTY.
EXCEPT MAYBE THEM.
BUT THEY PEAKED EARLY.
ALL RIGHT. LET'S
COMMEMORATE THIS EVENING.
GOOD NIGHT, EVERYBODY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO HOME,
BUT YOU CAN'T STAY HERE.
BUT YEAH.
I'M A REPORTER.
WOW. A REPORTER.
REALLY?
I LIKE THIS ONE.
YOU NEED TO COME
VISIT US IN D.C.
OH. YOU TOTALLY SHOULD.
IT'S GREAT.
THERE ARE LIKE 50 PLACES
YOU CAN'T BRING A KNIFE.
OH,
I--I DO NOT FLY.
[LAUGHS]
NONE OF US CAN.
THAT'S WHAT
PLANES ARE FOR.
NO. I MEAN
I'M AFRAID OF HEIGHTS.
I WON'T EVEN DRIVE
OVER A BRIDGE.
NO, SERIOUSLY, I MAKE PAUL
SWITCH PLACES WITH ME.
DO YOU WANNA SHARE A CAB?
OH. THANKS.
I'M GOOD.
HEY.
DON'T DRIVE.
I WON'T.
I PROMISE.
I'M GONNA--I'M GONNA
JUST CALL PAUL.
OKAY.
WE'RE KEEPING IN TOUCH.
I'M ADDING YOU NOW.
OKAY.
GOOD SEEING YOU.
BYE.
AW.
OH...
OKAY.
BYE, GIRL.
SAFE FLIGHT.
CALL US.
[LAUGHS]
[SIGHS]
HEY.
HEY. CAN YOU COME
PICK ME UP, PLEASE?
CAN I CALL YOU A CAB?
UGH. I THINK
I MIGHT BE SICK.
PLEASE COME GET ME.
MM. OKAY.
JUST...
GIMME 15 MINUTES.
THANKS.
I LOVE YOU.
YOU TOO.
HMM.
HOW DO I LOOK?
KIND OF SLUTTY.
AWESOME.
IT'S A FIRST DATE,
SO I WANNA MAKE
A GOOD IMPRESSION.
CAN I BORROW THESE SHOES?
HEY, I THINK
KAREN AND PAUL
ARE HAVING PROBLEMS.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU KEPT
IN TOUCH WITH HER.
YEAH. WE TALK A LOT
SINCE THE REUNION.
I DON'T THINK SHE HAS MANY
FRIENDS LEFT BACK HOME.
THAT'S BECAUSE
ALL THE COOL PEOPLE
GOT OUTTA THERE.
SAYS THE GIRL
BRINGING ME
BACK HOME FOR THE WEEK.
HEY.
WHEN IT'S A ROUNDTRIP,
IT'S NOSTALGIA.
YEAH.
WHATEVER.
HEY. LISTEN TO THIS
STATUS UPDATE.
"WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
THE TRUST IS GONE?"
THAT CAN'T BE GOOD.
I GUESS.
UGH. IT SAYS SHE
CHANGED HER PROFILE PIC.
IT USED TO BE THEIR
WEDDING PICTURE.
NOW, IT'S JUST
SOME RANDOM SELFIE.
MAYBE SHE FINALLY REALIZED
HER DRESS WAS DATED.
IT WAS NOT--
YEAH. OKAY.
IT TOTALLY WAS.
I JUST HOPE THEY'RE OKAY.
HEY.
INTERVENTION
YOU NEED TO GO OUTSIDE,
EXPAND YOUR HORIZONS,
AND GET A TAN.
[BLOWS RASPBERRIES]
I HAVE A LIFE.
AW.
OH, NO.
HI. YOU'VE REACHED
KAREN BARNES.
IF YOU LEAVE YOUR
NAME AND NUMBER,
I'LL BE SURE
TO GET BACK TO YOU.
HEY. IT'S JESSICA.
JUST CALLING TO CATCH UP.
CYNTHIA AND I WILL
BE IN TOWN NEXT WEEK.
IT'S HER MOM'S BIRTHDAY,
SO...
I WAS THINKING MAYBE WE COULD
GRAB LUNCH OR SOMETHING.
CALL ME BACK.
[CYNTHIA]
ARE YOU SAYING
YOU DON'T WANNA
STAY AT MY HOUSE?
YOU DON'T EVEN WANNA
STAY AT YOUR HOUSE.
YOU ARE SO LUCKY YOUR PARENTS
MOVED AWAY AFTER GRADUATION.
HOMECOMING'S GONNA
BE SO MUCH EASIER
WITHOUT THE HOME PART.
EXCUSE ME,
DO THESE ROOMS HAVE WI-FI?
YES, MA'AM.
CAN IT BE DISABLED?
YES.
HILARIOUS.
SO, WE GOING FOR DRINKS?
I THINK YOU HAD CAKE
AND ICE CREAM WITH THE FAMILY.
RIGHT, AND I PREFER IT
TO ALL BE A BLUR.
YOU'LL SURVIVE.
FINE.
I'LL CATCH UP
WITH YOU TOMORROW.
REMEMBER. NO INTERNET?
NO INTERNET.
NOT ON YOUR LIFE.
I'M REALLY GLAD
YOU CALLED ME TODAY.
SORRY.
NO, DON'T BE. I GET IT.
IT'S PICTURE WORTHY.
BUT IF YOU THINK
THAT'S IMPRESSIVE,
YOU SHOULD SEE
MY TEQUILA SUNRISE.
IS THAT SOME KIND
OF EUPHEMISM?
NO. IT'S A GENUINE OFFER.
I BARTEND DOWNTOWN,
AND I USE TWO CHERRIES.
OH. I REALLY LIKE A MAN
THAT GOES THE EXTRA MILE.
HEY, WHAT CAN I SAY?
I'M A GIVER.
SO... HOW DO YOU
PAY THE BILLS?
I'M A SOCIAL MEDIA
MANAGER FOR AN AIRLINE.
I BLOG FOR THE COMPANY,
TAKE CARE OF ONLINE ACCOUNTS,
AND I HELP ANGRY PASSENGERS WHEN
THEY TWEET ABOUT FLIGHT DELAYS.
HAH!
AND I'M GOOD AT IT.
THAT DOESN'T SURPRISE ME.
GO AHEAD. I KNOW
YOU'RE BOUND TO POST IT.
OKAY.
EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH.
FINE.
ANOTHER DRINK?
I THINK I'M GONNA
CALL IT A NIGHT.
BUT I HAD
A REALLY GOOD TIME.
WELL, ME TOO.
CAN I SEE YOU AGAIN
BEFORE YOU LEAVE?
I'D LIKE THAT.
OH. I HAVE TO WORK
TOMORROW NIGHT.
HOW ABOUT I BRING YOU
BREAKFAST IN THE MORNING?
GREAT.
GOOD NIGHT.
[LAUGHS]
NEED YOU TO
TALK ME OUT OF SOMETHING.
OKAY.
TWO HOURS AGO, KAREN POSTED
A STATUS UPDATE ONLINE.
"ON THE PLANE TO HAWAII.
ALOHA, BATON ROUGE."
DOESN'T THAT MEAN "HELLO?"
IT ALSO MEANS "GOODBYE."
WELL, THAT'S CONFUSING.
I THINK IT ALSO
MEANS "THANK YOU."
ANYWAY, SHE JUST POSTED
ANOTHER STATUS FROM THE AIR,
CLAIMING SHE WAS
OVER THE PACIFIC OCEAN,
BUT THE LOCATION TAG SAID
SHE WAS STILL IN BATON ROUGE.
OKAY, NOW I'M
SUFFICIENTLY WORRIED.
SEE?
NO, FOR YOU.
IT'S THE MIDDLE
OF THE NIGHT,
AND YOU'RE CREEPING
ON KAREN'S PROFILE?
OKAY, KAREN HERSELF TOLD US
SHE'S AFRAID OF FLYING,
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN SHE'S
JET-SETTING OFF TO SOME ISLAND?
I DO NOT HAVE
A GOOD FEELING ABOUT THIS.
SWINGING BY HER HOUSE.
IS THIS WHAT I'M SUPPOSED
TO TALK YOU OUT OF?
BECAUSE IF SO, I'M READY.
TOO LATE, I'M HERE.
WAIT, DO NOT
GET OUT OF THAT C--
THERE SOMETHING
I CAN HELP YOU WITH?
HI.
JESSICA?
HI, PAUL.
LONG TIME, NO SEE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN MY BACKYARD?
KAREN AND I RECONNECTED
AT THE REUNION.
SHE SAID TO STOP BY
WHENEVER I WAS BACK.
IT'S ALMOST MIDNIGHT.
IS SHE HERE?
NO. SHE'S IN OAHU.
[PAUL GASPS]
I-- WAS FIXING MY FENCE,
AND I CUT MY HAND.
IT'S ALMOST MIDNIGHT.
IT'S THE ONLY TIME
I CAN FIND TO DO IT.
SHE NEVER MENTIONED
ANYTHING ABOUT A...
VACATION. IS THIS LIKE
A LAST-MINUTE TRIP?
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
DO YOU KNOW WHEN
SHE'LL BE BACK?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE DIDN'T TELL YOU?
SHE DIDN'T TELL ME SHE WAS
LEAVING UNTIL SHE LEFT.
SO I CAN ONLY ASSUME HER RETURN
WILL BE A SIMILAR STORY.
OKAY.
I'M GONNA...
LEAVE YOU
TO YOUR YARD WORK.
JESSICA.
DO YOU WANNA
LEAVE YOUR NUMBER?
SHE'S GOT IT.
I'LL BE SURE TO LET HER KNOW
THAT YOU STOPPED BY.
THANKS.
[STARTS ENGINE]
SORRY.
REBECCA?
IT'S JESSICA.
MILLER? WE WENT
TO HAMILTON TOGETHER.
RIGHT. HI.
I DIDN'T KNOW
THAT YOU WORK HERE.
WHY WOULD YOU?
HEY, WE MISSED YOU
AT THE REUNION LAST YEAR.
I DON'T LIVE IN THE PAST.
YES, I'LL HAVE HIM
GET RIGHT BACK TO YOU.
MM-HMM.
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
HI.
I'D LIKE TO SPEAK
TO KAREN BARNES.
MRS. BARNES ISN'T
USUALLY IN THE OFFICE.
I THOUGHT SHE OWNED
THE COMPANY.
HER HUSBAND PAUL BARNES
RUNS THE DAY-TO-DAY.
I CAN SEE IF HE'S AVAILABLE.
NO, THAT'S OKAY.
I'LL TRY HER ON HER CELL.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
SHE WAS LOOKING
FOR MRS. BARNES.
I BELIEVE I MADE IT CLEAR
LAST NIGHT THAT SHE WAS AWAY.
YES. YOU DID. I JUST CAME BY
TO SEE IF ANYBODY MIGHT KNOW
WHEN SHE'LL BE BACK.
I THOUGHT
SHE WAS AFRAID TO FLY.
EXCUSE ME?
KAREN?
YOU SAID SHE WAS IN OAHU,
BUT I THOUGHT SHE WAS
AFRAID TO FLY.
I THOUGHT SHE VALUED
OUR MARRIAGE.
PEOPLE CHANGE.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
YEAH. FINE.
BOONE SHIPPING.
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
HEY! YOU REMEMBER
DIANA, RIGHT?
SHE WAS A GRADE BELOW US.
YEAH, HI.
YEAH, I RAN INTO HER EARLIER.
AND YOU'LL NEVER BELIEVE
WHO HER BEST FRIEND IS.
KAREN.
I WAS HER MAID OF HONOR.
YEAH, SEE, JESS HERE
BELIEVES THAT KAREN
HAS BEEN MURDERED.
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO GET IN TOUCH WITH HER.
IT HAS ME
A LITTLE WORRIED IS ALL.
OH. KAREN'S IN HAWAII.
YOU'RE SURE.
YEAH.
I HELPED HER
BUY HER PLANE TICKET.
MY MOM WORKS FOR AN AIRLINE.
SHE GETS REALLY
GOOD DISCOUNTS.
DID SHE HAPPEN
TO SAY WHY SHE LEFT
OR WHEN SHE'D BE BACK?
NO. I GOT THE IMPRESSION
THAT SHE NEEDED TO GET AWAY.
IT'S BEEN
A REALLY TOUGH YEAR.
WHY DO YOU SAY THAT?
KAREN'S PARENTS REALLY
PRESSURED HER TO MARRY PAUL.
BUT I DON'T THINK SHE WAS
EVER REALLY
IN LOVE WITH HIM.
IT'S MY BOYFRIEND--
OR FIANCEE.
I GOTTA GET USED TO THAT.
YOU'RE ENGAGED?
YES.
OH! CONGRATULATIONS.
WHEN'S THE WEDDING?
OH, WE HAVEN'T SET A DATE YET.
JUST SEEMS LIKE THERE'S
SO MUCH TO DO BEFOREHAND.
I'M SURE.
YEAH, I SHOULD PROBABLY
CALL HIM BACK.
YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT KIND OF TROUBLE
HE'S GOTTEN INTO.
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU.
SO I WENT TO PAUL'S.
WHAT IS IT GONNA TAKE
FOR YOU TO REALIZE
THAT KAREN
IS ALIVE AND WELL?
A PHONE CALL WOULD BE NICE.
IF I WAS IN HAWAII,
I WOULDN'T
CALL YOU BACK EITHER.
YOU ARE A REPORTER.
HOW ARE YOU
NOT ALL OVER THIS?
DON'T YOU FEEL THE NEED
TO, YOU KNOW, INVESTIGATE?
NO. SOME OF US KNOW HOW
TO CLOCK OUT OF OUR DAY JOBS.
CAN I AT LEAST
TELL YOU WHAT I FOUND?
BUY ME ANOTHER ROUND,
AND I MIGHT CONSIDER IT.
FINE. WHAT'RE YOU DRINKING?
NOT WHAT I ORDERED.
BARTENDER'S
IN A FOUL MOOD TODAY.
OH NO.
HEY, GIVE ME YOUR PHONE.
WHY?
I NEED TO BORROW IT.
YOU'LL SURVIVE.
STOP RIGHT THERE.
PUT DOWN THE PHONE.
WHAT CAN I GET YOU?
A DO-OVER?
I THINK WE'D BETTER STICK
TO WHAT'S ON THE SHELF.
OKAY. TWO GLASSES
OF PINOT GRI.
I'M SORRY ABOUT
THIS MORNING.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
[KAREN] HI, YOU'VE REACHED
KAREN BARNES.
IF YOU LEAVE YOUR NAME AND NUMBER,
I'LL BE SURE TO GET BACK TO YOU.
[JESS GASPS]
HI. IS KAREN HERE?
PLEASE DON'T MAKE ME CALL THE POLICE.
NO, I JUST NEED TO TALK TO HER.
IF YOU COULD JUST TELL HER--
FOR THE LAST TIME,
KAREN IS NOT HERE.
BUT I JUST SAW HER--
THANKS.
I WAS SURPRISED
TO GET YOUR PHONE CALL.
I'M USUALLY
PRETTY GOOD AT SENSING
WHEN I'VE BEEN BLOWN OFF.
YEAH. ABOUT THAT,
YOU DON'T OWE ME
AN EXPLANATION.
I DO.
YOU MAY HAVE NOTICED
ON OUR D-- DATE
THAT I WAS
A LITTLE DISTRACTED.
IT'S NOT THAT
I DON'T LIKE YOU
OR I DIDN'T WANNA BE THERE.
DO YOU REMEMBER KAREN BARNES?
YEAH.
KAREN POSTED PHOTOS
FROM HER HAWAIIAN VACATION.
THE ONE SHE WOULD NEVER TAKE,
BECAUSE SHE'S AFRAID OF PLANES.
BUT THEY WERE STOCK PHOTOS
FROM THIS CHEESY RESORT
ON AN ISLAND
SHE'S NOT EVEN NEAR.
I'M PRETTY SURE SOMETHING
BAD HAPPENED TO HER,
BUT I DON'T HAVE ANY PROOF.
SO I WANNA BREAK INTO
HER HUSBAND'S SHED,
AND SEE IF HE IS HIDING
HER... BODY.
THAT IS A LOT TO PROCESS.
I MEAN, WE CAN JUST
PRETEND THIS NEVER HAPPENED.
I'M IN.
WAIT. WAIT. UM,
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T DO THIS.
YOU KNOW, WE DON'T KNOW
WHEN HE'LL BE BACK, AND...
COVER ME.
"COVER ME."
CHECKING INSIDE?
UH-OH.
[DOOR THUDS]
HEY.
YEAH?
HI, UM, I JUST--
MY CAR JUST BROKE DOWN
DOWN THE STREET.
A JACK... YEAH, I GOT IT.
THANK YOU, SIR.
I HAVE ONE, BUT I CAN'T
HELP YOU WITH IT.
'CAUSE I'M RIGHT IN
THE MIDDLE OF SOMETHING.
THAT'S FINE. THAT'S FINE.
I CAN DO IT BY MYSELF.
BUT NOWE HAVE ENOUGH
TO GO TO T POLICE.
NOBODY GOES TO THE AIRPORT
WITHOUT THEIR WALLET.
HOW ARE YOU GONNA
TELL THEM YOU GOT IT?
RIGHT.
JOSH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
THAT'S ABOUT?
SOME PRESSING BUSINESS.
I HAVE A NEW THEORY.
KAREN DISCOVERS
PAUL IS CHEATING.
THEY FIGHT.
KAREN THREATENS TO LEAVE.
THERE'S A STRUGGLE.
HE KILLS HER. HIDES THE BODY.
THEN HAS TO COVER
HIS TRACKS.
OR KAREN DISCOVERS
PAUL IS CHEATING.
HOPS ON A PLANE TO HAWAII.
HAS SEX WITH CABANA BOYS.
I'VE GOTTA GO TO WORK.
[JESS LAUGHS]
IS IT WEIRD TO GO TO WORK
WHEN THE SUN HAS SET?
YOU GET USED TO IT.
HEY.
CAN I COME WITH?
PAUL AND REBECCA
WERE KISSING.
NO KIDDING.
REBECCA DREIDER?
PAUL WOULD NEVER DO THAT.
I'M SORRY. I KNOW
THEY'RE BOTH YOUR FRIENDS.
BUT JOSH AND I SAW THEM.
YOU FINALLY VENTURE OUT
INTO THE DATING WORLD,
AND YOU PICK AN ENABLER?
I NEEDED BACKUP.
SOMEBODY ELSE REFUSED.
YEAH-- UM, I'M SORRY.
I HAVE TO GO.
IS IT JUST ME, OR DID SHE
SEEM A LITTLE TOO UPSET?
WHAT?
NOTHING. JUST WAITING
TO SEE HOW DEEP DOWN THE
RABBIT HOLE THIS REALLY GOES.
YOU DON'T THINK
SHE BOLTED A LITTLE QUICKLY?
YOU JUST ACCUSED HER
OF UNWITTINGLY HELPING
TO COVER UP A MURDER.
I'D LEAVE TOO
IF I HADN'T JUST
PAID FOR MY DRINK.
WAIT, ARE YOU MAD?
I'VE LET YOU RUN AROUND
AND PLAY OUT YOUR
DETECTIVE FANTASIES
BECAUSE IT REQUIRED YOU
TO UNPLUG FROM CYBERSPACE
LONG ENOUGH FOR ACTUAL
HUMAN INTERACTION.
BUT YOU JUST TRADED
ONE OBSESSION FOR ANOTHER.
I AM NOT OBSESSED.
AREN'T YOU?
'CAUSE YOU'RE ACCUSING PEOPLE
OF SOME VERY SERIOUS THINGS
WITHOUT ANYTHING
TO BACK IT UP BUT SUSPICION.
IT'S RECKLESS,
AND IT'S WRONG.
SCREW THIS.
DO ME A FAVOR?
DON'T CALL ME
UNTIL YOU'RE OVER THIS.
KAREN'S PROBABLY FINE.
I THINK I ALWAYS
KNEW THAT. I JUST...
GOT SWEPT AWAY.
[JESS CHUCKLES]
YOU KNOW, THERE WAS
THIS MOMENT LAST NIGHT
WHEN I THOUGHT I SAW HER.
OKAY. CASE
OFFICIALLY CLOSED.
CONSIDER ME OFF
THE INTERNET BEAT.
WELCOME BACK
TO CIVILIAN LIFE.
SO...
WHAT IS SOMETHING
TWO PEOPLE CAN DO IN PERSON?
FACE TO FACE?
[DOOR THUDS]
OW!
SORRY. SORRY!
[BOTH LAUGH]
[JESS LAUGHS]
STOP RIGHT THERE.
PUT DOWN THE PHONE.
HEY, WHAT IS THAT?
IT'S MY PHONE.
- -PUT DOWN THE PHONE.
WHY IS SHE YELLING AT ME?
STOP RIGHT THERE.
PUT DOWN THE PHONE.
B-- HEY! LEAVE IT.
NO. WHAT IF IT'S KAREN?
I HAVE TO.
--DOWN THE PHONE.
HELLO?
WAIT. SLOW DOWN.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT PICTURES?
SOMEBODY HIJACKED
THE SOCIAL MEDIA SITES
THAT I RUN.
AIRLINE?
THEY'VE BEEN POSTING PICTURES
TO THEM FOR THE PAST HALF HOUR.
POSTING WHAT?
HOW IS THAT EVEN POSSIBLE?
LOOK AT THE ANGLE.
SOMEBODY HIJACKED
MY LAPTOP CAMERA.
THEY CAN DO THAT?
I MEAN, YES. IT'S, LIKE,
THE EARLIEST FLIGHT
TO D.C. YOU HAVE.
YES, I'LL WAIT.
HEY. WE'LL FIGURE THIS OUT.
I COULD LOSE MY JOB
OVER THIS.
I PROBABLY ALREADY HAVE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
MY CREDIT CARD'S BEEN DECLINED?
WHAT IS GOING ON?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
ANYBODY HOME?
HI. I'D LIKE TO THANK YOU
FOR MY NEW RINGTONE.
FOR WHEN I'M NOT THERE TO REMIND
YOU OF YOUR POOR LIFE CHOICES.
PUT ON A SHIRT.
I'VE GOT NEWS.
FOR YOU, THAT'S OPTIONAL.
I SAW WHAT HAPPENED ONLINE.
I BROUGHT TEQUILA,
SO WE CAN EITHER
CELEBRATE YOUR
MENTAL BREAKDOWN
OR COMMISERATE
YOUR IDENTITY THEFT.
IT WASN'T ME.
I FIGURED.
YOU'RE NOT CARELESS.
FIVE DIFFERENT
NEWS AFFILIATES HAVE
ALREADY PICKED UP
THE STORY, THOUGH.
AND I THINK CRUISING ALTITUDE
IS CURRENTLY TRENDING.
WHAT DOES THAT EVEN MEAN?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
YOU'RE THE ONE
FLUENT IN INTERNET,
NOT ME.
THIS IS A DISASTER.
IT'S NOT ALL BAD NEWS.
I DID SOME DIGGING.
AND REMEMBER HOW WE THOUGHT
REBECCA WAS SUPPOSED
TO FOLLOW PAUL TO YALE?
SHE WAS.
THE TWO EVEN HAD
AN OFF-CAMPUS APARTMENT
ALL LINED UP.
BUT AT THE LAST MOMENT,
HER ADMISSION GOT REVOKED.
WHAT HAPPENED?
SOMEONE PHONED IN A TIP.
APPARENTLY SHE HAD HACKED INTO
THE COLLEGE BOARD'S DATABASE
AND CHANGED
HER S.A.T. SCORE.
SO WHAT? SHE HAD
A CERTAIN LIFE,
AND NOW SHE'S TRYING
TO GET IT BACK?
SOME PEOPLE CAN NEVER GET OVER
THEIR SHOULD-HAVE-BEEN'S.
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
SHE USED TO SKIP COMPUTER LAB
TO WORK ON HER TAN.
MAYBE SHE HAD US
ALL FOOLED.
HI. I NEED TO SPEAK
TO REBECCA DREIDER.
MS. DREIDER HASN'T
COME IN YET.
DO YOU KNOW
WHEN SHE'LL BE IN?
I'VE BEEN INFORMED
THAT YOU'RE NOT
ALLOWED IN THE BUILDING.
AND IF YOU DON'T LEAVE,
I'M AFRAID I'LL BE FORCED
TO CALL SECURITY.
IT'S KIND OF IMPORTANT THAT
WE THAT WE TALK TO HER FIRST.
I'M CALLING SECURITY!
IT IS. YEAH.
OH.
OR NOT.
SO, WHEN'S LUNCH?
HEY! JESSICA?
DIANA--
WHAT'S WRONG?
THERE'S SOMETHING
I HAVE TO TELL YOU.
UM...
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I WASN'T COMPLETELY HONEST
WITH YOU THE FIRST TIME WE MET.
KAREN DIDN'T ASK ME
TO BUY THAT PLANE TICKET.
PAUL DID.
I DIDN'T THINK
MUCH OF IT AT THE TIME.
I THOUGHT MAYBE IT WAS A GIFT
OR A SURPRISE OR SOMETHING.
BUT AFTER
WHAT YOU SAID LAST NIGHT,
IT'S ALL I CAN THINK ABOUT.
IS HIM WITH HER.
HE NEEDS TO PAY
FOR WHAT HE'S DONE.
HI, PAUL. GOT A SEC?
I'M NOT QUITE SURE WHAT YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR HERE, OFFICER.
WHERE'S THE CAMARO?
WHAT CAMARO?
THE ONE I SAW PARKED HERE.
THE ONE YOU'VE BEEN
USING TO RUN ME DOWN.
I DON'T OWN A CAMARO,
AND I NEVER HAVE.
IS THAT IT?
MS. MILLS EXPRESSED SOME CONCERN
ABOUT YOUR WIFE'S SAFETY.
WHERE IS SHE CURRENTLY?
SHE'S IN HAWAII.
MAUI.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID SHE WAS IN OAHU.
IT'S A BIG ISLAND.
ACTUALLY, IT'S AN ARCHIPELAGO.
AND THAT'S NOT HELPING.
SORRY.
DO YOU KNOW
WHEN SHE'LL RETURN HOME?
NO. I DON'T.
THAT'S BECAUSE
SHE'S NOT RETURNING.
SHE HAS NO IDEA
WHAT SHE'S TALKING ABOUT.
ASK HIM WHY HE THREW
ALL OF HIS WIFE'S CLOTHES OUT
IN THE TRASH BIN OUT FRONT.
YOU WENT THROUGH MY TRASH.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT, OKAY?
ACTUALLY, WHEN IT'S ON YOUR
PROPERTY, IT'S TRESPASSING.
BUT ONCE IT HITS THE CURB,
IT FALLS UNDER PUBLIC EASEMENT.
THAT IS CORRECT.
MY WIFE AND I HAVE
BEEN GOING THROUGH
A ROUGH PATCH.
NOW, WAS IT IMMATURE?
WAS I ANGRY? PROBABLY.
BUT IT'S NOT ILLEGAL.
IS IT TRUE THAT YOUR WIFE HAS BEEN
OUT OF COMMUNICATION
FOR THE PAST SEVERAL DAYS?
NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE AT ALL.
NO ONE HAS HEARD FROM HER
SINCE THE SUPPOSED
"TRIP TO HAWAII."
I HAVE. MANY TIMES.
DO YOU WANT ME TO CALL HER?
YEAH.
FINE.
LET ME SEE THIS.
HELLO?
HEY.
PAUL?
YEAH, SWEETHEART,
I NEED YOU TO--
I'M NOT YOUR SWEETHEART.
DON'T EVER CALL ME AGAIN.
SHE'S STILL MAD.
THAT'S NOT HER.
SHE WON'T CALL ME BACK.
THAT'S 'CAUSE
I'M HER HUSBAND,
AND YOU'RE HER STALKER.
I THINK WE'VE GOT
ALL WE NEED.
THANKS FOR YOUR TIME.
ABOUT TIME.
NICE CAR.
SWEET RIDE, GIRL.
THANKS.
DO YOU HEAR THAT?
HEAR WHAT?
YOU MAY WANNA HAVE
A MECHANIC CHECK THAT OUT.
WHY DON'T YOU GO ON UP? IT'S
THAT FIRST DOOR ON THE RIGHT.
I'M GONNA TAKE A LOOK.
OKAY.
[MUFFLED SCREAMS]
QUIET. QUIET.
EVERYTHING'S
GONNA BE OKAY.
AT LEAST YOU KNOW
YOUR FRIEND IS SAFE, RIGHT?
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW CAN SHE BE IN HAWAII?
DIANA TOLD US PAUL
HAD HER BUY THE TICKET.
WHY WOULD SHE LIE?
SHE SAID SHE WAS
THE BRIDESMAID.
SHE'S NOT HERE.
SHE'S NOT ANYWHERE.
OH. MISSED CALL.
HEY, IT'S ME. I'M GOING TO GRB
A DRINK WITH DIANA TODAY.
YOU SHOULD COME IF YOU
FINISH YOUR INQUISITION.
I JUST TEXTED YOU
THE ADDRESS.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
HAPPENED TO KAREN?
TO BE HONEST,
I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
A COUPLE DAYS AGO,
I WOULD'VE SWORN SHE WAS
ON AN ISLAND SOMEWHERE
WITH A STRAW AND A COCONUT.
BUT RECENT EVENTS
HAVE ME WONDERING.
RECENT EVENTS?
WELL, WE FOUND SOME THINGS.
REALLY.
WHAT KIND OF THINGS?
NO, I KNOW
SHE'S YOUR FRIEND.
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO FREAK OUT, SO...
IT'S BEST FOR US
TO JUST THINK POSITIVELY.
SO, YOU DON'T
HAVE ANY PROOF?
NO, I WOULDN'T
CALL IT PROOF EXACTLY.
WELL, WHAT WOULD YOU
CALL IT?
HEY, WHAT'S THIS?
WELL, I GUESS YOU CAN SAY
I'M TECHNICALLY ALREADY MARRIED.
MY FIANCEE, HE PROPOSED
TO ME WHEN WE WERE KIDS.
HE EVEN MADE ME
A RING OUT OF YARN.
THAT'S ADORABLE.
YEAH. WE HAD
A BACKYARD WEDDING
AND EVERYTHING.
AND HIS NAME'S PAUL TOO?
MM-HMM.
COULD I USE YOUR BATHROOM?
YEAH.
IT'S THROUGH THAT DOOR,
DOWN THE HALL.
YOU'VE REACHED CYNTHIA.
LEAVE ME A MESSAGE,
AND I'LL GET BACK TO YOU.
SHE'S NOT ANSWERING.
I'M SURE SHE'S OKAY.
JUST TRY NOT TO PANIC.
CYNTHIA?
HEY, CYNTHIA?
I'LL CHECK OUT BACK.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
REALLY, REALLY RIDICULOUS.
I MEAN, WHAT THE ACTUAL F--
DID YOU FIND HER?
NO.
SHE'S, UH--
INSANE.
NOT GREAT AT PHOTOSHOP.
BUT ALSO INSANE.
THAT'S KAREN'S PHONE.
OH MY GOSH.
HOW LONG DO YOU THINK
THIS HAS BEEN GOING ON?
YOU DON'T THINK DIANA
SET UP REBECCA TOO,
LIKE, BACK IN HIGH SCHOOL?
I HOPE SHE NEVER FINDS OUT
I KISSED PAUL
AT FRESHMAN HOMECOMING.
WAIT, YOU KISSED PAUL?
[DIANA GRUNTS]
ARE YOU OKAY?
BEHIND YOU!
WHERE'S CYNTHIA?
SHE'S GONE!
[BOTH STRAIN]
[JESS SCREAMS]
I HEARD WHAT YOU SAID
ABOUT THAT KISS, BITCH!
ARE YOU OKAY?
YES.
ARE YOU?
YEAH.
JESS.
JOSH!
WE NEED TO
GET YOU HELP, OKAY?
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
THAT MIGHT BE
A TRICK QUESTION.
SHE PLAYED US ALL.
SHE WAS TEN STEPS
AHEAD OF US THE WHOLE TIME.
SHOWING UP WHEREVER WE WERE
JUST TO STEER US
IN THE WRONG DIRECTION.
MAYBE IF YOU DIDN'T PUT
EVERYTHING ON THE INTERNET,
SHE WOULDN'T HAVE
THE UPPER HAND.
SHUT UP.
SHUT UP AND COME HERE.
CAN YOU--
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
--ON THIS,
I'M GOING TO FIND HER!
CALL 911!
JESS, NO!
HEY, PAUL.
[PAUL GRUNTS]
[DIANA SOBS]
STOP! SON OF A...
CALL FOR HELP!
[KAREN STRAINS]
PAUL? PAUL?
PAUL? SOMEBODY HELP US!
HE'S NOT BREATHING.
[PAUL COUGHS]
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.
[DIANA GASPS]
AAH!
[DIANA GRUNTS]
YOU SENDING ME OFF
TO HAWAII?
NO.
I WAS THINKING
COSTA RICA.
PURA VIDA.
YOUR PHONE'S GREAT,
BY THE WAY.
I KNOW.
I'M WRITING UP
A SUICIDE NOTE.
I'M THINKING ABOUT POSTING IT
SO THAT YOUR FRIENDS AND FAMILY
WILL KNOW WHY
THEY FIND YOUR BODY
IN THE BOTTOM OF A RIVER.
NOBODY'LL BELIEVE THAT.
OF COURSE THEY WILL.
PEOPLE AREN'T PEOPLE ANYMORE.
THEY'RE JUST THESE PERSONAS
THAT THEY PRESENT
TO THE WORLD.
IT'S AMAZING.
WHEN I HAVE YOUR PHONE,
I'M YOU.
YOU HAVE A SERIOUS PROBLEM.
YOU'RE TIED UP,
AND I'M ABOUT TO KILL YOU.
YOU'RE THE ONE
WITH SERIOUS PROBLEMS.
AH-AH-AH.
SO ARE YOU JUST GONNA
PRETEND TO BE ME?
IS THAT
WHAT YOU DID TO KAREN?
NO. I SLIT HER THROAT.
JUST TELL ME WHAT'S WRONG.
I AM NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GO HOME
AND COLLECT YOUR SANITY--
AND THEN TALK TO ME THERE--
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT.
YOU'RE NOT TELLING ME ANYTHING--
IF THERE'S NOTHING LEFT,
THEN LEAVE!
YOU'RE NEVER HOME!
I WAS ENGAGED
TO PAUL FIRST.
ORDER IS IMPORTANT.
I'M DONE.
AAH!
YOU SHOULD ALWAYS
HONOR YOUR COMMITMENTS.
THE MOMENT HE PUT
THAT RING ON MY FINGER,
I KNEW THAT
HE WAS MY FUTURE.
BUT YOUNG LOVE
CAN BE REALLY TOUGH.
IT'S FRAGILE.
IT NEEDS TO BE PROTECTED.
I KNEW PAUL HAD
THINGS HE HAD TO DO.
SO I WAITED. FOR YEARS.
I DID IT ALL FOR HIM.
I'D DO ANYTHING FOR HIM.
SORRY.
IT REALLY WASN'T SUPPOSED
TO END UP LIKE THIS.
I JUST WANTED TO BE HAPPY.
AND I'VE WAITED
FOR A REALLY LONG TIME.
STOP RIGHT THERE.
PUT DOWN THE PHONE.
BUT HOW'S JOSH?
AMBULANCE CAME
RIGHT AFTER WE CALLED.
HE WAS STILL YAPPING
WHEN THEY TOOK HIM AWAY.
THAT'S GOTTA BE
A GOOD SIGN, RIGHT?
SHE DID IT.
WHAT?
SHE KILLED HER.
NO.
DID SHE SAY WHY?
SHE WANTED PAUL.
KAREN WAS IN THE WAY.
AM I THE ONLY ONE THAT
DOESN'T GET THE APPEAL?
NO.
I'M WITH YOU.
OH, NANCY DREW, YOU LIVE
TO SLEUTH ANOTHER DAY.
BARELY.
MAYBE WE SHOULD'VE EASED YOU
INTO THE REAL WORLD.
NOTHING LIKE THIS
EVER HAPPENS ON TUMBLR.
I WANT TO THANK EVERYONE
FOR COMING HERE TODAY
TO CELEBRATE KAREN'S LIFE.
AS MANY OF YOU KNOW,
WE WERE MARRIED
RIGHT HERE ON THIS SPOT.
THAT WAS OUR BEGINNING.
BUT TODAY,
IT'S ABOUT ENDINGS.
AND A VERY, VERY
SPECIAL WOMAN...
THAT WAS TAKEN
FROM US TOO SOON.
I LOVE YOU, KAREN.
MAY YOU BE AT PEACE.
I OWE YOU AN APOLOGY.
NO, YOU WERE JUST
LOOKING FOR HER
CAUSE YOU THOUGHT
SHE WAS IN TROUBLE,
AND... YOU WERE RIGHT.
TO BE FAIR, THE ODDS
OF THAT HAPPENING
WEREN'T GREAT.
I WASN'T
A VERY GOOD HUSBAND.
NO. YOU WEREN'T.
HEY!
DIANA WORKED OUT
A DEAL WITH THE POLICE.
SHE GAVE UP THE BODY.
WHERE WAS IT?
SHE DUMPED IT IN A RIVER.
THEY'RE DREDGING IT OUT
NOW IF YOU WANNA WATCH
THE LIVE FEED.
- -MISSISSIPPI RIVER THIS AFTERNOON.
KAREN BARNES OF
THE BOONE SHIPPING FAMILY--
YEAH, I THINK I'M GONNA GIVE
THAT INTERNET EMBARGO A TRY.
REALLY?
YEAH.
BESIDES, YOU KNOW
JOSH IS IN TOWN THIS WEEKEND,
AND I HAVE A DATE.
BUT YOU'RE NOT WEARING THAT.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THIS?
I THINK IT LOOKS NICE.
[REPORTER] ...FOR PEOPLE TO
WITNESS THIS YOUNG WOMAN'S BOY.
WRAPPED IN A RED TARP,
AS IT WAS DRAGGED
FROM THE RIVER TODAY.
BRAD BLANCHARD, LIVE ON
LOCATION, CHANNEL 4 NEWS.
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
ME TOO.
I HAVE SOME GOOD NEWS.
MY LAWYER GOT ME A DEAL.
25 YEARS WITH GOOD BEHAVIOR.
THAT'S GOOD.
WHAT'D YOU TELL THE POLICE?
NOTHING.
I SWEAR.
I KNEW I COULD
COUNT ON MY GIRL.
I'M SORRY ABOUT YOUR HEAD.
WHEN SHE TOLD ME
ABOUT REBECCA--
AND YOU KNOW
THERE'S NOBODY ELSE BUT YOU.
YOU CAN WAIT, RIGHT?
OF COURSE.
IT'S ONLY 25 YEARS.
WE EARNED IT.
I LOVE YOU.
YOU TOO.
HEY.
COME BACK TO BED.
I HAVE TO GO.
AND SO DO YOU.
I WOULD LOSE EVERYTHING.
ARE YOU IN LOVE WITH HER?
I LOVE YOU.
I'M GONNA FIGURE OUT
A WAY FOR US TO BE TOGETHER.
I'D DO ANYTHING.
WELL?
WHAT?
WHAT'D YOU SAY TO HER?
NOT MUCH.
SHE KILLED YOUR WIFE.
SHE DID US A FAVOR.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
YOU CAN LOOK HER IN THE EYE.
I JUST NEEDED CLOSURE.
WELL.
DID YOU GET IT?
YEAH.
I THINK I'M READY
FOR MY FRESH START.