Isn't it funny how a few short days
can change your whole life.
And sometimes, its not until later, much later,
that you realize what happened to you,
and when it happened, and why it happened.
Life sure is strange... sometimes.
Hop in.
Let's hit it man.
I'm Harmer and this is Stokes.
Hey, how's it goin'?
I'm Allen.
Ya feel that earthquake?
When?
I don't know, just like ten minutes
ago.
I didn't feel it.
Well, there will be another one.
Where you from?
From Kansas.
Kansas? Woah.
Kansas?
Yeah, right near Kansas City.
Well, you're not in Kansas anymore
Elder.
Welcome to Los Angeles, Elder, the
greatest mission in the world.
I got a letter here from your bishop
about your father.
He's going to be in prison for a very
long time.
My stepfather.... he's my stepfather.
Says here that you are sealed to
him, that makes him your father.
How's your mom doin'?
She asked to have her name removed from the records of the church.
I suppose you are wondering what you are doing out here
on a mission while your family is falling apart back home.
Your dad served a mission.
A lot of good it did him.
You're not here to do good for yourself.
You've been doing that for nineteen years.
You come here to do good for other people.
Help them turn their lives around.
Your parents made some decisions that were bad decisions.
There's nothing you can do about that.
No.
Your job is to help some people make right decisions,
to turn their lives around. To do some good in this world.
Do you think you can get out and
do that?
I don't know.
Well, why don't we go out and find
out?
He's such a sweet boy. I know,
I know he's a sweet boy but he's driving me crazy.
I'm going to put you with one of my
best men.
...flipped back his coat, he's looking
up at the guy, and he's smiling..
He's 29 years old.
He's one of the oldest ones we ha ve.
His name's Dalton but mostly they
just call him Pops.
Dalton!
Yes Sir!
I think your husband caught us
flirting.
Oh, no!
Elder Dalton, this is Elder Allen,
your new companion. He's from Kansas.
So... you're the one.
Alright, let's do some good.
Is this our place?
No.
Well who lives here?
We're about to find out.
Why can't we just go home first?
We are going home...
...one door at a time...
Hi I'm Elder Dalton, this is my companion Elder Allen.
We're missionaries from the Church of Jesus Christ...
Listen, I'm a little busy.
Well, we just have a short message
we'd like to share with you today.
Look, I don't have time right now.
What would be a more convenient
time for us to come back?
Look, I don't want to be rude but I'm just
not interested in what you have to say.
Well, I think if you aren't interested in what we have to say,
you must not know what it is that we have to say.
I'd like to leave you with this pamplet that talks a
little bit about Jesus and his visit to the Americas.
Do you know that Christ came to
the Americas after his resurrection?
No.
Well, he did.
And I think you'll be very interested in what he had to say.
I gotta go.
If you have any questions, give us a call,
the number is on the pamphlet. Thanks.
I could ne ver do that.
Yes you could. Right now in fact.
You got the next one.
You don't knock on people's doors
like that!
At that rate,
we'll be home before you know it.
Ok, why are we here?
To gain physical bodies, experience
and wisdom.
No, not everybody, just us, just
missionaries.
To baptize.
No.
To preach the gospel.
Wrong. Wrong?
Wrong. It's to preach the gospel by the spirit. Ok?
It can't just be you and me, it's gotta be me, you, and the Holy Spirit.
Right.
Yeah, good afternoon sisters.
Hey, you lonely today elder?
I'm lonely everyday. Did you read
that book I gave you?
Oh, we've been too busy.
Well read that book. Then you'll stop and talk?
Just read the book....
Okay, its not about us. Its not about how smart we
are or how fast we can flip through the scriptures.
Who were those girls back there?
How many people are you going to con vert?
What? In my whole mission?
Over the next two years, how many people are you going to convert?
I don't know. Like 30, yeah like 30.
Wrong. You're not going to convert any.
You're not going to convert a single soul. Because it's not about you.
It's not about me. It's between them
and the Lord.
We give them some tools, some information.
We're like the telephone company.
The Lord's on one end. We hook up
the line, but it's their conversation.
The Lord converts them. They convert themselves.
All we do is teach... by the spirit.
The field is white Elder, ready to
harvest. Even in Los Angeles.
That was kind of a trick question.
Yeah.
So where are we going? And who
were those girls back there?
Your turn.
I did the last one.
You need the practice.
Yeah?
Hi, I'm Elder Allen and this is my
companion Elder...
Dalton.
...Dalton, and we're missionaries
from the Church of Jesus Christ...
Not again.
We have a short message..
How many times do I have to tell you guys? If you come knockin' on my
door again, I'm gonna step out there and I'm gonna beat you to death.
Hey buddy, take it easy. We're just trying to share something with you.
If your'e not interested that's fine but there's no reason to be rude.
Rude?
Yeah.
I'm rude? I'm not the one knocking on your door all day.
I'm not even going to listen to this.
He y!
Hey, get your foot out of my door!
I'll get my foot out when you
apologize to my companion.
Yeah, I'm not apologizing to
anybody!
You're going to apologize,
and then you're going to sit down and listen to what we have to say.
Yeah, I'm going to get my gun!
Open this door... get in there and
teach him a lesson!
That gets the award, that gets the
award.
I'd like to thank the academy and all
those who voted for me.
It was pretty good man. I'm going to
laugh myself to sleep tonight.
Yo, this dude that took your picture,
for which you will always be remembered...
...his name is Magnum.
Hi.
Hey, hey. I want a copy of the
picture.
Yeah, before the second coming man. Yeah, right. Not happening.
Come on. And this worthless bum right here is Sandavol.
How's it goin' man. That was great
man. It really was!
Sandy was just pla ying the blues because his
girlfriend is going to marry his big brother.
She's my fianc'e.
She's your sister-in-law. I'm Banks,
and that funny looking spud over there, that's my companion, Kinegar.
This immature beha vior has got to
stop.
Come on man, I'll show you your room.
This isn't funny guys, it's not funny.
Did you see his face?
Who was were before?
Lambert. He left to Culver City
about five hours ago.
Five hours. Wow.
That's one of the blessings of the life of poverty.
Doesn't take long to pack.
Yeah.
Hey, tell me. What do you think of
Pops?
Um, I don't know.
He means well. I think he tries a little too hard.
Ya know? I guess you don't do ya? Yeah.
Well, anyway, welcome. And I'll
watch out for you, ok?
Singing
Dear heavenly father, thank you for
a good day's work.
Thank you for sending Elder Allen and forgive
us for the manner in which we welcomed him.
Please bless us as we go along and
just help us through our days.
In the name of Jesus Christ.
Amen.
Alright, goodnight!
Don't touch me.
Thanks.
We give thee thanks for our Savior and through Him
we may be forgiven of our sins and our weaknesses.
That we may serve thee in worthiness we pray.
In the name of Jesus Christ, Amen.
Amen.
It's good to have you.
We're not finished?
It's a personal prayer.
It's 10:30 Elder, lights out.
Pops, hey Pops wake up.
What time is it?
Its two o'clock. Get up. Your greenie
just went AWOL.
What time does the bus leave?
6:30.
That's quite a wait.
You don't have to stay.
No, yes I do. See, I'm your companion.
At least until you get on that bus.
So what? You're going to try and
talk me out of it now?
No, you're a big boy. You can make
your own decisions.
It's bad timing. That's all. I might
come back later.
No... they won't let you. You throw it
away and it's gone.
They'll let me come back.
Well, yeah.
When you are 65 and you've got arthritis and kidney stones,
maybe they'll let you help people
with their family history...
Boy, wouldn't that be fun?
I just didn't think I should be here.
Well then you shouldn't. Three hours from now you won't be. Good for
you. And good for me. I don't need anymore deadbeat companions.
I'm not a deadbeat.
Then you must be a coward.
Ya know, you don't know anything
about me.
Alright, fine. Why are you leaving?
What, I've known you for half a day and
you expect me to bare my soul to you?
At least no one can say I didn't try.
Yeah. You gave it a whole 12 hours.
He y!
You got a girlfriend?
You miss her I bet.
It's not a girl, I don't even have a
girlfriend.
He doesn't want to talk about it.
Ok! So what are we going to do
here for the ne xt three hours?
Maybe its a word of wisdom
problem.
Maybe he likes to take a drink now
and then.
Maybe...
Or maybe its a morality problem.
Maybe he's in love with you.
Fine, I'll go back! Just leave me
alone!
Ok, good decision.
What?
I told you, I don't want any
deadbeat companions.
I can sta y if I want.
You do it my way. You do the work,
you keep all the rules.
Fine.
But I'm keeping my ticket.
Good idea.
And, I'm not unpacking my bags.
Fine.
Alright then.
Alright.
That hurt?
Yeah.
What?
It's nothing.
The Book of Mormon talks about
horses in America.
What?
There were no horses in America before Columbus.
It's pretty much a documented fact.
Why you still reading that stuff? It's
as bad as pornography.
How do you expect to defend
yourself against these people?
Man, these people are the enemy.
You want to look stupid in front of them?
You gotta know their weapons and
their strategy!
You know, you got some weird
terminology there.
You ought to be reading the
scriptures, not this garbage.
Whatever you say.
Hey did I ever tell you what the snail said
when he was riding the turtle's back?
What?
Weeeeee!
Ha ha
How many of those are you going
to do anyway?
160...
Hey Pops, why don't you get down
there and do a few?
I could be dead in six months, what
do I want to exercise for?
Because it's fun Pops. Don't it look
like fun?
What do you call three lepers in a
hot tub?
A stew.
OK. Why did the lepers have to
stop the poker game?
Cause they threw their hands on
the table.
Ok. This will do it.
Why did the lepers have to stop
their hocke y game?
There was a face off on the ice.
Yeah, that's pretty good
It's 7:30. Personal study.
Right...
What am I supposed to be
studying?
Well then, that would be personal.
Hey wake up! It's 8:30, companion
study.
Why don't you turn to the book of
First TImothy? Chapter 1.
First TImothy. It's in the Bible?
Page 1506... second column.
In the New Testament. Top of the
page.
Ok. "But we know that the law is
good if a man use it lawfully.
Knowing this that a law is not made
for a righteous man...
Alright. Let's do some good!
Hi. I'm Elder Allen and this is my
companion Elder Dalton.
Look, I'm very busy right now.
Why don't you just go and talk to somebody else?
Ahh, there's no nobody home.
Hi, I got to go to the bathroom. I've
got to go to the bathroom
Hey Pops.
Hey.
Man that looks good.
Hey guys.
Hey Connie.
You must be the new one.
Hi.
Yes this youngster here is my new companion.
Hi, I'm Connie. I'm Brandon.
I mean, I'm Elder Allen.
Connie I would like one of those great big greasy double cheese burgers
With a couple of onion rings.
On the side this time?
No, no, no, no, no in the burger.
No lettuce, no pickle,
some of those french fries around the side like you do.
And one of those great big
chocolate shakes with extra syrup.
Anything for you Brandon?
No. I'm fine.
Will you close your mouth when
you're eating? It's disgusting.
Man, is she really pretty or have I
just been out too long?
You've definately been out too long.
I think she's pretty.
Yeah well, you know what they say, if you don't look once
you're not a man, but if you look twice you're not a missionary.
How many times you guys look?
I looked once. What about you?
I'm still looking once.
Here you go.
Gracias. Thank you.
And here's your check.
Hey, uh, Connie...
Yeah?
You know we're missionaries, right?
Sure. I know. You guys come in
here all the time.
So, you know what we do, right?
Yeah, you're kinda like nuns, but
you're men?
Yeah, kind of. But you know we only
do this for two years
and then, you know,
we go home and go to work or go back to school...
Or get married.
Sure, sure. We could do that.
You know, I mean I could do that.
You know, with someone.
Okay.
Can I ask you a question?
If I gave you a book, would you
read it?
You don't have money for a tip, do
you?
No, we'll leave you a tip and the
Book of Mormon. If you'll read it.
I like to read.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I sure do lo ve missionary work.
I'm not quite clear on this. Was that
called finding or flirting?
I wasn't flirting. I was being flirted.
Yeah, that's right. I wasn't dancing
president. I was being danced.
I wasn't kissing president.
I was being kissed. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Are you going to eat that?
Yeah.
Hey, did you guys know that Joseph Smith
gave four different accounts of the first vision?
Did you?
Why don't you put that stuff away man?
That's really starting to get on my nerves.
Alright.
I just thought you might want to learn about your own religion.
He gave different accounts because he was talking
to different audiences in different circumstances.
That must be why the first presidency never e ven mentioned
that God and Jesus Christ appeared until after the 1900s.
It's not true.
It says it right here.
Look its not true.
Orson Pratt and John Taylor both taught it, repeatedly.
Why don't you look it up? In our
books for a change.
How many lies do you have to find in there before you're going to get it?
Just forget it okay?
No I'm not going to forget it.
Look at this stuff.
Who are these people?
Don' they have anything better to do with their time?
I mean we've got drugs, disease, people living out on the street
and these people spend their time
trying to tear down other people's faith.
Doesn't that give you a clue?
Why are you getting so upset
elder?
I'm getting upset because you're wasting your
time with that garbage instead of doing your work.
And why aren't you with your
companion?
Because he's sick of listening to this
stuff.
You're dragging him down and you're dragging the rest of us down too.
So why don't you get it together?
Excuse me...
...I have to use the restroom.
I better go.
I'm Catholic and your mother was
Catholic.
I know Papa.
And your grandparents and your
great grandparents were Catholic.
We know that Papa. You've been good to us.
You and Mama always took us to mass.
You're mother was devout.
But these missionaries, they have
the Lord's spirit.
Laura felt it. She felt it at my
baptism.
I feel it every week at church and when I
pray and when I read the scriptures Papa.
Do you feel the spirit when these
boys come to visit?
I do. Do you feel it now?
I do Papa.
I feel nothing.
We have a baptism scheduled for
Saturday.
Laura still lives at home. She needs
your blessing, your consent.
Laura has already been baptised.
We're Catholic.
Hello there sisters. You're out early
today.
We're the early birds. We get all the
worms you know.
Did you read that book I gave you?
No.
I read it.
You read the book?
I read the book.
You read the Book of Mormon?
Yeah. What, you don't think I can
read or something?
No, it's just...
What was your fa vorite part?
I like the part where that prophet...
Abi-nadi?
Abinadi, yeah.
Yeah! Where he tells the king and
all the people to repent and all
and they won't do it. And so they tell
him to deny Jesus
and he won't do that and so they tie him up and the y put sticks
under him and they set him on fire and they burn him to death.
It was kind of sad.
But I like that part a lot.
So can I have that appointment
now?
How about Saturday night?
We're working Saturday night.
Yeah.
Ok, how about Saturday day?
Yeah, we can do that.
Alright.
Can I do that?
Yeah, we can do that.
So what is your dad like?
What?
I mean, we're companions. I'm
supposed to get to know you, right?
My dad's a really great guy.
Not much of a sense of humor
though.
What does he do?
He's a janitor actually.
Yeah, he works at my old high
school.
He was always hoping that I'd be a surgeon in the military.
You know, become an officer.
So, he didn't want you to go on a
mission?
No, he's not Mormon.
Oh.
Not yet.
When he found out that we don't get paid for this,
for being missionaries,
you should have seen him. He
didn't understand that at all.
How about your mom?
My mom died a long time ago. She
had cancer.
What about your mom?
She's still alive and all.
Well, that's a good thing.
Yeah. My dad... left when I was
seven.
I haven't seen him since.
I don't remember much about him.
Just that he took me to this baseball
game once.
And the last time I saw him... he
gave me this autographed baseball.
...Hank Aaron.
Really?
Yeah...
Wow!
Yeah, that's what I thought too.
But then when I was thirteen...
and I saw Hank's real signature on a baseball...
...didn't look anything like mine.
No wa y!
That's the kind of guy he was, huh?
Hey, Dalton!
Brother Rose! This tadpole here's my new companion,
his name's Elder Allen. He's from Kansas.
Kansas?
Yeah, right near Kansas City.
Well Elder, you're not in Kansas any
more.
Yep, heard that one already.
Brother Rose, are you in our ward?
Brother Rose isn't baptised yet.
Why is that I keep forgeting...
Brother Rose can't give up his
coffee.
I'm trying.
We got a deal going. For every cup of coffee he drinks,
we get a free ride somewhere.
What are we up to now?
67.
You know there's only one way to
pay that off...
clean the slate.
I know.
Benny's getting baptised on Saturday.
Feel like going for a swim?
Elders, Brother Rose, hi!
Hey, Benny.
How ya doing?
Great. Benny, I would like you to
meet my brand new companion.
Elder Allen.
Elder Allen, hi.
Hi.
Where're you from?
Kansas.
Where?
Back east, mid-west.
You know, Toto, Dorothy, yellow brick road.
Yeah, I love that movie
Come on out back, Brother Rose.
How are ya?
I'm doing well. How are you?
Good to see you.
Hi elders.
Oh, my gosh, what is this?
Oh Elaine, you didn't have to do
that.
Oh, yes she did.
I see you finally made it.
I am right on time.
If you're not ten minutes early,
you're late.
Yeah, who told you that?
You did.
So is this the greenie?
I'm Elder Allen.
Hi Elder Allen, I'm Sister Monson.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
You too.
This is Benny's sister Elaine.
Hi.
Benny, do you want to eat first or
shall we have an interview?
Honestly, I think I'd rather eat first. If
that's alright.
Give you time to relax.
That's right.
Benny, who would you like to say
the blessing?
Brother Rose, will you say it?
Okay.
Our Father in Heaven, we thank
you for this food...
Okay, Benny...
the reason l'm here today is to talk with
you a little bit about your baptism.
Yes, it's on Saturday.
Yeah.
And to be sure that you understand the
covenants that you'll be making with the Lord.
And also to be sure that you are ready
and worth y to make those covenants.
So I need to ask you a few
questions.
And whatever we talk about is just
between you and me.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Alright.
What do you play?
I played a little baseball...
No, I meant musical instrument.
Piano? Guitar?
No. Not really. Do you... play
anything?
Cello.
It's shaped like a really big violin.
I know what a cello is.
My brothers were all jocks.
I'm not a jock.
They could bench press 300 pounds,
but they wouldn't read a book to sa ve their lives.
I like to read.
Oh really?
Yeah, I do.
Alright then...
in a jock's opinion of course,
what would you sa y are the three
greatest books ever written?
Wow, there's so many...
why don't you go first?
Alright that's easy.
First would be "Grapes of Wrath" by John Steinbeck.
Second would be Tolstoy's "War and Peace" or "Ana Corinnina".
You take your pick.
And then maybe Chaim Potok's "My
Name is Asher Lev".
Have you ever read any of those?
I think I read one of Steinbeck's
back in high school.
It was about the dumb guy and he
strangles the rabbits, you know?
"Of Mice and Men"?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a short one.
Okay, your turn.
Wait, let me guess.
Volumes one through three of the
Goosebumps series.
Actually um, hmmm, I think my
choices would be...
...the Bible, the Book of Mormon
and the Doctrine and Convenants.
Yeah, those would definately be my
picks.
You set yourself up for that one.
So, you think I'm ready?
I think you are.
Elder?
Do you think...
...could someone like me teach the
gospel?
...be a missionary I mean?
Absolutely. You just take a year or
so to prepare and study and then...
if you're worthy and able, you could
be a missionary, yeah.
I can run faster than you can in
these.
I know you can. I know it.
But I'm 24 years old.
Benny... when I was baptised I was
25.
I was in my second year of medical
school.
You could have been a doctor by
now.
This is the best thing I've ever done.
It's the best thing I'll ever do.
So, what do you think of the
sisters?
I think Monson's nice. I don't know
about that other one though.
Yeah. Sister Fronk.
Yeah, what a...
What?
She's a very smart girl.
She thinks so.
Well, she is pretty, don't you think?
No, I didn't notice that.
Maybe if she'd smile once in a
while.
She had on a nice dress though...
don't you think?
You know, I didn't notice.
Kinegar! Elder Kinegar! Kinegar!
Hold him down!
C'mon, his tongue, hold it down!
Not with your fingers. He'll bite your
fingers off
Oh great, here we go again. Call
9-1 -1 now!
We need some oil.
Wait, I've got oil. Hold him!
I'm holding him.
C'mon!...
Say the blessing man!
Hold him!
No, no, no. It's North Lincoln. Just a
block from Bundy.
Marcus James Dalton,
by the authority of the Holy Melchizedek Priesthood,
l annoint you with this oil which has been
set aside for the blessing of the sick.
In the name of Jesus Christ Amen.
North Lincoln.
Let me seal. Take his hands.
Marcus James Dalton, in the name
of Jesus Christ and by the power
of the Holy Melchizedek Priesthood,
I seal this anointing which has been made by a worthy
and faithful preisthood holder. I
leave a blessing upon thee...
Okay, let's go, let's go!
Dr. Betrune, 7203.
Why don't you come with me?
A brain tumor is a very difficult thing
to treat.
They operated and took most of it
out before his mission...
but, they didn't get it all.
It stopped growing and that's when
he put in his papers.
He had to go through chemotherapy, radiation.
He lost a lot of his hair,
he lost his energy.
I think that's why they sent him here,
because we have the best cancer center in the world here. Just in case.
He's got maybe three or four
months left.
You can learn a lot from him in that
time.
You're not sending him home?
I tried sending him home. He won't
go!
Hey, how ya doing?
What day is it?
It's Thursday.
We got a 3:30 appointment.
Take Sandoval.
Yeah, sure.
Just rest.
3:30.
I got it.. .3:30... Sandoval.
Take Sandoval.
I'll take him. I'll take Sandoval.
What's that again?
As l was saying, family relationships
do not have to end with death.
Couples can be married for eternity
in temples.
Didn't I tell somebody to take out
this trash?
I'll do it in a minute! I'm talking to
somebody here!
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
Families can have the promise that if they live
worthy the y can endure forever, not just until death.
Let me get this straight...
You're telling me that even after I'm dead...
I'm gonna be with my family and all?
That's right. But only if you live
worthy, of course.
Look guys...
I really don't think I'm interested.
That's my mom and that's my dad.
He lost a little weight since then, though.
Those... are my little brothers.
There she is. The one I told you
about...
she's waitin' for me.
My little brothers are gonna get at
her. I know they will.
Isn't she gorgeous?
She's beautiful.
Where's the rest of them?
...the mission pictures?
Oh, right here.
Wow!
Can't afford to get them developed.
I figure... I'll just wait until I get
home and do it all at once.
Probably cost me... about a
hundred thousand bucks.
Hey! Get outta here!
That's not funny!
That's just plain childish!
Somebody get back here and close
that door!
I've had enough of this
childishness.
Short sheetin' beds, pictures on the
toilet.
It's getting way out of hand. Way
out.
I can't pray this morning. I don't feel like praying.
I feel like strangling somebody.
Mangum, you sa y the prayer.
I said it yesterday.
While Pops is gone I'm in charge.
That's what the president said, so you say the prayer.
Father in Heaven, thank thee for
this day and for a good night's rest.
And please bless Pops that he'll be
back with us again very soon.
And bless us today that we'll have a
good day out there on the streets.
In the name of Jesus Christ, Amen.
Amen. Let's just eat and put this
childishness behind us.
What'd you want? Granola?
No, I think we got a bad box.
Gimme the sugar puffy things.
Dalton's death bed...
Pops, its Allen?
Yeah. Where are ya?
I'm just on the street right now in
Hollywood.
Are you wearing your watch? Do
you know what time it is?
Yes, I know what time it is.
Alright, what are you doing?
We're on our way to that discussion.
Who are you taking?
Kinegar.
Take Banks.
Why? Just take Banks. And hurry up,
you're going to be late.
Fine. I'll take Banks.
Alright. Goodbye.
Take Banks.
Figures.
Yeah, okay, you see what I'm asking... what's that all about?
Blacks aren't good enough to be priests?
I already told you blacks can be priests.
Look at me. Do I look white to you?
You are starting to look a little white
to me, yeah.
And what is this 1978 stuff?
Why couldn't we hold the priesthood before then?
My daddy was a good preacher.
Why couldn't he have been a Mormon preacher?
The first thing you gotta
understand...
Oh, I understand all right.
It's that the priesthood isn't a right,
it's the authority to act in God's name.
It's not just something you can take on yourself.
I mean, it has to be given to you.
By the white man?
No, you're missing the whole point.
It's not about race.
It is about race! It's always about
race!
And what about that part in the Bible, you know the part where
it says God accepts e verybody no matter what race they are?
Right! That's absolutely right!
And that's when the apostle Peter was
commanded to take the church to the gentiles,
the white people, because before
that it had only gone to the Jews.
It's another kind of parallel.
It's the ancient church of Christ with the Latter-Day Church of Christ.
And it's probable that we were the first church in the country
to have black leaders in front of white congregations.
That's right. And I think what Elder
Banks is trying to say...
Hey, nobody cares what you think.
Alright?
And even when the Jews had the gospel,
even when they had the priesthood, not all the men had the priesthood.
Only the tribe of Levi. They were the only ones that
were given the authority to officiate in the temple.
And that's in the Old Testament.
You can look it up.
And that's another thing,
Why just the men?
Why couldn't I be a Mormon
preacher?
I'm sure I know more about the
Bible than he does.
Yeah.
That's the last thing that you all want is a black woman behind the pulpit
It's the Lord's Authority. It's the
power to act in his name.
He gives it to whome ver he sees fit,
whenever he sees fit. That's all there is to it.
So, when is he gonna let us
women have a bit of it?
Is he ever gonna let us have it?
I don't know.
You'll just have to ask him that.
Boy, they are makin' a fool outta
you.
You're going. I know you're going.
How do you know?
Because we've been together three
months.
I've been in the same ward for five.
Yeah, there's no way. You're outta
here.
Hey, Steerman was in Westwood
for seven.
No wa y!
Yeah.
I could talk to Beecroft for you.
What? We're kinda tight.
That guy owes me.
I'm sure.
Here.
Thanks.
I didn't even know about this stuff
until after I was baptised.
Threw me for a loop you know?
It's like the Lord just led me smack
up against a big, brick wall.
I read everything I could find on it.
I asked everbody else what they
thought.
I called this guy, this African guy, I
mean, a real African guy.
This Mormon guy and I didn't even meet him,
I just knew that he was black.
He didn't help any.
You know,
my brother served his mission in Mexico and he baptised like 80 people.
No wa y!
Yeah, I'm gonna be pretty embarrassed when I go home with,
like twelve.
Twelve is good. That's nothing to be
ashamed of.
Really... 12's good?
Yeah.
80's better, but 12's good.
80's better.
Well, 12's good.
I was on this youth activity thing
and...
We rode a bus out to Nauvoo,
to Carthage where the prophet was killed.
Have you ever been there?
Well, they walk you through the jail and they show you the rooms and...
then they take you to the room where
the mob broke in and killed the prophet.
And they play this tape, this audio
tape.
Man, my heart just broke open,
and all my pride went away.
And trying to look good in front of
my friends and I just started to cry.
And not because I was sad,
...because I was full of light.
I was full of heat.
And it wasn't me.
It was like the Spirit of the Lord just
came in and sat in my body.
And I knew right then...
that all of it was true...
all of it.
It's like I wanted to share that with
them you know?
But I couldn't...
cause it's sacred.
Sometimes I think God does it on
purpose.
It's like He gives you a hundred
reasons to believe,
and then He just drops one or two
for you not to believe.
So that you can choose,
to see if you really want to believe.
I am Sandoval the Lamanite!
Oh, Hollywood! The days of your
probation are past.
You have procrastinated the day of
your salvation
until it is everlastingly too late,
...and your destruction is made
sure.
You have sought all your life for that
which you could not obtain,
You have sought for happiness in
doing inquity.
So repent, oh Hollywood!
Repent I say. For the day of the
Lord is coming.
For not your houses, nor your
mansions, nor your movie deals
will save you from the wrath of God!
Hey.
Oh. Hey.
What would you think if the apostles
and prophets weren't telling the truth?
I mean, what if the y believed all
their lives...
worked their way up to the top and
now...
they know it's all a big lie.
I mean not just mormonism, but
Christianity, the whole thing.
They won't tell us.
Hey there.
Hi.
The man that was here Markus
Dalton?
I'm sorry, he's gone.
Is he dead?
We came to bring him breakfast, he
had snuck off on us.
Kay, thanks.
Come on!
Gwen Yule, having been
comissioned of Jesus Christ
I baptise you in the name of the
Father
and of the Son and of the Holy
Ghost. Amen.
"The spirit of God like a fire is
burning
the latter-day glory..."
Well, looked who showed up.
They're looking for you at the
hospital.
I don't think they're gonna find me.
Where's Benny?
He didn't show?
Hi.
Can I sit down?
I guess.
Just don't be rude to me, okay?
I wasn't rude...
I was rude...
I'm sorry.
Do you forgive me?
Sure.
I wrote down the names of those
books that you told me about.
I'm gonna read them when I get
home.
Yeah, look at Pops.
Thinks he's still young.
Do you know wh y I came on a
mission?
Because you couldn't get married?
I'm sorry.
I can be a real jerk sometimes.
I almost did get married...
I backed out two weeks before the
wedding.
He was a returned missionary. We'd
grown up together.
I loved him so much.
I wrote him every week... and sent him cookies...
and neck ties... and everything.
But when he came home he was
just so... different.
Better, you know?
He was just so strong.
And his faith, when he bore his
testomony... wow.
And, I couldn't bear my testimony.
I mean, it's not like I was shy or
anything I just
...I couldn't say it was all true.
That Joseph Smith was a prophet...
the Book of Mormon's the word of
God.
I believed it, but I
I wanted to know.
I wanted to be strong like he was.
He wrote every couple of weeks
for the first few months...
but, he doesn't write anymore.
I'm sorry.
Now I know...
I really do.
Harmer took the van.
Yeah, that figures.
No sign of Benny?
I think maybe he changed his mind.
Let's go get him.
Should we take the bus?
I don't wanna take the bus.
You're not tired.
I'm exhausted, but if I sit down I'll
fall asleep
and if I fall asleep I'll probably lapse
into a coma.
And if I lapse into a coma I'll probably die,
so I don't want to take the bus.
Pops, what time is it?
It's late.
What about those girls?
What girls? You know. The girls.
What time is it?
They're early.
Hi. We're the sister missionaries.
Elder Dalton said you might like to
speak with us?
Man, this is really strange. They're
always here this time of day.
Check this out, there's like three
days worth of mail in here.
Have you been a member all your
life?
No...
Well, yeah, kind of...
My mom married this Mormon guy
when I was seven.
So, you know, I got baptised when I
was eight.
We were Pentecostal before that.
Pentecostal?
Yeah.
Cool.
You close to him?
Your stepdad?
No...
He's in prison now.
Turns out he molested some kids.
He traveled around a lot and
he did it in a bunch of different
states.
So, they're taking turns keeping
him.
I'm sorry.
He never touched me or anything.
I'm grateful for that, you know?
Count your blessings I guess.
He brought us the church.
He baptised me, ordained me.
Sometimes I can't...
separate what he gave me
I mean, where does the good stuff
stop and the bad stuff start?
When I think of what he did...
When my mom married him, he...
I had to take his last name.
She wanted me to.
Sometimes I just wish I would
change it back, you know?
I guess, I just haven't had much
luck in the dad department.
Well, people let you down...
at least your real father's there for
you.
I haven't seen him in thirteen years.
I was talking about your real father.
Pops, Pops...
Wake up.
What?
Kinegar's gone.
Let's go.
Don't tell me, it's past curfew.
What, are you guys gonna go with
me?
Actually. I was hoping you'd come
back with us.
Read those books I left you.
There's a lot of things
in there you should know.
Get your hands off me!
Look, I've read e verything you've
read and then some.
Why do you think it took me four
years to join the church?
Because I had to know every stupid
accusation.
You're gonna go home,
you're gonna research and then you're gonna wish you could come back.
Well guess what?
Naw, I know what you're thinking. Look at you,
you were so afraid that you were just gonna disappear.
Well maybe I'd believe a little more
too if I had cancer.
You know it's true.
I've heard you say it.
I was lying.
This bus goes right through Kansas
City.
Come on.
Suit yourself.
Elder?
Yeah?
He is wrong... isn't he?
Why are you still here?
I keep training you guys...
kids like you.
Guys I came out with, they're zone
leaders, assistants to the president,
and he just keeps sendin' me you
guys.
Nobody made you come out here.
You could have stayed home.
Nobody would have cared.
What were you thinking?
...that you'd put on a name tag and necktie...
and suddenly you'd be a different person?
Your faith would be stronger?
Didn't you pray before you came
out here?
Didn't you study?
I can't solve your problems.
I can teach you the rules, I can teach you the discussions,
but what you really need to know,
what's gonna get you out of bed in
the morning,
get you out on the street and talking
to strangers,
I can't teach you that.
And I can't convert you, Elder.
Father in Heaven...
...I've been in this place for days.
I don't know if I'm doing the right
thing.
I ask...
I ask you now to tell me...
if this is true.
Father in Heaven...
Father...
Father.
Hey.
Get up.
Let's do some good.
Elders.
Brother Morales, hi.
Hi. Laura's not here yet...
she didn't tell me you were coming.
Today we're... here to see you.
Brother Morales...
I know you might not believe this,
but we're here on our Father's business.
And you might be the first person
that's hearing me say this...
...you are.
The messages we've taught you
are true.
I know they're true.
And I can feel the Lord's spirit is
with us right now...
right here.
Can't you feel it?
Well, I know that Laura's felt it.
I know that's she's found what I've
found
and I know that the Lord
wants you to let her join his church.
Elders, I really have to get back to
what I was doing.
I'll tell Laura you came. She'll be
sad that she missed you.
Would you mind if we left with a
pra yer?
Could we kneel?
Of course.
Who would you like to say the
pra yer?
Our Father in Heaven...
Would you mind saying the prayer?
Our Father...
who art...
in hea ven...
Our Father
who art in heaven...
hallowed be thy name...
Elders..
Hi. We just saw your dad.
Thank you, elders, thank you.
...and we ask Thee to help us find
Benny as soon as possible...
and we ask thee to look after him
and watch over him carefully
wherever he may be,
And... we...
Yeah, he would have been admitted
probably yesterday or the day before.
Okay, yeah, thank you.
Hi, yeah,
I'm looking for a friend of mine I'm worried he might have been
in an accident or something...
His name is Benny Yao.
Y -- A -- O, Yao... Benjamin.
Uh-huh...
Thank you very much.
Sent him home an hour ago.
What am I gonna do?
I never even saw them coming.
I was just walking, you know?
I was just walking.
They took your money?
I didn't have any money!
They saw that I didn't have any
money, so they beat me even more.
I can't even walk.
I can't sit up.
Hurts so bad.
I think I'm infected.
Gonna die.
Benny, you're not gonna die.
They wouldn't have released you from the clinic if you were gonna die.
They sent me home because I don't
have any money...
have an y insurance.
I don't wanna die.
It'll get better.
This is just like when my mother
died.
I knew that something was wrong,
and the doctor said she would be fine.
But she's not fine.
My brother, he's laying in the bed and the doctor says he'll be okay,
and he's not.
I thought the y were gonna kill me.
They beat me with their guns.
They beat me, kicked me,
they stood on my throat.
Look...
they broke my crutches.
Why would they break my
crutches?
Elder Dalton...
they say you're a doctor?
No... I never finished medical
school.
I'm sorry..
But is there anything you can do?
Do you belie ve in Jesus Christ?
I do.
Do you believe that he died for your
sins and that he has all power,
even to raise you from the dead if it
is his will?
I do.
Benjamin Yao,
by the authority of the Holy
Melchizedek priesthood
I anoint you with this oil in the name
of Jesus Christ, Amen.
Benjamin Yao...
by the authority of the Melchizedek
priesthood
I seal this anointing and following the prompting
of the Spirit I leave a blessing with you
our Saviour has told us that...
...if we knock, he will answer, if we
ask...
we shall receive.
Our Father in Heaven has heard your many prayers these
many nights as you ha ve asked for the ability to walk.
This day, Benn y, you will receive
this great blessing.
Through your faith in our Lord and Savior,
Jesus Christ, and through the power of the priesthood
you may rise from this bed and walk
and from this day forward you will walk
and not be weary,
and you will run and not faint.
This is the blessing you desire,
and this is the blessing that our father in Heaven desires for you.
And I leave it with you in the name
of Jesus Christ, Amen.
Amen.
They just called me at work, and...
I don't know. I was just thinking, they didn't let
me out, and then I couldn't see him. And then I
thought that maybe he died. I don't want him to die.
He's not gonna die... he's not gonna
die.
Elaine.
I'm so glad
Wow...
I feel...
Hey, Pops...
You doin' okay?
Yeah, are you kidding? We've got
three baptisms on Saturday.
Yeah.
Yeah! Woo!
Hey, Elder?
Yeah?
We did some good today.
Yeah...
Yeah we did.
Hey, its 6:30, let's go...
Companion prayers, let's go!
Pops?...
Elder Dalton?
I'm Gene Dalton, Mark's dad.
Excuse me.
Hi, pal.
If a few of you will come forward and grasp the casket
by the handles firmly, then we'll proceed to the...
We'll handle this. Can you just give us a few minutes alone?
We'll take care of it... thank you.
Elders, come on up here and help.
President...
maybe you could...
say a few words since we're not really
gonna get a chance to say good-bye.
I can't help but think of the
scripture...
"Greater love hath no man than
this,
that he lay down his life for his
friends.
Three years ago Elder Dalton found
out...
that He wouldn't grow old...
that he probably wouldn't get married,
and that he wouldn't have children.
Most men would've cursed God and
given up, he came here.
He chose to be with us.
And there isn't a day goes by that I don't run
into somebody whose life Elder Dalton touched.
Somebody that he taught. Somebody that he trained,
or reached in and pulled out of the world and into the light of the gospel.
Now, he wasn't perfect, we all know
that.
He had faults and weaknesses and
he made mistakes.
He lacked patience, he lost his
temper.
He even flirted with my wife.
But he was just like we are, imperfect,
even clumsy spiritually sometimes.
But other times perfect...
if only for a moment, in his heart,
and he had his eye single
to the Glory of God.
Now I want you elders to know
that even though you may not give your
lives as dramatically as Elder Dalton,
that you are heroes and martyrs.
You are giving your lives,
your hours and your days and your months and years in service of God.
"Whosoever will save his life shall
lose it,
and whosoever will lose his life for
my sake shall find it."
Elder Dalton has lost his mortal life,
but we know that he's found his
eternal life.
Amen.
President Beecroft didn't let us
grieve too long.
He told us to get right back to work.
Transfers came two days later.
Only one person from our district
was moved.
We knew it was going to happen.
I'm gonna miss you.
Sister, Costa Mesa, huh?
Yup.
Go get them.
Thanks.
Sister, it's been a pleasure.
Good luck with everything..
Thank you.
Hey, I'll call you when I come
across some good books.
Alright..
Try not to drive too many people out
of the church.
Yeah, maybe somebody in Costa Mesa can do something with that hair.
Kinegar's replacement finally
showed up,
...another spud named Elder Rex.
He arrived with my new companion,
...Elder Downey, from Salt Lake
City.
How ya doin'?
Hey.
So where're you from?
Kansas.
Ah, Kansas, wow! Big tornadoes,
right?
Yeah.
Cool.
Help my sister please, she's been
looking for a job for so long...
I just hope that she finds a job that she
likes and that she feels good about.
"For all have not every gift given
unto them.
"For there are many gifts,
and every man is given a gift by the spirit of God".
...and bless us with thy spirit as we go out on the streets today,
we pray,
in the name of Jesus Christ, amen.
Amen.
Alright. Let's do some good.
Hi.
Everything worked out as Pops had
hoped.
On Saturday I performed my first
baptism,
...actually my first three baptisms.
Thanks Mangum.
Later that night we taught 15 of
Benny's friends and family.
Within the next three months,
eight of them were baptised, including his sister.
Dalton was right, the field is white and ready to harvest,
even in Los Angeles.
The last I heard Laura was going to Ricks college and she was engaged.
Her father never did join the church.
He died of a heart attack three
years later.
One year to the day after Benny's baptism,
he left for his mission to Taiwan.
He served a successful mission and he's now the
mission leader in the Santa Monica Third Ward.
Brother Rose ne ver went back to drinking coffee,
but he is still giving free rides to the missionaries.
I recently heard that Carla did get
baptized.
It took two years and a major career
change,
but now she's the spiritual living
teacher in her relief society.
Sister Monson went home and somehow within a year,
she became a secretary for one of the general authorities.
She married a construction worker
and ga ve birth to twins.
Magnum found out that his father had
sold his car to help pay for his mission,
so he stole his father's motorcycle and went off on a cross country tour.
He didn't come back.
Finally, President Beecroft bumped
into him in Casper, Wyoming.
He was living in a trailor behind a
truck stop.
He was a cook,
his girlfriend was a waitress who was expecting their first child.
They gave president a free bowl of chili,
president gave them a free wedding.
Sandoval the Lamanite used the Navy to help him finish college.
The Navy is now using him to train torpedo men somewhere in Virginia.
He's married, no kids yet.
He says he's going to retire at 42 and
live the rest of his life on a houseboat.
His wife says otherwise.
Banks returned to Los Angeles after
his mission.
He studied comparative religion at Loyola University and
married Elder Sandavol's little sister in the L.A. Temple.
He now teaches seminary to high school students in St.
George, Utah.
I don't know what happened to Kinegar.
I ne ver heard if he came back to the church or not.
My parents, so far, have not.
Elder Downey and I became good friends.
We still talk every month or two.
We talk about all the people we taught, all our companions,
all of our funniest, and all of our most sacred experiences.
As for me, when I went home,
I transferred all my credits to Brigham Young University.
My first day of class, my freshman
English teacher became ill
and was permanently replaced by a
graduate student named Jeanine Fronk.
We were married two months later.
Somehow I still got a C in English.
We're thinking 40 years from now,
maybe we'll go on another mission...
...together.
Oh, yeah, two months shy of our
first anniversary
we had a baby boy,
a beautiful baby boy.
We named him Dalton.
Dalton Allen...
Mostly...
we just call him Pops.