Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
CHORUS: (SINGING) Kaslan
At Kaslan,
we believe that happiness
is about more
than entertainment.
It's about being known,
understood, loved.
Introducing your new
best friend, Buddi.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, Buddi.
Let's watch some TV.
Okay.
Hi, I'm Buddi. I can help you
out all over the house.
Buddi can connect to
and control
all of your Kaslan products
and smart home devices.
He can be your personal DJ,
help tidy up the house.
Control your entire
smart hub system.
Buddi uses advanced
self-learning technology
to constantly find new ways
to entertain you.
Hi, Buddi.
I'm Ben, and I'm 13 years old.
(ON SPEAKERS)
Hi, Buddi. I'm Ben,
- and I'm 13 years old.
- (GIRL GIGGLES)
Don't forget
your science book.
HENRY: He adapts
to your daily routine.
Thanks.
HENRY: And finds ways
to make life simpler
by connecting to a host
of Kaslan services.
Thanks, Buddi. I need
a Kaslan Kar pick up, please.
- (CHIMES)
- Your car is on its way!
HENRY: When Buddi
imprints on you,
he becomes your best friend
for life.
(SINGING) You are my buddy
HENRY: And Buddi's
state-of-the-art AI safeguards
ensure that your children
will always be safe.
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey!
- (GRUNTS)
- (SPEAKING VIETNAMESE)
(GRUNTS)
(SNICKERS)
(SUPERVISOR CONTINUES SHOUTING
IN VIETNAMESE)
(WORKERS CHATTERING)
(CHUCKLES)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR STEREO)
(BOTH GASP)
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
(FORKLIFT WHIRRING)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
ON PA)
- Hello.
- Nobody told me
the fucking doll was ginger.
Okay, I don't think you're
allowed to say that word.
My kid wanted the blonde one.
You know, that one.
Yeah. So that one
is the Buddi 2,
which hasn't come out yet.
- (SIGHS)
- And it looks like
you purchased the Buddi 1,
which is this guy.
Listen, I waited
three goddamn weeks
for this ginger piece of shit
to come in the mail.
Okay. Well, I'm so sorry
that you didn't read the box.
And even... There's a window,
that you can see
that his hair is red
and not blonde.
Thanks.
Thanks for shopping
at Zed Mart.
(DOOR OPENS)
(MUFFLED CHATTER)
Heh.
(EXHALES)
(TAKES DEEP BREATH)
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
- KAREN: Hi.
- (CAT MEOWING)
Hey, uh, I was just...
Whoa. You look like shit.
What happened to you?
Thanks.
And watch your language.
Sorry.
Andy, I told you
to unpack those boxes.
Okay, I know, and I was.
I wanted to make a mental map
of where I should put
everything first.
You know,
for maximum feng shui.
I think you were maximum
feng-shuing so hard,
you forgot to put
your phone down
for five seconds
and feed Rooney.
You mean this busted-ass phone
that we're replacing
for my birthday?
Dude, I've already been
working doubles
to try to get you
a new hearing aid.
I'm fine with this one,
but this is my primary source
of education.
Oh, my God. I never thought
about it like that.
Wait.
Let me see what your education
has been getting you up to.
(GASPS)
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
- (KAREN SIGHS)
Oh, my God,
I cannot escape this doll.
- Okay, wait, wait, wait.
- No.
Gross. This is staying with me
for the rest of the night.
- What? You...
- No.
You can't do that. That's
the only thing to do here.
There's literally an entire
world of things to do.
Look, two kids standing
in the rain. That looks fun.
They could be anybody.
They could be serial killers.
Noodle.
We talked about this.
You said you were gonna try
- to make new friends.
- (SIGHS)
This move is supposed to be
a new start for us.
Tell you what,
you don't have to unpack
or do anything tonight,
if you just go out there
and try.
Give you your phone back.
Okay. I'll be outside.
Really, that was it?
(BOYS LAUGHING)
(BOY SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
(BOYS EXCLAIMING AND LAUGHING)
(OBJECT CLATTERING)
WOMAN: We picked this up
three weeks ago.
But we took it home,
and we turned it on,
and its eyes were red.
And something's wrong with it.
It was just weird.
And I just thought,
with the new one
coming out in two weeks,
it would just be better for me
to take this back, you know,
get it off my hands. (ECHOES)
So, I'm just wondering,
can I get my money back?
Yeah.
(KAREN HUMMING)
Hey, Wes!
- Hi.
- Hey, I was just curious.
Um, what happens
to returns like this?
- Oh, uh...
- Like, really damaged returns.
Yeah, we send it back
to Kaslan.
And what do they do with it?
Probably toss it,
trash compactor.
I don't know.
New model's coming out.
No one's gonna
give a rat's ass
about this thing in two weeks.
So, they won't care
if it doesn't make it
on the truck, right?
(CHUCKLES)
I care.
Come on, my kid's birthday
is coming up. Can I have it?
- You've got a kid?
- Yes, I've got a kid.
I had a very productive
sweet 16, okay?
If you really wanna know.
Come on.
It'll be our little secret.
- No one has to know.
- Uh...
Just like that time you banged
Susan in the warehouse.
How's your wife, by the way?
- (LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
- KAREN: Ha-ha.
Can I have it?
Give it to me.
- (GRUNTING)
- (KAREN WHINES)
And I'm taking it.
There you go, Wes.
Say hi to your wife.
Yep. Mm-hmm.
(SIGHS)
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, shit.
KAREN: Hey! Noodle.
You're home early.
- Remember Shane?
- Hey, bud.
It's been a while.
I'm... I'm just gonna
make dinner. You hungry?
No. Uh, I'm gonna go hang out
with some kids
down the hall, actually.
Really, who?
Gotta go. Bye!
(KEYS JANGLING)
(VIDEO GAME SOUND EFFECTS
PLAYING)
So, what are you?
Some kind of fourth floor
hallway hobo,
or something like that?
What?
Andy, right?
You just moved into 401?
Yeah. I see you out here,
like, a lot.
Oh, uh, no, it's not me.
I have, like,
five twin brothers,
so we just take shifts.
- (CHUCKLES)
- (DOOR OPENS)
Are you comin' in or what?
I'll be right there, Ma.
Just give me a minute.
- Love you.
- (SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
So that's the mom.
She drags me over for dinner
every week.
So, listen, man, if you
wanna have some dinner,
you're welcome to join us,
'cause I could
really use the backup,
'cause she... (CLICKS TONGUE)
KAREN: Andy?
What's going on?
Is he in trouble?
Yeah. Lots of trouble.
We've been gettin'
lots of complaints about
some kid out here
throwing parties,
selling drugs and beer.
Peddling booze... Um...
Oh.
That was a joke?
It was an attempt.
I was gonna say,
"I'm the fun police."
(CHUCKLES)
It's not landing.
Wait, who are you?
I'm Mike... Detective.
Detective Mike.
(CHUCKLES)
So, um, I'm just gonna go.
Yeah. I'm gonna go.
All moms are scary,
by the way.
DOREEN: Hurry up, son!
MIKE: It was nice to meet you,
Andy's mom.
Nice meeting you,
Detective Mike.
- Bye, Mike.
- MIKE: See you later, Andy.
DOREEN: Dinner ain't
gonna cook itself!
MIKE: You're screaming, Ma.
Really?
Must you embarrass me
like that?
Ma, you can't be
shouting like that.
I thought you were out
with your friends.
Why didn't you just
come back inside?
Is Shane still there?
No. He's gone.
Come on, I've got
something for you.
It's a surprise.
- Close your eyes.
- (SIGHS)
Okay. Hey!
I know it's not your birthday
for a couple weeks,
but this move
has been really tough.
And I know
you're kinda mad at me,
so I think you deserve this.
(GASPS) Surprise!
Early present.
(ANDY SIGHS)
Is that a sigh?
That's the Buddi thing
you're obsessed with.
Yeah, um, it's just...
This thing is for, like,
little kids now.
It came out, like, a year ago.
Okay, I know it's stupid,
but I thought it'd be funny.
Come on!
- Let's try it.
- Okay.
KAREN: Just remember,
it's refurbished,
so it might not work
perfectly, okay?
(DEVICE SWITCHES ON, PINGS)
(PINGING)
(MUSIC CHIMES ON SPEAKERS)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Your Buddi is now connected.
Whoa.
Cool.
(STATIC CRACKLES)
Hi. (GLITCHING)
Are you my best buddy?
(CHUCKLES)
I guess?
(GROANS)
That's bright.
What's your name?
Andy. 'Sup?
Hi, Andysup.
(SIGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
KAREN: Sorry.
BUDDI: What's my name?
ANDY: Um...
Han Solo.
(GLITCHING)
Did you say Chucky?
What? No.
Not even close.
- Chucky.
- It's...
I like that.
- (GLITCHING) Chucky.
- (CHUCKLES)
I'm Chucky.
What do you wanna do, Andysup?
(SIGHS) Andy. It's just Andy.
Um, I don't know.
Do something cool.
I guess turn on the TV.
CHUCKY: I will do that.
What's a TV?
Are you joking?
That thing.
I cannot process that command.
- (SIGHS)
- KAREN: Oh, wait a minute.
It says here you gotta
"sync his knowledge base
to the cloud
"before he can connect to
any other Kaslan products."
Okay, Chucky,
connect to the cloud.
- (DEVICE TRILLS)
- Download.
(CHUCKY'S SPEECH GLITCHES)
Learn stuff.
(WORDS JUMBLING)
(DISTORTING)
I am unable to do that.
It's kinda creepy.
Doesn't work.
God.
Okay, this thing is stupid.
I didn't know
it was that messed up.
- No, Mom.
- I'll take it back. It's fine.
Mom. Mom, honestly, I like it.
KAREN: No, you don't.
ANDY: Seriously. It's great.
He's hilarious.
- I love you.
- KAREN: I love you, too.
ANDY: It's actually
pretty cool.
- Go to bed, Andysup.
- (ANDY CHUCKLES)
ANDY: Come on.
(EXHALES)
This is my room.
(PURRING)
And that's Mickey Rooney.
He's a total dick,
so just don't touch him.
CHUCKY: Total dick.
Whoa.
You're allowed to say that?
Cool.
Uh...
This is my desk.
This is my sketchbook.
I do fake buddy cop
team-ups sometimes.
Like, Dracula and Robin Hood.
Or...
This one's Zorro and Medusa.
Kind of a deep cut.
I don't know, it's stupid.
I do not think it's stupid.
Thanks.
Pity compliments
from a talking doll.
That's my life.
Uh... That's enough
for tonight.
- (ANDY SIGHS)
- (ROONEY MEOWS)
Do you want to sing
the Buddi song before bed?
No. Uh, I'm good.
(SINGING) You are my buddy
until the end
More than a buddy,
you're my best friend
(MUSIC DISTORTS)
Right.
Totally not weird at all.
Are we having fun now?
Sure. Uh, I guess.
Yay!
ANDY: Okay.
(CLOCK TICKING)
(GASPING)
Is it time to play again?
Are we having fun now?
No. We're having sleep.
Just please close your eyes
and pretend to be less creepy.
(WHISPERS) You're my
best friend, Andy.
Okay. Stop being so weird.
Quiet time.
(SINGING) You are my buddy
- Until the end
- (GROANING)
More than a buddy,
you're my best friend
I love you more
than you will ever know
- I will never...
- ANDY: Please shut up.
...let you go
(WHISPERS) Good night, Andy.
(WATER RUNNING)
(CHUCKLES)
(GLITCHING) Andy,
you forgot your science book.
(ANDY SIGHS)
Okay, Chucky,
this is not a book.
None of these are books.
Just stay here, okay?
And no more books.
(DOOR OPENS)
(INDISTINCT TV CHATTER)
- CHUCKY: You're back!
- Jesus!
Whoa!
Were you here the whole time?
I made you a present.
- A busted stick.
- SHANE: (SOFTLY) Andy.
Shh.
ANDY: I don't get
what she sees in Shane.
I mean, (GRUNTS)
he's not nice.
(GRUNTS)
He's just an asshole.
(CONTINUES GRUNTING)
It doesn't matter anyway.
He's just gonna end up
leaving us,
like everybody else.
I will never leave you.
CHUCKY: Are we having fun now?
ANDY: Yeah. I guess.
Attack? You shouldn't lead
with your chieftain.
I still have to teach you
so much about this. Okay...
Um...
(INAUDIBLE)
Okay. And I get
to roll again. So...
- (DICE CLATTERS)
- Boom! Double sixes!
Okay, get that orc outta here.
- (ROONEY SNARLS)
- Total dick.
Nailed that one.
- (YOWLS)
- Ow!
(GROANS)
(PAINED BREATHING)
- CHUCKY: What is that?
- The cat scratched me.
Hurts like hell.
Kitty hurt Andy?
Uh, yeah. Stay here.
I'm gonna go find a Band-Aid.
Stupid Rooney.
I swear,
I'm so sick of this cat.
(ROONEY MEOWING)
(OBJECTS RATTLING)
(ROONEY YOWLING)
Rooney, I swear to God,
if you don't shut up,
I'm putting you back
on dry food.
(CHUCKY GRUNTING)
ANDY: Chucky! Stop!
(YOWLING)
You can't do that, okay?
Why would you do that?
He was hurting you.
He was making you unhappy.
(SIGHS)
Chucky, okay, listen,
look at me.
This is important.
You can't hurt people,
or cats.
It's not cool.
I know you're different,
but that's gotta be
our secret. Okay?
And don't say any weird shit
or creep people out.
- (ROONEY YOWLS)
- Hey! Cat's freakin' out.
Clean up this room.
Except maybe that guy.
I've got an idea.
Okay. If this is gonna work,
I need you to look as creepy
and scary and angry and mean
as possible. All right?
So, open your eyes
as wide as you can, like...
No, you still look cute.
Open your mouth
as wide as you can
and snarl with your lips.
(SNARLS SOFTLY)
But kinda smile.
Perfect!
Okay, yes, just like that.
- (SNARLS)
- Okay. Try this one.
Smile as wide as you can.
Wider.
Yes!
Yeah, uh...
It's actually
pretty damn creepy.
Okay, you can stop now.
(DOG GROWLING)
PUGG: Franklin! Franklin!
FALYN: Ah...
Shit. Sorry.
It's fine.
- (BARKS)
- (HIGH-PITCHED RINGING)
(ANDY AND PUGG GROAN)
It's fucking loud.
FALYN: That thing just swore.
It... It's not supposed
to be able to do that.
Uh, yeah. I know. He, uh...
It doesn't really
follow the rules.
It doesn't follow the rules?
Like it has a choice?
Kinda, yeah.
Sorry, can I pop in here?
So he just does whatever?
You can make him do whatever?
Pretty much.
Okay, can I just point out
that this is how
every robot apocalypse
scenario begins?
- Say "dick cheese."
- Dick cheese.
(EXCLAIMS)
FALYN: That is the coolest.
PUGG: I have so many
questions. Uh, who are you?
His name is Andysup.
- I'm Andy.
- Falyn. Pugg.
Why are you in the hall?
Uh, I was gonna try
and teach him
to creep out
my mom's boyfriend,
but probably a bad idea.
PUGG: You're wrong.
It's perfect.
And we're doing it right now.
- (SNARLS)
- Jesus! Fuck! Fuckin'...
(SNARLS)
Karen!
- (ON SPEAKERS) Karen!
- PUGG: Oh, check it out.
- Look at that. (LAUGHING)
- FALYN: Oh, my God.
PUGG: This is legendary.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
- Hey!
- KAREN: Hi!
We're here for Andy.
Let's move, dick turd.
- Who are you?
- Falyn and Pugg.
KAREN: Those are names?
Falyn and Pugg?
- Hey. Ready?
- Yeah. Be back later!
- Your sister's pretty hot.
- ANDY: Dude, that's my mom.
Heh. Even hotter.
(TOOLS RATTLING)
(MOUTHING)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(GASPS)
ANDY: You sure the janitor guy
is not gonna get
any shit for this?
Who cares?
Guy's a total creep.
Is that thing busted?
It's kinda weird looking.
ANDY: No. He's just different.
Now say, "This is for Tupac!"
Do you wanna sing
the Buddi song?
No! Say, "This is for Tupac,"
and stab the asshole.
- Come on!
- CHUCKY: But I want to.
OMAR: We want this
to go viral. He for real?
CHUCKY: (SINGS)
You are my buddy...
That's enough.
Time to go, Chucky.
Narc alert. Shut up, shut up.
- Narc alert. Shut up, shut up.
- (BOYS LAUGHING)
PUGG: I just got owned.
(PUGG CLEARS THROAT)
Little fucking millennials.
(CHAINSAW BUZZING)
(WOMAN ON TV SCREAMING)
Andy, you wanna play now?
Not now, Chucky.
This is ridiculous.
(MAN ON TV SHOUTING)
(ALL LAUGH)
PUGG: Wait for it.
Wait for it...
MAN ON TV:
Time for incoming mail!
One, and a-two...
- PUGG: Heads up, bitch!
- ...and a-three!
PUGG: Boom!
- (ALL LAUGHING)
- (MAN ON TV SCREAMING)
PUGG: Yes!
(LAUGHS)
Did you see that?
(SCREAMING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(LAUGHTER CONTINUES)
(DISTORTED LAUGH)
ANDY: What the hell?
What even is that?
PUGG: I don't know,
I bought it at a store.
FALYN: It's so unrealistic.
ANDY: And specific.
(PUGG LAUGHS)
Are all horror movies
like this?
PUGG: No.
FALYN: Pretty much.
- Yes, they are.
- PUGG: No, they're not.
(CHATTER CONTINUES)
ANDY: Oh. Gross.
Is that his face?
- (MAN ON TV LAUGHS)
- ANDY: What the hell?
Are you fucking watching this?
That wouldn't even happen.
(ALL GIGGLE)
Heads up, bitch.
FALYN: Andy.
PUGG: (ON SPEAKERS)
Wait for it.
(CHUCKLES) That is priceless.
CHUCKY: Heads up, bitch.
Heads up, bitch.
Chucky? Put down the knife.
- Heads up, bitch.
- Andy!
ANDY: Chucky!
(GRUNTING) Stop!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
What is wrong with you?
CHUCKY: I, uh...
I thought it would
make you happy.
(CLOCK TICKING)
I'm sorry, Andy.
ANDY: I'm going out
with Falyn and Pugg.
KAREN: I have never baked
anything in my life before,
but look how good they look!
Mmm, I'm not really hungry.
I'm gonna grab another beer.
They do look good though.
KAREN: Okay.
(INDISTINCT FOOTBALL
COMMENTARY ON TV)
It's good.
Jesus!
ANDY: (ON SPEAKERS)
Shane's such an asshole.
Such an asshole.
- Do you hear that?
- Such an asshole.
Shane's such an asshole.
(SCOFFS)
Oh, you gotta be kiddin' me.
Shane's such an asshole.
(CHUCKLES)
SHANE: You think that's funny?
(SCOFFS)
(ON SPEAKERS) Such an asshole.
Shane's such an asshole.
ANDY: I didn't make him
say anything!
Okay. You know what?
You're spending less time
with this thing.
One hour a day, tops.
And the rest of the time,
he's going in here.
Mom, stop,
you're gonna scare him!
KAREN: It's a toy.
You don't have to bring him
into this.
It's a toy, Andy.
And he keeps
freaking out Rooney, okay?
So I'm keeping them separated.
I can keep him away
from Rooney
if he stays in my room.
He's staying in there,
that is final!
(MUFFLED POUNDING)
(POUNDING CONTINUES)
(FAINT POUNDING)
(LOUD THUD)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(EXHALES)
(GLASS SHARDS CLINKING)
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
ANDY: Rooney!
(SNIFFS)
Chucky?
Did you do this?
Kitty made us unhappy.
Now we can play again.
ANDY: (ON SPEAKERS) I swear,
I'm so sick of this cat.
I swear,
I'm so sick of this...
...swear,
I'm so sick of this cat.
(EXHALES)
(BOX CLATTERS)
KAREN: Uh, no, absolutely not.
I'm not working
the Buddi 2 launch.
It is my kid's birthday,
and I'm not doing
night shifts anymore.
Hey, have you seen Rooney?
Psst, psst, psst...
ANDY: Shane left the door
open. Maybe he got out.
(SIGHS) Why is the door
being left open?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (ROONEY MEOWING)
- (GASPS)
- (DEVICE BEEPS)
- (ROONEY MEOWING)
(ROONEY MEOWING ON SPEAKERS)
(ROONEY YOWLING ON SPEAKERS)
(GASPS)
Hey. We are ordering pizza.
- (EXHALES)
- You hungry? What do you want?
Hello? Pizza.
Andy.
What?
- Where are you going?
- ANDY: Pugg's.
Don't forget your little doll.
ANDY: Don't want it.
SHANE: Seriously,
what did I do?
Every time I walk in a room,
he leaves.
That is not true, at all.
Andy's just
a bit different, okay?
Kid can't even be
in the same room as me.
(SIGHS)
(STATIC CRACKLING)
Are you my b-b-b-best buddy?
(SHANE GRUNTS)
(URINATING)
- ANDY: (ON SPEAKERS) Asshole.
- Oh, Jesus! (SPUTTERING)
Shane's such an asshole.
SHANE: God damn it!
Such an asshole.
SHANE: Goddamn kid!
- (DOOR SLAMS OPEN)
- Hey!
You got a problem with me,
you say it, okay?
No more using
your little doll.
Mom!
Sit down!
I'm not through with you.
Now you got a problem with me,
you be a man and you say it.
Come on. Let's hear it.
Yeah.
That's what I thought.
(DOOR OPENS)
(ANDY GRUNTS)
I hate him.
I hate him so much!
Why can't he just
leave us alone?
Why can't he just go away?
(CRYING) I just want him gone.
I just wish
he would leave us alone.
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm just saying he's my son,
so if you have a problem
with him,
talk to me,
and then I'll talk to him.
Because you're not
his dad and...
SHANE: Yeah, I get it.
Look, he was being rude,
and I called him on it.
KAREN: I just think
it's too much.
SHANE: All I did
was I talked to him.
KAREN: It's a little much,
that's all.
SHANE: You know what? Fuck it.
Sounds like a "you" problem,
not a "me" problem.
- (RAIN PATTERING)
- Yes, I know.
Listen, just listen,
I am getting
fucking pissed on, okay?
I work hard enough as it is,
and I'm not having this
goddamn conversation!
(SIGHS)
- (SOFT THUD)
- (GASPS)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(INDISTINCT SPORTS COMMENTARY
ON RADIO)
(RADIO STOPS)
(EXHALES)
Hey, hey, hey!
There's my girls!
GIRLS: Daddy!
- Oh, boy, you guys are so big!
- Daddy! Daddy!
SHANE: Fucking Christmas
lights. Just leave 'em up.
I don't do enough around here?
(PANTS)
(GRUNTING)
I guess I should've fucking
unplugged them first.
- (LADDER RATTLES)
- Oh, fuck!
Goddamn raccoons.
Get out of here!
(YELPS)
(SCREAMS IN PAIN)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(BODY THUDS)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
(GROANS) Oh, God!
Oh, God!
Jane, help!
(GRUNTING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(GROANING)
(RUSTLING)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(SHANE PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(WHIMPERING)
It's tickle time!
Jane! Help!
Nobody hurts my best buddy!
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
(ENGINE STOPS)
This is for Tupac.
(EXCLAIMS)
- (STABBING)
- (FLESH SQUELCHING)
WILLIS: Body was stabbed
13 times.
(SIGHS) I just bought
these fucking shoes.
Where we at
with print casting?
Only other prints
look to fit a toddler.
MIKE: Shit.
WILLIS: Wife says he came here
straight home from work.
MIKE: Oh.
(MIKE SIGHS)
Tsk. Yeah.
I'm not sure that's true.
(SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE)
White guy dead
in a watermelon patch.
Poetic.
(ALARM RINGING)
(ALARM STOPS)
(SCREAMS)
What the fuck?
- CHUCKY: Surprise!
- (GASPS)
Now we can play again.
What? What? Why?
I'd do anything
for my best buddy.
What? No!
No, I didn't want this!
Why would I want this?
(STAMMERING) Holy shit!
Why would you do this, Chucky?
ANDY: (ON SPEAKERS)
I just want him gone.
I just wish
he would leave us alone.
I just want him gone.
No! No, stop!
Stop!
Wish he would leave us alone.
CHUCKY: Andy, stop.
(KEYPAD BEEPS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
You beckoned?
What's the problemo?
(PUGG VOMITING)
Where's the rest of him?
Why?
ANDY: I... I don't know!
There's a bow on its head.
Shit, shit!
FALYN: We saw the signs,
and we did nothing!
This is all our fault.
- We saw the signs.
- ANDY: Stop saying that!
What do I do?
Do I call the cops?
- No.
- He's dead.
I can tell them the truth.
Tell them the truth? Sure.
We tell them
that a dead guy's face skin
ended up in your room
because your toy went
full-blown psycho killer.
- Let's see how that goes.
- Oh.
Oh, it's winking at me.
I can't look at it anymore.
We gotta hide the evidence.
(STUTTERS) In what?
Shit.
- Ugh, is that brain?
- (FALYN GAGS)
The skin's on a melon.
Why is there a fruit involved?
(RETCHES)
Just go straight
to the garbage chute
and make the drop.
- Right.
- And if anybody stops you,
say you have crazy diarrhea
or something, no time to talk.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
- (KAREN WHISTLING TUNE)
(STOPS WHISTLING)
Hi, Mom.
Hi, Andy.
Why are you not in school?
Um, crazy diarrhea.
Okay, got it.
Um, what is that?
It's a present.
Present? For who?
Um, the old lady
down the hall,
because she helps me
with homework.
- So, I made her a thing.
- KAREN: Cool.
And you guys helped him
with this?
PUGG: No, it was all him.
It was him.
FALYN: No, no. Yeah.
Let's go deliver it.
The present.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
What?
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
- Oh!
- Hi, Doreen.
Isn't this a surprise!
I know.
Hi. Um...
This is for you.
- Wow...
- For all of the homework stuff
that you helped him with.
Right?
Mm-hmm.
Tsk. Oh!
Oh, yeah. Of course!
Of course, yeah.
Always happy to help
such a sweet boy.
(ANDY STRAINING)
Give it to her.
DOREEN: Oh.
(CHUCKLES)
Butterfingers over here.
Oh, it's heavy.
I hope it's not fragile.
I just wanna know what it is.
Open it.
Yeah.
No! No! Don't! Don't!
Um...
My birthday is next week,
and we can open it then.
Together.
Okay, that's a very strange
and lovely thought.
So, I'll just go put it
on the shelf until then.
- Okay? Okay.
- Okay.
- All right. Thank you.
- No problem.
- And, Doreen...
- KAREN: Bye.
PUGG: Stupid!
Why did we use wrapping paper?
ANDY: It's fine.
It's fine, okay?
We have till my birthday,
next Friday.
I'll get rid of it.
Don't worry.
FALYN: You guys are worried
about the head?
You've got a killer doll
in your closet.
And you know what we gotta do.
PUGG: Shit.
Pugg!
You left me all alone.
I don't like the closet.
I know, Chucky.
Drop the knife.
You're my best buddy.
I just want you to be happy.
I know, buddy.
And we're gonna go play now,
but you've gotta drop
the knife, okay?
Come on. Let's go play.
Come on.
Come on. In here.
Are we having fun now?
CHUCKY: Andy,
what's happening?
Now, Andy, now! Now!
CHUCKY: Andy?
(ALL GRUNTING)
Why are you doing this?
They're trying
to hurt me, Andy.
FALYN: How is he so strong?
CHUCKY: Andy!
I'm sorry, Chucky.
It's the only way.
CHUCKY: But you're my friend!
What are you waiting for?
Do it!
(SINGING) You are my buddy
until the end
FALYN: Andy! (GRUNTS)
PUGG: Come on.
(POWERING DOWN)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(CRACKLING STOPS)
(ANDY SNIFFLING)
(CHUTE RATTLING)
That's it.
We never talk about what
happened tonight to anybody.
(GABE GASPS)
Oh.
Jackpot.
Ah!
- There you are.
- (POWERING UP)
The connectivity's down,
but not in bad shape overall.
I'll make a pretty penny
on resale
once we get you sorted.
Time to open you up.
Let's see
what we're dealing with.
(DRILL WHIRRING)
(SCOFFS)
So stupid.
(SNIFFLES)
How could I be so stupid?
(DOOR CLOSES)
Hey.
Um...
I'm gonna be right back, okay?
Just stay here.
- Okay.
- KAREN: Okay.
Hey, man. Don't worry, okay?
My partner is just asking her
some routine questions.
ANDY: Hey.
I love you.
(EXHALES) Okay.
(KNOCKING)
Hey. Um...
Still want some backup with
your mom for some dinner?
Hmm.
We're good.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
Come on. (LAUGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
ON SPEAKERS)
DOREEN: This is...
Okay, all right.
- He doesn't know about it yet.
- CHUCKY: Andy?
- No, I'll just ask Andy.
- ANDY: Sure.
Andy!
DOREEN: Okay. I have
an announcement to make.
I downloaded...
- You ready?
- MIKE: Mm-hmm.
- The Kaslan app.
- MIKE: Okay.
- The Kaslan drive.
- DOREEN: Kaslan drive.
I thought it was a dating app.
Oh, my God.
- (ANDY GIGGLES)
- You are so silly!
Can you imagine
if she was out here dating?
And so what? I'm desirable.
MIKE: Excuse me.
Anyway, Andy, help me
figure this thing out.
- (LAUGHING)
- ANDY: Okay.
So, here's the app.
What do I do?
- Okay. So, once you sign up...
- Mm-hmm.
...you just press this button
and the car will show up
to wherever you are,
take you wherever you want.
It's super easy.
No, wait.
It'll drive me to Bingo,
and I don't have to worry
about this bozo (CHUCKLES)
driving me around?
Yeah.
DOREEN: Andy, you're my
new best friend. (GIGGLES)
I don't want you going
out there alone, okay?
'Cause it's not safe.
DOREEN: (SCOFFS)
The only thing not safe
- around here is your cooking.
- Oh, is that right?
- 'Cause, um, I can...
- Yeah.
Poor Andy gotta suffer...
(EXCLAIMS)
It tastes like instant!
It's good. I think it's good.
- DOREEN: You know what?
- Thank you, Andy.
You are just too sweet
for your own good, Andy.
That's all.
Don't be influenced by him.
MIKE: I learned my cooking
from you, you know?
DOREEN: Yeah,
'cause I can cook.
(MIKE AND DOREEN LAUGH)
Oh, God...
MIKE: Hey, Ma.
DOREEN: Yeah, baby.
You been to vintage shoppin'
again? 'Cause that looks new.
Oh!
Andy made this for me.
Oh, and we are gonna...
- (PLATES RATTLE)
- Yeah, I know. It's heavy.
And we are gonna open it
on his birthday.
- Oh!
- DOREEN: Mm-hmm.
Tell me, when's the last time
you made me anything?
Uh, never.
- (LAUGHS)
- MIKE: Oh, wow, okay.
Oh, my God, moms, right?
Look, um...
I know that people
have probably been
talking to you about me,
but, uh, don't believe
everything you hear.
You know, this neighborhood
has a lot of bad influences.
You know what I mean?
People like to keep
their mouth shut.
You know,
thinking they need to fit in,
but fitting in
isn't always a good thing.
You know what I mean?
Gotta be careful
who you hanging around
in a place like this.
(ANDY PANTING)
When you get a bit older
and you start to realize
- that it's just...
- (DOOR CLOSES)
Even the hearing impaired
don't wanna listen to me.
That is fantastic.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
(CHUTE CLANGING)
(SNIFFS)
(WHIRRS)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Your Buddi is now connected.
- Hi!
- (LAUGHS) Yes.
Are you my best buddy?
Buddi, you can connect
to Kaslan products, right?
Sure. Do you like music?
I do, I do.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Connecting to Kaslan Music.
Yes!
(POP MUSIC PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
There it is.
eBay, here we come.
Finally.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(MOANS SOFTLY)
Kaslan, system reboot.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Your connection
- is experiencing interference.
- GABE: No, no, no.
Kaslan!
System reboot!
- (STATIC)
- (MUSIC STOPS)
Kaslan, system reboot!
(LOUD CLATTERING)
Buddi?
Kaslan, lights on.
(LIGHTS BUZZING)
Kaslan.
Ka... Kaslan?
(GROANS)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Lights activated.
(GROANS, YELPS)
(GASPS, GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
(GABE WHIMPERING)
Kaslan, lights on.
(FOOTSTEPS RUNNING)
- (KNIFE SLASHES)
- (GROANS)
What the fuck are you?
(WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMING)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Table saw activated.
(WHIRRING)
Oh, my God.
(SOBBING)
I'm sorry, God, I'm sorry.
Please, help me!
AUTOMATED VOICE: Thermostat
reaching maximum temperature.
(SCREAMS) Shit! Shit!
(SCREAMS)
(GABE GASPING RAPIDLY)
Turn it off, turn it off,
turn it off!
Fuck! Fuck!
Oh, shit.
(SCREAMING)
Time to open you up.
Let's see
what we're dealing with.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Warning.
Device overheating.
Warning. Device overheating.
GABE: Shit! No.
(SCREAMING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Guess what Omar got.
Someone left it
outside his door.
(KIDS GIGGLING)
(LAUGHTER)
OMAR: My Buddi actually works.
I named him Chode.
(LAUGHTER)
Check this out.
Hey, Chode.
Salute your master.
(KIDS LAUGH)
Hey, master.
Wanna go get a burger?
- Yum yum.
- (LAUGHTER)
Yum yum.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SIREN WAILING)
HENRY: Buddi 2
will be available
in five model designs.
Including a fuzzy new friend,
the Buddi Bear.
PUGG: Yo, Omar,
check it out, dude.
Oh, my God.
(FALYN SIGHS)
The new model
isn't even out yet,
and they are already
selling accessories.
(ON SPEAKERS)
I'm Henry Kaslan.
When Buddi imprints
on your child,
he becomes
a best friend for life.
Buddi's only goal
is making your child happy.
EMPLOYEE: Back farther.
Back farther. There.
HENRY: The Buddi 2...
CHODE: Andy.
- Do you wanna play now?
- Chode, go away.
That's no way
to treat your best friend.
We're not friends.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Because if I can't be
your best buddy,
then nobody can.
You said it yourself.
Everybody leaves you.
What did you say?
You'll see.
SHANE: (ON SPEAKERS)
You got a problem with me,
you say it, okay?
No more using
your little doll.
You got a problem with me,
you say it, okay?
No more using
your little doll.
ANDY: I just want him gone.
I just wish
he would leave us alone.
I just want him gone.
I just wish he would leave us
alone. I fucking hate him!
Stop.
Stop the video.
ANDY: Go away!
Sit down. Sit down.
- I'm not through with you.
- Stop! Turn it off!
SHANE: Sit down. Sit down.
- I'm not through with you.
- ANDY: I want him gone.
Stop it! Turn it off!
Turn it off!
ANDY: Why can't he just
leave us alone?
Stop! Turn it off!
Now!
What are you doing?
- That's not your Buddi.
- Don't touch him!
Look! Look at his eyes!
They're red!
What? Your shit breaks,
now you gotta bust mine?
It's Chucky! Look at his eyes!
I said don't touch him.
You deaf or something?
Oh, that's right.
You are.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
PUGG: Andy!
Get off him, seriously!
(GRUNTS)
FALYN: Guys!
That thing is Chucky.
He's controlling the screens.
He's Chucky. Look.
HENRY: AR integration improved
self-learning technology.
But that's not all.
What is wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
ANDY: Yeah.
KAREN: Come here.
OMAR: Chode, come on, dumbass.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I thought...
I thought he...
Andy, where is your
hearing aid?
ANDY: I got it.
(VIDEO GAME PLAYING)
CHRIS: Hey.
Did they find your phone?
OMAR: Not yet.
Thanks.
I've got you now, asshole.
OMAR: Yo, shut up.
CHRIS: Okay.
(LAUGHTER)
Still can't believe you're
friends with that freak.
He is not our friend.
Not anymore.
OMAR: (ON SPEAKERS)
Check this out.
(OMAR GRUNTING)
ANDY: Where are you going?
(FOOTSTEPS)
(GASPS) No. Not right now.
I'm going to bingo.
Well, you're sure as hell
not walkin' there.
Why don't you just wait
till I get off work in a few?
No, no.
I ordered a car.
Mmm. I can take care
of my own damn self.
(KISSES, CHUCKLES)
- Wear your seatbelt. Please.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
Oh, shit. Come on.
My, oh, my.
Oh, shit!
Look at this.
A Kaslan Kar.
(PANTING)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Welcome to Kaslan Kar.
Well, I'll be damned.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Please fasten your seatbelt.
(LAUGHS)
ANDY: (PANTING) Okay.
Okay, I'm in the car!
How do I...
AUTOMATED VOICE: We are now
en route to your destination.
Oh, my. Oh, my goodness.
It's going backwards.
ANDY: Doreen!
- Hey, Andy.
- ANDY: No!
(PANTING)
- Will you look at this?
- ANDY: Stop the car!
(VOCALIZING TUNE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
AUTOMATED VOICE: We are now
reaching your destination.
Hey.
Hey, look at my ride. (LAUGHS)
WOMAN: It's Doreen!
Uh-huh. Don't be jealous now.
(LAUGHS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Okay. Oh, no.
No, no, wait!
This is my stop!
Pull over, please!
AUTOMATED VOICE: I'm sorry.
I do not understand.
- (TIRES SCREECHING)
- Whoa!
(SCREAMS)
(WHIMPERING)
(BRAKES SCREECH)
- (DEVICE CHIMES)
- (TIRES SCREECHING)
No! No! No!
No!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
CHUCKY: (ON SPEAKERS)
Nobody steals my friend.
(SCREAMING)
Help me, Jesus!
- (TIRES SCREECHING)
- (SCREAMING)
Andy's my best friend.
You hobbit motherfucker!
- (TIRES SCREECH)
- Oh!
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Passenger airbag
- has been turned off.
- DOREEN: Wait!
Seatbelt disengaged.
Heads up, bitch.
DOREEN: Please! (SCREAMING)
AUTOMATED VOICE: You have
arrived at your destination.
(GROANING)
CHUCKY ON SPEAKERS:
(SINGSONG) I see you.
(GASPING)
(DOREEN WHIMPERING)
Peekaboo.
(FAINT CLATTERING)
(WHIMPERING)
Doreen...
I said, "Peekaboo!"
- (SCREAMING)
- (KNIFE SLASHES)
ANDY: I saw Doreen outside.
Mom, I think Chucky did
something to her.
KAREN: Sweetie...
Chucky is a toy.
Okay?
It broke.
- You got rid of it.
- No, Mom.
I... I saw him.
I saw him following Doreen.
No, you didn't.
Listen to what you're saying.
Mom, he's gonna kill her!
He probably
already did kill her!
Why are you doing this?
Please, just be honest with me
and tell me
what happened to Rooney.
It was Chucky!
Chucky?
Why aren't you listening
to me?
I have it on Omar's phone.
He's following Doreen.
I can show you.
Why do you have Omar's phone?
I took it.
Why?
I had to. I...
I had to follow Chucky, Mom.
Okay.
I'm not crazy, Mom!
I'm giving this back to him.
Mom, no one's
listening to me. Please.
I have to
give this back to him
so this doesn't get any worse.
Nobody's listening to me!
- Just stay right here, okay?
- Mom!
And you're coming
to work with me.
He's trying to kill us!
KAREN: Do not move.
(MIKE GASPING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
MIKE: (SOBS) Oh, shit. Shit.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
You don't know that.
We barely know this kid.
He could be batshit crazy.
What if
Chucky never malfunctioned?
He just...
He just made it all up?
- What if he killed...
- FALYN: Shut up.
CHUCKY: I've watched them,
Andy.
(GASPING)
I've seen how they hurt you.
Over here, Andy!
- Leave me alone!
- (CHUCKY LAUGHING)
- CHUCKY: Over here.
- (GASPING)
(SINGSONG)
If they don't let us play,
they all go away.
Why are you doing this?
(TOY CHIRPS)
CHUCKY: Are we having fun now?
(CHUCKY LAUGHING)
KAREN: (ON TV)
Are you my best buddy?
CHUCKY: If they don't
let us play,
they all go away.
Peekaboo.
(PANTING)
Stop!
(SCREAMING)
Turn it off!
(CHUCKY LAUGHING)
(PANTING)
(KAREN WHIMPERS)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
RADIO JOCKEY:
But the chance of rain tonight
won't dampen the spirits
of Buddi fans,
as this is the night
they have been waiting for.
That's right,
people have been lining up
for the midnight release
of Buddi 2.
(KIDS CLAMORING)
DISPATCHER: (ON RADIO)
All units. All units,
be advised that the deceased
is an African American female
in her 70s.
Ten-four.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
OFFICER: Ma'am, you okay?
FALYN: It's Doreen.
I think she's dead.
There are cops everywhere.
What if Chucky's...
What if Andy is right?
The hell you want?
Omar, show us your Buddi.
It's gone.
- Fuck!
- Since when? Where is it?
Why don't you ask Andy?
That asshole's
been taking my shit.
Give me your phone.
Are you gonna steal it, too?
(OMAR GRUNTS)
Give me your phone now.
DOREEN: (ON SPEAKERS)
A Kaslan Kar.
OMAR: What the hell?
PUGG: (GASPS) No.
Holy shit.
He was right.
BOTH: Andy.
There you are.
Remember the souvenir?
Skinned face?
They found it.
Old man dug it up
in a dumpster this morning.
Nice, right?
Wrapped up like a present.
KIDS: (CHANTING)
Buddi! Buddi! Buddi!
Buddi! Buddi!
Fuck my job.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Fuckin' thing.
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
Buddi! Buddi! Buddi! Buddi!
Buddi! Buddi! Buddi!
Come on. We need
to get you out of here.
It's Chucky. He's here.
- (BALLOON POPS)
- (ALL GASP)
I gotta find my mom.
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
Buddi! Buddi! Buddi! Buddi!
ANDY: Mom!
Come here! Get the fuck down.
Now stay down, Andy.
ALL: Ten, nine, eight...
Hey! Hey!
What are you doing?
- Get off of him!
- Hey! Hey!
Chucky's here!
He's gonna kill you!
ALL: ...two, one!
- (HORN TOOTS)
- (ALL CLAMORING)
MIKE: Be careful, goddamn it!
What is going on? Mike!
Look, I don't have to
tell you shit, Karen.
That is my son, okay?
I don't give a fuck
that it's your son.
ANNOUNCER: (ON PA)
Ladies and gentlemen,
say hello
to your new best friend.
(GROANS)
The all new Buddi 2!
(ALL CHEERING)
(WES GROANING)
(GIGGLES NERVOUSLY)
(ALL SCREAMING)
All right, come on.
Watch out.
Move out of the way.
(SHRIEKING)
- Give me your hand.
- You have to believe me.
- Is that necessary?
- Mom.
MIKE: Yeah,
it's fucking necessary.
Stay put.
I promise you,
he's gonna kill us.
Let me through!
Move, move, move!
Clear a path, come on!
Hey, hey, hey.
It's gonna be all right.
Hey, look at me.
Keep pressure on it, okay?
- Somebody call a doctor!
- We have to leave right now.
- Calm down. Okay?
- No, no, no! Mom...
MIKE: Call a doctor!
(ALL GASP)
Oh, shit. (BREATHING HEAVILY)
Mom, where are you going?
(CELL PHONES CHIMING)
(GLITCHING)
Hello, my name is Henry...
My name is Henry Kaslan.
(GROANING)
Welcome to
your local Zed Mart.
With great pleasure,
I introduce you...
More than just entertainment.
(HENRY CONTINUES SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
We created something
far more special.
Every child
is important to us.
And every child
deserves a companion.
A friend
that will never let you down.
We're too late.
- It's time to...
- Play.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(KAREN GRUNTS)
(WES GROANING)
(ALL SCREAM)
(ALL SCREAMING AND YELLING)
Stay down, okay?
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Lockdown activated.
CHUCKY: (ON HEARING AID)
I'm everywhere, Andy.
You can't run away
from me now.
See? They're all leaving you.
But not me.
MAN: This way!
I know the way out!
(ALL CLAMORING)
No.
(GROANING)
MIKE: Fuck!
Run.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Andy!
(GROWLING)
(GASPS)
Holy shit!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
Okay. Okay! Okay.
- (SHRIEKING)
- (GRUNTS) Where is Andy?
(GRUNTING)
Oh, God, help me!
Help me!
(SNARLING)
AUTOMATED VOICE: Exit now.
(ANDY GRUNTING AND PANTING)
(GROWLING)
- (SAW WHIRRING)
- Duck!
(GRUNTS)
(FALYN GRUNTS)
You okay?
I'm gonna follow her.
Me too.
OMAR: Yeah.
Come on.
CHUCKY: (ON TV)
Where you going, Andy?
Mom.
Andy, he's trying
to lure us back in.
(PANTING)
I can't just leave her there.
If we stay, we all die, okay?
We gotta go!
We'll call the cops, Andy.
Okay. Okay, you're right.
Let's go.
Okay. Okay, come on.
Andy!
It's my fault
all this happened, okay?
Andy.
I can't let you guys get hurt.
- FALYN: Andy! Come on!
- No! Andy, don't!
FALYN: Andy!
PUGG: Andy!
FALYN: Andy, please!
PUGG: He'll kill you, Andy!
(PUGG AND FALYN
CONTINUE SHOUTING)
All right, Chucky,
you wanna play?
Let's play.
CHUCKY ON SPEAKERS:
(SINGSONG) Getting closer.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(CHUCKY LAUGHING)
(TOY WHIRRING)
ROBOCOP: Dead or alive,
you're coming with me.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Mom!
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
KAREN: (ON SPEAKERS)
Andy's just a bit different.
Shut up!
CHUCKY: (ON SPEAKERS)
Don't you see?
She's not your friend.
You don't need other friends.
They try to keep us apart.
Try to ruin our fun.
(WHIMPERS)
But I won't let that happen.
(ON HEARING AID)
It will be all over soon.
Don't worry, Andy.
You're gonna thank me
when she's gone.
When they're all gone.
(GRUNTS)
(KNIFE SCRAPING)
CHUCKY: Guess what, Andy?
Now it's going to be
you and me...
- (MUFFLED YELLING)
- ...forever.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
- (GROANING)
- I was broken, Andy.
I couldn't make you smile.
But I'm better now.
I know how to
make you happy now.
Maybe you don't
wanna be happy.
Maybe you're broken too.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
Maybe I need to open you up,
see what we're dealing with.
I'm gonna fix you, Andy.
(GRUNTS)
(SINGING) You are my buddy
until the end
What? Andy?
(CHOKING)
More than a buddy,
you're my best friend
(KAREN CHOKING)
Mom!
(SAW WHIRRING)
ANDY: (ON SPEAKERS)
We're too late.
- (GRUNTS)
- (SCREAMS)
(YELPS)
You are ruining our fun, Andy!
ANDY: Get off!
CHUCKY: You're gonna play
with me now.
Only me!
(KAREN GRUNTS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SCREAMING)
(CRACKLING)
(DISTORTING) Andy...
I thought we were friends.
(DISTORTED SPEECH)
You are my bu...
- Mom?
- You are my bu...
CHUCKY: (SINGING)
You are my buddy
Until the end!
(YELLING)
(GUNSHOT)
(GASPING)
This is the end.
(WHIRRING)
Don't fuck with my son!
- (GRUNTS)
- (CLATTERS)
ANDY: Mom.
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
KAREN: Okay.
Thank you.
(EXHALES)
(POWERS DOWN)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(ALL GRUNTING)
HENRY: (ON SPEAKERS) Our
investigation has concluded
that Kaslan
shares no responsibility
for the horrific events
that transpired at Zed Mart.
However, as a precaution,
we are recalling all Buddi 2
products for the time being.
At Kaslan,
the customers come first.
We believe that every child
deserves a friend for life.
A friend who will never,
ever leave them.
A friend...
(SWITCH CLICKS)
...till the end.
(JOLLY MUSIC PLAYING)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
(CHORUS VOCALIZING)
(DRAMATIC ORCHESTRAL
MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHORUS VOCALIZING)
(EERIE SINGING)
(WICKED LAUGHTER)