(CHIME)
(DRONING)
(BEATING)
(SLOW TWANGY MUSIC)
Subtitles by ViSHAL
www.OpenSubtitles.org
(PANTING)
(CHIRPING)
(SUSPENSEFUL CRESCENDO)
Hey boy.
(LAUGHS)
You better come here.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(CHUCKLES)
Time to die, boy.
Time to die!
(SCREAMS)
(GUNSHOT)
(CHIRPING)
ANGIE: Ladies and no gentlemen,
welcome aboard Angela Airlines.
I'll be your host for the
weekend, Angela Cooper.
The getaway girls'
grand vacation
is officially underway.
(CHEERS)
It's so great to see you guys.
Oh, me too.
Here we go.
Since it was my turn
to plan this year,
I thought let's do something
a little different.
I mean, we've done
Vegas, cruises, spas.
And, all of that
seems so boring.
Come on, I'm serious.
You know, let's get out
there and really go for it;
Push ourselves like we used to.
It could be fun.
ANGIE: Alright.
I'm in.
I trust you.
ANGIE: You better.
Let's do it.
(CRICKETS)
We made it.
It's all like I imagined it.
(CELLPHONE RINGING)
Hi Paige.
How are you?
I miss you too, baby.
No, I'll be home
real soon, okay?
You being a good
girl for grandma?
Good.
Okay.
I'll talk to you soon.
Let me talk to Grandma, okay?
Hey Mom.
No, we're kind of in
the middle of nowhere.
But, there'll be a car
to pick us up soon.
The reception is
really bad out here.
Hello?
Mom?
(SLOW TWANGY MUSIC)
(UPBEAT MUSIC)
About time.
Howdy, ladies.
Y'all must be the Cooper party.
We're a party alright.
And, what's your name, cowboy?
Down, girl.
Name's Danny.
I'll be your ride.
Well, I guess we better
saddle up then, huh?
Yeah, saddle up, bareback.
To be honest with you,
it don't make much
difference to me.
Excuse me.
Let me get your bags.
You just don't waste
a second, do you?
Alright, right in here.
Hey Brooke,
why don't you get up front?
There's only 87
people who live here?
Well, there's 81 now.
A few folks have passed
since they did that sign.
Wow.
I think Chicago back home
is nearly three million.
(HORNS BLARING)
(HOLLERING)
Hey boys.
What are they doing?
(CHEERS)
It's okay.
Oh relax, Mom.
Later boys.
Sorry about that, ladies.
It's just some local wildlife.
We don't get too many
city girls out here.
How many of you have
ridden these things before?
Right here, cowboy.
Alright.
You guys go ahead
and take your pick.
Turn these things out.
Looking like a bunch of
kids in a candy store.
Ladies like these things.
Alright.
Wanna make sure they're neutral.
Make sure your key is
in the on position.
There you go, just like that.
Put your brake on.
And, go ahead and hit that
little green button right there.
(ENGINES TURN OVER)
There you go.
Alright.
Looking good.
Rev them up a little bit.
There you go.
Alright.
Now, all you got to do is
put your brake up, put
them in drive and take off.
You guys know where
you're going, right?
Oh yeah.
We know how to do this.
See you guys later.
Follow me.
(PLAYFUL MUSIC)
Slow down.
Wait for me.
(CHEERING)
(PLAYFUL MUSIC)
(HOOTING)
This is crazy.
Come on, Meg.
Speed up.
Kat.
(BOLD MUSIC)
(SHRIEKS)
Let's go.
Bitch, come on.
Go.
(BOLD MUSIC)
(SHRIEKING)
Ange, are you sure this is it?
Pretty sure.
Why don't we go check it out.
Come on.
What are you guys waiting for?
(CHUCKLING)
Shoot, watch your step.
Oh my God, you guys,
I can't wait to
take a hot shower.
Girl, you are not kidding.
I don't care.
I call the shower.
Hello.
Oh wow.
Oh my God.
Have you ever seen
anything like this?
It looks like a fricking
romance novel in here.
Check it out.
Ooh wow.
Ooh.
Oh shit.
What the hell is that?
Oh come on.
You're not serious.
It's a boar hog.
That's disgusting.
You're sick.
There's some great
hunting around here.
Hey, the only thing
I'm hunting is a shower.
Okay.
Well, you go do that.
Hey, girls, it's party time.
Now, that's what
I'm talking about.
(SUSPENSEFUL WHIR)
(WATER RUSHING)
Care package from home?
Yeah.
Paige made me promise I'd
bring Mr Teddy for good luck.
Aw, that's so cute.
Yeah.
She's such a sweetheart.
So, how are you guys doing?
We're doing good.
Busy as ever.
School, dance, soccer.
It gets crazy.
I mean, how are
you really doing?
We're hanging in there.
We're working through things.
Since we lost Stephen...
I'm sorry.
You don't have to talk about it.
No.
No, it's okay.
She just,
she doesn't really understand
that he's not coming home.
And, she still draws these
little pictures for him.
You know, I am so proud of you.
I mean,
I just can't imagine to go
through something like that.
Well, I have to
be strong for Paige.
Come here.
Do you know how lucky
she is to have you?
Come on.
Let's get you a glass of wine.
(LIVELY JAZZ)
Oh look.
The getaway girls are
up to same old tricks.
What's going on?
Okay, you guys.
Here is where we pick up
the four wheelers
with Danny, girls.
And, we rode along
these trails (MUMBLES)
all the way to the east.
That was a blast.
Wasn't that a blast?
It was.
I'm just saying.
Alright, new rule.
New rule;
This cannot get out.
I mean, I can't believe
how trashed I am.
I love it.
What was I saying?
Like I said;
Whatever happens in
Vegas, stays in Vegas.
Were you in Vegas?
(LAUGHING)
Angie, what the hell is this?
Oh.
Okay.
So, when I was a little girl
following around my
brothers in the colony,
in the woods learning to
hunt and all that shit,
they told me that
it was (MUMBLES)
Moonshine.
I'm serious, you guys.
I'm serious.
This is my own special brew that
I've been saving
just for you guys.
And you know what,
this will knock
you on your asses.
You think?
(LAUGHING)
Cheers.
Oh my God. Oh my God.
Do that thing that
you always do.
No.
It's so stupid.
(SHARP MUSIC)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(LOW METRONOME)
Come on, let's get back.
Why didn't you shoot?
I didn't need to.
He was ours.
That's all that really matters.
Hey.
Where were you guys?
Just looking around.
It's really beautiful out there.
Yeah.
Well, you could've told
us where you were going.
We woke up and didn't know
where the hell you guys were.
Sorry.
Well, let's get going.
We got a big day ahead of us.
Let's get dressed girls.
Be right back.
(SLOW TWANGY MUSIC)
Hi.
You guys catching
anything today?
Is that a gator?
Do you mind if I get
a picture of you?
I have a little girl at home.
She would love to see
a picture of you guys.
Ain't no picture
taking out here.
Okay.
Sorry, I didn't know.
What are you doing
out here anyway?
I'm just with some friends.
We're going camping
in the everglades.
What the hell you want to
go out in that swamp for?
Get in there and
you can't get out.
Wish you hadn't.
Get out of here.
I just wanted a picture.
That's all.
Git now.
Are you okay with all this?
All what?
I mean, going out to the camp.
Absolutely.
Why?
Everything's all been arranged?
Megan, what's the deal?
Seriously, what's up?
That guy and the little
boys just freaked me out.
It's like they
don't want us here.
Sure they do.
So, it's just me?
I mean, yeah, it's a
little different out here.
But, people say
that about New York.
I don't know.
I'm just a little
unsure about all this.
Megan.
Come on, don't be low.
I know, it's just... Okay.
So, there's a few colorful
locals out there, you know.
That's just part of it.
It's just like the
sky and the water.
It's all wild, and
it's the everglades.
Didn't you have a
blast last night?
Yes.
Okay.
Well, you guys, these
places are dying out.
Like, it's all being
built up by condos.
You know, we may never get
another chance like this.
We're gonna remember this trip
for the rest of our lives.
So, you guys in?
Of course.
Guys, is that our ride?
(CHORTLING)
Is that an airboat?
Oh my God.
That's what we're taking?
That's awesome.
(LIGHT MUSIC)
What are we doing?
I've never been on
one of these before.
Pick yourself a spot.
There you go.
And, you're gonna be
up top with me today.
Oh fun.
Alright, let's go.
You girls hang on,
and enjoy the ride.
Thank you.
Here we go.
Woo-hoo.
(CHUCKLING)
What about seat belts?
You just hang on to the side.
I feel like we're on Safari.
Here we go girls.
It's so fricking loud.
I can't hear you guys.
Some people go forward.
(COUNTRY INSTRUMENTAL)
Hey, it's a gator.
Oh, there.
Hang on.
Welcome to 4,000 square
miles of fun and bugs.
Don't we all like
having our fun?
I got a few ideas.
Some of them might
even be legal.
Yee-haw.
How far out is camp anyway?
Ah, we're close.
About 17 miles.
Now, we're getting in deep.
Hey, Kat, this is
looking a little creepy.
How crazy is this?
Water's awful low
for this time of year.
Is that a good thing?
Yeah, if you like big gators.
How am I supposed to call home?
She'll be fine.
(SLOW TWANGY MUSIC)
Don't forget to follow the map.
Stay on the trails, and it'll
keep you out of trouble.
Yeah, I got it.
We're good.
This is home for the night.
Should be everything you need
right here waiting on you.
Thank you.
You all have fun?
Yes.
That was cool.
It's sure been a pleasure.
Let me get your bags.
That was awesome huh?
That was cool.
Alright, you girls know to
watch yourselves out here.
A lot of hogs, gators, snakes,
and a few two-legged vermin
running around here too.
Y'all take care.
And, I'll see you in a few days.
Bye.
(SLOW TWANGY MUSIC)
I swear this is
better than any old
five star rack in Houston.
Yeah, nice job, Ange.
To the chef.
And to Danny for making sure
we have this key
to our survival.
You think he's single?
I think you should find out.
Maybe I will.
I just loved his little accent.
Tell you what, in
this crazy world,
you got a cowboy by your side,
I think you're
doing pretty good.
(SIGHS)
Okay, you guys,
I got to tell you;
This is pretty cool.
I mean, I feel really connected.
You see, this is
what I'm talking about.
Couldn't you believe the
fricking snakes, though?
And, you and your spa.
You know what's really amazing?
None of our daily lives,
schedules or routines;
None of that really
matters out here.
It really is like
a whole other world.
I mean, I don't even remember
what a car horn sounds like.
(LAUGHS)
You guys think we'll keep
getting together for our trips?
Sure.
Why wouldn't we?
I don't know.
You know, it just seems like
people drift apart, you know.
I mean, look at Derek and me.
Ange, you guys were so
young when you got married.
I mean, you can't
really know what
you want out of
life at that age.
Yeah Ange, I mean,
you both were going in different
directions, that's all.
Maybe that's what this
whole survival thing is about.
You have something
to prove to yourself.
He never let me take the shot.
What?
Derek.
He never let me take the shot.
You know, I could always
track better than any guy.
So, I'd always take
the position to track.
You know, I'd put them
in position, and then
he always took the damn shot.
You know what the
worst part was?
It's always yours.
You just let them.
So, all your hunting,
you never really shot anything?
Well, you know, little stuff.
Nothing that matters.
Let me tell you.
I know I wouldn't be
able to kill anything.
Oh, me either.
Hey, all I was asking is
whether we'd keep getting
together for our trips.
I say we all swear on it.
Deal?
Let's all promise to
never drift apart.
I will never ditch you guys.
Thank you.
Me either.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, I love you girls.
Okay, so
Alex and I are
gonna have a baby.
What?
That is so cool.
No way.
Yeah.
Look, he really wants a boy.
Oh my God.
That's so great, Kat.
And, better you than me.
That's for sure.
We're gonna start trying
as soon as I get home.
Well, you're gonna
be a great mom.
(SIGHS)
Well, you guys, nature calls.
I'll be back.
Hey.
Pee at your own risk.
Yeah, be careful.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
How much wine did you have?
(CHUCKLES)
(ZIPPER)
What happened?
I leave, and the party dies?
Dude, I'm seriously tired.
Yeah, we're really beat.
Come on, wild women.
Hey.
We have to get our
beauty sleep, Angie.
You guys are such wimps.
Angie.
I know I've been like the queen
worrier since we got here.
But, we all think
this is really great.
Yeah.
Way cool.
We never would've done
anything like this.
Yeah, no kidding.
I figure somebody's got to
keep things interesting.
Right?
You know, I guess after Derek,
I did wanna take
something on, you know.
Something bigger than me.
I just didn't wanna do it alone.
You guys are all I have.
You're gonna make it.
Absolutely.
Alright, you guys sleep tight.
Hey.
Do you want any company?
No.
I'm just gonna
check on the fire.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Goodnight.
Love you guys.
(FIRE CRACKLING)
(BLEATING)
You guys.
Megan, Kat.
I hear something.
Hurry!
Grab the light.
Something's out there.
(GRUNTING)
Run!
(SCREAMING)
(SHRIEKING)
(BLEATING)
Oh my God!
(SCREAMING)
Angie, get up!
Get up here.
(GRUNTING)
You are crazy.
You could've killed yourself.
I think I got him.
Oh, I hope so.
You are insane.
I can't believe you.
Now what?
Are we gonna sleep in the tree?
I'm not sleeping
in a fricking tree.
Are you nuts?
Let's go back to camp.
It's not going anywhere.
It's staying with us.
Are you guys sure you don't
wanna check out the shot?
Angela.
Please.
Don't you think we've
had enough for one night?
Thanks for saving me, you guys.
Alright.
Brooke and Kat, you
guys should go together.
And then you and me.
Alright?
And Kat, you're
probably stronger.
So, you take the stern.
What the hell's a stern?
Oh, the back seat.
So, you can steer.
Alright, just promise me
you guys will not lose us.
Oh please.
I kick butt on the
club rowing machine.
You guys.
This isn't a race.
It's gonna be a
fun relaxing day.
What about the
snake we just saw?
What about it?
(PEACEFUL MUSIC)
Ooh boy.
(MUMBLES)
(MUSIC CRESCENDOS)
Come on.
Kat, maybe they will lose us.
Come on slow pokes.
Hold on.
(PEACEFUL MUSIC)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Oh, get your camera.
Oh, it's adorable.
Say "hi".
Hi beautiful.
Are you having a good time?
Yes, thank you.
(MUMBLES)
Wait wait wait.
Just don't leave
me here by myself.
(LAUGHING)
Where should we be?
I don't know.
Over there.
This way?
Yeah.
(CLICK)
(GASPS)
Kat.
My my my.
Look what we got here.
Mighty fine.
Sure looks pretty.
You right, buddy.
You sure are right.
Look, we're sorry.
We didn't know this
was anyone's land.
We'll get out of your way.
Well, that's okay, little girl.
Damn.
This must be your lucky day.
(CHUCKLES)
Three of us men
for the two of you.
That's what I call
ladies' choice.
Ladies' choice, yeah.
Leave us alone.
Don't you press your
luck now, darling.
Hey.
Leave her alone.
What are you doing?
You just do what I tell you.
Watch it, Bubba.
Kat.
(CHUCKLING)
You a long way from
home now, ain't you?
What you doing way out
here in man country?
We're just on a camping trip.
A camping trip?
A way out here in the
swamp camping trip?
Just leave us alone.
Yes.
Hell, we best keep you company.
So, you're not in
dangers in Blackwater.
Nothing's happened here.
So, if we can leave,
we don't have to say
anything, I swear.
Shut your mouth.
Do you want money?
We have so much money.
I said shut your stupid mouth.
Don't get him all pissed off.
We don't want any trouble.
Do you know how the
hell he gets on me?
We just wanna go home.
(WHIMPERING)
What's your name, darling?
TUCK: Hell, tell him, baby.
What's your name?
TUCK: Come on. Come on.
Brooke?
What kind of name is that for
a pretty little thing like you?
Polite thing to do is answer
a man when he talks to you.
Don't they teach you
city girls no manners?
TUCK: Ain't got no
manners in a city girl.
(CHUCKLING)
Well now.
Maybe a little Miss
Mouth over here
has something to say.
You got manners, girl?
We got us a fighter.
Oh yeah, we got us a fighter.
BROOKE: Kat.
Get off of her.
Just go.
Smells so good.
(CRYING)
Don't go nowhere, bitch.
Stay right there.
No. Stop.
(CHUCKLES)
I like that.
You ain't going
nowhere, little one.
KAT: Get away from her!
That's the way I like it.
This one's got
some fight in her.
Come on.
Alright, little girl.
We going up here, now.
Get up now.
I said get up there.
Kat!
Quit shovin'.
Get away from her!
No!
(SCREAMS)
Get off her!
Get away from her.
No, we gonna finish off.
(CACKLES)
You want some of
this now, Bubba?
You want some of that?
(CRYING)
(MUMBLING)
Go get Brooke.
(WHIMPERING)
He was on me.
I tried to kick him off.
I tried, but I couldn't.
(CRYING)
(SOBBING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Is he alive?
Help me with the body.
What are you talking about?
We've got to get rid of the body
and get the hell out of here.
I think we should report this.
Take some pictures or something.
Of my bolt sticking
out of his chest?
No way.
No.
We get to the police,
and we report these guys.
Report what?
That some inbred swamp rats were
messing with tourist
girls out in the woods?
We're the outsiders here.
They're not gonna
put me in jail.
They're gonna put me under it.
And, they just may
decide you're going too.
This swamp creep
was gonna kill Kat
while his friend raped Brooke.
And, you're worried
about justice?
He got his justice.
He came from the swamp.
And, I say we put him back in.
Feed him to the gators.
It's not up to us, Angie.
No?
Then, what is up to us, Megan?
They've made all the rules.
And, they take what they want.
They take what they want,
and they take who they want.
And, if those are the rules,
those are the rules.
Would you listen to
what you're saying?
We can't do this.
Look.
There is a right
way and a wrong way.
And, they chose the way.
Now, there's only one way, okay?
We get rid of the body.
And, we get the hell
out of here now.
She's right.
What?
Angie's right.
Kat?
What Megan?
They've seen us.
And, they sure as hell
know we've seen them.
You think they're just gonna
let us waltz out of here?
Not gonna happen.
We sink his ass, and we go home.
These guys,
they'll do whatever it
takes to protect each other.
They'll cover for each other.
That's what they do.
We know that.
I think we should
do the same thing.
We have to protect each other.
She's right.
Meg, come on.
Okay.
Grab his legs.
Alright.
Let's roll him in.
Hey.
Do you think we
should get the shotgun
and put it in with him?
No, let's keep it.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
What if we get caught with it?
Look.
We're not gonna take a freaking
vote on everything we do.
Now, I got us in here.
I'm gonna get us out.
Okay, but you guys
have to trust me.
Now, check his pockets.
What?
I've never seen a man killed
in front of me before.
He was a human being.
No, he wasn't.
(GROANING)
Maybe we should say
something over him.
Big mistake.
Let's go.
(DARING MUSIC)
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Hurry.
Angie, the gun.
Get the gun.
(DARING MUSIC)
TUCK: Damn bitches killed Bubba.
BEAR: Let's get my gun.
It's our turn.
(WILDLIFE NOISES)
What are we gonna do?
Back to camp.
Just keep going.
TUCK: They headed in deeper.
Let's start from the bottom.
Gator's stink as shit.
BEAR: Gonna be some
fun before we kill them.
Jesus.
It all looks the same.
Are we getting anywhere?
We just got to keep going.
I'll take the lead.
(THUNDER)
TUCK: Tell you what.
I'm gonna get what I got coming
from that sweet little blonde.
Let's cut 'em off.
Is this the right way?
Yeah.
Where's the camp?
I can smell 'em.
BROOKE: Where are we?
ANGIE: We're gonna
be okay, Brooke.
Let's move.
We're starting to
lose the light.
BEAR: They ought to be
right around here by now, Tuck.
TUCK: Damn.
Slow and weak as they are,
we probably beat 'em.
BEAR: You hear something?
Take this.
In case we get separated.
I don't think I
can use that thing.
Take it!
Let's go.
BROOKE: Yeah, you guys, come on.
BEAR: I'm starting with
the bitch who killed Bubba.
Watch this.
Time for some fun.
(GUNSHOT)
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHING)
TUCK: Good shooting, Bear.
What's happening?
What are they doing?
Oh my God, Angie.
(GUNSHOT)
BEAR: Hell yeah!
Come on.
TUCK: Woo-hoo.
Hey, that had to hurt.
(CHUCKLES)
Help me.
TUCK: What y'all doing later?
Come on back, now.
What is going on here?
We're going to die
out here, you guys.
Calm down.
Just calm down.
Is that okay?
Oh my God.
Could you hold this thing?
We need something to
stop the bleeding.
Here.
TUCK: We're gonna get you now.
I've got a bandage in my bag.
Megan.
Oh God.
This is going to sting a little.
(YELPS)
Are you okay?
Son of a bitch.
What was that?
Let's get this on.
That hurts.
What do you think?
What do we do?
We need to move in
the opposite direction
as fast as we can.
Can you walk at all?
Yeah.
Let's just go.
Let's go as fast we can.
We're gonna get out of here.
(GROANING)
TUCK: You can run,
but you can't hide.
(CACKLES)
For you, Bubba!
Ooh yeah.
TUCK: Looks like it
time to tighten up on 'em.
Come on.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
What you kill Bubba for?
You hear me?
Come on back.
(CACKLES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Getting close to
suppertime, Bear.
BEAR: Four course meal, buddy.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Watch out for snakes.
You alright?
Yeah.
Come on.
Oh fuck.
(GROANING)
Now what?
Angie?
Did you bring the map?
I think it's in my bag.
Shit.
Alright.
We're going this way.
Let's go.
Dammit.
(WILDLIFE NOISES)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
What is wrong with these people?
(SOBBING)
Come on, Brooke.
We have to keep going.
Maybe we can find his airboat.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's good.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Females got to be
working up an appetite.
Won't be long now, Tuck.
I got an idea.
Wind's blowing.
What you thinking?
We steer 'em.
Come on, boy.
This will damn sure
get 'em moving.
Hell yeah.
(LAUGHING)
Bear, you're a crazy
son of a bitch.
BEAR: Torch these whole
goddamn woods if we have to.
TUCK: I say we torch it up.
BEAR: Hell yeah.
Smell the burn.
Hell yeah.
You gonna feel the heat.
For you, Bubba!
Send them all to hell.
No way in hell they
coming out this way.
Let's get them girls moving.
Hurry.
Tuck.
Let's look around.
Okay.
If you get them
first, wait for me.
I want some too.
(THUNDER)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Oh God.
We're surrounded on
all three sides by water.
It's just a big peninsula.
The only way out is
the way we came in.
What?
Right back to them.
I'm so sorry for everything.
There's nothing to be sorry for.
It's all my fault.
Ange.
Don't talk like that.
If I hadn't dragged us out here,
none of this would've happened.
And, you wouldn't have been...
Hey.
We're hanging
together like always.
We're gonna get outta here.
Come on.
We're not the getaway
girls without you.
I'm sorry.
So, how are we, really?
I think I screwed us up.
We're surrounded by
water on three sides.
They're right in the
middle of the way out.
Let's just wait for daylight.
No.
ANGIE: We have a much
better chance... No.
No, you were right.
It's always been by their rules.
Not this time.
No inbred pig's keeping
me from my baby.
Megan, no.
If we sit here,
they're gonna kill us.
Well then, I'm coming with you.
No.
It's quieter with one person.
Megan.
No.
Stay here with Angie.
She needs you.
Here.
Megan.
Please don't go.
Please.
Hold on to this.
Okay?
You know I'll be back for it.
I love you.
I love you too.
It's time to go home.
Mama's coming home, baby.
I'm coming home.
(GUNSHOT)
What was that?
Shotgun.
I'm getting Megan.
Kat.
I'm going to get Megan.
(DARING MUSIC)
Oh my God.
God, please help me.
KAT: Megan.
Kat?
I'm over here.
Don't shoot my ass.
Thank God.
Are you okay?
Okay, come on.
Everybody's over here.
Come on.
Oh my God.
What happened?
I got him.
Are you sure?
I saw him go down.
Oh my God.
What did I do?
You survived.
What should we do now?
You know what, no.
We can't stay here.
We got to go.
Help her up.
Come on.
We're going this way.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
Oh yeah.
Bubba, you knew how
to make this shit
like nobody did, Bubba.
(WHISPERING)
That's him.
Shoot him.
That's the guy.
I'm gonna kill you, bitch.
Hurry, Megan!
Shoot him, Megan!
(GUNSHOT)
Keep going then.
She's okay.
Hang in there, Angie.
Just keep going.
Help her, Kat.
Oh God, Angie's bleeding again.
Come on.
You okay?
Megan, where are we going?
(GROANS)
I think we're headed east.
Help her.
Megan.
There's probably gators.
We got to get outta this.
Get us out of this shit.
I'm trying.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
We're almost there.
Alright.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Holy shit.
Is that what I think it is?
It's a hunting boat.
You know, they usually
leave them out here.
But, they'll be back
for it eventually.
Yeah, not this time.
Get in.
Come on, let's go.
Hurry.
You got it?
Okay.
(CROW CALLS)
(SCREAMS)
He's got Brooke!
(CLAMORING)
Shoot him!
I can't.
I can't get a shot.
Come on, Megan!
I can't.
ANGIE: Megan, take the shot!
I can't get a shot.
(SCREAMS)
I can't.
Take the damn shot.
(GRUNTS)
Shoot him!
Kat, come here.
Get in.
Kat, get in the boat.
(SOBBING)
Come on, Kat, hurry up.
Get in the boat.
(SLOW MUSIC)
Holy shit, you guys.
Is that a house?
Look.
Oh my God, yeah.
We made it.
(UPLIFTING MUSIC)
You guys, we made it.
(PIANO FLOURISH)
We made it.
I can't believe this.
You guys, we did it.
I can't believe
we really did it.
I can believe it.
My baby girl's waiting.
Let's go.
Let's get out of here.
Look.
Oh my God, who is that?
What if it's them?
Megan?
(PIANO FLOURISH)
It's just kids.
Y'all need a ride?
Yeah.
Come on, hop in.
We'll give you a ride.
Careful, you guys.
Angie.
Hey Meg.
I almost forgot.
You know, I don't think
Paige would be very happy
if you didn't bring this home.
I told you I'd be back for it.
(LIGHT MUSIC)
Subtitles by ViSHAL
www.OpenSubtitles.org
(LIGHT MUSIC)
♪ Gave your trust
and you took my hand
♪ Followed me to a foreign land
♪ Day turned to night
♪ In the lives we left behind
♪ Sky grew dark in
the pale moonshine
♪ Wait for the light
♪ In the face of the fire
♪ Try and make it 'til dawn
♪ We had each other
♪ And we stood our ground
(HARMONICA SOLO)
♪ Side by side as
the sky went black
♪ On the run, no turning back
♪ We had a long
♪ Don't give in 'til
the fear is gone
♪ Stay in close and move it on
♪ Yeah we stood strong
♪ In the face of the fire
♪ Try and make it 'til dawn
♪ We had each other
♪ And we stood our ground
(HARMONICA SOLO)
♪ In the face of the fire
♪ And we made it 'til dawn
♪ We had each other
♪ And we stood our ground
(HARMONICA SOLO)